[Music]
w
K
KY I forgot to put the
chat into the chat
[Music]
window K
ho uh I I
I had a small
nap uh I was awake before the stream
would have started but then I needed to
make tea and all that so sorry I'm a
little bit late and now I'm a little bit
sleepy
small really
small really small like 20 minutes
normally my naps are like
hours maybe this remaining Cocola will
wake me up can't wake up wake me up
inside call my
name
ah again I have Coca-Cola and I
have uh tea green
tea which supposedly wakes you up a
little
bit
Sant well well what's this what's
this I have to get this off my chest and
ask in Hollow parade one of your voice
LS while attacking sounds like you are
in constipation I have no idea what you
talking about so I can't give a comment
on
it do you guys want me to play Hol
parade by the
way cuz at the moment I I'm like not
really like that uh like interested I
mean it looks really cute and fun fan
game really high quality fan game but
like at the moment I don't really feel
like it but I thought if I will play it
then I should probably play it while
it's the flavor of the month which it
will probably
become uh I don't know if I
should no
[Music]
maybe I'll I'll check if I need a filler
game for the upcoming
week cuz I didn't really fully plan it
out yet oh thank you Meo mow is very
lovable yeah which game just got here uh
Holo parade the new fan
game I watched some clip of P zai
playing it which was funny you know
reacting to you know M and zai walking
and the voice lines and all that that's
funny yeah but like I don't know somehow
I'm not quite feeling it right now
personally
like I feel like it's like a a mood
thing I'm not in the mood right now
starting to I have
right I knew it I knew
it the Advent game also dropped there's
a Advent
game copy link address quote retweet
starting now
finally
for real for
real I game is more
diverse
oh yeah you like the thumbnail this
thumbnail is kind of different cuz I I
ran out of apple blossom art um the one
who drew the other
ones uh and and this one was very
conveniently it in the right
theme but uh when lining it up when I'll
make the YouTube playlist it will
definitely stand out but I mean why not
make the finale stand out right yeah
yeah very eye
catching it's kind of difficult to make
a thumnail though because like I was
looking at the like this art this artre
and I thought N I don't know
I think I'll change it for the last
thumbnail because of the art the fan art
and then I I
chose let me show you can I just Flex my
editing
skills the the
peach here the peach in the thumnail
she's not supposed to be there I mean
she does you know look like she's not
really supposed to be there because of
her looking at the camera I
guess but I had to cut out melow and
Mario so that she can kind of stand in
between Bowser and
mellow Mario's mouth
is Mario's mouth is bleeding into your
hair ah [\h__\h] no wait let me fix that let
a no I didn't save it never mind ah okay
I [\h__\h] up uh I saw that when I was
editing and I was like I'm going to fix
that later
[\h__\h] no why did you make me realize
no but yeah there was like you know I
wanted to use one of the cutscene
pictures because they look really nice
but they all have like like one member
missing or so like for the attack ones
and then I don't know this one was kind
of nice for a thumbnail but Peach was
missing so so I had to edit her in there
no don't look at that don't look at that
don't look at the mistake I was so
proud I was so
proud M the cut scenes are really nice
all of the special attack cutscenes as
well let me pour some
honey maybe a bit more yeah honey into
the te
[Music]
probably already 3 minutes pass so let
me take out
the the tea bag there we
go okay they Ru no we got the important
parts
yeah oh
music
yesterday we
uh had two very big fights in Monster
town that took up quite a bit of my time
and thus we we weren't able to get that
far in terms of story I guess but now we
are so much stronger because of all the
stuff that we gained from
it so I think feel like it's going to be
a walk in the park we
also did some other smaller side stuff
like yeah the the
dream the dream thingy challenge with
the
three uh Flags scattered across the
lands
I equ the single there's only one more
oh really okay I might even sense
it uh who has it on right
now Peach so what should we give her we
have zoom I don't care about the zoom
[Music]
shoes that's that's pretty
good double defense wait wait didn't she
wear that before we can give her the
ghost medal what do you think level 20
basically for end game okay I will get
[Music]
there or I don't know what do you think
is that good was there something
better I mean the
feather M boosts a few other things
too
yeah
doesn't need
defense no her armor makes her
Invincible wait
ah doesn't need
defense safety badge the Healer doesn't
transform oh I mean yeah we can do that
currently someone else has it right Malo
has
it
Swap and then
[Music]
mellow either keeps the feather
now a lazy shell already does
that for real it doesn't say that it
does
that it doesn't say that it
resists such effects M can really have
whatever I'll give him booster's
charm it's kind of outdated at this
point in terms of power but
whatever equipment has a lot of hes
damn
but
then uh which
[Music]
one then I'm going back on
it well peach is already so powerful
like really doesn't matter she keeps
Boo's
charm I don't know why she needs Boo's
charm she's already Charming on her own
aha
[Music]
aha wait shouldn't I buy items am I like
fine on items I feel like I used up so
many in the
big what was this name cool
coolax uh pick me up
four Cox
Timaya that'll be fun all right
ah okay well H we already checked out
that part I would have been there on the
right
side
oh he's not going to wake up really
okay let's not
wake him if he's resting I wouldn't want
to be woken up
either so far I'm just ignoring the
monsters cuz they're so easy to dodge
what the
[Music]
hell until how about now let's let's
fight
him oh ant an ant again let let me share
my tangent with you guys because
everybody was so amazed by it on on
Twitter uh one one lady who went
skydiving
once her parachute
failed and she was falling and falling
and she was going to die but she landed
on an ant where thousands and thousands
of
ants stung her in the moment when she
left landed and thanks to that
adrenaline that she got out of that her
heart kept on you know
beating and does she survived only
thanks to landing on an anill but how
lucky do you have to beat them
sheesh it's a crazy story right but it's
real it's a true story oh but where are
the [\h__\h]
enemies why do you give that to
me
[\h__\h] no I barely got to make use of it
well that was like one of the most
weirdly placed and useless
Stars oh wait what what what am I going
for
uh
interestingly her physical is being
boosted still want to
skydive wait could I have destroyed this
thing with my
star if I wouldn't have like stumbled
around so much
here oh come on SO III so so so
so and that looks difficult to destroy
without a star now they're back even oh
my God change Donkey Kong is
back it I kind of want to get can I get
the star
[Music]
back oh my God they don't let me run
again nothing in this game will be
difficult
[Music]
now all right let's fight you idiots
oh wait I thought I did Ultra jump but
it's on this
bud and he yeah I mean okay yeah he's
spiky
so
yeah God damn
it let's just do the Gino
[Music]
Flash
should I
reload just because of that big enemy I
wonder I
bite oo big damage holy
macarona holy macaroni yeah go for it no
not worth it oh my
God
ouch beat him faster than R okay
okay okay I'll do it
uh but uh but what he is he sending out
all of those Earth
spikes how
annoying please please please be
[Music]
effective did I bring
my
oh
uh
[Music]
okay I have an idea let's switch to
mow they surely have a weakness to snow
or
ice right oh wait maybe not oh no it is
okay because I mean logically fire melts
ice but at the same time maybe a lot of
ice can take out a flame you know
that's you know they are each other's
enemies I would
say that was so anti-climatic for real
it was such a normal enemy how the hell
do you get that frog
coin I guess you just have to jump into
the
fire oh okay this enemy is like a pretty
common
one uh how's this one work again
[Music]
I
almost oo is's physical flame is
[Music]
Magic just need to jump in
there Ah Yeah by but okay you only get
like one chance cuz you need to jump
correctly otherwise you're like sent
back
[Music]
H
ow
attack
[Music]
up
weak oh you brought his babies they have
stone
babies feel like I've seen that before
though this enemy with its
babies lava W kill yeah but like it
brings me back to different spots I have
to run around again
lucky is it our lucky
day uh-oh ah one
damage small small T Rock smaller
smaller Stone why you
see RI I
saw your
wife yesterday
your future
wife should I introduce you to
her I know you guys say Berto is a dude
but for me Berto
is a pretty Yoshi girl
okay
I I don't even know like where you get
that info
from
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah
finally yo Yoshi is the girl nah now
you're just making [\h__\h] up
right
what it's from a Mis transation A Mis
[Music]
transation so it's a
misunderstanding
I my honestly I think I need a new
controller cuz my jump button really
doesn't seem to work a lot of the
time I don't know if it's the lag like
the input
delay
but a Miss translation that they made
somewhat
[Music]
Canon oh my
God what you can update your controller
what what
[Music]
what oh that looks
like HP
buff you can do it in the settings
[Music]
H maybe I have done that before oh oh do
you get there later up
there the froin how do
you how do you get the
froin
[Music]
wait sorry sorry that was by
accident
okay oh I thought optical illusion I
thought it was uh on actually on the
stone platform uh like like where I'm
walking on right
now I was wrong and I am too stupid for
this kind of
stuff
I
can't this kind of
angle a wait let's look at the
shadow ah it's more over
here the
perception oh my god oh it's
rumbling
I should charge my
FP
320 how are you not dead I mean I guess
you kind of
are oh my God it doesn't even say it's
a
seven it doesn't even say only magic
kills them cuz I was going to say it
doesn't even say that it's a uh super
strong Enemy
No oh okay what the
hell I didn't know that you guys tell me
when when you know there like there's a
the my last treasure box treasure chest
right you'll tell me
right
because I have the thing
off uh wait
what oh I don't have uh
[Music]
any besides the maple
syrup
oh
fren ah the water would work too true
true true
true almost level 20 our
party oh my God what the [\h__\h] is that
it's a stone tree let's
fight wait oh I fought his babies I
think
[Music]
h
oh I will meet Cinder toad soon okay
okay no yeah okay that's what I want
thank
[Music]
you probably this one is also less
strong than it looks
like
[Music]
no oh almost down
all right
bye-bye time to go to
bed wherever trees sleep I guess your
bed is just the
Earth
sheesh that is a very cozy sounding
bed I want to sleep in Earth it's like
sleeping in the sand on the
beach warm and you feel so tucked
[Music]
in am Mia some I don't know why but I I
really love
that am
Mia it's such a Charming
phrase
[Music]
uh
well m
I don't know I mean this isn't even that
much buffed so I feel like I don't have
to go for
HP yeah there's no
boost I feel like no
boost what does he need right now do I
feel like he's lacking
something can't remember maybe maybe
some magic yeah
[Applause]
why are
there no more Treasure Chest there's
like so many rooms here I feel like you
could
easily um Implement a couple more are
you sure I'm only missing
one cuz like last time we talked to
that uh that NPC that tells
you uh they said I had like
left you're
positive did I get 10 of them already
last time since I talked to the
NPC e I'm not a completionist but the
thing is with the treasure chest like a
lot of them give you like the flowers
and all that and the flowers are pretty
PR important like I do need FP as much
as I can get cuz these attacks are very
[Music]
costy only one more hidden chest I'll
encounter okay I mean I know that I
probably missed one in the early
area but I don't think I'm going to go
back
there
oh
[Music]
for real for
real
okay flowers from booster
Hill
uh I'm
good I'm good I I only want to get stuff
now that comes naturally to me I'm not
going to go any side paths now no side
tracking no
backtracking only go
for what is here and what is
[Music]
now
oh
[Music]
n cuz I want to I want to I want to I
want to finish early today if possible I
need to cook yesterday I just BR
together some mid pasta with a finished
pre-finished sauce cuz it was so late
and I have a feeling that the sauce
maybe wasn't I mean it wasn't off yet
but it also wasn't that fresh so it may
have created a little tummy hord I'm not
sure it tasted fine though but I had it
standing outside of the fridge cuz I
forgot uh like like 2 days before for
for a few hours like half a
day well but it tasted good tasted good
yeah pretty good
yeah it was a pesto sauce
so I don't know I think it was probably
fine who
knows who knows who
knows open that's the thing it was even
opened I didn't even close
it but it smelled and tasted fine and it
looked fish so yeah I I I ate it because
I had nothing else to quickly whip up
without much
effort now I don't know if that may have
created a tummy hord oh my God is
that what you meant with cinder
[Music]
Todd I expected something completely
different
H will show those footsteps were you for
a minute I thought I was hearing things
I'm send to to this place is a regular
Inferno come on step
inside why does he move like that
oh he serves me at every table welcome
to the Inn 30 coins will get you a room
expensive what room like that's probably
going to be me sleeping on some boxes
no welcome to the armor
[Music]
shop should I even
replace my armor anymore cuz don't I
somebody's wearing armor that I don't
want to replace
right fzero oh my
God Peach okay only Peach okay
[Music]
okay I have so much money
actually party is refresh during battle
does that mean everybody gets healed and
uh debuffs
get cancelled what about
deaths cuz it's relatively
expensive H only only the debuffs
okay yeah maybe
one do do do
do
he hey
hey hey
he
it's it doesn't flow as well as I would
hope lose attack speed and Magic attack
for more defense maybe
no this is this is going to be the bed
isn't
it you know what let's do
it who can sleep on that Mario are you
okay especially like on your
tummy like with your face does does his
nose go in between the gaps of the
boxes morning now wasn't d a cushy bed I
can't believe you're charging that much
for
this and then I don't even get a special
cut scene
what
what he follows
me thanks for stopping by you can always
come back you
know
I follow him in I I wasn't going
[Music]
to in a volcano woodn't I don't know I
feel
like especially in a volcano you
shouldn't want to use wood because it
could
burn uh maybe a steel bed would make
more sense or iron or stone honestly a
nice Stone bed could warm up so
comfortably ah no way come back it's
going to come back
right
yeah there surely were times where a
stone bed was a thing I hate this I hate
this I hate this I hate this I hate this
I hate this I hate I I hate
[Music]
this I have to uh keep an eye out for my
DMs cuz today's tonight's Advent V
Advent calendar video I haven't um
received yet
have to keep an eye out because they
would send it to me on on at DM and I
should send it over to the
team
so I shall keep no you
[\h__\h] don't fall don't fall don't fall
don't fall yes ah never again
again never
again oh we're at the
boss already look
ha
H or is it a mid boss kind of mid not
going to
lie what is
that wait that's your drag that's your
dragon okay I
[Music]
I
expected a way more powerful
intimidating looking Dragon than that
also bigger in size what are
[Music]
you that is indeed a mid boss
because
[Music]
what a dorky Derpy goofy Dragon it's not
even a real
dragon like is is is that even like like
the the
body at the
head is is that not just all being
carried and Made Alive by the flames and
like the actual thing you're fighting is
the Flames because the rest is just like
decoration is it an actual dragon that
has its own life
or you know what I mean or is it being
puppeteered by the flames you know what
I
mean I think it's a
puppet a
[Music]
[\h__\h] I mean the eyes they have a little
bit of life in them cuz the eyelid is
moving a little bit but besides that
he's not blinking do characters in this
game blink let me look at Mario do you
blink Mario
ever
no Mario you should blink your eyes is
going to dry
out no I just noticed they do not
blink or he's having a stare off with
me
qu
I will lose this staring contest okay
um how about
special star Riders let's go wow let's
look at it cuz it's so nice haven't seen
it in a while wow
rainbow wow yeah this one looks so nice
oh oh flame wall again
blinking blinking has not been invented
yet at the time
perhaps H let's go for snowy because
my previously my logic worked out I
don't know if it's going to work here
cuz the Snowman is sitting on the lava
it is his weakness though
okay you
geta it was pretty low on damage though
surprisingly oh well I guess he just has
high
[Music]
defense not
nice you got some more where that came
from right bigger dragon
no ah there we go they were like posing
nice I like that fake out oh that looks
better kind of ghost dragon probably has
different
weaknesses but
um
M I'll go and try
to actually would the water work on this
one no way right cuz it's a
boss no way
right it would be funny if it works on
him put Sky it at
all just as a joke let's try
it no
way it does do damage but it doesn't
kill okay I mean 130 wasn't too
bad not
[Music]
bad yeah
no
oh Gino did almost as much damage as the
water
um let do a little
jump oh my God this one's
[Music]
difficult he's not in frame for a long
time so oh that is his weakness
oh you guys said to peek into him let's
see
oh sorry I I I wasn't able to get what
he thinks I'm not really good at that
cuz I I don't do it much so I don't know
the timing very
[Music]
well but lightning and jumping nice Wawa
nice
[Music]
oh then let's jump again he's still
bouncy oh my
[Music]
god oh yeah
Bo Ah that's where it ends it also said
thunder so let's shock him just as the
boat lands and
go
unsatisfying
Peach Peach taking one
damage how is it
even how is how
[Music]
how I can't get further than that for
some reason
[Music]
Peach The
Immortal yes
[Music]
yes
meanwhile Mario keeps on jumping just
for fun he's not even doing it because
he wants to fight or anything he's just
doing this for fun it just has some
positive side
[Music]
effects
ah that one you would think you have to
block when like in the beginning but no
you block it at the
[Music]
end I wonder if G would do more damage
than mow but his weakness is
[Music]
funer hey I got
double yeah
[Music]
bye already out of FP
again
546 I know I know sometimes Noble
attacks are stronger probably cuz his
magic uh stats are so bad for Mario but
like I would I wouldn't expect it if it
says oh it's his weakness so let's do
that and
what I have been using normal attacks a
lot though in the past couple of
yesterday as well no no for Mario it's
always strong
ah true cuz he has the lazy
shell yeah holy
[\h__\h] wait why is there
special okay that confused me now there
is a
path I wasn't sure looking at it cuz we
only saw like part of it wasn't sure if
the there was like a third eye on the
left side of the big eye was the the
middle eye but no it is kind of Droopy
it looks so funny wait
no it looks so
[Music]
funny why is there no secret
here
nah that
easy what
was I mean yeah fights are easier
now but I thought the dungeon was pretty
short the music just cut
off I love that I [\h__\h] Lov that cuz I
was thinking nah can't be that easy
you're not just letting me have it so
easily
[Music]
right I want to I want to watch that
again that
moment that was maybe the most
entertaining funny thing I witnessed in
this
game oh that was my favorite thing that
was my favorite
thing we got to
[Music]
start we're
amazing we're unbeatable and there's so
many holy [\h__\h] oh it's like the Power
Rangers ah we got
this you better leave now
chimps you little
shits that is not
acceptable
oh they're still
here hey red look down there that's got
to be the ugliest mustache I've ever
seen ew gross
disgusting that gu is worst looking than
CL
Mario uh that is that that is Mario you
idiot listen everyone we got to we got
to get the start to the blade
immediately we'll deal with Mario later
ah the
blade
oh oh the
music
[Music]
oh holy
[\h__\h] he's like to M you're not getting
that he careful with this your
[Music]
FS oh my
God look at my jumping skills
[Music]
sh
oh please keep the music please don't
stop the
music where's that
BL help be
here are you
sure relax
people Mario's here
it's too
late where where's the blade shut up
already
holy
macaroni
finally
jeez
oh what we're fighting the ship and them
let's go we fight for evil I fight for
um dreams and Friendship and
Magic like what we
do we struggle for
chaos we
are the aom Rangers the aom
Rangers wish I could do more than one
voice at once we fight for burgers and
pizza it needs to be
destroyed
oh okay fine yeah yeah I keep on
attacking Peach she's my
[Music]
tank
Peach he I wonder in this game if
someone's like
full health and they get healed like on
the enemy side do they gain extra HP or
had a tiet to meet you let's go and
front
here make sure to think of some
questions you wanted me to uh you want
to ask
[Music]
me burgers and
pizza
um fired everyone oh let's do that I
wonder if I can melt them you know maybe
maybe the logic is fire is strong
against them cuz I can melt them or have
they I want to do they have
different weaknesses ah it's only the
weakness of the pink one and one
resisted it even okay so they all have
very different
weaknesses I I don't know if it's even
something I could guess on their because
of their colors that's too
[Music]
snowy m
yeah pretty good two weaknesses and only
one
resistance thank you for continuously
attacking
Peach make me mad and boom wait I didn't
notice she had a new attack like this is
it
[Music]
good oh
let go P oh that didn't even do that
much damage oh well at least it's uh
[Music]
AOE yeah it's fine please keep on
attacking
Peach melow I thought you were going to
die good for you for not not dying I'm
sure jump should work on some of
[Music]
them nice yeah good damage good damage
yo red what what look my
shades okay they they seem fine sa they
right y R
what I'm
hungry Sho on your
tongue does he have a
tongue okay we did snowy snowy was
decent
[Music]
right well let's do one good old
Thunderbolt wait
oh it shows that it's only on free but I
mean it should hit everybody cuz it says
shock all your enemies that's kind of
misleading oh it's because he's down oh
that's why they were saying that ah wait
that was really little damage never
again never again oh when they talk they
died
ah oh h
M how about normal attack
then
yeah let's just do normal
[Music]
attack oh he died too my head is
spinning so you out yeah he's out h
H
[Music]
nice
nice ah he's out
too I've got headache you're totally out
of shape but you you shouldn't be saying
anything you're dead too the only ones
left is your your lady in
pink she should be your
boss
change of hierarchy after this oh oh she
died okay T finish this oh oh oh
formation here we
go oh what are you going to do for beam
energized maximum charge no fire the
breaker can't block
uh-oh um
oh that looks like it would kill me but
Peach takes no
[Music]
damage they have nothing on peachy
Wei wait so are we fighting ah only the
blade
I'm just going to go physical I
[Music]
guess pretty
reliable at this point especially cuz
the Koopa is so easy
to uh guess the
timing thank
God was that a gust of
wind
400 damage
yo this isn't impossible we are
invincible I doubt it friend I doubt it
can this be happening to the exxel range
[Music]
ass ship down ship
down holy [\h__\h] how easy was this whole
volcano Arc
is that it is that am I done with this
dungeon you get so overpowered if you do
those secret
bosses holy
[\h__\h] but they should know that a lot of
people going to do that
damn lazy shell
insane I mean I guess if you don't want
to be so overpowered just don't use
those items is a good
[Music]
argument I beat the super boss yeah I
stalled the super boss one more star to
go six star pieces have finally been
collected where could the last star
piece
be maybe the real star pieces are the
friends we made along the
way yeah I
mean that's literally that feels like
something the game would
say
oh
oh are we going to ask for advice or do
we think it's
[Music]
here Nimbus Land where should I go
inside perhaps talk to the king let him
know that I got the
[Music]
star let's update
the
king GE I wonder where the last one
could
[Music]
be I genuinely don't
know I really don't know oh the birds oh
my wait before those were empty so I
wouldn't really say that the rain is
better now with the King because now
they're keeping Birds prisoners what the
[\h__\h] what did the birds ever do to you
bir are
dangerous no we are birds guys we are
look at all these imprisoned Birds
they're so cute and yet they are forever
imprison who's this town no I didn't
check it out I I I don't
really
nah we are dangerous are we are we
though mom
D are you able to find the star dear
yeah the a just took it away from us but
we got it back
again that's wonderful now the star
starway can be repaired
right why did he stumble I guess not you
still ah because he wasn't sure what it
was called I guess you're still missing
a piece I take it the last
star wait the only place left to look is
in Bowser
oh right that was still a thing
like Bowser's
Castle like in the beginning I thought
it would matter a lot but then
immediately it was just kind of pushed
away and Bowser even became a
friend so it seemed very
[Music]
unimportant yeah we know but there's
there's no way to get in believe me
we've tried
but yes yes even Mario can't jump that
far all right I'll let you use that
that's it dear you should use the Royal
bus yes melow the time has come for you
to take the
bus the Royal bus can we at least call
it a Royal
Limousine why when I was your
age really are you sure it's all
white of course dear I'll order the
repairment to have it fixed by the time
you leave but the time is
now you simply have to help Mario and
the others to get that last
star I love how he plops out of his
pants do they also if they jump do they
also plop out of their clothes like
that I
wonder
where would
they where would the point be that they
plop cuz for the king I would think it's
where the collar is but his arms are
underneath there I am thinking too much
about
it you bet mom come on Mario let's
go let's go it's me Mario let's go let's
go what's in
here have I been here
before
his Club is what prevents him from
popping his arms pop out of his sleeves
with his
head oh I yeah
right ah yeah this is where I was
wondering can I jump this way for
example no ah you can only jump from
this
[Music]
way how do I land there okay you guys
have to tell me how to land
there and
here that's one thing I I just cannot
let go please tell me please share your
wisdom with
[Music]
me why is my tea already so cold what
the
[\h__\h] oh I guess it's been an hour since
I made it holy [\h__\h] it's been an hour
already huh
[Music]
it feels like it's been 20
minutes uh you climb up from a different
Vine did you ever take a sip no I didn't
just
[Music]
now okay climb up from a different Vine
wait where where where are the vines
here Bean talk bean bean stalk Bean talk
like Like Girls
Talk which Vine is this already the
wrong
Vine
[Music]
ow the
yellow the yellow one okay if I ever get
there CH the
[Music]
I perceive this
angle hallelu FR
coin
[Music]
platform what about
the okay okay
okay
oh what see I okay it's I'm going to buy
a new controller I think there's really
something wrong with my B button
I'm not even like trying to cope or
[Music]
so you think an update will fix it I
think it's like just a button has has
become
old cat
hairs how do
you just jump here what do you mean just
jump here Oh you mean on top of the ve
Vine
ah so I probably go there from the red
[Music]
one sorry
guys okay and and H from here onto the
green one
a oh thank
God so
musuki
okay okay the defense scarf is that good
better than what I have
now I guess down from
here
okay
flower
[Music]
nice now I'm
satisfied that was pretty worth it
yeah uh going to oh oh I yeah right okay
we'll see if my bus is
[Music]
ready
ah do I have to run for the whole castle
[Music]
again my
nimus Nim you know that's funny because
in German take is Nim so you could say
take the
bus n bu uh
so just get rid of the D and it's
nimus yeah the bus is outside what is it
really is it really a name it's with n i
m m double M
actually the nightmare dream of toad I
didn't get it but I know it exists and
oh oh wait I've never been here I
personally don't
care cuz I already started oh that's
where the bus takes off okay we can
start operating again let's go I'm going
to take the bus Prince
mow we want to go to boun keep could you
give us a lift please no I I will give
you a bus not a lift by the way we say
we say elevator
[Music]
[Laughter]
here
a double joke double
[Music]
pun I've heard a story from kingy but
she'll be there in no
[Music]
time here it comes here it
comes
oh is that cute
why is he so huge the
dude so how's the engine
running oh it's paring like a
kitton could you take Prince m to the
entrance of bower ke oh of course can't
wait to get this thing running again
come Prince come on
board it looks so soft that's the
softest car
ever perfect for a road trip let's
go
alard we're all
[Music]
yeah they're stupid Expressions
man uh cute oh oh interesting
view ah I love how they just kept
shitty this and the the the paper the
seed falling down
straight As
[\h__\h] Kos is yeah it's like sliding it in
like it like like like
wait wait a
second Super Mario
RPG uh
bus
[Laughter]
I [\h__\h] saved it as a [\h__\h] web PE I
hate this world
PNG
[Music]
yes so much
effort same same thing same
quality that's probably how they did it
they just recorded it in OBS like
[Laughter]
this top Notch
animation oh it's so funny a the scent
of boiling lava it's so nice to be home
Smith is going to pay for stealing my
Splendid Castle from
me oh revenge is
sweet sweet uh as as honey
mhm the last Treasure Chest must be
somewhere in this dungeon right why was
there no secret treasure chest in the in
the lava dungeon what the hell there
were like so many in other dungeons or
areas but nothing in the the I don't
understand why were there no none in the
volcano they're so
green you guys feeling
sick
M Pro
Goomba
Pro let's terrorize them because they're
betraying Bowser you little
shits
boo yeah I know it doesn't do much
damage but that's
okay what did that say bows is scaring
what what what what did his scare t t t
tactic uh get rid of
[Music]
them you scared them off for
real oh what are they doing that's so
cute they're chasing me cute wait since
when does that fat Koopa have such a
cute
smile I don't think he was smiling this
much last time right let let's stomp him
with a meta Koopa
stomp right that one looks very
different from
him
aw wases he always like
this no problem
[Music]
hi K's Mom
hi who are you kobo's
friend I I I do not approve of
you why are they so
scared serves you right you should have
been serving
me AKA
Bowser
[Music]
it is different right his smile is
different I thought
[Music]
so kind of
dark these fights are so short
[Music]
now h
what is he
doing every everyone thought they were
Bowser
what that sounds like a big ass excuse
to
[Music]
me
oh not dead yet
really
time for a psych bomb
[Applause]
psych
ah Peach finally gets an actual attack
at the end I appreciate that cuz like
when when there's no one to heal it's
like what do I
do let's do our B one yeah Mario's
Family let's go let's
go where do I go where do I go oh
oh I guess we'll never
[Music]
know oh oh well they are alive look at
them what what the [\h__\h] was that did I
get poisoned what oh it was probably a
flower tab you fought I didn't see you
so cute how they jump out a so cute it's
like surprise they're just playing games
they're happy that I'm back that
Bowser's back they're just
[Music]
happy God damn it the forky what en
raptured what does that mean why does it
look so funky why is this forky so
great
nice oh it's it has come to its senses
it's so
cute he and ENT trur with you left he's
he was in
love
what why did I kill
him doesn't attack on to E that's so
cute oh that's a
room that's a
[Music]
room I found that by accident I wouldn't
have thought that that was a room holy
[\h__\h] it's kind of a secret room
right cuz it it cuts off the same way
like this wall so it doesn't look like a
[Music]
room oh is that a heal and regenerates
endlessly M
Mia oh ah that's why that room is there
a free
[Music]
heal endless mushrooms just so you guys
know can we sneak by
kocu should
I I can just sneak by talk to him
okay Mario did you remember to use the
safe oh there's plenty of danger up
ahead so it's best to save now you need
anything are you're a shop
now but everything is stolen I don't
want your stolen
goods
no I'll sell you something though maybe
how
about this old [\h__\h] and this one this
one this
one bye ah he wouldn't have attacked me
huh there are six doors need an
explanation
yeah is this a game
show of the six doors only one is the
red path or
what two open on two action courses you
can handle a lot of action right no no
no no please no two Hors will lead you
to a battle course you can fight right
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I last to open onto puzzle course
no sweat for a great puzzle solver like
you my favorite would be the fighting
one once you choose a course there's no
turning back the only way to know what's
behind the door is to walk through it
m you must pass through a four of the
six courses to move
ahead
[Music]
okay you know you still have what
that one Toad's
wallet oh Toad's
wallet
[Music]
what wait this this way okay show
more okay wait show
again
show
me ah
wait I don't like this is this an action
course could I jump from here I feel
like maybe I could but maybe not
[Music]
try does it only show up when I jump I
think it does
okay
oh what 10 tries wait wait wait what
what oh it starts me on a platform how
nice of them but I want to go to the
treasure chest
okay uh switch ah no no my button
doesn't work I swear
ah that is such a nice safe Point holy
[\h__\h] there it is oh that was easy though
oh wait there's one more I missed there
was one more
chest oh well it's
okay the donkey are you up
[Music]
there wait wait wait wait wait wa wait
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait no no I'm jumping
no
no no no no no no no
no I can hide okay okay how oh okay it's
not really underneath but
okay can I do that here too
okay okay let's play it
[Laughter]
safe
am I am I am I only have three tries
left oh God
[Music]
okay well I'm just trying to you
know look good to Donkey Kong with my
screams there he
is it's literally
[Music]
him okay and
now
fight no oh thank God God are we done
[Music]
please got the super slab what is that
for
peach that's like a peach no item her
final
[Music]
weapon it is so we're not using the fan
anymore okay
okay new door
M po please please don't be the puzzle
ah it's the puzzle why why do I not want
the puzzle
guys how is this a
puzzle hey hey hey it's me quiz master
and it's quiz time need an
explanation I'll give you 12 call them
12 questions if you're right the block
you're standing on we'll move up one but
if you blow it you go down too you have
5 seconds if you
[Music]
can't quiz on the game
[\h__\h] are the questions like always the
same do you guys know if you look up a a
a game
FAQ frying pan in Moville frying P okay
fine thank you for telling me Oh no oh I
thought you're telling me a quiz
question that I need to know they rotate
them oh God oh
God reach the eth step within 12
questions and you one oh
red
scarecrows when she was kidnapped by
Bowsers she was maybe looking at flowers
maybe they live in Monster yes okay
what's the chef's name at
marmore to it to it to it to it German f
f i don't know uh uh guessing no [\h__\h]
Jagger Sensi what's the name jinx
PO is what generate uh eight what might
is
dinos oh [\h__\h] how many under links does
kroo have who's kroo
again oh the first one Mar pad maybe
no a boss [\h__\h]
there did I save before that I don't
mind doing it again is it the same
door I didn't do so bad
yeah but damn that's tough cuz the time
pressure and
sheesh trying to remember in such a
short time oh my God same door
okay same questions but different order
well well okay the the first star is not
Mar's P was the other one the not not
the Bowser keep either though the third
one what where's the third star from
again some quests can be the same a few
new ones maybe
okay
Miss mole hill okay
mville oopsie sorry I already
know let's go
Smithy uh
red T loves which
beverage maybe a movie no I don't know
that sounded
interesting that was the third star
piece found the Third
mvo how long have the couple
inside an hour what what the [\h__\h] I
don't what toad of toad of
Sky
sculpter uh
healing rainbow what was Peach doing
when she was looking at
flowers what is the full name of the
boss at the sun can shame Johnny
Jonathan Jones oh [\h__\h] yeah H A
Boss it I still missed didn't I only
mistake two
questions did I mistake free questions
but I knew was surprising good amount so
let's
go uh gives you strength I suppose send
the to in charge of at the middle count
of the in what's the full name of the
boss in the sunker ship Jonathan Jones
what did carot bus what the [\h__\h] is that
a carrot okay how many legs does wigler
have eight [\h__\h] that's were like uh
scarecrows what's the password in
this pearls what technique does Bowser
learn at level 15 met what a wait
15 Exel R his husband name gas [\h__\h]
hell I already lost
whatever no let me go I don't
know
oh my
God gas
[Music]
gas I want to win this
now tot of
Sky gives you
strength
[Music]
free maybe grape [\h__\h]
now now we know it's which one it is now
uh
eight
[\h__\h] I had that wrong before 30
minutes
[Music]
Crusher healing
rainbow uh 10 [\h__\h] it's
six
Dar I don't know man
there's still new
questions there's still new
[Music]
ones okay no I want
this G oh R
[\h__\h] cricket
by helpy rainbow oh [\h__\h] getting
confused I'm getting really
confused
soil can't wait till which season skiing
skiing oh
Jonathan
pressure
red
smiffy oh a you know the the NPC one
who's waiting for skiing season you only
know that if you talk to him and that's
optional I actually did it I thought I
would lose this round again because I
failed so much in right like the first
round
already W let's go and then and then I
made a mistake for something I actually
got right before
so
Kaa wait that we get getting more
quizzes or is that the only one ah we're
just getting more puzzle things let's
see how well you can
count what what I can start counting now
no or are you going to change the
lineup cuz now it's like 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11
12 oh
okay [\h__\h] I'm not good at this kind of
stuff
that's probably two uh uh wait I can't
count my brain is not activated uh I
literally maybe it's 13 cuz it looks
like it was one
more
okay oh God okay please count please
count this time Wawa like I was
literally not
thinking my brain shut off this time we
have 20 seconds we really really have to
count
okay
guys please please I'm I'm not my brain
literally shuts off I know you could do
it by like you know knowing you know
like the back row is so and so many and
46 thank you I love you like I literally
cannot handle this under pressure it's
like I'm taking a test at
school thank
God I'm getting transported let's
go Now for Something Completely
Different okay boo goo bones and Kip
competed in the triathlon okay the
triathlon includes swimming cycling and
a
marathon okay it's up to you to guess
which place each person came in so
listen well to what they have to say
oh oh I didn't have to listen I came in
F for swimming and never did better in
the events after
that uh I plac the same in the swimming
and cycling events but two others beat
me in the
marathon same in the two others beat you
in the marathon same for swimming and
cycling but two other speed you in the M
Maron I outd Kip both on my bike and in
the final rankings wait who's Kip are
you Kip
no are you Kip no okay so the the you
are Kip wait so what you out did I out
did keep both on my bike and in the
final rankings wait [\h__\h] I lost like all
my information
already came in F for swimming so you're
probably the worst
and yeah cuz you could have done you
said you never did better that also
means you could have done worse for the
others so maybe you were fourth and the
others uh place the same in sing and
cycling but two others beat me in the
marathon that was uh goo right goo okay
swimming cycling I to keep both of my
bike and in the final rankings final
rankings so you
first sounds like he's first I fell into
fourth place during the bike race but
finally ended up in the same place as I
did in the swimming
event fourth place during the bike race
but finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event and you
said you out did Kip on your bike and in
the well I don't know you probably first
you probably
last M two others beat you and the
marathon you're probably fourth h no
you're probably fourth
third second first how about
that what
that yeah did I get it
right someone in the chat says it too
oh
yo okay okay
fourth ah that order okay okay oopsie uh
first yes yes yes yes
second yes yes yes and I said third to
the Goomba and last for the ghost
sadly yay I actually got it I
think on my own on my
own and yeah probably that's probably it
yeah
y that makes up for me not doing the the
barrel counting
right
yay I'm quite proud of
that I like that kind of riddle it's
like the one where uh you say oh so and
so many people entered the bus so and so
many people left the bus m you're
impressed thank you
wow I got the rock candy oh wasn't that
the FP thingy was
it wait no what's rock candy again the
[\h__\h] is rock
candy let's
go
okay there's Apparently one more puzzle
course which would be funny if I get one
more puzzle course but I don't care
whatever it's fine let's go
six another a puzzle course
all right do we get like the same kind
of quizzes
again uh yeah are you doing questions
again oh 21 coins in this box will take
turns removing them the one who takes
the last coin is the
[Music]
loser
so
so so I should start I should
start oh but I can grab four at once he
M A this is like a wasn't there yeah
like wasn't there a game like this in
Super Mario in Mario Party
[\h__\h] but like there's probably not much
time for me to think either is there you
can grab forward once if you want to
grab only one or two press a where you
want to
stop
ah
uh can I do more ah okay how about we
start
with
4 One
5 6 let's just go like this now actually
oh wait a
second uh wait where is seven are we at
seven
now I forgot 1 3 four 5 six we're at six
now 7 8 9 10 but he might take more than
one too
right can
he I
wonder
eight four five 6 7
9 10
11 12 13
15 16 17
19 oh now I take
two 1920 yeah one two
done
y this music is so good like I feel
really accomplished in this
situation the topic you ask Magic
Buttons want
instructions step on one button and
you'll re the surrounding buttons so on
becomes off oh
no I hate
[Music]
these all and
on well they're all on
now what do you mean ah okay I guess on
is when they're all
down I hate this wait
[Music]
okay
I hate this how much time do I have
forever
say he didn't say anything about a time
limit
right oh okay well then we're fine
[Music]
probably does it always do it in a cross
like yeah okay ah it's a cross okay h
[Music]
I should have like known that from the
beginning
then can I reset
[Music]
please
yeah I realized that from the
[Music]
beginning now I have to BR force it
man I I feel like if I press give up
it's going to just let me win
[Music]
no
man oh
[Music]
interesting m
I am such a genius I am smarter than
everybody I am such a genius let's go
genius oh my
God oh my God I I actually like the
puzzles because they're they're fun
they're more interesting than the other
other things now the topic is ball solit
soliter one instructions I guess when
you kick a ball it's a Leap Frog it it
will Le frog an adjacent ball which will
then
disappear so it's like the the the
Windows
PC solitary right keep making balls
disappear until one remains you can't
kick a ball into a space occupied by the
another
ball the bodyall you kick must always
Lea Rock a another ball
uh okay I don't know if I understood
that uh I think I did so
like wait how do I kick it I jump on it
what
huh wait what
how oh do I push it
what
ah
button what I'm press pressing
a do I have to do it in a specific
[Music]
Direction that's go over one
ball ah so this one would be
ah ah it even shows me that I can do it
okay all
right now that I
understand we can do
[Music]
this oh this one again
that's not really what I wanted to
do did I mess it
up can
I lock myself
into cuz I can't kick diagonally I think
no can I read them wait if I leave the
room
[Music]
no can't go that
way what about this one I wanted to kick
it over that one I guess that's where
the field
ends keep going till you win or lose
okay well maybe it's not over over yet I
mean I can reach this one
now but these
ones how
about there we go but then this one's
kind of May maybe
maybe if I kick that one it will it will
end up here could get that one but then
this one's lost if I kick this one it
will end up here that can get this one
but then that one's
lost
so yeah I got it it's doable M
there let me
think if I kick this one it will take
this I have to clean up everything right
oh oh having one left is
fine I I thought I have to clean the
whole field having one left is okay
only oh
[Music]
okay oh wait that does
work oh well that would be the last one
okay okay okay oh that's
[Music]
fun that's
fun oh my God
uh winner winner Puzzle dinner so what
is rock candy is it ah is that the one
that
automatically increases my FP
H H one more M can we get another puzzle
room how about
two ah too bad it's a fighting room
please don't say it's obstacle
I think it's fighting room
e ah too
bad too
bad I would have really liked another
puzzle
[Music]
room oh he scares them off you should
stay this is literally like a challenge
fight
I
can't stay how lame is that you should
play late in games
nah
ooh
wellow cowards for real for real fight
me fight
me
K you don't have to do that each time
also why does he teleport with like
PlayStation controller
marks and another one
leaves the best way to win this one is
just have Bowser in your
team the fact was before PlayStation I
guess
so Bowser is a cheat for
real big guys is ready to
launch oh no big
slap
Peach oh can't believe it her attack is
a
slap mow maxed
out Max
low oh two
three HP seems to be the most buffed but
I could go for magic so let's go for
magic oh wait fruity is max level oh
oopsy I thought 20 was
[Music]
Max what's that
face ab ab ab Abu AB how about we use
the pure
water stay hydrated
boo you want to stay hydrated trust
me
nice oh
shees I've got too much
[Music]
power my fees are so cold cuz I'm not
wearing socks I might have to go get
some socks after this they're
[Music]
freezing
it was it was uh
um what's the
word what do they always say in Elden
ring
when with the
[Music]
bosses not
so not that no no no uh your your do
something with your hopes and dreams or
so a foolish yeah it was foolish of me
to not wear socks you know that's what
I'm trying to say where is
Yosi in my heart which is here
Yi
is that more of course there's
more that's very
sockless I know I'm
ashamed I'm showing everybody in the
world my
fies exposing my my toesy
[Music]
boies I love that
Melody
that's one of my favorite enemies I
think cuz they're so cute with their
their
shitty
[Music]
Wings again oh we're lucky
today
see oh [\h__\h] I'm not sure right or middle
that's the first time I'm kind of
unsure it switched weirdly at the end
mid right most say right ah wait ah it's
kind of
split oh right gang let's
go let me go get the stop
case I I got some cozy socks that have
uh that that that make my feet look like
cat paws
[Music]
okay
did you
hear chky wonky I'm holding her right
now she the moment she like heard or saw
me she jumped out of the closet and
immediately like flopped so that she was
like showing me her
belly she's so
cute she's so cute
[Music]
a she threw up so much like
in yesterday and the day before it made
me worried
again but last time before my Japan trip
when I brought her to the vet to talk
about the throwing
up like it turned out that nothing was
wrong with
her it's just like some because of
digesting hair I
guess she's okay yeah I don't know I
thought it was weird because what she
throws up doesn't look like hair balls
but the vet said yeah but
still she's okay she's okay my mom said
when I was gone she didn't throw up
surprisingly so it's just like phases
where she froze up a bit
[Music]
more cat grass I'm not sure if she would
eat it but I should try it out yeah cuz
the vet also said try try cat
grass I I feel it CU she's such a picky
eater okay byebye chy won she's such a
picky eater I don't think she would like
it but I I wouldn't mind having more
greens in
my in my
place on a cat
note you know I told you yesterday right
that that
movie has become fond
suddenly surprisingly of being under my
blanket and I was like shocked by that
but very pleasantly
surprised she did
it several times today like she never
stayed in much like she would go she
would like sit next to me curiously and
I would all open my blanket and she goes
in Happily then she stays for maybe one
or two minutes and and lies down happily
in there but then she leaves and then
she comes back in 1 minute and then she
kind of goes into the blanket again and
she repeated that like five times
today so she does like it so I'm I'm I'm
kind of excited that she might be
becoming a blanket
cat suddenly now she's
like 5 years old and now she decides she
wants to become become a blanket cat I
am excited she may not be a lap cat but
she has potential to become a blanket
cat a blank cat
[Music]
yeah so
excited a
blanket as I get older blankets are the
best why are you saying this as if you a
cat just like oh yeah I I I I can
totally you
know approve of that yeah I can confirm
yeah that's that's how it is yeah just
like me for real for
[Music]
real your cat became a shoulder cat oh
my God shoulder cats are quite the
interesting kind of cats
[Music]
I keep on
missing my cat wants to my cat wants to
lay on me any chance she gets ah my cats
used to do that when they were kittens
but they stopped doing it when they grew
up oh my God God again what's going
on they stopped doing it and that made
me really
sad cuz I'm like they love being right
next to me and they're they're they
always follow me they're super clingy
but they're they didn't want to be lab
cats which
just it would fit their behavior so much
but
honestly H with me being like you know
kind of of
like what's the
word you know how I told you like when
I'm when I'm supposed to stay still when
I'm like trying to sleep or when I'm
sitting in a bus or in a train cuz of
the weird pain that I have in my
body I like slightly adjust my body here
and there all the
time and if my cat would were to sit on
me she would probably be annoyed by that
yeah kind of restless fidgety
[Music]
yeah yeah and actually now that I fall
asleep so fast it's not even an issue
anymore in bed but but still very much
an issue on the airplane and like any
any kind of
Transportation I keep on adjusting my
shoulder cuz it hurts so much and my
neck and all
[Music]
that m
yeah like
constantly legit constantly makes me
wonder like oh is the person next to me
like thinking why is this lady not just
sitting still and I I tried to do these
like move ments really really slightly
like only tiny small small movements but
you
know when it gets really bad I I try to
massage my shoulder and all that
but I have to do that all the time on
flights it feels like it's the worst on
flights for real for
[Music]
real which made economy recently flying
economy really really
bad but at the same time I want to save
money
so I take it cuz like I I rationalize it
like saying I'd rather spend money on
the hotel you
know I I like keeping my flights cheap
if I especially you know during the
current issues that I
had yeah but okay
[Music]
yeah but just generally yeah I think
it's more worth it to spend more money
on your your hands hand gets bigger uh
more worth it if you spend more money on
the hotel rather than the flight don't
you
agree I feel like you get more out of
it cuz if you spend more money on the
hotel you might even be able to get a
hotel of a pool or so bigger room more
space better bathroom oh my God this is
so weird first
stream none of Yoshi Shenanigans second
stream all the time third stream
Yesterday Once in like 7 hours today all
the time
huh what if the pool yeah that was kind
of weird spent a lot of money on the
hotel and then it was [\h__\h]
wobbly water weird weird everything not
worth it that one was not worth it but
normally I feel like it's worth
it ah Yoshi let's
go middle
yeah at the mold yeah
crazy that hotel was so
weird wobbly water brain rot
forever oh he danced a little bit that's
so
cute
nice get them all get them
all why do I have Peach in the team
anyway doesn't really matter I guess
because lucky again cuz both both Bowser
and Mario are
plenty doing plenty of work what's going
on is it it
last time I was like asking you guys is
it like a thing with certain enemies
drop the lucky thing more often and
there were some people that said
yes but I'm not
sure is it the
enemies oh my God
middle he's tiring out my
eyes
wait where is the storage box anyway is
it in my H oopsie is it in my in my
bachelor
pad you can decline I don't want to
though why would I
decline the drill
claw claw maybe for him oh it does
a
did I miss anything
else
no uh Bow's best atem oh
okay cuz it tires out your eyes it's
fine it's just for the
[Music]
moment he's going to
fall come on old ass slapstick comedy
there
[Music]
nah nah the other jokes are
funnier nice carpet did a carpenter make
that he a CO so this is where you went
off to this is H sm's castle and no
trespasses
allow uh you're going to stop me
[Music]
you oh wait I have a different attack
right
[Music]
okay is he strong he doesn't look strong
I guess he might be strong
[Music]
though carpenter joke it's not a joke is
this a joke to
you is this a [\h__\h] joke joke to
you it's not a joke to me
Yi a that's not a Yoshi what the hell
he's hiding behind King bom it's nice to
see
you actually excited to see you uh let's
let's shoot
you or let's give Mario even more power
[Music]
y I didn't get oh I did get it oh
okay I get to attack
[Music]
again no just trust me bro don't look up
definitions I am the one that decides
all
definitions
oh that's pretty low actually I wonder
if special attack would be better in
this
[Music]
case oh wait he's almost
down well well that's enough anyway why
why put more effort into it
[Music]
right that's it that's
it so you were
saying he turns blue oh was he like uh
uh
Enchanted where a
Cooper huh where am I hello how have you
been I you made it back here somehow but
it seems like I've I have been
brainwashed or something it can't I
can't seem to remember anything have I
done something
wrong a don't worry about it I'm like
really nice now so I forgive you of
course it's great running into a loyal
minion like you what a I'm glad it looks
like you've got some tough new minions
now ah but my magic can still help
you oh get what you
for
I was just reading it as if it's like
some random rambling this magic treasure
box or never run out of coins just keep
on hitting it I'll be here if you need
me come by whenever you need to rejuven
are they doing this because it's the end
of the game and it doesn't matter
what what do you mean it doesn't run
[Music]
out oh it sounds SI similar to the one
in the movie oh I'm not aware of
[Music]
that well I guess it's really slow
yeah do I still need some money for
[Music]
something can we get to 1
million people tried 100 jumps challenge
but how about the Thousand jumps
challenge for
[Music]
coins it's so lame that you give this to
me at the end you little
[\h__\h] oh you heal me oh thank you is it
really the end why is there no safe
Point here why is there two
doors oh hi are you're the shop
I'm in a good mood I can't always be
coming to your rescue you now if there's
anything you need you just buy now
oh I don't need oh wait maybe some pck
me oh I can't six is
Max wait there's
more okay
ooh another new set of outfits we said
don't change the one from Peach
[Music]
right okay ooh
okay oh why does he seem like kind of
emotional about it see you
pal see you on the flip
side you know what you can use this box
instead of me I don't need it anymore I
don't need money to be happy I have my
friends after all oh my God can't walk
properly ah ah what the [\h__\h] I can't
jump
dude does that seem fair to
[Music]
you his new attack is so cool like his
hand kind of
[Music]
twists the friends you kill what my
friends are alive what
in ah
ah
m
[Music]
he looks so
funny I love him well can we leave if he
loves me then let's not fight
him oh big
boy he why fight someone who's in love
with me H so cute
fory more exp do I look like I need exp
now at this point
H H is this Smithy
[Music]
laughing is that Smithy no it's a samur
thingy so you're the notorious Mario and
PR you made it this far I didn't think
you could oh we're back up here again oh
Facey little fellow aren't you but this
is the end of line now you got to deal
with me oh
good
okay yeah I don't know what voice to do
for this one oh nice nice closeup there
W is he
[Music]
strong wait this is attack and above the
shooting star shooting stars rain on
foes from the sky while boosting Al
okay let's do
it okay Boomer what do you mean what
Boomer his name is
Boomer what didn't see didn't pay
attention to that oh it's really a
boomer was he always called the Boomer I
feel like when the game first came out
the word
Boomer did not exist yet
did
[Music]
it it
did really really in the same sense
really oh really really though really
are you sure like for
[Music]
real
I'll never get it right not
available
[Music]
really
ouch
M baby boomer m yeah but like did this
game come out when baby boomers were
already a thing I thought it might have
been
before is the game not that
old thought it was pretty
[Music]
old Boomers were born in the
1950s he
so damn can only really call people
Boomer if they're like
70 people are overusing the word
[Music]
Boomer well that's
nothing
[Music]
he's so sad I can't be defeated by
them I won't let this happen I want
Fallen battle battle gasp cough
hack having an attack
gasp
1963 I don't need you shi sh I am a s I
am prepared to go
go take uh Di
shine
theia see you lat k
k Boomer a boomer poor
Boomer but not to worry A Little Fall
isn't going to hurt
you it is not well I guess he's the
armor protects him we must hurry to the
appointed
Place hang on TI and where away we go
they
dance now
let why do peach and Gino not get to
dance faster FAS
[Music]
how did that happen did it suddenly
stop
wooho there she gets the oh no actually
not cuz she has a level up so she
doesn't get to
dance hey
oh is it really the final
fight end of Z game the eyes are
protecting
extor
ahuh Smithy this
you not
[Music]
yet
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I I kind of want to use
mow but I guess you could
only Peak on like one of these four
things
right no I I don't it will zoom out a
little bit right if I do ultra jump
s
yeah he doesn't even go out of frame it
is there weakness he doesn't even go out
of frame in this one cuz they're so low
but they have to zoom out for for the
top the
[Music]
exer
nice let's see what exer
thinks well we won't get to see it
sorry and no weaknesses that we know of
f how about some
[Music]
poison just because it's
alien oh that's pretty
good oh it's Prett protection is gone
let's
go now we can
attack no don't turn me into a scar I I
I I I I thought I resist that [\h__\h]
no wow not flare that's pretty strong ah
there we
go but I can still jump if I wanted
to yeah let's
go
[Music]
ah he didn't even jump on the left side
oh well that still pretty good okay time
to switch to our tank
Peach and do a group
[Music]
hug thank God we're back to
normal
m a [\h__\h] I I always got this timing
right now I get it wrong what's going
on 145 I wonder if he's just really
really really
[Music]
tanky
MVP Peach MV Peach that's right let's
let's try although we're so low on FP
already I don't know if I want to do
that put Gino in okay yeah for the
AOE so
true all in or nothing Kaboom Kap
Kaboom M that's big damage
L I like how the mouth moves properly
like as if it's singing
it
um Mario Mario wake up this is not a
dream you little
[\h__\h] thank
[Music]
you let's go for the weaker one don't
want to waste too much of the
f I'm guessing that is a sign that
the the mouth is dead because the jaw
[Music]
dropped ah too early let's see ah the I
back one of the ey and other ones
[Music]
Yik
yeah Gina worldl is
instakill oh for real gin worldl
what on on exer or on the other
parts if you time it perfectly I never
ever timed it
perfectly priority to contact okay let's
go stop
it do I have to do it when the other
parts are down only if you time is
perfect the eyes also need to oh okay
okay okay
okay I a
[Music]
bit m
M thank
[Music]
you well we might as well use
our FP
items not hoard them
endlessly I want to try the disc
shooting
again but I will fail again I will
probably never
[Music]
succeed why don't you go to the top okay
that's fine yo 600 let's
go and now we go bop bop bop bop to the
top h
M can bring Bowser back just for
this weak
but we're just waiting for the Gino
world to hit with probably zero
damage it oh I mean it was 73 at least
not zero but I did not get the frame
I'm definitely too early
[Music]
always no no the mouth is
back oh well nothing to worry about y b
I [\h__\h]
[Music]
up
uh plan is to get the FP back and bring
Peach back for a
[Music]
heal a big group
hog oh the mouth doesn't protect ah
right okay so I can I can still do the
world okay okay wow are you for real are
you for
real m
[Music]
all right oh one eye is
bad Ur
jum no it's so hard when he oh one two
and three St it
oh so hard when he goes to the top one
because the you there's barely any
[Music]
space I thought that star attack was a
AOE but I guess it wasn't cuz I don't
think I I I blocked on everybody wait
but I did block did I block did she
resist or did she
[Music]
block are they're all
alive ah
switch ah he's still sleeping oh well
that's
[Music]
okay I did block oh so it is not an AOE
because I only saw her
[Music]
blocking no ah when he
switches so
tough
[Music]
20 memberships what made you do
that
what thank
you so generous what the
hell M good
damage
[Music]
ah maybe I should have used it with
peach
honestly maybe she can do a psych bomb
why
not
yes yeah so many new eggs welcome
eggs I'll make some nice cookies
Christmas cookies out of you next week
so your life span will be short but
enjoy it while you're here I actually
just yesterday uploaded the new members
wallpaper so you can grab that if you
want uh in the community
[Music]
board eggs eggs
eggs it's cute isn't it it's very
snowy building building a snow
[Music]
chicken
[\h__\h] mouth already back oh he's dead oh
it's sucking me into dark dark space
no happy music
nonetheless this is where the last
starus oh
no ma
there where the [\h__\h] are we oh uh do you
do you know where this leads to it looks
like exer the contact between the two
worlds in other
words if we follow this road we'll find
smiffy so what's keeping
us hang on hey I only joined so that I
could get my castle back I'm not going
to be dragged along to the stupid hunt
I'm going to gather my minions and but
I'm your minion where are your minions
you little [\h__\h] you Mario is an official
member of Bowser's minion so
delusional you got to help Bowser you
completely missing the
point I ought to rip your stuffing out
now think about it Bowser exer connects
to Two Worlds right even though we
defeated exra there will be other weapon
beasts that come through that connection
Your Castle is at the entrance point to
your world in short the weapons will all
pass for your Castle is that what you
want
uh more weapon things coming to take
over my castle what about my
privacy yikes this isn't good at all in
fact it
stinks but I can't just be pass with
these n poops what I've got an image to
keep
up I've got it no one insults Bowes
minions and gets away with it I've got a
bone to pick with this Smithy Guy come
on MAR let's go teach him a lesson right
now together I'm so
Sly it looks like we're together on this
one let's go ha I I could leave through
here how nice that they place a
trampoline to leave here so nice of
them oh interesting
design what
what do I run sideways to roll wait how
do you wait wait wait wait how do you
roll that [\h__\h] did I just
jump oh oh B oh like this ah we I have
to jump kind of with
it the you bumbs on
[Music]
me uh
oh pretty cool
[Music]
music uh
uh oh what the [\h__\h] is
that Dodge at all cost
[Music]
everything my my my my my perception of
this Dimension is growing stronger
I'm you
[Music]
changed oh there's so
many oh no there's even
[Music]
more if you kill it before it turns into
more I guess that
is the way to
go I have
failed I would like the Advent Reef that
I bought because I'm not making one now
so I bought one and it's it's not made
with the tree branches it's made out of
moss genius right
[Music]
no I'm his favorite
thing
oopsy it actually looks really nice I
like the the Moss
re oh God these are so
bouncy my
God what why am I already at a safe
Point oopsie didn't
see is this already the middle of the
dungeon did I take the right path cuz
there were two paths and and I got this
one what the
hell
oh the ultra
Hammer but it can't be better than a
lazy shell because
it's not it's indeed not better okay and
what
[Music]
about no no way does that lean
me okay back here what the [\h__\h] is this
done oh that brings me up there
[Music]
uhhuh this is really tricky
yeah hidden chest by the safe block
no what does it
have feel like since we haven't had one
in like two dungeons it must be
something special should I go
back what the [\h__\h] is this though looks
like a mid boss
mushroom oh to heal now whatever we
don't even need
that Cy
it's Mario yeah it's Mario yeah how did
he get here I don't freaking know we're
about to do
something ring a ding
[Music]
countdown is it already New
Year's let's hit allos let's go no time
to
[Music]
waste
I should bring out a tangent I have so
many tangents but I don't know I've just
been vibing with this game that I don't
even feel the need to tangent too
much let's see shut up what do I
[Music]
have I told
this oh I told
that okay I have a bunch of random small
ones that could possibly end within a
second I just wanted to let you
know I don't even know why I wrote that
down why did I okay I can turn this into
a small tangent you know you know you
know in airport sometimes there's like
these dogs that sniff
you you know right looking for something
and I oh
oh I've seen them here and there but but
in Japan at the airport you know you
know they can be different breeds right
but you know in Japan it's a beagle it's
a cute ass beagle and I've seen him
several time and I always was hoping
that he would sniff me because he look
so cute but he never did and this time
he did and I was really excited for the
Beagle so popular like everybody's like
looking at him while he's doing his work
he's so cute he's a [\h__\h] beagle yeah
so cute so small
and cute
dog cute
aggression I just wanted to tell you
that I met a cute
Beagle I think I even took a picture but
it was blurry cuz I kind of felt weird
about taking a picture of the
beagle I didn't want to make get too
obvious and I'm taking the
picture but yeah yeah that that was that
was important right thank
you it became smaller time to
recover
[Music]
and let's do a
switcher thank you thank you thank you I
was sniffed but nothing nothing was
found I should have put some food in my
bag because like a lot of the time they
don't even I I watch some documentaries
sometimes about like the Japanese Tokyo
airports that they have where uh
especially in the Nita one um but
sometimes they follow
the what do they call the the the what
do you call the the thing where they
check what you have and then possibly
throw it
away if if it's not allowed in the
country what do you call
that
oops Doom
reeverb
TSA Customs I guess Customs
okay yeah so I
watched [\h__\h] I missed the
timing I watch that sometimes and
they're so Leni and nobody ever gets a
fine they're just okay you brought like
uh 20 kilos of meat oh no problem uh
just we'll just throw it away but next
time don't do
it it's so lenient so if I want
interaction with the Beagle maybe I just
bring some
food and hope the Beagle finds
me but it's actually ridiculous I can't
believe that so many of these
Travelers like even if you don't look up
the
rules do you really think it's okay to
bring like like some people bring the
craziest [\h__\h] like one full suitcase of
bananas one full suitcase of already
cooked Curry one full suitcase of raw
chicken meat or stuff like that like are
you for real they open your suitcases
I'm like in what world did you think
that this was going to be
fine also like Japan is Japan seems to
be like extra uh strict about what you
bring in terms of food like
no most products are NG not acceptable
to [\h__\h] why am I why can't I do this
anymore Gino
[Music]
down and then yeah usually there the
excuses oh because uh I brought this to
Japan because they don't have this
specific fruit in
Japan uh but I mean I'm pretty sure if
you look hard enough they might or they
say oh the banana from my country is
better than the bananas in Japan well I
mean really do you need it so so
desperately especially if you have a
full suitcase of it is that really the
real reason are you not trying to sell
itm and if you're trying to sell it then
I feel like you know that in reality
what you're doing is bad and I can't
believe those custom agents are really
just letting they're actually too nice
they're actually too nice they let all
that
[\h__\h] pass by they say we take everything
that you brought but you don't get a
fine just don't do it again those
bananas are important Well w
[Music]
w just got a permit beforehand man time
to view the Aurora let's go show
me so
[Music]
pretty time for peach to come back Mommy
save your children
please don't get there Mommy save us
thank you thanks Mommy okay so what's
effective here maybe we'll try some
jumps cuz I feel like it's it's it's uh
good to jump on a clock
[Music]
they were Donkey from protect no no no
no support them I mean no I I they could
but I also feel like they should just
find
them what they don't zoom
out that was tough that was tough the
top left Bell is so hard to hit oh my
God cronies can you
confirm nice jumping though right I got
pretty
[Music]
far broke the
clock we don't need
time was this effective did I try
already oh it's PR good it's pretty good
uhoh Dark
Star well it's on Peach anyway so it
wouldn't have mattered much I
guess just one
[Music]
left and I knocked it off let's
go was that the mid
boss let's save again
wait this is a different safe Point not
the one with the hidden Block H
[Music]
that was a boss okay so there's quite a
bit
more
okay oh
treadmills I want to buy a treadmill I'm
I'm I'm still thinking oh it's those
boys but painted silver another
Hood a come on oh come on stop it you're
so annoying what you going to do what
you going to do
you're barely doing any damage oh my God
just wasting my time I can't believe
it thank God that's
effective I bought one for my stand up
desk it's been pretty
cool really really help right I just
can't decide which one to buy maybe I'll
buy whatever no no don't send even
more oh no
[Music]
okay does this move okay where did I
go God damn it [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] where am I why am I
here well I'm not complaining I guess
what the [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
oh okay
another one
[Music]
more what the [\h__\h] are those enemies
they look
funny see I actually did end up making a
way bigger tangent out of the beagle
then I thought I could I am so
powerful and yet I fall down there what
the [\h__\h] what what what do you want me
to
do I criticized the
Customs at airports for being too
lenient I can make a tangent out of
anything that's why I voted for you this
is the perfect example yeah why you
should vote for me is there still time
to vote like when's the deadline maybe I
should advertise one more
[Music]
time nomination wasn't for nothing so
true W for president already did thank
you thank you you know you know it can
only be me I mean I probably won't win
cuz it's a twitch event so I feel like
you
know don't have the best
chances what what's the
deadline I
[Music]
wonder wow
300 thank you if anybody didn't vote yet
please vote for me can only be wa let's
think
logical who else can take tangent like
that about seeing a
dog holy
[\h__\h] where do this go
back
[Laughter]
wow this is like the final test for
me the paths are so narrow too where the
[\h__\h] did I go this
side
[Music]
what no
way I guess oh they bringing back the
bosses cuz that the those those Rangers
were also the
bosses
H you even brought his
weapons I don't see a deadline only the
date of the stream then that might be
the deadline or like a little bit before
I guess when is the stream what's the
date 3 years SP thank you so much thank
you 16 oh that's still a while to go
okay I can still add the T okay
[Music]
okay now that's pretty
bad
that's also pretty
[Music]
bad it that's the
worst and no normal attacks I was going
to normal attack now though oh
man please be why is everything so
weak
I feel like it most serves to promote
fillian I don't know I
mean I don't think that that's the
intention but it may have that effect
yeah M shock an enemy should we shock
him falling
[Music]
star
it's on the website if you look up
vtuber Awards twitch or something like
that it will probably come up I
retweeted it on Twitter but I might make
a community post one of those days
[Music]
let's throw out some
items do these work anyway on on a
special enemy like
this no oh why not throw out those items
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah if not now then when
e oh that's actually weaker when mow
uses it interesting but we got a freebie
[Music]
so
what
what what what where can I find that
Alexander
what I'm going to
cry you're joking
right
what where
how what how do I see
that no the game didn't crash I saw
something in the chat that I have to
check out you better not have like
trolled me Ty
faster it's something good if it's for
real no way you little [\h__\h] why are you
typing so slow
explain what
explain what do you
mean did you fall
asleep where where where
where what what you mean she talked
about
me well you you have to
elaborate what do you
mean I'm looking for the needy you
Twitter but they don't like like talk on
there don't leave me hanging just like
that that's literally the the definition
of uh doesn't elaborate and leaves kind
of just
dips maybe cuz you're embarrassed cuz
you just made it up or
what refuses to elaborate for I I
can't what do you
mean stop draging my name for the
mud maakan said she loves you what right
now so Random why is everything so
Random right
now okay I will give you some time maybe
oh maybe he's like trying to send it to
me on Twitter but blue blue found it
what it's
real I have been Hest the thing is like
I recently uh like every once in a while
I like use my kiaha uh YouTube account
to like comment on some K-pop uh mvs or
performances and I recently did that on
on a niiu
uh
NIU video and then a lot of people like
upvoted my comment so they may have seen
it maybe that's why she mentioned me did
she mention
me wait wait
she saw my comment what the [\h__\h] where
is this where is this still looking what
what where
is I went to Blue Twitter but I can't
find it on Blue
Twitter you add you in her
tweet she add it she added
me why can I not where is
this
it's it's my OSI in a uh Japanese adle
group that's
like it's a
fan Oh you mean the fan account and
Alexander fought that was really HT cuz
I thought she doesn't have a Twitter
anyway like you mean the fan account
that's not
her I hate you right now
makes me want to cry
now fan account I know that fan like I
know that that was a fan I know that you
thought it was her or what yjo
room one year one year and nothing
[Music]
less m
what do you mean gullible it could have
totally
happened but just not really on Twitter
cuz like maybe on
like even then like they don't
normally
mention like I mean I may not be just a
normal fan like the
but still it's not really something they
would do
TB that's why it sounds so
[Music]
unreal that's incredible Legos are back
but just in your usual room only in your
usual
room
still 1,600
[Music]
okay can't believe this I
can't cuz like Nina she's my AI in an
idol group called
niiu and there's a fan account that I
guess could deceive someone who doesn't
know Japanese that
it's her but wouldn't she have more
followers you
[Music]
know cuz like he apologize like you
better but yeah cuz it's the span
account uses her picture as a profile
[Music]
picture uh
yeah
[Music]
no this apology alone will not fix
this that damage is so low what a beefy
beefy
monster yeah see this is one of the
reasons why the check marks should not
be available to
everybody
M oh my God all my syrups do I get get
another chance to buy
something cuz this one like it could
force you to Forever use your special
attacks and then you kind of
[Music]
[\h__\h] the count didn't have it oh
okay
I don't even remember that you know
um oh now it's a bit more
[Music]
damage man I I honestly think one day if
it could be real it could
happen could
happen it's not completely unrealistic
so I will work towards that statement
one day being real people in my chat
will be like oh my God she replied or
said something about you and and and
this time it will be real I will work
towards
[Music]
that
I don't
know oops see
[Music]
uh
it's been a long time since I watched
your stream thank you life do be busy
sometimes but I appreciate you taking
your time all of you guys to watch my
long ass
streams finally we can attack normally
Hallelujah now
die die I
said
shn
no
[Music]
finally do we have to fight is this a
Boss Rush kind of dungeon do we have to
fight all
[Music]
bosses I
said hoping Luna says not like
that I already skipped some yeah I
thought some
uh they they dropped that [\h__\h] endlessly
no
way I hate
this let me
go
am I not going to run out of the FP
items I feel like I
might well I I didn't see the answer in
the chat is there going to be another
shop anytime
soon they usually go down faster uh was
I really
unlucky there won't yes yes yes there
will be
oh
Gino yes okay right before the end when
is the end the end will never is never
the end it's never the end it's
never
whatever oh little damage
[Music]
oh
one jump
600 I must think if I would do one of
them like one two three four like
several jumps it might even be less
damage cuz the game is Just So Random
with this kind of stuff to me that's
what it feels like to me 600 holy
macaroni how how
many
six okay let's use up these uh
six and three of
those I I have to be a little bit uh
spazm from now
[Music]
on which means we're not going to use
P's skill even I'm going to
heal like
this oh wait oh no there
yeah
[Music]
a can I run can I run from this
fight oh man can't even do these simple
ah
[Music]
jumps
let me go if you love me let me go oh no
not not again let me no no no no no no
no no
no is he normal he's
normal I'll try to leave though yeah
[Music]
okay
enough
oh another safe
Point
okay we're all level 20 now oh no never
mind we were level 20
now is this it I don't know is it that
would be nope too easy too short for the
final
[Music]
dungeon these are easy to
Dodge I wouldn't say I'm on the leveled
right guys so I don't really need to
fight all of them right see how this
deceives me it's here but it looks like
it's
here H got the heel and the
flower okay I appreciate that what a
great room this is so there may not be a
shop anytime soon but oh where's the
path where I
go where do I go is this not is this a
dead end
you have to fight the one that's
bouncing oh
okay
okay land on
me machine
mate let's
[Music]
go
what he what's
he Pro prone is that the right way to
use that word to
jumps I feel like logically like jumping
on the tip of his spare shouldn't be
good for me oh yeah I should just punch
normally right right true true true true
it's kind of low damage
[Music]
though
let's see what he
got ah BR 34 that's really low let's go
let's go
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah that was
nothing can't can't really be considered
a boss fight I guess probably just a
normal
[Music]
fight easy peasy lemon
squeezy just inferior copies so
that's howdy Tel hi did you just
arrive welcome
welcome oh now we can drop down here
okay I wonder if the the healing
mushroom over there in that room that I
just was in also recharges oh these are
real
bosses we all they're taking a
bat h
I a seconds for a few minutes why we
didn't like to
[Applause]
play Domino and
cloaker I was saying I wonder if that
would have recharged like the other one
that I saw and I could have healed
again but any in any case let's see how
they react to normal attacks
first no pretty good
damage ouch
ouch you like the
boys what do you mean faas in this game
nothing sounded like FAA well which what
are you saying that for sound like f no
it did
not
[Music]
nice
it did it did some damage on the cloaker
but not at all on the Domino that makes
me wonder if uh cloaker is weaker to
special attacks and Domino is weaker to
normal
attacks perhaps oh he's
down he's got such a fancy hat is
tougher than I fart I don't like what
this is going where are you going oh
snake if if I kill cloer first would I
have this fight with the snake and the
other
one he he fits in right perfectly
what bad Adder bad Adder is that
supposed to be a
pun
ooh if I do ultra jump but he's sitting
on top of the snake do I just always
jump on cloer kind of more or less
[Music]
snck is
long oh I I guess it yeah it goes
down like Mad
Hatter ah oh cuz he's the Hat maybe
let's see how this
[Music]
works that's that's that's that he like
jumps into the snake and you have no
idea
oh my
God take out cloer first and then add
her I'll
try but I'll just do AOE for
now yeah pretty bad cuz it's hard to see
cuz he kind of jumps through the
bodies too
so not my favorite thing to
do
[Music]
it makes me so
tense just normal eh oh yeah well I mean
but wasn't he like more it felt to me
like he was weaker to uh special attacks
you
know yeah see I mean that's just mow
being weak as well
but no it's all right okay snake let's
go to the
snake I feel like from Mario we can do
normal attacks but but mow actually I'm
going to switch mow
[Music]
out I know the timing for that now it's
when he bends his
[Music]
elbow can we try
this
[Music]
y I don't
know danger
no we love danger
[Music]
noodle oh that's
weak how
much 300
[Music]
M
danger El
squiggle so
true
[Music]
me let's see can I get another
tangent that one is also so short what
what am I why am I writing down these
things and there's a bunch that
I can't tell yet
this one
[Music]
I I told that I told
that I told I I already told quite a lot
I mean only so many things can happen in
one and a half weeks but uh I told the
Pokmon cards I told did I tell the
fridge head incident or was that Twitter
only I told the I told you guys about
the
Starbucks we talked about the panel
pretty
much I'm going to watchong uh I saw
someone else's inan is doing a watch
along along so I thought
but I guess I there's probably no need
for me to do
one it was Twitter
only that you put your hand in the
fridge yeah yeah yeah yeah but you guys
do you all know the fridge in the head
[Music]
story I feel like most of you guys
follow me on
Twitter no I didn't go to k do Bo I was
like like totally booked out no time
sadly next time next time I have one
thing to do next time then and we could
combine it with an off
collab yeah but I forgot I was there no
you were
not you want to hear it in Tangent form
okay okay okay was nice to hear your
gigles as you tell us I'm stream you
guys love me too
much H yeah
okay so I was I had like two 3D
recording days that I swear they they
took like 10 hours each and it was so
exhausting I was so dead at the end of
each of them thank God there was one day
in between
off but on the second day I think this
happened on the second day
yeah
oh do I go this way on the second day uh
there was a time where after like we
were taking a break oh wait a second
wait a second
clerk who is this a
boss production is on schedule this
despite the fact that clay [\h__\h] board
Spirit of and Dax and rers were defeated
at this R mayy will have a new Army in
no time a new Ary you can't be making
more weapons haven't you caused enough
trouble
already oh yeah who are
you this is DB
Mario H give up now you still have a
chance so cute shut down for now or
he'll stop
you what did you say little puff oh mad
mullet trash
him H you can
try you guys look weak as [\h__\h] though so
good luck I guess yeah I was alone in
the like break room waiting room thingy
changing room whatever for a while and
like I I I got just I just got done
dancing one thing and I was so so
freaking hot and sweaty and there was I
think no air conditioning running in the
room
so I enter the room nobody's there I
look around I'm like what can I do I'm
I'm feeling so hot and I see the small
small mini fridge in the room that has a
few water bottles inside I'm like okay I
have to this is the only way of cooling
down here I
think it's it's on the ground so I sit
on the ground I open the door I put my
head in and I'm like yeah this pretty
good but I got to go deeper like first I
was just trying to without having my
head inside just like opening the door I
thought it would help but it wasn't
enough so I stuck my head in 2 seconds
in the other side of the room has the
door and and uh the producer director
enters just to like you know go through
some stuff kind of like meeting time and
sees me and I noticed someone walked in
I turn around I noticed it's the
director out of all people and we both
burst out in laughter cuz it's such a
weird
scene and I why laughing I I tried to
explain myself like it was it was so hot
you have to understand I was just trying
to cool my head up cuz there was a
little break I didn't think anybody
would see me and yeah then then he he's
like oh oh never mind uh please please
continue it's okay like I I I'll come
back later I guess I'm like okay I will
continue cooling my head often thanks
bye and I couldn't stop laughing
afterwards and then I had to tell
everybody the story jenma and manager
assistant
Chan I'll you person person slowly backs
away basically it was so funny was so
com
comedic like one had to be there
honestly but the thing is like uh even
in the actual Moab
room there is some kind of air
conditioning but they can't like turn it
down too low they say because of the
cameras you
know it's not good for them which I
guess I understand tactical things and
all
that but yeah when when you dance
endlessly in there in that in those
clothes Idol outfits mhm that are really
[Music]
hot it's really bad no
it gets so hot mama M all right let's
see what you
got he's so cute he looks like a little
toy he it's just made out of wait is
this Potato Head with armor
on from toour story
again B making another
appearance you can't fool me Potato Head
Mr Potato
Head Pizza while recording is lit how
Bruce what
what for real why are you telling me
that are you saying I should be careful
because I could get a heat stroke and
die that's like pretty
pessimistic Mama
Mia I would hope
not yes oh my
God what was it like was it a recording
in a tropical country cuz then I can
understand my God I'm so glad that
generally Austria I mean it gets hot in
the summer but at least it doesn't have
like tropical climate where in the
summer it's like really really humid cuz
humid summer that's the one thing that
gets this Phoenix
[Music]
down Geno is Woody of course he
is you just
noticed H hope you learn a
lesson we're almost there Mario come on
he's so positive and excited
wow what are you supposed to oh probably
nothing
good maybe produces even
more oh no mow mow meow's a claw machine
what's the funny face Mario I know
you're trying to make me look aren't you
I'm not going to follow for that
one
no so
stupid help me
Mario every day is a humid summer in
Florida for real Florida also has
humidity like in
Japan oh we saved him boy that was scary
I guess the queen switch controls the
cran Oh I thought we would have to
rescue him like he gets abducted and I
have to go find him we have to fight for
a while without
him even higher okay I'm never going to
Florida thank you uh wait how do I
control it then oh oh I don't Mario
Mario how the [\h__\h] did you get
here
was
[Music]
oh Dam it's really
unfortunate
how how how how did he get here ah I
finally made it up here I gave you a big
break for this playr so you don't have
to voice me but now you have
to let me help you guys out
princess oh he doesn't know right I'm
sorry I snuck out without telling you or
the chancellor I just wanted things to
go back to normal I want to do my part
to help princess
Ah that's it and dro the last me help
both Mario and the princess's
Worf what can you do oh is he the last
drop you guys said it would be a toad
right oh
nice I got
everything bye bye bye bye now or never
all right perfect thank
you actually that that's uh
pretty much all I'm going to buy I mean
I could buy like a couple of
these that's it I have no space
anyway thank you though can you oh am I
healed can you heal
me go ahead and spend it all like
there's nothing to
buy I mean some mid
mushrooms Max mushrooms that's enough I
don't need anything I got
Peach this is for you rock candy but it
goes into the storage
boxs literally I don't remember what
that is anyway we're almost there come
on let's show him thank you Toad is this
really the
end
oh blue you blue
now reminded to switch a
[\h__\h] guys that's not the last boss
though right so I can still switch it
maybe after this
one drill B will be finished on time
we're ahead of schedule me too 3 and a
half hours so much for 7 hours uhhuh oh
makees smiy proud good work everyone
good work everyone the harder we work
the stronger smiy will become the
weapons we manufactur here will be just
to think of it when smiffy takes over
Mario's world it's my world we can do
anything we want they consider it to be
my world
wow oh yeah ah I already did right thank
you thank you good good night mate I
wish you some bloody good dreams
mate we talking with the manager yeah
yeah
mikiah not so fast you sure are a cocky
bunch I rule this world not Mario don't
you forget
it it's Mario the clay Morton and spirit
ofage clones didn't stop him no no leave
Mario out of this I'm the one you need
to worry about not him Mario you're
about to make the longest jump he still
talks to
Mario a bower you're not even part of
the fight too bad too
bad let's go all
[Music]
[Applause]
in well that's that's
decent oh he gets more okay then I'll
just focus on the middle
man the
manager I think I guess if he it seems
like he immediately calls them there's
never an end he's producing
[Music]
endlessly why am I not attacking
normally I should have tried
[Music]
that also because of the helmet the
jumping might be oh no it was fine it
was
[Music]
fine ooh not
bad
[Music]
yeah I mean I guess it's not the last
boss but I still imagined
more expected
[Music]
more
uh yeah same like the Moon Over The Day
My genius and Brun are lost on these
fools
hiu like the Moon Over The Day My genius
and Bron are lost on these
fools beautiful beautiful you should
become a poet Bowser you have such a
soft
soul I just noticed they got spray
painted here oh
who okay uh go next oh I got
healed oh now a red one do we get
RGB oh it's a safe point so maybe it's
the last actually so I guess we already
had a green one it was it
green you there are you the one in
charge here do you know what your
weapons have been doing to our world
stop this nonsense at
once the director I'm afraid this isn't
possible and the against Smithy will be
dealt with immediate
meltdown
meltdown you can't scare me I've got H
up on my
side the sentence will be eliminated
production will
continue I don't know what that accent
is first I was going for something more
American can you
know pound
dead it's a
[Music]
girl
m is this guy going to go down as easily
the last one
perhaps and I'm just going to attack
normally ouch
ouch [\h__\h] I'm
stupid nice flip nice
flip I can't do that oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] at least he has pretty predictable
attacks
here oh [\h__\h] that counts I pressed it so
early oh [\h__\h] I'm so stupid
what am I doing I'm just
[Music]
chilling
a oh really but did Bowser ever get to
show this kind of
personality after this game in in
another
game once again let's
go did
and arpes is's always silly
a okay that was
scary but we can't run away now we've
got to kick these low lives out of our
world so that we can marry and be happy
forever
together okay for our marriage so that I
also finally get that kiss from you lady
can't believe I got Bamboozled there ooh
what is
this let's
go are you making
fo what is this melted cheese I'm not a
big fan of cheese
but I don't know maybe I could
try Factory chief M
Mario I'm surprised to see you here just
going to do a normal voice but this is
the end of the line for you this is the
closest you'll ever get to smiy so save
it a
moment you'll be father for my
incredible invention the gun yolk
yolk is
egg
fry what you turn me into a [\h__\h]
mushroom you little
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh I did it I did it I thought I
didn't
and what do we want to focus
on I I would have absolutely no idea
what to use to attack the gun Yol so
first I go for the chief oh that looks
pretty
good oh what it has a face it's cute OU
[Music]
[\h__\h] one more boost before Gino goes
home oh and ah I can't do the Gau right
now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
n what is the status effect thing ra
this
uh become
[Music]
invincible do I have a single one or do
I have to take the Cora cleansing
juice ah okay thank
[Music]
you yes do we get another
turn no uh-oh Gino don't
die bye-bye
Gino that's is really unfortunate cuz I
was going to use the gosh move oh I can
oh ah that's how you could use the toad
assist again I thought you could never
ever use it again but ah if somebody's
dead you
can I don't
[Music]
know and
yeah now
technal ah we need
[Music]
Peach
CH this is why he didn't make it to
smash don't say that's so
sad okay let's do this it's AOE too
perfect my sneeze was too
powerful
oh nice block wa I didn't think I could
do
that hey the chap is down let's
go
woohoo thank
you I I can you when when would you
block this when when when
when
timing did you are
you did was that a mistake normally you
just gift one when I
sneeze did are you are you okay did you
do the mistake I can I help you by
canceling it or so I don't
know
[Music]
oh my
God thank
you
50 I hope that was on
purpose oh my god there so many new
members today we have a sudden
influx ooh what should I do for members
only this
week this coming week I have to make the
schedule m
thank you so so generous
thank at least
Sana Jones watch along egling stream
sneeze
[Music]
stream H is it already movie time I mean
we did not watch a movie for a couple
streams
now so I could but didn't want yeah I
wanted it to be shorter on the shorter
side I I'll think of
something
H
[Music]
19 it's okay Peach you're you're so
powerful in so many other
ways okay now send me to Smithy already
I fought enough mid bosses that have no
chance against me
the production line hasn't
halted look Mario this is where the
weapons come from yeah I see I'm not
blind why is there crane machine still
there this must be where Smithy makes
his weapons to find the last star piece
and stop the factory we've got to defeat
him first Mario there's no turning back
now are you ready our Quest is almost
over and and when the time comes I will
become a real boy no let's get this show
on the
road he he didn't really say what
happens when the time comes I guess he's
trying to say sadly that he will leave
this body and it will return back to a
puppet and he can't say it because that
means that we won't able to be we won't
be able to be together
anymore and he's gone because he just
yeah vapor R safe
how can I hear huh what do you mean safe
do I go
back
spoilers I mean that that seems kind of
obvious from the beginning because we
know that he's just using the puppet as
a vessel
right and he's just here to accomplish
his goal and then go back to you know
this world so we'll see him in
Smash I guess
what did I just do what does that do I'm
making more what what's
happening
oh
oh oh I'm sending myself
there to where it all
starts
W that's not smiffy is
it it looks so
different there not what Smithy look
like hey there's still l oh there it is
it looks I like his design though it
looks really
cool
wow reminds me a little bit of that one
Pokemon really helpful
right uh there's a Pokemon that's also
like this big and has like such eyebrows
I think or something like that yes the
bom no
Obama yeah that's the one I was thinking
of I think or maybe like a mix of
several
ones all right finish your tour of the
factory H all right then how about a
little
demonstration
bul yo smiffy stop making those things
and hand over the star piece now Yahoo
woohoo
so you Mario looks like we're going to
have a little dispute over the
S oh [\h__\h] same voice what I do just hand
it over and get out of my
castle my am I a little touchy today
aren't we you know I'm actually growing
rather fun of this
place please don't make us go through
anymore just give us a start now or I'm
going to call my dad oh right I don't
really have one do I
oh better yet why don't you give me your
stars why then I could easily conquer
this world then we could get rid of all
wishes and create a world filled with
weapons sick
woohoo over here now I'll Crush you all
Crush Crush Crush Crush Crush Crush
nothing compared to a quiet even glow
just one
two ooh interesting Final Boss music I
want to dance
chaa one two one
two don't worry guys this one is not
suitable for Chate
ch
ch yeah no it's not not
suitable
uh it's so sweet that if you switch you
don't lose a
turn that's
like Unthinkable in other
games in other RPG
games the fireemblem weapons those are
yeah those would be great to have right
now I know another another Square game
you may like that's like this
FFX
10 I can't visualize like I I feel like
I've seen like you know a lot of
characters and this and that but I can't
even realize which one that
is uh okay let's just start by trying
normal
attack oh yeah oh wait what is that an
enemy on the side oh it
is
[Music]
oh let's do some damage
peachy what can you do oh that's so [\h__\h]
uh I should have switched her
up a little bit disappointing but she
wants in on the action at least once
okay does have a sad end
yeah I've learned that that's the thing
for Final Fantasy games
oopsie oh go
up which concerns
[Music]
me oh n is he going to create something
BL
oh interesting they don't just make them
appear they cre
create a minion together interesting
interesting so if we take one out they
shouldn't be able to do that
anymore oh I did
it damage kind of
[Music]
mid
this one's better I
think x -
2 oh nice there's an idle class an idle
class oh my God how are we even alive
after
[Music]
that wait is this thing
dead I
[Music]
no
yeah well if I have a feeling playing
another Final Fantasy game don't worry
guys I will consult you all uh because
there seems to
be doesn't seem to be an easy
Choice
[\h__\h] wow that's so weak mow I think you
got to go
I think you got to
go fire
saber oh oh no I never was able to block
that ever before
shees let's
go
melow going to switch you out sorry
oh they're making another Minion maybe
start from I do want to play more T off
games
yeah well we do have a DLC
upcoming oh
wow wait if I switch someone out who's
dead can I switch them back in again to
revive them
eventually whatever I'll use an item for
now I think ow oh my God oh my oh
oh oh oh
oh I I know the DLC is out but I want to
[Music]
wait
sheesh
[Music]
y revive first or heal first
let's try to get a full heal here a full
revive yes sir that's what I like thank
you
nice no oh he's really mad
oh he's moring what are you
doing so angry milk come down smiy your
head is like a geyser don't get worked
up think of your blood
pressure oh so supportive we just built
this yesterday and the foundation's very
weak calm the [\h__\h]
down I hate you all oh what e oh my
God seat belts guys that's why you need
seat belts even if you're not in the
car ooh
interesting we're in a basement that's a
creepy what what what are those things
anyway what are that supposed to is that
supposed to be
him I'm burning saing never have I been
so
wronged guess it is him it is time for
what I will show you my real form uhoh
I'll show you my true power I'll teach
you respect and I shall have my
revenge
that is not necessarily much more
[Music]
intimidating uh you don't look much
different it's just like it took off the
wig and the the
mustache
[Music]
what and didn't get healed
wow he can Dr more by by by smiiing
himself she that's kind of funny and he
looks funky now I like it I like
it n let's let's let
uh Mario do it let's use this
one
empty he's like a
dle yes nice finally that wasn't even a
full heal even though I got the timing
right
[Music]
oh something to take down Peach
what
what how much xp do she have left fall
no
uhoh oh this one's fine that attack is
fine the other one is very very
yby we got to take him down immediately
or maybe
even switch to mow for now while we have
some
yyu some room to
play what could
work I don't know I feel like mow is
generally like so weak
now Shocker on the tank
okay [\h__\h] I missed but it's okay oh it's
his weakness let's go yeah no it's tried
to block it but it's insta kill holy
[\h__\h] ow ow ow ow ow ow ow yeah okay this
actually a this is actually a b this
might actually be
a holy
[\h__\h] like everything else is manageable
but that attack is going to take me
down if I attack with Mario NEX is mow
right
I
hope then I'll heal with
mow
[\h__\h] y
[Music]
y when I
can't I what when is the timing
I mean I see the exam I'm trying I feel
like I'm I'm pushing it down
but we have to take him down we have to
take him
down please be good please be good
please do damage okay that's
decent I might bring Peach back or
should I uh what if I problem is if I
use too many pikme UPS
now
um and then let's say peach dies
eventually she can't revive herself so I
should keep some pickme UPS you
know uh do I have
some there's ice bomb there's fright and
fire is there like a
thunderbomb
no what the hell why
not yeah save it for peach then let's
bring in Peach is peach dead right now
she is
right but I can only revive her if she's
in the
field he switch
heads he'll Swit wait when you say
switch he's not going to bring it back
after he switches it once right he's
going to change to a different head
forever oh she's not dead okay then then
that's kind of good that's fine
um where's my
controller oh oh I think it was bugged
my controller vibration was bugged for a
moment it was vibrating in this in this
screen it was vibrating until I pressed
attack it's genuinely
broken my
controller
ah wait
uh I might bring in Bowser for a moment
so I can use a special
attack because they only have the
healing
one or I should I I feel like I want to
do that
now triple
move it will give us a boost too which
is pretty
nice
let's
go give it everything you
got this is the final
[Music]
battle oh oh yay we got the head down I
hope the others are not as
Troublesome his body can't his body
oh
he's I thought his head was down his
body is down what do you mean his body
is
down I'm done with my game today just
going to restore my
sanity okay uh we already did our our
specials so we can bring ah [\h__\h] I I
skipped I meant to bring in uh me lady
[\h__\h] I messed up
[Music]
heal himself or bring in Peach now I was
going
to switch Peach for Gino but you
okay let's get a full revive for
Gino oh that was a bit too early but it
counted thank
god oh he changes it though
oh back to normal head and down
two oh what the hell is
[Music]
that are we going to say something about
his nose and I I leave it to you
guys
wow
hey Ash OH yo I got oh almost missed it
darkar okay one two three yes I still
got it I still got
it still [\h__\h] got it yeah woohoo m
H I think we can oh not afford to switch
oh because they're dead oh my B's not
dead I have an
idea might as well use something like
[Music]
this and keep a full fighting team
in yeah yeah
yeah let's
go I'm burning with power Mo his bodies
back
o can't block how much damage oh
[Music]
my if we were to switch someone out for
peach for a heal who would it be or we
stay Who attack can we live without Gino
or Bowser for just one turn I mean don't
have to think too much about maybe I'll
even use one of those um heal the whole
party
items wait a second I could even become
invincible for free
turns [\h__\h] I still got so many good
items I have to use
[Music]
them uh what am I what was I going I
heal everybody uh party recovers 30
that's not oh all members recover fully
let's use this one
[Music]
I panic so much
uh wait so I mean these probably this is
just one person right
[Music]
maybe now then they they'll use it
themselves
sparing oh wait that's going to be a lot
of damage
[Music]
again
yo let's
[Music]
go
can you hear it in your head I can hear
[Music]
it I feel like he there this form is
very very receptive of normal attacks
so I'm just continuing to do that I I
hope I'm not like losing out missing out
on some good damage but this looks good
to me
[Music]
oh can't block don't die
Mario [\h__\h] I missed Bonk Bonk oh head
changing so we're done with that head
it's not coming back right it's a sign
of me winning right oh wait I mean I'm
fine with that form so it's
random it's a
random is should I be attacking the body
more is there like
a if the head can be changed
[Music]
endlessly yeah as long as it's not the
tank I'm fine
honestly no it is head always
okay wait wait I should heal [\h__\h] O's
see Mario sorry Mario sorry
Mario
[Music]
heal Mario or I don't want to switch out
Bowser and I don't want to use my pickme
[Music]
UPS one more Attack One More attack
is
there oh one more Invincible but then
after that maybe there okay time to
switch to
Peach revive Mario perfect I
think ideal I would
[Music]
say I know but I I don't know what's yet
what's like still to come you know like
it could be another moring session and
then another big fight what do I know
you know for all I know there's another
hour of boss fight and and and what if I
use up all my Revival items and then
Peach dies you know that's the thing
that's the
[Music]
thing yeah by I just going to die
maybe yeah that's okay Peach will revive
tank we're going for tank again please
don't it's tank does he only have two
options tank wait so was the tank uh mow
would be nice for the tank right he has
four I've only seen
two what's the tank more receptive of
special
[Music]
attacks magic right
M what about
fire let's let's
try only electricity but okay well we'll
we'll try
anyway that's
fine
um if it goes to Bowser again I'll bring
in mow and revive mow
I guess but while Peach has a turn we
could also revive
Bowser at least my FP are looking really
good throughout this fight I don't have
to recharge it at
[Music]
all Bowser resists
it
wow okay that's good to
know
that's good to
[Music]
know you're welcome mow now help me out
here
uhoh
this is why I have to keep the Revival
items for
peach where out of here
[\h__\h] yeah I hope this battle isn't much
longer a freebie thank God freebie
freebie is good uh shocker just as the
boat
lands mm didn't get it but
okay
[Music]
um oh it did way less damage than uh
before
[Music]
Oh
yes
nice I wasn't Magnum
oh he missed I he changed his head his
head okay okay okay okay
okay how much more if he can always
change his head does that like I don't
understand how his HP works man and it's
still wait he changed back to the same
one let's see what do we got interesting
firebomb is that one good I
wonder or we could
[Music]
do
just trying to use my
items you're not going to see as other
two forms wait wait maybe
now oh is it over is it for real for
real
over did I do it
woo woo
and I told you it's going to take 4
hours no I'm finished done
for you medlers you little
[\h__\h] I told you I was going to not take
longer than 4
hours unless there's more much more It's
The End right I beat KX yesterday
yeah come on
Mario send the last one way up
high oh
what not seven
hours I don't want to do post game Boss
rematches that doesn't sound good to
me
yay
[Music]
wooo now you're just being very very
very exact 4 hours 10 minutes so what i
t i I didn't even I didn't even start
the game right away I tangent it for
like 10 minutes had a waiting screen for
five six
minutes so maybe it is four minute H 4
hours thank you
everyone if you want to be exact I'll be
exact too
yeah yeah you're lost Chad the Star Road
is back to normal
and and you're leaving aren't
you
huh
wooo
go
I beat a Mario game the first Mario game
I ever
[Music]
beat he's gone or just the puppet left
over just small small small
small his
eyes oh oh he says
bye
[Music]
a the music is
cute what you doing what you doing
Gino I hope wherever you go you'll be
celebrated thank you for your
help bye bye
G thank you for everything
you saved the world not Mario you
did yeah take him take him
home and then reveal yourself as a True
Villain and challenge me to the final
fight
oh finally everybody's wishes will come
true
again and who's going to take out the
[Music]
Excalibur or it disappears on its
own
a nice
[Music]
view to of
sky
a what is he
singing a he got this doll
[Music]
back that's not that you see what is he
doing gifting people cookies oh
what
oh what are they
besties that's kind of
cute his
face oh man
booster why don't you want to be with
her HH she got a smoking hot body and a
weird personality but you got weird
personality too stupid star
man was so unimportant
Johnny a he's so badass so
cool but I'm I'm sad they never revealed
that he's actually a
cat he's not ready to come out of his
fur suit just
yet is it a fur suit or is it a scale
suit a sweet
sweet oh oh they relling the
castle maybe a slime
[Music]
suit what he angry
or supportive
oh kiss no oh man
wooo py py py the full cast oh
W booster is like peeking on the
side D
andle thank
you w party party Super Mario Super
Mario
RPG since 1996 based on the work of
original development Stu what that's
that's such a cold way to give credit to
them say her name say her name
Luigi why is Luigi there why the toes
there what's going on what is he oh he's
doing a bon
dance
B AI is
[Music]
God is that tot of
sky
[Music]
was old credits this was the old
credits
[Music]
wow a the cat
PS cute
[Music]
music yeah well let's talk about my
rating of the
game I think
uh it shall receive a good
one like I feel like my experience was
mostly
positive I'm surprised how a Mario RPG
could work so
well uh I was very surprised even though
they're on the cover but I thought just
because they're like important
characters they were on the cover but I
was surprised that you can actually play
Bowser and and Peach and all that and
and uh all the characters are really
Charming especially mow I like bullied
him a little bit but I feel like mow is
my favorite and he really grew on me and
there's a lot of cute Side characters
too and the Toads have a lot of
Personality which I I hear from a
certain Nintendo YouTuber that you know
nowadays toads they all look the same
and they all act the same but uh this
game like all the side characters have
their own personality there's a big
variety of enemies too the boss fights
are uh fun and original and the dungeons
too and they're not too easy at the end
it gets a bit easy if you do all the
secret bosses and all that but that
honestly at that point I appreciate it
because just uh not because I got sick
of it but I I did feel like okay let's
let's let's end this now I'm motivated
to end it I feel like I'm this journey
could come to an end
now the updated Graphics are really nice
and it's really really applaudable that
they didn't
change so many things that people really
enjoyed about the game so they kept all
the the charms all the
charm seems like when people first heard
about the Remake people were worried
that you know they will definitely
remove certain things but no like pretty
much everything stayed in they removed
or changed something that was for the
better pretty much
yes it's a faithful
reproduction the humor I really enjoyed
the humor in the
game it left me speechless
sometimes and uh yeah the story is nice
too and I would say it's like not
too it's a simple story but it's not too
too to how to
say I guess it's kind of predictable but
it's not tacky or or or too
predictable I don't know I think it was
fine getting to see a different side of
characters like Bowser was also really
refreshing and music was bopping toate
toate I I was V in to so many of the
soundtracks and I know sound the
soundtrack is one of the things that
people loved the most about the game and
I heard that fans of the old one are
Yosi very happy with how the new
soundtrack is still very faithful and
pretty much surprisingly even an
improvement it's like a Disney
thing an improvement to the OG even so
it didn't lose its quality at
all pretty wow
wow wow yeah they got the original
composer so that's why it turned out so
awesome oh NY
NY
you still carrying Gino around I'm going
to cry
[Music]
Bower Bower
oh everybody's
friends everybody's
friend and they took down the
[Music]
sword nice
ending happy
[Music]
ending
wow wow oh it's a
to I wish there were real fireworks like
that for New
Year's every party M feels like a big
party yeah and like there were genuinely
no useless party members uh I mean mow
got a bit too weak at the end but still
usable even someone like Peach i f oh I
don't need a Healer in my group but
Peach really uh saved my butt here and
there the end the
so every party member was really really
important
H Peach was MVP
surprisingly but if I were to say like
if I were really picky there were some
things that yeah maybe like two things
that annoyed me a
bit uh there's a bit of a
Spam of enemies in some map
where like you really can't help but run
into
[Music]
them and uh the
controls are difficult but that was in
the OG game as well and and it's just
like I guess with this kind of
angle there's not much you can do but uh
get used to the angle I guess
like optical illusions were tough on
me
M oh and I mean this seems to be an
issue that not many people have but the
timings were so difficult for me to
grasp a lot of the
time man you guys kept on roasting me I
was so bad that people come in and think
that I'm like I don't even know about
the timings and I'm purposefully
ignoring them or so no I really
tried and I don't know I did not play
for OBS but I don't
know maybe we can blame the controller
maybe the delay or maybe it's just a
skill issue um but it didn't
really make like the
whole process of battling that much
worse for me for me in
particular only for me personally I
didn't feel like it was was a big
problem uh because I feel like I still
did a lot of damage and it maybe it made
the fights more interesting that the
timings aren't too easy because if
they're too easy you can block
everything and you can do huge damage
and it's like too easy maybe you know I
don't know I feel like it was fine the
amount of uh timings that I got right
was I feel like kind of kind of balanced
out in a in a good way maybe
H uh and you got to remember that I
never played the OG so you
know and I'm just generally not good
with timing things like that's why I
can't play Rhythm
games some some like for example the the
Koopa shell the lazy shell I pretty much
always got that right and Bowser attacks
too there's certain attacks that were
just extremely unpredictable to me and
um hard to remember because especially
even when you get it right the
exclamation mark
disappears and then you then I forget it
like then I feel insecure and I'm like
well where was it
again
so I feel like I didn't do too bad and I
could I don't think I can blame myself
completely I think I would did
[Music]
fine so it was a lot of fun there was so
many characters too like wow wow wow
they really put a lot of
work and like even elements like Puzzles
and riddles and and hidden treasure
chests hidden rooms and all that even
that I was able to enjoy and the world
was interesting and had lots of
variation and like designs the mini
games were ridiculous and entertaining
like the cart and the waterfall like
there was a lot of
that yeah there was just
was great and then like the balancing
overall of like money and leveling and
everything was pretty great uh maybe on
that point one more criticism I I don't
think I really liked the way the stats
worked like how they would more or less
force you to go for certain stats
because they're buffed so you should go
for those you can't really get your own
build I mean you could but you're
ignoring all the the potential extra
stats and yeah that's you know I don't
know if I like that generally no but it
also at the same time gives me a guide I
guess that for some for a first player
tells me what's the best thing to do
maybe because as from what I heard it's
not random it's like there's a pattern
in uh what stats get buffed and maybe
there's like this whole plan they have
in mind as to what stats are the best to
get for these characters and that's why
they do that and in that case I I'm
grateful for them giving me a hand and
leading me in the right direction you
know yeah
MH oh man I could like I could say so
much so much good stuff about this game
I could go endlessly on and on and on
like how I found that the the boss
fights like in other games it's just
like always the same [\h__\h] always the
same just bashing bashing bashing the
the boss fights are all like the same
they don't have special gimmicks but
there were so many special gimmicks
too and and stuff like the booster Tower
uh I know I didn't like go back there in
the end but like having something like
the curtain thing before the boss fight
is really Charming
too and then there's also like options
like you don't have to kill certain
bosses or like mid bosses you could
absolutely nail the mini game and then
you don't have to fight them or the
other way around however you want to do
it you
know character designs were really cool
too from the bosses and the normal
characters yeah there's so so many
things I could say I'm like praising it
to the
heavens personally for like
RPGs you may know I prefer like more
like fantasy style RPGs but this was
really cute visually nonetheless and uh
yeah I really enjoyed
it different the also cool thing is that
like depending on the weapon that you
give the character uh the way they
attack change it's not just like for
example Mario gets a sword so he always
attacks the same way no he can get a
hammer he can have you just punch or he
can do this and that that's that's
pretty awesome
to yeah other games don't really do that
so they always attack the same way they
have like one class let's say they
attack with a hammer they attack with a
sword they attack with a magic stick
they attack with their fists this and
that and then they always attack the
same way but this this gives it like a
lot of variety again so it's like you
never get sick of anything in this game
cuz there's just general variety is like
a word that's written in the biggest
font
ever yeah it seems very ambitious
yeah I feel like I'm still missing
things to say I could still say
more yeah I heard that frog coins were
more like harder to get and more
important so to say in the
OG I didn't really
need my frog coins much I only needed
those 50 for the FP item but that was
really
it uh so I don't know if that's a good
change or not maybe people who play the
OG would say it's a good change or you
would say it's a bad change for me
playing this for the first time I
say
well frog coins were fine it didn't
really give me a reason to go really
hard on collecting them but I personally
appreciate that cuz I don't want to
spend too much time like looking up
where every single frog coin
is so
yeah frog coins are easy to get in the
original tool you just bounce on oh okay
so there is a way to get like endless
frog coins there too
huh you granted for them this gave them
more usage m
you were so happy when you got them you
know the happiest I was because there's
Yoshis in the
game the Yosi presence is big and I like
it they even showed Berto for one fight
that's amazing wow the only thing
missing is Yoshi uh Luigi but even for
Luigi they make like funny references
that like what we're looking for him
somewhere why did they not include why
did they bring someone like birdie Berto
into the game but leave l she hanging
somewhere must have been on purpose like
they brought so many characters yo but
no Yoshi H Luigi green is green green
sorry mixing up things I mean
Luigi they hate him they were maybe they
were trying to punish him Mama
Mia at least they show him in the
credits I guess that was something so um
I guess I have to rate this game as as a
point
9 9.8 out of 10 the length was really
fine too I didn't feel like it was too
long or too short I I saw other girls
finished it way earlier but for me it
was a good length
honestly might have been one of my best
rated games
ever yeah like there's barely anything
negative I can say and even the negative
things didn't impact me too much like it
didn't annoy the [\h__\h] out of
me
so the things that did annoy me were
funny
though me raging over that stupid those
stup stupid jumping course for example
like that's like
whatever yeah a quality I have to I have
to objectively admit that this is
quality pure quality yeah
great game and uh they should make more
like this too I know that's Paper
Mario but like besides Paper Mario they
they don't really do stuff like this
right so you know they could do
more gave you a new hit
[Music]
song Mario and Luigi uh but aren't those
like super super old I mean like now
noways they don't really do stuff like
this besides Paper Mario that's what I
mean nowadays in these
days
yeah well uh save you clear
data
yeah clear data wow it's so clear I can
see so clearly it's
beautiful so clear it's almost
transparent
they made one for the 3DS o that's
another game I never really picked
up but like I think I had a 3DS but I
didn't use it much
anyway should we check it out like this
is post game do they acknowledge that I
finished the
game that I saved the
world
oh or is this the beginning of the game
why you make you look like you about
leave to dream about defeating smiffy
did you oh CL I got you before you went
off to the factory I got you this
present what Factory am I going to stay
voucher take a night Cress up in the
marrymore hotel suit before the last
push ah that one I saw it in dendo uh
video that's all I had for you hope you
enjoy your stay in the suit sweet not
suit wait it wasn't a dream because he
mentions defeating Smithy so I would say
they acknowledge that I didn't which I
like and that's another thing I have to
appraise because I
hate but I hate how in most RPG games
when you finish the game you get a post
game but it's even like the beginning of
the game or right before the boss battle
basically there there's no after you
can't
experience
[Music]
it
well okay well then I bring me bring me
a freaking
game that acknowledges that I finished
it and gives me a post game that really
means post game not pre previously
before you killed the boss game
name Pokmon oh okay now you finished
the game Sound Player and play report
have been added to the journal now that
you've cleared the game the names of
monsters that were have oh
[Music]
interesting were you able to rescue the
princess from Bowser that good for
enough what was that OD noise he's with
me what's all little peaches
they think Peach is with Bowser but
Peach is in my team so schinger is peach
or
what peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches peaches why you still playing
cuz I want to see how what what what
what's up here all we can do is wait
here don't let us
down I'm done I finished the game if
only somebody would acknowledge it
nobody ever acknowledges it in these
games okay zero out of 10 just
[Music]
kidding gas they're gaslighting me for
real I'm a hero I'm a
hero what yeah what was that parade
nothing was that not existent did that
not happen the parade is it all in my
head
somebody said to check uh someone's
entry which
[Music]
one
what cool
X must be pretty much at the end ah
there it is this the
middle he crossed dimensions in order to
come here from the world of last
illusion a story about crystals too bad
he's still so
[Music]
two-dimensional
ah is the the what's ah Final Fantasy
last
[Music]
illusion wait is every Final Fantasy
game about mother
crystals cuz I only played one I don't
know check his
room room what do you mean room his room
a his
room a lot of the early ones
are most
what
[Music]
what was it this way no it
wasn't but they're not mother crystals
not a
hotel you have to visit Mary more oh
it's not
here I have to visit marry Moore
first really
[Music]
uh uh here
this who did I talk to
you
yes please let me
stay let me enjoy this as I am the
hero if if if I didn't already do it why
would toad give me the voucher
huh it's it's a reward right cuz I did
do it it
happened yeah I already know what this
room looks like so I'm not surprised
looks really cool though really nice
just a around please make yourself at
home
first use this ter cloth bathro bath the
Bing can I get
naked
[Music]
really it's it's too small for me great
it's toad size or
what
[Music]
man that's
useless you can use it he says but only
has the tiniest size available
ever am I not like really famous in this
world like they all know Mario so you
should have one prepared for me I know
he gets really red here that's
cute okay I will not get any room
service because I know that little [\h__\h]
wants a lot of money from
me how do I turn this off I want to
sleep what
[Music]
I want to
slam I have to get out of here
no well he wasn't
[Music]
rude
surprisingly G
no oh
a well I guess yeah he's not back to a
puppet yet
because we apparently didn't kill the
boss the world is not saved I saw a
bright light for the window during the
night I believe it came from Star Hill
why don't we go find out what might have
caused it Star
[Music]
Hill I said I don't want to play post
game why am I doing this
[Music]
uh I
believe
addiction hey I just want to know if
there's something important left to
[Music]
see what's up Star
Hill
it's not like
uh boss fights like you guys said I can
do in the post game right cuz I don't
care about
[Music]
that you Star
Hill oh you
know nothing seems to have changed here
let's keep looking further in you making
me turn on these stupid lamps on
again at least oh okay then then I don't
care then I do not
care all right that was fun
oh
yeah the video must have gotten it
gotten it uh oh no just
recently
no okay uh I guess we'll read the
chats not too long because uh we got
done early and not earlier than I
thought but I must make use of this to
cook but let's go to my
[Music]
room tomorrow by the way uh
no stream uh I make a a schedule
probably also
tomorrow I just reminded myself that I
have
something small to record before I go to
sleep and hopefully I don't
forget music music
music is kind of fitting I would say
[Music]
okay and thank you for accepting me even
during my I know who I am raiding after
this so stay cuz Ollie is in the middle
of a ollie Marathon I was um like she
asked you know for some participation
for something but the time was kind of
bad cuz it's like in the
nighttime um so I had to say
[Music]
no unfortunate
I won't be there but I'll support her in
different ways all right we finished
reading part one Super Mario RPG Super
Chat so now we're at part two part
[Music]
two well also I I really enjoyed the
game but I hope you guys enjoyed the
play through watching me play it did you
enjoy
it
part two part
[Music]
two she to hear what now is she
being emotional right
[Music]
now yes very much
so but you enjoyed it or she needs to
hear
it I did now I want to play it
nice go for it
we heard on the stream seven deep yeah I
know I just heard one one word but I
thought okay that's deep talk time right
now can't get to the m out of my
head brainwashing
complete
successful oh this one has a lot of
super chats huh okay all right here we
go um but wait let me eat one cookie one
cookie is the last cookie I have anyway
I didn't eat any cookie today so
far
yum so
[Music]
good have to buy more cookies
tomorrow
M no I will not put the cookie down
actually funny I was just looking at
your super chat in the
[Music]
list my
cookie yeah right I'm going to bake them
maybe I shouldn't bite
them but those are different cookies I'm
I need different cookies for certain
types of
moods
[Music]
I cookie
m
[Music]
m m
M yeah I saw the subway
cookies a 30
cm long Subway
cookies I've never seen such a long
cookie
before it's a cookie stick Cookie
Sandwich yeah I saw the advertisements
like on Twitter I
[Music]
I wonder if they have them here too I
never go to
Subway last time I've been to Subway was
ages ago I don't even remember when I
was I couldn't even tell you
roughly it's really
new doco air than thank you wow a that's
sweet thank
you thanks Jacob
47 J monkey will space waterful is thank
you
what
oh
what what does that mean you're lifting
[Music]
kilg oh yeah I think that's what that
means can you lift 250
kilogram that's like five
houses sheesh well I'm glad you
recovered isah and I wish you lot of
Health please stay
healthy Studio Rob F on the pinky t e
reminding you to think about if you want
to do
another the timing of me reading the
Super Chat is perfect cuz today was
supposed to be the Christmas re binding
stream
um but yeah I kind of cancel it
cuz to me it makes no sense to bind it
after the first of Advent cuz hey today
is the first of Advent congratulations
this is advent anniversary how could
they not debut the Advent
members on the first of
Advent did they not think what what are
they doing what are they doing
Mama
Mia but yeah uh what was I saying oh
yeah so like making it
afterwards and I I looked at stories and
and their uh like branches and all that
they didn't have the branches anymore
cuz I was too late I didn't want to go
to a forest and cut them off of the
trees
so we're making cookies instead and we
might even make it into a weekly thing m
M if the first one goes well let's
see besides narissa wanted to confess to
you
what she has something to confess to me
what dides she say that in her stream
what L this year I will start simple
with uh butter cookies and decorate them
with chocolate and sugar GL play and all
that but then I want to do I want to do
uh Linda
Alan one stream for lin Alan one stream
for some
chocolatey wait when I make L aan I
should also make
liner
tungen I don't know if it's easy to do
both of them in the same
stream we could
make ah s Sana I have to make
timana yeah then it's probably already
Christmas now maybe one more I could
make vanilla the vanilla kipel again
again I know we'll see we'll see but
those are some that I definitely want to
make a lip oh yeah I could make edible
lip C this time
because when I made the house the lip C
house that's not really something you
should
eat it's not not the good type of
Li I remember when I was uh a child like
I think at some point like
in elementary school or so for example
we would make our own lip cun and
decorate it our own for I think for the
uh Nicolas
TG gingerbread we made our own
gingerbread people decorated
them mhm
yeah that's wow that's such
a elementary school kind of thing to
do but yeah maybe if I have time I'll
also make gingerbread cookies or
something like that yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah we'll see we'll
see where was I oh yeah thank you Studio
Rob I hope you weren't looking forward
too much to that stream but uh I hope
cookies replace it uh well enough for
you
[Music]
of
for
ADV ho ho ho ho for fire Target
[Music]
Alice black
am a refile of cookies
oh
interesting and thank you Lucas and um
random collusion thanks for the red
super chat hi I'm happy you're enjoying
one of my favorite games from my
childhood well are you here random
collusion I finished it and I rated it
really well looking to re-experience the
memories myself so I'll catch up with
you in the vault oh then you're probably
not here are you unless you finished it
by now and you can watch my streams live
now are you round random
collusion go go go play the game faster
faster come on
I need you to react to what I say live
on
stream damn he's not here but I feel you
will uh be very delighted by how much I
enjoyed the game so uh you hopefully
also enjoy the game I feel like uh this
is a remake that is very faithful and
going to be enjoyed by all of the Super
Mario RPG fans around the world so I
wish a lots of fun with it too and hope
you're going to enjoy the vud when you
get some time thank you so
much go to
danard picture of a telephone indeed you
are I said that in 2020 that I was going
to swear less well the 2020 was my
beginning it only got worse from there
it only went
downhill Anthony weapons with pinky k I
love your ability to improvise lyrically
and lock in with a rhythm
really really you do oh this is when it
started the
CH this is where it
began did you still love it after I sang
it for 20 minutes
Anthony if yes then high
five I was brainwashing myself too but I
I I I could go on Chate in forever and
ever and ever and ever if I wanted to I
just ended it for you guys for your
guys' sake even after the stream I was
like walking around my apartment like
Ching on my own guys I really couldn't
get it out of my head I didn't even have
the melod playing I was just like doing
it
[Laughter]
[Music]
Acappella
yeah but it's fun it was fun F even on
my own it's just a nice melody to have
in my head it's not even like that
annoying you got the risler song in your
head oh my God
I I am glad I'm not deep into that
yet H kind okay D
comy why am I
getting Tex Ry made
rise of fre you got Mike thank you for
the pinky o we're guing our Scandinavian
trip we went there around the same time
you went to Japan nice how was it
probably cold as [\h__\h] is only the best
experience I've had seeing two Aurora
for nights in a
row uh seeing Aurora two for Nights two
nights in a row is something I'll never
forget I love Norway so much and Europe
in general I am really really glad to
hear that thank you so much Europe do be
beautiful I am proud to be European in
Europe very proud I don't think I've
ever seen a Aurora before though IRL so
hopefully I can see it too someday I'm
looking forward to that I want to do a
Scandinavian trip as well like you just
like you glad you enjoyed it I hope you
were able to rest properly too and reach
charge some energy yeah thank you so
much for your
support I'm glad it went
well
chicken for the pinky giving
future but that's a OG Melody oh I I
actually right now I can't recall the
other one and probably better that way I
love you w thank you I love you
too
Choate much love to you thank you I'm
I'm happy you enjoyed the
[Music]
Choate you should release a choa cover I
don't need to I really like the one that
cow carrat uploaded
so that was really good
you're welcome to visit our Frozen
hellscape don't call it that I mean I'll
probably yeah be freezing my ass off and
then and then my jeans will fit me again
but
uh so
beautiful right now I just want to stay
in the coffee warm apartment that I am
in
now but one day I will tackle the
Scandinavian
region with my
ass Moral Moral Dan spider Dan who Cru
Dan spanheim thank you for the red chat
sorry I haven't been active in chat but
I just got home from a trip and small
cat is being extremely needy small cat
also if we had a discussion about CS it
would technically technically be a more
M
what
M what what language is that a motor
chat the way you write it it sounds like
it's a different
language quite a stretch again spank
andhe thank you though I want to see
picture of small please send picture of
small thank you I am
awaiting on Twitter than
than greet your cats from me please
please please do it I need your cats to
be greeted by me we'll send okay I'm
excited certainly thanks for to pinky
it's me the jerk trying to make you
listen to met I want to tell you that
I'm not just uh making random
suggestions but try to consider what you
say you like since you saying baby metal
and Papa Roach and like the metal
remixes of your songs I thought you
would enjoy some types of metal it is a
more versatile genre than most think
heavy and death metal are just the most
wellknown if my recommendations bother
you just say so and I will find other
topics for super chats like Silly Pond
no no I'm no it's fine it's fine but I
mean I'm interested in your puns as well
maybe you can make
it I mean yeah I I I liked the the
Sparks remix I like baby metal but it's
not something that I would like in my
free time just say like oh I feel like
listening to that now let's listen to it
um but I do enjoy it when I listen to it
yeah I don't know
I it's fine I guess it's just not not my
genre of
choice I will not be turned into a metal
head no I am orange head I am made of
nuggets
and
uh what's that sauce called again that
you North Americans love so
much gravy gravy gravy gravy yeah gravy
gravy yeah sent me orange music n I'm
sorry Sirin I don't I want you guys to
you know I I want I want I don't want to
disappoint you guys with my tastes but
it is what it
is thank you for your support you're
welcome to recommend something again but
uh I don't know how far you'll get with
recommending metal to
me El Alita morally immoral than Bruce
jedy Lee
D true
Virgil Fox Dan Dan Bruce J Dan Nathan
cotton thanks for the
[Music]
pinky you can't disappoint us any
further since your cat oh my
[Music]
God Nathan says hello tal sorry I'm late
to the stream but I just finished all my
Christmas gift shopping so early wow so
many board games so many at least boxes
are easier to wrap than anything else
anything you want for
Christmas well currently I want uh a
running
machine but not that anybody's going to
give that to me I'm buying it
myself
um I thought about this recently in
another stream
but I feel like you could give me like
makeup stuff but you will have to kind
of know what what you're doing like
yeah maybe know what's the good stuff or
what I could make good use
of stuff like that yeah one thing I
really don't need is body lotion body
lotion like oh my God every everyone
gifts body lotion even even I'm guilty
sometimes and like in the I would
appreciate like clothes and accessories
but uh well that's kind of like hard to
choose for somebody else
[Music]
right small VR said yeah yep he had the
headset yep yep yep yep
definitely I don't know I mean this is
all uh kind of
um hypothetical anyway
so doesn't really matter to get give a
good answer I suppose uh but
uh a GameCube that would be really cool
to uh get an old GameCube that is still
uh usable
[Music]
mhm a gift card I wouldn't mind a gift
card yeah I want IKEA gift
card or Zara gift
card Gucci gift card
no chocolate would be nice too lots of
chocolate lots of Kinder chocolate a
fruit
basket I've never h received a fruit
basket before and honestly that would
[\h__\h]
[Music]
rock a coupon for doing doing like
construction work in my place like
putting up a shelf or something like
that so that I don't have to feel
bad uh a coupon for cable
management at my
place it's just stuff that I can ask you
to
do W I would I would appreciate that
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah if you're an
artist any fan art would make me happy
art of
me but don't forget my
feathers I I I always feel like so bad
when I see actually good usable fan art
of me uh but it's not it's missing my
feathers cuz then I really hesitate to
use
it and I don't want to like I said this
before but I don't want to go to the
replay and be like hey um this is
amazing and I would use this but you're
missing my feathers can you please add
them I don't want to do that you know I
feel
bad my feathers are not optional okay
and sometimes people draw me with just
completely orange hair they don't put in
any grad
gradation graduation
gradation which is also a
bit iffy
[Music]
uh I mean it doesn't even have to be
this color like cuz I have different
gradations in some outfits you you you
have freedom in the color I would say
but yeah I feel like that's like pretty
important cuz if it's just orange hair I
could be any character that could be
anyone you know if it's just plain
orange hair these colors and the
feathers those are like something that
really makes the WWA the WWA and makes
me recognizable so pretty
important to me but I'm not going to
like complain to an artist uh cuz not
it's not complaining but it seems like
complaining but you
[Music]
know sometimes I feel like maybe they
just forgot they they didn't do it on
purpose and other times they probably
wouldn't even be mad if I said something
um but maybe a little bit embarrassed
and I don't want to embarrass them
either you know so you know I'll just uh
unfortunately
M oh yeah I'll I'll just be Nami if I
just have orange hair I'm just
Nami it do be my distinguishing feature
so e if people forget it I still
sometimes use it but the low the chances
are much
lower and I I want them to have high
chances you know of me using their art
so
ideally uh you
know getting personal message from Tano
what an
honor uh I am yes I am Nami from One
Piece no
Nami she's so pretty the actress is so
pretty she's so cute I'm looking forward
to the next one Piece
season I've seen people remind the
artist when they post
whip oh that's good like reminding them
at the stage of the whip is still like
totally acceptable when when the art is
finished I also feel like
uh it's too
late and sometimes you know when there's
like official art uh for like projects
any company projects or so and they take
care of like uh organizing the art and
everything uh one thing I actually quite
often have to tell them is you you
forgot my feathers
uh but I've done it so much
so often that by now at least the
staff tells them so that I don't have to
tell
them my feathers are not optional you
forgot this
yeah yeah I mean it it's part
of Ip
basically it's like forgetting lapa's
horns although I feel like would be nice
to take off her horns cuz they take up
so much space and I feel like
they restrict her design a little bit
like if you want to make new designs new
new clothing designs but it's basically
it's it's in there it's in her head just
like my feathers are in my
head her massive
sleeves oh that's that's a well only the
default
outfit
don't saw them
off yeah removing horns is not allowed
anyway
there that's a
pretty strict thing I think for like new
outfit guidelines yeah and then the
thing is like for me I personally say
this this is like feathers belong to me
because for the casual outfit my my
first uh outfit after the default one
you know hook Papa left them there so
they were still there
but then came the Kimo where he changed
it into earrings and then I was like
hook hook
Papa I thought we hadn't I thought we
never talked about it but I just thought
this
was like a must have part of me but then
he changes it and I'm like well I guess
it's fine just once but uh I thought we
both
had an unspoken agreement that this is
like part of my
body but maybe he just wanted to make me
look fancy so I I said I said yeah it's
fine for this one time but every other
time I said feathers must be there then
for the fancy outfit they were like
changed visually quite a
bit but that's fine you know I like that
putting in some variety in
there nice I like that they look
different there CU it gives it a more
mature look as well they look quite
fancy
yeah yeah and a different color
too a fite out that's because well Mama
Looney drew that and
uh yeah that's fine it's just for music
video for something like that yeah I
guess I don't know I think it was
because it was a ponytail and I wasn't
sure if the feather is sticking out of
the ears and the ponytail would look
fine so sometimes I make exceptions but
yeah
ideally
yeah the next outfit is just feathers
and no
hair no please no not acceptable anyway
let's
continue Bruce D T off I a pinky sorry W
I wasn't really there during the last
streams kind of had a busy week I know
how that feels like don't worry I have a
lot of catching up to do anyway I'll
just enjoy the rest of the stream for
today no problem you don't have to
apologize for not being
around thank you for being here at all
you know that is
already like the the best
thing so don't worry about
it oh my you
star Creator
Brandon thanks for
[Music]
pink I see
thank
you H yeah that's right it was H
[Music]
anniversary ah nostalgic ziply thanks
for the red chat we have a bit of a cold
snap in Finland and attemps are hitting
minus
25 C
yes your blanket and fers have been
absolute life saviors especially since I
was too lazy to fix my drafty window in
the summer you should know better living
in Finland thanks for keeping me warm D
oh my God are you okay are you frozen
yet do you want to build a
snowman or what oh my God that's say
that's so [\h__\h] cold are you
okay do you have you have a a good
heating right
hopefully please please stay warm we
have very pleasant very pleasant minus
oh my
god well I guess that's kind of
normal please stay warm and cozy in the
blanket h do you want to be a
sow
sheesh my God you made me very scared of
going
to
[Music]
Scandinavia thank you
though don't freeze your ass
off I'll keep you
warm rub rub
rub Brandon
Michael
hello My Fair Lady o CH chel thank you
you're the
best looking for the toption quick
thinking personality test what is the
first thing that comes to mind when you
see the word
CH don't
addtion uh when's kobo's
birthday I don't know what her plans are
cuz I uh if she planned something I was
not invited yet
[Music]
what do you
mean for my
yeah well she's adopted
[Music]
so I know it's the same
guy December 12th oh well I wonder what
her plan
is maybe solo
stream don't know oh I don't know of
anything that she's
planning maybe she'll do it more
spontaneously or or is something without
me about her
mommy we'll see I'm sure she's got
something exciting prepared maybe
Brandon D thank you for the reminder uh
I will probably need one again maybe
tomorrow on Twitter guys maybe M eight
thanks for Pinky nail collab was great
hope you can do more with Iris next time
you go to Japan today was fun too though
you most likely have two more streams
left oh yeah yeah I did in the end I did
maybe you can fight a certain opal boss
I did feel bad attention thank
[Music]
you she doesn't want her mom at part no
she loves me I'm a cool mom she thinks
of me as a cool fun Mom I'm sure
but yeah I did I I did a lot of optional
things y I'm happy it was fun it was
worth it it was really worth it those
items are so worth
[Music]
it okay
uh there I'll read one
more uh the one from my thousandth
[Music]
video thanks for the membership
welcome so many members
today very much
appreciate
[Music]
uh uh
um this
one and I mocking you so
smug
[Music]
wait
I need to try
[Music]
something
B
the problem is that one's 3D and a
different hairstyle and all that so it
doesn't fit perfectly also cuz the head
would have been angled like upwards but
so I am mocking you this is the Super
Chat I am the the stream I will be or
the video I'll be reading off so I I
just put it on my head on my
face something wrong with my
face
something
wrong I have my face on my face is there
a
problem take for the for the looking for
the top looking for the
top bir
po ultim
MK you are sytax era D picture of a
telephone picture of a telephone Mar P
Maxell the first
[Music]
shyon
monke
golden iown thinking kiaha don't go I'm
sorry I only streamed love 99 times
instead of 100 promise that will do
better anyway congratulations on
Thousand videos you're the best yay
thousand videos
yeah that's a lot so many videos and
more to come I'm
already zooming past that
number yeah it could be a face mask
merch but I don't really know if I want
to do a face mask merch cuz I don't
really I don't use ever face I don't
ever I don't ever use face masks so I
don't really feel like it would
be a really
useful item I mean it could be really
cute design just to have as a merch it
would be cute but I want to make sure
that my merch is useful
[Music]
so it would be cute yeah yeah I come
back and see this what it's my face are
you what what's wrong with my face
[Music]
wait my
[Laughter]
eyebrows
wait please I don't know what is this
what is this face with these eyebrows
what does this
mean this is so good I'll keep these
eyebrows is an extra
smoke I I don't know it's more like pity
or
yeah you
suck you suck
you little [\h__\h] you'll never reach my
level of
amazingness get on my level oh right you
can't
[Music]
ha oh my God anyway thank you unknown
thank you so much I I would never even
like think
of asking for of more from you you
always do more more than enough temp
talkity chat Dar Bobcat
Mr Papa I want the 20 watt cable than
Alita thank you for the comment on
thousands for the video thank you you're
even using the same writing as me wow
it's becoming a trend huh thank you so
much for watching them all
right
right everybody
right right right Alita are you
here you here
absolutely
okay I mean that's that's that sounds
pretty
confident you got a kiss for that r s
thank shagy Channel d m than La thank
you for the red woohoo wo
oh
sure W thousand for video and I'm going
to witness it in
life
I am not
sorry no I am a little bit sorry that it
was what it
was what I just wake up to good
morning
[Music]
anyway thank you L I'm glad you were
there I hope I hope I I I did not
disappoint I mean I probably did but
whatever I'm smug about it totally I am
confident about it uhhuh
you look pretty with that face thank
[Music]
you space
wonderful ziply D
action what that's oh God are you
okay you didn't get too much in your eye
but Jones than for Pinky congrats on
your thousand video K also come here let
me hug you with my feathery Wings anger
anger anger h uhuh what is this are you
trying to approach
me I will not be disciplined you good
now okay good I'm glad m m be
[Music]
careful Dominic D Sky clone D Salon D is
Sonic thanks for the
red congratulations on your thousand
thousand
video K I'll be going back to nap now
see you next stream totally war video
obviously obviously right
mhm thank you I agree very
much even the Sun that the chief agrees
that it was worth it so I believe it
was
[\h__\h] Bruno thanks for the pinky thank
you this changed my life
I I'm
glad
good I'm
sorry thank you thank
you
Cru will ad Z RIS the shortest
giant thank you Dex Jaden D I am
delicious
D Mar pipp d g d now thanks for py did
you tell the rest of you were going to
do this or was there some Panic no
because I think everybody was sleeping
anyway Nissa woke up early like she's
the only one who's really awake at that
time I think but I want to know her
reactions since death nobody nobody
reacted congratulations on Thousand
videos K here 200,000 more honestly
nobody reacted I was wondering after
seeing your guys's reaction and seeing
some people freaking out I thought maybe
staff or like Jenna at least after she
wakes up maybe they'll come up to me and
be like w don't do this again
no the only one who spoke to me was
nura she's the only one who cares about
my
[Music]
demise no no no I don't think it's like
they they were like uh whatever about it
no they were just not available like it
was it
was night like night time for yeah
middle of the night for Japan and it was
a early ass morning for na right
so yeah not early at morning maybe more
like early noon was
it yeah but
uh nobody really
[Music]
yeah Japanese managers sleep
sometimes at least the ones who maybe
would have noticed like jenma she was
asleep maybe some others were awake but
uh they don't really take a look at what
I do I think so they got plenty of other
[\h__\h] to
do so all is good I did not get in
trouble Sean Ian than you cus be
D Brandon Dan and S Kuro s Kur D thank
you that was of course on purpose the
countdown I
feel especially smug
about oh that will definitely be a a big
time frame of no trolling from me if I
ever want to be taken seriously again I
am aware of
that but yeah um that is where I will
leave the Super Chat rating for today
mhm for next week I I'm hoping that I
can take some time to uh finish signing
the
Polaroids and uh hopefully we can finish
GTA did I put that in my calendar
already I wonder um I'll probably make
the schedule tomorrow I'll just uh go
cook some food and record the last
little thing that I have left over for
work and yeah and what's your TIY a
what's your TIY a oo o I wanted to do a
k also there's a convention appearance
next week end with uh cie I need to hit
her up and ask her what are we going to
do
also oh yeah sleep talking I mean it's
obviously late already so I don't even
care when it comes out um it's already
past the November so it really doesn't
matter anymore so I'm not stressed out
about it uh there was a certain time
frame that I wanted to keep it in
but no so now it doesn't matter but it's
probably going to be out next week
probably sleep talking
[Music]
yeah Gta Live trailer yeah that's right
I scheduled it for a specific day in
order to react to the GTA trailer
[Music]
right wasn't that the
thing
let me check when did I schedule it
[Music]
for ah Sunday is it on Sunday does this
does the trailer no it's on Tuesday oh
oh well um I wanted to do GTA on Sunday
because it's a long stream
probably but
uh I'll probably do a different stream
at that time so will I will
I fifth is the day you know Tuesday H GJ
trailer we'll see I mean if it somehow
fits into my planning I'll do a live
react if not then not it was 300 p.m. or
something was it feel like you guys told
me it was 3 oh yeah okay it was indeed
okay we'll see what
happens
[Music]
okay
oh o I just noticed something
Saturday I have
like the panel is at 900 p.m. my time
the meet and greet is at 700 p.m. my
time so if I wanted to do a Koka it
would be after the panel at like 10:30
or something it's pretty late for
me I could still do it
but maybe before is better that's so
early
too I have some thinking to
do swap GTA and no I can't because I
need like the day open for
GTA and Saturday is not open Saturday
has all the anime front hear
things oh well oh well whatever you guys
don't have to concern yourself with such
[Music]
things it's not something a one brain
cell chicken should concern concern
itself with yeah yeah and any casman say
I'll Fe Us
in
[Music]
bye-bye byebye
I guess that's
it
uh put your foolish Ambitions to rest my
children good
good say goodbye to this face as you
will never see it
[Music]
again we
me to
say ah we're going to raid Ollie so stay
let's raid oh
[Music]
we let's give her some
support
only
only is it going to show
up yes
[Music]
okay