K first
album point of
view
pineapple 1 2 1 2 3 it tastes so so so
sweet when you the r kiss me I'm taking
up perfect
picture you're stck to me like a
stick love
[Music]
Rush never let
go you're in my heart you always St
right here won't
F the great Wanderer the
great I I'm walking by the FL before my
eyesone Sil still I'm reaching out to
you con sacrifice
life
retrospective and PR and calls me to
truth and every part of my being that's
the best feeling don't tell me what I li
to
you sleep
[Music]
talkinging breath you got meing oh baby
don't you know got me I'm HED I I'm
breathing you and I just can't forget
but you got me stressed I'm just rting
oh baby that's what you do
[Music]
will heart
Challenger
[Music]
Sparks your head is only what make it
you're going to be
okay so go ahead and do it do it you
want let's get to it everybody's going
to know your
name
favor
[Music]
night alive move my through something
new I don't need no drinks tonight give
me do
you all the same if you know play that
game theide know I can fight the feeling
and I want love hate all the same if you
know play that game maybe you decide if
you sh
[Music]
it Tak first
album point of
view
pineapple
it's your
[Music]
baby stream point of
view
I saw from
R the
pinky I'm so
happy you enjoy Austrian desserts after
all yay let's go let's
[Music]
go
uh
wait wait wait wait um I'm going to
write down because I forgot to bring my
phone over here I'm going to write down
some tangent topics I want to talk about
but wait where's chat I see you chat
don't worry it's just
um a matter of OBS
okay hello k
[Music]
okay I was felt like I wrote it down
um
uh uhhuh
uh ah
mhm
uh
[Music]
ah
um feel like I'm forgetting
something
[Music]
a nah you know what I'll bring my phone
I wrote something
down hey what's
[Music]
up
yummy yummy yum yum
yum
ah
[Music]
ah M
ah oh so many tangents
okay oh oh 5 DMS oh from Kori oh 5 DMS
from
korei oh what oh my
God
oh my
God what is what is this oh my
God h no it's something yeah uh
surprising no not one piece
related uh she sent me some graphic that
is very
graphic what is
this
okay
okay uh b b you are now my property
because I'm going to be playing bers
gate and you will be watching me yes
that is how things are that's how the
world goes
around um
yeah
gate yeah guess you have no choice no no
let me do I do I Play Baller skate in
full screen don't
remember where is it
there oh it got another update I heard
that carlac story got an update like
really quickly because some people were
complaining about its like H death lack
of death
thereof uh but I think like it's it's
not something we uh came across yet it's
like something about the end yeah and
and they like really quickly added some
more dialogue they did that in like what
two days or so um yeah record wrote a
new script wrote a new dialogue recorded
the voice acting recorded the motion B
blah blue and implemented it immediately
in between last update and this update
Isn't that
cool it didn't have an ending what well
now it definitely does
which is good because you know I I want
to get deeper and deeper into kak's
heart
and you
know you
know K
car
same me me me me me oh it's full screen
it do be full screen
okay
I put this here
be
so things have changed a little bit I
was going to stream this on Sunday but
now it is Friday one might think we
jumped over a few days but
no I had some scheduling issue but the
things that I needed have arrived
today um so all should be
well uh and then on the weekend I will
not be streaming yes I'll be filming
something
interesting
yes
uh I I'm going to leave really early
tomorrow and come back really late I
think on it depends it depends but yeah
Sunday is kind of like unclear when I'll
get back
home
what
oo oh nice cold water I put ice cubes in
my water now it's really
cold oh no I'm so sorry if you had your
days off and you wanted to watch
something from me but
unfortunately uh I'll be prepping
something you you can watch Lena's
birthday though uh I recommend Lena's
birthday yes there may or may not be an
appearance of me um
yeah is the weather finally getting
cooler I don't I don't I think it was
cooler for like a week
maybe uh it's at least not as hot as it
was at its peak now now it's it's it's
hot so I I went swimming
I actually did go man I wow I was
already very productive because I have
no time to waste at the
moment I went swimming and I went out to
buy something for
tomorrow oh no no swimsuit not found
yet I have to actually make a call and I
forgot about that I forgot about
that can I make a quick
call can I make a quick call it's
already like a week ago since I lost her
swimsuit I already called them before
and then they were like uh sorry can you
call tomorrow I'm like
[Music]
okay can I just really quickly okay
thank you I love you
guys
Goins AR smart enough to poison their
blade
wanted the
easy we're exposed
now
sure
great
uh the corn has
spoken my my my favorite my favorite
swimsuit is
gone it's just yeah as as the lady on
the phone said sorry I'm so sorry in in
it may have maybe uh grown its own legs
implying that it ran away on its
own yeah uh she looked through all her
boxes but there were no swimsuits at all
only
bathing uh swim swim shorts bab short
yeah
shorts I have to buy a new
one uh goodbye corn goodbye maybe I
leave it here no
no so sad I mean I have plenty of
swimsuits but I like this one because I
told you before but because I don't have
to
show my much of my body in it and only
it like the only thing you see is my
arms and my legs the back is completely
closed the front is completely closed
the neck is completely closed it doesn't
it doesn't uh cover the fighs some of
you guys thought I was wearing like one
that also covers the fighs no no no no
not one of those but it it covers like
uh yeah the everything except the
limbs and my
head
mhm
ah yeah it embraced me more like anyone
else ever did before and uh gave me this
sense of security like no one ever else
could give it to
[Laughter]
me sorry for your loss thank you I don't
know how to feel after this
loss
Muki byebye Muki give it up for the Muki
which I only had for
maybe three three months but it was very
loyal and protective to me of
me and I treasured it I wor it many
times in this short amount of time and I
will never forget about
it
man guess I'm talking about swimsuit
that I really
liked that I but the the lady on the
phone even said that they clean cuz I
left it in the shower room and they
clean it every day so and they they you
know they would have obviously found it
so does that imply somebody took my
swimsuit and it's a it's a lady's only
shower
room somebody thought that was their
swi what what
maybe I
guess well it probably won't suit
whoever took it because it's kind of a
small
size
oh a
thief oh wait I can open this one I'm
allowed to open this one
e this one I can't but this one I can
open oh there nothing inside what I do
salt of course I want to bring her salt
is it possible for me to bring her
salt she really wants the
salt is that possible at all I
wonder so small yeah honestly it was
kind of tight for me too so I was
wondering maybe I should get another
one ah fun for the swimsuit thank you
actually I I I don't need a fun for the
swimsuit it's okay uh but I'll I'll use
the fund for going to Japan soon I
checked prices and it was a bit
surprisingly expensive but that's the
reality um no swimsuit Well for now I'll
use my other swimsuits I
guess perfect time to get a new size I
guess
yeah the one that JMA got me is also way
too tight it's so hard to get into it
once I'm in it kind of fits yeah but
it's so difficult to get into
it Airlines have been price ging oh is
that
so you mean they're racking up the
prices it it feels kind of weirdly
expensive
yeah oh
well H forgot about the one Gemma got me
yeah yeah Gemma got me a swim
before it's so funny to
me what's erratic about that horny
bunk
what hope you have a lovely day thank
you we should get started uh plans for
today yeah last time last time I wanted
to go to the tea house so we went that
way uh the blighted village however had
so much more to show me than I expected
so yeah we'll we'll teleport there I
guess and then we'll go that
way well hopefully hopefully this time
we'll reach the tea house and if the tea
house is anything like the bled Village
and I then I assume that that will be
all that we're doing today that area
is a game of many distractions yeah how
much tea will we be having well a proper
tea ceremony takes its sweet time you
know you know got to do it
properly there's is there there's no
respawn of enemies in this game
right haven't seen that game in years
game bers gate well yeah new new new
bers gate free yeah first one in a long
time no missing poster no respa right
cursed let me let me read this missing
poster who's missing children Maggie
teren Marcus Terren Maan dech relle Kirk
can I find
them did they eat did you guys eat those
children
they are eating
something uh oh they're eating tee
flings so if those names are for
teelings I think they're eating teelings
that's kind of up but okay
books what what game was she talking
about though a
well apart from an overgrowth of moss
the well looks unremarkable no it looks
beautiful oh what we can throw coin and
or appear
why am I so excited what do we do what
do we do do I get a wish come true uh oh
well oh well um let's peer into it what
if there's like a monster down
there I'm so
excited
ah so much for the tea wait maybe this
is our path to below at the bottom
something where I already was in the
dappled
light something gleams uhuh what could
that be climb down the yeah okay that's
probably just another way to get down
where I already uh checked out before
it's a SP area what happens if I throw a
CO coin disappears into the darkness
Landing with a soft
clink okay we're not we're not climbing
down cuz I think I know where that leads
ah sorry need something no no but that's
such a sweet way of asking me I love
you uh so you guys didn't you tell me I
can talk to this oh yeah I don't have to
fight them
huh excuse
me oh oh my God they're really eating
the sings
chicken no
chicken tlock
face gentle
contain yourselves this quarrel SS are
faced
besides
tast and what surprise is this another
teethling brothers look here I avoid yet
another tling prize no no no fortune
favors our bellies no no no that's not
what I'm here for
stranger be you friend or food oh the
Mark is her measure shows the brand of
the absolute I think I can do that would
that make me your friend do you want one
of the uh uh yes
um I guess I'll go with this yeah I get
all my bonuses from it too
yeah I'll do you one better I'm one of
the Absolut chosen disciplin the
disciples
sorry yeah I'm just that special
so so respect me and stop eating those
children
indeed how regrettable that your meat
must go
unsaved food food
food food friend yes I guess so although
I would like to kill you ideally uh but
uh we just started and we have places to
go so
um I noticed you don't bear a brand of
your own seen a few
OG yes I remember seeing
something H you're quite the articulate
ogre yeah let's listen am I not
astonishing a robust diet makes for a
shrewd mind you're saying food the right
food makes you smart a a gorant oh and
you a
delicacy were I so L that almost sounds
like a flirt to
me I've seen a few others of sense of
blood and gold to all lands fertile
friend and this land proves
particularly fruitful yeah but can you
stop eating those kids what the of
no use for the absolute or any God I
follow two masters only
gluttony and greed two of the sins the
Goblins understand my
appetites they saake my Hunger for gold
gobl and the rest save my Hunger for
meat boss Goblin give gold we check BR
good
deala
talk bnk
a calm down love each
other what an
interesting dialogue option forget
goblins you should be fighting for
me I am by all accounts a student of
higher Commerce and
extortion make me an offer tempt
me what did he help me
fight I give you 500 gold if I can call
you into battle th000 gold after you
fight for me I'll pay you in the flesh
of the Fallen you'll have your
fill yeah I
mean then I don't have to pay him
anything thousand sounds like a lot of
money to me and this way he can just eat
the corpses right easy easy easy I don't
need the
corpses I need a
20 h
lucky it's my lucky day
baby a brilliant night a brilliant I a
bone to my aching belly I'm a genius
have a deal my tasty kble I'm a k don't
don't nipple me take my bone horn one
blow and the ground will family
name use it when the need arises and
never moment before okay OK kill
everyone around then OK eats them how
does this work and E this is like a SP
ATT everyone around
mhm interesting thank you we will keep
close when you are ready sound the
home H it's a summon where is the
summon oh whoa whoa there they go they
made the this place free we can talk to
this dead seeing and that's curious
that's curious why is it cracked support
oh is it going to fall there's another
one braa Bre braa Bre was not one of the
Lost Ones uh and they just
poofed it's going to fall
when or I guess I could like hit it and
then it
falls hey wait I want to can I don't
don't don't smash me I want no no
no no no no what what the that is a lot
of possible
dialogues wait wait wait
wait oh a book fabl of f one the dim
with the drw oh that sounds lovely that
sounds absolutely delightful
all right let's go reading time long ago
in the city of menzo Baran Zan a Dro
wizard called zad studied magic in the
academy academy of
sorcerer each 10 day the arch Mage would
ask zad to demonstrate his new found
skills and each 10 day zad would fail
sorcerer educates only the brightest of
pupils warned the arch mage your
scholarship must improve or you will be
expelled that very night had slipped out
of meno Baran to seek the hidden city of
mine flayers orindo the library there
boasted the most complete body of
knowledge in the whole of the underd
dark and learn about all that is and
Ever Was vode s the arch Mage will have
no choice but to keep me yet the longer
that searched for the orend though the
more lost he became his body weak and
his stomach empty the drove fell to the
ground and reality faded zoke within a
vast circular Hall lined with tombs and
tablets until knowledge etched upon them
or and all I made it I will know
everything he
exclaimed a white smile acrossed zad's
face he barely noticed a tadpole
wriggling just above his left eye yes
said a voice in zad's head
everything
ah wait so did
he just get a mind flare in the in the
process of
this
uh let's
talk
ooh was it worth it probably not the T
fling's corpse stirs with the
spell
um why why you not tell me you're
name what brought you to the Village Str
Warriors
gold skin I can Rec Sil
blades
okay where' you see those Warriors
mountains Road are we going there
gate oh I got a Quest from this I think
something updated up
there where you
from
zor
friend okay why friend
what true sight no coin what's that mean
she got no money but what's the true
side part mean oh good
or blood I'm so sorry
man that's really
unfortunate well rest in
peace so you didn't have anything huh oh
well well well well I will take those
things thank
you
f see I'm still I I need to move on I
need to get
going survival something over there s
Survival trck let's
go yes this is what you need a shovel
for all right ooh 1006 gold and aat a a
stuffed bear and a milk can wa milk
is is that not uh cam supplies I take
only these things
and shovel my best
friend wait level up wait when did we
have a level up what the
H when did that
happen yes finally finally leveling is
so slow uh okay can trips what why is
this empty did I never choose one
before um they don't use spell slots and
can be cast at well blade Ward take only
half the damage from bludgeoning
piercing and slashing attacks bone
chill I'm picking a new one oh okay
prevent the target from healing until
your next turn an undead Target receives
disadvantage on attack RS
friends gain advantage on Charisma
checks against a hostile a non-hostile
creature Mage hands create a spectral
hand that can manipulate and interact
with objects
H yeah you guys think friends is good
poison spray project a puff of noxious
gas true strike advantage on your next
attack
roll
[Music]
oh let's you roll twice on pers
persuation and stuff good for
conversations you get two dice for
persuation and
[Music]
deception
wow so many fans of that
[Music]
one okay I'll Trust you guys I
guess uh learn spells okay new
spell blindness cloud of
daggers
um crown of Madness ooh conceal Madness
in a humanoid
enemy all you need is ELD blast we
already have ELD blast right or do I
have to choose it again what what what
what
what invisibility wow so
good Madness is a good charme spell d is
pretty good scorching very good uh hold
is very strong but will only work on
human I yeah I yeah yeah yeah yeah saw
in action being really good cloud of
daggers I also think is pretty good
especially cuz it's like
AOE more or less small
AOE we can oh this reminds me of a
different game where I always wanted to
weaken people before attacking
them and it's stayful reduce a
creature's peripheral vision and make it
look at you
oh free illusionary duplicates of
yourself that distract attackers
oh that's also kind of
cool how much HP do they have like
one command a creature to flee with
closer freeze drop to the ground or drop
its
weapon oh if I could tell someone to
flee that would be quite
powerful
gain Dash immedately and as a bonus
action on each of your turns
until and as a bonus action on each of
your
turns each flammable Target is hit with
three to 18 fire damage
each what what do you mean every like if
there's five enemies surrounding me and
they're all flammable I can attack all
of
them it's meing not very
good oh it's a short
range arms of Hadar prevents targets
from using
reactions a and some damage okay shatter
damages all nearby creatures and objects
creatures made of inorganic material
such as Stone have disadvantage on their
saving
throw sounds
interesting a dark shroud that heavily
obscures and blinds creatures within
creatures can now make range attacks
into or out of
it well what about me I can still shoot
in there right right right
right Shadow is quite nice Shadows an AE
M the best AE
oh oh I can't okay yeah I thought this
looks uh this sounds
interesting sounds fun should we go for
it all nearby creatures and op but but
what about what about Friendly Fire does
it do Friendly
Fire yes oh oh oh
oh
oh well I don't know how how big that
area is usually I'm like unfortunately
really close to everybody I'll do cloud
of
daggers cuz I know it feet choose a feet
oh no yeah I think last time you guys
told me what to choose was that the was
that with my
Ranger what do I there's too many
guys ability score
score ability you increase on one
ability by two or two abilities by one
oh okay thank you
[Music]
Santiago okay
let's
go I just did what was written in the
comments wait we got to do more Shadow
heart
next cleric level
four new C
trip uh for J blade W have damage
produce flame well no these don't seem
so special first
one first
one advantage on intimidation and
performance checks H
okay and should we also give her ability
[Music]
improvent
forecaster oh oh oh ooh and advantage on
saving froze or maintain concentration
on a spell a two you can also use a
reaction to cast shocking grasp at a
Target moving out of me oh cool cool
cool cool
okay mhm sure why
not and then
aarion LEL
up oh he only gets the feet the new feet
is there something for
him musical
instrument
um sniper
NOA hello
[Music]
noisa Sharpshooter so the one I got for
myself
before Oh
[Music]
H your ranged weapon attacks do not
receive penalties from High Ground
rules see this sentence I don't
understand because when I'm on High
Ground I or is it meant
like you if it makes no difference like
if you're even on Lower ground you still
get The High Ground damage or so is that
what that
means is is also here let's
go he's not a cowboy but he's so
[Music]
good when you are on low ground you get
a normal chance to hit
mhm so what it basically means is that I
don't get penalties from being not on
High
Ground oh it's for when they are on High
Ground you just don't all disadvantage
when the target is on high ground oh
okay oh cool well that's
good Y and last but not least
Carla H she's she's getting a feet as
well more feet please please don't
please ignore her outfit it's not
something I want her to wear but it's
good for her right
now uh great weapon master
when you learn a critical hit or kill a
target with a melee weapon attack you
can make another melee weapon attack as
a bonus action let's go let's go let's
go attacks with heavy melee weapons you
are proficient with can deal an
additional 10 damage at the cost of U
minus five attack roll
penalty okay that didn't really enter my
brain but I'll trust you I don't know
what that meant but I'll Trust you okay
where uh where are we
okay we are going in the right direction
but if I go over here I don't think
where does that lead nowhere but there
must be a reason why we can go
here there's a backpack and Vol guy to B
the
skate a poorly drawn map of a city is
captured in flamboyan script what
follows is the most thorough and
accurate account of the city and people
of balers gate thear sorted Gem of the
sword coast and another note in Crimson
ink follows this volume is startingly
accurate starting startlingly
startlingly safe for the nonsense about
the Black Dragon Gate it is not alive no
matter how many vagrant haags claim
otherwise commission someone else to
draw the
map
okay we got a potion on some
garlic okay that's it that's it that's
it and a nice view is is what we're
getting I
guess I know I know oh more more more
book more book no not the
Builder here the
book oh there's there's the A A is for a
wait didn't I have
a didn't I have that book before or like
a previous one or a later
one lra Lady of deception the goddess
who wears many masks invoke her name
avoid perception she hides you lies and
secret tasks for Joy To lra You must
call and worship her through selt dance
so find her presence in Fest Halls do
not give idleness a
chance is this stuff that I can do like
if I go to a certain Fest Hall and I
dance in there does it make me summon
lra or what Lara's pleasure is your pain
wait
latar is that the guy narissa talked to
your scars are an offering scorge or
candle Whip or cane can you devotion
that sounds
like that sounds ah then the others must
exist too he's
real and the others must be real
too yeah the torture guy
I just even though I didn't read it out
loud I already saw the rest and I
thought that sounds like the guy that
she talked to oh was he's a clerical FL
well then you know these others must
also be possible at some point
interesting what is this oh this is too
much I'll read that in my private
time wait there's another book no where
uh the approachable East
why am I such a book
nerd what is this about what the land is
cor Meir certainly the geography is
dramatic edged by mountains and sea
filled with forests and swamps but why
well on these when the Great Walls of
Suz Loom ahead one sees the city's walls
as one approaches but there is no
understanding them from a distance it's
only as one gets close and they Loom
higher and higher and higher that one
appreciates the Majesty of Suz I passed
through gates to sze of cast to enter
This Magnificent City the streets are
patrolled by Elite armored Knights known
as purple dragons so
senen senty and frequented by Nobles in
the most elegant elegant Fashions its
Port is filled with ships from across
the sea of fallen stars carrying goods
from lands I only knew from Legends the
docks overflow with fruit spices silks
and animal pelts you will not see a fin
a market if you have the golden Lions to
spend also the harming of cats is
strictly forbidden a forly civilized
land I agree with this
sentiment this is my kind of land um so
maybe we got to go down here or down
there
oh could this be one of the be something
in this I don't want to I don't want to
activate these goblins do you think
they'll fight
me oh there's a there's quite a few
actually well you know if it happens it
happens shall we jump oh it gives me
prone though let's walk
around I can try to talk to them
okay oh opened that chest who opened
this chest you guys you must have done
it you opened the chest I did not give
you permission
you sniffing where you ain't ought to be
friend might have to take that
nose are you sure you want to threaten
me as the symbol glows power courses
through you authority
authority that is
me
um
uh or you could let me pass and live to
see the
Nightfall
friends so which one is better now
guidance or
friends oh
easy
wow fair enough both oh oh can do fair
enough that's it that's all you say
okay all
right you're not fooling anyone no I
apparently fooled you
so should I you know you know how much I
would love to uh look at every corner
here but we got to get going we got to
get going hi guys yeah talk to you go on
more of us
inside okay but I'm going
outside Moon Haven Moon Haven I see more
than one sign though what do the other
signs say if one says Moon Haven what
does the rest say what does the rest
say okay we are going this
way yes it's so confusing though the
directions are so confusing to
me Birds you know uh oh I I found that
looks like a trap I found
um another the algorithm found something
for me let's say it like
that the algorithm is
currently um recommending me lots of
woodpeckers attacking security cameras
videos it's a thing me oh
hello just an ins I'm sure you'll
survive oh wow lots of meat o and the
Beres give me an you guys must have seen
it before right it's all specific yeah
but I'm getting I watched one video and
now now YouTube thinks that I want to
watch five to 10 videos of woodpeckers
destroying or attacking
uh security cameras per
day yeah there's a lot
apparently
oh Joel deir and Auntie ATO wait this
looks nice over there she get to see you
we know she did you know absolutely
nothing you e just what are they going
on
about let's talk to them make some new
friends Lads For the Love of All That is
Holy I've never clapped eyes on your
poor sister drop the ACT hag you was the
last to see he's calling her hag in the
sense of her being old
please thank goodness you're here
sweetie I I don't know what's come over
these boys wait Auntie actually it
sounds familiar we won't ask
again
H and also possibly a witch oh oh so it
is in the sense of being okay I just
assumed cuz she was old
too
um do I know her cuz the name is somehow
familiar to
me
uh how about you all just calm down
what's going on here careful I do don't
trust the word out of her mouth our
sister
went a seen her since hand over har I
don't know their sister I will gladly
help you all look for her though
enough where is
she e what did you do to your sister nah
I won't let you hurt Auntie eel we're
about to drink
careful she's with the H am there gaping
get
her well okay uh four versus to that's
[Music]
easy
not enough Movement we can go here
quickly hi new
approach and we have a perfect advantage
against him let's go deir you must
die unfortunate really unfortunate you
asked for it
violence I can use non-lethal damage
well well um well well well well well
well well well let's C with fire baby
well but we're not doing that so she's
pretty far can she
reach she can shoot 80% is actually not
so bad and
no yeah yeah why not
whatever it's not going to take so
long don't care I don't care where're
end in this immediately in this
turn trust
me shadow
hard can you get your together
please where do I go from
here
Mal
Miss uh where's my ELD blast here
Elber Blast Your Face
Off oh my stars I I didn't mean for this
to
happen what
happened those poor boys were looking
for their little sister Marina the girl
who's staying with me D why did you stay
like that my fault but I made a promise
stay with me Marina begged me not to
breathe the word if they came looking
for and my word is my I had chicken
nuggets before the stream by the way
poor thing will be distroyed very yummy
you can't let her know it should break
her poor harsh I best get going but
please stop by my house I'd like to
thank you
proper okay see then oh There She Goes
everybody's teleporting
now 16
wow
I'm I'm um ooh I'm sad I had to kill
them let's read this will I regret that
I killed
them you're Jolan deir don't get mad I
mean it I'm only leaving this not so you
don't sh
estaran so you don't panic and do sh do
something stupid I'm going to the hack I
owe it to Connor to make things right
you know he'd do the same for me I'll be
back soon so not a word to Mom did I
tell Marina's
brother
oh let's not tell her keep
going no I mean I obviously understand
that's why I just asked you that
question to confirm my
assumption
oh potato carrot carrot
carrot
M we we we we'll be fine I don't know
why I would want it a chill runs up to
be friends with that child anyway you
feel like you're being watched
uh what is
it he's watching me a bir may
be show
yourself oh
wow
wow you BL and the Wilderness
changes the swamp stinking and Insidious
assaults your
senses
stinky so that's it okay oh K is
inspired by
this why do I hear like monkeys and
Barbed B Rush
Barbed open up
uh shk Land wait is this the tea house
no I'm kind of off path will I
reach it if I go this
way a loving
note um
a what the
what the ah what the what
was that we're
bleeding what the get your
together
W the swamp hates
me what
happened why does this stank hurt me so
much get out of my swim okay okay
[Music]
okay wait but I have to probably go
through let me read this a trap time to
dance time to dance all right at least
you saw a trap okay uh the
note take a bav lovelies and have a
bite that sounds like the Apple that I
just picked up is like
poisonous are you guys
okay Spike arm this arm Spike trap this
arm um careful how many of those are
here I mean that should work
out a
lot
[Music]
shees
I would save around here okay oh what
was that what was
that I think I just had some audio
glitch and now I don't know where the
Trap is
anymore H
weird shouldn't I still be seeing the
the Trap even when it's
disarmed it's
gone
ar oh there's someone
there I can talk to
them hello hello oh I one
here what is
this where am I oh more apples
[Music]
M oh why is there so many baskets so
many baskets here with all with
apples what is it me
mean what does it
mean
w I'll just help
myself that's please
do ooh Wine Cherry and
tonic
oh
interesting why is it so foggy here
we're right at at the beach now though
that's
nice what survival fails ah okay
nice yeah no
pineapples would be better then oh dig
for victory I got an achievement for
digging got to dig more I dig
digging okay hello uh Red Cap blood
stage oh I got a
waypoint
oh Riverside Tea
House it succeeded a saving throw
against
rotting
n rotting keep it quick can you come
here I want to talk to you or you I
don't care oh I don't want to I don't
want to why are we
rotting what's going on oh
you diminutive creature sporting a red
hat glares at you you recognize the Red
Cap a fay creature known for its blood
lust Red Cap sounds like a poisonous
mushroom he's a sheep is the creature
pretending to be a sheep yeah that's
what I
thought take a deep breath and
say
but I wanted to
hear oh my God
Carla flesh Rod flesh is the king oh
man should I get out of
here at least things have stayed
interesting
indeed it is this whole place making me
rot
gandell don't waste a step hello gandel
who are you you look
interesting
ah stranger forgive the aroma you catch
a waft of something foul metallic and
sickly sweet what a weird combination
powdered iron Vine iron an old Hunter's
trick most monsters will think twice
before making a meal of me you're a
monster hunter I'm surprised I thought
old G were vagrant Cutthroats oh
uh uh wait the
elf who's the elf here him he's an elf
He looks like a human to
me
uh am I talking to aarion or to the
guy aan okay so this would be towards
aarion
right uh that's that's that's
interesting Darion you little I
knew you were a jackass but a racist
just heard rumors of my people that we
steal chickens curse your crops seduce
your
daughters I wish I had half the power
settled folk think my people
possess alas I am a simple Wanderer oh
unlike me who is the great Wanderer and
Monster Hunter but I'm no witch doctor
or
Cutthroat if I were a cut froat I
wouldn't admit it
either yeah but he seems fine what I
just I mean what moners are you hunting
something terrifying no doubt Dragon
psyclops Cobalt nothing so dramatic I'm
hunting for a vampire spawn oh his name
is a star I fear he's gone to ground I
hope the hag of these L him out if I can
afford her blood price
interesting
well should i r him
out when you find the sister and you'll
kill him let's ask this
first only a spawn what does that mean
not like it's a real what does that mean
only a
spawn I only know the word spawned in
regards to some mob spawning or
something
a low rank
uhhuh well what will you do oh my orders
are to capture him from who for whom and
bring him where exactly Boulder's Gate
my people wait for me there well that
would be an easy shortcut to get there
maybe I want to say
this a vamp vampire servant oh wow why
you guys all know this
save first can I save during a
conversation ah I have like sore muscles
on my lower
Legos probably from the from the
adventure I had the other
day
Okay I feel like even if I stay this we
can still get out of it with a fight
what what it's impossible you idiot what
have you done
I've deliver the monster to a monster
relax he's not taking you anywhere there
I'm afraid you're wrong oh fight fight
fight fight oh
oh uh yeah sure missile
snaring what that do oh oh oh
oh
uh oh I'm snared well
great uh wait ready can I UNS snare him
somehow he mainly went for Starion of
course he
did
take oh and I can I help him out of the
snar
oh yeah
okay
nice let's have some
fun
good we can go
here this will niely try
that 51 that's really
low I'm I'm a hidden though
right oh well we got to try 51 come on
please please please please please
no slow because of Sharpshooter you can
[Music]
what where can I toggle that and why is
that now problematic to
[Music]
me
I don't know where that
is that's so
stupid what the
[Music]
that's so stupid why did I take
this lowest hit CH but does more damage
well that
forever pal oh
[Applause]
angry very very
angry hell everything's missing
she has that too you guys said
right I don't like it
I don't like it at all I'm going to lose
this fight because of that
man
[Music]
man at least someone's doing damage
here on oh oh he's trying to run away
and he's going going for the that might
not end well please miss please miss
please
miss oh oh oh he
[Applause]
dead now it's off
right kill
him to kill
him
yeah that's good damage M you're going
down you can't take Aion away from me oh
no his backpack is burning
no this is worth the
cost huh what I what did I miss
money talk to me m
M attack with her or help him there's no
way she's going to do 22
[Music]
damage you're the one that ratted him
out it was a joke I was interested in
what
happened yeah yeah yeah
sh
35 that's not even worth
it but if I help him up next turn he's
just going to be targeted again
and be killed I can't even he heal him
well
enough to you know make it worth can he
just not try his best to survive until I
end
this
so you just going to let him die now
he'll be fine but okay
okay then then yeah at least at least he
won't attack the others I guess I
wouldn't mind him attacking Shadow hard
though at least uh staran does more
damage kaha hello
hello just keep him
down oh oh oh everything's so
dark uh why why so dark because you're
so dead huh uh so we can't reach the guy
huh oh well then I don't really think I
can do
anything I could jump wait
but oh those are two bonus actions wait
I have two bonus actions
right uh let's
[Music]
[Laughter]
see
oh you little you have made K very
angry is my is my passive like
there again automatically or no
okay you solidarity Keeps The Troop
together where are you going
without as we can him
in well um what's happening what's
what's what's What's Happening Here
what's what's happening no time to
waste what's happening what's
happening let's help everybody back up
and
um should we do a a long rest rest my we
head what's so what might you be
hiding
[Music]
oh look at this gandel's
aspiration interesting when gandel was
seven he was frightened badly by a
vampire spawn during a public burning
seized by the Flames the creature didn't
shrivel up it swelled and burst like a
squeezed leech brain splattered the
boy's shoes is gray pink and pulpy he
would never forget it but you're saying
that was ay stum or that was just
another
spawn weth to kill him yeah for the rare
crossbow
nice
oh just another
one oh yeah I guess he didn't die so
um shall we do a long
rest CU short rest doesn't heal so
much talk to aarion oh yeah we have to
can we still talk to him now will he
give me the same chitat aaran what's up
sorry for ring you out
but oh H so there's a monster hunter
after you not anymore hun anymore which
is all that matters really you're
welcome so you're not mad at me
right what if there were others he might
have not why was he hunting you why why
was he hunting you I didn't do anything
do anything I was kidnapped just like
you it seems kazador wants me
back kazador who is
[Music]
kazador your past is chasing us who is
kador kazador Zar is a vampire lord in
Boulder's Gate the patriarch of his
coven and a monster obsessed with power
he turned me nearly 200 years
ago I became his
spawn and he became my Tormentor
oh you're sure cat door is behind his it
was him I'm
sure only he would know to send the G
after me it was a group of G that
attacked me me that night in Boulder's
Gate I would have died had Cazador not
appeared and saved
[Music]
me
um huh why would Monster Hunter serve
Cazador he's a vampire idea who they're
working for cador likely paid someone to
pay someone to call in a favor
and here we are a friend of a friend of
a friend he doesn't do simple plans not
if he has a complex one that pits a
dozen enemies against each other no this
Hunter is a message mhm kazador is
letting me know that even out here he
can get to
me he wants me back
oh why capture you why not just kill it
true true true maybe he wants to do it
himself
self maybe he wants to make an example
of me to show what happens to runaways
or maybe he thinks death is too good for
me should I be concerned concerned do
you know the power vampire lord
possesses so is that a yes sh turn into
mist call woles to do his bidding shove
up blows like they're nothing are we
going to fight him camp tonight and kill
with his bare hands n he can't be lucky
if death was the worst thing that
happened to
[Music]
you no our camp nobody can walk in
here all right what do you suggest first
we have
to uh you don't have a plan I don't know
well if we kill his lackes he'll just
send more we just have to be vigilant
keep our wits about us and kill any
monster hunters and maybe not R out
aarion anymore on our
own do
do unless there's more good good loot
involved uh okay thank you for all that
info very interesting I'm sorry for
dragging you into this but you're also
dragging me into some so you
know not riding him out my improve
relationship not like I want to
necessarily I don't care about us having
the best
relationship I don't care about that
that's not my priority my priority is I
used n but I Auto Select
it
my priority
is
becoming the
leader of everything and
dominating this world in a te pose yes
yes
yes I should throw the poisoned Apple
away where do I have a poisoned Apple I
only
oh those are poisoned
apples n
could I have accidentally eaten that in
my camp supplies no right also what is
this anyway nobody no explanation about
this no
lore leaving me with question marks
another another well and what the
oh oh narissa don't
look or maybe do look
where
Isa poor bird poor
Raven hung from the
tree can I can I
help no I don't think there's another
one oh they're all getting stuck is
there spiders
here what do you mean I can't get there
of course I can get there go
around and then does that mean that just
well also leads to something underground
this feted smell assaults your
nostrils dead flesh lies below a great
deal of
it why would
no that would be stupid I will not drink
from that
stinky
oh oh there's some stuff I'm apparently
not allowed to
take uh I can't get up up there can I oh
well I can I can where is she going ah
to the side
here okay
um
so are we just going to
enter there's someone oh oh oh Monty
she's going to be nice to me right
hello I've arrived I don't want a crumb
left on that plate girl Auntie Ethel
please it's disgusting one more bite and
this pie is going to come back up to say
hello don't make me get the wooden spoon
you're eating for two so get to
it this isn't my hero you talk Ages come
in come in sorry someone on the
way some fun with
it Gods grant me patience eat up
Marina I won't say it again oh
frightening uh no no bad news
um uh
ah I forgot about this yeah yeah yeah
yeah you said you had something for the
parasite of course oh I'd lose my head
if it wasn't attached to me well I'm
starting to lose trust for her I told a
bit of a white lie I said I had
something at home that could help yeah
well that's something is me forgive me I
didn't want the Grove's prying eyes in
my business oh okay what do you say want
me to take care of the little bugger
uh
[Music]
yes you're a sharp one I am proposing a
deal but it's different from your little
packed you see I prefer personal
things okay creep you pretty little
peepers my you want my eye it from your
head kiss it for luck then back in it
goes won't take but a moment you want to
my eye my price nothing more do we have
to take it out in order to kiss it can
you kiss it while it's still
in I'm afraid that's my business palal
it's nothing the fairest though I
promise maybe it makes it into like a
security camera and she can like see
what I'm doing gives her like footage
from
everywhere that that sounds bad like
yeah no I don't know I feel like I I
won't be seeing well afterwards or will
I will will I a touch but sure you have
two eyes in your skull don't you no need
to be
precious no Etho can I please quiet you
had enough
pampering hey and you my door is always
open petle aunti is here for you I
realize now I shouldn't have killed the
brothers
because the real problem might just be
her but
let's dig deeper spoiled triacle oh
investigate why is everybody
failing did he not
fail he said that's not a real fire what
are you hiding you mean what what what
what's not a real
fire
what not a wheel wheel
fire behind the
fireplace this is kind of sussy
looking one step at a time
Nowa scary eyes
fun jump in jump jump jump jump
in well who wants to try maybe Cara
story she she doesn't really care about
the fire anyway right all right get
in can she oh she turned it off
oh well the that that thing behind
though is kind of I mean that's not
normal that's not
normal use jump okay with the fire
on
oh go
on where is she where'd she
go
where oh they're
coming invisible invisible but is she
still here I wonder
what should we send kak
back cuz inside well I guess we'll just
explore the inside
afterwards she's running away she's
there but invisible no no should I
should I randomly cast
uh The Cloud of dagger is like over
here I I I would hope she's still there
I could be wrong and this could be a big
waste I saw her here I saw her standing
[Music]
here it's
yay ooh what happened to you oh oh oh
we're breaking things don't break the
books though I want to read the
books um what do we
want I don't know
take oh no it undoes it oh no oh no oh
no oh yeah cuz it breaks my my my my
concentration I'm sorry let's go up
here I'm sorry but at least we see her
for
now uh yeah that's that's fine that's
fine that's fine and we did some
starting damage you
know let's
go
[Music]
Miss into the
Shadows faith will protect
me I couldn't bite her it was too far
for some reason that's so stupid
why are you always surprised it misses
because it's surprising to
[Music]
me should I spawn the weapon again could
be nice
cuz bless up ah I forgot about the
blessing oh yeah where which one was it
um this
one
[Music]
wonderful and I guess yeah we'll spawn
something okay maybe I should have
spawned it over here
actually oh
well now I can however directly attack
uh 45 is probably not going to go
through
though
yeah it's she going to go invisible
again I hope
not ah I can't jump
out can't jump
[Music]
out you can't get very
far
[Music]
m 2 m 2
m Target is
blocked I got to do a ranged
attack
45 that's also so
low I want to throw something can I
throw something cool oh what if
I
um what she have we have Grease We have
a scroll of
shatter and Tasha hi is L we could
probably take the others
too we have Mirror Image Scroll of
scroll of
web maybe this cuz then can she maybe
not get invisible anymore I don't know
don't throw the scr yeah no no no no I
would use
them your new crossbow oh yeah do I give
that
to to
her
wow oh well then
maybe wait did I already shoot why why
can I not shoot
anymore it takes an accident
equip okay okay
okay free free of
them what are they
doing
bloodless what's that do oh oh
they're dashing
in okay don't okay oh oh oh oh break
illusion oh she's oh oh she went there
she went enjoy playing with your new
friends bye-bye not
bye-bye can't have gone
far uh is she still there or do we just
fight her later
maybe should we just take care of them
[Music]
now
uh
uh ah can't get over
there
[Music]
um 45 they're actually
quite
use your vampire fangs for
buff what do you mean what my vampire
fangs what what
what what what
what well not
good you just mean vampire bite you mean
right
okay okay cuz it says vampire bite not
thanks you know sometimes things can be
very specific just want to make sure we
understand each
other um opportunity to attack an enemy
moving all of War maybe
[Music]
warter
shook miss miss
miss mhm H ooh
60% critical hit let's go let's go ax
let's go Act Fast good
[Music]
job s
this
nice nice inflicting of wounds
oh speaking of inflicting on wounds
remember those new knives I bought
they're really nice and all and I can
cut things so much faster and better
with
them but I also cut myself like twice
yesterday it was like so so like easy to
cut myself
accidentally only small Cuts though H
but I was like what the how how did
I just what how
ah got to be careful with those new
knives nobody needs really healing can't
even catch my
breath
um wait what about what about
reapplying did I
why I'm so
confused oh cuz she ran away with my
hex
okay
[Music]
okay why does that still count that must
mean that she's like still in reach
no if she can run away with it and I'm
not like released from it
no yeah 85% and a miss what the God
in
here
[Music]
angering ooh 94 need to learn the
Hardway
[Music]
okay was cooking a lot better with the
new well yeah cutting cutting onions and
stuff like I noticed when I was cutting
onions before the new knives came in I
was like kind of squeezing them rather
than cutting them espe us around when
you get closer to the
the the drunk or
so yeah now it's just so smooth wow
wow um I I Feel so amazed I haven't had
sharp knives in
years
um over
here leave no Trace
pretty good pretty
good 91 pretty good pretty
good finish it with a pokey
poke D knives are dangerous well but
obviously sharp knives are more
dangerous you can kill people with them
and I uh cut myself with the sharp
knives I didn't cut myself with the dull
knives n of course they're more
dangerous I'm going to have troubles
slicing you guys up with a dll knife
while the sharp one will be much
easier who are you guys talking
about I never hurt myself with a bell
knife no you're
wrong you're just
wrong
uh well
okay
oh can't afford to let
up talking about real injuries well I
also never had a real injury from a Dull
Knife are you up to date on your Tanis
shots no I am not should I be concerned
about this now oh no oh no I don't think
I am up to date on anything
besides Corona
shots thank you swatter oh my God happy
birthday oh my God you're heading to oh
my God oh my God you're watching the L
of the
Bic let's
go you'll tell them I love you let's go
sorry I'm so excited I'm so
excited and I just can't hide did you
actually took my my only guy my my
request and my advice I love you happy
Birthday wait so you're not going today
right but you you you're going there
soon I suppose that's lovely that's
absolutely lovely
Dobby um got to press
on oh this is uh close range forgot
forgot I keep forgetting
that try
faier or guiding bolt but the guiding
bolt is it never really does
anything for
me oh wow it was trying to fix its
reputation with me so that I don't kick
it out or replace it with something else
close one guiding bolt very close one I
know I see what you're doing I know what
you're she doing another fight let's go
she's still chilling up here very
comfortable is that the last one no
there's another one there right
somewhere there okay 98 come
on
although yeah no okay we'll finish this
one
off okay
afterwards we can open all of this right
even though it's red mean she's not even
here now so who is he going for heating
up two more only
see one
but I might be
blind 98
another oh yeah that must feel
good just from above
like smash
him oh is there still one coming from
the nest maybe oh yeah maybe I see uh
wait no I don't like I I don't see any
other red
dots this one is that
one are you ever planning on joining us
are you just going to waste my time
where the is
he do
not I don't have all
day
oh he's on his way I'm not going to go
over to his
[Music]
side um
what's with
him okay we done here for now we're done
is he going to continue dashing over
here can I open
this how delicious I'm
scared oh
yeah oh yeah I'm opening everything oh
yeah household
prayer this lady has a prayer a
household prayer
really po ties potion of Greater
healing oh yummy yummy yummy not
poisoned apples supposedly ew no I don't
want the rotting basket
uh campfire no turn it back
on
um portion of healing is that outside
what
oh sometimes things are a little bit
hard to
see the
bases
potato oh oh oh okay uh white bread
let's not take the spoiled Treats but a
bun but bun M lots of
bread yummy yummy yummy where did the
girl go by the way I guess she
teleported her to
wherever we're going oh the key
mhm wherever she went is probably where
she teleported the girl to simple poison
recipe
M potion of speed potion of fedal cool
we used one before so this makes up for
it elixir of
heroism temporary hit points become
blessed
ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh why does it keep on reminding me
that I am in the gnarled tea house
huh whis
weed oh I didn't check up check out the
bodies
yet I think the guy gave up on dashing
over here bone
cap
okay
wh a crude
chest okay I think I'm ready to go
in did I miss something important I
don't think so let's
go yeah let's go
in I'm Coming For You Witchy Witch o o
they're going so
far um do to click on the stairs or what
okay Adventure
o
green I wonder if this is don't look
don't Lauren I wonder if this is somehow
connected to why is it so
red this is connected to um where we
explored
yesterday yesterday last time green mins
go oh it means I can't rest in here oh
okay as long as the map is red
maybe don't look down what happened to
you you are as thick as they come
sweetness this is my personal Playhouse
and you don't have an invite get out
your personal Playhouse I thought it was
a tea
house forgive me I'll leave right away
will she just accept
that I think I'll stay a while has that
wler eaten your brain
already
leave or you'll end up in tonight's stew
we'll go nicely with Marina she's
already Mar
I KNE
no where she go don't
look headless
person well this is delightful
no maon
maon magron my darling maon she wished
for the mind of a genius but that silly
head crushed me mawan was what that one
of the lost kids no right right was she
don't look what's that don't
what that that guy won't shut up guys
what is this though the skull is looking
into a mirror huh my sweet Cali
whose beloved asked that his Beauty
Never
Fade
well it it's C something certainly
faded uh don't oh look that looks it
soundss like a staring man for some
reason oh blinded elf is this what would
have happened to my
eye oh guess I'll take that uh wait I
want to um indeed
talk was the other one with the head off
was she dead I wonder if she could be
considered dead she looked kind of alive
regards you
lifelessly m
why did you go to the HG my family took
her my baby girl oh no
pretended she never
existed told e never wanted to see them
again she huh took my eyes so funny
taking it
[Music]
literally is there anything I should
know
run no I will run further inside if
anything what can you tell me
about nothing really
matters nothing really matters to
me why did your family take your child
they didn't like me having
something they couldn't
touch that doesn't really make that much
sense to me but
okay what about the ey this poor dear
wish never to lay eyes on her family
again oh what's going on here family
portrait my dearest EF he beged me to
help the deadly disase that RAV so so
quiet deadly disease that ravaged him
well you didn't really help him you're
doing a really bad
job at being a helping
witch stop please please chill the
out I'm too scared to pick up those
things gal
door pakisha started a conversation did
I crushing waves of fear as the presence
within the door
recoils can't let people through not
again looks like a
face what happened the last time you
open images flash a man cowering a bag
open at his feet gold coins spilling
onto the floor uhhuh his cries for Mercy
are cut short as the hag slices into him
dismembering him
painstakingly limb by limb she cackles
the man's remaining flesh twisted and
contorted becoming the Twisted surface
of the door before you oh that's him
flee you feel it crying he his face got
so
big
what or did he just become a part of it
huh M
door wait I want to talk to the guy
first before I try getting in I'm not
afraid of the ha though tears in your
mind two paladins and a cleric marching
through the door mhm shroud Ed in the
glow of the Divine wow weapons
brandished they charge into the hag's
Slayer screams of Terror pierce the air
you let them
in
naughty that's a decade for each you're
mine for 30 more years
Peeta well that doesn't impress me
either
m
it's like cracking okay the dialogue
kind of leads me
to to demanding to let be let
in let me through the door stays silent
okay
oh oh open up or I'll burn you to
ashes or I would I would like this can
we just kill the hack first you know
no
[Music]
the door will get punished for 40 more
years for letting me through oh
no I'll kill the hack don't worry don't
worry intimidating doors but this is an
actual person you know oh well that was
a close one dear dear you see the she
walks through the door this is on my
side right the light Touch of Hope
brushes your mind as the presence within
Retreats oh that was a vision right
don't what's this St
Shield stop a who tried to steal from
Auntie now the good little pet guards my
home okay away so what is the matter
with you no no don't look must look must
ins that's very
gumy uh Smile as he
Twitches yes okay let's let's let's get
back into role playing again but no she
I mean would she be that like much
enjoying this well I see it I see
come me dead dead flesh rotten boat
shining
um I don't understand what's going
on hey look at me no no can't stop
can't did you just call me a me oh
please please please please
please I think about
it every time you open your mouth it
gets a little more tempting no yeah
that's more like it that's more like it
Monster huh well maybe I am dripping
flesh peeling mind player well so so
what look at me I'm not a mind
player I know I'm I'm walking away F FL
mhm whatever wasting my time with
you no intention of letting that happen
don't look don't our glass my to laen he
wished to know what was to come please
please and then well I I you ended up
killing him I hope I don't need him at
least uh cuz my character
says I am not willing to put myself
beneath him so garly calron don't don't
people like sometimes say oh gnarly like
a really weird and cute way of
describing something cool that's so
gnarly gnarly oh Nar gnarly oh
[Laughter]
gnarly G okay well what do we do about
the
door am I missing
something let
me let me for tell me about different
entrance you feel the beest hint of Life
fromin perception it just walking
through again okay I was thinking if
maybe that works again the same way oh
it does stop please oh
incredible not much of a door are
you uhoh but it's kind of rotting here
again okay
ooh
ooh 1 2 3
4 mask of Terror of regret of Vengeance
and of
servitude okay uh suddenly fight they
didn't they're not even looking at
me where's this one ah over here okay
can we get up somewhere with
tanakha probably not let's try to jump
oh can I I would like to jump up
[Music]
here
not enough movement too
high too high oh okay safe now
now ah I think I can't manage this
battle should I go for him first then
cuz he's
like don't know if I can do anything at
all right
now maybe
not not good all or maybe you can I
reach 75 okay I guess that's worth a try
what do I have to
lose okay
well I gave it a
try
M how far can we
get this
way
91 yeah oh they don't have much HP very
good by the way I think finished one
piece first
season like uh two days ago
actually I really really liked it I
really
[Music]
did
yeah it was uh yeah uh I ended up
finding out more about nami's story I've
tweeted about you know crying emojis
about Nami and Sanji and uh what was his
name zeff zeff
um I I think I can say now who my
favorite character is besides
Nami I think it's
Sandi I really like
him yeah I like his character like he's
kind of a flirty character right but
he's not flirting in like an OB noxious
way how many flirty characters are often
written um he's fine
honestly nice critical 10 HP hit when we
don't really need it in the anime he is
okay well then I think that I'm I'm glad
I'm I'm glad they tuned it down a
bit um
like wow wow
wow yeah he
seems like a gentleman I almost feel
like bad for him like he there was I
think there was a scene where Nami ran
to the others um back to them to like
say hello again give them a hug they're
like welcome back Nami and he's like you
know yeah she she's he he's like so
smiley and happy and opens up his arms
and she ignores him and just runs past
him and I'm like E I mean I get it you
you're not as acquainted to him yet as
the others I guess but man poor
guy Zoro Zoro is not really like I find
him cool and all that but he he's not
that interesting to me yet he's
not
so like I don't
know so far he's not that special to me
I
guess heading out
he's just I just can't I don't like
these kind of like super quiet types
that much you know he's cool though and
um
sweet actually never
mind wa what they why are they all
looking
away
even where are the others ah ah one's
here
oh
so just vibing and getting
lost I really like the the fight scene
that they had in the that Fishman place
with Sandy and Zoro kicking everyone's
butts speaking of
butts sanji's butt in that suit is quite
nice when he does all the jumps and so
on
but generally I think Sanji has also
just the general extra of
um uh
wait of having a suit on you know how I
feel about
suits he looks so good in it
yeah and and the love he has for food
but also the story the back story with
death ooh that that hit hard when he
went to the other side of that like
Cliff or so and then he sees death and
then oh he realizes oh man oh that hurt
that
hurt man oh how did he even survive
like like it's already a a miracle that
Sanji survived with that little food and
then for that long amount of time how
did he well yeah I guess he ate his leg
but that that's all up that's so
w he ate it raw I
guess what the man involuntary can
cannibalism lots of meat on a leg I
guess so but like how do you even eat
that
ra
um yeah so that was
interesting I'll go can I go up there
no damn
it no
please I went with manga guy ate his leg
and not get lost in a
wreck I guess so they did the thing
where he eats his own leg
Yeah which is spoilers I'm sorry if you
guys didn't watch it yet um maybe may
maybe you'll forget about what I said
anyway
[Music]
um wait wait I feel like I asked this
question before but like not all of this
vision is his vision
obviously but like their Vision counts
together is that is that what what's
happening because what if I want to hide
from him but I don't care about hiding
from the
others like I should be able to hide
here for example if it was just for this
one it counts
together
m
uh and what was that about I can like
still do these attacks even when I'm not
hidden as long as my friends are close
to the enemy or close to
me ah uh t to the
Target if I don't have a this I don't
think that really applies right
[Music]
now m
okay you when I
have guess I'm bringing it before I
spoil anything
else well now it's too
late the barrel scene where they declare
their dreams so hard that was sweet too
yeah
yeah I feel like Nami could have
honestly told her
sister feel like that was oh well I can
go here can I hide here let's have
a like that was a little
bit over like like her being over
dramatic a little
bit but yeah oh we took him down in the
manga they all knew oh oh
okay um and oh yeah now now the clown is
back great
great I can't go up there can I
yeah still on my feet that's kind of
lame like uh I found it funny though at
least he helped
them was kind of obvious though that
when they let him out that he was going
to go uh and run for it
so ridiculous that they let him out
they're too nice they're just too nice I
can imagine him being around for a long
long long long time and you know that's
the problem if they don't ever kill any
of these guys they're going to keep on
reappearing and it's going to maybe
eventually become a little bit boring is
what I'm thinking am I frightened
oh what do I
do need to stay
focused
can I help myself from being
frightened they meet a lot of ton of
people and don't kill any of them
great characters always appear again but
they're quite different it's kind of the
point okay it doesn't become it does
become a problem for
you so what about the fishmen cuz they
were like really evil can we consider at
least some of them dead
because like what we're never going to
accomplish anything if we don't like
kill
them they're in
prison some do
die you know what I'll do healing on the
have I blessed everybody yet I guess not
now it's kind of late to bless
people well I guess I'll do
it
huh
I can't reach everybody what too far oh
okay never mind
[Music]
then I don't know what to do I can't
help her right I don't know are you too
far no but are you still alive okay
m
try nothing will stand in my
way people losing their dreams is worse
than death that's why death is rare it
kills a person used to be even if
alive nah I wouldn't say that that is
accurate in real life but I guess it's
okay to make that a thing in within a
like a you know a story like
that I wouldn't agree that's true true
in real life
though
M I don't know what to do
here yeah symbolism no that's
fine wow and you go back up you little
so hard for me to rage you little
ah
ow God damn damn
it can I do
this oh
shees I can't believe I could reach it
with a jump
m not bad not bad not
bad
strong characters can jump at oh really
okay yeah yeah yeah one piece is great
and and I heard that they uh already
wrote the the whole second season and
they would be ready to film if it wasn't
for the strike so they're they're
waiting for that to be done and and then
they can do the next
season mying I'm excited and I I I saw
that and I tagged cie cuz I was
excited oh taged Celly like look look
look look it's real season 2 is
real
wonderful oh yeah I tweeted at the
actress she didn't she she seems
relatively active on Twitter but she
didn't I don't know if she even saw it
but you guys I don't know if it's a good
thing or a bad thing surely you we
spammed her reply section but that might
also like spam away my first reply and
she might not look at it I wonder I
wonder if it helped or if it just did
more damage that you guys all went in
like thank you for saving my little
sister uh in that fire the other day
you're such a hero
I'm not sure but doesn't work right
hell ready I probably got muted
no I love
her I love her she can't use
twiter because of the strike if but I
saw it like just a day ago she was using
Twitter
H I don't believe that maybe I should
try on Instagram though but on Instagram
it's genuinely more difficult to be
noticed because I feel like famous
people do not look at their comment
section uh if they get like a million of
comments and their DMS are closed so I
feel like on Twitter you're just more
inclined to check the replies and all
that because it's just more like how
Twitter
functions if you know what I
mean I can't do these guys got
to finish it from over there
somehow is this so
[Music]
annoying no I can't do
anything
be kind what what happened our guests
are you okay be kind to Our Guest oh now
I feel bad for killing him he's just you
know another suffering visitor who
didn't want it to be like this
but oh
man what's this sacred Ms infus your
crossbow bus with holy energy wow
possibly inflict turn
Undead Okay interesting
but death is a
release in this situation I think yeah
that's
probably oh I can jump so far I didn't
think I would be able to
oh oh
man
just like old
times come on give me good
damage I didn't expect that good damage
oh thank God cuz it was really difficult
for me to get
there
y can you guys be careful what the
I still can't rest
here
[Music]
um
girl uh no I'm ready whatever it takes
drink uh can I eat
this consume how this wait is this a
poison one oh yeah don't oh my God that
was
close wait can I do short rest
though
time to get going oh I can do short rest
okay all right all right then um okay
let's
see it's
red
oh I
wonder if I would have taken those masks
and put them
on actually look
close
would that have been
helpful don't equip it it scares
me got to press
on mask of
Vengeance uh should I go
outside poisonous slime bomb
faded
note read this every morning remember
she's not your friend oh she's not your
family do not eat the food unless she's
watching do not drink the tea unless
she's watching do not wear the mask
oh he was trying to remind himself even
though you or she she didn't really seem
to be able to control
herself oh
man those poor people people I feel so
bad K's head
great pick this one
up yeah obviously I know that's what the
point
[Music]
is
okay well if I leave then I have to go
all the way back here
ah I don't like
that thank
you safe and try to R yeah I'll be
fine
baby how does how does this work is this
another
jump
oh
yeah oh
oo looks like a trap oh nice nice
perception we are wet okay we got to uh
disarm the vent and the peculiar
flower be
careful not you didn't I click
on I click on the
Starion ah did we not proceive certain
other things is that what's going
on ah she's
[Applause]
dying I was going to say oh we won't
need
this Mom mmy it's a gfx but does poison
smoke it's a bug I can't see the poison
and supposed to be
there
she's
[Music]
dying those time stop while I'm like you
know the
um is it does it does it come from the
from the vent
difficulty class
biry how the am I supposed to reach
30 step like let's just leave um but
about her well your savior is here oh no
she's she's like constantly
dying my faith will guide me die
what what I
do the
this is so
stupid maybe if I reload then I actually
see the poison
Cloud
uh this one
right oh my God everybody's dying help
me help
me
I can block the vent of something e
how can I put a stone on
it I just like ST stand there and drop
the item or
what oh I oh I throw a big box orell of
collar wait wait wait wait this way not
hold
no
ah well ah okay now I see it uhuh
uhuh now I see it very
clearly be careful guys don't walk into
it
um I don't really see where the thing is
I see the
[Music]
flow proo
uh let's
try I don't know how do I throw this do
I have to put it in her
inventory Pro
this
uh
here it
worked
yo let's r
i i perfectly aimed at first
try cuz I roughly remembered where it
was um and the flowers should this still
dis aim the flowers
[Music]
probably
flower
flow did you guys watched my Minecraft
tour with the we saw yesterday
huh so many
memories so many
things so many let's be quick things to
show you
know I I I I think I did a good job you
know there's of course always things
that I might not be be able to show
because I'm I can't be aware of like
everything can't be aware of everything
that happens at the server first of all
I I I I like never got to like really
like collab in Minecraft with Council
so you know I was never streaming
Minecraft at the same time so
unfortunately I don't know a lot of the
things like I catch up some things and
like clips and so on but you
know I can't be aware of what everybody
builds in the
server yeah and and like why and who and
this and that but I tried I tried my
best okay so here we have the same thing
I
suppose but here I don't know where
exactly it's coming
from we can
bro I wonder how big it has to be I'll
try with some stones but I doubt that I
can figure it
out how about
here mhm how
about
here well
how
about clothes to I is interrupted how
about
here yeah
if you go right up to the edge it
should be in perception
range oh she perceived it ah she
perceived the flower
M what if can I go here o I can I can
walk around what don't TR you
don't walk on it don't walk into it
you're going to die
again
um pering the wrong
thing use Shadows fire fire wit and
Blades always Shar at this
thing or or this just a normal fire can
I burn the
flowers don't use
fire oh but it
worked I
don't see but it's gone I don't see the
thing
ah ah there it is it probably has like a
30 disarming thing again so I
better ah it's coming back okay okay
okay okay um Let me throw this leather
armor it's probably big
enough um it's good to be alive I think
I know it's like ah it's here it's here
that's it
beautiful nice The Masks too I was
wondering if the masks could work watch
how you go uh a trap oh nice you
actually perceived this one beautiful
oh this is also a way to get rid of all
your items in your inventory I
suppose there you
go all right and then I guess we have to
go through the ladder my
way
oopsie
okay
um be careful to not step on the
flower
idiots Mama
Mia Mama
Mia H I told them and they they just
don't
listen just don't listen I don't have
many potions either ah wait this guy has
a
bunch did it go to
her I think the rest will be
fine pressing G so I don't they so that
they don't follow like
[Music]
ducks we go deeper and deeper
oh what's
here come on this will be F someone's
left a trap out for us what's here
though this is
sus this is sussy to me sussy
path we need to get better at proceeding
leing
things maybe there's nothing
here maybe
not I can't actually go there maybe I
was
wrong where's Shadow heart wait Shadow
heart no wait I am Shadow heart where is
me can't give up
now what
stop everybody stop how did she get
there especially without getting
poisoned
what so confused okay what a uh ah
didn't I perceive it and now I can't see
it again
H
[Music]
uh can we perceive it again I don't
remember I don't remember did I actually
see it wait is it this thing
no now I would prefer to see the uh
unsee the cloud again
actually yeah let's do the Firebolt
again but kiaha take a step back never
mind let's get on with
it you're you you're doing great thanks
honey
uh am I blind I can't see
it and it's coming
[Music]
back um what it comes back so
fast can I like out of battle spam that
forever can they just walk
around
I don't see anything well well well
we'll walk around we'll walk around be
careful everybody no no no no no don't
there place oh I saw it I saw
it
uh
uh everybody calm
down there it is easy why won't they
perceive it
earlier that would make things so much
easier e wait it didn't really work did
it no
[Music]
no wow Kiwa is actually like so smart
tamaka so smart we can just jump around
I
guess everybody jump
here
yes join
me no yes now don't come they're so
stupid they're so stupid yes yes thank
[Music]
you
um disarming is this where I came from
or am I going the right
way I hope I'm going the right
way wrong way
no
really yeah
no oh there's two two paths that lead
down here huh
okay can we all just jump over here
without getting into the no no oh oh
close you didn't jump but
okay there she is in the gnarled cage
cage is this immediately going to turn
into a
fight that helped there in the cage I
hope
so cuz I just just heal
gnarly
narly I see you no you didn't fail that
I literally see
it try again oh
ooh finally I see you again my home
interfere in my business and now have
the goal to face me in the heart of my
lair
you P I could have killed her the first
time man that would have been nice but
then not your assho we would have had
I'll use your blood to spice not so many
reasons to come down here I'll keep you
alive until I've sucked the marrow from
your bones marrow and then I'll bring
you back and do it all
over sh no crazy lady here
please nuh girl I have a hero complex I
need to be a hero this is my hero story
no what the
uh wait where did she go oh is that
her what she doing she can't let
make her
drop water
water po did she just shoot that at me
who shot that
okay uh chill out do I even have
water um
oil
antidote I don't know if I have water
what if I don't have water an ice spell
or water or cold
uh oil oil oil oil arsonist
oil Poison Poison
Poison an ice
[Music]
Arrow
okay
then oh who should use it can I can I
there's no way I can miss it
right
[Music]
uh so like
this
o I hope she will be Dau okay uh Auntie
is over there
uh oh I can't do anything besides
shooting
that h H I
go I'm
ready carock is by the way already quite
low on health what the
hell that is
[Music]
concerning can
you jump
here not enough movement are you sure
about
that
I want
to she's not that far I feel like I
could if I get here I could shoot
her I'd focus on the spelling the Clones
oh wait yeah they're all
her
H dispelling AKA killing them is that
the same
thing
[Music]
I don't know what I can do
though I can just do normal
what would you
do
let's throw something
indeed have have so many fun things that
we could we could for the smoke powder
bomb or is that too strong should I go
for something weaker I I'll go with the
smoke powder
bomb where is
it
here
hom ah so they just need like a little
bit of damage and then they're they're
dispelled
okay well
well on the hunt oh he can't hide there
okay and if she doesn't die right away
that means she's the real one right she
the real
one
yeah I got
both um should
I I'll
try what if it's
zero H I thought
so oh did you not go into frenzy
oopsy oh I should have healed her I
should have healed her I should have let
her drink
something
o still breathing despite everything
light on my feet still
breathing oh did I get my hex back
[Music]
wonderful I think that's the real
one that's my my idea but 60% what what
why so low oh it was not the real one
scripted there she is
now we so far hope she comes closer to
me enough don't do this don't do the
fire again
please don't let oh okay she's just
teleported that's it
wait what she made what
huh you're telling me that
one of them is
real
nah nah I can see who is
real this one says marinaa level one
hacks
trickery
H one is level one one is level five so
I would say level one is the real
one
mhm
um but yeah kind of difficult does she
purposefully stay away so
far they won't know what be can I
reach no he try to shoot from here
dude it's not that
difficult ah
ah man this
sucks don't don't worry I won't hit you
I know you're you're the real one can I
examine her hi Marina you look kind of
wobbly and blurry
there you
good m
her natural look I don't think she
looked like this before I don't
know I think it might be an optical
illusion I managed to hring her holy
this never works I
think wow does that make her like unable
to move
properly to concentrate wow can't
believe it the percentage was so
low now shall we try our luck
with uh actually what are we going to
try our luck
with
uh
50 um maybe I can also throw something
fun at her we have so many things to
throw I want to throw
that may
I uh just throwing at where she is or I
I know I asked this before but do I
throw it at her or where where she
is at her ground at her and okay better
get to
work she's poison it may have missed but
she's poison yeah that's all I wanted
okay okay okay
car
thank you congratulations oh my God two
years bye two years you're in the bucket
W or you out of the bucket you're out of
the
bucket Mama Mia under their
noses
congratulations what if I throw a mask
at
her going to keep on throwing things cuz
she's so
far thanks for the membership uh R new
world I'm having fun throwing things now
so
easy cool cool cool cool
cool
mm
wait I could have done an enraged
FR why did I not do
that ah I didn't realize she has a
special fro I can still what will I
throw with my enraged proo
[Music]
wait do we still have like a javelin or
did I sell every
Javelin can I do it with a dagger
too
I don't see any
javelins Pitchfork Pitchfork
Pitchfork we have a Cleaver we have a
dagger dagger
dagger let's go with the dagger then I
would say so too dagger is very
Frable uh there it
is oh 55 well that's all right
oh but I missed okay it's fine it's
fine need to find a way
forward just got hex though right oh
what happened with my
hex what
happened what difficulty I'm like on
like normal
difficulty not the easy
one she pay back to
me
oh no you didn't she took the idea
from me I hex the Clone all right
you little
ah going to bite you for
that but
first
I'll do it my way I'll do it my
way no
Escape ooh 16 and then and then a good
bite let's
go
yeah
marvelous kind of disgusting but you
know anything will
do this uh how bad is this poison are
you guys okay
you guys
okay better be
okay I'll try
this maybe let's make this
quick
oh walk out of it at least is she out of
it I feel like she is now
yes I got this oh got
this let's get as far as
possible still not quite far enough
M that's so bad with that low percentage
I don't know
man I don't
know
this thing is pretty weak I think
although wait would that hit
[Music]
aarion she has a good
crossbow yeah
but
mean in order to see the good damage one
has to first
see a higher
percent and that's not happening nothing
important is ever easy
oh
well
why why why why why why why because of
my
debuffs
ah she mocked
me T kakaria is not easily influenced by
some one below her mocking
her that thought alone is mocking me
that that would mock me that's that's
mocking to
me I am looking for I feel like I
remember this
one
25 why so low should I let someone else
cast that one where did it go
there let someone else cast it grease
her
[Music]
up
but then our baby is Darion also gets
greasy wait let's let's put it like
here I
guess should still be H oh oh oh I
didn't realize there was something there
to burn
ha oh no I totally knew
that how too
damage hey but she got another
free she's she's mocking me only by
copying everything I'm
doing
she's coping everything
Z what you little I'm going to
destroy
you I don't
care they see me no they
don't thank God that didn't
miss she's a tough one though yeah and
she's a bit annoying the way she uses
her her venue it's a bit annoying let's
finish
this I like leaving everyone in AOE area
well sometimes you just don't have a
choice
but
uh uhm
[Music]
moving how much percentage does she get
on
this
35 don't like it don't like it
a
yeah I'll
try one can only
try ready for another
round oh
you
can she make it
up incredible she's chasing her no
matter where she
goes yeah no mercy we follow you until
the Deaths of
Hell what if no no no no it's important
to do damage damage
first first and foremost damage damage
damage damage damage control I won't
give
in but
uh um I might heal with
her yes and don't waste a
step
how's that going 40 we're at 40 now hey
hey hey hey that's worth a try oh it's
certainly was worth a try let's
[Music]
go yeah what no not again not
again I have to find the real one
again ah
annoying she really makes you like run
around so
much that's so
unnecessary can't give
up I'm going to
miss not enough
movement what is
this
oh I didn't miss mm I am very
surprised let's have some
cage if you throw water on the real one
she says she stays wet
uhhuh well but I don't really want to
waste my turns with
that
the
subtle is
it what is it even possible to hit the
right one or is everybody the wrong one
until I you know dispelled
everybody why this check if her Fireball
has a better transer B
okay
[Music]
should I go
down I'm going
down to get closer to
them Harlock as
well but I don't know if I'm to if I
want to
not enough
movement ah this is so stupid ah so
stupid H so stupid H so
stupid oh
well yeah I should have just thrown
something again this is so
stupid that comes easy these
days
these boots have seen everything These
Boots Are Made for are you serious
walking that's just what they do I can't
reach
anybody I have an illusion
no oh I saved myself from being held oh
and she did too
wow
already did you guys see ID whole life
ID is getting free uh whole life ID free
is getting
free ID free
fre yeah he said he
said he said next month right did
they
it feels so fast it feels like suddenly
yeah everybody's like w w w w speeding
up we're getting so much 3D like council
is coming up Iris already happened that
happened it felt like it happened so
fast probably just because she's just
one person so it's like over in an
instant we'll do it my right let's do
I wasn't I wasn't really trying to
hide
[Music]
um yeah we'll throw something don't
worry what could we throw maybe this
thing how about the range oh here we
could get both
apparently
nice bye-bye suckers
new genen will have fre within free mom
so I'm calling
it uhhuh I don't think I don't think so
I don't think
so generation Deb and 3D in two M so
much happening yeah this summer is kind
of crazy but there one thing you can say
is they're keeping up the hive
got to keep
fighting
versus 30
so and I
miss
turn man if you don't have like endless
things to throw
uh then good luck with this
fight
wait this says like coating but are the
coating ones also for throwing
too jump over and
meing I'll I'll try yeah that works
probably
um
you that's the second time that she's
missing with a pretty high
[Music]
percentage sometimes the only way
out you push her into the oh but then
you don't get the loot I mean yeah sure
that's always an option for these fights
that is quite interesting with haste
but no I'm not going to I'm not going to
waste another turn like
that I
can't what if I throw the ball it makes
like a squeaky sound and that's it
maybe I could thow
this Alchemist
fire oh but that will hurt car oh wait
does she have this fire resistance or am
I imagining
this will it hurts
Carla
ex examine her to find out I'm just I'm
just trying to remember I
know
what about throwing an object um cuz I
when I if I understand correctly like
even if if if I throw an object you know
it could miss but if I throw like a bomb
or so or
fire it's it's going to do something at
least
something oh wait I have a spiked
bulb that's also
[Music]
AOE well well well you know H 16 it's
not going to do that much damage
right wait I I can throw it
here yeah okay I was able to do it with
minimum collateral damage where is
she I he are you going to take her
you're one start from betraying everyone
uh OB just do weak damage unless they're
heavy no I mean I I just needed one HP
damage that's all I
needed need to stay
[Music]
focused G but
oh no feel death's cold
grrip well so much for peace you
teleported right to chakaria I don't
like this I don't like this I need
[Music]
height I want some height oh
man
I'll just go further
away
15 how blast not looking so good today
there blood in
a just not looking so
good
20% oh this is like my least favorite
fight in bers gate so far I really don't
like it talk to
me did her did her can't stay
idle can't stay idle must become
comedian right
Carla
jump down the bridge and then hide and
S
what I'm throwing something once
[Music]
again or or maybe I'll cast
something what if I hold
her is she human Nord what is humanoid
humanoid doesn't necessarily mean human
right hope she can reach a tea party the
stream is this not the tea
party I think this is the Tea
Party just not a person oh and I can't
cast SK skills when I'm
angry means human humanik okay well I
guess she's not
[Music]
humanik here goes
nothing
shall just like all times
oh
aarion as always killing
it what you going to do what you going
to do what
don't don't do annoying again okay
that's fine I can take that as long as
you don't bring all your doubles out
again I will
accept go no this time he
misses so mean so
mean what should I
do it's okay you tried your
best now let's end this I wish I could
yeah this turn I think we can do it this
turn I I think we
can unless we miss
everything but we can reach with Carla
that's just really
low
why
fun this one's better and it's still m
ah I'm going to go into a rage game of
Rage
no what is going on and that's cuz she's
mocked but the other one had 70% though
still on my feet the first one was
yeah the other
one
50% Mama Mia is this considered
higher not really
apparently 50 do it it didn't work last
time oh
wow still
disappointing please don't make doubles
please don't make doubles please don't
oh oh wait just a tick no killing me is
a waste of time I find a way to return
always have always will really but it's
unpleasant so how about we be civilized
about
this I have something you
want the only way I would not kill you
is if you undo everything you've done so
far to all these innocent
people is what taka nikara would say but
[Music]
M what do you have what do you think you
have are you thinking of
Marina I knew I liked you Deary let me
leave with the girl and I'll give you
power you want to be stronger tougher
smarter anything is possible just
believe what and her babe trading some
wealth we just met for impossible power
no it's a fine deal honestly yeah I
don't really have a connection with her
but it's pretty
evil and only I'm allowed to do evil not
her I think a dead hag is the answer
[Music]
yeah if you want to live handle Marina
on this power right now my
reinforcements are nearly here give me
the girl what reinforcements you think
that's going to scare her more she's
already on the brink of death
[Music]
anyway yeah
both but minus one Charisma we need a 20
we're not getting a 20 out of
this didn't you guys say I can do
both was it a different
[Music]
thing
there's no way oh two
oh
oh do they get added or do I like choose
which one is better or
so we'll see ah it chooses the better
one
huh oh
shall we try again
I'll give it another
try wait even with a Nat 20 it gives me
minus one Charisma though so I'll always
be at 19
no that's kind of impossible wait wait a
second oh no TW not 20 always
wins
ah
I couldn't
add I'm C add guid ah so
close no I used so much
inspiration I'm clicking on
it isn't it because it's Shadow heart
she can't herself like both I don't
[Music]
know I don't know if I want to use any
more inspiration on this ah damn
it why are we on Shadow heart
anyway he was all believe in the Goa
M are these like this inspiration cuz in
the collab we found out that our
inspiration is like all together counted
like if I see two if I see two here that
means we as a crew only have two but is
it here
separate
yes
okay okay
m
here see do you hear the clicking
sound so I was clicking on it it just I
think it's better though to have like
two chances of a n 20 rather than the
guidance no I want the I think it's
better to have this
one I think
so here we
go
no no
please one more
inspiration ah please come on come on
that 20s happen every so often and now
is the time now now now please please
please please please please please
please please please
please I'm
I'm I'm wasted I've wasted we are
wasted oh
no not a hope then I'll kill you one or
the other no then I'll kill you why is
shadowart having this conversation
anyway I don't get
it uh what is what is the
power no honestly I I don't know why
should we even believe her like she can
say I'm coming back anyway but
no no I don't think
so ah plus that was the P
ah
well I
think tanakak karia
would choose either to a threee because
she's pissed off at the hag interrupting
her and she just wants to finish what
she started but also at the same time
she doesn't care about Marina and she
could also just take the
power
yeah but who gets it everybody or or
just one
person the girl isn't worth it well we
still didn't tell her about the brothers
and if we let her go if we let her
survive she might find out about the
brother she's going to be mad maybe it's
better for her not to know and just
continue living like
this yeah she has nothing to live for
yeah her brothers are dead anyways yeah
one person gets it A wise choice here a
staran approves kak
disapproves are we keeping it to Shadow
had automatically I hope not e what the
is this what about me de's on girl
and you're not leaving my side till you
deliver deliver the baby you where did
she get from
anywhere if I ever see you again you'll
be fertilizing this swamp what what what
was that me get out of here before I
change my mind you oh don't act
like you won't miss me bye-bye petle you
promised me be
tea oh oh okay it's for Tanaka we made a
deal with the ha in exchange to give us
great power you receive choose Auntie
eel's hair permanent Plus one bonus to
wisdom per per permanent plus one bonus
to strength Constitution dexterity
intelligence
cisma
kisma
kisma my is at plus4 right now it will
go to plus five then H yeah
yeah' no e it said e what it says plus
oh a something and then plus a yeah 18
okay 19 is
good uh
yeah all
right I don't know if that was another
step step forward really the right
choice but it seems Seems I'm just
pissed because I was trying so hard for
this stupid fight and then it ends with
this stupid dialogue interrupting me
right before I could kill
her that's just so unsatisfying man
control orb let's
see I have to eat the
hair
ooh it's like an
elevator E I don't want
to
e well and now we go through this
door where's that
go by the way let's save and now I could
I can rest now let's go should we rest
now we should rest
now
okay do he's so excitingly looking
towards there oh you see his
stand oh aarion what's up like some time
to talk what's going on I want chocolate
I have no more chocolate at home guys
there you are my friend I mean I kind of
do but not really the one
want my friend what happened why are you
drunk I have drunk not alcohol of course
a bear oh he took a little of my blood I
took all of his worth
[Music]
it
uh is is Gail okay look at
Gail as long as you're leaving me alone
you think I'd kill you just like that
darling I would never I still need you
anyway not sure will sustain me and it's
a marked impr and flies Cazador would
feed me preference of
genders sometimes he confuses
me he's very as I learned in London
Camp he seems very camp
let me turn on the light okay yeah
everyone's aggressively by yeah but not
not everybody acts like
aaran know what I mean you know what I
mean party members are you
sexual aren't we all aren't we
all what did you say the bear will
sustain me and it's a marked improvement
over the rats and flies C would fill me
ew yeah I don't really want to continue
this conversation asion I don't really
care exactly as appetizing as you'd
think why am I so cold towards him
again I'll never have to grel for him
again I think I just I was I was a
little bit you know in in a love days at
the beginning but uh I I quickly cleared
up my mind and I Can See Clearly again
so yes I will not be deceived by your
ways I don't care
exactly I can be better than him
stronger love days more py
more
oh you meant be
kinder pet bunnies that sort of thing I
I have no objection to being nice of
course once I have the power to bend
others to my
will love days I feel
every
[Music]
you we not powerless head are quite the
acid indeed they are now that I can walk
in the
sun well that opens all manner of doors
it could open coffins too coffins
too no these tooles are a gift I intend
to use to the
Fest you should do the same oh oh that
was suddenly a different tone
there uh G this he doesn't have the
exclamation mark but does he maybe need
something he'll have to speak slowly I'm
finding it quite difficult to
concentrate my condition Goring at my
insid like a teething displacer kitten
what teething displacer
kitten uh I think I have a MAG magical
artifact which would be wouldn't
wouldn't that be the third one
already you guys got to help me decide
is is anything here okay to give to
him the Watchers
guide equipped by Shadow heart equipped
by Tanaka equipped equipped the only
thing I don't have equipped is the haste
um the
pendant they don't provoke I quite like
it right now maybe oh wait oh wait
there's more
oh but
everything's wait no these
ah wasn't this something that we'll
probably never get to use but it was so
cool so I I didn't want to get rid of it
but car shirt it doesn't do anything car
shirt oh this
thing I guess
so yeah cuz nobody has a spell with
poison damage right
now
okay what okay then she will look hot
again but didn't we throw away her
clothes wait we thr away her clothes
though thank you
if we remember
correctly oh
well she needs to air out all that fire
in her heart anyway are you feeling good
it hardly has any
effect the mistra have mercy on us all
listen I need to speak to you to all of
you it'll be unconscionable of me to
remain silent I'm did I waste my
item um yeah this better be good we
wasted small fortune on you already I'm
so mean I'm so mean and the waste it
might have been no you have to know who
I was you have to know who I really am
what I am is a walking shadow of the
promise I once held so edgy what one
might call a wizard Prodigy you from an
early age could not only control roll
the weave but compose it much like a
musician or a wow such was my skill that
it earned me the attention of the mother
of magic herself mm the lady of
mysteries the goddess mistra she
revealed herself to me and she became my
teacher
mhm in time she became my
muse and later even my lover
M you make love to a
goddess
we
toas you telling me you made love to oh
yes oh yeah enjoyed each other's
company body mind and
soul but even so I desired more you see
no matter how powerful a wizard we Mor
can
become we never scratch more than the
surface of the weave mistra Keeps Us in
check there are boundaries she doesn't
let us cross yet every time I was with
her I stood on the precipice gazing into
the Wonders that lay
Beyond I sought AC cross her boundaries
uhhuh
how
oh I tried to convince her I pouted I
pleed he pouted swore my ambition was
only to serve her better but she only
smiled and told me to be contented
inconceivable As It Seems to me now I
shared a bed with a goddess yet I wasn't
satisfied damn you'll never be satisfied
I sought to prove myself worthy to her
instead we come now to the Crux of my
Folly should I share the story behind it
or would you rather head straight to its
sworded
finale
uh tell me all very
well here
goes once upon a very long time ago a
mighty Lord lived in a tower
flying Tower to be precise I'll save his
history for another time but the gist of
it is he sought to user the goddess of
magic so that he could become a God
himself he almost managed but not quite
his entire Empire netheril and crashing
down around him as he turned to stone
the magic that was Unleashed that day
was
phenomenal roing like the Prime Chaos
that outdates creation even the weave
itself could not withstand the onslaught
fractured then shattered and all magic
was lost to the Mortal Realms until the
day mistra
returned she restored the weave
reuniting all its scattered
shards or so I thought until in the
course of my studies I learned of a
book a fractured weave have been sealed
Beyond her reach uh what if I thought
what if after all this time I could
return this lost part of herself to the
goddess what lost
part
uh what your grand plan was akin to
emptying a cup of water in the sea
brilliant oh that's making fun of him
isn't it I like it I certainly thought
so sometimes there is great strength to
be found in
symbolism I was certain that this deed
of raw power draped in Romance would
convince mistra to take me by the hand
and welcome me into her hither to
forbidden
domains I was
mistaken I obtained the fabled book and
took it into my study mhm as for what
happened next mhm mhm mhm what
happened place your hand over my heart
why did you have to go down for that
show you we're like approximately the
same
height now I'm bending down quiver as
you realize Gail is letting you in into
the
dark awkward
before at least make some grunting
noises of chaos weave that lash out and
overtake you I'll do it for you this the
first
time just as
[Music]
unfair oppression just doesn't
matter
uh
yank terrifying isn't
it that is only the beginning
this nees blight this orb for lack of a
better word is bowled up inside my chest
and it needs to be fed as long as I
absorb kind of like basically both have
something in their hearts quiet that
needs me to bring them something
stabilize
however but I already gave him free
things right
so m
go on I will
erupt I don't know the exact magnitude
of the eruption but given my studies of
nether magic let's say even a fragment
of small I carry it would level a city
the size of Water Deep
what are you saying you're going to
explode and like make an explosion that
could wipe a whole
city if you're not saved or
what don't be so
[Music]
dramatic my chance upon a king's
collection of magical artifacts around
the corner we might cross paths with a
miracle Round the Bend then
again we might not all of this it must
feel like a betrayal no not really I
mean say the word and will be so
dramatic like
what I not feel feeling that concerned
about
it like I don't care that you waited a
bit to tell me that either like I mean
like it's not it's not that much a big
deal I mean there's no answer that I
like but yeah nice a great relief oh a
great relief indeed he could blow at any
moment but most of the time he's alone
in the camp from all my else so he
better explode in the camp if
anything I understand if you stand
against me I'm humbled if you stand with
me either way I will do my best not to
let you down now we're going to give
stand pre going to let if you do not
give up hope neither shall I I'll fight
I'll resist as long as I can
now I am tired of the sound of my own
voice H let us Venture
forth well uh at least he's not
suffering in the background anymore
that's
good
wonderful well well well now we shall
sleep like
Cola oh all right
uh all right a little
bit I got to sleep early really really
early today by the way so hey the good
thing is I cooked yesterday so I can
just eat that I don't have to waste time
cooking um but I also have to prep and
stuff
so I can't I can't I can't play that
long that's what I'm saying no I should
be in bed but by midnight like for real
for real with a
melatonine in me but uh even then it's
it's looking
[Music]
bad I think I'll play one more
hour and maybe Read Super chats for half
an hour
maybe
yeah yeah I'll try uh which means we
don't really have time to flirt with her
right now so let's
go I don't have time for
that Mommy is
busy why does it choose like more when I
do Auto Select
huh uh
huh
[Music]
okay let's just do
this it doesn't spit items M oh well one
over is I think not a big
deal has an awkward relationship
Stacks dogle wants to okay well if dogle
has an exclamation mark that is very
important guys dog wags his tail a small
bag clenched between his teeth oh what
did you get from
[Music]
me I don't have animal handling I'll
I'll I'll I don't want to be mean to him
I don't want to intimidate
him maybe eh that seems also mean I want
to do this but I don't know how much how
[Music]
much I'll I'll do I'll do I'll do this I
guess cuz dog Keepers do like you know I
guess this is what they do you have to
listen to me
Dogg you have to listen to
me oh my this Advantage thing is
actually
wow I get it
now
wow I don't want to you know he's he's
see he's still
happy is it money and surrenders his
fine
surrenders as
if I really like threatened him really
harshly a good boy was a good boy
scratch his tongue LS out happily his
tail wagging even
faster a
baby
cute thank you I I got a
bone it sounded like money like coins
okay wait I got more than one thing
healing potion
and okay that's
it what's a shadow heart what's a what's
her
scratch why is he glowing red is he okay
because of the friends thing I
guess oh well um we are moving
on
oh y
b
acit
Workshop can I take the stuff
goodbye potion of speed work loin potion
of speed bitter divorce what is
that letter to and letter from E what's
inside a lot of fancy rings
oh my God Missing Pets what what does
that mean what this old
potions what do they do Heart of Stone
Insanity's kiss I mean Heart of Stone I
would think yeah turn somebody into
stone
oo staff of Cronin oh oh
wait can somebody use
that like Shadow
heart kind of does well can I use
it it's oh when when nobody here really
uses stuff
[Music]
so spell cast Shadow heart
could
to9 is it does it make
sense not sure myamc use use staff more
for spell yeah that was what what I was
thinking like I do do
spells I've got a long road
ahead let's oh wait where does it go
does it go where does oh there we go hey
I'm kind of suits me it looks good on
me me what is this mushroom Circle
should mind my step what does it do wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait is that
like an exit am I done
here going
in Walking on Air k is inspired good for
you oh okay I I feel like that's a
really random place to teleport to ah
okay but we can go in every time if we
want for the
same uh C uh not coffee Circle I guess
Bing coffee is there someone inside yes
there is Connor vinder blad wait he
won't wake
up he doesn't have anything with him
anything of use I could talk to him but
I don't want
to is this
uh just a back entrance to the
house the door is
locked that's marena's
husband wait
what
oh oh yeah it does say so wait wait wait
wait oh cuz he's
Undead
n it wait is it one of the potions
[Music]
right
uh Missing Pets last
time yeah I should
search ah this
thing clumps of hair and Flash stick out
from the
Twisted so it's a
spell what how do I use
this
did I kill the girl no but uh you know
her F future is
uncertain uhhuh to release Marina oh I
wonder if we'll get a chance for that
sometime well are we done with the tea
house
now is is
this the sign that we're done
here
H okay H not as good as uh the other
stuff we explored the time before in my
opinion uh because that fight was really
annoying
and I didn't go as deep Al we're kind of
stuck here aren't
we
[Music]
then I would like
to
I'll teleport
here and I'll try can I go that way I
wonder that
one's that one would definitely attack
me right no we don't want that not
now yes now I want to uncover a bit more
of the map here
head up Northwest I'm definitely going
north um yes yes Northwest that's where
I'm going
basically reinforced great
swword almost it's like tempting me to
pick it up oopsy what was that a no I
want to point at it no no no I'm not
pointing at anything you know I I have
this like habit wait ah no don't go in
there I think that's poisonous ah I
suppose you want to hear about C no no
don't don't don't don't don't oh then
what do you want
nothing uh I was going to say that um
have this little habit when I talk I I
am the kind of person who
sometimes will point at
people during a conversation not in a
mean way you know yeah and and then so
often so often people just interrupt the
whole conversation like and don't you
point at me and H it gets on my nerves
so much every time every time I hate it
it annoys me so
much but it's mostly like when I'm not
even in
Austria I think it even happens with me
in Austria sometimes but mostly outside
of austa you get you would get
intimidated yeah the problem is I talk
with my
hands and sometimes it's not like a
straight far
pointing thing no more like you know
like a light
close somebody you know is like really
close to me we're having a fun
conversation and I'm just like oh my God
you did that and I I would like you know
when I say you I pointed them you know
just like it's not not like obviously
not meant in any mean way but some
people get immediately
so stupidly annoying about
it oh no I'm sorry then why does
everybody see it's it's such an offense
wait a second
KY
wait a second I just I just
realized can you wear
this wait I mean that
doesn't she can't
uh well oh you'll stay naked what is it
with this rabbit uh Ribbit uh Frog's
entire body shakes it ribits you look
very
poisonous um but something's wrong wrong
with you the creature's limbs shake with
effort hind legs ready to pounce I think
this is this was a human
somebody may
have
um may have uh cursed
them let's drink this and
talk hag is gone happy ah you're happy
HG is gone yes
I'm glad I could helpy happy Come prison
really frog really seems happy froggy
waa Alliance helps me after
all qu qu rabbit rabbit rabbit would you
guys be like pissed off if I pointed my
finger at you in a friendly
way would
you no thank
god
oh do I talk to you
again I do it too shiny
yay you would feel warmed you mean
warned or
warmed ice knife and detect FS cool I
mean cool thanks that's nice thank you
can we say thank
you shiny bye bye
byebye I love
frog
cute yeah yeah it's it's really just
that that I use my hands to talk with a
lot
yeah this could kind of be related to
that but I had an accident a while ago
on an airplane this was on a flight
Froman to Austria yeah it doesn't look
like I can go there
huh do I have to go from
above um on this particular flight oh
wait a
second uh I was
seated next to a Japanese lady who was
like maybe
4050 and even though she was sitting
elsewhere she was on the flight with her
daughter
apparently and
they were doing a little Europe travel I
guess maybe I'll teleport
[Music]
here and one of the countries that were
that they were visiting was Austria
and um we didn't get into talking until
like the very not not the end but like
kind of the
middle way the middle of the flight
because
uh so
I I I was the reason why something was
spilled on her I don't remember so well
anymore but I either spilled my drink or
I spilled her drink by
accident uh I think it was just water or
so like definitely not a big
deal um but yeah I spilled like this
whole flight we didn't talk but
uh yeah we were just you know like
normally I don't talk to whoever's
sitting next to
me um but you know in an airplane
especially for such a long time you're
in like a a really confined
space and it's hard to move around and
yeah so I accidentally knocked some
drink again I think it was just water
over and oh does this path not is this a
dead end was that a dead end maybe
not um and then she reacted this
Japanese lady reacted first of all like
kind of like shocked and she seemed kind
of
angry where are you
guys where are they I they went that way
oh my God
ah
uh oh okay we went here with the collab
team okay okay let's fight then
um yeah yeah she seemed kind of like
like she didn't outright like get super
angry like scream at me but like at her
expression and her silence tell told me
that she was kind of pissed
goblins very intelligent of you one of
those can summon Fighters far and wide
Ward
drum far and wide really which Ward drum
I don't see it
you fy how do out there so can I like
destroy
it she gave you the look kind of but you
know I speak Japanese and I kind of knew
she was Japanese so I I immediately was
like and I took like my my blanket my
own blanket uh to wipe up like
thankfully it was like only really on
the
table and uh a little bit of the water I
guess went on her blanket
um and so she's she was like H after I
apologized a million times she was like
okay this it's fine at least it didn't
go anywhere besides the blanket but now
I will need another blanket it's not
like that oh I see that it's not like it
like
really like became drench ah hey I was
not on it
yet it's not like it was like super
drench not at all like it was really not
that much but okay you know when you're
in a situation like that I I can oopsie
don't go there I I I kind of you know I
can understand um people will be like
automatically like oh exaggerating
everything you don't want to
like and they'll treat everything as
like a bigger deal than it is right
um I might even do the same so yeah is
there nothing in here nothing
interesting maybe over
here for sake left to trap out
for us oh really well you just stepped
on it you little
but yeah I was really apologetic
and this was like in the middle of the
flight where everybody was uh like
mostly sleeping and the the flight
attendants they just wouldn't come I
tried to call for them I'm like I don't
I'll take care of it I I'll get your new
blanket and all that so I tried to call
them but nobody would come no no no one
there was like a little little call the
cabinet tendon thingy button but I
waited for like 10 minutes on my seat I
was like on edge but nobody would
come right we fight them I don't
care don't touch me don't touch
me
um watch the
Shadows why color naked well things
happened let's fight let's fight guys
let's go look it claw sap I'll continue
my story in a moment unless you got
another reason to be here F site oh we
can do this with just normal talking as
the symbol glows power courses through
you
authority authority again can we switch
yes oh my God we
can
oh on my can she have this conversation
[Music]
perhaps how's this
work still breathing despite
everything I can
reload well I'll try this is four
minutes
ago I want I want kiaba to do the
talking
okay that's
unfortunate cuz I wasn't aaran in that
moment
okay load faster once we're in battle
I'm going to continue my
story cuz I'm I'm guessing we will be in
battle
or what do we want last time we
definitely battled them in in our collab
group Goblin
ahead
right it claw Sapp is here I don't have
to unless you got another reason to be
here fake site
exploration as the symbol glows power
courses through you what our choices are
Authority uh ah are we still looking for
house is that
so employes inside glossy coat on an
animal does she belong to the nordland
warata family huh how would I know that
your leader summoned
me wait is the goblin Temple behind this
right behind
this oh
wow are you kidding
me and I only have one inspiration are
they like connected after
all it I'll roll again I can't
critical fail this that's
ridiculous huh
all right I guess we're fighting
you
huh there's a party on celebrating a
raid we are you need to wear our war
colors he still not hostile there's nice
across the mug do it
no swinging in his face wait isn't that
what we did I feel like we did
that
h no them's the rules you follow him now
or you follow him dead we got to fight
be we
attacked
um
attack but uh what do we do about this
thing I don't remember if we even like
did anything with it
I guess we just got to kill the person
who goes up
there can we break
it it has four
okay
100% is it because it's an
object okay well that's taking care of
on my
way okay ready he so yeah I was like
waiting endlessly and then the cabin
attendants would just not
even be anywhere close by to like wave
them over so I eventually I was like I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry I'm going to I'm
going to uh I'm going to take care of
this I'll go I'll get up and I'll I'll
I'll get him I'll I'll get him I'll get
you the blanket a new blanket um she she
seemed like it was really important to
her for her to get a new blanket because
otherwise this is now unbearable you
know
having a few water drops on this blanket
it's unbearable it I swear it wasn't
like really wet but
okay so is CH no you are here yeah a
little bit extra drama it's okay it's
okay you know it's fine wait bless let's
bless
people bless hash
[Music]
plus so I went over and I uh finally
found a cabin attendant I told them I
spilled something can you please give me
a new blanket and then I had to wait
even longer like it took them quite a
long time to just give me a freaking new
blanket nothing important is ever and
then I came back and I still felt like
you know I got to make up for this cuz I
honestly I felt like like I felt pretty
bad um it didn't have like a big impact
on anything but I still felt pretty bad
about it so I tried really hard to make
up for it um I saw that she had like a
travel guide uh for Austria and so you
know I started talking to her like oh
are you going to Vienna let me help you
oh my God like I really recommend this
place so I started giving her for like
20 minutes in Japanese I told her like
my recommendations and she was so happy
about it she was like oh my God I'm so
happy that you can tell me you know like
like somebody who who's from Austria can
give me recommendations oh my God thank
you so much like she was she was
really appreciative so I think it really
made up for
it
nice yeah I honestly I just wanted to
rest too on the plane but I I felt so
bad for it so I spent like like in total
probably 40 minutes sucking up to
her ever since I spilled the
drink I gave her food and place
recommendations I lo that makes me lose
concentration too man that's so
sad oh
wow but I I and I was going to do El
blast first but then I thought they're
so close to each other I should do an
AOE you
know
wow Overkill
much
yeah in the end I did a good thing I
think it it was for her in hindsight a
good thing that I spilled water on
her
yeah oh please stream pineapple yeah I
don't know why it's doing
so the
algorithm like I put so much effort so
much sweat and money into it I would
really appreciate if the algorithm would
treated nicer
please pineapple
e
pineapple
[Music]
more
sharing with others outside of KP might
help are you saying that to me or to
them I've been trying I've been trying
and and you know the girls who were part
of the MV um like mum and Rea they've
been like retweeting it
too to help
out
no
I don't
know I can't hide anywhere
man
but I can still do it because
everybody's close by
[Music]
y
your
go
yeah Des serve so much more views
true so true what about the shark I
don't know I don't know is
she I didn't check her account did she
not retweeted that's fine like I'm not
going to force her that's that's fine
she doesn't have
to can I reach oh my god let's
go
yes can't give up not
now but
yeah uh I think it's just you know a
matter of the stupid algorithm being a
meanie to
me critical Miss let's
go never a dull moment listen to the
album instead Envy both both I want both
Listen to album and
envy I need
both I'm not even on High Ground And
that's pretty
good oh yeah ooh of course you have to
leave him with one HP
mhm album is so good you keep replaying
it thank you I'm happy to hear
that it can't attack what's going
on
absolute bless you too my
friend numbers on Spotify are increasing
more steady really I have absolutely no
idea what's going on with the streaming
numbers I need to
inquire um is there somebody there oh
yeah um
can I jump over the daggers or does
this count as I'm jumping
through it will hit
me
no
[Music]
no maybe maybe like this could this
could
work I'll take a little bit of damage
whatever
[Music]
ah I mean nobody can tell me who's
playing this game that this doesn't
sometimes happen to them like they
select the wrong thing
cuz especially with something like that
weapon thingy it's like so hard hard to
[Music]
see but at least it wasn't actually a
human
companion but just
a
um
SP to the oh why did you why why did we
do that why did we
that well well well
how are we going to can I like shoot
that other guy from here I wonder I'll
try
it oh yeah let's end this I often
hit the floor or air yeah yeah that too
I attacked the ground to many
[Music]
times you feel it you get
it there really needs to be an AR you
sure popup if you're targeting an Ellie
yeah at least that would be nice yeah
cuz that's like why would you want to do
that why what when when would I want to
with a damaging attack want to hurt my
Ally maybe they're just like
purposefully not giving us this luxury
because you know they're thinking if
you're stupid then we can't help you
then you deserve this but it's not about
stupidity it's just you know I'm
lucky good press
on
man
oh
wow okay okay okay can I get this one
again wonderful I love that I
can um bring like spawned over here
that's wonderful what
now now well I don't know you won't
really be able to do 70 that's actually
not so bad 70% kidding me
but path is interrupted I didn't even
see
that
um well I don't know if the weapon can
handle this dude alone it might be
sometimes it gets really good hits
but it's kind of stupid um have to keep
going
I I'll I'll try to get there just in
case oh yeah I forgot about all my all
my summons uh where are they I can't
summon them now I forgot about
them but most of the time those summons
are kind of the weapon is actually
one of the better summons oh here he
comes I can dis fell
oh well well
well I hear it again oops I hit it
again
oh it is what it is he'll just you know
what he he'll just stay
here yeah maripan maripan I hate
marzipan I guess she said what's the
plan
um well so far we had a pretty good
track record with guiding bolts
today go here of course you can't get
there of course you
can ah
n no
just no if he was able to shoot an arrow
from there then you're certainly
able ah it I'm not doing anything
except I'll heal
four only that's such a weak he can't
even catch my
breath and now the weapon please thank
you can we finish it with the weapon ah
ah you want to try some more
ah why can't the weapon attack let me
attack with the
weapon there it
is go go please end
it do me a favor
no this would been so good
incoming nice movement nice
movement why no
jump I need a
Fone
yes yay victory victory
victory I
[Music]
hope let's go now let's pick up
everything oh it's it needs at least
three more movement left damn it damn
it ah no uh uh uh how to how to how to
dispel
uh where is that dagger you guys talking
about oh now it's done well
what was it where was
it I it was it was still there when I
was looking for it and then while I was
looking for it Focus my my mind on it it
disappeared okay okay it wasn't gone at
first
here
okay there was nothing interesting in
right so I'm not I don't think I'll go
back in
there I guess it's just a way
around if you don't want to fight and
you don't want to
talk
is that how it is give col some clothes
I don't have anything I don't think I
have
anything like this one she can't really
wear
right oh she can
but want to dance she's not proficient
with it can she still carry it though
like is it is it a
problem
and she's not proficient in any armor
well then she's got to stay
naked
yeah she'll stay
naked a dis advantage on well then we
don't want it I can't believe we're in
the Goin Camp I didn't want to go here I
don't want to go where I should be
going I don't want to advance in this
game I want to mess around oh
[Music]
hello are you guys like what are they
doing goodbye
goodbye
open should we try to talk to them as
well oh we should do a short rest though
we can keep going a little longer now oh
they having a drink maybe they're also
doing a tea party with a c of tea all
well that ends let's check it out
could we can go north in the blinded
Village before going to okay maybe I
will hello they're ignoring me
hello looking at a future true soul I
like those feathers boss Raglin says I'm
next in
line what what about the
Priestess hell no
tribe uh tribe tribe
tribe sound like a idiot we
could fight these too huh wonder if the
gods are watching can fight anybody
where does this
[Music]
lead enchantments enchantments
what
oh no I don't want to do I don't want to
do Sports I don't want to I don't want
to do situps I don't want to do any of
that no the you can't make me I'm
too weak for It Anyway the overwhelming
Authority that you've used on others
only infinitely stronger and turned
against you your vision CL you
in a dark I don't want to play any more
R Shadow Escape nothingness in every
direction
then there are three figures before you
an armored male elf exuding power and
command lag handsome younger man quick
easy
smile and a pale young woman with even
paler
eyes These are My
Chosen they speak for
me Aid their search for the prison
and you will be worthy to stand beside
them n in my presence stop can't do
push-ups I refuse I reject oh
oh what why why is she using that why
does she know that she needs it now and
what does it do what's she
doing
oh you feel energy pulsing from the
artifact lifting the pain from you
pushing the voice
away my power
grows my forces
gather the Reckoning
draws huh context
please H don't give me that look I don't
know what just happened any more than
you do are you sure we should keep going
what the nice one Shadow heart yeah
what happens when she's not in your
party powerful as hell I'll remember
this happening to
us yeah uh explain what is that I don't
know not
exactly all I know is it's important I
get it back to Boulder's Gate at any any
cost
mhm sorry I was so focused on that cute
face that you have right
now hey don't don't make that face that
doesn't look
cute yeah I need you to level with me
you know everybody else is opening up to
me as you can see Kash Gail Starion it's
only you who still keeping their stupid
little secrets
I I am I am a servant of sha mhm my home
is a secret cloer in Boulders
gate I need to bring that artifact back
there no matter what I can't tell you
anymore this Mission required utmost
secrecy she's under an NDA we all
submitted to having our memories
suppressed so that we couldn't betray
Sha's confidence oh you don't even know
I reach my contact in the city I'll have
my memories
restored until then I have to go the
artifact with my life there you have the
that's a really functional efficient NDA
just making
people lose their memory World entitled
to our can't tell them if you don't know
you don't
remember
yeah
um I don't know what to say well I'm not
that mad against again like I really
don't care um just like with Gail I I
don't I it's not a big deal but
um yeah your faith is your own concern
not
mine I didn't think you'd react so
pragmatically I don't know I don't think
so either sooner yeah you should have
like I don't
care um thanks for
showering
wow I sound so like
authori of of of
auor
uh
authoritative
[Music]
authoritative that sounds so stupid
too
uh
H yeah gu tell me more
we've got more pressing matters to
you're right I have to go to sleep
soon why did it happen here though out
of nowhere is that just
random can't you what do you mean there
we
go what's
inside the only good thing is the grease
bottle the rest is r
honey invisible portal through the
mountain oh misty
ey make sure to you're about to end it
will be bitterly difficult for a party
of your
oh
no that's act
too
oh thank you Game for warning me before
doing something
stupid
[Music]
then actually has it been an hour hour
since I said I'll play one more hour I
feel like it might have
been not sure let's go
north
north more or less God damn
it
I mean I'm I'm struggling to find
oh what's happening here and
now just
listening go on then how did they miss
this like why is there so much going on
in this Village rescue The Gnome look
what we got here another little birdie
war in to
fly stop this thing okay we will save
there's no one done flat those wings
some more and I'll you a
worm and you hope you got a stomach for
Hees I
I I had to have a stomach for Heights
the a day um so I think I I am
fine what the hell is that you doing
what's it bloody look like we're
teaching this ear pipsqueak to
fly um maybe I'm the better person to
teach him
that Rel lease a gnome at once you want
this little cave lurking watchs it find
your own he ours as the symbol glows
power CES through Authority again oh no
Authority I have more
Authority I I will not be authorized by
you I do not authorize your Authority
um let's do intimidation I Won't Let You
harm a defenseless being even though
this is out of character but it gives me
the most bonuses so
it let's go 15 oh ah there we go that's
just what I
need
the Goblin's nostrils flare as if trying
to judge you through smell
alone we're leaving yeah you better
better know ain't we supposed to bring
it to I said we're
leaving there's plenty of sport and Rich
pickings out there for
us right then I'm inspired she's
inspired
so did the right thing bye-bye
yeah yeah get rid of the work how do we
stop this thing where is The Gnome there
he is how do how do I how do I how do I
stop it
uh maybe
inside release breake lever breake lever
uh breake
lever wow I'm such a genius wow
so oh hey you stopped at the perfect
position is that just uh
scripted let's talk to him first before
we let him down cut me
loose what's in it for me see we're back
in character free me and find
out
oh
no I'm back come on what are you waiting
for I don't know I don't like your
attitude come on what are you waiting
for okay if you if you're not going
to say anything else then I guess I have
to there we
go magara that that like Mama Mia pent
thugs well get on with it she's been
spinning for ages yeah I
mean I'm surprised she's not covered in
vomit at this point um I freed you
little composition would be nice uh what
get get on with what get on with what
you saved me now you'll extort me yes
that's how this works yes yes uh yes my
reward now as expected
coer hard to proof take my pack if you
can find it the only reason those
goblins caught me was its weight I'll
travel lightly from now on yeah yeah I
guess you learned your lesson you're a
little far from home for a deep gnome
uh-huh is that so ignorance is alive and
well it seems oh wow what did I say
something aren't restricted to the
underd dark you know I've lived in
Boulders gate for years EXC I'm in
search of a friend for making an
assumption
see this I gave it to him years ago
before I left home I found it around the
neck of a thug in the lower
City it was speckled with blood my
friend nowhere to be
found but I still have hope I have
reason to believe he's in the underd
dark mhm hopefully I'll pick up his
trail from there I was in the underd
dark always help my friends beond the
dark right on that
note I bid thee farewell
if we should meet
again well we will have met again yeah
true very very logical conclusion
bye-bye where did you leave your
stash in the Sheep
maybe where is
it maybe inside or oh wait there's a
there's a hatch in here
o
n is this
thing smoke powder s w okay and some
yummy
food boots boots Speedy light feet ooh
Speedy Sparks Sparks spit up five times
when the wearer dashes or take similar
action during combat they gain free
lightning TS Cool Leo and glorious
vaulting oh triple triple you jump
distance
wowers
e okay o Pitchfork maybe we can throw
the Pitchfork at
someone um why is she walking she's
encumbered what like are you becoming a
cucumber or what stop it that's not good
what's hiding here don't become
vegetable oh oh she's become too heavy
okay that's that's that's not becoming a
cucumber I don't understand what you're
saying to me
speak clearly to me lady and do you want
to wear
these or should I give it
to maybe
him I don't know I feel like he might
Dash more often than I
do where are the other
boots
where' the other boots
go I'm
blind there
okay um here helmet what's really heavy
here I'll give that to her sort by
weight
oh is the heaviest
here oh oh yeah my camp supplies are
really heavy here you you carry those
nice okay easy so shadowed wine
barrel barel up
S oh one of
those wow pretty
shoes I like
um
okay I think I looked at everything okay
well worth exploring once again oh I can
send them to
Camp oh wait
oh
Nar learned a new thing that was his
stuff right that I was supposed to find
what is this
though Shadow heart's attention is fixed
on a damaged old statue just like me for
real for
real
oh why is it better the other way wait
we should keep
moving uh yeah what happened you already
know as much as I
do best ignore it as long as it doesn't
hamper us too
much
okay I'm still curious about it though
any books lying around
no man man it will stay a mystery for me
wait book is that a book no that's a
stone God damn
it why not
book okay I should probably leave it a
man
man but look at our crew wow up here on
the
hill beautiful I will
safe and we'll read super chats for half
an hour cuz I I have to if I don't end
it like somewhat early today I I'm not
going to be able to sleep and I have to
get up so early tomorrow before
10 before night
even and even
before
yeah how will I
survive
yeah he can't use
those who can who can them then
her car look good right
probably oh wait what
happened Shadow
heart Shadow
heart
what what is this with this like when I
put something on there and it just
doesn't switch it out I'm so
annoying I'm fine of skipping super
chats but I I'm I'm how behind am I I
need
[Music]
to not that much anymore
really outside of members oh yeah that
was one big member stream
there oh well uh
uh
[Music]
well you want the supplies bag in your
inventory so the camps get out sorted
into it what Out Auto sorted into
it uh okay I don't really
know
just focus on anniversary
preps well well well I'll be once again
you know for um for the thing the flying
thing that I did I had to travel quite
far uh I mean I didn't have to but I
chose to the location I chose was pretty
far and where I'm going tomorrow is also
really far my mom lives really far I was
going to like like I asked my brother if
he could like drive me because with with
a car it would be much
faster he doesn't have a car anymore but
we we would have rented it but my
brother has no time so now it takes me
more than double the time
mhm
yeah really I'm like spending like half
of the day
traveling uh and I have to go really
early cuz they no no good routes later
on
mhm and they will just just take me even
longer and they're just stupid routes
oh I never went to my uh mom's
place uh like the full
trip um with like public transport like
it was either fully by car or Halfway by
a
car so it's it's
stupidly far and complicated
H yeah H I need to pack my stuff
for tomorrow I'm
bringing a good amount of stuff but
right now since I didn't unpack it yet
it's still like a a reasonable size I
wonder if I when I have to leave it can
if I can uh pack it back together into a
reasonable size probably
not yeah M I have I now have my own tent
wow yeah right now it's
prepacked so I'll pack I'll pack all
those like supplies I don't want to I
don't want to stay too clearly yet what
it is but yeah
camping and um how big is it is uh it
said two to three
people
yeah did you bring any s'mores no no I I
don't really like I don't like
marshmallows um but I have some ideas I
have to like think a bit more about like
you know I have plenty of time to flesh
out my ideas when I'm like
traveling did I have s'mores before good
question I think
not actually I had marshmallows out of
campfire
before is the tent orange
color
no no no but you know I was actually
lucky like first when I was looking at
at at tents just normally um like they
came up with like mostly green colors I
guess people want their tents to blend
into the nature um but the green not
pretty um but I was lucky orange is also
quite a popular color for some reason to
um uh produce tents
as so uh
I I yeah I there there was many many
choices for orange tents as
well unfortunately I didn't find like a
pink tent or so so I just wanted orange
yeah yeah it's it might also be good to
stand out yeah and some sometimes you
may want your tent to be hidden but
sometimes you may want it to stand out
so you can find it
again yeah yeah yeah
depends on what you want to do be hidden
or or not so
much yeah I didn't even tell you I
bought like this really expensive camera
um I was I was going to borrow some my
friends uh my friend's family's GoPro
but they didn't find it uh like they
were looking for it for like 3 4 days I
was like uh so what about the GoPro I
you kind of need it and they're like
sorry I couldn't find it so I'm like
okay okay I guess I'm buying my own
now uh yeah I have a vlogging camera but
the thing is I want for this like
specifically I want a camera that I can
even mount on my on my head or on my
chest so I can you know do handsfree and
um yeah uh you know I want you guys to
see my POV when I'm doing stuff I think
it will be more like nice you know so I
was was first thinking of a GoPro but
somebody sent me uh a new product that
is like kind in some ways better in some
ways maybe on the same level like as the
GoPro um it's a it's called insta
360 Go free or something like that they
have they had several models before but
this new one is like uh yeah pretty cool
it's like about the size of a
GoPro and but you can make it even
smaller and the cool thing is is like
magnetic you can like snatch it onto
anything that's magnetic
easily and it also comes with like some
some cool mounting options has like a
clip so I can put it on a hat or I can
put it on uh my t-shirt because it comes
like with like a magnetic necklace thing
that you put under your T-shirt I guess
and then yeah you put the camera on top
of it over the
T-shirt yeah there's like a bunch of uh
mounting options and and it's pretty
cool pretty cool action camera I looked
at some reviews before deciding to buy
it and my conclusion was
well it's it's roughly the same price as
a
GoPro it's in some ways better in some
ways maybe not better like it has its
pros and cons but it looks
cuter and it's it's you know not a GoPro
maybe it's cool to buy something that
not a GoPro cuz everybody gets a GoPro
what if I don't get a
GoPro yeah I had some some some nice
features I would say that are um yeah
helpful for me uh I like the mounting
options so
yeah it can erase the support in the
footage and make it look like it's yeah
yeah yeah I think I think like the the
the the store person staff told me oh we
have this like
invisible uh like selfie stick basically
or like tripod thingy I'm like what do
you mean invisible I didn't buy it but
apparently yeah there's like this
mounting
stick uh and I I guess as you just said
it it like deletes it yeah I guess like
because 360 I don't know I didn't need
it though at the moment so I'm I just
want the the first person POV
and I'll be wearing gloves and then you
can see my hands reaching out to things
and
yeah it's an insta 360 camera I have one
is so useful is what I took all those
videos with at
ctw yeah Ki
POV indirect promotion of my album
filming videos in my
POV yeah so that's what I went out to do
I went swimming and I bought that camera
H so I I haven't used it yet but I hope
it will be easy to use I have to charge
it
too I have to prepare everything now so
what I have to do I have to charge the
camera uh download some stuff for the
travel to watch uh I I want to download
there should be new episodes of Wheel of
Time now so maybe I'll I can download
that uh so I can watch it
offline and I got to bring all my
camping and I I don't know brain
empty portable
charger oh don't worry like in terms of
like electricity I won't be far from
electricity um don't worry
about
um
um you making me nervous um I might
still have to do some work related
things right now before I leave I
think oh yeah I have to record something
a short video okay okay so thank you
guys for letting me go off the hook uh
it still has been almost 5 hours we're
at 4 hours 50
minutes so short
stream if I get back earlier than
expected on Sunday then I could
do maybe Super Chat reading or something
like that if I if I I don't know depends
I don't know when I'm getting
home uh wish me
l
wish me luck wish me
[Music]
luck I'll be back on Monday streaming on
Monday okay and we
say byebye thank thank you for watching
today it was fun I wish I could have
played more oh one of these days I have
to schedule Boulder's Gate on a day
where I can spend like 8 hours playing
it where I'm not time
constrained
yeah so much for a tea party man I'm
going to make some tea now how about
that I'm going to make my own tea
h fine I'll make my own
tea
[Music]
byebye