foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
assistant
oh my God
sweet wobbly it's way too wobbly
oh my God what a hot mess
oh sure
what the [\h__\h] am I moving
oh Funky Music and you don't even hear
it yet
it's really funky though
uh I don't understand I I set it in
Window mode but it always opens in
non-window mode I don't understand why
give me a moment please oh God this is
so wobbly
my weapon is so wobbly
oh [\h__\h]
oh
YouTube is slow
music is not playing ah
wobble wobble I think it's attached
to my boobies that's why
I feel like the bgm is also asking me
why
I don't know why
so
miraculously for no particular reason
the chat is working again
I'm like like recently
it's gonna be loud
I think
prepare your ears
[Music]
I told you I told you
I told you
foreign
but
the game is
about cool music right
let me make it quiet though it's too
loud
and I'm supposed to have bad eyesight
right like on this game
Maybe
like around this
[Music]
okay
why does it not start in Window mode
though I don't get a I pressed Window
mode it doesn't work
[Music]
my whip
let me attach it to someone else
something else okay
oh no it was attached to my hair I had
seems
okay that's fine that's better
Hill
now
that shouldn't be so weirdly wobbly
anymore
what do you think this thing I think
made its appearance
during
um
is this mirrored
during yakuzao
hmm I think it's uh one of my Yakuza
weapons you guys said I might need a you
know weapon
for this stream I don't think they use
this weapon
I've seen like guns but also some
non-guns but I don't know how fitting
this is
do they use this kind of web what's it
called again Morningstar do they use it
in Hotline Miami
for sure no
yeah no nah sort of they probably use a
bath though right I made this a bit
higher and a bit lower in game
[Music]
no I said Lola lower
too loud in my ears we're looking louder
so uh this game I saw both on Senpai
playing it a little bit
so I understand it's a stressful game
uh I will probably be bad at it
it's too quiet TV8 no are you sure about
that let's see let's see I I I need to
be babied into it oh yeah but don't say
if I played a while ago
um
and then I know it says continue but it
didn't really start let's start properly
oh hello camera what I'm here to tell
you how to kill people oh I know
I know how
but feel free to tell me do I have to
press something to continue have you
continue talking miles okay
this game is controlled with your wazzo
keys and mouse
oh no you mean what's the right press
the left Mouse button to punch aim for
the face once you've knocked someone out
you have to finish him
oh okay to do this you press space ah
finishing move is space
you guys are you sure yeah punch and
spit yeah okay thank you for explaining
it it's like I'm a child do you
understand me don't mess this up okay
okay
do they not see me yet uh
what what I was kind of stuck on him
when I press space and I have to press
Mouse button again you didn't tell me
that dude
all right now you should try killing the
next guy but use the bat in the Red Room
over here okay
but one doesn't he already see me press
the right Mouse button we're next to it
to take it then you press the left Mouse
button to swing it
uh does that go for you fix skull did it
I'll have to test it out I'm not sure
right right Mouse button so pick it up
live passes okay
see me
okay it's a bat right
what I didn't what well done so let's
get to the guns Charlie wow you guys are
just moving on so quickly you go and get
the shotgun in the Blue Room you do it
the same way you picked up the bed just
press it yeah okay I'll do a shift
button to look for enemies out of view
oh I can do that it is very useful for
not getting yourself killed you can
press the scroll wheel to lock onto
enemies oh
oh okay that's already too many controls
my friend that's already too much just
make sure to place your Crosshair over
the first uh uh right Mouse button to
grab shift to look left to shoot scroll
to lock okay
it's too fast now go ahead and kill the
guy in the yellow room okay
why don't we just stay with the Batman
uh what shift yeah no I mean I see him
am I locked on now I'm trying to lock
but I still can't move it around
what
the Batman
I don't think this is he's looking at me
why he not shooting
yellow room oh
ah okay now it works
wait I threw it
oh guys
[Laughter]
oh man what
oh no oh
my heart turned
all right clicked oh we're gonna do it
again
he's not even gonna comment on me dying
in the tutorial that's really nice but
stay okay
yeah okay okay okay okay okay
Charles I got confused
okay
okay but maybe it's good this way so I
can um
get everything deeper into my brain
okay lock
left click
[Laughter]
all right that about sums up the basics
however there is always more tricks to
learn you can throw any weapon you pick
up as I did but then I should have acted
faster to get it back the door is going
crazy
by pressing your right Mouse button you
can use doors to knock enemies over oh
really
guns are very loud and will alert your
photos oh what is that is that
cockroaches or what is that
on the screen so plan your moves then
use melee weapons when you can God damn
it you just get yourself killed anyway
that's exactly what's gonna happen yes
won't you yeah
how did you know wait we left one alive
didn't we
why would we do that oh God
hey I don't see anything
[Music]
what is this place is this a cell no I
wouldn't have a bathtub
and who do we have here why is the horse
talking to me
oh you don't know who you are
you guys friendly
maybe we should leave it in that way
ah it's the chicken man but I know you
yeah of course you know me because
you're KFC
look at my face with bed before yeah
yeah I know of course I know I know you
you're Timothy
probably yeah
Mommy oh yeah I know you why do you
think you don't know me Mama you're so
forgetful I don't know you why are you
here oh it's funny that the chicken is
the only one who knows me though
You're No guest of mine
why is the chicken there
perfect
[Music]
do you really want me to reveal who you
are knowing oneself means acknowledging
one's actions as of lately you've done
some terrible things
you don't remember me I'll give you a
clue does April the 3rd mean anything to
you what did I do on April the 3rd that
was that's fairly that recent a month
ago
they rewrote the game for me
but what did I what did I do on April
the 3rd
[Music]
we probably streamed
what was it Kelly's birthday
that was after corn caught pizza so it's
not that well that wouldn't be anything
because that is only me doing good
things for the world
I believe that was the day of our first
encounter
nah you're wrong Timothy our first
encounter was 20 20.
one
did I Deb you in 2021 or 2020
period
2020 right it sounds crazy
[Music]
you look like you might be remembering
something
[Music]
[\h__\h] 2020.
is this game playing in my memory
what is this
oh can I play some games here this looks
like a game console fun
see no people oh this is after I killed
everybody
oh
yeah yeah
thing here
you have one new message babe
hi this is Tim
at the bakery the cookies that you
ordered should be delivered by now a
list of ingredients are included make
sure that you read them carefully click
so many Timbs
okay I'd take
[Laughter]
[Music]
I
I just messed something up
[Music]
did I just read the game's mind
wow
[Music]
the target is a briefcase discretion is
of the essence leave Target at Point F32
inside the dumpster failure is not an
option we'll be watching you
Timothy that wasn't cookies what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm so disappointed I guess I gotta make
my own after muffins my next
is the car where's your dumpster
after cookies my next big thing will be
no after mapping to my next big thing
will be cookies
[Music]
it opens but where's the dumpster
I guess we're going by car
that's a sick car it looks so futuristic
or also at the same time just looks like
a fridge
Prelude the Metro
no his name is Richard what
I thought you were Timothy when I'm I'm
Richard now shift to aim what I mean
shift to aim oh
do I have something to shoot with
oh no
oh it's just my face oh
I can't print there we go ah
tell me that you had to continue
like
punching after you were already locked
on
I pressed right button again I'm I'm bad
at this
okay
take the bat what is this can I read
this no okay
um here the best thing would be to lock
on
and then hey let me finish him where is
he finished
are they sometimes just finished
immediately I guess once they bleed
they're finished
okay
it's not that kind of game oh where I
could pick up things and read them
[Laughter]
room that you
that you died in okay that's very nice
of them
where's the other dude okay this time he
didn't hear me
or see me
he came so fast
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh oh I was thinking
Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
Mommy
what is this a crowbar maybe crowbar is
better
he has a knife I think
come here come here
nice
nice okay okay okay okay
now that I'm playing it
the various uh impressed by Photon
Senpai because she was able to
uh kill everything so fast is the knife
better I wonder no is that a gun
oh yeah bye
he's dead though it seems like he's dead
wait that's a TV or what go to car why
is it shaking
what am I carrying
huh oh no oh no
oh
uh [\h__\h] what what is my weapon though
okay now he didn't see me
a briefcase that's so useless but I need
it huh
okay well
just don't panic wait there's a crowbar
there
um
come here
I mean he had one too
I can't pick it up ah
oh man
okay
I just I just gotta be I'm
[Music]
well a briefcase is not very efficient I
can't do much with this there's a
there's over there now like a big rifle
can I pick that up please just go to the
car maybe I should
I can't I can't
you guys
can't
Buy
stupid I need to fight I know I know I
know
um
come here
bye
[Music]
this is a big big challenge already
this is very difficult
uh because I hope so
finish them too
okay
[Music]
it took so long
okay Sage clear go to class okay now I
can go
I swear I was pressing space like
frantically uh what is this
[Music]
ew
it was so messy
that's a dumpster
who's there I can hear you I know you're
there
stage clear it says lies oh the the part
of the briefcase is clear is there any
weapons here no
okay fist fight first fight
but he's kind of bad and I can't why can
I not log on to him
before I could
chapter clear
I can't pick it up either ah because I'm
throwing up where why why are you so
sensitive
don't be so sensitive
well tutorial complete
uh this was not gonna be so easy is it
oh
three pounds no 32 000 points until next
weapon unlocked how many did I make it's
hard to read
seventeen thousand
it was hard to read man
execution
exposure exposure C plus wow
what
new mess
Mommy
oh my god um bird mask nice oh it's just
like ah like like burglars do like when
they walk in the store
and they have to put on the mask uh so
that people don't know who they really
are
makes a lot of sense so are we like
am I gonna Rob them or am I gonna like
buy talks to them is it like the you
know a little conversation oh yeah okay
no killing this time
hi there man haven't seen you around but
something might have happened to you you
seem really down over losing your
girlfriend don't remember seeing you
after that what is that accent
maybe we should talk about something
else so app for a midnight snack huh oh
don't worry about it it's all the ha I
don't and my my accent is
trying to go for a Texas accent but now
British is mixing in
good to see you have a nice night
wait so I I what what happened what
who is that what is that is that beer
and what now do I leave or do I kill
people
I can't okay
okay I guess I'm leaving
you gave me some free drinks wow thank
you
April 8th oh
yeah are we back in my memory or
a bit
oh new message
[Music]
hello it's Linda I need a babysitter
right away got a few kids that need to
be disciplined here I'm at a seventh
straight make sure you have a long talk
with them I really need someone to get
through today these Rascals and like
last time please be disgraced that
sounds
like I need to kill people but I hope it
will be your children and that's all
just like a
cover for I don't know
uh adult people
discipline means that boss you sure you
want to be disciplined with the weapon I
have in my hand currently
Richard
let's go Richard
you bought a name Richard
where are they
okay
it can't be so difficult in the
beginning
yeah I'll get him I'll get him
[Music]
why is the range of space so bad eh
Mommy
oh there's one here too
oh [\h__\h] wait uh um
but he'll see oh he'll shoot me uh maybe
go maybe let's first
I don't know he's got a gun too but
[Laughter]
which side I'll go here too
[Music]
it's way too loud
I need like what do you call that thing
that makes guns quieter hmm
silence or something like that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] all this is difficult
you need to be very aware of your
surroundings it seems
okay
okay I can do this I can do this
[Music]
oh oh
the rest is not coming for me
Sean how am I not dead and discovered
yet
what
okay now I'm invincible
which one
okay this one
here
or was this just the one specifically I
had to kill I know he's he's a he's dead
nevermind okay
[Music]
I'm so I'm so so good at this
I'm such a good babysitter I hope I get
paid extra for the clean job than I did
twelve thousand points
B minus oh that's better than before
though I had a c before
new
masks Tony
all right is it the pizza place oh it's
a pizza place
oh do you wanna maybe make me a corn cup
Pizza what do you mean you don't have
corn cob Pizza what the [\h__\h]
wait isn't this the same guy just
working at a different place hi there
welcome oh you don't need to order
your pizza's already done I had a
feeling you were on your way here
well let's just leave it at that for now
shall we don't worry about paying it's
on the house
did that sound like Texas accent baby
a pizza yeah yummy so good with corn and
pineapple best pizza
yes no well at least one person said yes
[Laughter]
start off thank you
because I always have to run over to
this thing
Oh Thomas from the methadone clinic
we've scheduled the short beating for
you tonight we're at uh Northwest
184th Street Apartment 105.
I don't worry we know this question is
is of importance to our clients
uh that was later on an Austrian accent
jump
wait didn't that it sounds like
terminated to you
well then good you have good good
recognition skills
is that how Arnold talks yeah that's
because that's how austrians with a
thick accents talk in English
can I switch
is that what what that strangers was
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
what a bait I thought this was through
easy having him right there with no one
behind except that one dude who didn't
notice me what the [\h__\h] okay I wait is
that person gonna like come closer
where is he now
[Music]
Panic oh my throat is gonna be [\h__\h]
man
[Music]
different massive different stats oh
okay well I like the chicken mask for
some reason I feel a connection to it
ah
mean maybe I should actually take the
BET and then because I was already now
taking the bat before finishing him what
if I take it and then go up to the top
left guy who has a gun that's more
dangerous like he will come up to kill
me before I can finish this dude
um
I didn't really want to do that
[\h__\h]
oh but the throwing is also very
efficient so apparently even though it
was an accident
knife throwing very I mean yeah
good aim necessary though
okay okay
um
[Music]
this time and y'all
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh okay
okay uh okay oh no oh yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
no
where'd he go
okay
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that that's like a
bazooka what I have oh four out of six
rounds left okay okay
bazooka
[Music]
okay one's on the toilet
okay that's the only ones left on the
floor
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
oh he didn't hear me what
me
okay okay can I uh take a gun with me to
the eh
come on
right in front of him oh man okay can I
take it to the next floor
yeah okay wonderful oh dear
[Music]
what is that is that a weapon
it's considered a weapon
[Music]
do I lose my weapon now no okay I still
haven't ah
too many shots fired
um what does this do
oh this hot water I can take it um
maybe it's a nice quiet kill you know
a well wonderful wow impressive and
where's my other weapon no no
Don't Panic bro
what kind of crew the water was not
efficient in the way I used it though
um okay move
my heart is tokidoki
quiet kill because otherwise there's
like 10 of them coming after me
have to do it somehow it does
um
uh wait wait
wonderful yeah that's good that's good
that was a nice quiet kill he's dead
right you see you see
yeah
he's not bleeding but
he's definitely dead and he looks like a
lobster now
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
but that room is open huh
oh God
[Music]
how long will it cook
let me cook
can I get more water please more more
water no
okay I am
let's see
[Music]
um the door is even closed but did he
hear me
[Music]
oh oh no no okay that can happen
okay
bye
what maybe after that nah
[Music]
blur them out
I'm gonna move faster
goodbye
[Music]
he opened the door
well if he comes back I can try I can
hide behind it
they ignore the dead dude yeah I'm
hoping for the same person to come out
but
no
[Applause]
Thor
what did I do
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
that could have been so good that could
have been so good I could have been so
good
laughs
all right but that somehow could work
what if I just make this guy see me high
nice oh he dead he's dead okay okay
[Music]
one down we're in the rest
they got guns though oh I should go into
the room before they walk into it and
and then yeah
because now they're gonna chill there
forever
[Music]
okay the more you know
I'll I'll just
oh
one round ooh one round
[Music]
that's okay
please don't come no I'm on here I'm not
here yeah okay okay after a while
they're like whatever and they go away
okay okay go away go away
I could even take this one that has 12
rounds now I feel a little bit more safe
going into the situation
foreign
[Music]
so Tactical
people I don't want to mess it up
[Music]
no no this works okay
ah
[Music]
he's alive [\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
what weapon what weapon do we have oh
[\h__\h] no not this
[\h__\h] that
I know where the gun
gun France
it's pretty clear
you scared me you're scared me in front
of your
foreign
[Music]
okay remember I have a gun there okay
fog
okay how did I do this
[Music]
come here
he was faster they're so fast but okay
that was the strategy that I used
[Music]
I threw my water huh
that's okay
[Music]
hello
see me
okay okay
[Music]
I wanna go
I wanted to pick up the weapon can you
even pick that one up
I thought I should be fast and pick up
one of the weapons but I ignored that
part man
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
that's not a weapon
it's not
I think I need a throat candy
the police is gonna come to my apartment
again thinking someone is being
strangled to death
um
God
oh [\h__\h] hell
I'm still 10.
wait
no I think that one I'll still kill
silently if I manage to bait him again
successfully
[Music]
you can see how bad I would be in
baseball because the timing is of the
essence as well and baseball isn't it
[Music]
not my specialty
[\h__\h]
that [\h__\h]
oh man
um there is no gun there but I have a
gun
what if I go now
[Music]
sorry guys
sorry
I'm getting better see I got a system
this is I think this is how you play the
game you fail and then you succeed oh
there's a gun there now hmm
I think we'll wait for them to come in
and then bait them to
[Music]
he made the move
I didn't miss right I'm just not as I I
can't I didn't
[Music]
oh
wow I missed I was locked on
as far as I know
now it's not a gun anymore there that's
really sad
yeah better to be
[\h__\h]
oh God damn it ah God damn it
foreign
hi I'm here
come here
[Music]
I just wear a heart monitor while
playing this game huh
nice that was that was a good one that
was a home run
ah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
okay wait wait he's patrolling now
I'm gonna
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
there's only one left there and there's
one up there okay
and there's one over there but he
doesn't matter yet okay
your next buddy
oh he's got a friend over there though
um
maybe maybe I can do it like a somewhat
silent kill
if he he's not gonna come to the door
though is he
what about this one this one this one
comes to the door I think
ah Mamma Mia
foreign
what am I doing this whole time I'm
always throwing
figuratively speaking
[\h__\h]
I don't have the courage
[Music]
[\h__\h] room
I don't like that
why would you do that
[Music]
come back
or anyone really
[Music]
that's no that's not gonna work out
that's that's not that's not gonna work
out
[Music]
can they see me no okay
foreign
no why did I kick the door
fro
yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
oh [\h__\h]
oh there's so many in that room now what
the [\h__\h] the [\h__\h] I need like a AOE
damage
does this weapon even do AOE damage
because it makes a big bubble
[Music]
fog
[\h__\h] that's impossible it only has two
shots
let's take this one my savior
[Music]
he's also unlocking a completely
different route which is difficult
ah he's gone
going somewhere else now
but if I shoot they're all Gonna Come
but I'll just run
I was [\h__\h] up
oh don't worry my friends my my best
friend
but it's still it's even more now but oh
they're all [\h__\h] camera
if I believe it man
ah
don't let the door hit you on the way
out as they like to say right okay how
about
trying to get the door to be my friend
[Music]
come on at least one at least one has to
leave the room please
[Music]
I don't have many shots left either
shotgun may help the big one
oh no
[Music]
at least the door doesn't hurt me huh
okay stay there door
[Music]
[Applause]
listen oh bait bait come and see me
someone see me
oh they don't look here
look at me look at me
[Music]
hi
what what what look
s Sure oh
wait
[Music]
oh yeah
what is this weapon I have now it looks
like it goes boom pretty big
of them all okay there's one down there
and there's two up there
[Music]
um masturbated yeah
why what are you talking about guys
what
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah
nice nice okay happy I am happy now
oh [\h__\h] there's I forgot there was
someone there thank God he didn't right
here
oh my God
[Music]
can you sneak onto someone
no need what was that ah
save this one for now
okay we gotta do it this time we gotta
do it
we have to
but they're still they can [\h__\h] me up so
bad one I can knock over at the door
this one probably somehow maybe but then
um
what is this one even doing
maybe yeah adore him and the other one
and then shoot him like I don't know
what if I [\h__\h] up again
come on come on come on I'm ready I'm
ready I'm ready when you are
[Music]
that was so difficult for me you have no
idea holy [\h__\h] uh
I was so rough for me
oh man
oh that was so difficult oh
Mamma Mia
ah what about me let's get into my car
and get a pizza or something
I will get such a bad score for this
I already tried so many times
I've got a lot of points though oh wait
wow oh I'm getting a lot of extras to
see okay I'll take it with pride
a pig mask nah
but I wonder what those different stats
are
should I not be using the chicken
anymore
a samurai sword wow
you can't shoot with a dog can you
VHS Palace those don't exist anymore
these days I mean
do you have like a
erotic section somewhere
I heard uh tales of the erotic section
in these stores
but like when these were still a thing I
was like too young like I think if
anything
I I don't even remember someone ever
saying hey I'm gonna go rent a movie at
the VHS place
and I don't think I ever walked into one
either for real though
I think we may have
got movies in other ways or or I mean we
just tapes
they were around
when I was a child they were around but
soon soon after I think they turned into
DVDs I think I'm not sure anymore
but I didn't deal with that much
um
ah you again how many side jobs do you
have man hey dude good to see you again
did you hear about the mistaker the
other night yeah that was me a bunch of
rescues that hurt no loss if you ask me
they say so Maniac wearing a rubber mask
dude I thought it was bubber mask
sounds like a scene straight from a
slasher flick
oh yeah I have the perfect film for you
the one on the desk take it it's the
it's on the house
enjoy yourself dude
but like when I get all these items but
like I can't really do anything with
them can I
[Music]
April 25th let's go who are we killing
next
Hotline Miami he's a dating service we
have set up a date for you this evening
place
as usual make sure you wear something
fancy
kite
kite Nash
I love kite Nash
wouldn't ever want to hurt her
hopefully it's a different Kate
tip be fast and efficient
these tips are mocking me okay so
and I for Secrets Fists of Fury oh
stronger like punches more guns more
guns spawned because they are like kind
of randomly is that what you mean
[Music]
which one should we go for Tony Maybe
I'm gonna test those fists out
okay what are the secrets though
okay The Sims Project Safe
wow okay
so one hitting uh weapons now amazing do
I even need the Crowbar them or the
baseball bat right now until I got a
shooty weapon probably not
oh is there that's something yeah
but he doesn't see me from here I think
yeah okay
oh that was efficient that was efficient
again
food nice bgm yeah
uh I think I'll go for this one
first
[Music]
wait okay okay that was just the first
first one okay
[Music]
I succeeded
[Laughter]
[Applause]
laughs
I just ran back for a while panicly
shooting
I screamed too much in this game [\h__\h]
hell
[Music]
nice music
why would you open the door you idiot
let's do that
we're just gonna try this
I'm moving down
ah I thought that was okay
[Laughter]
I thought he gave up man okay ooh knife
now we're knifing now
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
let's go
there's no smarter option for me guys
there's no other way to do it for me
[Music]
we're all stupid
oh what did I do
I I just held on to him oh oh okay okay
I'm still a nice thing to receive from
the heavens
okay
but I think I'll oh
why why
what is he's new
what the [\h__\h] what
she's gonna move somewhere
um
Invincible wow
oh
wait was it the guy that was walking
around here that walked out and then was
here why I didn't even make so many
noises
okay well then is he really the only one
left in there okay
good
he had a gun no one hurt me
ah okay
I was going so well it was going so well
[\h__\h] up
what what is this randomness
egg
where's the feeder
huh that ruins my whole plan
Nani the [\h__\h] they've all three of them
have guns too
if they're they're at the same time okay
foreign
now it's always free huh
date
if I fail so many times you're not
supposed to make the game more difficult
you're supposed to make it easier
[Music]
uh-huh now you're leaving okay bastard
all right
[Music]
all right Revenge Revenge Revenge
actually does he come by the door again
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
I thought it was over I thought it was
done for her
[Music]
how do I shoot first before him
like from here it won't work
okay there we go did someone hear that
no oh hello Kate is it you
wait what's going on here
what
wait
did you kill her what what the [\h__\h] is
going on
okay let's not mess it up now
okay okay
[Music]
Mamma Mia
oh
this game is getting me really heated
but it's fun
[Music]
that was so reckless of me
[Laughter]
so funny
[Music]
[Laughter]
I wanted you to kill me at that point
because my plan was ruined
[Music]
I'll try this again I'll try it again
I think
I just need you to come a bit closer my
friend
wow
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just like when I'm not locked on I'm
just shooting aimlessly
oh
my God
the space wasn't working again
oh I got them all I got them all I got
them all I just have to kill him
[Music]
oh you can do it even off screen oh
that's interesting good to know so what
the [\h__\h] is going on here can I walk in
no oh
they're closed for me
oh it's continuing
uh okay
you can use this can too
um
[Music]
what did I what what did I just what
what did I throw
did I have a knife
how did I have a knife I thought I only
had a gun
[Music]
oh God
two rounds no
not with this loud
loud gun
[Music]
that's a big opening
oh oh it's broken though that's funny
[\h__\h] okay
okay panic
oh there is a dive
I was just saying
Sandy though
[Music]
[Laughter]
they are so bamboozly with their routes
what on
wow wow
skills well
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah
cause I canceled this game
[Music]
I'm gonna report you to the GMS [\h__\h] you
oh oh I know you better now bunny I know
you give me that give me that he's gonna
see me
[Music]
no
this is what you may call a double kill
wow
oh it's so far
[Music]
God
girl big guy moments come here
come here now
come on
why'd you change your route again
you coward what
really
fine with me all right let's do it your
way
[Laughter]
what you wasn't you weren't paying
attention before
good safe koala good safe
I'm gonna go for him but I gotta look at
the timing
[Laughter]
gosh it's been an hour and I'm like so
exhausted I'm telling you
yeah now they don't have guns these ones
that's nice okay good to know
[Music]
I know should I go for punches then
um
probably
just gotta be careful not to be caught
okay he's quite busy
[Music]
okay they still they still
Panic is the best strategy my friend is
how are you alive what the [\h__\h] I missed
my Pro that never happened before
Mama May yeah how did they not hear good
question
um okay
um
that would have been so good
[Music]
foreign
he's going down there now
okay I mean sometimes violence is the
only option to survive how did he his
body
him
ah I feel bad
Two Shots two rounds Make It Count
I did I did
can't lose now
oh please okay two here two down here I
have a loose I will lose I will lose but
it's okay I will I will win
some different weapon though because
this one only got one shot
tonight no I can't safely walk over
there it's only got two this one's empty
I think
I don't know I should be able to walk
how cute I'm out of out of his side out
of his mind out of the Bieber
right I should be able to walk by and
into this room
it doesn't look like he has a weapon but
he probably has right
can see me no I don't think so
[Laughter]
nah that's a difficult room no matter
how I end Nah if I
um
I'm gonna mess this up but
keep in mind kiwaba you only have two
rounds
[Laughter]
did that work
[Music]
Ed all right all right all right all
right all right all right
I want that weapon feels safer hmm
six rounds okay I can work with that the
the chairs and the table probably block
my shots right
I think so from experience
they won't
I'm counting on your words now
hey how dangerous I shot pretty late I
walked pretty far because I didn't want
to miss even though I'm locked on but
you know you know you know ah that was
close
yo now should I go for a rifle for this
weapon for these bodies they look very
busy oh is the door gonna hit him as I
walk in it looks like it could
um
stay with shotgun
door too far it won't
so what do we do
maybe I can bait him
I know there's another entrance but um
yeah maybe this this entrance could be
better for baiting
if I shoot like diagonally and then the
other one will come for me surely and
I'll just run away a little bit to to
gather my senses
just walk in and shoot them go but what
if I
met I didn't expect that I was ready to
run back let's go
let's go oh
they weren't one line
little scale kill of the skill oh blood
oh you still here
are you gonna oh
to kill him
I
is he like bulky does he take many hits
away can I not
iced
oh wait oh God
God
Nani what the [\h__\h] is he doing
what happened
are we done
what are we done I I I I
oh
okay there we go
am I
say I'll just get over with
I knew it would end like this
yeah what I'm supposed to kill her too I
was gonna let her go
or I don't know
okay
oh wait one room
the way she's drawn here like it looks
literally looks like a like a blown up
plastic doll I mean
it doesn't look like a person
wow
[Applause]
for this I'm scared
I got 20
000 points
D plus one
taking into account how much time it
took I mean how many redos because
otherwise would it really be this bad
[Laughter]
they are oh God
so bad
for dramatic I got no time bonus oh [\h__\h]
hey but I did my best I tried went fast
I had fun too
hi there welcome you don't look well sir
are you all right are you sure it is
okay for you to be drinking all right
then I will get the it was something
special where what Austin accent do you
like sweet or sour maybe you want it
bitter and there you go sir Andrew I
didn't even answer did you just put
everything in wait where's my other what
is that
the rest of this place is just uh
what the rest of this place is just for
nothing
you you'll make this for nothing
it's useless is that what you're telling
me
just for show
no no story no NPCs I can talk to
hmm
okay for atmosphere
part two
questions
so one week later chapter or what
my wife's so dark again I don't like
this
ah it's you again it looks like you've
been busy since we last met
do you remember me now don't you but you
still don't know who I am you don't even
know who introduced us to you
why did you come back here you're not a
nice person are you you make me sick
picture is starting to take from here I
wonder if it's a accurate some pieces
don't quite seem to fit or maybe I just
don't like the way it looks
I think our time is up but we'll meet
again before you go here's four
questions to ponder question number one
do you like hurting other people Ah
that's why they wrote that on that fan
art question number two who are you
leaving messages on your on your
answering machine question number three
where are you right now on the final
question why are we having this
conversation that's all for now see you
soon
I guess I do like it in in the context
of this game yes
can I talk to her no oh
I don't know if I'm really the best
person to come along with well one of
those movie producer found dead in
villain last night surveillance tape
reveals Master salient
so so that guy
that the boss
unidentified female adopted
[Laughter]
abducted from the scene
she she's happy here okay maybe she
shouldn't be here and maybe she
shouldn't be happy with me
feels kind of wrong probably not the
best boyfriend to have but
adopted adopted
yeah not abducted she's adopted I
adopted wait
if if if if you know this this is the
best argument when someone says you were
abducted someone to say no I I adopted
this person I am adopted this person
yeah
[Music]
they wanted to be adopted mm-hmm
price adoption
a good evening this is Blake
's you have a job for you there is a
power outage over on the 24th
Northeast Street we want you to take
care of it we already sent someone over
a while ago but it seems he didn't do a
very good job
head over there right away they're
expecting you
keep it quick and clean
that is what I am very good at plus
panicking you know but that is just an
addition to the end product
of quickliness and cleanliness of course
[Music]
we'll expect lots of panic again
I
I I I okay I see one there we should go
into this room first one has a gun
don't know who to go for first let's
will one of them come to the door are
you dog
reflexes
[\h__\h]
I don't hurt animals
okay he won't really come much closer
huh
I didn't mean to open the door
okay wait for the dog
[\h__\h] I'm getting so many heart attacks
man
samurai sword I want to use it
okay please can you not where is the dog
here
change your routes
the [\h__\h]
ing girl [\h__\h] hell
swear to God
give me a moment to enter the room first
and think about what to do okay I need
to make tactical decisions because
without that I have even more lost than
I already am give me a freaking chance
okay this is not fair
oh
all right all right
at least now we have lots of time to
think
dude
this dude
come on
move out of the corner or maybe whatever
I hate you
foreign
had a good run that was going incredibly
well that was a miracle that was a
miracle
I almost got through that sheesh
I can't
oh
a bit closer
foreign
at least that's outside London didn't uh
whatever
is he gonna come over again you don't
have to I mean
it's it's an open world for you
I'll I'll leave the choice to you but
the dog is coming let's do the dog
hey
once you're in you can't get out it
seems
oh
[Music]
brother answer this room fast
why could it not have continued the way
it was before it was going nicely
[Music]
shot something
what's going on are you okay
I feel so bad for you that you have to
live in this environment
of mass killers
you're supposed to be happy doggo that's
being taken out to play with ball
like the others and you're supposed to
be
all taught tricks and treetos
yeah wait what choice did I have with no
weapon but my face
okay I don't care I don't care I'm gonna
do that now
why why why why why why
[Applause]
[Music]
do you have a gun yeah he has one so far
my fists are plenty good dog don't pick
up the gun
thank you
did you see me panic there oh
[Music]
[Applause]
don't look at me guys don't look at me
I'm not here you are not here no one's
here okay okay okay pretty clean
squeaky clean
where next
I think that guy
[Music]
the door that's the door
bother me
you won't know
[Music]
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
don't rage kiwala don't rage
this is most like the game that makes me
scream the most not I'm not really
raging I'm happy while playing this but
it's definitely inducing a lot of rage
in me
Mamma Mia
I'm here doggo
do the fails count
what
the dog I tried to throw the thing at
him but somehow he was faster
[Music]
oh
my God
yeah okay dogs first or see
dog dog first dog first
okay one punch man hey
what what
you can even even double punch kill
people that's incredible but I got no
one with a gun here that's uh not so
good he doesn't have a gun either though
maybe let me try to throw something
from a distance
oh [\h__\h]
didn't work out so well
sure
music Come Back to Me
where'd you go
[Music]
guns guns guns
so many guns
oh here no guns no guns gang
okay
um
good good good wow
foreign
gotta bait them
thing I want to clean up down here but
no there's also this guy but maybe he
doesn't see me maybe the others will see
me first and I can bait them
four rounds hello anyone hi no
it
hurt me
what
[\h__\h]
[Music]
just waiting for it okay well at least
this time if I kill this guy I should be
able to get his gun where was this gun
before
[Music]
whenever I do something right it makes
me very happy
oh doggo is coming
I just want to punch him
is that that's not a gun right that's
just a crowbar
foreign
[Music]
laughs
oh that was so nice Stone no way
Sony mealy broken yeah yeah that is true
it was coming first this time don't go I
think
okay
noise
right no I just come closer please
who was that that caught up on me up
there anyway I don't see anyone maybe
came from different room
I think I sound like Subaru today
sometimes
the sound of birds screaming
[Music]
okay
come here let's play Let's Play welcome
let me adopt you
Tony I'm counting on your punches don't
do this to me
[Music]
and now oh
I want to see like a punches only run
from someone
I feel like you could do it
just gotta get good
[Music]
nah please why don't I get the double
kill the double punch again
it has been done well of course it has
been done yeah I can imagine
laughs
hey yo hey yo
I thought I could bait them from there
so he's faster but no
why would you leave your room don't
leave your post your post
the post right the post where you post
that you shouldn't be doing that I don't
think you're supposed to do that
nothing
[Music]
at least the 999 emote is getting some
good use again
dog come here
I got no patience let me out of this
beginning room
[Music]
I can't help it I kind of need to wait
for the right moment down here
and then a double punch before but
um
not this time
is it counting my fan
my failed nuts
punches man
okay I'll try I should
okay now
[Music]
get on him Oh Mamma Mia
I survived I survived I survived
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
no
tore him apart man
yo
so good okay okay damn that this one's
got quite a reach I I would like to play
more with it but I'm scared that we
didn't get both of them out of that room
now nice
and here they're gone too okay
okay okay
no one here is that a bathtub that's a
weird big ass bathtub
four out of six rounds
[Music]
oh wait we also based
room
nice if I just shoot randomly does that
bait them too like the sound even if I
don't kill anyone it could bait them too
right and also wait they don't all have
guns
two of them have uh melee weapons hmm
Hmm this is our chance
this one this one's got a gun okay okay
should I do the big one first
at least they don't see me right away
hey I'm scared oh
window in the big room window ah on the
other on this side ah okay okay okay
I wouldn't have noticed and you can
shoot through the windows
um
okay
yeah
um I'm scared no one coming for me
really oh [\h__\h] but he's still alive
okay okay okay I mean slowly but surely
if this is how we gotta do it when
you're gonna this is how we're gonna do
it
nice okay oh wait oh wait the windows
are gonna say you can also see me from
the other side oh yeah yeah that was a
thing and which means I can also shoot
from my side right
what
I can right don't stay there
snap him
[\h__\h]
okay so this kind of furniture is in the
way
um
[Music]
no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
I forgot how to throw
it shush
that was close
hey don't go our body was just gonna
look strange man
okay
okay okay
oh
this room sucks
what
such a luck shooter holy [\h__\h]
sometimes you really wonder like how the
[\h__\h] does she do it how does Chihuahua
do it incredible luck is how I do it
save my butt because they can even kill
two when they're right like inside each
other mean lucky
I don't know if I should do even close
the door
oh [\h__\h]
like it's also scale yeah in many games
that is true you can skill into luck uh
oopsie
I'm scared I'm scared I'm gonna hide
here combo begin I got an achievement
he's going there now
okay
all right all right step by step
um let's change weapon
one left in this room
let's go bait them
[Applause]
[\h__\h] I'm gonna
absolutely losing my my blood pressure I
think
is
oh no oh no no
no that was too many yeah
you should close the door you don't want
to know what happens behind closed doors
trust me
no one wants to know
that's right
right close the door close the [\h__\h]
door
it's a weapon
oh hello
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
just
showing his back to me big mistake big
oh
I wish that even when they were down
that it would work
you know
[Music]
to just punch why do I have to press
space ah
why are you gonna make it so difficult
ah come on okay
what
oh
[Music]
good time
is over
[Music]
what happened to my crowbar
[Laughter]
I don't know
I don't even know I don't I I went in
there fully knowing I this was Reckless
I will die
don't go you want to come here
do me a favor
[Laughter]
[Music]
why
[Laughter]
don't give me that I just wanna
oh sure okay
sometimes that's easier uh
oh my God
us
um
foreign
I don't I don't understand
I don't understand
where did that weapon go
where did the good one go ah there it is
you can sometimes hide under the
way
you're with me and sister only me
okay
um
oh
[Music]
come on we even shot each other at the
same time or like killed each other at
the same time
for this [\h__\h] level I can't
will it ever end
okay I I I'll do the dog first okay oh
be
the math is never ends
[Music]
okay
I literally locked on the gun guy
[Music]
why is he alive will he die eventually
where are you going
punches are so much better for that
situation
[Music]
oh
okay come come come
here
okay
no I don't give him I don't even give a
[\h__\h] about that
again
[Music]
I'm just too good
nice
anyone alive oh yeah okay not anymore I
was I was almost gonna turn my back on
them
good that I didn't
um how many oh four
what weights we have uh two guns two
mealies
two guns here
I don't even
I don't know
[\h__\h] stupid very stupid very stupid
oh nobody came why not
I changed his route
okay okay good paid good paid good paid
okay
now we're talking
that's that one oh he's the one the one
that's left over has got a gun
I'll wait for him
come on this is very dangerous
I know I have no ammo but one shot
should very do it
oh he's not he's not walking over here
dude
oh there's someone out there
oh oh oh
I hate this gun it only has two rounds
okay
okay uh
this one's better
all right all right we're in this
situation again
we gotta do it we just gotta do it
which one first
so the other one
in the door I'm just lucky that doesn't
like
come back to me
um
okay
[Music]
I'm very systematic right now because I
don't want to fail again
which one first they can't can they
throw too when they have these weapons
for the windows I'm scared
he'll probably come for me if I if I
shoot the other dudes I should take care
of him first huh
window or bait
they count for okay
this one's so difficult
I don't know how to show them I'm not
getting a Time bonus ever
ah bottom Grandma's Windows add that one
too oh
wait the bottom broom too
[Music]
I can bait them through the windows see
me
okay oh let's go
can't mess it up now kiwawa you've gotta
shoot first okay
I have two rounds
oh
it's continuous illusion about the
different weapons
Mamma Mia Mamma Mia this is crazy it's
absolutely crazy
[Music]
don't want any unnecessary attention
which one
come on empty punches again
oh oh
[Music]
where'd he come from ah
why am I stuck oh because behind me I
can't go any further okay okay
let's just let's just do it quietly
that's better that's better
laughs
yeah okay okay
seems like in this kind of room when
they're both mealing I can just enter
when they're further away rather than
when they're close by what the [\h__\h] they
got like snipers here
always in position as they expect me oh
what's that
is this person looking at me feeling the
face is looking upward wait what is
going on is he being wait is this person
being tortured
oh this person's being tortured oh okay
cool
um don't know what's cool about that
don't know
um
is he dead yes
yes
yes not so bad pretty easy so far
I think I'll kill him but ooh those
shots is this Thor
is this door like different from the
others I wonder
can you hear is that doctor that crazy
doctor scientist is he gonna come for
you if he hears me shoot
nobody gives a [\h__\h]
nobody gives any shits
so far I'm having way less traveled this
one than the previous room
what way
why
the shark the snipers maybe aren't a
problem
do they even have weapons
or jinx it
oh and now what now
what now
walk through that door and what's gonna
happen
one shoot the door of a shotgun
ho ho ho ho
I don't I don't see a shot is this a
shotgun
don't open the door shoot it hmm
I don't even poke it okay
huh
maybe the other one because that doesn't
feel like it did anything
the other one is like close the other
way yeah
turn my volume down now
why
[Music]
why would you do that
why guys
why
I was so close
the [\h__\h]
Ed up
okay beautiful beautiful beautiful
oh
systematic
I've got one shot could do it
okay okay
all right all right all right I'll take
the knife where did the knife go here
two knots
laughs
[Music]
almost
stop it
it's pointless
getting faster though thank God in this
level I feel like hey hey on this level
I feel like I can be fast
a little bit faster
and it must have been pretty loud for
you guys but it was one thing louder for
me
I
was scared actually I thought that was
what was supposed to happen and
I thought
I thought I I did it right
he's alive no
not today
[Music]
laughs
okay okay so this time further away
and then what happened
oh nice
just gotta wait a little bit and then we
can enter I suppose oh
yeah I think um at least we released the
victim from suffering more torture so we
did a good thing
now the Sharpshooters
I think my weapon if it can go through
doors then it can go through the tables
can it
otherwise how am I supposed to do that
because they're on the ground
and he dropped the mask
wait what
[Music]
ah this thing
what what do I pick up I don't see
anything
I don't think there's anything
get behind the couch
eh
by the top door
there's nothing here
just peek and shoot okay
missed why
[Applause]
no problem no problem no problem
I'm used to this now
get the purple dots secret oh okay I'll
try to remember that
Secrets huh oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
once you say I'm getting better it does
okay
uh care careful everybody volume down
please three two one
okay
[Music]
uh are we good we're good okay volume
back up
that is really [\h__\h] loud man what a
[\h__\h] jump scare
you can't do this also oh yeah purple
what about purple purple Dot
I want to see a purple Dawn at this one
how do I take it
back that's the second I'm getting okay
but no no no no
um
no thing for my head
no nothing no hat no mask that was
actually this one who Shot Me Maybe it's
easier for me to shoot him too then
oh no did that work no
[Music]
um
behind the wall can I do that without
them shooting me like they started
shooting when I was even standing in the
door
it's a bit tricky
timing
gotta run in and then run out I need to
wait and then shoot
[Music]
maybe I'm the machine gun is better in
this case
all right I'll try
[Music]
what okay that's the only thing I don't
I just don't understand about this map
you can hide behind the fountains next
to the couch okay okay
all right
oh nice for putties thank you you need
to wait don't get up and shoot at you
okay
[Music]
where's that
huh did he change routes
he was like um this is a weird Deja Vu
I'm having
something maybe I should go somewhere
else uh you finally Ah that's finally
come to this is my knife still somewhere
or do I have to use the other one
wait that's so now I can't even get my
gum right away [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
and stealth scale but how do I get the
gun
right I have one one shot on on this one
was pretty loud
what well it's still hard for me to
reach to you that gondo okay wait other
um desperate situations called for
Desperate Measures
foreign
okay this one go away I'm 24 rounds okay
okay
all right here we go three two one
[Applause]
it's so loud
[Music]
it's really [\h__\h] loud can you hear me
still hello
I need to get the purple dot again huh
Okay so
um
okay
how
I have to wait for them to get up but
can they still shoot while they're
sitting that's not fair what did you say
don't worry guys just watching
eventually maybe your hearing will
return keep doing that
okay there we go just have to wait a
tiny second longer now about this one I
feel like I have to do it from the
bottom
can I arrange from the top like from the
angle and all that you know
I wanna fail
okay nice
[Music]
[Applause]
finally finally wow this one was rough
this one was difficult
oh
yeah
I did
wow look at this ah we had so much
trouble here oh
I was crying something are you gonna
give me a bad word
I think on the second floor I wasn't so
bad that was way easier oh but I I got
more more points
oh
yeah
[Music]
redeemed ourselves and a new mask a
bunny mask Graham
I wonder what his uh
the the thing that bonuses that we get
with this mask oh and a new weapon
I haven't used the other one much but oh
glass bottle wait it doesn't explode
does it is it just like throwing and
then the shards will kill them I broke a
glass by the way one of my Coca-Cola
glasses yeah
but it's a good way to get me to buy new
glasses because my my glasses they're
all like I would say normal size they're
not that tall but like they're like
Tumblr tall glass size and they don't
really fit in my uh washing machine
unless I put them in the bottom
compartment uh and dishwasher and I
don't like that because that's where all
the plates go it pisses me off so I need
to get shorter glasses not the colon
glass you know got a couple Coca-Cola
glasses not one of them is dead
[Music]
um
not the washing machine of course you
know what I'm talking about
the dishwasher is in if you think about
it also just the washing machine
for dishes
how did it break
um I was cleaning because of the whole
problem with not being able to wash it
in the dishwasher I was cleaning it by
hand for once
and then I was kind of trying to dry it
by shaking it then it flipped out of my
hand and fell into the sink and just
broke which was really stupid of me
because it was still wet and I was
shaking it to get the wetness off of it
grip and thank God it didn't like hurt
me though didn't get any shards on me
imagine me doing that genius
Pawn
pom pom pom oh hi there good to see you
I was a bit worried about you the city
streets don't seem so safe anymore you
know
what with all the killings and all that
I mean don't worry about paying you're
my friend your money is no good here now
have a nice night
yeah oh what is this what am I getting
there what is that doesn't even look
like pizza what the [\h__\h] is that looks
weird it looks old
what does he give me top left uh
why are they dead now I didn't do this
they were alive a second ago weren't
they
yeah
what
happened
uh hello
that is unfortunate
okay
let's just ignore the scene and move on
nothing happened here
it's awesome May 11th oh that's pretty
close to the actual date yesterday was
apparently May 4th
is everybody playing the the jediary
Jedi game right now because it just came
out because I saw a coordinate plant and
some en member too was it Ahmed
did it just come out
ah did they release it on the fourth on
purpose
[Music]
you should play it nah not interested
I mean I would probably enjoy the game
more than the movies though I think
can I not answer you're doing your
makeup or something all right I'll leave
you to yourself then
[Music]
from Miami Pest Control
[Applause]
to try to handle it as quick and Swift
as you can someone else will clean up
for you after you leave
make sure not to bother any of the
neighbors wait when you say someone else
will clean up does that mean I don't
have to do The Killing
[Music]
normally they say I need to do it quick
and clean now he says I'm not the one
cleaning
what
oh it's like a pest
or do they actually mean actual cleaning
like real clean disposing of the body
okay okay well good to know you can
shoot for some walls oh some walls
all right where's the new one
oh hey we skipped some
walk fast now I'll stay with Tony for
now I think that's pretty pretty op
okay
um
what are we dealing with two people
there
[Laughter]
wasn't even me the door started to fight
it was the door
wait Carlton 4K yo you guys just look at
the Vault I didn't start the fight it
was a door and they're stupid for like
blaming me for it oh there's another
doggo
there's only one in there
is it
I wish you were two rounds I wanna shoot
just yet because it makes such a big
mess
oh and I also don't have uh
okay okay but the door is being so wide
open let's not Spade the dog double
did he not see me oh he went straight to
the other room
yeah
yeah good reflexes kiwawa got good
reflexes I'm training my reflexes in
this game
okay
Diana's also gonna pass through
no
did he shoot could he then just what
was that did you see my Panic punches
Panic punch is my specialty Panic pun
snug Falcon Punch [\h__\h] that the new cool
thing is panic punch
okay
um I'll wait for him to turn around okay
um
you see that yeah
oh
I'm counting all my punches
[Applause]
oh the bottle is there let's see how
that works
new weapon
aye
this head I mean okay
um it will Shadow but it will also
mostly just knock out people right
um
doesn't even seem like a good weapon in
real life
[Music]
combo
let's camp for the dog
or anyone else for that matter
broken glass is sharp
it didn't give me the desired effect
though
hmm
okay okay cool cool cool
[Applause]
oh he saw me
nice okay very nice very nice very nice
I like to do everything silent today I
feel like very silent now
[Music]
I don't know about this one I feel like
we can do him silently too
[Music]
um
whoa and I'm relying on the punches it's
not not so bad
didn't even have to but okay so here we
have four
two
guns oh there's one here only one though
but if I shoot him I don't mind bait
them unfortunately but that might be
good actually
[Music]
um
I somehow would have preferred it if it
baited them
okay
this might go wrong
why does the door not bait people when
it like
bumps them
[Applause]
it was so good okay okay okay I'm
motivated
I'm motivated
I'm motivated I'm motivated
[Music]
understand
[Laughter]
wait let me get the knife
oh
[Music]
okay
calm oh there's a mask that makes doggos
friends oh
really
so they won't attack you but they also
won't help you right probably they won't
help you suddenly when they see you they
they change the switch to your side that
would be nice little dog friend
they wait for dog is he gonna come if
the door isn't really open
they won't help okay no you say won't
attack but they're not even like such a
big problem for me
looking door
come on Dogo
now it's open
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah oh
I was gonna do a punch run man punch and
run punch and run
both
completely aimless didn't know what to
do such as life
oh
what did I did I was there a dog still
coming yeah right
[Music]
come on
I don't think that long
ah
I gotta be ready I gotta be ready oh oh
this time
bad again huh
okay fine
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
stop it wait there's a oh there's an
opening here I never realized that
there's an opening there
do I not learn
again
I feel so safe here oh wait what am I
doing
[Music]
it's not always there
oh
just checking if everything's all right
there I guess oh fine fine it's not like
a little knife lying around no
because knife at least when you throw it
it kills
what's another weapon that kills when
you throw it that I already have do I
not have any because the Crowbar I think
doesn't kill
[Music]
um
knife by bed
no
I felt like I had to go for it because
no time
there there's one I'll keep that
why don't you see me
come on
they never come when you want them to
come
[Music]
a baseball bat where did the knife go
here
[Applause]
I'm scared
[Music]
my new my new mouse is gonna probably
die soon because of all the damage I've
done to it in the Stream oi
[Music]
double kill
oh
[Music]
okay then just go elsewhere that's fine
that's fine
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
out with the door when the Gunner is far
away
um
[Laughter]
get them both
I couldn't
how short is the memory of a dog the
attention span
surprisingly short
hey
[Music]
I still got that problem
yay okay okay okay we're talking we're
talking guys I can do this I can do this
I know how to do this and the knife is
still there if I want it
um
[Music]
okay this time
do it as you said you were gonna do it
wait for the dog
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I thought maybe you know I was just
me my non-existent skills before but it
turns out it's just a dog thing
why it's not like there are too too low
standing for it no
I was bound to happen
foreign
page like this also very effective
[Music]
as a [\h__\h] dog what do I do about this
[\h__\h] dog
um do something about it
[Music]
this triggers me hard we had situations
where and the dog maybe when they're
here together where the dog was already
out of the room then it wasn't so bad
okay they they end up there together
sometimes
don't want to lose so much time please
but we saved time with the Rampage
[Applause]
this is how it's supposed to go all
right
[Music]
well this is game we're playing oh last
time I feel like I didn't go for it but
that's good because now we got one
Gunner out of the way hey and the door
is open no don't close it no I thought I
could shoot through the door
foreign
wait there's a secret here
if this time is it
[Music]
um
what I do
[Music]
a little bit off
so close
yo okay okay okay
get a nice combo bonus for that
okay that was dangerous too oh his head
[Music]
let's take the gun
no more games with these [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
we got the combo too
[Music]
ah this time we didn't hear it [\h__\h]
should have done it when they were
closer so that they would come out
um
that's bad that's pretty bad also
because I only have three rounds what
did he drop what what weapons
six okay
if I do the dwarf thing again I hope I
can paint them out
um well I open the door when he's there
then I shoot one the rest should come
out I walk back a little bit
[Music]
all right
okay okay
[Music]
I think
probably hopefully
Nice Shot nice shot right yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
okay next room next room
that wasn't if they don't count like how
much time I needed to get to this point
then this round on its own didn't take
too much time
I think
oh he's peeing
um don't be careless
when
oh
okay okay okay okay
no problemo
no one needs to alert everyone else to
what's going on here they don't want to
know they don't wanna know they're just
better to live without the knowledge of
terrible things happening sometimes
because you can't do anything about it
anywhere in most cases and then I guess
just just don't think about it
um
okay they're both
what do you call it melee
so I'm I'm
probably an honorable Warrior I will oh
wait there's one Gunner I
[Music]
I'll go in with with my fists only
changes it hmm
[Music]
well I don't know
what
[Music]
we shot at the same time did we what
happened there
I didn't look my fault my fault what oh
[\h__\h] they'll just kill me
what
anyone else still alive okay okay
um cool I mean
I mean if you know you're already dying
the only thing you can do is fight for
your life
was there always only two in there
does he not have a gun
he has a cigarette
interesting that's interesting there
were more I baited them all
wait so the the the the cigarette guy
[Music]
can we just punch the [\h__\h] out of him
I feel like he had something a knife or
so
[\h__\h]
maybe I should be shooting here to to
get all these [\h__\h] to come
how did they do it you don't even like
want to do it
yeah what
ah
can't do it on purpose
[\h__\h]
yeah
another
see
okay but I think I learned uh some out
of there
[Music]
at that point I should have just
switched to my Tony guns AKA my fists
[Music]
four doing me the favor
and making my path shorter but okay this
is so this is quite the problem when you
don't bait them
um
they have a weird route
[Laughter]
yeah I mean
of course that's how it's gonna go
that body was gone
so close really
was I close
okay but that's how I'm gonna do it I
think
I think I I got my strategy down
set in stone now
okay
spawn count
not everybody hearses what's going on I
don't care but I mean we got two one I
got one
oh
[Music]
oh yeah
everything
wow did you see that oh
y'all that was some Next Level kind of
[\h__\h] where is there any knives can I
throw the katana
it's one about this guy I gotta shoot
him
[Music]
slice and dice time
Katana leaves like
um
oh no that works out okay
huh
I think I should get a gun
beheaded
just like one of the tutors
if you're a fan of them because then
isn't that like an ideal death
I'm a fan of them
the thoughts did you see the Dodge
like I'm some Dodge Coin or so
funny is there only no wait there's two
you don't know what weapons they have
guys
the side step yo
okay I'm scared I'm scared I don't want
to mess it up um
I can't mess it up it's impossible what
did you not notice what's going on well
I started walking though
he's he's on alert
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] I'm so scared ah wait wait wait
ah
[Music]
I'm such a chicken I decided chicken
this is such a chicken
oh I got the chicken
oh
what's good
oh I'm so happy
okay I gotta say this game is a lot of
fun a lot of screaming but a lot of fun
too
uh where's the exitoko
uh What uh
here here here here I remember wow
hey how long is this game I wonder for
especially for someone like me I wonder
because now I'm motivated to finish it I
was not thinking that I would be
motivated to finish this game like not
today but oh 45 and look that's not bad
[Music]
I see mine I thought that was an A plus
five hours
oh
yeah okay but I'm finishing today let's
play it again next week I need to read
some super chats hi Dennis
and then take a break until uh the Titi
rpj because it might be a pretty long
one I don't know gotta ask Kelly but I
should maybe take a nap
hey that was for you to be age and
that's okay
I like having a game to come back to
does it save like
um after each of these like interactions
or can I save
D good evening how are you doing you
look a bit distracted something got you
worried these are Harsh Times we're
living in ago I haven't seen many uh
customers lately maybe they've lost your
tasteful Pizza you gotta try something
new oh innovate I can tell you a secret
recipe that's gonna blow everybody's
mind put corn cob on the crust trust me
bro it's gonna solve all your problems
maybe it's time to close shop once and
for all no listen listen
anyway got your order right here take
care now oh thank you at least you know
he won't sell it on his menu but at
least he makes special order for me
yeah so I appreciate that
I have 16 levels left in the game but
how many did I do
can I like to get out of the game now is
it safe resume
be right
I know my stuff yeah I tasted it myself
can okay good to quit okay nice so that
was fun
exit game
I was a lot of fun
can't do it for like 10 hours or so
because that would kill my throat and my
mouse my computer mouse
my poor poor Mouse I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry for hurting you so much oh
at least now I'm peeling off all the
plastic that you still had on you oh I
didn't realize
peeling porn
well well I'm feeling so hot too because
like it's getting so hot temperature
wise
man it's rough
excited for part two ah I'm glad I'm
glad you guys enjoyed me screaming so
much like a horror movie or so but no it
turns out it's not a horror movie
thank you for streaming this Kiara ah
you are so welcome
you are welcome to stay also for a
little bit of a Super Chat rating I
guess
uh I wonder
I wonder where we left off oh that's my
stream
got so [\h__\h] hot I should eat ice
cream
Nostalgia trip oh I saw that there's a
another Hotline Miami Miami too but I
just started out because I with this one
because I saw uh what I'm saying I also
played the the old one the first one
um two isn't that as good oh two is
great two is also great well there you
go
I finished all the talks about Chad ah
okay thank you
then we continue after that
two is good two two is great oh okay I
don't know one only one person says it's
not as good
or not good
um
there we go
okay so next is cute
um
well one person can fight me
to have some banging music oh really
let's move to the office
oh [\h__\h]
uh yo speaking of the office I wanted to
tweet this but I think uh my app every
time on Twitter man I couldn't I
couldn't tweet sorry I got it seems like
I got
turned into half kiwawa by a katana
accidentally
um what was I saying oh yeah I was
watching Charmed and uh in third season
I was shocked to see a certain familiar
actor
um as a side character for one episode
uh Dwight from the office
a much younger twine from the office
makes an appearance as like an evil
um guy like a demon in charms and when I
was like when I first saw him appear on
the screen I didn't recognize him right
away because he looked so young but then
in combination combination with his
voice I was like wait a second
is that what
the [\h__\h] that's so funny because in his
role
it really feels like white really
passionately playing out a play that he
wrote
that's so funny
it was so funny to see him in a
different world when I know him as
Dwight but this is like much earlier he
he was looking much younger
um it's so funny if you look up Dwight
and Charmed it will come up
it will so if you're curious what he
looked like what he did you can do that
yeah Dwight Origins
I wonder if the office was his Breakout
role I guess
maybe it was the office was he already
getting good rules before that
he's so young there yeah so funny
it's so cool when you see actors that
you recognize from other shows but then
they they play something very different
often they also get Typecast and then
they play something very similar that's
um
oopsie ocean hmm
okay and let's get rid of this
everyone but Michael's breaker what's
that mean young versions of actors you
think you're familiar with are so
off-putting yeah because like back then
when I first watched Charmed of course I
didn't know Dwight yet because he didn't
do office at that time yet so it didn't
look familiar to me it was just another
funny
side character
also oh for everybody who watched chime
before I'm I'm in the coal Arc right now
and uh I'm past the point where they
Vanquish him once you know oh man and it
feels so nostalgic
this whole coal Arc is just so epic
it's so epic
those were the good times yeah Colac was
very good
ah the chat is still broken here
didn't it show up for a second
why does it not work here it worked on
the other screen not again
I'm sorry guys only super chats allowed
this is the the super chats only
TV screen sorry
I see you guys though
it's fixed because uh it worked on the
gaming screen and I messed it up over
there too the other day didn't I
don't understand
I really don't understand what what
happened to make it bug out so much
um you got payworld
only super is allowed and and member
messages
it's looking way cleaner now though
maybe the reason is I did some cleaning
huh
some quick cleaning only the super jets
are left
so nice because I can see so much Clara
recently I've been using these pictures
from the hollow gura
really useful
I haven't gotten any invitation for
another hologram since but I hope there
will be and I don't even know I'm I'm
actually curious like after they let us
appear once does this mean then we'll
ever be invited again or are we you know
oh it's done we did it once we don't
have to bring them in anymore
I hope they will though because that's
good for thumbnail use these are good
materials they have good Expressions
that I can't even do
clean my OBS shut up you don't know
nothing about what my OBS looks like I
need all this [\h__\h]
I need I need I need it I don't need all
those stupid rooms because I ever need
them you know then I'm like oh [\h__\h]
where is it I have to set it up like my
Ballroom for example I know I don't use
it much but when I want to use it then
well and my stages I need my stages I
need my I have four four different whole
talk scenes and I need those
I need all of this I need a loading
screen I need an ending screen I need it
all and I don't think that's like the
reason why it's bugging out anyway you
guys know nothing you you guys don't
know [\h__\h] about this
no no no no no no unless you're a
streamer with OBS experience I will not
take your advice in this case I like
getting you guys's technical advice but
in this case
um
no no
uh-uh
hmm
I will just have a lonely empty chat
that's okay
oh
keep your screen credits
the deny the proof that no I don't think
I have them on my
current scenes at all
I think um they were in a different uh I
think they were uh in like the graphic
this one I think yeah yeah they're here
um
yeah okay I could get rid of the scene I
mean
but but
you know what
the nine that's what I have to say to
you
oh [\h__\h] ah well that's where you go all
of you who who try to obey me
disobey me
be careful be careful
it just so happens that I have this
magical button that will bring you to
the usual room
it's not very nice there
hmm
okay let's read some chats Jacob Duncan
Jacob's monkey Duncan what's Amy thank
you for the rest of the chat
hello Kiana
I'm back from long way where I was just
moving drifting away from you was
drifting back to you
oh yeah I heard something about it yeah
you're a checkered flag for me could I
get a new kfb fan name as a new start
why salt and pepper dispenser is too
long
[Music]
oh my God what's in
La London
Iran
is it Korean or is it it's Korean right
[Music]
um
what
corn
yeah what
I read it but I'm confused is it
supposed to be Japanese written in
Korean letters again
let me check
[Music]
Omega what same is Young
I just realized I had no bgm going on
now do you hear it
the secret that Luna gave me to the name
of what's AIM uh-huh another secret
anymore is it what's it made
[Music]
keep on asking
ask your additions from your ooshies
now you want to get rid of the salt and
pepper dispenser
well how about SP dispenser that makes
it much shorter
foreign
Spicer is that a word
kfp Spicer the person who spices things
up
you can choose one of those
or SNP yeah
something like that
pick someone to
sprinkles spice over everything so I
can't give you completely different uh
position no no no no
thank you for the rest
of the red
[Music]
I can speak more Korean now but still
not very useful to replying to you I
think
[Music]
um
I learned some stuff yesterday and I
forgot it I learned how to say how's
your life recently
oh but I forgot how to say it
check my notes
count to 10 again
no no but my to praise me uh yesterday a
lot
because uh I remembered the numbers
really well and some other things too
so yeah we did some exercise to see if I
really remember it
like she played uh some audio of a guy
and the lady having a conversation and
saying a phone number really fast and I
was able to catch even though it sounds
really different when they speak so fast
and when they speak so naturally the
numbers don't even sound like what I
learned anymore partially
very confusing but I was able to
somewhat uh be fast enough to write it
down
correctly at least after the second
listen
um
yeah I practiced well thanks to putting
it in my stream and then and then yeah
we did more number thingies and then and
then what do we do I don't know oh she
taught me so many verbs
and like every every uh adjective
becomes a verb like tasty is a verb
something being tasty
and then oh the the difference between
tasty and drink is so similar because I
think
one is
my [\h__\h] machine needle Maybe
one one party makes it go that way and
one makes it go that way
um
I don't remember which one was which one
anymore
uh yeah uh-huh wait masi machine
one was drinking and one was tasty for
sure
to be tasty there's an adjective no no a
verb I'm talking about verbs but uh
they make uh adjectives into verbs
in in Korean
um
like you can also say
as a verb
that's I guess yeah something is boring
then it becomes well I am bored
basically but you can't I guess you
don't really say
I know I don't even know
but somehow yeah then I got
um taught a million verbs I don't know
how I'm supposed to remember that
because next lesson is not on the first
day normally we do it on Thursday but
she my teacher can't do it on the first
day so next lesson is on Tuesday so I
don't even have that many days to learn
of all of this
I'll try
no I haven't kept up with the news
when is it coming out
where is it out now
you guys have to remember remind me of
these things
next month okay so that time
still got time done
okay there's a free demo oh
the burp is the verb
ing I'm burping
I will show them later today oh yeah I
heard about it
anyway thank you one thing is
a math for ssj free donation not
applicable thank you
thank you for use that it's my second
birthday as a full-time kfp I want to
thank you for inspiring me to go after
my dreams and even go back to some
dreams that I gave up on I have so much
I want to do now there's some big
decisions ahead and it's a little scary
I don't know what the future holds but
the only thing I'm certain of is that
I'll be here supporting you any way I
can because no matter what this cute
amazing orange purple lady always makes
me smile and love thank you for being my
Oishi love you
for the sweet words and happy birthday
yay happy birthday to you happy birthday
in your shoe happy birthday to your cat
too happy birthday to you because you
got a cat in your profile picture it's
cute it's not a real cat but maybe you
have a real cat
it's a little bit late but
better late than never
hope you had a wonderful birthday you
have a dog then why do you
you profile picture trying to get on my
good side huh leaving a good impression
you are the cat you you are a cat you
have a dog you know what that seems very
cat-like
to own a dong
because cats are just above us all
that makes sense yeah
um
thank you for all the support and the
love you're so sweet thank you so much
please continue being the Way You Are
glad to have you around
meow meow meow meow meow Duncan thank
you
thank you
this guy that question is
I almost got scammed out of twenty
dollars yesterday why so since I'm
getting the money back I'll send them to
you boss
all I want was a one meal and a cold
bust instead of my usual 7-Eleven
sandwich on my shift
oh
why what Casey would have never done
what happened
why did they scam you how
the [\h__\h]
would be nice to have a warm meal I'm
sure
wait when you have a break and you eat a
meal do you eat it in the bus or do you
have like a room where you can go or do
you have to go in the restaurant and eat
it in the restaurant or do you guys have
a break room something like that
20 bucks more safe of me oh oh man y'all
treat me as you're safe I suppose
I won't let anyone crack me
well that's unfortunate but
I love the 7-Eleven sandwiches in Japan
at least but that's the ones in other
countries are probably not so good
because I know I've heard from you guys
before
7-Eleven in America is like something
completely different right
I haven't been to one I think when I was
in America I missed out on that I think
boom
hmm
anything is good with a Slurpee we have
many tacos in our 7-Elevens oh like warm
ones
I love the warm food in convenience
stores in Japan it's so good
[Music]
foreign
the best convenience store in America is
called Lala no way there's a community
called Baba and it's a good one really
wow it's so good really wow
[Music]
what really and people love our
Northeast North East ah over there where
everything looks so funky on the map
with lots of um
like weird looking map pieces yeah I
remember from my Geo guesser
lava is golden really the mascot is a
bird too what the [\h__\h]
no way
wow wow a tie Upland wow
wow
wow convenience store
why is lava golden what makes wobble
golden oh looks cute
oh
I like the baskets
in front of their cashier wait what is
that
let me look at that picture
where's that sandwiches that's so hard
to see it's so small they got small
things
oh it's like a a gas station or does it
just normally often come with a gas
station
[Music]
I don't know why I'm I'm inspecting this
I'm very curious right now
it looks really nice it has seemingly a
good atmosphere wait what
Wawa open store in Vienna
it's not Austrian Vienna right what is
there Vienna in
north VA
what
guamas news DC area store opened
Thursday morning in Vienna Virginia
for me but I feel like
that was uh very unrealistic for it to
open in Austria
[Music]
Paris Texas yeah you guys
come up with better names and are not so
confusing come on
what okay continuing where was I oh yeah
twice thank you
Captain jerk pants 636
foreign
[Music]
Alex I hope it didn't hurt when you fell
from the sky and it's not even a pickup
line calling you an angel
foreign
[Music]
okay but you were up there I returned to
science book in the next few days I will
be visiting more cities in Austria
everything is so beautiful here
including the chicks really
how was the view I think that's because
they're beautiful right are you gonna go
to instruct two if you go then let me
know afterwards which one you liked more
and if the answer is not South poor then
I'm gonna hit you with my morning star
where are you are there you are you went
you went to both okay tell me tell me
honestly which one did you prefer that's
for Christmas the sad thing is that
sad's book is I think more touristy than
in this book just because well it's just
it just became like that
it's unfortunate and that probably maybe
ruins a little bit I prefer hashtag well
okay you escaped the question by
choosing a different non-optional answer
but hashtag hashtag is the tourist
destination
it's beautiful but
so basic
such a tourist thing to say but yeah
it's beautiful
you went there too
you saw a lot of good places huh
are you still there
if I look out the window can I see you
hopefully not
what do I have to look out for
chicken wild chickens
okay Munich now oh
so
have you have you done some sightseeing
in Munich too
Munich is still one of the
um cities in Germany that I prefer
um I don't know why but I think like
buildings and so on Austria's buildings
are prettier and more interesting
in a week you've been in Munich for a
week
going wrong next let's go I said that
before when I went to Rome Rome is
Top Notch you're gonna be mind blown
wait are you alone
you should go take a tour at the
Colosseum if you just walk around the
Colosseum the tour guides will pick you
up even if you didn't book anything
it'll be a bit expensive though but it's
nice to hear about it from them with a
friend
yo please enjoy Roma is so amazing
so great
book The Future ah smarty pants okay
I hope you're not getting ripped off
anywhere and oh if you like
um in that there's this area where
um
I had I had oh oh wait you should go to
the ah you should go to the place and I
went with Mommy for dinner because so
close to the tourist attractions I mean
think about it obviously a lot of it is
a scam it's too expensive what was that
uh can I find it if I go to Google Maps
there was this one place you know where
mommy ate my mommy ate the octopus this
kind of small
um restaurant that had really nice
atmosphere cozy that I could really
recommend it was really good you want to
go there I'll try to find out what it
was called
you have to go there
you're taking notes okay let me try to
find if I find it if I go to if I go
here
did I like does does Google take notes
of it and it should know where I went
but like
um
it was it wasn't classy yeah
Google tell me where I went
um
wait is it this one
looks good though
Mommy if you're watching do you know
which one was the restaurant that we
went to
with the
uh the the octopus
I don't know Mommy maybe not watching
location where is it
where is it
um
[Music]
I wanna find it now for you
um
I'm like somewhere in that area on my
map now but
[Music]
when did I do you guys remember when I
went
like which month
foreign
ER
November
okay I went in November
no that's not it
Austria Austria Austria okay that's not
it
end of it okay
yeah okay
[Music]
um
went to a restaurant called Bitcoin
I may open a different window
oh maybe that's it
oh yeah that looks like it yeah
foreign
I want to see the inside
uh
is it
no wait was this just true
no this could be it
did
[Music]
uh
what the [\h__\h] I feel like my brain oh
let me see the area is like
in class Denver I think so it seems
makes sense
makes sense oh
I think that's it
pretty sure
because they make their own noodles I
mean who doesn't I guess in Italy and in
Rome
I think that's it
okay let me write it down did that thing
get the
yes I have I has Android I mean I have
an iPhone too but I don't use it for
this purpose
okay
that was I think my my most recommended
one the other places we went to I think
were okay too but this one was so good
you know that's when I had the oxtail
Bolognese there with the really thick
noodles it was so yummy strong tasting
because I went I didn't want to go for
seafood options but I think they had a
lot of seafood options
if you like seafood
it will be good for you
let me pour some water
wow
I lost some water
[Music]
ah oh God this looks exactly what I ate
it looks so good on the photo
oh yummy ah 180
on the food I think that's what I'm
going to do today yes it looks so good a
good pasta
it looks good
oh the gluta spell because maybe they
have some asparagus spoof I need some
asparagus
I haven't eaten anything with asparagus
yet what a crime
feels like a crime
you know what you should write you
should ask me on Twitter
um after the Stream
okay and if I have some time I'll look
uh into it a little bit more where I was
exactly because I think I showed you
guys pictures and all that but I don't
think I mentioned the name of the
restaurants at least not all of them but
if you write to kiwawa on Twitter if I
see it I'll I'll take some time to look
into where I was and
tell you everything so you can trace
mommy's footsteps
both mommy kiwawa and mommy mama Tori
kiwawa
[Music]
let's continue
um
ah you're gonna be wearing the kfp
hoodie thank you for representing
kwj.com
is a friend that you're around with also
a whole life fan or just you
because if you are all if your friend is
also whole life fan you know what you
should do
you should try to meet up with
European International
cave people
maybe you'll meet some or just you oh
man okay
and then on
wait
only onion
Young
Ali
foreign
um wow wow wow
the nuclear other reduction slap of
Shadows
thanks to the pinky what's the attention
a full series of the Japanese version
of ff7 remake yes of course I would
watch that to keep asking for those
perms to fill out the rest of this the
fast and see collabs are really great
and he'll talk with coconut enjoy your
break thank you uh what break
um
yeah I don't know what's gonna happen
this time for MC uh I I I I don't know
if anyone's gonna be around but the
thing is I'm thinking I might actually
go to Phoenix then try to
improve it and clean it but it's always
such a pain in the ass but that might be
one thing I'll do
oh the weekend about streaming ah yeah
right that was then
yeah
ah yeah this one and we'll turn it into
a Hotline Miami stream I guess
maybe I'll see if anyone has up
reservations a few hours before if not
then
I might not play it we'll see
the Guild Hall or the thing is like
um
like we are in in the talks but very
slow talks but we want to make a plan
together so I shouldn't just like
go ahead and do whatever you know
start without even having a plan because
we don't even have a plan yet if we had
a plan then I could like start working
on it but we don't have one yet we're
just like hey should we really do this
and everyone was like yeah let's do it
that was like two or three days ago
confirming if everyone wants to do it
[Music]
Warden prep what entails Warden prep
the area yeah I just don't know how much
space we need
oh well we'll find something to do
anyway
and that's the Q stream super chance
next is Minecraft
Minecraft there we go
[Music]
cute from now
thank you guys
the book club oh the book club
um
[Music]
it could still happen
but I'm not sure
um
I forgot about it that's for sure
girl stuff give me something
don't worry I got these things on my
mind especially girls songs and don't
stress me out
give me time
it's not a weekly thing
give it time
please let me cook slow cooking
slow cooking Jacob thank you soon every
year thanks for the pinky pinky Kiana I
love you oh sudden suddenly
confession I love you too and I had tons
of fun watching your kill stream
yesterday on the show system instead of
clearly
huh
why did I say I love you I take it back
[Music]
you just said that so you can roast me
afterwards
not very sad I'm very sad I thought it
was true genuine love
you just said that so you could roast me
in peace
hmm
wow
the thing is already I think I already
kind of saw this super chat before
and yet I forgot it was just to taste me
um
Crimson Phoenix
seems like you have another connection
from 6am Jersey
what
it's not the one I already knew about
that said we thanks for the pinky food
fun for Mama Tony no one deserves lack
of tasty food oh that's sweet of you
Mama Told Me currently very happy
because good weather and her garden
is glowing
Garden looking good
[Music]
she's making those noodles probably
daily
you missed it oh it was a lot of fun you
should watch the archive I was screaming
like a strangled monkey
I started off stressed yeah yeah once I
got into the floor it was fun but I'm
guessing that normally you should just
not wait so long for things but oh oh
forgive me I I need to go step by step
sometimes
[Music]
this is the one that we were questioning
if it was the real one I think so trim
orango Duncan Vengeance donation for the
pinky and visiting you for the first
time on a solo trip this fall oh so this
is an appreciation post for your past
German 101 streams I've got six months
to become fluent at cursing When I visit
Germany and Austria it will be useful
right you're visiting EU and you also
come into Germany and Austria
why why don't worry like genuinely you
don't have to know any German you'll be
fine with English
in all of Europe I think
well pretty much I mean sometimes
I think in Spain for example I had some
issues but if you go to the most
touristic places you'll have no issue I
think you good so don't worry but yeah I
think people will be happy to hear a
little bit of uh German but the thing I
never really understand I guess
with like learning just the most basic
things and then using them like saying
hello or thank you and so on in that
country's language
like
it only really serves you if you were
trying to
I don't know suck up to them because
hello and thank you and all that anyone
can understand in English just say it in
English then
you're German or whatever it's not
impressing me at all if you're just
gonna say like three basic words says
anyone knows and anyone can say or
understand in English even even the
people who don't speak a word English
will still know what hello and thank you
means
hmm you're not gonna get nihongo Joseph
by me in German or whatever
yeah so I don't even bother often uh
when I when I'm like somewhere for
example I think in Korea
uh I mean yeah I could say
and so on but often I would just say
just the English words because I feel I
feel like a faker
and and I don't know if I if I make an
attempt at Korean even though I only
knew two words or so back then I mean
why even bother trying
in Indonesia I didn't even know the
simplest words I should have looked them
up but I didn't have time but then in
the end I mean
whatever
no need to fake it speak English for
[\h__\h] sake
it'll be fine
I mean it's not a nice attempt but if
really all you're gonna be able to
remember is like three words
that's not really gonna help you it's
you could just speak English at that
point
um
the sweet thing English speakers make an
attempt yeah yeah
I get yeah I mean really that's the only
effect like you would make whoever
you're talking to just think ah
they tried to speak my language they
tried to speak the most simple words
they tried
nice
yeah you put a little smile on that
person's face
yeah
yeah I'm just saying that
those simple words would come across in
English just fine
you tried if you go to Japan though do
it they'll be like oh
videos no you have to that is part of
our greeting ritual you have to say that
and the problem is if you actually do
speak some German words add to some one
then there's a little chance that they
assume that you actually speak more than
you do and then they'll start rambling
at you in German or whatever language
you know and then you're like
oh [\h__\h] what did I get myself into now
they think I speak German
overestimated
it happened to you
yeah that's that's
um
[Music]
and you gotta be like sorry sorry I
don't speak that much German
I only speak two words
it happened to you
so then just be honest from the
beginning is what I'm telling you then
you won't get into this situation
um
a flirting Facebook well
if you're going somewhere with the
intention of flirting with a lady a
local lady sure
I guess
if it's just supposed to be
something shallow
I guess
wouldn't work on me though
[Music]
twice thank you
no painting information out of Wawa not
allowed neon Phantom Danke Schoen Falcon
boom Danke Schoen thank you thank you
oh yeah all of this was like kind of not
realistic I think
mental Jenny Duncan Jeff star banks of
the pink
car
yeah as always you always a sticker
person you like stickers huh
I like stickers too to put them on my
notes
cute stickers
I put some uh you know because I can't
use French magnets on my fridge
the kiwawa birthday merchandise magnets
I ended up just putting the stickers on
my fridge instead
and the the magnets I put on my on my
microwave
[Music]
same thing though because this is the
same art
just as a sticker and then you know if
you have my birthday merchandise and you
know if you have the stickers you know
there's like certain ones the big ones
that you can just peel off but I thought
that the the little Arts uh that are
around it just as decoration are really
cute too like the little burger and the
little kotoni so I cut it out by myself
because that was still um thicker
material
yeah I also did it yeah so I cut out the
little ones
um
I almost lost my chonkers magnet no help
that's helpful
well yeah so the rest even after you
peeled off all the stickers the rest
like the surrounding things is also
sticker so don't throw it away
um
just kind of cut the shape out and then
you can peel it off
we use the glove for the bake for baking
cakes multiple times nice I feel like
they're pretty big
um I have this one like oven glove
that's out of plastic and it's like a
crocodile shape that one I use all the
time
now the one I have is merchandise I'm
gonna be honest it's a bit difficult to
get a grip with those because they're so
big
I prefer my my old one
but it's nice to have an extra because I
only had one and when I need to hold
things from both sides then it's useful
like a big lasagna thingy or so
um for stuff that is in package
containers so it don't get messy like
frozen lasagna um
yummy sounds good
can you tailor an oven mitten
is it worth it even if you could is it
worth it
oh if you use your airfryer so much
damn I don't
welcome
[Music]
thanks for the pinky and trombone champ
should be in the unfinished section too
since it has a final level boss that you
never be don't tell them
don't
no that was finished
what do I need to do to shut you up
boohoo 723 Duncan invisible
um
thank you thank you
[Music]
Ultimo thanks for two pinkies today is a
very special day do you remember one
year ago on this day you gave me my
employee number and I've been wearing it
proudly ever since oh the two of three
oh yeah and I guess it's also like my
birthday or whatever I can't believe
it's already my third birthday in Cafe
damn
so I found about doing something special
a Carefree cake to show my appreciation
for being part of such a wonderful
Community pictures are up on Twitter
did I see it
I want to see it
yeah you did donate about the Mario
movie
I don't think so
where tweeted at me again again I wanna
see yummy cake I'm really hungry right
now I ate my two of my crepes in the
morning one of them I filled with some
of the remaining Apple
cinnamon stuff that I made it was pretty
good
it tasted like an apple strudel but
instead of the strudel
it was
um crap
pancake rounded
ah right now it's premiering right now
that video
I have to look at that
well I have English
I don't I haven't seen that one
[Music]
oh
no way
[Music]
what that's it
huh
we watch it again
I'll go
hello
[Applause]
could be a good
[Music]
oh goodness
cut that out make that into a PNG for me
I could use that
[Music]
my way
she was role-playing one of the NPCs
that's too little context was it funny
was it funny I don't know if it was
funny
but at least we see some more moving
3D myth
okay let's make a BTN yeah
[Music]
um
okay continuing ah where's my cake
Ultimo if I checked with her now will I
see it
it better be there
oh there it is oh whoa
oh
very yellow
oh wait did you make it yourself
what was inside I want to see the inside
too
yummy
oh I want to see inside did you want to
take a picture of the inside
looks it looks um
like a big ass egg yolk
it was supposed to be orange
maybe it's the light
but good job I want a good taste I'm so
hungry now man it's not there
I want to bake a cake too
but that's too much effort so please
give me a piece of yours okay
there's not much inside I'm not that
good
is it like two layers of sponge cake and
in between like a little bit of cream or
something like that
looks yummy though
good job
and happy belated birthday
congratulations
[Music]
ah congratulations
your third birthday hopefully your
fourth one will also be here with us a
big bunch of biscuit base
um yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum
I'm so hungry
ah
you guys made me so hungry and just
looking at you guys already is
hunger-inducing
you guys look so tasty
Sita
wow
eat me up I'm ready
[Music]
thank you for offering yourself
thank you
I'm hungry I can't focus thank you
Altima when Christian
thank you sure
foreign
[Music]
big kiss for you thanks for the support
I appreciate it thank you soon
your voice is beautiful and also very
cute tension I can literally listen to
you talking and singing Forever Without
ever getting tired of it there's no one
else I'd rather listen to your voice is
the best thank you what prompted that
ah the karaoke
before or after that
Maybe
thank you
I need a nap I need food and I need a
nap and then I'll be happy you know I've
been cuddling so much with my cutthos it
makes me so I'll be
[Music]
I missed them
kind of hope it was after that and that
makes sense
thank you
[Music]
I know I know it's not for everybody but
I'm glad it's for some people at least
um
really happy you like it oh
thank you you're the sweetest
[Music]
so
and yeah I do want to do a plushie
froggy
I'm gonna do that Julian B thanks for
the pinky thank you
black briction evidence
oh this is when I told my whole life
story to you guys
I think
Black Bridge
plushy after no
no
you gotta tape a knife to forgiana plus
you so she can find my two other
Obama plushies Ah that's a good idea
you can have plushy theater
oh the poor Wild Ones
well if it's two hours Against One
Froggy Wawa it should be okay
the Wawa should win I think
hopefully
well I mean your name I said flag bridge
and not black friction wasn't your name
at all
the wow ones
Chihuahua eating a croissant plushies
I'm not gonna waste the merchandise slot
on that no
I'm going deaf no I said your name I
said it's just wrong thought it was
funny
it's you it's about you
use induction
I never get tired of hearing your story
I always support you and cheer for you
even if I'm not in the chat or I'm able
to catch your streams as much lately oh
okay I love your performance at the
fourth Fest and met with honor kfb thank
you thank you wow you did I still need
to watch the remaining Vlogs
um I only watched that one
uh
uh for fast vlog
you need to check out the other ones I
haven't had time yet because they're so
long
or whatever they got recommended to me I
had no time in that moment
yeah but they're good aren't they
you got owned in the day two vlog
what does that mean I need to
investigate
oh an Ian connect Vlog oh that sounds
great I mean it's just like one day but
maybe one could combine it with an ax
Vlog because I'm sure a lot of kfp or
whole life fans will be at ax first
right and then later on in the day go to
the concert or so
anyone was going he's too far gone
well you are you are motion
share ax with me in a vlog please
although must be very overwhelming if
there's someone good at vlogging do it
do it do it
I want to see
sound tired yeah I'm tired I'm always
tired though why am I always tired
uh
by the way I am
oh
skin cancer freak I went to the doc
dermatologist I thought you know I would
be smart to check up because I haven't
checked my my skin bowls uh my
birthmarks in a million years
and they're all good
which is a miracle because I have many
you may not see them but I have many so
you know could have been any of them
yeah
I don't know
the sunburn oh yeah she she did say
something about myself I was like right
before I went to her I picked up in the
store I picked up after sun
and she was like well you should not
only put actors on you should put before
you know something there but I said well
you know I I know I know it's too late
now but
yeah the first the surprise son of
spring that you don't expect to get a
sunburn from it big bamboozled
and not only after sun before Sun mm-hmm
yeah but I think it's quite common at
least my sunburn is not that big it was
pretty small but you know
it probably will not be the last sunburn
of the year for me
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
excitement from the game made me very
tired I screamed so much
but let's play it again it was so much
fun
if I need like a shorter stream again
I'll I'll do a Hotline Miami
um I want to finish it I won't let
motion put any more unfinished games on
my games list and ruin my overall score
[\h__\h]
na
yeah I'm gonna treat myself to some food
food
what time is it oh 6 p.m
[Music]
motion too easily as potions
nah it's okay it's okay you're just
doing your job
probably still the highest game finisher
in the end at least
if you think about it I should be but I
was shocked when I saw the amount of
Unfinished games
but you know all of those are never you
know what the intention of finishing
them well I guess it doesn't count I
have a higher game finisher score than
you huh
I am the game finisher
[Music]
is there scores is there like um
like statistics for the other members
too
those pie charts is there a pie chart
for the other ones too
there's probably a huge piece of pie
that's unfinished games
I want to see
yeah because most of them just leave it
open-ended all the time yeah
uh
I'm always close to you at one point in
terms of completed games really woo
I guess she plays more shorter games
that you can finish and the most of the
games that I finish are really long
commitments
um
I'm gonna play some short fun games you
know like the the alligator stuff
ah Oblivion well that's a short a long
series of hers
and she said
fairing didn't she respect for that man
what's the next long game it will be uh
tears of the Kingdom starting soon this
month right I think this month oh I saw
a cat walking by meow meow meow
I will ignore the Outlast comment
next week oh yeah I actually already put
it on my schedule I want to play on
release day
I'm worried I'm really worried
do you guys think I'll be decent at it
like it already looked always kind of
challenging when I watched Dom tend to
play and he's good at these games
supposedly
I'll be fine really
I'm scared you'll die a lot in the
beginning
roofline's good
that was pretty good today wasn't it
um
apparently there's Crocs again
those little beasts sizzle the Rascals
they're there to be collected again
I guess you needed something to make
your inventory space bigger again
because that's what they were for before
well my English is so weird today isn't
it
it sounds weird to me yeah if we didn't
sell the games before I guess but this
one just feels intimidating to me
um
Cox
if you can do this good at Hotline Miami
you can come for anything you are you
saying I did good in Hotline Miami
don't don't give me false confidence
April I did fine
foreign
[Music]
I am drunk on praise now I have tears in
my eyes
my voice survived damn
all those Subaru screams
scream compilation no no no no please no
calculate let's not make just the scream
compilation let's just make an overall
clip okay if anything
I'm not asking for it no no asking for
the scream compilation
cause that would be very painful
oh hi donkey one all right bye-bye
[Music]
I'll be later on Callie's channel for
ctrp man
okay I mean I hope this is some funky
meows just did she see a fly
a really funny meal I'm gonna check up
on her
bye
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]