n
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
hi Darlings this is Hall life English ad
Dev one and only narissa Raven Crow I'm
sick but thank you for coming to more
leg of
legginess legs for days we love legs leg
I love leg I'm wearing a mask so I don't
get these lovely ladies
sick thank God we're just virtual yeah
thank
God how did Ione do it
today
J
jood J
jood I'm ready for Leal lean I'm ready
for Le a Le
and then Path of Exile 2 came out today
did you see kiaha I was going to play
that but then I you know the the queue
isn't looking very good with over a
million and um just didn't seem very
likely that I was going to play anything
today so good luck everybody's invite
came at a good time yeah over a million
it's really bad the server is down too
so right now yeah it's down and it's an
hour in and people in KY are not in but
I didn't expect anything else it's not
running game is not up God uh oh oh yeah
the game is not up so there is no
quue
okay so good luck gigy later all right I
was like should I be logging in right
now to get through but it's not even up
then n you can't can't even get in path
of EX out we should we should play yeah
I'm I'm
I I would yeah yipp
yippe let's play When the servers calm
down more yes all right yeah I was
thinking so too maybe like next
week yeah would be safer next
week are you girls showing your like
this the screen like the where the names
are yes
okay I shall I'll even show them my DMs
with you what the
p.m. I just opened my and it's
redownloading all 80 gigs of Path of
Exile so I hope I lag in League of
Legends
amazing amazing this will be
great this will be hello wonderful hello
okay I'm back
okay
hello
hello what are we
aing what what
what we want to still my cats even
though she has her own now messed up no
Raa no messed up messed up
indeed get yourself more then don't take
mine away steal them steal them this
have gotten two minimum anyway narissa I
could have told you that
no why no you just want to steal are you
a kleptomaniac are we ready to play some
League of
Legends audio check can we do yeah
everyone introduce
yourselves
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh G mood Le of Legends Cecilia
spin League of
Legends don't think that's the game name
Elizabeth oh League of
Legends Nissa Raven crop spin a win
League of
legs it sound like nerve nerv veras if
you're nervous I
am she
is uh uh Top Lane uh and and H singer
checking my ass out W leag of Legends
all right what what is he doing we ready
to find a match thumbnail he's checking
my ass out CeCe I am too CeCe you ready
aren't we matching am I ready yeah U
yeah I think okay we
match so
loud very
loud we I have to switch to window
anyway do I choose a character here yeah
I can choose
by
exciting yeah yeah whoever you want all
right who
we
[Music]
okay I'm going to start
off with uh uh uh uh rats rat rats rat
theat rat top fight don't question it we
are the rats rats rats rats rats ooh
what that choosing seraphine I see I see
yeah I'm your support wait I'm I didn't
pick
yet uh you got I feel like I picked
click lock in I think you have already
locked in have you
ohing
uh uh select your runes oh
God I have no runes okay there we go
ruins okay H I
think I think it's good now okay okay
sorry guys I'm I'm struggling with uh
audio balancing my biggest
weakness it's okay okay window
switch oh my God I love your AR
skin wow hot KDA k k
down down down down down down take it to
the
top should I buy this world
atlas good luck what do I buy did your
girls not buy items I bought
items buy little red potion K I think
what what what's Sor what buy the little
red potion I think that's a nice okay
why is the camera so
weird oh you camera the click the camera
at the bottom and it will follow you oh
thank you you hit Y and it'll follow and
unfollow you you'll have to answer a lot
of beginner questions it's
okay W Senpai um thank
you so well in the shop W Senpai it does
give you suggestions so I mean I buy the
little St that it pops up with it at the
start when you open it initially okay I
did that too gig and narissa are the
peeps like that know it inside out yeah
so careful with the
tower who did you say that to to me kill
everyone and and and and kill the
minions and
okay don't die all right I don't have a
a distance
anymore AR I like the way you said
minions oh wait let me change my I'm
going to make filet minion out of them H
yes yes oh God goodbye thank you
goodbye goodbye and I click and then
click and click click the things and
press the buttons yes yes yes I'm here
for you my
queen I have fed the enemy don't do that
they're Bots oh oh what what would be oh
what would be
do B is to go back to base go home like
teleportation yeah
oh it has a channel time and people can
cancel it by hitting you
oh
uhoh am I alone in
your your skin keeps making me think
I've accidentally got dmca music on or
something no I'm so
sorry like I'm always like did I leave a
tab on no just just list to League of
Legends the most with in the game is
like the camera to just like have to
hold it down and I keep
forgetting I die again hold it
down like
space
oh you don't have to if you don't want
to you can press y to keep it
fixed really oh
yeah let's go let's go oh shop oopsie
uhoh good it's
okay
press she was waiting for me even even
now don't do that you're
welcome thank you are You The Bard yes I
the wrong button please avenge me that
snake lady has been bullying
me thank you that was good
timing oh why did the they have a
jungler is that a jungle character okay
they have a jungler
why you leave her I thought she was
doing
fine I guess not R rat you must live
rat I am rat let hey turn get
her okay okay are you ready getting
better CeCe what CeCe right here thisy
right here yes okay yes she is so
confused an she has no I thank you yay
she's dead we did itff
transfer chat what in in short words
because I can't look at the the text
what does w do in this
case it's a passive and breaks armor
okay wait now I can
read the
same I don't have to do anything it's
just always
working what's always working my
passive yes nice we got her okay yeah
yeah yeah reset rats rats we are the
rats we are the rats the rat world of
Atlas was it not
good yeah I think the way V works is you
hit something three times and then they
take more damage and then her Q goes
through terrain and walls but charge it
up and she has one more skill forgot
what it does but
something it like does AOE
stuffs it's a bit much right now I don't
understand in your that's
okay yeah I snake here
grab I don't
understand to eat the gr she shot my
[Music]
booty too late
okay did I not sell it did I sell the
wrong
thing what' you sell I don't know
an item
that I didn't need I guess but uh
whatever I sold and I bought again oh
okay
skin she's
living what is she up
[Music]
to grubs leave me alone leaving where's
your mid laner what how where are they
yeah where are they hold Q to fly
longer the Mida is here it's
Misfortune their jungle bot takes void
grubs
ew what to grubs is this an objective I
just can't believe the b in this game
take objectives they're annoying
n so how what how many times have you
girls played this as a collab already
third time three yeah wow hey you in
bottom Lane mother trucker I remember
you I'm I'm
dead don't die don't
die help me kill them l no no wait come
back don't do it oh the deer is here the
deer is here oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
dear dear oh dear thank you she's being
really mean fly longer
through oh oh oh you got this this that
is a
deer isn't it I was you send me the a
little deer
de it's okay almost back Li I'll support
you she's Charmed she's Charmed kill her
I'm asleep run from
Tower what get away from
me
what I ran too late I uh oh I committed
too much where are my
minions minion they're dead that's
messed up don't worry I'm here to take
your farm why would you do that to me I
leave don't comeing back Nissa are kind
of crazy all the things they're
doing what is
this don't be afraid go my little
minions oh minions cute cute
cute oh no Cecilia is grew now
[Music]
how do I buy
that buy what no would have been F
probably oh there's another one I didn't
even see that one uh oh watch out if you
see that white thing around her it means
the next spell she hits you with you'll
get
stunned oh
okay I see
yeah go blood flame go blood Flame
she's a queen get drag you
fool what an idiot true what an
idiot is there like did you set these
Bots to a high difficulty or so they're
normal could they be easier yes not
I have a bad match up no you're
okay you'll do fine difficulties is it
normal it's normal why is the horse on
our side horse kill the horse oh what is
that uh it's just like um oh the dragon
oh God I'm going to
die just explained it like me and I
still don't understand explain why what
the what the
um the stake that um gives us gold and
gives us some passive staff so it's a
good objective to get W it's an enemy we
have to kill or yeah it's a jungle mob
don't worry okay usually in like actual
games people fight around this and then
you have to be aware but we're just
playing B doesn't matter too much I I
got
this you sound like you totally got this
i got this I'm going to go top for a
little bit got this you going to be good
down here
mhm I cannot tell the one thing I can't
tell these games it's like winning on us
evil jungler just took my my my Raptors
you're
Raptors yeah I can't believe that Bots
counter jungle
you I just can't believe it it's weird
it's weird right yeah it's so strange
that that b will counter jungle
you so should I CH choose someone that's
far away chat
probably yes run after me you fool and
an enemy has been
slain get out of
there
nice all these before i k that maam get
out of here what the freak are you doing
in here I'm here no go in the forest
care careful careful get a B I'm
running oh that completely missed that
was nowhere near her where' she go wait
where is she Kaitlyn yeah maybe I want
raged Kaitlyn is the one
goodbye kayin is not
little well yeah blue
blue did you watch Arcane did everybody
watch Arcane no I haven't seen the
second season yet but I've
seen I watch both finished my Twitter
feed has se the second season of
I loved it although the second season
was a bit
rushed yeah a lot of things that they
were she charm she TR getting down
mhm copia is going back so you should be
able to get the tower pretty much
undisturbed mhm
okay charm she's Charmed she's
Charmed oops she did not run where I
wanted her to run ow ow good
job oh I'm turning I'm turning
she stunned she stunned
owie thank gosh damn you're having a
party there are you a DJ some else yeah
it's a it's a it's a
party oh the snake is back that's
okay oh careful back up a little bit
I wanted to use my ulti
yeah did I use it at oh my God leave me
alone work
Al all right let's yes come here mother
trucker you want come here if they stay
we can kill
them okay let's just kill
her watch out she know how to
combo oops that's that's a
minion oh you
here careful care she's
Charmed
careful I'm dead wow kill her kill her
kill hery yay
okay I'll kill her for you thank you
good job should have gone in there I see
the second
enemy people don't red red how do I do
Jing again and he's gone back to Jungle
ah no she's not okay I've got her back
good luck
Kiara get
this
no har has Nine Kills is she related to
Naruto back off buddy no she's a goho
well she is a ninetail fo so yeah
the oh goho like the
Korean thank
you yay we got her no come back come
back come back
nice you're getting toxic you're
learning the ways of League of Legends
yes it's true I shouldn't I shouldn't I
mean no you got this enemy bot you would
you go come here Lily jungle wonderful
bot let's go out of
range I'm going to try a different
character yeah I can't get thaty
me oh boots no which
boots there's so many boots which boots
should I buy I'm sorry I didn't have my
heal up you can get some
cheap I can't
afford I need cheap the basic
[Music]
boots you are Gucci I was being
pery oh there's three why are there
three people in mid that's not this is
not fair guys this is not fair top and
obsessed with you yeah they they just
you just are very
intimidating your
St my way oh oops on my way mid never
mind everyone left you yeah I she one
died
League leg League of leg
[Music]
okay I really like um like I don't know
if this is like the character or if it's
just the skin but when she teleports
home she like creates a oh that's the
skin yeah it's really
cool she creates invisible stairs and
then she sits on the throne that's so
leing Throne of legal
legging of
thr my favorite top Champion was always
Riven cuz she's voiced by Christina V
yeah can't fight
her
great oh what's that what's that what
the Inferno blazes what does it mean
they took the dragon so now there's
things that'll pop up on this the map oh
okay
nice nice job
yay God I'm zoning
out like mentally or in the yeah in the
my brain I wish I could zone out but I
can't even Zone
in just chilling playing leag with the
ladies we
vibing you got this you got this you got
this ah
yes aome cute look at you go oh my
God now thanks to
narissa she had to go it's all because
of narissa I'm going to die no you're
not I I'm I'm going to back you got this
no you're not you got this you're so
strong oh my god let's push the tower
push the tower yeah yeah get the
tower I guess I'll push a tower too
she's behind
you don't
worry oh you're you're going crazy
you're going crazy you're crazy you're
crazy you're crazy you're crazy and
because of that in a good way and I have
a friend and I'm going to bring you a
friend don't worry where am I going why
am running this way that's a cute friend
he's also crazy I di oh no oh no but I
sacrificed myself for a good purpose
yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm going to go
crazy again my first successful die
let's
[Music]
go I died
wow without my diving license can't
believe it hey you're doing really good
no I'm not don't lie no for first time
you got
this sure first time is Vai this is
great I sucked as Vai when I first
played
[Music]
V th looks
difficult let's go
but is really hard yeah she's really
really difficult I thought she was GNA
people were saying she's like one of the
easier ones no they lied to you in the
jungle she's a pretty simple jungler
yeah J desty yay a tower is
destroyed things unfortunate oh speed
for
moment wow
I'm
here I I missed I shouldn't it's
okay let's get her let's get her got
this yeah get the kill get the
kill nice look at
you
sure you you doing it it's your first
time how does this work take the
compliments
oh Annie's going you you got this you
got this you're crazy you're crazy she
sleeping you oh oh no
no I was trying to figure out how to
make my how to make my LTI work but I
think I have to stand still to use it or
what I don't think you have to stand
still I was pressing it the whole time
you have to press and then click
again on the person you want to use it
on or if you press um the settings oh in
um there's like these little arrows that
you can if you just hover over a person
you can use them instead of having to
click on
them
okay hey if if someone can help me just
get the inhibitor
bottom we'll have mega creeps and we can
abandon
Lane hi thank you
hello oh is it left
click everything seems to be right click
in this game oops is it left
click it's it's left click I actually I
don't remember I just do it by muscle
memory I have no
clue
yay
woo H
okay
W let's try again no woo
okay let's go mid every
time but it worked this
time enem
oh it's fine no it's just
me how dare you kill
narissa dare mother TR her away from us
nice L how do I buy
wild you're you're
bad okay what are we doing
team um what do I buy when I'm out of
stuff
push whatever whatever makes you happy I
always like to go for a rabadon's death
cat a a hat rabon's death C okay good I
forgot if if your ability power
yeah I
forgot
Rec don't kill
out um no I ran out of the things on
that one list that you sent me like the
three main items you lived by this and
then I did that's
amazing hello
nice welcome strong I thought the Dare
was going to me she's try she's TR okay
get her too get her to get her get her
get her she's so
fast don't worry we're here get her get
her nice nice nice nice get the
tower
okay get the inh him
what is that called what did you call it
inhib it's an
inhibitor
okay my now what now end oh behind
behind two behind us oh I'm
dead no you're not s you no you're not
her so Kiara if you attack uh
if you attack them
over when when there's not Creeps in
front of you or if you attack someone
over a
tower like the the tower will start
attacking you so if you're in the
tower's vicinity don't attack one of the
enemy
Champions
okay and if there's no creep don't don't
go up by the
tower no creep yeah what's the creep
the little gu fighting for you oh
minions
yeah
[Music]
okay live live live it's okay our creeps
are going to end dead it's
fine um Team okay I'll end the game
don't worry woo we won oh yay easy
easiest game of our
life so easy we're
winners easy winners we're winning we
are winners we are winners we are
winners AFP dinner
e yay first win of the day amazing our
first win of our
lives so
easy so
easy do you guys want to do intro Bots
or let's do real people oh actually K
should pick what pick what you want to
keep playing Bots or you want to do
people or you want to do bots all the
real people going to be easier than the
Bots just
depends there might be a chance that if
we go with real people we still get bots
like I'll be right back you guys talk
about what you want and then tell me
when I get back can we easy
Bots I mean I I I don't mind either way
I like playing against real people I'm
not sure if we can play against real
people yet since K is on a new account
we might have to more games right before
but we can see if we can go into Quick
Play
yeah maybe we should do bots first and
then um well right now we did M medium
Bots and we won uh so either we should
do maybe we should do hard Bots to see
if we can keep up against hard Bots
before real people mhm
mhm maybe maybe can I do Caitlyn and Top
Lane you can play yeah whoever wherever
yeah okay be whoever you want to be just
have just yeah just mix it up okay I
want to try her Kaitlyn Kaitlyn
Kaitlyn's F
that's Caitlyn and VI perfect
[Music]
match all these discounted skins
purchase purchase I'm
back welcome back thank you okay what
did we decide on what are we up
to and Bots okay Bots and do you just
want to do beginner Bots
I'm not sure what was the
conclusion we'll
do oh I feel like we can handle the same
level of bots you did really well yeah
we did beginner Bots we were playing
beginner Bots oh we're playing beginner
Bots oh we'll continue we're doing
middle Bots okay
okay okay there's intro beginner and
intermediate I'll do whatever
okay continue are we all ready mhm we're
waiting on kiar okay I'm pressing
buttons okay let's play you're already
perfect at the
game I don't like how that is Caitlyn
let's go let's lock in our
relationship yeah let's I try she's like
a narissa but with a gun what if we all
made a star Guardian team
who I do I need to buy a skin for that I
have so much star Guardians there's star
Guardian
Ari how much cost there's also star
Guardian usually like I think star
Guardian skin would be around
$15 oh 15 or 15 yes
15 I get to use my you're going to be de
if I want to invest into this game by
giving it money I will decide after the
stream okay that is
fair although I do want to look pretty
in the star Guardian skin why are you
Sona wait let's talk real quick what's
What's Happening Here for funsies okay
we'll win wor about it is it a problem
if she we're both supports is the only
issue want you you can build
AP go car yeah you can be anyone
anything okay
so anything you
want okay what do we
have are we already
running yeah can we do the thing where
we like kill them in the in the in the
bushes yeah we can we'll have to go over
here I'm so fast okay I'm fast as fudge
boy yeah I'm speeding
chos let's
go
hi I like your hat thank you I like your
ball orb oh no not the snake again why
do we get same characters there everyone
here they killed my ward
no we can try killing them I'm sure
they'll follow rata she's not even
running kill her kill her her I can't
tell yes yes get her get her kill her
get her get her get
her yeah first Blood hell yeah get him
uhoh I'm dead I'm dead no no no help me
you're not dead you're not dead you're
not dead I him I you y thank you get her
get her can die to
okay very strong power this I'll take
this this is mine
now nice the minion are here to save us
okay bye
goodbye you're
welcome thank you it was all it was all
us yes
yes oh we killed them tried being
through that
Walla can't believe you're here with
us yay I am here
uh I'm running for I Am low on health
yeah you
better what do you mean you
better you sound like you're directly
out of the game like I wasn't sure if
that was a game vo or
not should voice all the characters
let's mute the game and just have her do
it yeah can you make the noises Bard
makes I don't know what can you make my
S he sounds like like
wi her scream when she
[Applause]
[Music]
dies
d oh
beautiful
[Laughter]
pushing oh always missed the last hit on
these stupid minions no you're so
[Music]
good not bad though I don't know how to
ad carry sarapen you don't have to ad
carry just AP carry I don't know what
that means oh just just build like
normal AP items I don't know how to AP
carry your
radons RAB I just get my
rabadons yeah you can build your
rabadons where she going cuz she's a
coward surrender she's a coward kill her
she's Charmed she's Charmed B from be to
heal is normal
okay I'm out of Mana
I want
fight if we can just keep getting them
to go back even it's not too bad because
then they they don't get to level I need
healing thank
you can't do anything she's so low but I
can't do it I'm out
of guess I shouldn't have used all the
man on the minions minions
[Music]
seriously oh you can hide in the bushes
too like in the in the Pokemon game too
like you disappear when you're in the
bushes happening here you could become
stealth going on an assassin night
dragon dragon dragon
bees Dragon where Dragon
where Where Are You Dragon
us what happening here how do I are we
still on beginner bot [\h__\h] yeah they're
very strange
oop she keeps like zooming behind me
it's so
frustrating What if I
what have you want what have you want
what you want nothing nothing nothing
nothing nothing
nothing what have you want what do you
want
though oh rest in
peace ma'am stop it ma'am stop it ma' up
let us kill
you thank you good kill
I don't get the kill if the tower the
kill I don't get any like exp work on
leveling oh you're only level never mind
I'll stay you
back out of
here how does she know I'm
here I don't
know secret
Ward yeah I'm just trying to hit this
how does she have the knowledge that I'm
here these Bots are cheating nice of
course they are BS are always
cheating they're stream sniping I heal I
heal I heal I heal
[Applause]
Y how could they stream snipe that's so
rude I know it's so cringe of these
b i I have now
minions minions minions minions
minions and I go back us thank you used
to her thank
you thank you for the
assist should I go back for it
really I'm I mean Nissa I'm fighting
your mirror match oh
it's a dou
g do
that nice one thanks you're the best
you're the best
[Music]
musico what why are they getting these
an
ally how do the Bots know to get this
it's over no it's not over it's over I
diet's over there somebody in the bushes
BF sword what sorry BF big [\h__\h] sword
I didn't know what to buy is that what I
got oh I did get the BF sword nothing
wrong with the BF
sword oh okay okay
so takes a moment to channel line up the
perfect shot then
fires oh
no oh
no
inter all
right no he's running away I oh oh
that's not what I wanted to flash
oops
big big large
wall big very large
wall oops I don't like AER really
really no she keeps like she keeps like
I'm about to charm her then she
teleports behind me and she goes nothing
personel appreciate
[Music]
that yay I got her
yay oh my my B how does that happen
because I'm I'm connected to Le internet
what your stream died oh my God that's
really weird but your stream died yeah
rest in peace OBS issue it's okay it's
back it's back but
[Music]
yay welcome back from the
dead
back sorry woo well you missed me
killing 20 enemies yeah all of them all
of them killed every single one of
them don't kill me this is
mine oopsie I forgot if you hit someone
it was okay ah
he's confused he lacks critical
knowledge oh God I'll played her
yeah I went into Caitlyn I sent Caitlyn
back into her closet she was
invisible you
watch you heard her no yeah you heard me
you let me kill you let me I don't think
we should do that no I got her oh
god let's go
[Music]
minions let's eat more Snake
flesh snake for dinner snake
sausage snake sausage I already ate six
sausages
today
yeah
impressive impressive display I know
impressive display it's very unlike of
Caitlyn oops I should have done
the oh what's
this woven into everything I've got a
back
okay can we have a Like A League of
Legends voice pack from Elizabeth yeah
right oh oh God she's going into the
bushes you're not going to escape me
imagine running away from a
Healer
to why come back CL I have to be ignite
I feel like often I press it and nothing
happen come here come here come here you
H over it you can see the
range no there's another one
fre and another one you'll be fine
you're Sona another one okay okay okay I
need to go
oh no we
Running Oh Maybe
not maybe
not so many unactivated traps so
sad what do I do don't die way me on a
hover board okay
okay oh God how low are you very oh my
God you're very low 26 HP I died to
sarapen she aled me she how she do this
you're the sarap I know how could she I
have a
skin yes get hit by the turret yes
fool
yay these Bots are awesome I like yeah I
like when they run into the turrets
because it's like I would do that like
for you would do
that yeah
but I haven't today oh
yeah for my audience I kept getting
confused which one which which which
Towers were ours so I kept rning
into I think I think Le Riot gave me
free RPS so I did buy more seraphine
skins thank you R free stuff too Rian
please we can we can ask
there's two of them why are there two
what am I going to do okay one ran away
no next time
boots did not Riot give me free stuff or
I'm a I'm going to
Riot going to
Riot yeah before we start
rioting just kidding just kidding I'm
sorry Riot I have so much respect for
you sorry Mr RI we already are rii
get away from
me good trade it's good if I if I die
and I say good trade is that like does
it nullify any negativity I've created
yeah cre good trade good trade good
trade it's cre space for my TR your
skill good trade good trade good trade
good trade
oh nice go team finally the turret is
gone
we can now move on with our
lives all move on with our lives and
then the next
tet Target the
Aurelia no come why would you come here
aelia I'm trying to get this Rift
Herald
yeah my Rift I work so hard
on I'm a little bit too happy when I uh
kill a champion as you should be that's
good that's your life
Blood come over here has walk over here
I'm so
low your
little watch brain wants me so bad I'm
so
low walk over here just walk over
here this
delicious yeah come get
me come on over here keep pressing D and
nothing happens soise I don't get itbe a
little
closer do you also have it quick
casted oh
yes walk up
here sh her o she's charm she's charm
yay that'll show her for trying to take
my Rift
heral wonder I can get it
now my 3,000 gold it's
okay uh we fight for our
lives of us I do this one got to get a
needlessly large rod
lessly large yeah needless it's so
needlessly
large that's why I need
it
okay necessar necessarily large
Rod
yeah uhoh I slowed okay I'm fine live
live I live I live totally ignored me no
respect
oh no yeah yes come here sarap yes you
want me you want to eat oh she ran away
yes walk over here you want
us I'm on
over
damn okay Retreat tactical Retreat
tactical
retreating leaving my minions
behind for a better time and I'm going
to buy boots boots boots
boots boots maybe can I buy a potion
too
yeah here we
[Music]
go o nice let me get her let me get her
get her get her get her you get her you
get her I'm letting you get her y crazy
you guys are really
pushing right into
shall we go and help
M your team destroyed an inhibitor
inhibitor you said that an inhibitor
never heard of it okay an inhibitor an
inhibitor an inhibitor destroy an
inhibitor Goodbye Oh don't die dude stop
following me dude dude stor
stor dude
[Music]
yeah I keep forgetting about my
old see hi hi hi I'm here to
help
hi hi everyone oh I'm standing in it how
am I standing in it help
help o was everyone screaming
about okay okay okay okay ow she's
Charmed she's Charmed kill her crazy
yay y yipp
yipp you're on a rampage Ki you're crazy
yeah look at you
crazy that's
fine I'll avenge you nice to have I
won't let them get away with
this uhoh
uhoh oh why you run over here
yes yes you're
crazy uhoh oops I didn't mean to do that
run away run away run
away no I'll avenge you
too I meant to go here but I click I
clicked on oh my God let me out let me
out let me
out am I clicking the hardest part is
like the moving with the mouse because
like I you you you click because you're
trying to get away but Mouse is
completely in a different place than you
thought it
was and then you always walk into wrong
areas
hi hi thanks for the
heal got this I don't think I do
but scr over to you and I just see like
four enemies in of you
if I had more if I had more Mana I could
have done it you can do it you got this
one
more one
more come here
sarine what music I positive music maybe
it's the star
Guardian it's so
pretty God life
walk back over
here yeah don't be a coward Bots come on
yeah come on walk over here we're just
beginners just beginner
bot
healing okay now we're winning
[Music]
heing Victory May I'm in the
lives so
easy um I need we're ready for
intermediate B what I need to get water
okay me too actually sorry I'm like
since I'm sick I'm drinking so much
water that's good drink more yes drink
more watery girl I am so thirsty do I
still not have this skin oh I just need
the
I I was about to kill myself okay I'll
be right back don't do it don't do it
okay I'll be um yeah I'll be be mhm KD
still on my stream water KDA
k
k it
is again what do it
mean
k what does it
mean it lookist
doggy
animals oh so they saying it's killed
def assist yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah W
you got that way faster than me and
Cecilia did really really I don't know
if that's really fast yeah yeah yeah I
didn't notice until Cecilia brought up
she was like oh kill death like assist
and I was
like why is this why is this y are they
telling me I did bad for what my
character could do
potentially or is it just because that's
me what's yellow my damage dealt to
Champions is it just because it's me
okay okay yeah yeah yeah I thought they
were dissing
me can you get skins with the blue stuff
or not um there's the they sometimes
bring back like a blue Essence store but
it's usually a lot of blue Essence it
was here
recently don't know where it went I
don't know if it's still here what are
these mystery boxes oh it's here oh the
mystery which
one what when what you need I want can
you explain them to me like these loot
Loot Crate Box thingies are they in your
inventory inventory is it in your
inventory in my inventory sometimes you
get these like chest that you can use
and it give you character shards or skin
shards or um Wards and stuff but you
have to unlock it
with this other currency that you get
from breaking down what you get from
boxes
a I maybe
see so none of these loot boxes have
skins the loot boxes have skins if you
buy a loot box you can get a
skin there will go too right no where
there's
these City mystery mini icon
icons how are we doing
gers good good yeah are we ready do we
want to up the bot
difficulty sure by one maybe there's
only one more to go okay let's go nice
okay let's search we got this we got
this we got it let's search search the
BS that want to play against us yeah I
hope we find I am seeking Bots change
the world let's change the
world okay KDA skin time yay woo for me
I mean you're flexing so hard bro I had
to play to unlock this skin I'm
flexing still flex no I had to play so
much to unlock her we we'll get you a
pretty skin too K don't worry next time
I know I don't know who this guy is but
he reminds me of like someone from
Myspace he look beautifully sad yeah
yeah he looks like a MySpace guy oh
sorry I don't
know why P pool party Kaitlyn p po party
oops pool party pool party I want pool
party yeah no snake this time oh there's
a
cow cute oh there's a little
guy
cute Fair quart Lux oh it's Lux oh no I
hate Lu oh it's over oh yeah I feel like
I heard some bad things about Lux but
did not understand the context what do
you mean I don't know
evil um her bot AI really good because
she's really good at aiming skill
shots robot
yeah can we kill them all in the bushes
again yeah go over here D it thank
you wonder if oh this guy has a big
paintbrush let's go
okay I'll wait for everyone to get here
oh n you look so cute thank you we match
now y We Ready sparkly yeah I'm ready
ready to press the one button I have I'm
just going to look up this
guy
I'm
got don't
flash oh you thank you for a heal yeah
you're welcome nice thank you everyone
goodbye goodbye not here I'll just go
back to my uhoh oh no Lux is in the
middle it's over she's in the middle
she's always M she's a lux and she's in
the middle hate her she's Lux and she's
in the middle okay I'm not the same
person I was two weeks ago Lu in the I
will not lose to this spot this time
yeah you not the same person person what
did I do he's like the guy
from uh from
Naruto which one
sigh his name s I love sigh the guy you
drew that's
right he drew stuff yes
artist arti yeah how does he see me in
the
bushes if you hit him and then the
minions aggro you they'll reveal your
location and the bush oh yeah so if
you're aded by something it'll show
yourself he's so
cool
yeah
yeah can run your crimes is what I want
to say to Walter
White are you planning on watching saw
after yeah
totally I'm so excited I'm like halfway
through the last season of Breaking Bad
you're so close I think I'm going to
finish it tonight
maybe also I saw I saw I was in a museum
yesterday and um I saw a painting that
really looked like Walter White I took a
picture of it I need to show it to you
guys later to anybody who understands
what he looks like in the first place it
looks so much like him bald and and
glasses and
everything and depressed fa not really
depressed oh no push me in he pushed me
in Oh no just like his face just says
he's got issues
wow I agree he kicked me into the the
thing he's
rude
wow I'm a cute my space boy that draws
yeah come
on I never used my space yes even though
it was popular when I was
smaller uhoh an ally has SL my space was
too cool for me you run into our Tower
no but I I should have gone home like
ages ago a and I kept thinking I should
use my Mana before going home and then I
didn't oops
oh a pot of tea a bottle of
water
water bottle of water bottle of water
bottle of
water here I'm ready for
you are you bad really yeah I'm here I'm
here she charm her charm she's Charmed
she's Charmed she's Charmed all right
all right I'm on her I'm on her I'm on
top of her I'm on top of her okay
GG I feel like when it's two versus one
it becomes a little bit unfair why why
come here little cow what what do you do
when you're
not ideally in the game you're not you
have like a better understanding or like
you you know where the jungler is and
you know when to not overextend so she
wouldn't have been in that position in
the first place if she
was watching a map or she wed or she not
in the middle
should I and you are close to the middle
should I tell
you when I'm about to engage it's up to
the jungler because it's like um they us
evaluate the kill potential if like if
they went mid would you guys be able to
get a kill mhm or if just like other
objectives cuz even though you might
engaged they like oh it's not worth it
cuz I have to go to this other place
right now and it would waste much time
here I wanted
to in a game though but since this a
black game I can just come
in I wonder what skins he
[Music]
has oh you're so Mana poor good thing
she's not level six
yet I'm dead NOP I got her don't worry
don't worry I'm going home I'm going
home go home go
home go home yes go
home uh zigs is missing any minute now
oh there we
[Music]
go can you believe that
airplanes in the night sky are like
shooting stars yeah I can't
believe nice oh nice I'm going back
good I hear robots yeah you sound very
roboty right now
you oh
intentional I'm almost there I'm almost
there it must be the
p is it the ping okay charm CH charm
yeah yeah yeah
awesome I'll fix it in a minut yeah
it's am i w am i w
w oh wait I need man
good thank you like
him really good yeah you sound
good is there no Mana
potions in the shop no oh in the
shop there's like a refillable potion
but
people don't usually get it or it
depends on what champ in you're
playing I can't buy it oh why why is it
locked
there used to be but removed yeah the
cookies give Mana
uhhuh I love
cookies have you girls had some
Christmas cookies
yet have you girls been to some
Christmas markets yet no I did in a
voice pack not yet yeah right it's so
it's all just a lie I did in a voice
pack in the last 3 days I went to like
six Christmas markets that's aw speed
running Christmas Market I totally did
competitive Christmas mark and it made
it even more obvious like I never
noticed how like all the shops are so
repetitive in the Christmas markets but
it's it's still nice it's still nice but
it's really nice what's your favorite
Christmas Market uh snack this will
decide
everything get him get him get him get
him
[Music]
H the Germans are talking about German
[Laughter]
things can't
do o
[Music]
those are like candied almonds they're
like they're like roasted candied
almonds caramelized roasted yeah they're
really good they bought at the Christmas
markets I Leta eat them and she was so
fascinated she was like oh my God this
is the [\h__\h] in a good way good it's like
just the right amount of super week you
know M and crunchy and
crunchy uhoh uhoh he pushed me away
thank
goodness I'm going to heal up y go
ahead level I'm strut
away a he's
painting he's painting he's a
painter he's a painter
compare
toti attack me do I still sound like a
robot youed no no you sound noral oh it
fixed itself nice you didn't even have
to do anything you so I didn't even
touch
it Elizabeth Rose blood
[Music]
flame Flash and my fire switch oh that's
why I keep flashing why would they do
why would the game do that to me that's
why would they yeah why would they do
that to you I had it I had it rebound
and it it reset
itself arus is not interested in me
anymore he realized I am uh not
interested in him
either
good good go somewhere else there is
stay
away he go what oh channel so fast oh I
lost the ey included him
that uh
uhoh an oh my
God Dam
damn my aim is so bad man come
back stay
here no F should be flash flash nice
okay I got a back so be careful
Flash the
can't give up I can't give up for the no
for Flash or the
Lash they let's go for pilt
over pilt
[Music]
over oh my
God everyone's crunchy
uhoh everyone crunchy why do I have
looks how about
now oh I got boots I fix
[Music]
it good now okay okay see I get this guy
with this this
time
launch that sticks to an enemy Champion
for 3 seconds
[Music]
oh top like a b this real weird issue
recently it's happened like started a
week ago where my audio just becomes
like really robust but I can't hear like
it hears sounds normal in my my
ears jungle are you jungle you came to
the wrong
neighborhood you
jungle you cow come here come here come
here cow nice let's get this mid
turret this game is teaching me
restraint
oh uhoh wow he's so good he's scripting
we got
himing yeah kill him kill him kill him
kill him kill him kill him so fast he
died from
the Y I'm going home oh should I stay
with you I don't know uh n I'm a these
people
I just
run let's go Tower
two I'm here no there he is oh let's get
the
rumble Rumble come
what no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no please
Darius please have mercy let me go let
me
go let me go little hi hi hinger that's
zigs Dragon Spa he does look like hinger
though I fought the same when I was
watching the show I was like is this
character going to turn into digs or
what no no they they're their own people
oh unable
the enemy has been slain are they
related no they're just little just the
same they're just are they ortal species
yeah oh that's what I meant are they the
same species yeah yeah yeah
yeah his crazy
cousin yes there's another guy down here
Rumble it's who is ready to
whatever wow oh he heals back
up let's finally get someone with this
let's go a yay
[Applause]
[Music]
finally everybody's like Yay I'm like no
no
no out they are celebrating my death
they're cheating up there celebrating
your
death
yay W dies let's go it's okay cuz she's
a phoenix she'll be back yeah it'll be
back
BRB I just wanted to go shopping anyway
get
her oh I could do no you're not we'll
get her we'll get her flash for her oh I
don't do enough
damage it's okay we got him we got him
we got him we got him we got him oh he
flashed oh my God so annoying come
back oh
God okay we got him we got him we got
him
yay wow shut down shut you know we were
ambitious
yeah I mean we have three people against
yeah yeah yeah we did really well yeah
what is
that it's no issue we're still beautiful
it I'm a beautiful my space boy mhm so
she came back and then killed you that's
rude kind of mean finally there was like
this giant arrow on the map I was like
what could that be but it was on top of
an enemy so I thought the enemy was
doing something but it was her
teleporting I understand now at least
now I know
you get it you get it I get it now I get
it now does your guy have a Santa skin I
feel like he suit
one I don't think he has a Santa skin
this is his winter one right now he
would look really cool as Santa yeah
he'd be really
cute please have
mercy I'm on my way I'm on my way I'm
soone I'm so don't let him kill me Top
Lane is so
depressing you got this no be
can't Pi me I you she knows it you
didn't your flash yes yes your flash
crazy she dead so that's it's on the
wrong butt no it's not my fault you did
it you're
[Music]
crazy yo
snippity snipe don't don't let me kill
you please let me kill you give me that
satisfaction whoops you scared
me there he is it w you
coward
no oh
no I'm weak who is this Rumble where did
he come from the Jung can you come kill
this Rumble
Rumble can you come control your jungle
he's just chilling he lost his jungle he
has no idea what's going on you know oh
oh is that a
Teleport that is a Teleport okay I see
it now I see it
now there he is there is please let's go
should have shouldn't have done anything
when there it's a lesson I have to learn
when there's more than one enemy tum
full health I should not tickle them
they will St me and kill me tickle them
you out play them no I died no no next
time they
me next time okay okay I see yeah yeah
see what of you what if you I'll play
them next time oh that's a good Destin
actually maybe I didn't think of it
about it that way okay okay thanks
teacher get away from
me we got them yeah got
this get away from me OWI we I can't
tell
it's just one okay I can take on
one
[Music]
team took me long
enough she's a singer she's a
singer she's working l cuz she's a
singer listen to Espresso now on Spotify
thank you Ching listen to Blackbird out
now on Spotify Co off black out now on
Spotify your team destroyed a tret I'm
on a roll look at you Kiara you're
slaying yeah you're crazy all alone all
alone baby all alone a
uh destroyed inh all alone it's okay
it's like it's it's a character
development for
your
character it it's like The Angst
probably what's that why is that a red
circle around me what does that mean oh
no no no it's a buff it's a buff you
have a buff too many enemies please help
good good okay okay yeah good good good
good good you got red buff from Jungle
Red good if you have a blue around I
I'll protect you I'll protect you thank
you oh they're all oh there's so many of
them yeah leave leave
uhoh wa I was about to dodge that but
that came fast it just happened she just
got the both of us I'm glad we died
together yeah at least we're here
together she uh
oh oh thank you
oh there's three of them um get him okay
okay he's he's Charmed he's not Charmed
never mind I
lied what else I flashed again damn it
you're
okay there we
go oh the music cute your character
makes cute music thank
you she's just I'm going mid lane she's
a singer she's working
late uh oh there's two left
left he's Charmed he's
Charmed nice he's dead he's dead kill
him kill him I'm trying a it's okay it's
okay I'm running oh I'm dead you're all
alone it's
okay over
dominating oo nice dominating
dominating dominating
um
yeah yeah
yay
yeah you guys are
[Music]
crazy oh I'm going to
die that Dad
Lux damn it l all her
fault she's tearing us
apart play in the cloud Drake nice
honestly when we played her against the
lxs the first time I thought she would
be like super toxic character like um
you know like no no the way her
character is like her characteristics
and then I play positivity yeah she's
like super positive and love somehow
that makes it worse I don't know why
someone that's like he's in love stuns
you and then a in a line H nothing
personal
yeah nothing personal at all
yeah she doesn't mean it he's just
joking I see I see come minions be my
wall go g go kill her kill it get LS get
lugs oh there there there's like the
five of them
go go ah wait no run
run are those the flowers from the
[Music]
show no those are too jelly wheel I got
it I got it I got
it oo I can just figure out how to drive
this
thing I'll hit there I'll hit it I'll
hit it this way driving I'm driving
driving
here did you become the thing yeah you
can drive it I didn't look like driving
it seemed like you possessed it no
you're driving it
[Music]
was closer that's
confusing we can end yeah you guys right
now the game we're
winning we're so
[Music]
good I was late the party easy easy easy
easy easy easy
y well your first time playing that guy
Liz how did you like
him I loved him I thought he was really
cool
nice I'm going to see if he has skins oh
yeah can he be part of pup
Stars I got more more gold all of a
sudden malfunction describes it well
I got more RP too yeah how do we huh yay
y r thank
you R thank you Ryan I can get my
MySpace Bo I can buy my sarapin
skins my space boy skin oh did I also
get stuff I I don't know how did they
give me stuff yeah we need to we need to
submit to them your username and stuff
but I got some stuff how did I know my
oh you did you
got wait how can I well wait I also GL
okay it's time for a new skin what do I
buy thank you
League how do you know
my my number uh cuz they can probably
see it on my stream
oh oh it's here thank you Riot I guess I
won't riot it's done you you get away
scree
lucky has a winter
skin I'm going to get it yay how much is
that like the the how much is 3,600 is
that a lot it's it's quite a bit you can
buy a skin where do I buy skin go go to
the right by the RP there's like coins
stacked up you click
there uh uhuh uhhuh uhhuh and then you
you and buy stuff there
okay o short ha skin I think he only has
one skin W and it's winter I love winter
oh oh requ Champion I don't have Caitlyn
yet even though I'm playing her she's
she's probably free this week get her
with your your blue stuff my blue stuff
yeah yeah the in-game go buy her if you
like her
okay I do like
her you know sarine has a skin called
graceful
Phoenix ooh o is it red orange it's
orange fiery it's
nice oops don't have a lot of green SK
I'm a little bit annoyed AR doesn't have
a single green type skin yeah can't
believe it
cannot messed up
am I still in your party I can't tell
yeah uh probably maybe I'm not in it
right now I believe so I'm buying things
you're buying things oh you're not in
here I'll invite you to the game thanks
don't know something wrong hi guys okay
money is gone Riot thank you thank you
Riot thank you invested I spent
it I had billion dollars but I I spent
it all a mil billion dollars wow very
based what is chroma what does that mean
it's different color variations so if
you go to chroma and you look up the
champion you like they might have
different variation like color
variations for the Skins you already
have oh so it's like in skins chroma oh
chroma yeah oh so for example yeah if
you go into chroma and go Ari me she has
green here yeah then you can buy the
chroma and then you can use that
one instead you
know oh this is
green yeah she has literally an emerald
KDA skin that's
nice yeah purchase it buy bye bye bye
buy now buy now wait I have to pick I'm
going to get the the the oama it's time
to go to
bed to go to bed to bed it's time to go
to bed it's time to go to
bed so we're ending the stream no what
everybody's saying bye and it's time to
go to bed bye bye
bye to play League of
[Music]
Legend Jo summer so if I I should always
prioritize using the blue ones right
since those are in game
uhhuh yeah yeah that that was something
I did wrong when I first like got got
characters and stuff okay I got a green
one are we going to try real people now
or can we still not what do you want to
do what is this Gwen looks cool sesors
can we play against real people
sure I'm so ready I feel extremely
prepared for the
challenge I
believe nothing can stop me can stop you
uh I'm going to change my Kiara you need
to select uh Top
Lane Winter he has mult apparently
everyone wants me to tell you about
anivia
I've been seeing it in my chat too I
don't care I just invested in hot
outfits for Caitlyn play Caitlyn where
do I select where do I
select I don't know uh right under your
character icon C's character icon there
like a little square that you
can and then you click on the character
and then oh okay got it okay okay is it
possible to change the skin now no mhm
It Cosmetics yes
okay okay hot cute hell yeah hell yeah
how do I change the color of my skin oh
oh you hit the little chroma button you
can use the blue stuff woo I got it I
got it I got it let me know when we're
all ready switch flash to F I did flash
flash flash flash flash flash
bottom the blue stuff use the blue stuff
the blue stuff only the blue stuff 99%
Purity okay use the blue stuff female
dog you're ready everyone ready I'm
ready I'm ready I'll take that as a
yes we're looking we're going to play
people we're going to play people I'm so
scared wor they might be Bots too
they'll think I I I'm just the like 5
years we're 5 years old with how bad I'm
playing we're all bad oh you're doing so
good you're pushing top it's okay
because we're together with you so
you're not going to get
reported oh okay yeah that's what
matters it's okay even if they reported
me I have Riot on my side what can they
do a
lot it's fine
a pool party
Kaitlyn and a lox no there's a lox no
that might this seems like a bot team
you know oh okay okay that's good yeah
yeah I bet I bet they're I bet they're
bot I'm a star Guardian look I'm green
and gold my Orbit is gold I'm
[Music]
green I'll charm them with my swimsuit
like oh do we do the doesn't work I
don't
know okay are they real people or are
they not real people we'll see I walk in
if I walk in and I see them maybe they
are not real people check this out
everyone I'm about to face check to see
if they're real people do it I'm holding
it they might be Bots that's fine
oops I hope they're
Bots who's pinging me yeah who's pinging
us what's pinging someone someone's oh
the
robot oh who's that I oh no are the is
the robot intentional robot
again how do you even do
that robot maybe it is intentional we
don't know I don't think so Robo Liz in
the house Robo Liz am I back is a robot
again yeah you're a
robot terminate BOS B
terminate terminate exterminate oo it's
red now I'm so
scared
exterminate I forgot I can Auto attack
for a moment cuz I'm
nervous there's a guy
I'm
here
exterminate can't tell this is a bot or
not you you've been don't worry she's a
bot she's a bot okay maybe she will walk
into the thingy then that's good all
right all right you ready for this get
her get her get her ah okay she flashed
I'm leaving good bye I'll take some of
this while I leave they're so nice take
this while I leave goodbye no don't eat
them I'm going die I'm out of
here believe
it oh oh nice First Blood oh you back
thank
God I Avenged you don't worry
nice good
job okay CeCe in in about um in about 10
seconds I will come to you okay okay
yes no more no
l all right all right make her come back
make her come
back okay she will never expect this she
will never expect this she's not
expecting this one what is
that my snowball goodbye thank you wait
who are
you noooo and will and oh sorry sorry
you two people and will and will okay
okay oh no
oh no I'm so scared scared I'm in a back
don't be
scared you're
beautiful I am
retreating that's a jungle okay oh no
how do you know don't hurt me I am just
a Noo-noo and
will and
will oh Liz what are you doing by the
tower I'm reading okay that's
valid some bits to do
with this skin makes my weapon like
super super visible compared to before
it's crazy super visible yeah it's it's
nice it's kind of nice actually than
super super
visible super visible so
slow I am so slow
oh
God help
minions super
visible super
visible I'm going
home oh let's see what animation she has
here guys I'm going to run it down bot
Lane are you ready no have fun
okay well I hope you're ready
for me to run it down bot
Lane woo take him down
woo come back
huz oh thank you thank you I did how did
you know she how did she know I want her
to come
back goodbye Hi
Li hello I'll help you with this guy for
a moment thank you okay okay okay okay
okay okay
I love playing people who are totally
people and not BS I love playing against
people yeah these people I love playing
against
them I get it oh I
believe oh she's
here yummer two of them uhoh uhoh
uhoh why
is I heal there go is it yours o cool oh
no my guy's not a Healer I just had that
on
me okay I might have to retweet here
retweet retweet
retweet retweet get oh I just ran to the
wall never mind I know I forgot you oh
no oh no oh no I need to run run run run
run run run run R
run okay we're going going home you're
going home yeah I'm going home after I'm
the skin is like she like hearts and
stuff it's kind of like an
astrologian kind of
[Applause]
cool don't know
why pole is freaking out me alone Little
D I'm a noob pleas be nice be outside
today is my first time you'll be fine
you're doing
nice yeah you're doing great yeah is it
easy to stream snipe in this game we're
probably against bots right
now but is it easy to stream snipe no
you look
like
ow down oh you look like sa V thank you
I am a magical
girl higher
LS oh there's a guy there's a guy
here kill him no I'm not worried about
it if anything I would have welcomed it
getting stream sniped maybe they would
maybe they would be nicer to me
like may they go easy on me feet or I'll
ban you they'll just kiss my feet my
beautiful bare
feet please stream snipe us oh God or
don't I'm so
sorry it's
okay it's okay I died too and solidarity
down solidarity
yeah I'm slowly but surely overcoming
greed that's good no you should keep
being greedy oh really yes continue your
greed okay okay continue your greed be
greedy okay okay oh they're they're
right here why are they right here okay
wow I'm coming top oh you're welcome to
come as long as you don't steal my kill
okay I'll let you have have it I'm going
to set it up so you can get him going
why is he leaving okay
okay never going to expect this if he
just walks up okay okay okay snowball
get him get him get him really I'm not
ready okay okay I'm trying I'm
trying I took it oh it's okay it feels
like I did it okay we did that
together four of them what three three
just three oh that's
just okay so you're telling me if
there's two people I should still attack
them you should kill them
okay you got this
okay oh there's someone else teleporting
in so three people should I still yes
you should kill them I should still go
okay okay okay okay don't be a coward
kill them
out of my way knock turn got a blue buff
to get yeah I killed her I'm running
home you see green is good who's pinging
what did I say I don't unless not it's
not us it's not me I didn't even know
how to people what the heck I don't know
how to Ping I that which means what's
pinging I didn't I didn't click anywhere
there so um anything else I should
buy ow come back hit me under
Tower okay okay are you
ready are you ready go in go in okay
he's trying he's trying crazy you're
crazy he's charm you're crazy he's
dead okay I'm going
home I will also go home I
suppose focus on complete
one the G doesn't work guys I was
writing to my chat because they were
like popo box I'm like he's a
parrot he a coao
actually well he's a type of parrot he's
a
Kakao so like and parrots can like you
know mimic a lot of yeah can mimic a dog
sound if dogs really do sound like
that nice hey I got
killed
nice
thanks no
yes I let out an alt and it did
absolutely nothing it was so bad hey the
thought is what comes yeah my aim is so
[\h__\h] man
you spooked
him
what what is that what is that what is
that why are they all doing the
apocalypse is upon us
um turns thing ow why are they why are
they all
here they want you and they what they're
crazy oh my God BS are crazy I want to
take it I walk up is it dead is it
gone oh oh it reset okay I'll
leave you got this it's two of
them
yummy no come
back where is she where is she come here
no that didn't hit her
oo I can do this oh that doesn't go over
there yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
okay yum yum yum yum
yum I'm going home
okay going home uhoh they hit me
[Music]
uh woo turret time kill her kill her the
toad the toad killed her nice walk up to
me walk up to me okay you don't need you
don't need you don't need to do that
Liz oh it's that oh we got to mon
Drake
ow ow well I got Dragon the ch Blom so
was worth
it I did
WR what does it
mean what does it mean what does it all
mean oh what's he doing what the what
waa what was that he does a little
dance run he was teleporting uhhuh into
the minion
sometimes that's just what you have to
do biscuits heal you oh these I didn't
even realize I had biscuits in my
inventory hell yeah
biscuits oh that's why you guys
a I didn't realized I had any
[Laughter]
biscuits I thought you guys would cuz
you guys like cookies that's what I
cookie cookie sometimes you just wait
why did I leave I can buy more stuff oh
my
God yay I got
it you got
[Music]
her yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum um well if if okay so I am spending
a lot of time barely killing the the the
Bots and then going home should I rather
play it safe so I don't go home and push
the lane instead n kill n n you should
kill them yeah kill them okay oh what is
that that's a
nocturnal are you dead no I'm alive I
came to help you oh oh oh no I killed
him he's gone now don't worry okay I
just did what Chad told
me more
mins singing sing why she singing don't
sing okay okay I'm I'm roll I'm rolling
I'm rolling I'm roll rolling rolling
okay okay
yay
thanks My
Hero level 12 is this
one I'm just a
girl I don't know
delious I'm going to go mid I don't know
if I'll survive a die
you're not just
a hello welcome in my Lane thank you
hello please assist me get away from her
oh oh
oh oh oh
wao what happened Tower down you're so
crazy
help can you you just
Mor I mean kind of worked you should
morb more often almost dead she's almost
dead he's almost
dead is it the power of women that
compelled you to do this it was the
power of woman that really pushed me
into doing that that's so strong I also
believe in the power of women
sides it was very powerful okay I'll
charm her she's Charmed oh I'm inside
it's okay we're fine okay she's Charmed
yeah kill kill I don't have any heals
I'm
dead Sor okay you got her you got her
kill her kill her no no you got Qui no
it's okay it's okay it's
okay keep chasing me sarapen come on
what are you
doing nice try Lux your aim is as bad as
mine all right I'm here for you I'm here
for you I'm rolling I'm rolling it down
I'm rolling it down go
go I ran to the
wall oh nice nice you got it
[Applause]
double double kill um now I buy this guy
oh yeah oh yeah oh
noturno windows I don't know what that
means I
scared you win you win them you know you
Windows no minion don't kill me yeah you
win you windows
oh God desty Windows you windows and you
lose those that's okay sometimes you
have to lose in order to Windows
activation key oh does he have the same
skill as me oh behind
you he's trying to tr he's going to come
out from me come
out nice nice nice nice nice he's low
smoking he's low there's another one
coming from Top
jungle okay did not in in fact
come being chased oh here he's there
he's there oh more friendly people oh
hi I'm being
followed behind yeah I brought them over
sorry about that it's okay it's okay
charm
no kill kill kill
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
teport into the
thingy
finally I want kill
oo let's get this Tower okay let me kill
you okay okay y tower Tower I forgot
about
him you have your old kiaha yes if you
use it it's like a sniping if I can know
him low enough maybe you can can kill
him get away from her
Inhibitors
inhibitor I don't know why I I I I don't
know I I'm
sorry she just walked into
it but she she's showing me her pretty
butt get her get her get
him goodbye
bye come back come back he's
dead come
here he Charmed Yum Yum Yum
Yum oops I'm in there I've got I've got
back accidentally walked into their
home oops you walked into their home and
died
yeah it's
okay guys guys kill them all it's fine I
planted my ass there worse yeah yeah
yeah worse worse worse
oo we're so good at this game yay not
bad
laying no right now I'm just running
because I died I have been slayed though
you were slaying so good
though that is
questionable why am I here I don't know
run where is
everybody mother trucker no we're on our
way there two
away will I die to this no nice I did a
thing oops I got rooted
I did H guy's right behind
you
team don't die
Kiara an ambush
St I was
here we
wono we're winners y
winner
winner this leveling up huh does honor
players just never show yourself
or H yeah you can't honor yourself it's
just the others oh oh this is a screen
where you choose
oh why would you honor yourself Kiara no
no no I thought this was showing the the
good players of the game already
no you get to pick oh I haven't seen
that one do I skip it by accident I
don't
know um I just want to go get another
drink be right back
okay we're doing it wow we're so good
yeah we're doing we're doing a League of
Legends with the with the
professionals um quick say like some
terms only professionals would
know uh I think I need to restart My
League of Legends it's professionals
would say that is what a professional
would
say restart my League of Legends yeah I
see I see I'm going to yeah I'm going to
I'm going to restart League G I'm going
to Lane Swap and then I'll I'll mid Gap
and then I'll W State and split push and
then okay and then
I'll be to
to to I agree with
everything e
like pick any and say like I don't know
mid Canyon mhm yeah can someone tell me
why I got promoted to bronze they're in
the game yay she's
bronze you're bronze okay I'll do that
thanks for the hint invited you bad oh
you've invited me the game I just
checked their
streams they made it for the
queue damn how did they do that did they
cheat what they made what did they cheat
the poe girls got for the like bibu and
Kyla got uh into they did nice yeah I'm
trying to get in and it's telling me
that I need to purchase a code but I
purchased a code huh so what does it
want from me why is it ly want more
codes what's more of it that's all you
had to do wait damn
SC okay it's okay 5 minutes ago right no
it's okay it took them it took them 3
hours they waited 3 hours that's crazy
that is crazy I'm glad I didn't do
that hello I'm glad I'm here I guess
please welcome back I have no regrets
can play uh P Exile too or I have
partially regrets but mostly no regret
regrets no
regrets yes
regret absolutely no none
regrets no regrets allowed in this
household none of that
now none of that no
Cecilia yes you jump scared me are we in
are we ready for no yeah oh I haven't
said anything in like a while you did
you did something oh getting ready for
kill sorry oh are we in oh okay okay
okay we're queuing we're we're going to
queue six people I see I see that's fun
weing
are we doing yeah we we'll do real
people yes yes yes yes I
believe I like real
people o heart
throb Warick oh heart throb
War
[Music]
Warwick oh yeah I am a hard
Fring yeah
you'll love her be on that one
[Music]
remember darling you you'll love her be
on that one
k yeah does she do something
special
y you'll see I won't spoil
it I'm so fast do we go into the
bushes we can check we can see if
they're real people I'm big how do we
know if they're real people people um
Instinct yeah okay I think they're
Bots that's a
bot I don't have any CC I didn't start
with it embarrass myself oh thank you if
it's a bot they won't judge me too
hard
damn why W you're on my Lane hello no
you look so different how could you
I should have started double
you should have double
you oh the music's cute he's inviting me
okay never
mind get them get he's so
stupid go Nissa it's worth it I can't
get
anymore
annoying trash man oh nice that looks
cool Liz yeah ah
[Music]
pain
goodbye he didn't even heal up I miss
you oh they they're here they're here
really War really really no come on war
you little [\h__\h] they're low there's two
that are low here guys get them okay I'm
running worry
not
D oh
there come back okay I'm here for to
harass her
jungle okay okay
okay nice
nice good that was totally worth it I'm
going to die from these leave leave
leave run away run
away it's okay the minions are keeping
everything up I don't even have to do
anything yay
yay you can go home you should go home
I'm going
home let go going home cuz she's a woman
who's beautiful she's a woman W I said
she's a woman who's
beautiful a woman what are you trying to
say oh my
God I didn't know we were like that I
didn't know we were that kind of League
of Legends
team I oh that's the league experience
that I was looking forward
to wow she has to heal
uh what's that what's what's his
name uh
ow G
Gallo
galloo Gallo I hate that guy ow you hate
him yeah but he has a chicken costume
and I'm aware of it kfp I'm aware she's
aware everybody told me to look at
it I've seen it
I'm back
nice where are you running charm charm
charm where are you running
[Music]
to he gave me a kill for free he's so
nice paid
actor all
right he working late suuck my head
forever it's hard to get
out cuz she's
a beautiful woman a
singer I'll switch the order
now cuz he's high
minger oh my
god oh there was a sparkle in the
world wait why are there two of them
that's not fair that's a bot you know
she just doesn't know what's going on he
see like I'm going to
die you're not going to die not today
not
today look at this guy he keeps what are
you doing he keeps going back and forth
what is is
that they're doing their best their best
is not good enough die they're trying
really hard back up the BS are going to
kill you or the minions
it's m to dis oh God I'm going to die no
okay now so you're going to Flame the
bot are you saying I deserved this yes
you deserved that you deserved what was
coming for you for flaming the Bots yeah
don't Flame the poor Bots they're just
Bots right this one yeah maybe I
shouldn't have Flame the weird moving
Bots this is what you get for being
toxic and this is a lesson we should all
win
early okay
oh the that's so cute biggest snowball
ever bigger I
learned learn get I did it right he he
charm he's Charmed I'm killing this
Gall o kill him oh yay we did it get the
other one get the other
one
okay okay I she's Charmed it's Charmed
it's charm okay okay okay no
don't no did you get him oh no wait
there's another one behind I'm going to
get this dragon now get
it he could have killed me if he wanted
to I think he's in love with me I think
so too that's the only logical makes
sense I have my ult now I'm unkillable
because I can run away
oh I will just wait I'm leaving
obviously okay sorry wait there's two
there's three sniff I'm doing my best
sniff I'm defin ill you're doing great
Nissa ill fantastic you're doing great I
lost my lane and it's it's 100% because
of the
jungler yeah because of g no way wow
gigg yeah my bad it's just how it is
sometimes I'm out of Mana I mean I could
charm him
I'm going M I'm you get
rev all I can do now I have to leave
okay I'm running away too okay oh he's
confused confused hit him hit him
awesome okay okay hold on he's Charmed
he's Charmed I don't want to go walk
back anymore him kill him him go in yay
it's it's easy I'll show you CH easy
easiest game okay now I'm going
home nice
yay
yeah
we did you use your ult already yes
you're not asking me don't know who you
asking no one's talk no of course oh
really are you sure because I know I'm
alone here so no one's talking to me
it's okay no I I I watch I'm looking I'm
watching you yeah if he's really low
like that he's far away you can save
your ult for last and you should be able
to kill him you actually talked to
me what I have my eye on you you
watching me I'm watching you I'm
Charmed who thank you thank
you damn
uhoh do do you have my stream open in
the second
screen i c on the map and I look at
you why I why you even have time for
that cuz she's a pro I'm I'm losing my
Lane because of you you should focus on
your lane you don't want to you don't
want to watch Pros they they're like
crazy with doing that
yeah I can imagine they got their eyes
everywhere
ow there's one guy here up
here there there there there there okay
I'm Charming him he's
Charmed okay let's get get him get
him oh oh no can regret
living okay okay there another one
another one right here Warick Warick
wait never mind huahua is dying I'm
going to kill that Warwick no don't
steal my kill
don't die don't die her kill I'm going
into my locker bye no no no here this
kill for you I'll set up this kill for
you I'm already gone I'll get this kill
I'll I'll avenge you okay oh my God he
feared
me he
knew are you see what she takes out of
the locker what does she take out of the
locker it's a picture of VI oh really B
rolling the ball she has no IDE what's
going on don't spoil it's fine I haven't
seen yeah don't spoil please it's fine I
don't know anything what it's the
animation in the the be no no no I
didn't mean that I was asking followup
questions and then I I took it back
don't
worry
boink fool you stand no chance I killed
him what is that I see he dead you you
did that because I said that I lost my
Lane because of you previously huh I had
to I had to get rid of I I really got it
[Music]
back they don't care
chat we care no no no no
uh I I don't mean
you it's okay of course we care about
you no no no no we love you we care I'll
come back and kill him again no don't do
that I'll make him regret he's mine to
kill oh someone's
teleporting who's
teleporting tell him not to
okay I'll do that next time oh yeah I
need the eat the cookies eat the cookies
eat the cookies gy my ALT is ready and
I'm like lowkey dying though my I don't
know what he's doing over
here stop fearing me I keep forgetting
to eat my
biscuits at least you have biscuits
goodbye I all right good
Tower
yay there's some people up here but I
don't think they're coming up here yet
all not mean the flash fat fingered
that dud right here right here it's okay
di to her I can do an alt
yay okay
okay oh God oh God we can do this maybe
[Music]
yeah give me the kill give me the kill
get it get it get it oh
no no y I'm just I'm going to leave
right here right
here let look picture time
oh oh
no yay close that was
close just a little bit of Tower so none
of my letter abilities work on the tower
what the hell was that no that
sucks oh he has a lot of Health no weird
he's a tanky champ he's tanky don't
appreciate it why
tanky wow what's she doing over there
I'm going home
home the tower the tower starts walking
towards you yeah he like
uproots oh buy stuff I where'd he go
there he is I came for you Warwick I'm
getting my kill one way or another your
dest
grow legs and then he starts walking
towards you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
I'll be cute
en
oops ow we got
him I need more damage I need more
damage it doesn't matter who gets him as
long as he dies
right oh I mean no I I'm I don't know
how I got him cuz you're good that's
what I'm saying oh back I I didn't mind
to Tower to
Tower kill
him no come back come back back ride
back come back oh
no get her
all right all right I'm here he has no
Mana he has no Mana get the tower get
the tower keep going keep going
yay more
minions oh he's behind me behind me he's
behind me he's behind you oh it's a toad
why is the toad toad I mean just kill
him why are you attacking us Mr Toad
that's not very nice a toad
a
toad I'm coming
jungle coming
jungle if I'm welcome what is that what
was that oh is that a buff okay yes Hi
Li thank
you okay okay okay let's go get him I'm
leaving oh wait this cat I'm stupid I
can't
I I I thought maybe you were talking
last time so I was like oh Ki Oh I'm
down he's Charmed he's Charmed
oh I'm dying it's okay run it's fine
it's fine I'll stop them oh whoa who
still
running I missed him he's not
Charmed
lying ooh oops I didn't mean to ATT
oh oh
no one HP and the dream he's running at
me we all here though come back mid
we're all here
okay
nice nice nice nice nice
nice get the turret okay
awesome
nice
oh oh what oh I died from the tower my
bad my
[Music]
bad oh you think you walk out over here
yeah yeah he's coming your way oh walk
over over here come
back no he's not I think he's so scared
he's too scared of you what is he scared
oh he's coming
back don't be scared nice nice nice go
nice Gallo's too strong man this no you
got him you're two people and there's
Gigi right behind
[Music]
you what is that is that an elephant no
tiger a boar I'm not sure nice an animal
play time is never chunky wonky welcome
to the table I guess hello fluffy
monster a Bo she wants to play
league she is she only she thinks I'm
done streaming cuz I'm so
quiet girl I'm still streaming let's get
top Tower oh guess I should talk more
this is my sign to talk
more we're we're all locked in so hard
ah ah ah ah locked in but not not
protecting the
waa goodbye chunky
wonky okay
uh I am here but I am low ah shoot down
okay you did get it was worse it was
worse was worse
worse was
worse okay he's almost dead do you see
him yes on the right yes oh it's
you nice nice nice
nice
legendary CH charm
nice nice I'm going
back he going back where's my mouse oh
I'm
coming
[Laughter]
mid uhoh not again not again I almost
died I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine get him get
him goodbye everyone good job Ending
[Music]
game you got him nice uh-oh uh I'm
dead it's fine you guys can finish it
course you got
this nice crazy a triple kill look
you so good so
good no no live she's weak you can get
her nice you you you got a triple kill
you you got triple kill look at you
kiar
yay thanks to the question marks League
of Legends
Pro League of leing pro
g
g GG's good
work
GW oh my God I can honor more than one
person I can just honor all of you
oh
oops not biased you
think would would would L be okay going
top does wa want
bot Lane oh yeah you want to support
what the hell is bot lane or she can
still play Kaitlyn yeah kayin is Kaylin
is I don't mind uh doing
whatever okay it don't bother me I mean
I love I I love you Nissa I love you too
but I don't mind switching it up yeah oh
bottom L I thought every is bot link cuz
the Bots are everywhere no
oh okay what so should I go bot
yeah go bottom oh I'll I'll see a
different scenery for once mhm okay
okay yeah and then narissa will set up
all the kills for
you okay okay okay oh she will steal
them all is that what I hear from that
giggle I I nothing
intentional I believe okay one second
I'm just getting water up but I'm still
like here okay she will steal them it's
okay like if I don't she can't steal
anything that doesn't exist there are no
kills in the first place with me yeah no
she she's going to set them up and then
you're going to kill steal her it's
probably more like she's setting them up
and she's killing
them they're for you doing both I'm just
there for mental support we have to do
it
together
okay okay can't play play again okay I'm
here okay let's go I'm
baby I'm
baby baby I'm
sorry no no where are
[Music]
you oh mine's still mine's still loading
uh yeah still loading back into the
thing yeah now it's doing it well I've
recently met a baby so I think I'm
pretty good you know baby sound a baby
the mystical creature the and I get I I
I uh it it pulled my hair it was pretty
fascinated with me I gave it an elephant
it likeed the elephant yeah oh I think
it was in love with
me hell yeah so I'm good with
baby do I need to click something
different now no or okay no you can just
swap you can go
top baby was cute have to swap the
thingy you P my hair
yeah and I didn't mind I would like to
go back B them after this game though
okay it's just a
test
yeah with
great so I'm going to go Bottom now yeah
go bot
wa Fair cool this looks like Victor I
know it's so pretty the
guy are we on the oh no we on the other
side oh no oh no no is that
bad oh it's confusing personally it
doesn't change anything but it gets
really confusing no it is confusing yeah
let's see if they're real people so is
my bottom the top now cuz we're the
other way around yeah go this way right
here uh wait wait wait wait why is the
view always so weird in the beginning
why do I always have to change it I
don't know are we going
into into the bushes G we can see if
they're real I'll poke my head over
should I follow you n are we going into
the
bush yeah we might
die I don't see them they might be
starting
blue blue should I walk over there just
to look you want to I'm behind you I'm
behind you okay oh are are you guys real
are you guys bot guys are you real are
you bot yeah you real people oh where
are you going K where are they I don't
know I'm trying to be my individual own
person wait there's someone there are
they real are they real get them I'm too
used to
being oh no that's that's okay well come
hurry we'll just go to Lane are
they he's dead it's okay oh they're here
hey wait that's a real person that's
yeah they're they're definitely real
that's the real person okay I'm
running back to the tower back to the
tower wow okay I'm at the tower you're
playing against a real
person who the Lux is real the Lux is
real no bot Lane is definitely real
people it's okay I got this we've
trained for this guys no we haven't yes
we yes we
have sorry
sorry hey what ELO are we playing
against What's Happening
Here what's the best thing to do now
ah
bro
wow
um you just are supposed to kill kill
the minions last H them so you get money
so when you die or go back you can um
you know buy okay to get
stronger
yeah I meant more like running away from
me why she running away from
scared uh I mean there is no retreat we
just have to keep doing it if you're
struggling you can come back by the
tower
[Music]
oh I carry the Legacy blah blah AR blah
blah blah blah she's telling us her
entire life story blah blah blah blah
blah
okay this be careful
oops what the
hell come here
CeCe where's here up up yeah where I am
I'm
coming okay charm good good kill him
kill him kill him I don't have a ward
I'm afraid of walking in I'm very
low no I have to eat this okay he
there's two now I can't do it on
I die to this oh I die to
this cookie
[Music]
owie the music is so peaceful has so
peaceful ow ow ow ow
ow I prefer playing against bots no no
it'll be okay I like I like people I
feel more fulfilled when it's a real
person than a bot yeah it's a learning
it's how you learn it's how you actually
get
better oh oops I mean from like minions
oh I'll use all my man and then I'll
leave yummy yum yum yum no no I'm going
to die have confidence nope have
confidence
she's a high oh no oh no I am dead oh no
oh no oh no no
no all right I will come smack him soon
Liz maybe let me kill all these little
tiny
[Music]
babies you leaving they're pretty good
they're pretty good bot
good luck G you're gonna have to
carry I'm I KN new okay okay I'm here
Liz I'm herey okay I'm GNA
uh I need to get Clos it to be able to
do what I want to do oh no where did he
go no he healed oh I shouldn't have
flashed oh I don't know where they are
well nice try
there they
are okay she has no Mana I'm running up
cie okay go go go go
go nice ping can I blame the Ping I have
170 ping clim the Ping thank you
little it's that goddamn ping every time
maybe I can maybe if I charm
her ow ow he's hurting
me I'm going to go back let's go I can
walk
bottom wow he's ice sking with himself
it's so cute I'm going for the Draven or
the Jin go
on okay okay well I hit them but I have
to leave they're they're leaving back up
back
up oops I want to go get grubs so
careful side
okay grubs grubs grubs grubs just back
up we're really low
[Music]
mhm it up
thanks go my minion oh minions oh
uhoh what was that does this music come
from you I don't
know uh yeah the music comes from
nissa's
yeah it's so calm ouch double kill uhoh
ouch oh uhoh got you [\h__\h] female
[Music]
dog help
me jail Birds please save us I can't I
can't I can't fight 10 no no she's level
seven okay I got I can't fight this
Warwick where are
you it's okay he's on
can't really can't do anything
here I got you
biscuit no Lux leave leave our Tower
alone you fiend oh I'm yeah leave it
[Music]
alone I take my jumper off it's
hot we can go kill Warwick if you want I
don't think we can kill War way oh two
people two versus one can we win oh he's
just standing there we can walk or him I
don't think we'll make it there in time
it's the only
problem by time he leaves oh they're
already level six we're screwed oh he's
right there I see them they have alts we
don't oh I'm coming it's okay there's
two of
them I'm walking to you oh
no I'm I'm too behind to do much it's
okay it's okay sorry it's
okay let me grab
this please stop pinging
randomly
ma'am um I've been told it's a polite
thing to do if you do it
correctly oh I think retreating was the
correct thing to do it was just too
late would you agree re
chat no she rooted me she always rots me
no she rolled at
you that's rude I hate
her goodbye what the heck oh my
God where' you go like a is that the St
I
think I have this
[Music]
feel see will be
fine oh he's just walking oh he's just
walking okay I'm coming from behind the
war might come back I'm dead I'm dead
I'm I'm running away I missed I missed
don't worry I scared her I scared her
what are you doing with the ball SC I
scar oh oh no oh no oh no oh no I'm
going to be more careful oo it's good go
go go go you got
him ow O okay never mind I'm going okay
it's okay no you got this no I I was
trying to W the bush
no wait that's messed up only the bear
dies and the girl still lives and then
she just like lays next to him on the
floor what do you mean the bear which
bear noooo and W which one I don't know
the your animal your pet oh yeah he di
morning and she's fine and then she just
lays down on the floor she's
living that's messed up she
dies it's a ye Yeti Yeti is a bear you
think about
it okay we can still turn this right
guys yes we can still turn this around
no yeah yeah yeah turn this around we
can do it
duh I should have just played
Teo we're getting melted
[Music]
bottomy oh my God okay what Strat do we
do quick do the Strat number seven I
think Str seven we do seven I think we
got this so can you tell me cuz it's my
first day was is number seven yeah of
course I can tell you
I'm sure everybody else knows but you
got to explain it to me yeah so you
didn't read the manual on the
strats cominging behind me is coming out
behind me he's behind me he's behind me
oh behind you okay I'll charm him here
yeah he's over here somewhere is by
myself he was behind me okay I'm running
away again BL
okay your turret has been destroyed
uh-oh
that's not
good oh he's here oh wait
okay he's Charmed he's Charmed oh I'm
I'm going to try coming Mondo's on his
way Mondo's on his way oh going to try
coming back we're both okay yeah I need
help here for thein oh
he I mean I need help top I'm not bottom
anymore you need help top okay
yeah I need help help for a moment watch
out for this Warick let's get
him whoa what is
oh actually as
dundo what is this what is all this fire
everywhere fire fire light fire we're
liting the
fire high as you desire very collector
wow no not legendary that's fine he got
executed he was greedy oh nice nice what
a what a fool what a loser what a fool
just kidding he's kicking our
asses no he's a fool he's a loser
[Laughter]
pool I have to learn how to dodge
that let's go where am I to go
we're getting
stomped no we not it's okay it's okay
we're fine we're fine yeah we can turn
this around I don't know I don't know
can we just has to come up with some
Strat and tell us what to do that like
they have 21 kills and we have two are
you sure
two uhoh uhoh uhoh oh got that they're
all here the war and the freaking M got
wait I will die come up with like a cool
no don't die we going to bite them okay
that's a good idea I
think that is my plan mhm we going to
bite we will bite them them okay what if
we just went next you know res like a
reset okay okay next what next like we
go to the next
[Music]
game
what what if we went to the next game
that sounds like surrendering it's not
winning that feels like the opposite of
winning no it's winning it's
winning I can't get this ow they're all
here coming I'm coming I'm coming bring
them in uhoh there's so oh my
God dead body and the dead child
so messed up the dead child
too we can we can go next to reset and
maybe we'll get worse people you know
they're going they're going mid I think
they're all going mid
hooray
surrender
what dang
it who voted no wait easy
voted how many people have to vote it
has to be unanimous for early surrend
animous
man oh if only that was if only we knew
who that was too bad we can't figure it
it out oh it's only oh it is unanimous I
suppose that's the first time I see that
today it's very depressing I know no
it's okay the d stands for done well
done and the e f e a see uh I finished
my second liter of water give me a sec I
need to grab more don't start don't
start
without BRB BRB okay
BRB okay you are still not muted on my
screen you know okay
H 13 kills from that cloudy Jester
Jin
13 oh speaking of Jester I want to try
shako shako shako
shako um let's see do I even have him
yet
we fed him too
early but I am a fast food restaurant
owner so I'm here to feed people no
that's
true I need to feed them you need they
also
hungry I would be evil if I would let
people
hunger yeah you're just kind and
giving I I I do like to receive too but
that's in my private life I suppose
as a professional businesswoman I like
to
give
yeah yeah what's your love language
herb what's my love language
[Music]
uh
uh we should all take one of these
quizzes yeah I feel like I'm the only
person who didn't take this like Omega
quiz thing oh I haven't done it yet
everybody was taking it I is it that
short no well I don't know we can we can
still look at it afterwards after stream
after after stream cuz everybody was
taking it and posting the results while
I was busy with Lady and uh I don't
understand still what a mega verse means
it's it's
important it's important apparently it's
very
important H it has 40
questions oh that shouldn't be too long
returned hello did you take the Omega
quiz
Cecilia no not yet you you also didn't
wow I yet I I should I haven't your
excuse I forgot about it I saw it I was
I should do this and I forgot about it
really how can you forget about it when
it's been going on for like three days
everyting it K was saying that but her
and me haven't done it yet so yeah I see
I see but I have a good
excuse what is your excuse yeah I was
busy the past three days with ladies in
my in my house should I pick that one
yeah ladies did you have ladies in your
house I'm a
lady I mean excessive amount of ladies
excessive Ladi there's too many ladies
my mom's a lady have you been having a
nice time yeah me and the ladies or me
and the ladies me and L we had what a
nice time very nice time and magnificent
marvelous time beautiful they love
Austria everyone loves Austria so two
out of five of us here have taken the O
Omega quiz I will say one thing
yes how much longer do you girls want to
play because one person in this room has
a uh
thing to do I can't even get on don't
even worry I want to apply uh not
pressure but I want to remind a who is
it who has the thing to do
a someone sounds very
guilty I
see practically done it's just I whether
I whether I want to add a cherry on top
that's you should you should
okay you
know sure I'll add the cherry on top add
the cherry on top and I will eat it
should we play another one yeah yeah we
can play one how long does the Cherry
take um shouldn't take too long all
right if we do one more then yeah I'll
have I'll have time all
right oh go hold on are my runes correct
okay finding match Comfort pick
Teo oh you're doing P Teo this time
okay thiso I oh I want to change my
catak everybody in Discord room has
participated in the Advent calendar
already except for one
person I declined it you can switch your
character thank you sorry I can try try
Lilia actual Jung looks
herb oh my god teom with the be skin is
called leave her alone we're playing
we're playing League that's so cute beo
I love beo beo beo wait who are you
Arcanist ah can I go top again bottom
was stressful yeah you're going top
why would you say that like you want to
get rid of me you are not a good
goodbye but how do I learn then how will
I ever learn you're you need to read how
to play it read how to play it and then
try again wa
wo I am sensing some hostility is this
the toxicity that I have heard hovering
over the report button
no I'm just joking I'm ready now I don't
care either way but you it's okay I
broke up before you broke up with me I
already said I'm going back up good she
already said a letter before good fine
then
good I hope you'll have fun down there
being bottom I love without your top
yeah I already have top
love who's who's joining you down there
H herb me a
I said off I said before the last game I
want to go
back you want to go oh okay I wish you
to happiness I see I I've seen this
coming in the past weeks and months
anyway the signs were all
over oh my goodness gracious well you
knew that that we would be like pairing
in the in
the predicted amazing I seen those
pairing since the very beginning I've
seen the Synergy in your colors and your
designs
mhm well she's monitoring me you know
yeah I mean I'm monitoring yeah I mean
Cecilia and Gigi also monitor Nissa too
so
yeah o I'm ready I don't see us oh
there are we checking if they're real
people again they're real people I'm
sure W I hear KDA
music because of
[Music]
me are we going into the bushes or not
nah that's the most fun
part I'm fine on my
own me and my minions we're going to do
guys you want to you want to you want to
see this oh my God you're
little
clown my goodness who are you playing
against is that lux okay no Lux it's
okay wait now what is
this have smolder smolder is that a
character what do I need to know do
quick I know nothing about him I I I
think it takes him a really long time to
ramp up he needs a lot of
farm and his old is Big line and he
flies around and he's
like okay he throws a ball at
you molder from
AE hello yes that's CRA wa turn turn on
your screen question mark someone is oh
you can't tell me what to do okay okay
do whatever makes you happy that's fine
wait I have to I have to task manager my
way out of it why is it not Window mode
anymore what happened actually
wa why is he doing more damage than me m
up he's going to farm
huh oh w
Wait so nice to see you I was alone did
you you are wrong I I think you wrong I
think bot is real
people I'm pretty sure they're real
people yeah
still uh War Weck behaves just the way I
like it so I think he's a bot mhm can
the team be like half bot half real
people not sure I think that's what
happened last the first time we played
yeah I think if they don't have like a
full
team and there's like not a good amount
of people who can join with them they'll
just like supplement with Bots that
would be
evil oh it's okay she's
backed is it like common that the Top
Lane is always played a load and the
bottom is always double
yeah Bottom's not as aggressive as last
time which is
good maybe maybe they are bot maybe
maybe they you shouldn't have you
shouldn't have judged Me by One game
against
players I'm not judging you I would do
better now
perhaps I'm not judging you just bot bot
all the lanes in all the different areas
are play
differently they're all Bots they're
Bots for Wheels it's mine bot guys yeah
they're all Bots
[Music]
yay the jokes on you I'm getting very
here to come to where I am you yeah yeah
coming oh guys going want to come see
this what oh don't run up to him though
he's melee don't run up to him he's he's
a melee range
champ too late sorry I was I wasn't
looking at my HP you got him you got him
you got him you got he so confusing I
feel like I'm playing the game
horizontally flipped
messed
up no his life Ste well nice it's okay
they're Bots it's okay it's okay wrong
with a little
feeding I see right through you oh she's
so close so close to death I'm dead why'
you
die all right Oh I thought she was going
to die she so awkward she's so weird I
thought she was going to die
narissa oh God now I'm going to die wait
he's going home wait wait wait yeah kill
him kill the bot the bot oh he just left
yeah he teleported away oh he went
bot oh what that's a skill Oh I thought
he was going home if it's purple it's
teleport I think it was gold I don't
remember
wow if it's blue it's the
back oh I see
okay get her get her get
her oh
minions one
more thanks
G that was very very
productive no
problem
thanks no problem thanks G just doing my
[Music]
part oh no I'm out of
man bye my go back
home I'm living my best life she says
actually leave one of these byebye oh
okay goodbye
[Music]
I zo
many coming oh God oh God looks
funny jungle
attacks is that what you is that what
you
need was that what it was GG jungle
attacks yeah yeah is that part of League
yeah it's part of League you know it's
normal you should get used to it yeah
all right it's a normal thing that
everyone does all right all right all
right I understand now
mhm uh think I don't think the BX are
intelligent enough for that oh stop
him oh wait there's so many of them
there's three people in the jungle HHH
GG okay I have to back please stay in
LAN sure that they won't get the last
grub they're going to go to k
though okay I'm running oh my God they
killed my guy you got him kill him kill
him kill him G jungle tax jungle tax GG
jungle tax Jung ta jungle tax jungle tax
jle J tax jungle ta I'm getting the
jungler the jungle tax oh
owie he charm okay you're crazy do it
again uh give me like 5 Seconds an En
change my mind nice okay bye goodbye do
you have like a heal or something nah
okay it is what it is that's fine so
when they do damage to the to the Jungle
jungle animals don't die uhhuh can you
like kill kill them and then steal the
kill yeah you can steal the the jungle
animal M that's a strat
so that's why you always want to fight
objectives and take it from
them I misre
the let me have your let me have this no
please let me have your
blue oh where is he oh he's right there
hit hit it take it
take your blue they're weak H we'll
fight it together Vol
bearak goodbye I'm going this
together okay chunky wonky oh SMY is
also here babies oh hi hi oh my
here oh he's he's flying he's flying oh
he's flying
did you hear that so cute she just
jumped up
chirping oops don't press buttons thank
you she wants me to watch the
enemy she's so cute the enemy oh oh all
the enemy she left she left the moment I
sang that she's an Arcane
hater don't be a hatere from L League of
Legends yeah League of Legends League of
Legends you know they made a game based
off Arcane oh my god did they that's how
it feels to
me you're fake fan fake League fan they
made they made a game based off of our
that's the thing I'm not a league fan
joining you guys of course we fake F
what do you
think I'm an Arcane fan oh what's that
sorry Rian
well not first day soong
one so come here you little get him
clone get
[Music]
him aim
do
weak what was that going to take away my
skins yeah that was like a wave oh
there's a guy let's run oh that's his
old okay uh level eight I love taking
your farm I appreciate that you know
someone should take it I never hit the
last hit
anyway that was might as well are you
dead no I'm running
down oh they leaving oh what is he oh no
oh no you don't you don't see me I I see
you though a I'm helping I'm helping I'm
helping you're helping you're CR help
I'm helping nice you're
crazy nice nice nice you guys are so
strong oh there's two oh
no no but gig said
engage two at full heal afraid do not be
afraid always always greed I'm not
hitting any of my shots that's fine come
be here now okay okay okay
okay ow I'm just cleaning up yeah it's
my job perfectly
planned get him almost oh my God nice
nice nice nice nice who the heck is
that wor G wor what did you do with
Warwick let him die that he's a bear now
but really is that still Warwick yeah
that that's still him it's a bear why is
he a
bear it's volley Bear right yeah Voli
bear that's not war
rck they both they're like the same you
know are are they yeah they're basically
the same
Boozled oh okay I see Warwick and volley
bear at the same time now so I think a
she's so low you bamboozled me no no I
would not lie to you fine fine
f I'll scare him away from your lane
thank you please continue doing
so
an
goodbye
okay is it
fix ma'am stop
it I don't know why that is I have no
idea are we sure they're Bots yeah we're
I'm sure they're Bots
[Music]
I'm not
sure pretty
flowers
a what that do turet PL will fall soon
okay sorry about the audio
stuff maybe I should reinstall like all
my audio drivers or something yeah ow
every every single one
them what's your audio problem oh every
once in a while since like last week
every once in a while my audio just
becomes like super crunchy but I can't
hear it only chat can hear it for some
reason it's like what is you know it
must be
OBS that's
interesting go go get him get him get
him he walk back to us now is as good as
time as any no nice
an
[Music]
enemy so now G when I have like this
much health should I still what is
happening to my hold on something is
going on with my computer you got this
something very terrible
Isen I admitted something
bad my I think what is happening my
second monitor is flickering oh god oh
everybody's got issues today it's loose
crunchy it's it's like flick let me take
a video of this so you can see how
cursed this is it' be so funny if you my
screen
[Laughter]
record I'm going to start screen
recording what no that's not going to
work monor okay let me send this to you
uhoh what what is happened
no you killed
her you killed
her has problems with connection let me
upload and then send
this what speed it up can't believe he's
at my
tower here he goes
where' it go good joke
[Music]
sh oh my my goodness what is going on
yay Tower broken
finally ooh I don't have boots yet I'm
slow okay put it here and then I'll also
send to kiaha so you can see thank
you check after the game I I did have a
lot of uh flickering issues a while ago
yeah do you see that like what is
what is happening that's fine just hit
it once I'm sure it's fine oh I'm sure
you're okay oh yeah yeah oops Yeah it's
fine it's fine don't worry don't worry
fine fine I think it's okay yeah I think
it's fine I'm pretty sure it's fine
we're fine I'm glad it's okay and
nothing is bad bad is happening no no
it's fine
I don't even like what are these circles
and question marks and x's on my
screen
H let me know if it turns into a blue
screen I had that
before I can make it through this League
of Legends game yeah yeah we'll be we'll
we'll make it to this I bet it's Path of
Exile it's mad at me oh you are you do
you have Roblox on in the side as well
no I don't have Roblox on today I'm
don't very
surprising what it became dark what's
going on my greed I will die
now my
God I deserved
it I deserved it for my greed what is
that oh that's his Sal that's pretty
bad
die your
team I accidentally flashed I'm already
in the middle I no longer have second
monitor like at all no it's still
flickering but I I just can't use it you
know oh that's
okay I don't need a second monitor you
feel it you know what is you doing I
feel it I don't need to read
chat
yo all right has SL
what is we're
doing is that Twitter that's flickering
on my page what is oh my God takes
another video he's a shy puppy what is
happening oh what's that charm this
enemy hey looks
funny what do we want to do we're all
we're all doing pretty well
you want to do beautiful lady do we want
to all go mid and push mid do we want to
push bottom what do we want to do oh
this wait they're all here no I don't
like
here I'm here let's go let's go let's go
okay okay okay I'm let's go go
in okay I'll split P get him I'm pring
get
him y got nice dragon SC this one too
get G dead you got this though you got
it one
good Quadra kill goodbye wo the P the P
anything left over what the
hell what's going on what's he run to
wait guys oh yeah you you got him I'm
running you all running behind no he
keeps going oh nice
shotgun I'm too far I'm too slow you
still running he's just fing you
goodbye myw team
destroy very nice you guys are just in
their base destroying things it's
amazing that's
beautiful would it make sense like if
you just kill one lane and then ignore
the other turrets and then you go into
the base you could do that but um why
don't people do that that should be a
thing the more the more people that are
in a lane the you have to split XP with
them I have put that on the out so if
everyone went mid and tried to push
mid in theory it sounds like a great
idea it sounds like a great idea yeah
but if you're all level
one oh the the the single person in that
lane on their side is going to level
faster than you and everyone else is
getting lots of exp freeing
wow good
Jobo poor
computer oh no I did my thing chat it's
okay we we've almost won
G yes oh what's this it's it's
fine my homework I ever hit an wait how
[Music]
she's singing oh that's you right I was
like singer he's Charmed he's Charmed
he's Charmed y
sing hey
snake she's a singer himer
Dinger CH nice
nice nice nice nice
nice this is so nice we're so good oh
here we an end yay
Y come out twin let's go she's a singer
woo we
[Applause]
[Music]
wony my was here to see it
too my
clone good good work nice one good keep
up the good work all right I got a
dash
goodbye I'm awaiting your
[Music]
DM bye byebye bye bye I guess is
everybody
just is this the end for everybody what
yeah I think I need to restart my
computer I really don't know what is
going on it really is not having a good
time
this I mean you played really well all
things considered yeah this is my second
monitor something's happening to
it I can't explain your
problem I can't either I can't explain
my problem either have you tried turning
it off and on again yeah that usually
turns to help you've got it good job
today got it
yay thanks for joining you saved the day
thanks k for joining thank you for
playing yeah you did we had a five coma
she wakes up what did I
do I mean it would have just been a bot
otherwise right I no it would have been
a random person
yeah this it was very nice that I love
playing with you yeah join us again
sometime sure yeah will we can we can
Bot game
some B I hold your hand and I can teach
you yeah
sure just sure sure sure bye everyone
thanks for playing
by
[Music]
byee hia Darlings now it's just you and
me I'm sick
ah hi hi hi Darlings how we doing wait
one second I'm trying to trying to fix
myself please excuse my cough I feel
like I haven't gotten to just like talk
to you guys in like a hot minute so like
excuse
me I'm not going to leave just this
moment how are we doing
[Music]
jailbirds how are you please don't die
you're also sick I'm glad it's not just
me guys guys I drank 2 and 1/2 lers of
water in this 3 hour and 30 minute
stream 3 hour and 30 minute
is uh Happy fat
wait happy fat [\h__\h]
Friday
woo how do you get sick okay let me give
you guys a rundown okay so my sister
malfa came came to visit you guys
remember that right you you guys
probably also remember malfa has like 20
billion children okay she has five
kids she has five kids okay and she came
to the house with her five children when
she arrived her five children at least
two of them had a bad cough this I I
simply ignored okay I simply simply
ignored it that they had a bad cough and
said you know what it's fine it's
probably okay they just have a bit of a
cough and
um yeah and
basically
it
uh it was fine it was it was fine they
were just kind of sick and you know you
put up with
that
then you you can probably hear my voice
itself sounds okay apart from the fact
that I've been coughing up a
lung I can't sleep well because I keep
coughing I have cough
medicine that I have to take every day
it's it's not it's not covid it's just a
really really bad cold I I took a covid
test it's not covid but um yeah I'm a
little deeper than usual to again I've
been coughing a lot so my voice is not
perfect quality
but yeah they need to learn how to cover
up their cops bro they're
children no offense but you can't make
kids do most things how do you expect
them to learn to cover up their cops
properly when they're like
two you're always perfect even when
you're sick you're so
sweet but yeah what skin were you trying
to get we got it we unlocked it we
finally unlocked the seraphine
skin the sarap
all out KDA
skin
after after 5,000 years of trying to
unlock it it's finally happened thank
goodness feel better beimu thank
you I'm very happy because it is uh the
Christmas
season so merry Christmas jailbirds
happy
Friday one heck of a grind is AP car
seraphine you
know I did feel like I was a little bit
of an AP carry that is cuz purposely I
was going with an AP carry
build most of the time rather than
trying to like you
know rather than trying to get anything
separate the [\h__\h] is that it's my Santa
beard
and my Christmas glasses what do you
mean what the [\h__\h] is
that ho ho
ho ho ho
ho jingle bells jingle
bells it's already Saturday in my
place well that's too bad I think my
little darling is scared um because he's
I don't know where he is he's like under
the bed hiding I took I took a peek at
him to make sure he was like
okay um I have a picture of him for you
so for those of you who decided to stay
after the
stream I have a picture of my little
darling for
you uh in case you guys were anxious to
see
him just wait
let me quick
uh I just got to resize it real
quick it's really
big are you guys ready to meet our
son are you
ready say hello to little
darling here is our
baby our baby
kitty isn't he cute
isn't he so sweet
[Music]
looking isn't he
cute our little
darling our little guy he's so big and
fluffy he is big he's about 3 months
old he's as cute as his mother thank you
I don't feel very cute wait let me take
off these accessories I'm being I'm
being too silly I'm being too silly I'm
going off the
handles he's got blue
eyes and he's
beautiful don't you just love
him don't you love
him he's so sweet he's so
fluffy uh I adore him already
obviously and he is my son
fluffy and fuzzy
exactly he's so cute the blue eyes to
match you yeah he matches my hair and my
horns our son
yeah but look did you guys come with me
on the drive to get him I think
not he's full mocha he doesn't look
anything like
foko he's the most aesthetic cat I've
ever seen I know from the moment I saw
his cute little face I fell in love with
him uh
so I think I told you guys he had kind
of a funny story at first so like he
he's the runt of his he's the runt of
his genen that is not the prop he's the
runt of his litter is what I'm trying to
say he's big for a three-month cat I
mean it's his type he's going to be like
20 to 25 lbs if he gets to the
regular the regular weight of his
species but yeah of his litter he was a
little
runt
so but he's big he he's he's doing well
now um he's still not eating quite as
much as he should but um we're trying
different things to try and get him to
eat a little
more but he's still eating and he's
using the litter box and he's drinking
water
yeah he's doing great is my point I
wanted to share him with you sorry at
the r this random part of a league
stream oh I will I will
um tomorrow we're playing Clock Tower
rewind we're in a beat it in one
stream
uh and yeah give him treats I have so
many
treats I have delectable squeeze ups for
kittens supports Healthy
Growth I need to give him one today not
that he needs to have one every day
but I need you guys yeah spoil that
child trust me he is so
spoiled he is so
spoiled uh he will be the most spoiled
cat in the existence of spoiled cats
so you need not worry about if he will
be spoiled or
not because trust me he will be
spoiled to hel in back don't make him
into a fat he might end up being a bit
fat but uh I mean I don't think he will
just because he is the Run um
comparatively he is small which sounds
weird to say cuz he's a big he's a big
boy but comparatively he is
small so yeah I don't I don't let them
overeat but uh the thing with them is
they they have free food so they
actually have food all day whenever they
want
it so he as long as he wants food he
will have
food bigger or smaller than little lady
I think little lady is 20b SS but that's
cuz she's
rotund she's rotund she's not like large
but he's going to get like
large a large
boy yeah he's going to be big sorry I'm
dying I don't mean to
die does that mean he'll eventually be
big darling it doesn't matter how big he
gets he will always be smaller than me
and therefore he will always be little
darling our son our
son
[Music]
woo I love
him anyway sorry for again for those of
you who came out today who sat with me
through League of Legends which I know
as much as I like it is not everyone's
favorite I think uh especially if if the
girls end up not wanting to play it as
much in the future uh I don't know how
many jailbirds would be down member
jailbirds but I I think
maybe playing with members would be fun
I'm in I'm down
yeah my sister keeps calling
me give me one sec
sorry for it was malat was not
Aradia she she I told her I was
streaming and I presumed she'd hung up
she did not care she kept
talking I see yeah it's just sister
things but yeah I hope you guys enjoy
your picture of little darling again I I
figured you guys would like to see
him he's so sweet he's so cute I love
him help I'm coughing and my lungs are
dead help help my
lungs whatever am I going to do about my
lungs
do we get him on week
no he lives with me full
time back
here
yeah sorry uh
anyway I I that's all I I don't have
anything else tomorrow we'll be
streaming clock clock tower rewind I'm
very excited I've never actually played
Clock Tower but you guys know that I'm a
huge Haunting Ground fan which was like
kind of a spiritual successor to um The
Clock Tower series I'm really looking
forward to that um and
yeah I'm really happy we could spend
time today sorry again I know it's
really rough because reading chat's kind
of
very impossible and I'm sick so that
doesn't help cuz I'm like locked in
hardcore I love
Le ah game has multiple endings oh hell
yeah but yeah I I can't
wait and uh I'm so grateful to have
gotten to hang out with you guys today
and to collaborate with everyone who is
here for the collaboration today very
grateful to aaha for popping in and
hanging out with us as
well that was very
nice we asked her like this morning and
we're like hey or we asked everyone and
we're like who wants to play league we
need a
fifth so very very grateful for her to
come in to come to our
rescue hell yeah oh God sorry I died for
a second it's back
now but yeah we we won Hell
Yeah Wawa to the rescue yeah Wawa for
the win she saved
us but either way I will allow you guys
to get on with your day I will send you
over to
bioo as she is also playing game so
thank you all so much for coming and I
will look forward to seeing you all
tomorrow thank you again bye Darlings
[Music]