Wow, my
stomach already hurts! That's
why today's
live show is
on a fishing boat. I
look forward to competing with you. Is the
sound okay? I'm
serious. The level of tension is crazy. There
are members.
3rd place for the taste that matches the week.
Oh my god, I'm so nervous I've got to
eat porridge at the teahouse now
Subaru wants to do his best
as well since we've made it through the preliminaries I wonder who's going to get to the next section
Block d block I have no choice
but to run with all my heart I don't know
what will happen with small tricks.  No, I'm going to ask you to
go with JR. It's really too strong. It's
just
serious. No, it's serious. It's a monolux.
I caught it. I
smoked it. It's already 5.
Alright, I'm fine with Subaru's warm eyes.  Why are you
such a sincere Subaru? Why do you have two pens?
The saas world,
please give me a red one. It's like
Article 10.
Tour. I've
been getting a lot of calls like this. Wait a minute.
8.
It's okay to
buy this kind of thing
Oh, if you are
nervous,
if you are nervous, kill it
early. Don't look right, right and left. It's the
hardest time waiting for you to execute the execution.  I
thought I'd change it because I thought that if I didn't, people would criticize me, but
there's something about it.She's a woman who lived with Katarina.However,
Subaru won't change her name here.I'll call
Katarina Matsubara.To
deflect some hate, I thought of changing it.  I thought I'd try something like that,
but then I'll try really hard and
say it in words I already understand.Ramen, well, well,
well, I'm just
chillin', and I'm a sumo wrestler,
and my palms are so sweaty.Ah, ha, Lou, no,
look at me.  Come
on, that voice is so scary. Wait a minute. [Music] Ah, ah, ah, fast game, ana, trouble me. Okay, then, seriously. My heart rate increases the most while I'm waiting. I don't know if I want to go home, but Subaru is the only one.
But it's a fever, I want to go. ss.
Yes, I don't know how it will turn out, but I
think it's important not to give up.
No, it's true that the sound before the match eased the tension.
Subaru let me start the match early. I've been
thinking about this for a long time.  Every time I experience it
[Music] It's
crazy.
Well, it's okay. I want to have fun driving.
But if I make too much noise, things will get really bad.
So I have to carry the regulations on my back. I can't carry that on my back.
Subaru is already
giving away Dirac porridge.  But I'm going to do my best today. Okay, I'm
going to have a little tea.
Web
Well, the tax is relaxed and fun. I
want to be serious and serious. I want to go to Subaru Subaru in the sky.
Yeah,yeah.
But if you have fun, you'll have fun, so your
concentration will improve and you'll be able to get e 12.
There's something like that.The
lead curve in the runner parts has no choice but to get into the lungs.I
want it to start soon.But I
don't want it to start.Ca No,
seriously, I want the cheese to stop.I
want the cheese to stop.Subaru, maybe Peach.Peach mute speech.Solar
mutes the peach.  I do
n't want to aim for the color, but I thought the Musiper was good too,
but today I thought it was great
because I didn't run recklessly like that, and
when I thought about it, I saw that the short cut at the end of the par par
was too strong, so I thought it
was around that after all.
Donut A Yeah, it's
not bad,
but if you start honestly, it won't come with you anywhere. It's
coming.
So my eyes
tended to look like they were visible.It
's like there's some kind of garbage in my eyes.I
see a lot of things flying around in my eyes, and it's really scary.There's
something wrong with my stress.  The
appearance is you are the
edge power with the art binder nails. I
practiced saying it at the bar on the day. I got
pregnant on the first night at Baby Pa. The
best
concentration
[Music]
[Applause]
5 items
Added to the snow  - I
can't
turn pink I can't go back
[Music] I'm
here [Music]
From here
5 things
[Music]
Pabu
[Applause]
It's Ares day
[Applause] I
can't take it, it hurts
[Applause] [
Music] It's
so bad
[It's so bad]  [Applause] I
ate it.
Ugh. I don't have it. I
guess it's okay.
Ah, well, well. I was a trainee because I met a dog again at the end of the day. Phew. Okay, let's go ahead. Well, the rice was a little sweet. It was more pink. If I wanted it
pink.  Pink Turbo
Okay, ok
ok
Well, my wife's part
is too much.
Dad
Musi bread is also good.
Well, I don't really understand Nehru at the end. I wish they
would stop. There's a
sting in the front.
This is luck.
Okay.
8 catfish.
Let's go after that.
Gay
[Music]
No, I ca
n't get any points.
Wow, it's so serious. Front
f. You
can hit it, but it's going to come at you from behind. It's
going to aim for you.
[Music]
Karate, that's not nice.
Keep going home, a.
It's a hole, it's
dangerous, it's not bad. [Music] I don't want to
get points. I'm going to add this. No
one will accept this domestically. There
are no coins.
Collect them here. No, I'm
fine with leaving this one damaged.
[Applause]
Ocher is fast again.  Sehara Key
Yes, lucky, this is
lucky, this is lucky,
I don't need this, I don't
need this, I don't need this, I don't need this, I don't really need this
[Music]
Well, I'm not good at it
Bone Body
Double Draw
[Music]
Keep the herbs in. No, I've been
at home since I got frustrated.  I can't get enough of it, I'm
already irritated Bob and Khan
[Music]
Take the double
Knight's analysis Not
since Bob and Ylang Ylang Ylang Ylang I can't get irritated I
ca
n't get
irritated anymore Bomb and I can't get irritated
Yosha Roo Natsuyo
r r Dal Darley Reka
No.  I'm sorry for the pest control, but I want to erase the tag cow. I
really want to say it. It's
like this, but I can't throw the tide. I
think I'll go to Artic Tac.
And compensation. I
can't throw stones, so I don't know.
Bob is irritated,
irritated. Don't do it, it's naive.  Seriously
[Music]
When you say hi, ok Eat what you're good at
Mute I wonder if it'll bloom at the end How to use the item
Last, check that first one I can sit down
Hey,
Hokkeko Chuu-chan
[Music] I
wish I had a grudge against Abe
[Music]
Taco-chan  Bye,
there's no swabbing
[Music] It's
strong because it's a cheese that matches the
horsetails backwards It's hard to put the turbo in even the pins
No, but you don't have to replace it
Kids are being targeted [
Music]
Cut it hard for half a meter
[Music]
Here
No  That's right.
[Music]
What's in here? I don't have to cheer for you.
OK
[Music]
Abune, it's a reverse Nan color here.
Baba,
boke
[Music]
Aokeru, I'm going to
write a blue note.
I have no choice but to live without my
insurance.Insert the book.
[Music]
Abune
Knife
This is the summary of winning the king tile.This is sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!  I
can't concentrate,
hey,
my heart is pounding. Lou,
that's dangerous.
That's a dangerous place, I'm going to take a turn. Petit, now I'm going through things
like Mario Circuit. I'm
not really good at Marion Bar Kit either. It's
dangerous, just aim where. Well, Mario
Circuit.  Okay?
[Music] I
don't even remember where we'll meet anymore.
Haa, I want Musipan to be Animal Crossing Runners and
Animal Crossing.
Ah
[Music]
Big blue, right? Fick Blue, it's
scary to go without a book or something, so
stay stable.  Calmly collect your love and run
Ah, you're really
concentrating.
Say,
eh, let's
go outside.
[Music]
Come on, I cut the oily version. Bye-bye.
[Music] Be
careful. Blue
me.
Collect coins.
[Music]
Stop
this, what's this?
It's here
[music]
It's a mess
[music] It
's okay if it falls on its own wf it's not,
give me
[music] It's a
stand 6
Wow, I think this is it That's
right,
get involved, then this is a grand success.
That's lucky
5 Thank you for
doing it Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa--I-I-IA-A-IA-AAA-A-AAA-A-AAA-A-AYA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-SEWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWAAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  I do
n't know what I'm talking about right now Switch Switch
[Music]
Dobson or something, I'm going to do it anyway
Subaru's favorite Animal Crossing
Okay, I
want to win here,
then
Barley, okay, okay, Garley Satoshi, I've
been practicing pretty well The
only way to win is through the rituals,
okay.
[Music] I ca
n't seem to get it
[Music]
U.S. Const Trigger There
are some good works.
Wow, everyone should look carefully and
come over here.
Well, I can't get the item, but it's
tough. It's tough not to get the item here. It's
Yamato Tsutsu.
[Music]
And 3  Isn't it?
Well, it's fine.
Ayabe, you've calmed down. Kaizu,
people keep turning around,
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
[Music] I do
n't have any coins
[Music] I
want to go. The
curtain is already bad.
2 days
[Music]
Stars from behind,
double!
[Music]
Can We have a
long discussion about where to go?
[Music] I
feel like I've been drinking.  Not everything
[Applause] It's a
big killer
Okay,
Gaskelevan
Arm, I seriously thought I couldn't do it Now I
thought I couldn't do it anymore I
gave you something I couldn't do anymore I seriously thought It's
important not to give up Nice
killer Animal
Crossing Day
Sigh
[Music]
Car
Alright, the
whrar has
arrived,
and it's time for a
magic mirror called Bowser Castle
[Music]
Car
Concentrate
[Music] It's
okay, let
's go, it's
okay,
it's summer! It's
dangerous over here! Well then, it's
only the first week
[Music]
Love  Collect them properly
[Music] It's
too much today to just grab two caps.
[Music] You
can just run inside as usual.
[Applause]
This is a dangerous item.
Okay
[Music]
Hmm,
you forget. That's really
bad.  I do
n't need it Rider who [ __ ] Da Blue Replacement Scene where he takes a [ __ ] [Music] Okay, that's a bit around. Boo-boo, which one of them is put in a high-pressure game? Hey, he's an example of someone who has a bomb and is too strong. [Music] Part 8. I guess that's it.  Ba
Aburado
[Music]
That's all
Yeah yeah
bpa
[Applause]
Atta early
Please
p Ah ha aha
re
ran
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you, thank you, parents, thank you,
see you at [ __ ] Easy
I am
amaran