[Music]
[Applause]
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing sry soot
feel it rush through me
[Music]
feel R me
there feel it like you br me
[Music]
oh honey
feel it right for me
[Music]
intoxicating DJ keep
playing kick and the cake
oh
oh I'm I'm sorry I'm stressed like sorry
uh not so I I just got all these
accessories so I'm putting them on just
now uh
oh oh
little Austrian flags on me so I think
wait let me get rid of that chat I think
you can tell who I'm supporting can you
can
you uh I think it just said like I have
the audio still muted but uh it will be
muted anyway for you guys but I think it
just said uh they showed the the
Poland uh the Polish like setup from the
get go I guess that's a public
thing and they didn't show that famous
player like it wasn't he wasn't on there
which is a good sign I
think okay also I only ate half of my
quason so I might have to eat more of it
in a
moment
o yeah the the levy Levy guy I don't
know who that is a lot of people seem to
know him I guess he's the strongest
player oh they're coming in wow wow wow
it's so big by the way this is
happening in Germany in Berlin I want to
do a I want to do a bet I want to do a
oops I want to do a bet I wanted to the
to do the poll so generally when I first
had this idea I wasn't very uh
optimistic um about Austria because from
history from what I know Austria wasn't
very good but it seems in the past years
they have improved and uh therefore
maybe Austria has actual chances because
they played pretty well against France
France was I'm I already sound like a
commentator Austria wasn't even able to
score a goal against Austria Austria no
wa Austria wasn't able to score a goal
against Austria in fact France wasn't
able to score a goal against Austria um
they only lost because Austria made a
self goal and well that that was an
oopsy that was a bit stupid but uh
France is pretty good so Austria
defending themselves while playing still
pretty aggressively is uh something to
be proud of I would say I really sound
like a
commentator oh wait are they singing
which Alum are they singing to oh they
see the austri I need to unmute for
[Music]
myself I actually can't sing
it okay let me mute that again um
good try I only know
[Music]
the I don't know that's all I really
know uh we're not like you Americans out
there um what was I saying yeah so and
then I hear Poland isn't even that good
sorry polish friends but I hear they're
not at like that crazy good and Austria
has been improved so I
think I might actually bet for
Austria um we not unfortunately
true yeah but you never know like
apparently like there's already been so
many self goals um you might win for a
self goal who knows you never know a lot
of the wins so far have been self goal
wins or not not a lot of them maybe two
or so oh there's it's wet the camera is
wet have you guys all got a place to
watch oh do you do you do you do you say
have a stream
open or the Polish the Polish oh the
handsome
polish can't believe we're getting the
stream I had this idea a while ago and
honestly when I first had this idea I
was quite confident in it but then I saw
quite a few kfb were like me um and then
then I lost my confidence but now I'm
like actually this was a good idea
because a lot of you guys are seemingly
very excited for it
so that is a win a big
[Music]
win so usually they're like what two 2.5
hours or what was
it where austri 67% let's go
let's
go okay I refreshed My Stream because I
I I I needed to I feel like I fell
behind one
second I just realized because it's a
live
stream we're not matching up the time so
you guys will see things a little bit
before I do so you might be like like go
go in the chat like right before I
actually see it are you also in a
commercial okay me too you're going to
be like and I'm like or you can even
prank me with that I'm like what there's
a goal coming up in in two seconds wait
doesn't make
sense no wait that no wait that doesn't
make
sense no no I would see it before
you but my chat reaction would be late
and no you would see my reaction late
okay never mind never mind you would see
my reaction
late let me put up like
[Music]
um let's do Austria versus Poland up
there at the top and because we're both
like white and
red what the [\h__\h] is this
light oh it's like the there's like fog
there's it's so foggy oh they do be
dancing oh [\h__\h] oh who whoa whoa
H flare
smoke I
sure oh I'm excited I'm
[Music]
excited I'm actually excited
oh oh somebody died from the from the
W
dudes
G rest in peace when did he die was it
so
recently do you know a lot about
football I know
nothing I know some like I mean I know
every like there's sometimes there's um
11 elf met uh 11 meter
shooting and if you I don't know I guess
if you kick a ball so that it's outside
of the field sometimes I guess you can
like shoot it back in like you get to
specific no the other team gets to
specifically shoot it back in from the
side m also I know that there's no hands
allowed except for the gold
dudes wait is the red shirts is Austria
right
gillich depending on your stream you're
probably going to see different
scenes okay all right we oh my God is it
starting they're running already no
they're just getting in position right
oh what we haven't won against Poland
for 30
years today is the
day wow this this arena is epic I like
that opening over
there oh Austria has
anos apparently the weather is um
relatively chill today let's go seven
and six 5 4 3 2 1 kick
off go go go go go go go oh no fall fall
fall red card red card I'm eating my clo
sorry it's almost done you can't point
at the people you're passing to
then they
[Laughter]
no put timer on
screen okay I'll try in the
moment but then I don't know how to set
the timer when it's
already past zero
H oh he used his head wow C FL
do we have like a a good Austrian player
like someone who's
oh that was easy someone who's um
um you are so far ahead of me eh for me
it says 1 minute 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17
18 19
what are you guys um aren't you guys
more ahead of me
then some people are ahead some people
are behind I
guess mostly ahead what the hell
oh should I I don't know there's like uh
if I refresh I get ads again I think let
me do maybe quality less quality maybe I
don't know sounds like on online is
behind of TV H you guys watching on your
actual
TV
oh man I didn't look for a moment I just
saw someone fall people aren't
angry oh
oh you're watching actual TV damn
it so I I am behind after all
okay
um oh angry angry I looked at my qu for
one second I'm missing all the good
[Music]
moments who hurt who w w oh nice nice
slow motion
wait so what was the answer do we have
good Austrian players somebody somebody
who's known like like Levy probably
not
sa never heard of
him
okay
sa bad pass sa bad pass
wasn't
good I'm going to end the poll now
because you we're already in the
game and who knows when they're going to
do the
first goal but Austria wins in the poll
woohoo
see Austria is already playing pretty
well no like they have the ball the most
so far I think oh oh
oopsie corner
corner wait we're getting we're getting
a corner shot who
we have control over the ball
woohoo wait who's the one who's shooting
is that sabit I don't know that I don't
know their
faces oh yeah it is him he shot and
yeah it's okay it's okay we have so much
time oh who who oh they're like slapping
together their things are
they oh and the fingers I guess and
their I thought they actually don't seem
to have these things and I have the
tubes oh
oh
acrobatics oh oh discussion
time
whoa nah that oh oh oh oh he just flew
over
him and he's like what the the [\h__\h]
mate idle meeting soccer meeting sorry I
think the reason why I say soccer
usually is because in Japanese they say
Saka and I don't know that's just kind
of stuck with
me oh oh what what does he
want man I wish we were all on the same
time but this is uh shatan can't be
helped because everybody's watching
elsewhere so is a timer even
necessary maybe just so you just so you
guys know
where I don't know do you want one I'm
at 66 7 67 6 68 69
610 for the VA are people going to VA
this oh oh
ooh that was entangled the men were
entangled with each
other okay where what is what is this
kind of shooting called when he's he's
not even in the
corner what is this what is this called
again of to F when they shoot like that
from further away but in the middle of
the field a free kick why did they do a
free kick
oh he's
hot oh that was sabita again oh so they
were F fou fou get
fou okay let me try to set this up uh
timer it's so hot in my room I got to
make a I got to turn on
the the fan in a
moment I'm going to look away to set up
the timer I hope nothing too exciting
happens
leave me alone timer edit
timer how do I start
[Music]
from Poland hey what hey
hey oh another another free kick okay
take your time guys count to from the
count
countown
[Music]
count stopwatch
stopwatch uh I can't
edit time what if I give you my local
time n that doesn't
help uh wait I can I
could I could try to SC uh
[Music]
M A hey
hey oh this wait now they're doing now
they're doing this sidekick thingy is
this also freak kick or does this have a
different name watch TV I don't know I I
don't have like I have a TV but no live
stream thing I don't I don't pay for TV
although I pay for or if
oh what what what what
I watched that I saw that but I almost
later than you
guys let's
go W
who oh that was that was Frank that free
kick from the
outside w w that was
that was sick wow with the bald head I
think all bald men in the world should
should be uh confident and happy because
with this bald head a gold was shot a
throw in okay look at that beautiful
bald head it's perfect for shooting
goals it's so cute to see their
reactions oh my God w
let's
go okay I can't I can't focus on the
[\h__\h] alot
thingy oh now ah now now it was 10
minutes [\h__\h] I could have I could have
started from 10 minutes okay how about
we wait
until until it's like a a a a an easy
understandable time for me me like I'll
wait until it's 15 or or 20 for
me 15 okay and then I'll write a note on
the screen that the timer is minus 15
plus 15 minutes I
guess
okay okay we need to we need to protect
we need to
protect holy [\h__\h] I can't believe we
already have a goal this is going
fast yeah we're very
dominant are there any Japanese Bros
watching late at night cuz I saw some
people being interested even Japanese
Bros were like hey yo he
yo Japanese Bros who I've never seen
before there's so many
[Laughter]
okay okay the
score
indeed
okay I'm late I'm
late stumble wrong score a well okay if
you see it that way yeah on TV it's the
other way
around
[Laughter]
okay
okay okay okay
okay it's so hot let me turn this
on okay what are we seeing
sabita is right out there ready to take
the ball he's always always there speedy
boy Speedy boy yeah Lea the the the
famous Poland polish player is
apparently not playing he's uh
injured yeah Austria top per
mm a got a hell of a coach they play
where well as a
team yeah because the coach is
me the coach is
me I'm the
coach imagine like could you could you
imagine
somehow this soccer players who are
total
normies can you screen c i i could I was
thinking that too
but I don't know yeah
yeah I might but I'm
I'm I don't want to I don't want to
because
n
risky what was I saying what was I just
saying yeah imagine these n me soccer
players of Austria finding out
that that some animu girl was watching
them play and was you know supporting
them some anime girl vtu what the [\h__\h]
is that or was what
this
girl but I'm their lucky charm oh oh oh
okay
yeah I've got I got 8,000 people with me
that should get their attention
right
H what's with bald guy's nose what did
he do with his
nose tra his name is trer I
think oh oh oh oh oh oh oh getting close
to the goal again but this is like too
like when when all the other players are
already there from the other team like
when they all caught up and you're all
there in a big huddled group I guess
it's really difficult to get a
goal they can't steal the [\h__\h]
ball oh this is cute cute
cute don't lose the ball don't lose the
ball
wow you missed it missed oh oh [\h__\h] okay
20 is easier anyway 20 is
easier sorry I missed it I was like what
what do you mean I missed what
what like damn they're going to give us
some information like how much
percentage
W that flew high oh okay they stole the
ball they stole it give it back
uh how much percentage like how much
everybody's uh has the ball right I want
to know
that I will reset the timer for sure at
the half time or whatever that that
might be
good but if you're watching the VOD I
did
Count here and there quite a bit
so you can adjust to when I was counting
the time I
suppose and I did say when was when it
was kick
off whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh H oh Somebody Touched with their
hands I want to see the slow
[Music]
motion let's see I'm seeing it I'm
seeing it oh oh out that what not not
not that's obviously not on purpose like
what are you supposed to do when it boun
bounces yeah he has he was actually
trying
to just like pull his hands towards
himself
mhm no intention of touching the ball
wait there's two balls on the field
there's two balls on the field go make a
goal go make go they can't defend
against
two two balls cannot be
[Laughter]
defended let's go let's
go oh oh oh oh oh oh wa took the ball
back oh and they got the ball
back
oh I'm sorry to all the Polish viewers
and my polish fans
because Austria is going to win I'm
sorry and it does it doesn't mean I
don't love you oh oh oh T it flew over a
he looks so
young no Jinx no
Jinx we're in a good position also my
quality just went down to like 360p what
the [\h__\h] oh it's okay it's back
he looks so
young yeah we might you know then don't
just don't you know I'm Austrian I have
to support
Austria we shall see who will emerge
Victorious exactly prepare the time okay
okay okay okay okay I I will I will also
uh you have to give me a moment to show
it on screen but okay I'm ready I'm
ready 1 minute 15 seconds until I push
it
tki is 21 years old the one that I said
looks
young 21 that is I thought he looked
like 17 or
so being so sporty must make you look
young oh look at those look at those
slow passes everybody's everybody's
there
oh almost almost timer time timer time
timer
time oh oh oh oh oh oh see Austria like
every time I look which is all the time
Austria has the ball we like constantly
have the ball I'm sorry Poland I'm so
sorry yeah safe to shoot it back to the
what's his name 156 I thought I missed
again okay okay 5 five six
78 a got rid on the timer H but it was
like H bring it back bring it back wait
I see it at the bottom four five six
seven eight nine stop
okay mhm
a a where is
it I can't where it
oh it doesn't show
[Music]
up oh it won't show
up where is it timer where is the
[Music]
timer
what maybe oh
no ah maybe like this
ah no
no was
weird um let me
try what are they
singing what are they
singing
oh oh I'm late they already
stopped red white red
ah okay I think I I think I got it
working oh oh oh oh oh oh who who whoa
close one close one
Austria oh see
okay
wait okay there you go okay I'm focused
again I'm focused
nice safe Austria okay
white the white Poland has the ball for
once oh oh oh nice nice Austria oh nice
Austria oh well protected well
protected they attack but they also
protect yeah yeah yeah
nice nice
maybe maybe are even the other people
who watch on seos
TV uh also way ahead of
me where are the savos TV people should
I switch to like
ORF
uh are you are you saying it
Rd stream Rd but that's German can I
watch
that let me check
uh don't touch it now you have a timer
true I don't think I can ah it's okay
right it's okay you don't got you guys
don't mind if my reaction is pretty late
hopefully that's the problem when
watching live when there's so many
different
[Music]
sources okay
okay is there anyone who's kind of on
par with
me considering the stream delay
[Music]
too me
me yeah oh nice oh okay I a few ones
good good
oh ball possession
65% 152 passes yeah I mean obviously we
have more passes if we got the ball 65%
of the time
whoa you're only 5 Seconds ahead of me
that that's that's probably the stream
delay then nice
nice sick that's that's strong that's
strong
possession is a negative setat no what
how the more we have the ball the more
we can control the field and score a
goal exactly right why would it been
possession by demons that possession is
good what the
[\h__\h] if you're obessed by a demon that
is a negative stat
yeah wait so now the Austrian guy shot
it kind of
out so that's why the other guy the
Poland guy the young
guy gets to shoot it back in this
right why' he shoot it out I guess he
was like panicking oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh W whoa
sh
sh what are you able to watch the amiba
stream and that even that one is 20
seconds ahead what why is Japan why is
the Japanese streaming service 20
seconds
ahead oh
[Music]
W
whistle I guess that's what you do when
you want to boo a lot of them are
whistling
yeah yeah you guys did are head why
don't you pause the stream for a minute
cuz in my case when I paused my stream
it didn't like catch up when I unpaused
it if you guys don't mind if you guys
want to be closer to me you can pause
your stream
for like 20 seconds doesn't let
you you'll do it okay good you did okay
nice
nice we're 28 minutes 17 seconds
in do the math guys do the
math I can't pause from the
stadium there's no way there's no way
that there's someone at the stadium
right now watching my stream I think the
people sitting next to you they would be
like why the [\h__\h] are you on your
phone or maybe would they I don't know I
guess most people seem to be very
focused I mean if you're here
whoa if you're if you're all the way in
Berlin watching this live then you
shouldn't be on your
phone you'd be surprised I'm playing the
match I can't
pause I'm busy wa I'm busy on the
field yeah I was also supposed to play
today for the Austrian team but I hurt
my ankle so unfortunately but they'll be
fine they learned a lot from
me we trained together and I think they
they picked up my oh what why are you
guys no is there a gold coming no no no
no no no no no what what no no no no no
no no no no wait it's so slow how can I
get a go from here no no no no no no no
no [\h__\h]
you I got spoiled by the oh he's so
what's wrong what chill oh they're like
so so
[\h__\h] now good we'll give you that one
so that you feel happy at least a little
bit and then you don't get um
embarrassed I'll give you that one e
e
e one for
you just
one that's all you'll get we're early
game but yeah when you're so close to
the goal it gets like
chaotic it's like did you see that it
was like going
on it's okay you guys can spoil me it's
okay I mean would be more fun if I
didn't saw it coming
[Laughter]
but maybe there will be times where I'm
not paying attention to chat it's
okay Ma m
whoa what's that slide with the pointing
at yourself some nice poses from these
people wait I think I just it was a
closeup of a of a guy in the audience
cheering and the guy next to him I
literally just saw him uh putting his
finger in his nose going real deep going
real deep did you see that saos TV
people
he went real deep
there I don't even think the that the
camera guy noticed it or did it on
purpose that's like just a short moment
and then played in slow
[Laughter]
motion wait is the camera feed the same
for oh do we have the same camera feed
did did you see like the the sliding
pose and then right after the fan close
up
okay okay okay okay just a commentary
different
[Laughter]
[Music]
then 32 minutes in
ah the Polish guys are getting a little
up up is that how you say
it they're so
excited commentary yeah okay commentary
is W for
everybody that's right we all all got
the same
one
no you [\h__\h] pushed my boy and his
face he gives like a
huh
well you push my
boy he push my oh okay clap clap clap cl
cl clap clap clap St not it's going to
happen
right oh good chance though good
chance do
commentary oh this am I not doing
commentary this whole
[Music]
time he's holding the ball over his head
I thought that was
illegal just kidding I know it's okay in
this case
commentate harder uh uh I can just copy
what the commentator I'm listening to is
saying oh
oh blue guy stopped the ball with his
dick and now he's kicking it with his uh
Fe feet and and he's like oh who do I go
for and he shoots to a red guy wait do
they work together oh yeah they do oh I
shoot it back to the blue guy he wanted
to see more of that from
[Laughter]
before oh they they they whistling
they're unhappy with something probably
because he took too much time because
people don't like that when they do that
right because uh time is sticking oh he
shot back they shot back to him people
are very unhappy they're like what the
[\h__\h] are you doing oh they sh back wait
shooting shooting they're shooting back
so much they're so
T oh oh two accidents in the row oh is
that going to give a card or not no it's
going to be ignored because shitti is
uh also a little bit upy today I don't
even know what that looked like like
whose fault that would have been but
it's okay we're good moving on back to
Austrian possession of the ball going up
to 100% soon I'm telling you that
passing mag is called a back shot nah no
way in German we say maybe Rus
maybe 100%
possession 100% of the
time look pass okay
she blue blue
blue Twan
to
to to I I I honestly haven't talked
about or like heard people talk about
sock football in a long time so I don't
know the right terms anymore I
guess
bro ah he's like oh my leg
ah
ah whoa whoa that was a that was
interesting that was sick that was some
stunts did he get a card for that he's
doing a Peter
Griffin they always act so
dramatic but that was a he he fell from
quite
high he did for real
yo that's slide oh someone censored oh
never
mind nice camera
work so who who are they
censoring the coach wants to be
censored I
what why does people walking the Yellow
Jacket people why are they walking back
there where are they going in that long
line who what's their
job yellow and orange jacket people
security
oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
if there was a goal I would know by now
probably so y yep that's how it was
going to go it's okay good try that was
fast you got to go for the fast
ones you got to go for the fast
ones that's
like the best chance I would say when
the others are still trying to catch up
this is exciting this is fun I think I
will watch the Netherlands one to next
week on Tuesday Austria versus
Netherlands but if we lose this
one would we still be able to play the
Netherlands one because then we would
have lost twice is there still like a
meaning to it or is it going to be
canceled or so
ah you play them all
okay but if I if we lose two and then
lose that uh win that one would we still
proceed losing two games winning one
doesn't seem like a very good
score
no right it
wouldn't but maybe it's important for
Netherlands that they they might need
the result of it of the game
right they still they still would need
the results so Austria can't just be
like hey we're out so [\h__\h]
you no this is for the sake of
Netherlands in that case
but 40 minutes in W time passes fast
when you uh watch uh football huh huh 40
minutes
in damn that's some exciting 40 minutes
I'm becoming a football
[Music]
fan what do you mean free Austrian
Santos what whoa what whoa who
what whoa whoa whoa
oh yes oh Santa Claus is Austrian
yes wa I saw it so late
them
Santa go coming up girl coming up okay
but okay if you guys spoil me at least I
will look closer at what's
[Laughter]
happening oh did you guys troll me you
little
[Laughter]
shits I thought it was
a who I was so
close aim do aim Doo aim Doo vtuber fans
watching football be like aim
do what we
say well shout
sh it was the Ping it
was old them excuses oh getting close to
goal again I
stolen ball
stolen ball is
gone oh is that like okay he was like
super close to the line and shot it out
is that his fault because like how can
you it's difficult to get it to to keep
it
inside who gets to shoot it back in I'm
not seeing it oh they cut back too late
I think I think the Polish ones sent the
back ball back in
last touch counts okay
H yeah fought so
much play byplay commentary by Kiana
takanashi anime girl by
day cat uh Woman by
night I become a Catwoman yes yes
[Laughter]
F show by
night
yes are they singing yet gets
LS no h you never know it also sounds
like there you could you could insert
all kinds of things how do you even hear
what they're
saying but it kind of did sound like yet
get L yet get l
here we
go it it's pretty common yeah I think
get gets L I'm kind of sad I did not
hear an o o o
yet or did I miss
[Music]
one missed
it and I would be so scared when a ball
is like falling from up so high and so
far and I have to
like I'd be so scared I'd probably duck
oh hey someone's on the floor someone's
on the floor two people on the floor two
people acting dead ah his nose polish
nose
broken I can never take these these
football guys seriously because they're
always they're they they just always act
so Peter Griffin what he just he just
made his nose was just
flicked what what you're acting like
that your nose was just flicked a little
[Laughter]
bit what I thought he maybe got an elbow
on in his face or what they're getting a
[\h__\h] f m
she no it's a free kick okay wait
somehow this looked like something else
to me okay plus one plus one minute oh
because we're oh we're like What half
half half time what is
this what is this half
time it's 45 minutes I gave an extra
minute what does that mean
why oh safe say safe oh are they they're
not getting anything out of this aren
they at a time okay
and man
man I'm man first
sou German
Ki sh she
she good
one
woohoo nice catch like a baby he caught
it like a falling baby so Safe in His
Hands
okay well how much time is in
between how much
time I stopped my timer I hope that's
okay they're not going to cut I guess
[\h__\h] should
I do I continue it or do I reset it 15
minutes
wow and this is already half time let's
do longer come on guys
show me what you
got ah man have
[Music]
time they don't reset it right they
continue from 45 let me mute my stream
they continue from 45 Right started at
45 minutes I don't know if I can like
[Music]
wait cuz this one I can't edit it
let me find a
different oh you seeing
that let
me let me find a different
one yeah either to zero or to 45 let me
try to find one that can do
like stopwatch online
[Music]
how about this
one
uh not
oh
start from zero
W halftime analysis my halftime
analysis I'll tell you in a moment if I
find
something
[Music]
stopwatch 45 to 90 and extra
time yay I want extra
time what about The Possession well how
much was it at the end did it go
up did it go did they say something did
they show it again I didn't see if it
went
up no extra time for oh you're right I
think I heard about that 6040
ooh
[Music]
oo o
going back to zero and then adding 45 is
difficult math
though that's difficult
math
uh
stopwatch where you can set the starting
time ah okay
I think I found
one yeah it starts from 45 so okay I
think I found one um is this minutes
45 and then start and then it goes up
okay found
one reset set time okay
[Music]
while I
stream
uh big delay
just adding this note for people who
join in
later
okay so okay analysis well yeah um
Poland getting another uh one goal in
there and makes me uh a bit scared
indeed um Austra overperforming you
think so we're definitely good like I'm
not embarrassed I thought I thought this
would be a disaster until I learned that
ustra is actually you know pretty good
these days I'm proud finally cuz like
usually we're only good at winter sports
for once being able to show our strength
elsewhere is uh impressive
mhm yeah yeah yeah
yeah so we're one one1 now H so I don't
know it's a bit intimidating a bit scary
but I'm sure the Austrian players can
show that they're meant to win today
they're playing both aggressive but
while still having good
defense and they got the ball a lot of
the time so they have lots of
chances they're they're uh they're
protecting their own goal quite
well they seem to have control over
everything they don't seem to be too
stressed out attack and protect that's
our
strategy yeah treats the ball like a
baby so far no weird fouls either no
nothing serious we're all doing well
nobody's hurt except for that one guy's
nose just because he got INF
[Music]
flicked that one little flick broke his
whole nose his whole
face TW the ball like a baby kiss it and
pet it give it some nice soft Strokes
Maybe put it in a diaper so it bounces
less I don't know if that's a good thing
probably
not yeah
yeah can't believe there's so many
Japanese Bros also watching there must
be quite a few soccer fans out there I I
wouldn't think that they would be
interested in a European soccer
match
you soccer sorry in Japanese they say
soccer soccer is big in Japan it's not
even like their biggest sport they
prefer like baseball and golf and stuff
those are the biggest Sports
[Music]
there but I guess football is also up
there but the real the real most
important stuff is
baseball and golf I think
no swiming Buu
their national team is pretty decent
Japanese
team yeah I think they were not bad I
don't remember the last time I watched
them is I mean I don't think I ever
watched them really play soccer if
football you know in German we say fball
which sounds so similar to football
right maybe that's just that just feels
wrong to me cuz soccer just sounds like
a cooler word I want to say that I I
feel like I'm actually speaking English
when I say
soccer as opposed to saying football
just seems like like I don't
[Laughter]
know you guys get so angry at it even
though soccer is the American word
right h
sorry sorry ah sorry I
moved sorry sorry microphone didn't want
to be there okay I get
[Music]
it don't worry I have full faith in
sabita he will cook he's cooking they're
all cooking oh oh oh that reminds me
that advertisement reminds me uh you
know I have I I cook with hellofresh and
and they had um these past weeks and now
they've been having like they always
have like something special going on
like it's either like uh asparagus
season so it's like a lot of asparagus
dishes or so sometimes they have like
events event themed things and they've
been having uh yeah these this like
European Championship uh
themed uh
dishes oh Red Bull ad
I didn't get a single one though because
a lot of them are they they don't even
they're kind of
like junk
foodish not really but not not really
junk food
but I don't know don't want those dishes
also I made an
oopsy I forgot about my oh hey that's
the same ball I got in my maybe not
quite looks similar though and what was
I saying ah uh I got my hell fresh box
like yesterday like maybe at noon or so
and then I I I I forgot about putting it
into the fridge so I think it there's
you know ice bags in there but by the
time I opened it they were all melted
and just like chill
water I don't know if I if that was good
like I think I think it was in the box
for like
maybe
20 24
hours totally
[Music]
forgot but the water it was like still
pretty
chill and there are like several of
[Music]
them not two
weeks I think so I have one fish dish
one chicken and one
beef like all graded beef or whatever
you call it uh I forgot oh we're back in
the studio woo woo woo woo have you
noticed I'm in my in my new studio today
as
well then the me be yeah that one is
probably fine I
think throw out all the meat right now
right
now okay let me hear what they're saying
I'm actually interested
oh okay he's saying the first 20 minutes
we were like super in control and
then and then it was kind of our fault
to like give give the control a little
bit more to the
Polish
poish I don't know
out gold was beautiful though that was
beautiful [\h__\h] broken nose no not for
real
right no way did they say that his nose
is
broken oh the timer I'll have to started
at the right
time but uh would it start at 46
cuz they added a
minute he he broke his
nose 45 okay he
did what I mean okay if you did then
that was more serious than it looked
like but no
way what do you mean that that one flick
that we saw that guy his nose was broken
no way no way
what no different one okay okay okay
okay I thought
so flick of ultimate
[Laughter]
destruction flick that flick that is so
powerful
like Mikasa Mikoto from rail gun when
she flicks the coins
insane electric rail gun power coming
out of one flick and one
coin rail gun
reference one flick
man wait who ma
ma but what today or you mean the guy
who has a Band-Aid on his
nose where I asked what happened to his
nose or someone completely unrelated who
are you talking
about a French player in the French
team or French player in our team is
there
one Francis star player he's wearing a
mask oh was he like on camera or why are
you bringing it up
fr's best player a couple days ago on
the field or uh where did he break his
nose he was on camera
oh
oh versus oh in the match versus Austria
oops wait whose fault was it
ouch you can still play with a broken
nose the adrenaline will help for
sure and
and yeah I'm going to break your nose
too oh
yay we're going back into the
field let's touch some grass oh he
touched his ass touching grass touching
ass no difference no
difference bounce bounce jump
jump yeah yeah I'm on I'm ready for the
timer I'm
ready molder is is getting switched I
guess in the Polish
team do we have any changes in the
Austrian
team oh yeah poovi is being switched
with M M
M vamos
Amigos yes
Los
Los Patrick vimma ah gillich is being
switched with
vimma okay that is very important I
totally know everything about these
players and I say this is a good switch
this is a good switch because gillich
was not in his best today not in the
best shape he
performs better
usually no I have no idea starting okay
wait wait wait wait wait
one they're still standing around for
me just one dude running
oh what do you mean it started yeah now
it started for me
okay right at the
whistle what why are we so that's like
how many SEC maybe still 20 seconds or
so woo that's close to get outside of
the
line
okay he what was it passion uh passion
what was the
what's our team yellow
call was
it Justin no passion got to say it in
the Japanese way though
he's running he's running sa is running
a [\h__\h]
Marathon protect protect
protect mical
Justin mental physical passion mental
physical passion thanks for the
[Music]
membership passion we need to teach the
these people in the
crowd our
call do you think the Germans in the
audience are cheering for
Austria cuz we speak same language come
on
Germans I mean I would expect a lot of
Polish people and Austrian people to
actually have made the trip but for sure
because it's in Germany there's also a
lot of Germans right probably you do
yeah yeah yeah yeah you capturing for us
once we're playing against each other
though for
[Music]
sure sorry I'm fighting with the Germans
in the chat you think it's the opposite
he they don't like
Austria you little
shits if you watch my stream you have to
be for Austria unless you're polish then
I'll give you a
pass oh oh they're hugging a they were
hug he's like hey I could have had that
one why did you hug me
oh
huh that
was the Polish guys should shot it
out yay we're getting the ball no okay
see uh I think I've learned all there is
to learn about football I've learned all
there is to learn I
understand h
Levy coming no way what do you mean no
no
no no I thought he was
injured I thought he was
injured
oh yeah austri gets to shoot it in mhm I
see bounce
bounce he's okay now no no
no no God please no oh yeah right they
switched the sides right just realized I
know they do that halfway
through get in the robot Livy no
no no why he's so well known I'm scared
I don't know him
but people keep on talking about him so
he must be trouble he must be dangerous
very very
dangerous yeah why do they keep on
shooting the ball
outside concentrate
Focus he was good back in the day okay I
will only trust what you're
saying instead of the ones who say he's
super
good cuz you you're giving me a bit more
confidence is
38 I'm sure with 38 you can still play
good soccer when your whole life you've
been so so
fit maybe if you haven't been working
out your whole life then you would be
feeling like crap at 38 with back pain
and [\h__\h] but if you your whole life have
been playing soccer at football you're
going to be good you're going to be
fine AA
okay
oh wait what
who
ex oh let's go let's go come on come on
H come on come on
Boss P let get better you can do it next
time next time just got to go
harder
remember okay okay they're faster faster
zooming they're zooming they're Zoom
over the field and he goes for it and he
misses by far a
do could have had a chance for a pass on
the left side but he didn't see him I'm
just copying what my commentator is
saying he didn't see him so thank God he
didn't see him because if he would have
seen him then maybe he would have had a
better opportunity in combination with
passing to his buddy
[Music]
Ki going to kick the ball into the
[\h__\h] goal
Austria blind
Pawn I'm screaming like a true
fan it's getting
heated it's getting hot in here so take
up all your clothes I am getting so hot
I'm going to take my cloes off
well he speaking in strong Austrian
dialect my
commentator
whoa nah that was just you
know two dudes going at a speedy but
different pace he he balling gets the
yellow card
ah ah for what for what though let's see
uh ah oh he's pulling his shirt why do
you do this why do you [\h__\h] do this
though why do you do this I know like
both parties like in all games they
always do stupid [\h__\h] but why why do you
[\h__\h] do it why do you pull a shirt
why why are you trying to manipulate
this can you not [\h__\h] hold your
manliness manly instincts
back stop be be like that oh yeah yeah
yeah
yeah tell him what's
up the protu stop doing the protu it's
not supposed to be a thing in the middle
of an important soccer match football
match he's like bro stop stop doing the
Bro
t stop doing it or else you're going to
get a red card next time
I mean maybe it's like a natural
instinct when you're chasing something
and
someone but no like this is your job
your whole life you know it's wrong you
know it's wrong and you still do it
these soccer football players
sorry don't get mad at me guys don't get
mad yeah it's totally on purpose right
they know what they're doing but I get
the feeling that you want to do it I I
get it but you should know
you should know
better you just pre you obviously pre
trying to prevent something
there
sucks hoping that the ref doesn't see
the ref sees everything the ref has
sauron's
eye oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
too too slow
paced it's not happening that's not
happening otherwise chat would tell
me wo wo
W yellow card again
what what what what
happened oh okay I Sab I saw that just
now oh no it was Vima I thought it was
sa so they both have that man bun
give me slow motion okay okay okay okay
okay it didn't
look I wouldn't 100% say that that was
on purpose it could
be but I wouldn't say yeah he's like
come come Sean o I swear there's two
100% he said
OA austrians when they're like
it's just like dude it's like saying
dude they're like
o nice nice head
shots oh we're almost an hour in
it's Lev is preparing shut up don't
scare my team don't scare my
team are we getting a card for
that liy coming
no uhoh oh that's him a he looks
what he looks like a dad I'm sure he has
kids
huh looks like a dad a nice he looks
really
nice
oh no no not my Bal
guy is a wife and kids yeah he looks
like
that he's so tall wow and
fit he's he's got really pretty
[Laughter]
eyes he's a t n n Tik tocker 38 years
what does he
do wait is my is my bald friend or there
I guess there's several no that's the
one the one that got a goal has to go
out no
no what do you did so well I love you
tra is that his name I
think strong
man Danel Danel what kind of name is
that oh that sounded uh Japanese for me
I thought the Japanese Dude is coming
in
Dano dance dance on the so football
field oh the one that one that broke his
nose oh [\h__\h] maybe he'll break Li's nose
[Music]
girl going
crazy I don't know him I don't know him
I mean he's he looks Charming
but y y I am not intimidated not at
all Dan so
hard okay is
Dano pretty good too
is that a good
switch I mean somebody had to be
switched
in
okay nice
block what
what immediately blocked by Danel who
just came in his the the first second he
already touches the ball the first
Contact of the ball is already Danel
okay he's he's so ready
a
respect he gets the little yellow
sash so that people respect him cuz he's
a
daddy don't tackle him he has kids and a
wife is that what that says
for the players's legs she would watch
it for their legs oh they do have nice
[Music]
legs whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what
does that
mean damn Dono got thick
legs he
fake he do be fake
whoa oh [\h__\h] wait oh oh we do get to Sho
it in okay nice I guess I was yellow H
yellow white at the
end never skips like
day ooh ooh our attempts a little bit
lower now 11 attempts on uh by the
Polish nine by us
yeah they're they're already more in
control than in the first half Polish
[Music]
people
e oh W okay yeah that's uh it he's
totally
[Music]
[Laughter]
overacting but yeah it did look
like an obvious foul but he's like ah
the pain I got stabbed in my
heart I'm going to have to amputate my
leg it already switched out he's
leaving no PR not the bom
guy switched with
okay those shoes have studs but they're
they're like gummy right like
plastic
okay oh what no what no
yes is
close what's that mean what what did
that flag
mean o
o offside oh
man damn
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] come on Austria we got to do it
come on come on this anime girl is
watching you with thousands of people
believing in you no why is everybody
getting hurt now what is
happening why is everybody getting hurt
oh
yellow card for Li
Li I said don't hurt him and what how
does he repay me how does he repay me by
hurting mom m
in oh but that doesn't that didn't even
look no okay if he says
so one more out
[Laughter]
oh they're cute ow ow ow bro are you
good bro
no what happened with my trown bald man
I love
him what
[Music]
happened yeah this is real Ted
lassle I am Ted lassle what happened can
you guys just
play can you guys just play stop
interrupting everything with your stupid
acting come
on come on you're wasting everybody's
time if this ends in
1 and
then if we win the next match we can
still proceed
right welcome to
football is this like a pattern that
happens often where in the second half
people
just continuously hurt each
other on purpose goal
go I'm watching I'm watching I'm
watching pil
push no way no way no way no way no
way oh was it yeah I'm so far I'm so far
it's coming it's coming I'm sure we're
getting closer to the goal
and let's [\h__\h] go last one's L SK
head 20 memberships
vamos yo and I was just talking about Y
what if it stays one one
leowski
defeated who I'm going to marry that guy
I'm going to marry
[Applause]
him oh my God I'm going to cry I'm going
to cry I'm going to cry
[Music]
I have tears in my
eyes I'm screaming so much I need to
drink some
[Music]
water ah let's [\h__\h]
go I'm going you know his name means
tree
Gardener oh man a good tree
Gardener
sheesh
H wiping my
tears I'm so happy
what are they singing I want to sing
with them can I get subtitles on they're
singing Come on B
no
yeah oh safe oh oh is something
happening no oh after the Discord no no
no no no don't tell
me they're not getting a go right okay
nice safe okay safe safe safe coming up
okay to no not tutu shut up chat
trolling oh thank
God okay I love this this gold dude what
do you call the gold dude again in
English um go goalkeeper
goalkeeper no no no go no tutu no [\h__\h]
no no you're trolling still right it
would be more crazy I think oh [\h__\h] you
goalie goalie goalkeeper okay hey yellow
what for our
captain what did my captain do Oh
Captain My Captain okay captain that was
not nice of you
captain captain
chill your hormones chill your
hormones my
man
Mard all like a fan on camera dressed up
as
moart right I'm seeing ah there he is a
what the [\h__\h] with
L
Vamp the
vamp that's that's a weird M side I
don't think they were wearing Le hosen
back in the
day Dano is a manace he seems to be yeah
oh okay I see why you said that he has
Chun don't follow
him wait did banso get a yellow card or
the leandos because to me it looked like
banso did something shitty
get do I get a slow motion or what no
slow
motion yeah Lea got one earlier but now
nobody that was a crazy stunt
though you can see on my timer how far
I'm back sadly because I'm not watching
on actual TV I'm watching in like an
Austrian stream is kind of far
behind I can see if I can get live TV
going for the next
one cuz I am paying for the
Austrian like Standard TV that everybody
has to pay for just because you have a
just because you have a a
TV I don't know if I need to do
something for that I I'll
check yeah yeah the TV tax I'm paying
the TV tax
so nice block
what you doing what are you doing
guys what you got there no I just took
a uh a napkin out of the quasa
bag oh oh wait are you good guys
what's
happening someone's on the floor and the
Polish guys are happy oh somebody's
getting switched on the Polish side bomb
gner
H bomgardner has tummy
H Austrian fans
happy a taking the time yeah yeah I can
see why you would want to stall
everything now
yet we have
what
15 like okay more like uh 17 minutes
left
right
[Music]
yeah
oh what why do they
wear why do you wear that guys teach me
why you wear I just saw the sports bra
what
what protect the Cho
B is it for the Chik
be nah how does that protect the chu be
performance tracker oh is there like a
ah tracking devisor okay okay there's
something attached at the in the back of
the shirt
right okay so it's not chikui protection
close what whoa who who damn close it's
okay we don't need another goal unless
they get another goal we'll see we'll
see what's happening something's close
great play thank you thank you I I'm I I
taught them oh oh yeah that was
pretty that could have gone
in that could could have gone in easily
so
close needed a bit more of an angle an
unexpected
angle was pretty straight so relatively
easy to block I
suppose
yeah a deserve the win thank you I mean
you know I like my polish
viewers look at
the girl's
like what's the Rhythm to
clap when you can't find the
Rhythm okay switch out slish and Kiki
Kiki Hulk on and shambles I love you too
I like you too I I I autocorrected what
you wrote to I love you too damn it
what what's with
peopleo oh oh Ki it sounded like Ki to
you it's CR
Kiki o again another attempt and a goal
but
unfortunately
slide
sh I like seeing those Swoosh
slides
F oh what
who's who's
shooting I is fun I I want to see
that oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh what what okay wait who's oh polish
got the yellow for the goaly like kind
of
obstructing
sabit free one possibly
hey oh oh we're getting a big chance
from the 11 M shooting okay cool cool
cool cool cool
cool ah oh actually I kind of feel bad
for the goalie like he was
just I I okay kind of feel like the
goalie got a kick in his [\h__\h]
chin and the goalie was in his in his
own territory protecting the ball no I
mean he
said he grabbed his leg I don't know he
was going for the ball but okay I'm I
shouldn't be complaining
go no way no way okay wait wait wait
wait wait I'm not there yet I'm not
there
yet no way no
way no wa wait wait
wait oh God hey no way I'm going to cry
I'm going to
cry he's still waiting oh he's going
he's going he's going
[Applause]
let's
[Music]
go what what
what
ohg ch ch get my get my let's go home
let's go home pack it
up pack it up
cooking with
[Laughter]
gas let's
go a man it's it's like you it's so hard
to to know which direction he's going to
go right he just went for the wrong one
and then he's like [\h__\h] the moment the
moment of regret is
instant I that one austring guy in the
audience closeup was cute because he is
like cheering with his tongue touching
like almost his
nose I'm sorry Poland I'm so sorry I
love you okay I love you anyway oh the
child
a
a being golden a penalty that is like
the highest pressure man [\h__\h]
that no sorry this is football
[Music]
this
is me talking in Austrian
dialect today is the day today is the
[\h__\h]
day levandowski once scored five goals
in a row oh damn sheh was that in his
prime or is was it
recently whoa whoa what whoa what's
happening
chat a bit ex
excited in his
[Music]
prime damn damn damn we're going hard
austrey I'm so sorry I I didn't know you
got so good at football over these past
years I'm I'm I'm going to I'm I'm I'm
ready to marry you all
I'm
ready I'm
ready let's
marry and we want to marry the entire
team
damn
damn I'm joking how could I how could I
marry them
AUST football team sponsored by KY we
should we should
man we can give him some free kfp Fried
Chicken buckets after this
for
celebration we can sponsor their lunch
or dinner whatever they
want R paid by
kfp a man I feel bad for
the you know when you when you s into
something and then you
lose sad sad
day I mean I still have a chance
although in 10 minutes 8 minutes
[Music]
actually a miracle would have to happen
honestly
but it's not
impossible yeah sorry the commentator
said
something that I that I feel like is
vibing with
me this this
goal is is affecting the Polish team
seems what goal they got a [\h__\h] go no
way no way no way what he we got to go
we close okay bro bro chat no
wait oh close
okay
guys why you giving me
confused confusing Vibes but I suppose
when it's not everybody saying the same
thing that means that it didn't
happen
H nice try
we P fight till the
end I respect that I
respect but we protect and we attack but
we also respect oh
oopsy could not process the ball he says
in
German true true I'm not processing in
much
either how long is the delay look at
look at my
timer I'm like 20 seconds behind of most
of people most of the people seems like
it so close whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa po Poland almost got a
goal seems like it's going that
direction
good nice safe nice safe that wasn't
that
close no no whoa whoa
whoa you guys still reacting to what
just happened I guess wait I guess it's
still coming what are you reacting
to what's coming
now oh yeah probably probably
ah okay that one okay that one dud it's
okay we don't need any more gos they're
still going for it so hard damn
Austria damn that's what you were
reacting
to
really really very very I don't know
horizontal very
sideways that's a danger zone right
there going past the
goalie going for the very Corner very
sideways could have worked super close
I'll count
it
she great play I can't believe it's
already
ending somehow for some reason I
expected I would be sitting here for 30
for for three hours I don't know how
that would have we can read super chats
though we can read them super Jets I
guess why did I think this would be 3
hours I know it's not I didn't I cannot
calculate how much 90 minutes is
apparently what's with American football
Oh
Oh you mean when you say American
football you don't mean soccer happening
in America you mean the sport American
football
right what that goes for three hours
see that's so so confusing the fact that
you have a sport there that's called
American football that is a completely
different
sport what's hand
egg what a lots of ants oh in between
what's the actual T actual time that
they played in oh oh he touched it with
his hand
bro Reach for the Stars not for the ball
my
[Laughter]
friend hand egg
hand egg hand egg what's that mean are
you saying he touched his hand why are
you saying egg about an
hour they only play an hour and it's two
hours of ads what the
[\h__\h] ah it looks like an
egg wait why is it called football most
of the time they carry it with their
hands why is it called football oh you
saying hand is like an alternative
name H that sounds kind of lame though
yeah exactly nobody
knows correct name is hand egg I see I
see I see I see I see where okay I see
where you're coming
from that's
cute that's very cute although it's not
really egg shaped to be honest is there
any food that's shaped like
that cuz egg is different egg is
different and you guys know
that sometimes they kick yeah sometimes
but mostly they hold it
like like they just robbed the bank and
running for their life with the
bag mostly they hold it and
run man that would be chaos like me
watching a hand Egg Match cuz I I
wouldn't know anything I don't think
I've ever
watched
anything American football related ever
in my
life I would have no idea what's going
on although maybe it's easy to to get
into it who knows football
is soccer in that case is easy to
understand pretty easy pretty
simple I guess they gave up wait it's
yeah it's only one minute left right oh
man so
sad I'm sad for them and for the fact
fact that it's already
over I want to watch
more that video
footage wait this looks almost like it's
from a game sometimes it looks like it's
straight from a game like video
characters doesn't even look like real
people 4 minute extra time I thought
that was no extra time
when they when they give time like this
in a case like this in a situation like
this is it just because there were like
a lot of interruptions of like yellow
cards and so many you know and then they
calculated and they're like ah you know
what we'll give them like four minutes
because there was like a lot of weird oh
okay
a that's how they calculate they're not
like oh let's give Poland a little bit
more you know time to to get a
goal okay so it's like that France Got 9
minutes
damn in nine minutes you can get a goal
for sure four is rough especially if
Austria is stalling cuz four minutes you
can kind of try to just
stall Go full defense but you don't even
have have to go full defense when it's
one vers one free you don't want to let
your guard down completely cuz then of
course something can happen but just
play like you've been playing until now
and then you're
good there's penalty for stalling too
much it's just got to make it
unnoticeable park the
bus there's another game after this yeah
but I'm only watching Austria matches
oh there's a sunset right now you can't
see it but they are talking about
it sun is coming out to say
goodbye yeah next match is next
week Austria versus Netherlands on
Tuesday we're going to watch it too it
will be I think at the same
time I'm excited
we're going to watch it I had so much
fun
today this is kind of different from
movie watch alongs
honestly this feels really
different you're going to root for
Netherlands that's okay I wonder I I
have heard nothing about how good they
are
but I haven't heard that they're like
super super super whoop oh
oh good
try good
try Neverland is good Nea orange
a
man' yeah I don't even think I talk this
much in movie watchs cuz that there's
way more dialogue that I don't want to
talk over right I keep on talking over
the
commentators cuz like what I am the
commentator
I don't really talk in movie watch Longs
not this much it's so hype so many
emotions nevland has the best defenders
oo will be
hard it's okay even if we lose I I'm
just happy for one win
honestly I'm happy for this one win but
we could do it still we could do
it if you get them on a good
day they're going to kick your ass well
on their good day if you get them on a
bad day they become the biggest chokers
it do be like that
n GG I still have uh 15 seconds
oh man oh I see the the light on the
field is giving me Sunset Vibes
a it's beautiful over
GG
y I still one fre a [\h__\h] one
[Music]
free oh my God
damn oh I'm sorry Poland they they look
sad are they out or do they still have
another
chance did they how many matches did
they have so far is it their second the
first the third for
Poland I'm from Austria oh they're
playing second second loss oh okay
they're done but they still got to play
the next one but they have no
like nothing really to
lose oh I see even from afar I see them
going like this like the
audience arm and
arm they're swaying
it's an popular Austrian song but I
actually don't know it but they sing I
am from
Austria I've heard it before but I don't
really I don't really care about
[Music]
it
oh I hope know that this anime girl was
supporting them yeah you're looking at
the audience but you do you know about
this vtuber girl do you
know oh so
happy he's like C oh he's like me oh
he's like me for real for
[Music]
real
oh they couldn't have done it without me
so true so true it's the power of
anime I'm going to give him this power
in the next match
too Austria you're the best You're the
Best [\h__\h] The
[Music]
Rest oh love
them I'm so new to this but I'm so proud
oh man the dad he's bringing the milk
back home for sure today he's coming
back with
milk a it's him again the they show the
same audience guy it's okay to cry man
it's okay to
cry because you're crying especially
you're not even I mean it's it's okay to
cry anytime but he's not crying from
sadness he's crying from emotions
[Music]
happiness it's okay to cry it's
okay sorry Daddy
sorry
leevy I keep on showing
him good job neighbors thanks
bro hey
Austria so many Austrian
Flags it's
beautiful why do they all know the
lyrics I can't even hear the music
properly
I need to learn the song for next time
we win just prepare it just in
case oh cute print out it's like a you
know how they have cardboard cutouts
from animal girls in the whole life
world well here they have cardboard cut
out of the
trophies wow oh look at the
Sun so you
wow
okay I don't know if I should continue
watching this they're probably going to
do some nice
review let me listen to them a little
bit
a yeah he's saying if you lose the first
one you you're so under pressure in the
second one they didn't it didn't feel
like they
were and I don't think they had a reason
to be because they may have lost the
France match
but a cute group picture they may have
lost it but it didn't feel like a um
like really bad loss it didn't seem like
a like a desperate situation like they
definitely didn't play badly and didn't
watch it but that's what I heard
so I didn't think it would be really
impressed I didn't they didn't look like
it it's a time of Frozen yeah I stopped
it because it's
over yeah it was uh was a was an okay
loss you didn't take
any goals from the other team you only
took your own
goal h
H PL in the group let's go Germany game
is there a Germany game after
this who's playing
next a is Germany who do you support uh
obviously Austria I'm
Austrian
a meeting your Oshi your soccer OSI in
the stadium France Netherlands oh the
one we lost against versus the one that
we're playing next
oh o
interesting I'd like to analyze
Netherlands to be honest but I'm going
to use this time to maybe I'll watch it
on the side while uh reading super chats
I won't be like paying 100%
attention but I'll just read super chats
and see when a goal happens I'll look
over and I'm like oh
okay oh it's in 1 hour okay then we can
chill a little bit
before it goes
downlands
orando ohom God no is talking man of the
match
[Music]
I noticed that
yeah
a
a sorry I'll translate in a
moment at least the things I remember
[Music]
a
a bat the guy who did a goal he's super
TI with his team uh what do you call
team leader
team
boss
CEO 5050 the the broken nose guy will
play with a mask sheesh I was just
joking when I said you can play with a
broken
nose coach coach yeah
coach
[Music]
[Laughter]
oo okay he said he said uh he thinks
that after the 20th minute they kind of
lost their energy I feel like that was
starting from the second half not quite
from the 20th minute but if he say so
then it was probably like
that and he uh says that uh yeah he he
was like he was told by his coach that
he was needed he was needed and so he
did his best and when he got the goal he
ran right to his coach gave him a hug 10
minutes in they score yeah the first
goal was really early and they were like
full
energy in the beginning
obviously they lost energy when I put up
a
timer no like yeah even with losing
energy look what look how well they
did yeah
yeah and then what did he say at the end
uh yeah that like he they just got a not
that they're at this situation they just
got to be in their top uh form for the
next one against the Neverland
and he thinks they can do it we can we
can bully them and beat them is what he
said they didn't let it get to them yeah
there was nothing to let it get to you
anyway
[Music]
so they smashed it I no
bully we're going to bully you we're
going to bully bully the [\h__\h] out of you
now Neverland
people yeah I'm so excited Netherlands
will be harder but I believe I have the
same feeling yeah even though I don't
really know how they play I don't know
it at all but with how strong Austria
has been even against France it'll be
interesting I really want to know who's
going to win if cuz like to me it might
I mean it's not like 100% it's like your
performance may be different on
different days but if if if France wins
this
then that means Neverland is weaker than
France so we almost won against France
so we didn't but then I think we can win
against
devance if it goes like
that so
you not necessarily but like you know
you
know come on come
on you you should cheer for France on
this one
H because if Neverland loses this one
well they're still going to play the
next one but I guess then if they lose
this one then Netherlands is not moving
forward
right and we need at least a tie okay if
if France wins the Netherlands match
then all we need against Netherlands is
a tie and if Netherlands wins the France
match do we we need to win win
right it doesn't really
matter a draw is
better yes yes yes okay what I said was
correct okay math math football math if
the Netherlands wins we could sell it
for a tie I thought if if France wins we
can sell it for a
tie got look at the point tables yeah
from behind the outb normally I don't
watch our team because they were so bad
that's what I was thinking
or that's what I was thinking
[Music]
bro okay I'm confused but uh what's the
reason super chats are off and there's
like no rule but like in with the uh
World
Championships last last year right f i f
a uh I can't say it
uh they it wasn't allowed so I didn't
stream that but um I thought there was
no rules for this one but I F just in
case a two years ago damn I thought just
in case better to keep it
[Music]
off it's okay Cruz I asked Jemma she was
like H it's fine probably fine there's
no rules in the first
place just
because they probably didn't think think
there's any need for any rules because
nobody's going to watch it but I'm
watching
it yeah it's okay current group points
France free Netherlands free Austria
free Poland zero what free you get what
how does that work we only got one win
we got three points for that so all of
those groups have one win by now out of
two matches so France also lost a match
let me see uh
with a
[Music]
ranking wait
what that's not the right one
[Music]
I free for win one for draw who did
France lose against oh no this one this
upcoming one is oh
okay their second one is coming up now
okay okay okay
okay uh I can't I can't find a real
ranking St
shaft okay now I see it
Poland Ah that's the
[Music]
go is the next
Netherlands Austria match also in Berlin
cuz they have several locations where
they're doing it right is the next one
also in
Berlin well different cities being named
but
uh are you going to watch any more
soccer after this I was thinking reading
super chats and then in 1 hour if I'm
still reading them probably I will be
uh we can have the next match running on
the
side okay um
all right I had so much fun today for
real I didn't oh my God I didn't expect
such a good
win damn I'm very confident now
Austria let's
[Music]
go that was fun we were we were getting
really
hyped it was really fun to watch review
thank you
this so
hype oh oh I should celebrate by taking
off my shirt
true I have the I actually have the
things
separately real soccer Vibes sorry uh
football
sorry wait wait sorry moving to the side
a little bit rejo
the waas I should paint the Austrian
flags on the
waas there they
are how does this
look bit too big maybe maybe too big
[Music]
yeah that's that's probably
fun oh this this good that's a good
one let's go Austria let's go good
job I'm your biggest fan girl your
biggest anime vtu fan girl
actually I have a little hat too but I
don't feel like wearing the hat today
maybe next time next
time I need a performance tracker
too where would you attach
that but then I need to wear that that
weird white
shirt isn't this
better what if one of the players was
kfp there is absolutely no no no way
although I can imagine Maybe some of
them actually like like
Naruto I could see I could see
that cuz like I feel like some sporty
guys they do like
anime like especially football players I
feel like they they might like anime
they give me this vibe that they might
like
anime yeah Dragon Ball and Naruto those
are like the football player animes
okay do you guys want me to turn on some
bgm or are you guys watching TV on the
side
still I'm going to read super
chats but you
know starting from is it starting from
the myth one block Minecraft the first
stream no be gy is fine oh wow okay
silence it's killing me
one block the first one
okay I'm watching you on the side what
what I'm your side chick am I'm your
side chick I should be your main
chick you're playing Fallout New Vegas
on the side
oh my friend actually you know my friend
that I told you about who was like
excitedly watching my Fallout streams
while normally they wouldn't watch
anything else
uh I got like a message like yesterday
asking me like oh where did you get the
dog again tell me cuz like I
think uh he said he he played Fallout
before Fallout New Vegas before but the
other games he finished but this one he
like started years ago and never
finished but um now he's like been
inspired because of me playing it that
he felt like oh I'm going to play it now
actually
how would he miss a dog oh I don't know
how you cannot remember where I found
the dog that was pretty obvious it was
in the ev's house so I told him I in the
El's house he's like oh okay thank you
thank
you he's going to go get the
dog cat
hair okay
all right then we'll read super chats
from myth one block Minecraft the first
stream there's not much space in the in
the in this short stream so maybe I'll
just leave it like this I'm not going to
put up a thumbnail but no bgm okay you
know what I'm going to put up a small
one cuz I also feel a little bit empty
right now if there's no bgm I want
something
something small how about some
how about one of
these
moart
oh more hard
playing isn't this beautiful
nice this is nice after football
music Austrian culture
time Austrian music for Austrian win
yeah moart my man the moart this is not
by the moart in a lat hosen that we saw
in the audience this is about a real
Mozart just so you
know nice now this is pretty calming I
like it oh oh
okay okay Jack 47 t shirt dck Hood with
two pinkies again about Gilma girls okay
uh season 3 episode 4 rebellious Lane
keeps a photo of her purple hair oh my
God the hair was like so fake like the
wig they used it looked so obviously
fake come on Gilma girls get a better
wig when you're pretending that someone
dyed their hair rebelliously that was a
really bad
wig uh uh I wonder if La has a photo we
would find shocking glad Rory stood up
to Jess's girlfriend with the bad store
service
ah yeah yeah yeah ah you know ah the the
yeah yeah the okay this one I actually
remember these
episodes uh that girl was a [\h__\h] and
laurelai stood up to the moms who didn't
like her young pregnancy oh yeah why why
so be why so be so judgmental
why next episode the new neighbor hi I'm
your new neighbor what am I ah that one
is it the one with the where he will ask
uh laurelai yeah to water the lawn and
that's what how she like actually ends
up inside of the house and she's like
what the [\h__\h] is this
place I think so Michael Michelle
Michelle having fun with that battle
laurite trying to find Auction man was
cute but he's not Luke so not meant to
be okay that part I don't remember but I
remembered a lot of the other stuff
those were some good episodes thank you
D I hope you're having
fun than for the super chatos very much
appreciated
yeah but you should send the Super Chat
to the gim girls
producers years ago so that they can buy
a better WG for
Lane Mal content thank you for the pink
Super Chat D woo woohoo I think there
will be some unusual names here maybe a
few ones like yours cuz it's myth collab
time thank you thank you thank you py D
Studio Rob thanks for the pinky T my
forever
yay thank you is this an NPC stream no
I'm reading super chats right now we're
done with soccer for football please
explain the offside rule to us again
before the next
game what it's
easy easy you just
um so if you're
[Music]
like the ball right you shoot you
dribble not dribble like if you you
dribble with your feet and then there's
another person and then maybe you're
like entangling with each other and
you're getting all tangled up this
doesn't have to be but it could be it
could be a situation you know and then
and then um one of you guys one of them
shoots it outside of the line the most
outside line the white line on the very
outside then whoever shot it out there
is bad bad bad bad guy bad guy so the
other person the other team gets to
shoot it back
inside easy that's
not what do you mean that's on
offside
oh um then H offside is the one
where where they're Camp to stop camping
by the
goal I cannot explain that I don't know
where that line
is offside is a player getting the ball
too early what wait that's also
different I don't [\h__\h] know I don't
need to know I don't need to know I
understood plenty of the game Congress
on the win boss yay thank
you there's an invisible line behind the
Defenders it's about the other team
passing the ball through
it I I don't know I don't know man
doesn't matter I don't need to
[Music]
know no attacker can be closer to the
defending goalie than a Defender when
passes come what no attacker can be
closer to the defending goalie than a
Defender when passes
come know what m
offside is an attacker receiving the
ball ahead of all Defenders but the
goalie what that's was the problem why
if it happens that's good the attacker
is strong Defenders got to defend better
offside is when the attacker is closer
to the gold than any other defend well
that's just I mean that's it is what it
is so why are Defenders why the the
defender is not keeping up you know why
are we blaming the why are we blaming
the attacker
[Laughter]
just defend better yeah come on hurry we
I'm not going to wait for you all day to
defend the goal if I'm ready to shoot a
goal then you got to be there or you're
not there if you're not there then
whatever to prevent camping
[Music]
ah oh okay I see back in the day when I
had uh uh physical education PE Sports
class in in my school days and we played
football sometimes which everybody hated
playing but um it was girls only
anyway pretty much
uh I think nobody followed that
rule there was always like one one
person staying behind sometimes me
around the goal just to be
[Music]
ready so that's not okay that makes a
lot of sense
yeah so what I did was
illegal yeah gotta Camp gotta Camp it's
not a real match anyway [\h__\h]
that jail we w we w we yellow card for
kahua yeah I'll take it I'll take
it
h um I know thanks for the pinky as well
hi Mama I love you very parasocial same
same thank you
iown just like me for real for real yo
thank you for the red super chat oh yo
how you doing right now huh H life Ian
myth girls are the love of my life ah
same same same
everybody's so so so parasocial in the
super
chats thank you
[Music]
y just like me for real for real Jack so
love oh don't worry it was not not uh
not much planning at all but I've been
putting so many hours into Minecraft
like even off stream
yesterday it's been
fun but setting up the collab it's self
was no effort no not much really no
problem and D Justin R mon zly D rude
rules thanks for the red super chat it's
my 26th birthday today I would really
like if one my one and only oie could
sing me Happy Birthday in German I hope
to see you in New York City hopefully
and in Atlanta for sure
oh I hope so too so you're trying to get
a ticket for our big concert huh gamb I
hope you'll get it
let me sing for
[Music]
you rud
rul thank you so much for your support
and happy 26th
birthday yeah
[Music]
birthday kiss included with that
birthday
song it's already a couple days ago but
I hope you had a lovely birthday and
celebrated yourself the way you deserve
it now the only thing misses is a
birthday gift that when you unpack it
reveals itself to be a ticket for our
concert am I
right that would be nice I'm sure
[Music]
I st big
look a small cookie bear thanks for the
pinky I'm so excited for whole my being
together for Minecraft feels like the
old times tears of joy same yeah it it
did feel kind of nostalgic but I I think
a lot of you guys have been saying oh
this feels nostalgic and this feels like
back in the day but I feel like it's
definitely very
um like the fact that we're playing
Minecraft is nostalgic but I do feel
like
our what's the
word we just we just way
more we know each other way better
obviously so yeah the dynamic I think is
better and interactions are better and
we're having you know we closer the
chemistry is better yeah I think
so I think back then I was feeling not
very relaxed when we uh had like
Minecraft collabs and stuff like
that especially that first one that I
was still so new to it so I think I
was always very like on the mode of I'm
streaming and I this is big big
important collab
and I have to I have to perform well so
to say but um yeah just thinking too
much about it and not really I wasn't in
my Prime yet and I wasn't in my best
form
[Music]
yet like just thinking too much about it
back
then definitely just thinking too much
much and I wasn't as
close with most of
them
yet as we know as we know me and goba
for example we only grew close like a
couple years
in not like we hated each other or
anything but like we just didn't really
have much of a connection and not really
much of a possibility to connect in the
first place yeah we haven't even met I
yeah yeah like it's different from
Japanese Jens and ID gens where they
have the opp opportunity to meet each
other IRL right
away the door race Arc yeah that that
definitely helped when we had like 3DW
stuff going on that was one of my
priorities
like trying I mean we met before that
right like for um when we were all in
America but in Japan for me my goal was
like to grow closer with
everybody I worked on
that if only I didn't get
[Music]
sick Mission succeeded
y
indeed yeah F than Cru than 47 D
smokeless powder
jum red zaros d v
than Mr V
thank space wonderful
than uh idle business regulation
director for D oh another polish viewer
I wonder if you're here
[Music]
today are you here today
let me see that chat maybe you already
left because it was a sad day who knows
I don't see you I don't see you in the
chat already unsubbed
unfollowed sobbing in his
bed
marinski thank you very much dou Jones
dunas D Idol business regulation D
orbital vagab D business regulation
Director D Jam
Dan D Sky dun dearest novelet novite dun
Patrick FB D thanks for the membership
GI thank you Papa Smurf D Canon b cannon
ball D princess Niche D cool skeleton d
D why is your name so hard for me to say
cool skeleton d red Zar D na CL pinky I
thought you were with her searching
forly through the themes but you were
Dusty thinking of the Wither going
hither Ander while T fuming through
there I see what she's
doing while fuming through their furus
under thunderous weather I'm not sorry
my th pronunciation
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
H there it
is there it
is there's a stream for
[Music]
wait let me play the other one for
now this is
310 from
Mozart such original
titles fre the W they're free they're
free they're very free
[Music]
regulation director brown brown brown
brown
hawk thank you and no clips Tiara
asalan
Tiara Tiara my girl Chad maximum thank
you wings CV thank you V faction thanks
for the pinky Ena K Kelly good
that's us that's us that's myth oh my
God you just said all our names that is
US indeed thanks for the pink Super Chat
I just realized one thing in my
head
[Music]
tonight cuz it's
Friday tonight is Debut right of two
girls at like 500 a.m. I think I think
I'll be sleeping
[Music]
Pro depends I think I might be
sleeping so it's herb and
giggy herb and
giggy for me it's 5:00 a.m. now it's
8:30 p.m.
[Music]
for
for anyone catch your interest so far
well obviously all of them all of
[Music]
them but it's so hard to say like I
don't think we've had many conversations
yet
uh I think I may maybe maybe I talked
the most to herbs so so
far yeah maybe but pretty
much not
[Music]
much herb herb BB me and Herb got a
little bit hyped about an anime that I
didn't think she would know but she knew
and I was like oh my God you watched it
and she's like yeah oh my God I love
that I'm
like
[Music]
what better be
no
no wonder what it was I think I think I
could say
but it was a
and we were going hype about the
songs I say
yes yeah I was like what
what no way Bas don't blit super
[Music]
based it's been a while for me
too
[Music]
first it is very old what is it about
it's it's a a harm
anime about a guy who gets isekaied into
like
a a magic school and there's this girl Z
they call her Z zero Louise because she
has zero skills she sucks she can't
control her magic and she becomes the
like everybody gets like um I'm actually
remembering this quite well everybody
gets like a what do you call it like a
pet U what's the actual word not not a
minion but they they all like eventually
you know have to summon themselves a pet
and some get like really cool stuff like
a familiar yeah one gets like a huge
Dragon you know and then what what does
she get she gets a [\h__\h] talking sword
basically no actually no she gets the
the guy yeah yeah no she gets the guy
and he gets the sword basically like a
talking weird ass old sword that
actually turns out to be pretty useful
but um she basically summons this human
and everybody's like what the [\h__\h] huh
you
suck and then that's the isite guy who
was like what the [\h__\h] where am I and
then
he yeah gandal yeah that's the sword
that's the
sword but he turns out to be relatively
useful with C with the sword and then
over the time of the anime more and more
the so to say supposedly useless Louise
becomes more and more strong
and
useful and then she's like really
abusive towards
him treats him like a dog and like whips
him and he's kind of crashing on someone
else while she's crushing on him though
while she treats him like [\h__\h] it's cute
it's cute she's very
T I can't watch your game did you win
BOS uh look above look above
me this sounds like something narissa
would like maybe maybe
yeah yeah she always gets those
roles
Kimia she always gets the tnd Rolls
three minus one is
two good
math yeah back in the day when this
anime was airing she was known as one of
the best T
is she was part of
the the the legendary T
[Music]
is yeah she had so many of those
roles ah Hanukah was same VA as Siesta
oh
really oh it for real
really oh
H I didn't realize that either but
there's generally I guess a lot of
overlap everywhere in anime popular
anime at least always go for the popular
voice
actresses wake me up when it's already
kick off you you tell me when it's kick
off Psy crusty thanks for the red super
chat from
Australia it's 2021 Yosi and her friends
are playing Minecraft so you wake up
early to catch the stream you sip some
coffee and prepare to Vibe times change
and people change but myth will always
hold a special place in my heart thanks
for ongoing for the ongoing event myth
love thank you
[Music]
a the routine still the same and myth
still the same but better I would say
better I really I really liked the way
we've been um vibing in these
collapse it was
fun we've been having lots of fun I did
uh suggest the date to everybody like a
new date for the finale uh CI already
has a stream up but it's not 100% set in
stone
yet I'm hoping that it will work out
though m
[Music]
Callie started like narissa does this
too I think uh started putting up
reservations like one week ahead of
time I don't know if is this really like
a smart thing to do for YouTube cuz I
personally feel like when I go through
my like subscription feed I want to see
like what's coming up so if you put the
stream if you put it up like a week
ahead of time or so
I'm not going to I'm going to forget
about it but if I go on my feet and I
see the stream that you're actually
doing like in one or two hours up at the
top you know then I'll be reminded of it
yeah I think it gets
buried if you look at it like that but
then again like I I think it's nice to
see everything at once when you go on
someone's Channel and but I think it's
confusing when I go on the girls'
channel who do this foko does it too
yeah
if I go on their stream on their Channel
page and I see like five different
reservations or so ready I'm like wait
wait to me it's
confusing and I don't think it's like
good to push all of your streams
down like if you put five up all at once
okay the most up the soonest one okay
but the what about the ones that are at
the end of the week they're going to be
buried and they W be at the top until
you're actually live streaming
[Music]
H I don't know I don't know must must
have some kind
of I mean I think fle just does it
because they plan ahead so much they
love planning ahead and they want to put
up like everything organized and all
that they prepare for everything so far
in advance so I get it that's just their
style I don't know why cie started doing
it though is there some upside to doing
it I don't
know did she say why she's doing it
Elsie Lin you must know if anyone knows
you
[Music]
know for their
convenience I wouldn't want to do like
create five six seven thumbnails in one
day and put it all up I don't want to do
that much in one
go don't have that time either
she hasn't said why but it's probably
because her recordings have gotten so
packed she doesn't have time to make
them one by
one kind like it's
less timec consuming if you just do one
quickly like a day before or so I don't
know well well you know everybody can do
it the way they want to I just don't
personally see the um the Merit in it so
I'm going to keep it the way I'm doing
it
[Music]
yeah just one day
ahead approximately not one day
sometimes 10 hours I do always try to
keep it at least like 10 hours before
the stream I want to have up the
reservation for the people who don't
look at my Twitter and don't look at my
weekly schedules at least you have the
reservation up 10 hours ahead so you can
see that but I don't want it to be too
early because if you subscribed to a lot
of people then it's going to get pushed
down so far so I think it's good you
know to have it relatively up high cuz I
from I just go by my own experience what
I see in my subscription feed what I pay
attention
to
mhm and then there's Amo who schedules
the stream 30 minutes before it goes
live for real for real like I mean I
haven't been able to watch his streams
because it's at the shittiest times for
me but I do see that she's she's like
absolutely no
no no plan absolute biggest gorilla
ever the I'm way she gives you no heads
up Freddy Min is
[Laughter]
generous I think yeah Ena sometimes puts
it up relatively close to the stream
time but generally it's not too bad not
as bad as
[Music]
a the way
yeah you got to hope that you get a
notification at that
point
[Music]
bro random puts it up anytime between a
day before and 10 minutes before Oh my
God Mama
Mia
inconsistent yeah Ena always streams at
the same time yeah it's not so bad when
you always stream at the same time but
am doesn't have a a fixed time does
she
[Music]
so I wonder if the new girls are going
to have one fixed time slot where they
start streaming or if they're going to
be more like several time
slots curious anyway CR thank you so
[Music]
much JH Gardina thanks for the pinky I
mean so many so many
Australians I guess the streaming time
wasn't too bad for you for once because
we started at midnight for me it was
like morning and then like into a little
bit before noon wasn't so bad for you
was
it the BTM is uh
Mozart it's just some Mozart piano no
music it's always so fun and wholesome
to see myth playing together thank you
for making this possible T you're
welcome yay the good thing is like it
comes with not just one stream right
it's like several
streams so this one collab brings us so
much myth content and usually when like
when we do collabs like what was it what
was that game
um uh the one that was one was playing
and I thought was boring
not
[Music]
Aus not no not
jackbox not P
World lethal company yeah lethal company
like stuff like that those collabs are
just pretty short normally like 1 to 2
hours maximum is what we normally go for
thank God I wouldn't want to play lethal
company more than 1 and 1 half hours
like so repetitive
[Music]
when you stream vertical add a sub
counter that's a strat you can get 3K
easy from one
stream I don't know I don't want to do
that like I've been seeing others do it
and it's like tempting but I don't want
to put it up
there but yeah back to topic lethal
company stuff like that is short those
collabs are short now this Minecraft
collab comes with longer times and
several
streams isn't that
nice so much myth with one game content
warning
I did not look into what exactly that
game is really and I think I kind of
missed
the the hype time of that game anyway so
I'm good with not playing it at least I
don't know maybe one day day if I'm
really desperate for finding a collab
game and I need one and have nothing
else you kind of died down right it's
basically evil company anyway then then
I don't need it I think basically same
thing Leal company was so boring man
maybe it's just because we didn't get to
the cool stuff I don't know but we
played for really long and it was so
lame I'm sorry I don't like it
are you still doing the 80s kind next
week did I say I was going to do it next
week didn't I just say it sometime soon
cuz I don't think I have
[Music]
time I said end of
month damn we're already next week is
already end of the
month damn don't think I can do
[Music]
it how is it lame though it feels lame
to me if you guys had fun that's cool
but like I I I just tried to fill it up
with banter but the game was very boring
to
[Laughter]
me anyway space waterfall danash the Bal
Eagle danash Jim Tracy danash Ryan C
danin MV Perry thanks for the red super
chat I'm in your walls I'm in your walls
I'm in your walls my Squad Squad okay
you're in all of our
walls how are you doing that thank you
for the r Super chatah thanks for the
support
appreciated
[Music]
dratic thank you I finished the Super
Chat from the first myth Minecraft
[Music]
stream okay next one is the second one
day
two day
[Music]
two ja for the S duck Hood with three
pinkies Mama Mia Mama Mia okay uh two
episodes okay luk and Lane not trusting
Jess about his new car is understandable
but Jess is trying to be good no one
sees it y Rory and laureli devil egged
Jess's car poor egg also Market owner D
de that de
deu how did they call him what Deuce was
it deu really dislikes the town loader
laner life be rough I don't remember
this I remember the car thing a little
bit
though next episode Paris and Jamie have
some chemistry
Ah that's a weird couple though any
couple with Paris is a weird couple to
me cute seeing Paris not know how to
deal with it yeah that's pretty cute yo
F9 dance contest wait what just happened
Dean just broke up with Rory over
Jess uh H [\h__\h] Dean man
he's he is like I don't
know really he's like a mix between like
one of those good guys but also the way
there's so much gel in his hair and he
wears those leather jackets like
something about him screams [\h__\h] boy
even though he's not really one he's he
doesn't act like one he's
just I don't like him he's a loser loser
[Music]
yeah I don't think
Jess I I prefer Jess's personality too
he just the problem with Jess is he
can't help but be
rebellious and piss people off even
though you can see with how he is around
Rory you can see he's a good guy and
he's like actually
like fun and and has some good
priorities and he's interested in like
books and stuff right so he's not that
rebellious in reality but something
about him he just wants to like piss off
like his his whole family and everybody
in the city the only person that he's
nice to is
[Music]
Rory will watch France versus
Netherlands I was thinking yeah a little
bit on the side is it starting in 7
minutes
huh maybe maybe maybe on the side
although I feel like I'll get super
distracted
uh maybe I shouldn't watch it damn it
I'm interested but maybe I shouldn't
watch it like on stream maybe I should
only watch it off stream like while
cooking my dinner or so I'm scared of
cooking though I smell the fish and I'll
see if it's if it smells okay I'm kind
of scared that the food is off
[Music]
up to you watch it watch it on
stream we'll tell you when there's a
goal but I want to see it well I guess
I'll get the
replay if it was fish and it's a lost
cause I don't know not
necessarily not
[Music]
necessarily there's so much Orange
Stadium
kfb am I having a concert or
what KY showing
up in
Berlin or is it the different
Studio because I guess how would you in
1 hour cleaning up clearing out and
cleaning up and filling it in
again it's not so realistic I guess they
might be in a different studio uh
Stadium oh okay they are in Li t oh
[Music]
lick that makes
sense I kind of want to go to one if
Austria gets into the next phase I want
to go to one of them I wonder how I
expensive tickets
are they're entering the field now damn
damn okay let me open up um
[Music]
um Let me let me mute my
music
uh while watching
match this is just extra okay this is
like
overtime extension DLC
uh you're watching in person in litic
hey y it's expensive and probably sold
out but what about the the matches that
are not decided yet because you don't
know who's going to be playing how can
you know how can you
already like have a ticket
oops myet on the
bench oal maybe he's coming in in a
little bit
[Music]
uh Netherlands is kind of long
Neverland
versus
bronze I don't know how to say that
name
okay a oh almost played the audio
without muting my desktop audio for you
guys
okay oh oh it's quite the hot orange
too
oh well that's a sick
Anthem is this the French
Anthem
Oh it sounded really epic now it's more
like
marching whoa that orange
but the orang is for Netherlands
right H what was better for me for me it
was better if Netherlands lose I
think don't really care though
personally are they
booing am I hearing
boo guys what the [\h__\h] don't Boo for the
anthem when the game hasn't even started
like what's wrong with
you no
respect okay now I got a root for
Neverland why did we hear that one so
clearly camera mic is popping
off a wow holy [\h__\h] the Orange is crazy
it's just like with KF see the orange
just like stands out
insanely I love it orange so
powerful I just want to get the um the
timer off at the right
moment a
ads let me make it look quiet it
too tweet out you're watching this game
I'm not really actively watching though
I don't want people to be mad because
I'm not paying
attention if being Neverland fans use
oos to they should start using
penlights no they have their own
penlights they have these
like things that I'm
carrying the the the the the air tubes
add so long I was ready to push the
button come
on push the
button wait should we should we make a
quick poll who you think who you think
is going to
win let's make a another poll start
to oh my chat I sent the poll but it's
like falling apart Let me
refresh
hello hey did the poll
work is it
there
[\h__\h] okay I got to redo add TI okay who
will win Netherlands France or Tai
Ty is such a cop
out okay it's about to
start whoa whoa there's really a lot
more orange here than
uh uh French colors whatever they're
wearing
blue even though both
are really close in terms of location
they could make their way there
France
blue France so stack their bench could
form another national
team
damn I will say I actually have no idea
I don't know how any of these teams play
so I can
only hope for what's more
beneficial so I'll this is pretty
5050 oh well no really cuz I have free
options
oh people think France will win
huh okay I will make a tweet actually is
it starting
no are they starting when are they
starting can I tweet can I tweet can I
tweet
watching next match Netherlands
versus France while reading super
chats
okay okay hype hype hype hypee
hype oh oh
it's about to
start France yeah France is really good
right okay St I'm glad that our match
with France is over but considering how
strong they are that means we're [\h__\h]
strong if we could hold up against them
pretty well they're already why are
these people man football fans generally
suck don't
they like they also are so well known
like whenever there's matches here I
always hear news not just here just
generally in Germany Austria and so on
that there's like Hooligans messing up
[\h__\h] leaving so much
trash it's
just I guess not oh I have it running
but I have it
um there it
is we always get Mis represent well of
course there's know you know chill
people but then there's shitty people
okay let me put on the side
oh W that was that was
close okay I'm watching on the side let
me it's too loud though a
little little bit
quieter big
delay can't help it
almost yeah almost one nil two minutes
into the game that would have been
sick can they stop being so shitty in
the audience but I'm guessing the the
players are used to it so they don't
really care right
hopefully
uh okay wait I'm going to start reading
this I already did start reading now let
me
continue since my is not playing I guess
well maybe he will still come in no he
could still or is it set but he's
staying on the
bench these colors look kind of nice
together the white blue with the
orange kind of
nice yeah maybe later if they feel like
they really need him
[Music]
they look like ice in uniform it's you
guys but in human
form I hope you play well
guys you're all now from the Netherlands
congratulations am human am I doing good
can't really tell so
far I want to like it look so far it
looks pretty
slow not very
aggressive right they're singing the one
that I only
know o o o o o Super T super
ho what are they seeing though what are
they replacing Germany
with this is already intense is it oh oh
oh they were running
towards uh which side is that right side
is
that shot
was that felt
so
Random I felt like hey here here's a
gift for you here's a super chat for you
enjoy is this
offside what's happening he's doing ah
Corner shot why why are we doing a
corner shop oh what was it even a corner
shot I don't know what this was speaking
of super chats um chat you will tell me
20 minutes early if there's a goal
coming
so let me know if something's exciting
exciting is
happening yeah uh happy birthday also to
Kaz
Kaz says duck Hood duck Hood telling me
about Kaz birthday happy birthday Kaz
and thanks for free P du
Hood thank
you Rion thanks for the red super chat I
want a chance to be red now you are not
random collusion you are red
collusion there you
[Music]
go
shees that's going to score but only go
if you say
so might
be o
o that Super Chat that spawned your joke
what what joke did I say I want a chance
to be right ah
because he wants to be red but uh he
because uh he wants to be he wants me to
read him but was a right Super Chat
so yeah yeah the pun I feel the pun I'm
feeling
it thank you random
collusion oh yeah then I said ah the
random colliding I said the joke out of
that yeah about Goomba I want to collide
randomly with
Goomba so now I remember properly
wonderful
golden scary
scis D oh this was when I was like dying
alone yeah that was rough I was hoping
to randomly Collide into goba because I
was all
alone being followed chased by all kinds
of
enemies youf mod thanks for the pinky
funny coincidence I saw I saw in an
electric store a creeper formed mini
fridge middle body and head was openable
oh cute made a pick of it found a very
funny posted later there was even a
fridge in a TNT P where did you find
that in an electronic
store where do they have that is there
an otaku electronics
store I only saw in a video
recently
um of someone like showing what they
bought on Amazon recently and one of the
things was like a Minecraft
torch looked really cute you can like
hold it like a
torch you know like you would use a
normal torch or you can attach it to the
wall as well kind of like diagonally
just like the torches in Minecraft that
looked
foul did I miss a
foul or is it still coming for me oh
that they were pushing it oh oh they're
all getting up
but that didn't look like too much
[Music]
happened oh wait no somebody's on the
ground so many hormones
oh okay I I don't know that was just
like they
were wrangling each other that's
it okay they're boring it's boring so
far a testosterone is what I mean yeah I
kept on trying to think of that
word
orc wings Dan vus Dan fun fact before
Mario 64 even came out Nintendo had an
event Booth where Charles Martin control
that Mario ah this one I feel like you
told me this information you or someone
else told me this like years ago months
ago ages
ago the fact that that was the first
YouTuber we talked about this
before who told me this you told me that
Adon is
damn fun fact rep
repetitive repeat
conversation
B level 26 hyperpop girly D oh you you
started wearing hoop earrings they do be
cute I don't have ear holes so I
generally don't wear wear any I can't
talk today um but I do think hoop
earrings are super
cute they can also super tacky depending
on your outfit and your makeup but if
you combine it in a cute way then it can
be super
cute which team are we cheering for I
don't know we're already 10 minutes in
shees Austria had a goal by now
already get on our
level we're on the next
level yo
I cheer for orange I should just cheer
for orange yeah CU just because it's
orange no I don't really I don't have
any bias
[Music]
here France winning make it easier for
Austria to go for okay now France has to
win then but I don't like how the fans
are acting so far
French fans are kind of
op
op let me ask dict CC how to pronounce
up up
up
up up it sounds funny the more I say it
sounds better when other people say
it a ab ab
ab
ab cuz I was saying like up it's too
tooy
too I can't think of
words it's got to be more sof or like
ABY I'm trying to hard to say the
word if you like soccer you should play
Ina 11 it's a socer
CH well I know some of the songs thanks
to my favorite Idol group singing their
songs
[Music]
I even know this the the dance the
choreography France had a good chance
just now okay let me see
20 seconds late
W oh France fumbled something bottled
that how did he [\h__\h] that up okay okay
okay okay okay okay pass pass oh running
for it running for the ball from the
side shoot and pass and
ooh blocked it with his head are they
going in one more time or is that the
fumble that you meant oh they're going
in again they kind of still there oh oh
how did you
fumble he feels it the way he put his
hands on his face like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh yeah that's a he like stumbled over
his feet he really
fbl he's like so
[Music]
embarrassed oh oh oh oh what no way a
triple fumble
oh baby a
triple was it the same dude twice
seven
[Music]
chman it was it was the same guy twice I
just saw the
repeat he thought he could redeem
himself oh man that's sad that's uh yeah
he tried it got to him I think it got to
him spilling a
spaghetti
damn was kind of a triple
fumble but the other two the the last
two were so fumbled so hard that you
could forget about the first chance was
kind of free
chances damn griezman that's a German
name wa depends on how they write it
you guys all write it differently in the
chat it sounds kind of
German is he
German he won't hear the end of
it that was funny that was funny okay
continuing
FR
V also recommending
NCR ISO dope
dun Jerry dun yata strike dun Penny Vu D
TZ KK
Dun don't worry she was very aware of
her own stream coming up uh cam trail
mix than spank H thanks for the red
super chat I love the series fun and
educational you guys are my f my my
seven favorite grain vtubers
why did we get green why did we become
green and
seven oh something just happened kind
of
oh ooh Neverland almost scored a goal
there
almost this is about narusa in cin
ah but why seven though that's more than
just color blind
spanheim spanheim can't even
count where is no not fre for where's
six and
seven cuz 789
if we include the actual greenan members
oh it would told up is that really how
you how spanking I'm was trying to what
what you were trying to
say it's not really why why the seven is
seven I I won't know for sure until
there's clarification thank you though
speaking high thank you too bad that so
many people seem to be affected by color
blindness it's
dire times man why are our eyes so
[\h__\h]
up now you guys didn't know yet about
Justice you didn't know I
knew I've
known you guys remember that um
time fairly recently like maybe it was
actually just a week ago uh roughly a
week one of the and a half weeks ago
maybe where I said I have to get up for
this meeting it was like what time was
it what time was it 5 or
so really shitty time and then I stayed
up like two so long I told you guys that
my meeting was over like 2 hours later
that was first meeting of them I mean
the meeting was like only an hour or so
but then whoever wanted to stay and talk
more of them stayed and most of us
stayed for quite a while to talk more
with them cuz we were I feel like you
always want to you always want to when
the new girls are in same with Advent
and so on like we just want to you know
look cool and be the good senis who are
there to welcome
them and answer all their questions but
actually I was asking so many questions
like it was basically us as asking
questions and them answering but I feel
like um I I definitely asked like 80% of
the
questions
yeah I was like what kind of games do
you like to play what times are you
planning to
stream uh stuff like
that okay yeah is coming with the
catalog for real for real I'm asking the
good questions the best questions only
the best of the best oh what's happening
what's happening nothing nothing
happening uh yeah nothing they went for
it and then they went back it seems like
at least a little bit more balanced in
terms of uh ball possession
here I don't see one color mainly
carrying the ball so
far just both and it's pretty slow
[Music]
yeah they're they're so evenly matched
they can't really break each other's
defenses yeah I guess
so that's always rough yeah when the
teams are so close and their play style
and skill I would say I would say like
you know all teams that up in a
championship like this are on high skill
level obviously I feel like it's more
about the play style than the
[Music]
skill Poland versus Austra had more
action way more I mean the early goal 9
Minutes in definitely helped for the
hype and stressed out Poland so that's
why we had a lot of
action Nance probably has a
shot is he really that strong whoa whoa
whoa whoa
whoa yeah anyway continuing uh where was
I
[Music]
ah AK sf2
D thank you you're
welcome thank you
also the W on the man GD dun Epsilon D I
want to thank you k for always streaming
when you do been working very strange
hours and you keep my sanity up much
love me too I'm also been working
strange
hours stranger than ever thank you thank
you you know every time I go to the
store these
days like really much later than usual
to get a quasa and and even before I get
the quo I try my best to not
look like to not have my face literally
say I just woke up I think my face and
my voice already looks pretty awake but
somehow they can
tell I walk in and they're like ah good
morning at like 5:00 p.m. and I'm like
oh how the F how well and then I feel
like I have to defend myself
I said I had a I had a night
shift they can always sell how do they
know how do they know ew yesterday I
even put on some concealer on my eye
bags because yesterday was really
crazy holy [\h__\h] my eyebags they were
so apparent apparently there
very very dark and you could see the
line where they end
clearly and they were kind of like a
puffy
H maybe don't wear it's not pajamas it's
tie
pants sometimes I didn't even wear tie
pants and they still
know they always know
I always [\h__\h]
know they kind of look like pajamas
they're just super comfy I wear them all
the time now even if I didn't just wake
up I'm wearing them constantly they're
my best my favorite pants
now the elephant pants yeah cuz I have
like three different ones now so I'm
like constantly wearing
them nothing else
yeah no one comes in at late for a qu if
they didn't just wake up yeah yeah for
sure like but they already know before I
even make my decision on what to buy so
you cannot judge by the by my purchase
by my choice of pastry if you don't know
yet but they're already like good
morning I'm like oh how did you
[Music]
know h yes I'm only wearing the tie
pants nothing else you know what I
[Music]
mean 25 minutes
in no
[Music]
action I want to France lose the match
well for Austria it's better if France
wins but either way as long as Austria
wins the next match we we're fine if we
if France wins if France wins then all
we need is a
tie oh ball it is pretty 50/50 with
France having it
57% but the ball uh the attempt and all
that are also pretty much the same so
far I just saw it pop up on the
screen oh something's happening did
they
[Music]
oh okay he just shot it outside
the Netherlands were going for it right
yeah this is France defending I'm still
not sure which side is
which ow ow ow ow ow out the way he
landed [\h__\h] his
arm he's got like twin tails that
guy he's got twin tails on uh on his
head k
cute don't worry K I'm from Poland I can
guarantee we won't even get one
win that the neverland side is the one
with all the orang yeah yeah I know but
like even like when something's
happening I'm not sure like who's
defending what right
now Co there is that his name
yeah Poland is basically out right
that's maybe another reason why they
were super
sad they're super sad super sad but wait
a minute while I make you
[Music]
make super super
sad actually super shy I'm super shy
have you listen to Supernatural um um I
think wait I think I did I I I I heard
randomly I wasn't even I wanted to I saw
that they released something new but I
wasn't ready when I saw that and then I
heard their new song somewhere else um
it was Japanese I'm like what the [\h__\h]
they put out a Japanese
song what what what what the
[\h__\h] but I think they released like two
songs or
so that was close
oh
yeah I'm seeing the
repeats that was really
close yeah right now and Supernatural I
forgot which one was the Japanese
one who France just throwing
it why did your jersey go I celebrated I
had to celebrate cuz I won I won
myy this is the right way to celebrate
for a football
[Music]
fan let's go
okay let me continue I'm almost done
with these
um yeah EPS D looking for the top D and
endless thank you for the red super chat
New Zealand let's go thanks for
organizing the one block server K I
appreciate the effort put into events
like this loving the new outfit too it's
somehow loud and Casual at the same time
loud yeah the colors
maybe but it do have it do be having a
little bit of a casual Vibe which I
think is very useful it's both sporty
and Casual at the same time so very
versatile right thank you thank you
thank you so much
endless thank
you yeah I've been discussing about
accessories
and I
hope I hope they'll let me do the the
things I want to do but we'll have to
wait until till my anniversary for me to
reveal them sadly it'll take a while but
time will pass so fast holy [\h__\h] like
I've I've been getting my schedules for
like dance practices and
[Music]
stuff like I'm going to Japan pretty
soon for a really short trip that might
be pretty packed um my my birthday
happens to be during that too
and I have to stream from
Japan I'm trying to squeeze in like uh
two birthday streams and one normal
stream on the birthday weekend um Friday
Saturday
Sunday but besides that I don't know
when else I can stream I'm I'm I've been
asking to reserve the studio for some
streaming time as well but cannot
guarantee that there will be that much
streaming July August is July especially
July for August like there's a lot to do
but I'll have a a streaming setup I
think oh something happened yellow card
well yeah I'll have a streaming setup
and I'll be there for a longer time the
first trip is one week with lots of
packed things so that's a bit stressful
and then I'm going on some other trips
uh uh besides that too but the second
trip is longer so everything's a bit
more spaced out and I think think I can
stream somewhat
regularly they were pulling each other a
why were they pulling shirts again God
damn it
stop but that's also like one of the
reasons why I'm going so hard right now
on streaming cuz next week I'll be gone
for like half of the
week
sorry
sorry which is one of the reasons why I
should do a so that I can rebroadcast it
on one of days but
yeah sorry but hey I'm going really hard
now you I know a lot of you guys still
need to catch up on bods
too there's so much I've streamed so
much this week last
week you got shorts prepared too not
really I mean I have one from Elsie Lain
right I want to take one more um dance
video at least because the trackers are
loading again I don't know where the
difference is but suddenly they're all
loading suddenly I still have a coupon
coupon
[Music]
too I'll think of something
maybe
H does it have to be a short or can it
be a proper clip
can be
e maybe a myth
Minecraft highlight moments
compilation but that's a lot to go
through so you can say no don't worry
cuz that's that's a lot of content to go
through sorry you don't have
to no I it should be a short short not
short one not not an hour like 10
minutes maximum but yeah it's more like
cow carrots feeli of experience I know
expertise how's been kind of busy
though kind of
busy I wonder what else could be
[Music]
good I mean I would
say like Austria gold comp ation but you
can't show the game footage at the
game sock football footage if it's on my
channel then no no no can't do that
sadly Fallout moments yeah you could do
something with Fallout perhaps but
[Music]
or I can't think of anything right
now compilation of making fun of the
Legion oh
[Music]
oh there goes the
ball orange was going for
it t I was going to suggest iron farm um
creation process but I didn't stream me
finishing it so
H I spent quite a few hours on it off
stream
while also trying to fix like a lot of
other things and finish a lot of other
things like the the
bookcases at the bookshelves I
mean it was definitely a whole stream
Warth
yeah oh oh ooh nice catch
France was a bit too simple of a shot it
it needed to be a bit more intricate my
dear Netherlands
friend it needs more it needs to be a
more complex shot you
know that was very
predictable easy to
catch too friendly yeah it looked like a
pass oh that was that was something O
Let's see slow
motion well
he definitely stepped right into it and
his he it looks like his Cal touched his
peeee C to PP contact alarm alarm we
we we
we he hit the other kind of ball yeah
going for the wrong balls man too many
balls on the field too many balls on the
failed we need to get rid of these balls
there's too many confusion
confusion he oo that's a fire shot
wow oh he's so mad he's so
angry those really far big tall shots
are impressive I wish I could shoot a
ball like that
[Music]
replace the ball with a hornet
nest what a flop that's a flop what
flop okay we're going for it we're
France is going a France was
tackled free kick for France oh what
what
what okay I just saw in slow motion
that's kind of
crazy oh you call that move a flop
really the way he like kicked out his
leg
backwards never touched
him yeah I guess but like holy [\h__\h] that
intention was
there when you fake it hard to get
a what to get Oh you mean Oh you mean he
faked it but I mean the move even if he
wasn't affected by it much the move was
[\h__\h] never seen that before that kick
backwards okay
yeah if there was a goal you guys would
told
me okay continuing oh wait I was
finished thank you endless M was
finished heyo already two streams done
I'm pretty productive
heyo next Minecraft stream Day free day
free day free day free day
free are you ready for Day
free productive and we're only 40
minutes into the game only actually
that's almost half time
y
[Music]
hum oh he
fell what
orange
fouled
what what it looked more like orange God
fouled to me at least
orange kicked White's
foot
uh from behind cuz like white came in
front of orange sorry I'm just going to
say colors now my brain is too slow to
process
it like he just like scooched in front
of him came in there and then
it's like what you what you it's like me
walking on the sidewalk and then
somebody trying to pass me but trying to
pass me without taking the necessary
space in between us and like kind of
trying to Slow Me Down by doing that and
I'm like what the [\h__\h] I'm going to step
on your foot because I'm not going to
slow down for
you you
know they're boo so hard oh my God can
you not like you're ruining the
mood I don't even know who they're
booing right now but it's probably the
French booing Neverland
right
bro piece of [\h__\h] who threw
that it was the other way around okay
I'm so confused everyone booing the ref
oh they're they're ah at the throw of
the the drink was also more like towards
the
referee the Dutch are throwing stuff at
the FR come on no that's so shitty why
are these people so the the atmosphere
must be [\h__\h] like I feel like there
might be fights starting once they leave
the
stadium outside of it when people are
trying to go home feel like they might
like [\h__\h] each other
up too much passion too much passion
careful careful football fans
too much
passion mental physical passion you need
more mental you need to like balance it
out you can't have too much passion you
need physical and you need mental mental
very important to balance out the physik
Karu and the
passion you can't just go with one of
them never thought about it that way but
that's really a good balance
wait until you see our crowds whoa who
are your crowds leptic people better
stay safe at home for real like I would
be
scared seems like a shitty
atmosphere nice try with the head shot
though what do you call head shot in
this in English properly like in German
we just say copes or klow whatever
headers okay I I'll probably continue
saying head
shot that's it that's
[Music]
it
damn there was no booing between Poland
and
Austria not not what I heard not from
what I heard isn't that nice we're so
disciplined all of us respect to
Poland respect to
Austria okay going to read super chats
from dayre
Minecraft here we go here we
go yeah this is a good atmosphere and
more chill than
most that Thro is nothing someone to
shoot to the sky in my country what with
a
gun the
[\h__\h] that is why it's better to watch a
game on live stream so true or like in
one of those like I don't know like
restaurants or whatever like outdoor TV
with a big
screen where it's usually also just like
your own country men so there's nothing
really to fight each other about those
those look really really
fun outdoor in a
restaurant having a nice
dinner nice cocktails
mocktails I did not expect that you
didn't Austria
way football games in South America
they're usually even Wilder
[Music]
scary this has been a pretty dull first
half right I thought maybe it's because
I'm not paying 100% attention but it
feels super
boring super boring I guess I got to
stop in a
moment oh they're getting one
minute one minute sports bras better
than sports
bars for real yeah I would agree with
that sports bras
cute this is way less
[Laughter]
exciting maybe also because it's not my
country so I don't really care much but
still thank you Austria and Poland for
giving us a good
show might not just want to get the
timer right when I stop it although I
could reset it my way the way I wanted
anyway but
[Music]
still that pass was so lifeless cuz they
know it's just a few seconds oh because
I guess depending on who has the ball in
the last second that that way we'll be
decided who gets the kickoff next when
they restart
right oh he actually looked motivated
the guy who had the ball at the very
end no no the opposite oh
okay then why did they I guess they were
scared even in that last moment to not
protect their
there
[Music]
go okay now we have 15 minutes to focus
on the real
deal
okay Hal time we
we half time half time they were just
playing defensive they were just they're
just chilling uh D thanks for the two
pinkies season 3 episode 8 r rightfully
decided Rory rightfully ticked off at
Richard for the surprise Yale interview
ah that one mhm cuz she was going for
what was it called again not Yale um
what the other one called again uh
really famous I should know Yale and
Harvard Harvard Harvard it was uh it
went well but she wanted to prepare her
best stuff we appreciate you always
wanted to show us your best stuff it's a
lot of work but always appreciate it oh
thank you a that was a nice way to make
it about
me cat Kirk beat up human Kirk almost
the whole episode wait what the [\h__\h] cat
Kirk was he cosplaying for like a cat's
musical or
what wait what oh was there a cat called
Kirk did did Patty was it Patty no not
Patty the other um chunkier women did
they have a cat called Kirk I'm confused
I don't know anym about this one
Thanksgiving tofu turkey by Mrs Kim
tofu I don't like tofu have you ever had
to pretend to like a food not to offend
someone or does w just politely
decline I normally I I maybe I like try
to not be too much like oh this is
absolutely disgusting but at least like
I won't say I like it but I'll at least
be like oh yeah not my thing
H and I'm pretty clear about me
generally not liking a lot of
things I say that to people when I go
eat with them I'm like yeah I don't like
I probably don't like a lot I I look
very very very closely at the menu to
see if there's something in there that I
don't like and then usually I don't go
for
it so I haven't even had that many
moments like that not many
yeah I I don't remember having to do
that
much a moment of a hem where I had to do
that I don't even think so like it's
also not like they cook for me normally
normally we just go out for dinner
there's not really many situations where
one cooks for
another and when we go out for dinner
like usually we go for some cool places
in Japan it's often yakin niku and you
can't go wrong with yakin
niku for Yakiniku the only situation we
will run into sometimes is
like like there's like raw meat to be
eaten like that's why I always I'm like
I don't want to order a course I want to
order tping like single items from the
menu but the other members often they
want to go for a course and that's how
we get ourselves into situations where
there's stuff that some of us will not
want to eat and I can see that coming I
know it will
happen
so no
back to 45
okay
CC wasn't there a restaurant you went
with Cali where you didn't want fish but
almost everything was yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I remember
that but the food that I got in yet was
I think really
good oh and she enjoyed it a lot
too but I just had to like
that one problem was when me and Cali
were in Hokkaido and we were in this
onen on in the countryside and yeah that
one also only had Seafood but they
couldn't really replace it with anything
that I liked either all all the other
stuff was also
like there's a lot of so to say weird
food weird for a
European I barely ate that night that
dinner was I barely had anything
really yeah didn't like it they had so
many different courses like uh levels of
the course but most of it was BL for me
sadly it was very
traditional yeah often they'll have like
Western
influence uh even in Japanese
restaurants but this was very very
Japanese and then very Japanese and also
very
seafood and yeah like sticky stuff not
Nat but like other sticky
stuff and tofu and
stuff not my kind of
food but Cy liked it so I was just I was
letting her eat more so that maybe my
plates wouldn't look
as no filed like that I left that much
over but I mean she couldn't have eaten
all of it they also served like so much
like huge platters of endless amounts of
seafood I'm like how are we going to eat
this with two people
anyway not all your kind of food
exactly I don't like seafood either
yeah a lot of seafood haters here I like
normal fish grilled like any kind of
normal fish I even will eat eel because
that's pretty much normal fish I love
eel actually if it's cooked grilled
baked
whatever but the moment we step into
like crab octopus shrimp even shrimps
I'm sorry kind of territory that's
that's when I'm like I'm out I'm
out also you know those really really
really really really really really
really tiny fish that when you order
them you get like a mountain of them
because you know it's like tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny fish that are like
smaller than your or maybe as small as
your like half of your
finger I don't know are they sardines
they're really tiny anyway and they like
I had that before in like
grease and I regreted my choice I didn't
like it in the
end it kind of weird white fish yeah I
think I'm thinking of white
fish M white bait yeah I think
so congrats on your nation winning Yoo
let's go thank
[Music]
you super naturally salty ones oh are
they naturally salty they might have
been so yeah but I don't know do you
even would you even consider that
Seafood when I talk about Seafood I
really mean all those things that have
like a weird shell or
something anything with super long legs
or several sets of
eyes or some claws I just want a normal
fish a sh Shell Shell Shell shellfish
mostly yeah Crustaceans but also I mean
octopus is not a
shellfish sh
Shish
streaming just a bot of it oh
God [\h__\h] Ro
fish
man okay let me let me continue
reading thank you du
hood and spank time thanks for the red
super chat your new outfit so jiggly so
bouncy I'm in love with your eyebrows
yeah yeah I'm sure you
are no thank you very much I'm really
happy with my new outfit too I'm so
happy everybody likes it also thank you
for 40 [\h__\h] memberships in total holy
[\h__\h] thank you Lou
Moonlight he
faces Tommy HK
vulu D oh I've heard of the show but I
never watched it idle business
regulation director
d
f for the pinky
how
you oh boob milk please is what that
says I can actually translate that let's
go
come j SW D spanking
D moss bear comes on for the pink Super
Chat frogy wa merch is coming tomorrow
oh my God wait I didn't realize that you
guys didn't have it yet but it's like
coming up to everybody now anybody who
received froggy waa merch
already is it time
already I knew I should have bought it
of course you should have I didn't hear
about shipping yet read more oh
oh uh because whenever I get bored
waiting I Bonk my head and erase eras my
memory for 24
hours if I keep racing I'll eventually
get my merch tomorrow
what so it's not coming yet it's August
September that's so soon what do you
mean you're just like pretending that
it's
coming what you're really excited for
that froggy W merch
huh if it's coming in August then it
will be in Japan in August so hopefully
I can take my own set of froggy waa
merch
home
yeah let's
go end of
[Music]
September end of September I don't think
I'll be in Japan damn it hope I can get
it
earlier can't wait to put froggy while
next to dino yeah that's what I want to
see I think we would match nicely those
small little
menaces it's you
sh gold boom d space waterful thanks for
the pinky K hi wa for sorry for missing
so much of you lately take the Super
Chat from me as making up for missing
stream yesterday for missing the first
three hours of the stream and all the
other times by the way you look cute I
love you thank you don't worry I feel
like you're always here so not a problem
to
me you are always here half time is over
soon okay thank you space wonderful for
the
support yeah no pressure to be here all
the time
anyway the more the merer of course
but OK Okie doie let me unmute on my
side
for thank you
return to fireemblem
when when a new game comes out maybe but
we just had one like last year and it
was it was
okay oh
cheese there's a carrot sticking in his
cheese head funny
who
70% are in orange but the French F fans
are somehow louder says the commentator
guy I thought it was 2022 maybe it
was yeah was
it more like 2023 to me
have you ever visited the Netherlands I
think only the uh
airport
sadly and f d space wonderful D unknown
thanks to the pinky you're very
entertaining and it's always super
enjoyable to watch you do literally
anything so how are we supposed to be
bored we're here for you and no one else
while we love you well did I think that
that was that day was
boring I don't really remember remember
anymore what happened in that
stream all the all the Minecraft streams
are mixing into each
other but it was probably the day where
I didn't really get visited by anyone
but but Cali or so
probably you always say that no I don't
always say that there's certain streams
that I feel better about that and
certain stream where I feel less good
about it
engage with gener oh the beginning of
2023 then
okay have confidence I
try I try I do try thank you unknown for
the sweet words of confidence
[Music]
Jimmy Jack
fun it starting
are we
beginning started for
you
[Music]
and oh okay that took a
while that took a while holy [\h__\h] maybe
I should have refreshed to the browser
well I don't
think I don't think he lagged or
anything
okay okay here we go uh where was
I Alex
Sol ah now it's too late anyway but no
only myth allowed on the server we're
also the only one that are wh listed for
it 7 D CH D Jones D lunch box D unknown
D pyro wolf fox thanks for
Pinky in honor of watching The Stream
with my dad I'd love to send my support
thanks for making us love today
tento with your
dad with your dad you're not the one
that came to my meet and greet and told
me that your dad likes my streams
right you're not the one right are there
several
people who do
that who do D
dad dad's love Wawa
Daddy thank you thank you I hope you
guys had fun there thanks for watching
and thanks for the
pinky
oh Maximo kicker thank you for pinky
I've recently started watching YouTubers
again after a long break and now with a
job I can support the people who make
great content just like you charming
greetings from
Argentina thank you congratulations on
getting a job again let's go let's go I
hope you're having a good time with your
colleagues and so on I hope they're nice
enjoy your new job and watching
YouTubers again welcome back orbital
vagabon dag aor D for the pinky
and congratulations on getting your
armor I just noticed I got my armor
today now I look like a dashing night
chicken too you always did look like a
dashing night to
me thank you thank you thank you and
congratulations thank you for supporting
me for such a long
time make sure to polish the armor
polish haha everyday
every day when you go to
bed twin tail dude did not know where to
shoot he was
flustered I'm so far behind you guys
[Music]
man it's 10 p.m. now
so don't demolish the Polish even more
you're kind of doing it too with that
pun with that rhyme Jerry Dark Shadow
hawkk
you remember when you were living in
Japan you didn't really cook you used to
order food a lot congrat yeah but that
was mostly because it was a gas kitchen
I didn't I felt scared of using it and I
didn't have that many things in my
kitchen and also there were rats so I
didn't want to you know especially
downstairs I didn't want to go much
downstairs to where the kitchen
was I just really felt uncomfortable
there and
also like trash confused me so I was
trying to make less trash although you
might want to argue that it's more trash
when you order
[Music]
food depends but yeah was it a super old
stove the whole house was like super
[\h__\h] old the moment I moved out the
next people started renovating it that's
why I got it so cheap in the first place
from like a
acquaintance had only really cheap
[Music]
rent it was not a good experience I just
felt so uncomfortable that I I didn't
want to cook
because didn't really like this kind of
kitchen scared me didn't have many like
cooking things
anyway and yeah just felt kind of
disgusted
generally
yeah I
mean it was honestly a big blessing that
I could move in there because it was a a
a really
quick um
settlement cuz I started in that tiny
tiny tiny cheap apartment where I was
because I you know that was before I
joined Holo I was you know just chilling
in that cheap one room apartment tiny
tiny tiny
place and then I started and streaming
was impossible there pretty much because
of the thin walls even when I was
whispering they were bonking on the
walls I was really really not working
out so I needed something fast but I
still didn't have my first uh rent uh uh
my first uh income I think when I
already had started looking and I it was
still kind of hard to tell like how much
I could really afford and also there was
only like half a year or so left of me
living in
Japan so most
places that were like proper
places they would like more long-term
people um so yeah all those things
considered it was a blessing that I had
an acquaintance who had a a big house
empty partially with Furniture
tool because I I uh the other place was
also partially like not partially but
like pretty much like it had a table a
bed uh like small small table small bed
uh Kitchen Stuff
Etc so f pretty
much and the other place was also
furnished thank God relatively furnished
I had to pay uh I had to buy a table
though and a chair too I
think I think a few things I had to
buy comments on your country winning I
think France will win but we'll see
going to bed now watch the debut this
night yeah y good night you're getting
up early just for that
huh they will appreciate it I'm sure
but yeah we'll see we'll see who wins oh
you can see how they they want to catch
the
ball in the
audience you're going to sleep after the
stream for the new debuts yeah I I want
to watch it live too because of the
hype but I don't
know they're still doing one hour debuts
right that's how we do it normally we do
one hour debut so that would be from 5:
to 700 a.m. that means I have to stay up
until 7 a.m. if I want to watch
those what they doing 45 minutes now oh
okay they've shortened it still pretty
long though in
total interesting how they've shortened
it maybe because recently other
Generations other talents like I
remember like crony for example like
some others surely have struggled to
fill the whole
hour so maybe with that being a trend
they were like let's make it shorter
seems like people have less of an
attention span to these
days La La at
[Music]
30 I don't know I think back then I felt
like 1 hour was almost not enough
so I think 30 would be too short for my
personal
taste 45 is
okay laas was really
[Laughter]
short laas was didn't she also was that
the one where the stre the debut stream
was delayed because internet
problems was that
plus oh kick Frey
kick kick Kitty
kick oh you so focused oh my God the
pressure the pressure you're like one
hour in and nothing's happening oh like
this is this is where it gets
really mental passion mical
sh oh yeah if there was something you
guys would have told me
already
mus o was that
out that looked like
out oh
so close to not being
out will probably be good for Austria I
guess if they have a tie that's also
fine for
us if they have a
tie then minimum what we need is also a
tie
or are we in if we get a tie then
no we need a win uhoh then I want France
to win
please
yeah give us a little bit more of a
free
freedom I think we can do it though I
think we can do it think we can do it
just win against Netherlands and easy I
think we
can like looking at how they play now
too this
boring Austria will will bully the [\h__\h]
out of
them yeah
respectfully I love orange but I have no
problem with Netherlands as a country
cool country cool people
really friendly
people but we'll [\h__\h] you
[Laughter]
up yeah no goals yet it's kind of we're
1 hour in
y okay let me finish these super
chatos Jerry D dark wait did I read oh
wait I read these over I'm finished
actually I'm finished with day
three day four has like really little
super chats let's read those
too day four Minecraft stream starting
now D Hood thank you for two pinkies why
you going through it fast huh damn you
have to watch all my all my
streams and then additionally to that
you're watching two Gilma Girls episodes
per day wow wow wow wow Paris gushing
about her Jamie Christmas Is Like Us
jimin gushing about
Wawa she's perfect oh my God love
Wawa all Jess wants to do is slobber on
Rory Rory needs better love interest n
yeah if you think about it even until
the end she never really
had like perfect ones they all have some
flaws for sure I mean we all do but they
had some big
flaws big red flags Rory needs SP love
choice I will wait for the blonde boy W
mentioned yeah that one is good but he
still also has red flags
sadly uh next episode hey yo great gby
reference this Joe dude came back for
Suki 10 years too late oh Joe is a chef
like Suki so they can connect well in
the kitchen does w connect easily with
everyone or do you connect better with
shared common
interests definitely shared common
interest like anybody who's like in like
vibing with anime or so for
sure can't connect well with people who
go to clubs and drink lots of alcohol
and
[Music]
um I don't know too like that level of
Normie is actually a very scary and
intimidating to me especially if you're
like younger than me CU there's so many
[\h__\h] brats out there [\h__\h]
brats who think they're it who think
they can disrespect their Elders me I'm
their Elder and they treat me they
surely treat me like that AKA they treat
me like
[\h__\h] like at the
supermarket that I go to people have
like brats shitty brats have been
getting really up with me up
stupid brats look like they're like 10
years younger than me and they've got an
attitude
man oh almost go man you tried but once
again you failed sad wait fridge French
uniform has a [\h__\h] Chicken on
it French
uniforms did you guys know this
Neverland may be orange but they have a
rooster on their uniform
wa on their
chest I noticed now
yeah
why is this a French national animal is
it oh what what what what's
happening I want a closeup of that
please o give me give me closeups
[Music]
man what what ow ow ow
okay
oh oh and he tries to hold the ball with
his leg okay and then there what's
what's what's this
wrangling not really clear what the [\h__\h]
happened
[Music]
H manly tears someone's
crying the one that was on the
ground didn't see him
cry he looks like he's about to cry I
it's I don't really know what happened
there I looked really closely and was
just
chaos they're getting desperate though
you can tell 60 Minutes
in he was incubating the
ball crocodile tears
oh it's okay I can I
can imagine
the kind of pressure
and just is not not
a
shot over the goal too
bad not even not even that
[Music]
far man that physical Justin
there's some great defending going on
yeah yeah I guess
so Neverland tends to win last few
minutes ooh Strat
Strat last few minutes keep yeah it's
actually it might be might be a strat
keep it like keep everything's super
defensive go for a tie until the last
minute last five minutes when
everybody's letting their guard
down or are they though are they I guess
in that case if it's z z I would not let
my guard down but maybe that's what
they're hoping for and also
like hoping that they the others are
already tired
out yeah all out attack last few minutes
until then full defense
stall h park the bus the second time I
hear that
today okay well well well well well well
well thank you D
Hood how many episodes is it was it like
20 plus episodes still got like quite a
few to go but good good luck and have
fun Ultimo MK thanks for the pinky well
this is it now tomorrow will be the
first day of my exam period oh
it's going to be some super stressful
weeks from now but it will be worth it
if by the end of the next month I can
write Ultimo Mark
radiographer radiographer in my resume
going to do my best what is
that
radiographer are Allied health
professionals who take X-rays and autom
medical images to ah images to assist
doctors in diagnoses hey I see so uh I
was thinking of actual
radio
oh ah griman fast so close almost
goal I thought it was radio well you
going to take X-ray cool that sounds
[Music]
interesting yeah
come on
greasy MRIs too please take an MRI for
me
please okay let me finish this and read
this let's go check 47 than you sh oh
wait also let me just let me get got I
got to say yo G for your exams Focus I
know you can do
it you want to you want to take my MRI
scan my brain
please I I hope it will all work out
47 fur Demi n
d fi D Maxim k d Dark Shadow hwk than g
f
estan sta
a than today I've hit the terribly old
age of 35 and I'm glad I can spend time
seeing you all together and I'm see
again good luck on the prep for the
never thank
you see from an outside POV I would say
35 is not so old so don't worry about it
but um when you hit it yourself I'm sure
it feels very different but happy
birthday congratulations
thank you for your Super
Chat monkey Omega
gaming
Maxim space water
Maxim isn't that the name of that cute
vampire
girl for sure it is girl was so popular
when that anime was running she was like
everywhere
I saw cosplays of her
everywhere yeah from oin noaf
yeah is so
cute
ooh it's like they're purposefully
missing all their
goals damn
and Bop has broken nose and Bop cannot
go
in O coach really passionate but he's
missing the the the
fic if only because the coach has the
passion and the mental but he's missing
the physical see another case of one
thing
go upcoming go okay here we go I'm
watching I'm watching I'm watching
we's making a really good point right
now but okay no way no
way oh oh oh it goes back once it goes
back they're Gathering orange orange
orange
lucky orange
bastards oh that must be a huge relief
right
now finally finally that was sick like
he goalie tried his best man he he shot
it
back several times blocked it several
times and
yet they were
persistent no go it was
oh
oh okay I'm getting the rewatch right
now I don't understand why that was not
I watched I watched this it looked okay
I don't know what's what was wrong about
that I mean we talked about it but
a
[\h__\h] oh oh they look so
devastated oh I'm going to
[Music]
cry he was blocking the
goal the guy next to the goalie blocked
his path uh if they show it again I got
to pay attention to that
okay I worry about their
man Fu gold oh they're still checking
the
go
oh oh I feel like that was deserved I
feel like it was very deserv
deserved of a
goal the fans are like pen doggy eyes
pleas
Point go
St not Val which
one no go
W poor referee gonna get death threats
after this
[\h__\h]
damn that was awesome I mean if you know
like football that well I'm sure it was
to me that looked like very
legit ah ah
o oh they hate him ooh
ooh oh French people are like
haha how do you go haha in the French
way
[\h__\h]
h h
[Laughter]
a wait who was in the way who block ah
orange guy was like too close to the
goalie block uh blocking him from going
there to possibly catch the ball I I
think I can see it
[Music]
now yeah if you stand right next to the
goalie and such a case that is very
obstructing I almost feel like it would
have gone in
anyway but yeah still it should in that
case
Okay hard call I think it was very
deserved of a goal but yeah that dude
was too
close but everybody was close to the
goal that's the problem like everybody
gets so
up word of the day in
[Music]
brain wrong place wrong time exactly oh
there's like a
oh there's like a
graphic oh apparently that was off topic
that that graphic was
useless great must have been made by AI
if it was not even related to the
problem don't know why it took so long
because they went all like
[Music]
P this game needed some drama true true
it was related the my commentators said
it was not related they're like thanks
but this is not related
this is not what we
needed well that was
interesting that was very interesting
they're definitely going to get like 10
minutes extra for
this it is it isn't what was contentious
yes
H oh
switch
switch jiru come on jiru Griezmann tried
his best but jiru you got to do
it this is jiru last year is he
retiring 37 years
old let let me look at him
again let's
okay let me let me go back to Super
chats they how much time did they have
left 15 minutes plus probably
10 oh man okay actually I was almost
finished U Nathan coton thanks for the
pinky hi you really been enjoying the
one block streams and I felt like I
should keep you a prised apprised of my
baking Endeavors M I just finished
making a cheesecake with a CA this time
and it made me wonder what your favorite
non cake cake is nonc cake
cake what kind of nonc cake cakes are
there help me out here what would be a
non cake
cake yeah pancakes
maybe look it has cake in the name it's
not a cake but uh that's I guess that's
a cookie cake
cake pizza
ice cream cake is that is that really
not a cake who decides if that is cake
pie I would say pie pie is not cake but
it's basically
cake but yeah you remind me Nathan you
remind me of the the thing that um gooa
made in her
Skillet and I didn't get the recipe she
did not send me the
recipe she forgot about it I want the
recipe where's that recipe goo
the cookie and the skillet huh help I
need it I don't have a skillet but
still it's probably just cookie dough
yeah usual cookie dough and just make it
in Skillet
huh I want that I want that with vanilla
ice cream
freaki very interesting
Nathan thank you for making me hungry
for baked things thank you
thank you
Nathan Matrix free BC D and
spankenheimer
[Music]
completely I guess I'm just going to
read until the match is
over how's the diet going well I kind of
gave up about being serious about it but
I'm still kind of doing it
I'm so kind of doing it I I uh lost uh 2
kilogram slowly slowly
slowly I don't think I can tell though
when I look at
myself that it is progress It's him
H you think that's pretty good right
yeah I think so cuz I mean it can take
take a while to lose some weight unless
you're going in really
aggressively the first week when I was
going pretty aggressively I noticed no
weight
loss V
Quest and then now that I'm taking it a
bit more easy I I think that's when I
started losing weight
[Music]
VOR also very German
name but I guess Dutch can also sound
very German but maybe it is a maybe it
is a German person because you have like
all kinds of nationalities in these
teams
right takes a while takes a week plus
before it
happens hey kind of lagged for
me yeah I know I've been I've been uh
paying attention if it like fluctuates
and I've been like taking measured it
like uh at the same time of the day
roughly yeah also recently I just didn't
have time to get on my running machine
that's really unfortunate cuz I want to
but like sleep schedule being [\h__\h] and
and that makes me feel like fatigued and
exhausted and living at the uh being
awake at weird hours and and streaming
so much and like doing other stuff in
the background recording stuff and so
on why bikini because I
won and then I celebrate
it don't question it it's how you do
it yeah I think uh the finale will be at
midnight my time and it won't be too
long I think it will be taking only an
hour or so I'm and that's if we stall
because I think the ACT we don't have to
find the Ender Dragon right we don't
have to find the the stronghold it's
already there the act of just killing
the ender dragon could take could be a
matter of 5 to 10
minutes so my plan is um to let
everybody like I I prepared some things
but not everything in terms of armor and
weapons so I let everybody just like
gather their things for the first 30
minutes or so make themselves some
weapons and stuff uh and finish their
armor enchant it with what they want
therefore also like using the um the mm
a little bit to get their levels up and
after all that
stalling 40 50 minutes we can go and a
dragon kill it 1 hour
done probably going to go like that I
think but I was also thinking the game
is currently on easy and maybe we're
going to be too strong I was thinking
can I like
turn it up to normal at least
for the ending I I probably would have
to ask the people who set up the server
cuz I don't know how to change it but I
was wondering if we should maybe do
that is it easy normal hard or is it
just easy
hard why is it even une easy is that how
I normally do I normally play Minecraft
on easy I I legit don't remember is are
they the are our servers normally on
easy or
normal do you guys know we
don't normally I think you play normal
oh
wow Honestly though maybe easy was
suitable for at least the first one or
two days because there was still a lot
of chaos and
death maybe easy was better because like
the gas and so on and that was that was
even in EAS see there was a lot of chaos
now for the finale I might ask them to
switch it to normal
[Music]
then I before I forget it I'm going to
do that now
[Music]
to switch the mode to normal
please it's currently on
easy I need to go idle meeting y
b but it's okay I'll finish watching
this I can hold it
in I'll probably
run immediately after this is
done 7 minutes and then extra time I
think H okay the Minecraft day five
Super Chat reading
time Jacob for7 D unknown D for the
pinky Jacob how do you always manage to
send the first one huh daily reminder
that you are really amazing and we love
you you're the best Wawa oh no thank you
I
I'm getting worried like for ages feels
like you send so many
pinkies are please please don't don't
lose all your savings for me
okay careful careful I known too much
pinkies careful
now but thank you for the support
always what a Chad what a big big Chad
too much pinkies
careful yeah maybe he like he has no
pinkies anymore he like amputated them
donated them got uh money from uh other
people getting pinkies who had no
pinkies you know like a heart transplant
but in this case it's a pinky
transplant really weird uh Theory sorry
unknown yubby
yie y
y for the
[Music]
pink food poisoning
Doug Hood thanks for the red super chat
if you're going to work hey no gilr
review today if you're going to work a
double shift today especially when
you're not feeling well you sure is
schnitzel getting paid for it thank you
all thank you for all your hard work
hope you feel better or just the
schedule is needed we will understand
thank you
yeah but that was fun even with the
double shift of you know being a little
bit
much was fun I'm glad I woke up for that
stream I feel like so under pressure
with jackb
streams but quip lash us being able to
put in our own prompts definitely helped
with me having an easier time because at
least
well at least it was H live related
mostly what the
hell if it was the usual prompt and I
probably would not
know what to say at
all France are allergic to shots
H you mean for to them trying
anything in the first place like no
attempts you
mean love the sink with
M yeah that was some some weird
sink four three more
minutes it's so over
guys
but
maybe it does it matter is there a
difference for Austria if they have a
tie or are losing
Neverland does it even matter don't
think it makes a
difference we need a win in any case
even if they
tie or if they if Netherlands
loses win wins
yeah the only difference is
if you could get to second place of a
grip
oh if the Lev win you need to win
against them if they lose you need only
a Time
ooh
yeah yeah but I mean them winning versus
them having a tie
is for us in both cases we need a tie h
a win H yeah
whatever well see it's almost over 2
minutes let me let
me super chats H thank you thank you
good thank you so much for the support
hope you had fun watching both of my
shifts James Jackson
d seanan
d
what
oh I almost had IT Crowd was
cheering damn
that was your
chance he was really fast he was
[Music]
speeding I'm just getting into the
French's way is
hilarious as long as they're not fouling
that's okay
Mia
M hon
W nice head shot oh that's so wow
pretty they just flexing their heads
now committing F
play be
like first zero Z of the turny ooh is
it FY
D but now great grandmothers how you
feeling about getting more children inan
children uh well hopefully they're not
too
childish but um yeah it's it's actually
yeah it's crazy to think about there
being like free gens after us now
so our family tree is growing more and
more and
more we're becoming an even bigger
family it's maybe a bit overwhelming I
hope I'll get along with them
uh and I want to I want to make friends
with
them oh 5 minutes okay o you could get
one goal you could you could get a goal
in those five minutes either way we we a
party anyway yeah it's almost time for
their debuts so I hope you guys we'll
check it out when it's happening if
you're
awake oh oh
Neverland come on last minute win show
me what you got even though I want
France to
win
Y what are they oh
[Music]
come yeah
mean I'd be pissed
too
I'm France is pressuring way to late
now I didn't pay 100%
attention so I can't really make a
proper
judgment you set it the right way no
more
Justice yeah you think there was much to
miss I thought it would just super chat
reading no I'm switching I'm switching
back and forth nicely right uh Dark
Shadow cherry
pie for the pinky finally for the first
time ever Nintendo decided to make the
Legend of Link this was definitely a
wild direct with all the RPGs announced
I hope you'll give fantasian
the Dragon Quest free or Mario luigia
try too feel better stent tal out of
those threee I think Dragon Quest free
has the biggest chance for
me yeah and of course I'm so [\h__\h]
excited for Legend of Zelda like actual
Zelda this
time where's the ball I can't see the
ball oh
there still waiting on Golden Sun yeah
Golden Sun uh or uh I always think about
Dark Cloud I don't think anybody has
that on their radar that's just never
going to be ever I guess it's not
relevant but for me for me I I want
somebody to remake Dark Cloud hello
hello oh you guys actually hey really
you actually with me let's [\h__\h]
go a please Sony is it Sony
who knows if I would even get perms
done oh oh
wait uh no okay W one
[Music]
minute you can play Dark One Two on ps45
really but I want to I want a new
one a remake or something new
ORD was better right like this was a
snooze Fest
indeed indeed but it was good to have if
it was more exciting then it would have
been a problem as the background of my
Super Chat reading this way this was
this was actually like
perfect and D for the pinky what color
is Yago what his what his image color
is I might even say black I know we
talked on like about why is there no
black I talked about it on that
day feel like cuz Hey you think rainbow
color no you can't give him rainbow
color
no literally no because that would be
the image color of the nii Sanji EO
CEO come on ah yeah light blue light
blue for
Yago obviously I
guess is it over oh wait they're they're
still did they get another
five is over it's
over oh yeah over so over it's so over
okay let me close it immediately because
that was boring
I'm not impressed I'm not impressed
Neverland you were supposed to impress
me so that I would be scared but I'm not
scared I'm not scared at
all H what do you think guys now
watching how Neverland plays right after
how Austria played what do you think
what do you think we have a chance a
would crush Neverland
yeah they're motivated
too they're super
motivated also will crush him with a big
one one
no that's not crushing
them and we have a chance for sure we
do Austria a EST
[Music]
that was top two in the world that I'm
sorry but that didn't look like top two
in the world maybe it's really the
matchup making it look
so
lackluster no no France we're talking
about France
top two in the
world you go by the last uh
world the cup or
what France just didn't have
myup I guess so maybe it would be very
different with
him but you can't just have a whole team
only work with the presence of one
specific
player that's
ridiculous what if that one gets injured
you're just going to lose all your
matches you'd be surprised tell that to
Argentina
uh but that's that's stupid you need to
at least have a second good good player
that you can rely on like that at least
one more come
on that is your problem as we can see
just now this the this is the situation
that you're going to be left
in I wonder if he will play next time
against Austria h no wait that they're
not playing anymore uh against us but
yeah France has probably one more match
coming up right their third one or is
this the was this their third
one was the second one right everyone
has one more okay they play Poland next
uh now I'm like really curious even if
it's not my team I didn't think that
would happen I do want to see how how
they they're um how they
harmonize damn I've become a football
fan
H I just want to see the others that we
played against or we're playing against
it's interesting to see all of those
matchups
[Music]
I mean Poland against
France I wouldn't go I wouldn't so go be
so certain about a clear
loss for Poland because they got one
goal against
austrial they're not complete
losers not a chance in hell we're
winning hey don't say that don't say
that there's all always a chance there's
always a
chance I'm going to root for Poland when
it's up against France
okay I'm going to root for Poland
because they play more interestingly so
far it's like it's like Idol units
grouping them up some will work better
with one
another or collaborations it's like us
doing
collabs huh
thank you for such a nice watch thank
you too I had such a blast yeah it was
good to catch up with my super chats so
let me finish these I'm hungry I'm
feeling kind of sick right now y blue
top
[Music]
seven Maxim
canall it's probably because I've only
had a so far and some a lot of orange
juice I business regulation director D
macaroni King D
J hes theja thanks to the pinky at least
they don't have to go to the usual room
rest well jimins ah you think you think
death is better than usual
room that is
actually a good advertisement for the
usual room so that you guys are not so
up about it
anymore
right thank you for the super
J thank you very much El marel loano D
Elie La D just another kfp D just
never o name tag on roof you know even
off stream I lost like free zombies or
so like
once uh one
burnt uh because like when I uh found
the zombie on the
roof uh it was already the end of the
night and I didn't realize that the sun
was already coming up and I was still
trying to get the the zombie out of the
water the little hole in the Middle
where the Golems are supposed to go I
was trying to get him out the moment I
get him out the sun comes up and he
starts burning and he's like running
around and I can't build a roof for him
in
[Music]
time yeah yeah yeah it's
like yeah and then another one I think I
uh like the the first one you know you
know the first one that we captured with
cie uh I was like we we name I got the
name tag for him right no wait I think
at that point the he was already gone
but I got a name tag and
then uh that one died too somehow yeah
then I had to work on getting another
name tag um but I got the order wrong
and I got a zombie and then I didn't
have a name tag ready for him so he also
despawned so had to start again uh it
was like a lot of back and forth between
me running to my cows then to my bread
field then to the iron farm still fixing
things putting the rails
in getting rid of the carpets putting
the carpets there again BL blah blue
then the rails like one time I I set up
the rails and it was like uh already
running I had a zombie sitting in there
and I had three villagers but somehow
now it didn't work still there was no
Golems spawning so I tried two things at
once I tried like spawn proofing the
area a little bit more H and uh also
extending the rail one more and like
repositioning the red uh rails so that
he would be a little bit slower I saw
them literally reacting but I thought
okay I read something about the
milliseconds of ticks and blah blah blah
uh that it takes for a Golem to spawn so
maybe it's just a small adjustment that
is necessary so I made small adjustments
adjustments to the rail and then then it
was finally
working but then even then every once in
a while the Golem would spawn somewhere
else around the farm so that each time I
would like kill the Golem and then try
to spawn proof that area where he
spawned each time it told me like okay
so that area can still spawn a Golem
okay okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah
troubleshooting real hard but I figured
it out it seems to be working and I was
like I was farming a little bit AFK
farming I got like two stacks or so
every once in a while when I'm not
paying attention it spawns somewhere
somewhere else and I go back to my PC
and I
realize it hasn't been working for a
while
huh yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's not like super super
consistent but it's somehow working it's
working it's just not 100%
reliable saw you playing Minecraft with
more before I also heard that you do a
great valr accent because I have a
teenage sister I love that voice that
appeals to me oh your sister talks like
this so that appeals to you wow it kind
of sounds like you have a sister complex
ew just kidding
just kidding I'm I'm trying
to make an impression of how the a
valley girl would react to that
information like oh my God you're like
so obsessed with
me thank you thank you don't talk like
that near Ollie what is she into it or
is she like against
it is this where your
0.001% American blood goes
perhaps that that might be where where I
get that
from I like totes love it we both went
to the store and I S is totally cute
Gucci shirt oh my God Gucci ew nowadays
we don't do Gucci anymore Gucci is like
sell
2010 oh my
God 2010 is s crinch
yeah we only bring back things from
previous years when I say that we should
there's a time and there's a place for
it and now it's not it I'm so not Gucci
with your
Gucci it's so fad you think it's fad ew
what are you doing in this stream when
you think like
that I do not want to be associated with
people like
you stop trying to make pet a
[Music]
thing
H 80s aerobics yes 8s aerobics are
currently super
fat okay okay Super Chat let me finish
just this one stream here El D just
another
kfp D solti than KO Koy thanks for the
pinky W cute oh I feel like this is your
first Super Chat to me thank you thank
you KO Koy
cute very
cute see this is the one from my uh new
outfit artist yeah I read it already on
stream so I'm not going to read it again
but thank you
again Dash
[Music]
48 dun FR screw dun kist dun LC chal Lin
what happened to your name what
happened
golden black f d j SW D and dou Hood D
and take Monkey
D I changed my wait wait wait wait wait
wait hey I still had the polar up so any
any recent votes are not legal but we
did have a tie so anybody who voted for
the tie especially before they started
playing you
win it was it was not even a cool tie if
it was like 1 one 2 two 3 three anything
like that would be cooler a z0 tie is
like did you even play did you like even
play at all like what were you doing all
this
time it's like a loser
tie what's the priz boss nothing because
that was a lame ass
timee the poll shut up three times for
me so I voted for all options so I'd win
no matter what but you also lost you
then you only won once and you you lost
twice so in reality you lost
sorry to tell you the truth
sorry I know it's
rough I know it's rough to hear it like
that yeah I I said TW by accident don't
don't point it
out all
right uh
tomorrow
ooh I'm still kind of
waiting for the
reply supposedly tomorrow is MC
finale let me follow up with
someone hey little follow up
[Music]
okay
yeah now I don't know what to
cook I'll I'll figure it out I'll look
at my stuff I'll open the fish smell the
fish when I'm scared off the fish fish
I'm scared of the
fish anything about the fish what about
the chicken you trust the chicken
more it was at least chill is it was not
icy in there anymore but it was also not
warm it was chill is
[Music]
you trust the fish more cuz it doesn't
have
salmonella even though it's fish it's
not salmon though not salmon last time
was
salmon check the fish thoroughly it
might be still good how do I how do I
check it
thoroughly besides smelling
it what other food do you have another
dish is the one with minced meat but
if anything I should cook the other
things first cuz they go off faster
sooner tunella I wish I had
tuna color it's it's a pretty white fish
so it looks very
white it just looks very
white is it slime I don't know yet it
looked kind it was packaged but it
looked a little bit slimy but I didn't
want to judge it too much yet because
it's still in the package it looks just
weird no must not be
slimy we toss the fish well I don't want
to waste the
[Music]
[Laughter]
food you just toss it okay I'll think
about
it it's probably fine just eat it wow
that's how that's how what we fought
last time Di and look what happened to
me something [\h__\h] me
up can't be that
sure look where this led us this kind of
attitude what it has brought to
us um in any case I'm a bit in a
difficult situation I'm hoping that I'll
get an answer within the next hours
before I get to
sleep um actually did I just no okay um
because if we don't do MC finale
tomorrow then I would like to do watch
along members only for mono katali
movies
um but I don't have an answer yet so I
can't decide yet
guys just prepare the movies so you're
ready anytime I
guess
yeah if we do do the MC finale
Doo uh that would be at like
midnight but I think we can do cuz the
movies even all together aren't that
long we could do a
late uh like 6:00 p.m. 700 p.m. or so on
Sunday perhaps maybe but not sure yet
I'm trying to squeeze it in so that we
get
further uh ahead with this before the
new season starts but I doubt that we
can finish it all at this point we might
be overlapping a little
bit 3.5 hours okay that's very doable
very very
[Music]
doable but I'll have to wait so please
uh be ready uh I have to wait for the
reply sorry I can't give you a clear
instruction yet but anyway thank you so
so much guys for watching I had so much
fun watching at least the Austria Poland
match thank you Poland for being uh a
really sick partner you know for uh this
this matchup was nice was fun was
exciting to
watch shakes hand shakes hand I'll see
you again for more football on
Tuesday Neverland getting up with
Neverland up
counter was fun hanging out right what
about the kfp who were like man I don't
know how to feel about this idea I think
it was still fun
right surprisingly fun yay SK changed to
up exactly up counter 15 I would believe
that sounds about right it really fun it
was surprisingly fun this was fun really
fun no doubt it's was going to be fun
why made it fun I did nah the austrians
made it fun austri game was more funny
that father would be yeah that one that
one for the the other one I'm going to
say yeah that was lame
but that that one was just
extra here's hoping the Netherlands have
a bad day against
Austria I hope I pray oh by the way I
watched I will not talk about it now but
I watched Game of Thrones first episode
so House of the Dragon so uh next time
maybe if I need a talking topic feel
free to remind me about L of drinks nope
uh again House of the Dragon feel free
to remind
me
okay it was really cool but oh next
episode is in two days already so we
might be able to talk about both and I
even I even watched like an
hour uh like I watched two different
Recaps I watched a whole season recap
and I watched a last episode
specifically recap that took like 30 40
minutes or so um and that really helped
that really helped but I'm still so
confused like aen and Damon now I'm
starting to get it but for the longest
time aan and Damon I never understood
which one they were talking about when
those names came up and also like the
the girls names there also also Sim like
who the [\h__\h] are you talking
about yeah the [\h__\h] names they're way
too
similar way to
similar I guess I am talking about it
but yeah [\h__\h] even after all of the
recap I was still so
confused anyway okay yeah
a a her heroism viser
da [\h__\h] who's who who's the king that
died the king that died was viseris
right
right yeah
okay who was Jaris was that his father
I think I may have
been those are those are still somewhat
REM
memorable but yeah en thanks for
watching I'm now going to celebrate even
more by taking off my top and you're not
going to see
it o
o o I did not resize the ending screen
by the way
so don't look at
it just don't don't don't judge
[Music]
me
in let's
go let's
[Music]
go can't believe we got free goals you
just reminded me in that chat there's no
way we actually got free goals wait what
is Big announcements from M AK
tanig wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I need to react to Big announcements
from Moto akano from Whole Life English
6 hours
ago what what what what is this hello H
pans of the world yeah this is M Tano
CEO of Caba Corporation nice English
since we founded whole life Indonesia
and whole life English in back in
2020 we've seen debuts for six different
units for for Indonesia first second and
third generation as well as for English
prise and Advent I want to thank all of
you for supporting our members up until
now even in times like the co9
pandemic I've got some big news to share
as announced recently a new unit English
Justice will be joining us soon you made
this video and laa I look forward to
seeing each of these upcoming
firecrackers in the Journey of bringing
Justice to the
world in addition we are proud to make
beacha history together with you very
night event all the do stum in flexing
hard he's just flexing another
announcement I'm proud to make is that
15 English members with the addition of
Advent will perform on the king theater
New York stage yeah on top of it we will
support longit Second live concert yeah
it was inde
longit spreading our passion aims Beyond
and without limit to the just United
States it's First World Tour starting
from August 2 part of the world tour
Indonesia
Singapore the United States we are
pioneering new race in the Bri industry
to create a culture that can be loved
all around this year I expect there will
be even more opportunities for fans from
all over to enjoy and spend time with
their favorite forite members okay
there's still more to come and I can't
wait to share with
soon but just for now I hope that you
all enjoy the horve English Justice
first ever stream going live tomorrow
what what I see you there oh okay what
why did what is this just a
flex weird flex but okay did he just
Flex the overseas branches is that all
he came
for the the music the and the production
value I'm I'm I'm so
[Laughter]
confused there's an article in cover's
page a com this is it basically just
saying the same
things
yeah I think this is just a company
trying to
flex okay boss thanks I'm I'm excited
too but know it it was so intense I I
thought something was
happening uh like he was like starting
like walking down this line of units
right and mentioning them all I thought
he was like announcing like I don't know
some new Branch like not not Europe just
like whole live I don't know Korea
Korea that would have been cool I
thought he was cooking that and I was
like is that where you're going why do I
not even know about that I would know
about it I
think Korea would have been
cool you also fought that no
way I've got my eyes on you
yo in
Korea yeah I would have known that's why
I was like where is he going with
this
sus yeah let the man do his cool
presentation hey that was it was really
cool okay that was an extra watch
along
byebye was that
what what
this not a single s oh my God not even a
English equivalent
[Music]
okay I run to the toilet by