[Music]
thank you
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hey welcome everyone to at stream up a
gorilla stream uh we're featuring uh
miyos takanasi Kiana and or no uh Kiara
and then I whiz hello I always say hello
I always hi Luis
[Music]
and we have
enough say hello Ina
enough
it's funny because the game has like a a
song background sound so when you said
nothing it was just like comedicated
kids
crickets and then we have
Elmo
oh goodness oh wow wow we are all in a
very funny mood today
unfortunately Holo console W's have been
moved to and currently unknown date and
time uh but uh this would have been
without the fun hello
this would have been a a really sad and
lovely
is that a lonely Saturday evening for
all of us so uh I was like yo I don't
know if I should do a gorilla stream or
not I wear that in a Discord chat and
then gura and Ina were like kind of want
to do that too I've been thinking too
should we collab and then I I wheeze was
like I will join too what the hell let's
go
no counsel you get us dummies instead
oh that was fun time ghosting ghosting
oh yeah and Goa said that she wanted to
play a certain map of this game but a a
new one but I don't know if we can get
there today but we'll try we'll try we
have a new Ghost Hunter I whis
are you scared of the dark and of ghosts
yes very much and I have close to zero
experiences
hey guys you know what to do on the
Ghost Coast
all our life of course
what what we let the ghost Pig Irish
first
make the new be the sacrifice oh my gosh
this is because this is
[Laughter]
the rule and the ghost ghost hunting
Community yeah
uh well Goa is very experienced and Ina
is I think um very very decent as well
so I think we're safe we're gonna do
another running away oh can't we just
give a shout out to uh Ina's incredible
something
it's a multi-truck fun or I think
reference yeah I think my mom likes it
even more now because I think she was a
fan of gorillas uh
not specifically
oh yeah oh yeah I can't get the the
reference you guys got the reference
right in the chat you didn't just see
monkey and go haha funny monkey you
actually got it did you guys get it did
you I actually didn't get it right away
I knew a gorilla gorilla stream gorilla
that's what I got I didn't notice people
come on how do I pick up items again
question mark e e okay okay then I think
my tutorial has ended I'm ready to wait
how do you drop them
[Music]
oh yeah yeah the girls the three girls
are going to be using the in-game chat
uh in-game voice chat uh once we get
into the game so uh look forward to ASMR
or non-existent ASMR depending on where
the grills are
mic it's got right left Center Mike oh
God
[Music]
I can do it
maybe you definitely fit maybe the
closet oh my God
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
like sardines who's stepping on me
it's probably yeah
I can see the inside fish
uh
the ones that can explode
is so strumming yeah
[Laughter]
I have a spy view right now are we gonna
are we gonna explode
are we all in one Locker yes yes yes
I'm down can we get out of here wait I
don't know how to open the door anymore
have we broken the closet okay wait
where is the door which one is the door
foreign
[Music]
all right so
wait were you able to dash in this game
it's very slightly I think is that
really apparently if you crouch it makes
you go faster
oh that it feels like it yes but I can
also see how that is like a
um Imagination for me
wait it's like when you get off the
treadmill after a while and then it
feels like it was that a sneeze
love you thank you bless you did you did
you press V in order to sneeze because
we heard them
you wanted us to hear it
you don't have to hold the V is it
toggled oh is it voice recordings for
sure no nothing you can change the
settings it should be vegan settings
here after a while we have YouTubers
are we gonna hunt some ghosts or what
gorilla girls let's go I was about to
ask which man we want to do you guys
want to okay map as long as I'm with you
thank you
prison without the Ridgeview Roadhouse
got the Tanglewood Street aside I
promise don't High School whose butt am
I looking at
uh not not uh not the prison
do you have any houses we gotta choose a
map here
the the first one
not the prison though there's no prison
please no prison no prison I'm scared
there's a prison that's right it's scary
yeah it sounds big yeah that sounds good
yeah yeah let's go uh difficulty amateur
chaos
whoa
okay we're amateurs
this one this one look it's the council
colors kind of or is it sort of I I like
came out are we ready
wait do I so do I have to writing myself
up oh
yes excuse me let's go
that's cool I was you gotta go back to
the screen and then click radio
yeah why does your model have a bubble
butt
what's a bubble butt
it's a
it's a you know what a bubble butt is
don't no I really
I don't
writing isn't always the best option
okay if we have to can we all write that
down all right good now lead us you're
the professional Ghost Hunter here out
of all of us
today
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
Burger
[Music]
so uh okay let's read this [\h__\h] uh I've
done some more investigating for you
looks like the ghost's name is Nancy
Martinez and remember this ghost also
said it's the only respond to people who
are alone so just like us for the rest
of our lives
you should be able to use its name to
anger
what
apparently you got illness hear me
though right so I don't have to push the
button make sure to represent your
journal and write down any evidence you
find
foreign
with the EMF reader detect the ghost
presents with a motion sensor and maybe
have a member of your team witness a
ghost event that will totally be Iris
let's go
find it find the shrimp because there's
only three flashlights if we don't have
many meals
Twitter
what is that soda
salt salt is that salt I think I have
salt
um I think you can take some items right
three yes three three okay and then with
the mouse wheel which is broken on my
mouse but still kind of works
how is your mouse wheel broken how old
is your mouth what happens but it's like
cheap as hell
so uh-huh
I don't know man so I'm bringing
something that looks like a
I don't know what it even is maybe I
shouldn't carry the thing that I don't
know what it is
photos on and over all right I'll take
another I guess I'll take the camera
then oh okay
I got thermometer and the EMF emo
reader yeah probably EMA all right shall
we go oh by the way Iris uh there's
something called sanity
um who wants to understand what sanity
is to Iris
because I don't know something you give
to me okay
um so if you stay in the dark too long
like without any light you're gonna
start losing your son any points and
then the lower it is the more likely
you're gonna get haunted by the ghost
okay
yeah yeah okay so I have to stay safe
the activity screen is interesting as
well later on when we go back to the
track sometimes when we too scared oh
yeah but I don't think she'll see it
when things happen she'll be in it all
right let's go
this is the camera right what I'm
holding right now
not so sure I'm scared girl yes
yes let's do a video camera oh video
camera so we can set that up and we can
capture orbs
I hope I don't die no this is the first
one because
I don't know how we're gonna communicate
then stream is going to be quiet
open up
okay it's so dark you can turn on the
lights
where is where's the there it is oh I've
been in this house I've died in this
house before open up
oh yeah I was in this closet right here
I need that yeah
like at all times
good memories
Thanks for the Memories even though they
weren't so great
thanks for that your memories
Luigi board
where was that again it's been so long
what is this the board with like the
letters on it oh
good radio
ah nice music what am I looking for with
the FM thingy
uh
you shouldn't be yelling its name right
now should we
swear at you
what if I get FM over 100 is that good
or bad
you can only use that once you once you
cut in all the vicinity of a ghost
okay
I'll just uh not listen to it then
that's not clear
shall we go downstairs
Nancy Martinez give us a sign
penis
[Music]
also cleared
but how do we know it's clear when we
don't see the ghost
I got the thermometer
okay it usually gets a little colder you
know behind the cold room
oh oh have it take a picture
now take a picture now yeah
camera oh she got the video camera okay
you can set it up and go back and get
the
the actual camera
I'm gonna go get it because my arms are
useless
I'm gonna go get a camera
oh we have no camera
this might seem funny because I barely
can hear it
I'm back hello did you guys take the
picture
on the floor okay who made a oh no mine
is my thingy it was okay taking a
picture
I did it
all right I don't see any rooms
I got it I got it also should I put some
volunteer I don't know where do I put
the salt no no not yet I'm gonna find
the place well like doorways and stuff
you can put it so you can see if they
can step in it
yeah what what what what like doorways
and stuff you just put it so you can
tell if they like stepped in it oh what
was oh did the light turned off eh it
was me probably out the door
come back here okay okay okay
uh Nancy Martinez I'm going downstairs
Nancy this is a nice house Nancy Nancy
Martinez
don't kill me Nancy
what is that oh that's what a weird
Channel book Nancy
Nancy Martina 's
what is she having friends
I found it I found her
she has a nice nice mustache nice Monaco
I like the hairstyle aristocrat
s because it's really your families
you're so fancy
Franca she likes he works alone or in
groups oh yeah right alone that one's
that yeah oh God I don't want to be
alone I like don't see anywhere that's
like lower temperature though
what the hell maybe Nancy what
but there are some ghosts and have
nothing to do with temperature right no
but at least the temperature like drops
down a little bit at least
Journal if you want to go start
searching through your journals to see
what evidence
oh yeah
oh yeah fingerprints
uh
um
MF level five
so I do have to hold V the whole time in
order to talk okay yes yes
but some
uh yeah
there's what ah you were so far away I
couldn't hear you he was walking all
right
tuba
cookies I've been using the
walkie-talkie the whole time is that
what is that how it is no one is using
the walkie-talkie right now
I feel like we didn't bring enough
useful items
oh hello
[Music]
Nancy Martinez you saw suck you'll be
alone forever Nancy where are you come
on kill me try me try me I'm not a
chicken I'm a phoenix no matter how many
times you kill me I'll be alive again
not unlike you Nancy You're Dead Forever
you
sorry
Nancy be mad
but I was just so you know I'm not doing
this for fun this is you actually kind
of apparently the game reacts when you
swear at the ghost
oh really even swear words okay yeah
they want us to swear but don't worry
you will say so rich so you don't have
to swim
Martinez are you tall oh yeah oh yeah
are you a murderer
Nancy Martinez
yeah
[Music]
I saw her I'm gonna I'm leaving I'm
leaving okay I'm leaving I'm leaving
I'm leaving too
I'm gonna check out Saturday you know
for security purpose
oh my God
okay I have a point out last like this
no no she was like only there for a
second for like half a second
she was standing was that the question
where she was standing
um where it was oh God I don't remember
where once I am it happened so fast oh
my God I think it was um where was it
what where
um bedroom bedroom blue bedroom blue
bedroom
Oh that's oh yeah that's here how do I
place the salt though I was trying to
figure it out but I can't
this room
um
[Music]
wow
Nancy's a baby how old are you
Nancy are you a baby
oh yeah it doesn't matter if we step
into the salt oh does that salt not pick
it up
I would assume Nancy wouldn't understand
what we're saying then
Nancy's a baby
[Music]
I'm so scared
I don't want it done Nancy Nancy Lolly
[Music]
oh
okay I'm leaving I hear somebody's EMF
too
she stepped in it
for me too what now
say write it down that's uh that's ghost
footprint we have to write that down
write it down
oops
whoops
Victor hello am I still alive
someone dead the check is still alive
let me I'll check up I'll check right
now nope we're all alive okay as long as
I hear you in game I think you guys are
alive
yeah okay
okay who who is supposed to be in the
truck right now I said Iris
[Music]
the chickens here huh
I could I could see I could see I'm the
driver I'm the driver I can stay in the
truck
in there
hey Martinez write in the book The
Lights just flashed is that a sign too
it's playing around oh yes probably I
think so oh god
um
how old are you are you girls even at
the right room because like isn't she
gonna what is that why is that flashing
again is this you're gonna be in the
room where she where I saw her and she
walked over
salt yeah you scared I don't like this
little boy
Auntie Martinez can you read and write
are you literate
Nancy I think we don't sacrifice
somebody she has to be alone right so
Iris Would you like to um
walk around alone nominate
we should we should we should vote we
should vote we we let's go
live English
this is bullying
all right tiger get in the champ show
What You're Made Of all right
okay
let's let's leave her in there and see
what happens
she needs some alone time with the ghost
don't forget to call her Nancy Martinez
is her name
[Laughter]
we don't know where she is right oh yeah
don't worry
well maybe you're dead then
she wants to come play with you
all right
it's okay
okay
[Laughter]
it's just like ASMR she wants to learn
ASMR from you Iris
Nancy
are you here
I'm totally here
in the video camera we can set that up
I think ourselves
I dropped it dropped it oh
tripod okay bringing tripod yeah we have
one standing somewhere in the trunk
getting it really slowly really slowly
there it is
I try pod
let's go get some action shall we
alrighty how's it look oh dear
ghost seems to be active right now uh
well like
are you okay
okay
um here I am oh my God uh I'm just gonna
place it where don't go
what
problem oh oh okay okay
the door closes automatically when the
ghost hunts right so that's like really
scary oh my God
with some prank huh prankster
prank gorillas
moving really quickly or
okay anyone else has to go in alone I'll
go in I'll go in does anybody
uh
one more phone okay
the EMF though because we have a photo
so okay
okay
let's look at this
apex predator you're not gonna lose to
us you're not gonna lose to a baby ghost
B
there wasn't any freezing temperature so
I think we can roll that out
um
is it possible to switch cameras
training
videos
[Applause]
that program is pronounced or the city
I mean until until like last year I
think I realized last year
I thought it was on the city
in the room
good photo bad photo
[Applause]
being a prince yes
if you press J and go to the very last
section
uh so we have fingerprints and uh what
else do we have
activities a little higher than usual
do we have a ghost riding no we have
ghost orb I was wondering we have like
nothing what the hell this ghost is so
boring
[\h__\h] a little bit more like outside in
the hallway you guys put a book there
okay
um book is in journal our book is in
something else
over there I think I'm in trouble
ah I i i oh
don't die
you saw her I see girls feet hide and be
quiet don't die whatever you do don't
join the Dead
crossed out
oh
is that
okay
yeah let's just
so oh dear
um but it hasn't hunted yet right that's
not the things that we've seen is not
called hunting or is it is that hunting
yeah hunting is like when everything is
locked oh yeah and the Bloods are
flickering and turning off that probably
means it's just gonna hunt soon because
we haven't had it yet so I don't want to
be in there
um you know Saturday is really low and
doesn't even go up anymore why not
even though she's eating music doesn't
go up you have to shoot did she eat some
more pills sanity pills yeah shall We
join
or
yeah
another activity is pretty high
watch out
yeah
seven right now it's going down a little
bit
okay
oh oh the lights are off the lights are
off
turn off oh [\h__\h]
oh doors open door's open
she keeps turning the lights on and off
in that one room
I'm just gonna um
be in this room a little bit
and um I guess experience
is feeling a little bit
uh
You're Gonna Keep talking
so scary
are you here
Nancy Martinez
hello Nancy Martinez
Nancy welcome to the afterlife how is it
uh how's it going how's the food here
where do you guys see his favorite box
this thing there
Nancy Martinez
what what do you mean to touch the door
use the radio I don't have the radio
anymore I dropped it somewhere
spray books is the radio who's inside
the closet where did I put it
in there
how old are you
baby
yep okay
Nancy Martinez myself
Nancy Martinez
I feel like some kind of pressure of
having to like go out there and look at
everything that you girls are doing but
was there always a doll in this bathtub
they're always a doll in the bathtub no
that's probably not no there's there's a
doll in the bathtub now that's not
normal I'll take a picture I have one
more picture left yeah it's right it's
right here ah also I just yeah
oh God
I'm your teeny teeny twos
wait can we put that in the journal
a fingerprint and now we can kind of see
which one it could be oh okay let's see
wait was that photo
no either a Banshee or a revenant
um
cute box
fingerprints yeah hiding from the river
will travel a significantly faster speed
when hunting a victim well you know we
could make it even clearer if we see how
it hunts a victim that would be a make
it very clear voice
[Music]
I see you
hiding in that closet
let's just just try it out and then go
to another house it's probably safer we
don't want to die right yeah we gotta we
don't want to die we gotta make more
money I'm pretty sure we're pretty sure
about it yeah yeah Banshee probably
already would have haunted
so it must be a revenant
yeah yeah the other bedroom the big
bedroom where the the EMF five was
reading oh yeah we should probably put
the book down there you want to put the
book down there again all you can guess
and you can go on to another map
up to you Captain I'm totally up for
guessing because look at Innes inner
sanity
was in there the longest though if I
chosen the lighthouse in the third ah
you're not scared of anything huh
yeah I was just just chilling all right
if we all put Revenant in the back of
the journal then we should be all right
yeah right right right Iris you have it
everyone good
I'm doing it now okay I've also put in
the the the the
um evidences that uh you have
fingerprints and emfont were there three
there was no it's fingerprints level
five none okay
oops
special fingerprints Emma ready ready
yeah ghost gorillas
let's see let's see let's see what was
it
oh
wait but there wasn't like a freezing
temperatures
I guess we didn't find it yeah I guess
we didn't find them
damn we suck let's do another one
okay
all right uh
oh man
wow we suck
it's all right next time we're gonna be
more
uh attentive
willing to put ourselves
we can bring how can we bring more we
can bring more because we made money off
that last uh thingy so
um
yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna add flash okay
[Music]
motion sensor
okay never mind that's expensive
um do we have a thermometer
okay I'll put in my thermometer
um I put in my strong flashlight I can
buy I have salt
I can buy more stuff I grabbed a head
mounted camera
what do we need I'm just playing
basketball wait but we need a swimsuit
fix
do you want the delicious answer I can
buy it I bought a crucifix
do we have a Spirit Box
yeah oh we do yes okay
I'll put in my motion sensor
oh yeah
I brought a tripod
Oh I thought I did
um video camera for the camera it was
really good enough right
I think so about Five Guys we need we
need one more flashlight oh okay watch
my head mounted camera
you're sure all right we got two GoPros
now
vlogger time okay okay we got a lot of
stuff now we should be able to get the
next ghost come on come on
okay okay okay so for the job we have
prison
uh bully still Farmhouse and Edgefield
Street house
Farmhouse Farmhouse is the one that's
like the two stories right yeah
Farmhouse is good let's do Farmhouse
that one's scary
Farmhouse yes are there animals in The
Farmhouse chickens lots of chickens oh
yes
okay okay ready out
oh ready I hope it's time to hunt some
ghosts
[Music]
yosho
okay watch what you were saying the
ghosts are listening yes I
I am always careful of what I say
totally
okay head mounted camera doco
wait is it already on my head
is it all right
the EMF reader prevented the ghost from
hunting with the crucifer thanks
that's cute all right
crucifix
[Music]
Lisa Thomas let's take some things
what is that flashlight is that much
smudge smudge stickies
I don't know how to use them though
uh I'm an EMF and a thermometer does
somebody want one of these oh yeah I
think the thermometer and EMF okay I'm
not taking those things how long can
carry the voices me
yeah yeah okay what's that
oh I think that's the motion sensor
you can probably set it up to the okay
okay okay okay okay
so Lisa Thomas
is to respond to everyone you should be
able to use its name to anger and again
you make sure to uh-huh wait everybody
it's not a camera doesn't mean it
doesn't matter
oh head mounted camera
peace out
oh boy
oh God
hope that didn't break
man
[Music]
oh never was in this house before
eat
let's go
not that scary
awesome
rustical house raise the top raise the
Thomas yeah
a drinker apparently
what's considered a low temperature
this is kind of comfy oh
nice sofa
leather sofa
they should get a paint job
I like the wooden look yeah it's really
easy
[Music]
Thomas
where do I put this thing here
I think it was me
it's good time
turn it on oh is it how do I
how do I turn it down
Nissan
oh
how do you say I'm gonna kick your butt
again
speak into it okay
give us a Time
how do I place it thank you okay
[Music]
hello hello hello how
does this work you said Thomas
inside oh
motion sensor but this motion sensor my
motion too
all right all right well placed it
is it the wrong thing
okay
where are the girls where are the girls
are they upstairs is anyone upstairs
hello hello
oh I don't hear the voices anymore
oh you're here okay a far away I think
[Music]
hello
he's in here how do you know he's in
there
shall I talk Lisa Thomas hi what's up
girls
looking beautiful tonight what's the
makeup brand you're using could you tell
me please also I really love that like
that um antique rustical look you got
going on in your apartment
um
uh you don't like me too please uh uh I
I'm so sorry I know you were looking
forward to the whole console debut
tonight I'm so sorry it will happen soon
I promise I promise you all she is
coming ASAP right Too Young no no don't
worry let's evolve don't it's definitely
here
it's Thomas Lisa have a computer though
or uh
[Music]
does anyone have a photo camera
beautiful hand
I do not have it no I don't have one
either should I bring it oh my god
oh yeah okay we shall stay uh Lisa
Thomas
hello
it's me Lisa has Cali not picked you up
yet what's up with that is it uh is it
because she's on the vacation and you're
waiting for someone to pick you up Mommy
can't help you with that
oh I've been holding come on V I've been
holding me while I've been uh talking to
her
yeah
Lisa Thomas
hey hey hey it was on just a moment ago
though
Lisa did she move it down
does it go higher when she hears me or
or
oh there's another thing she moved oh
God please Thomas
give us a sign yeah
[Music]
Lisa Thomas
number means nothing we
give us
a sign from us
it's Thomas Lisa Lisa
Thomas
what does that mean
Lisa tell me
where are you
Lisa Thomas
what's your favorite color
where am I
Thomas what's your type
and why is it Irish
Lisa
who's your OC
where are you Lisa Thomas where are you
brought the camera where oh
she Lisa Thomas why are you taking a
[\h__\h] right here right now yeah we have
better things to do Mr Thomas get out of
the toilet
it
we said Thomas Lisa Thomas
oh is that the face I don't know what
you're using that's knife was a Thomas
your face looks beautiful
um
Lisa Thomas you're making me feel very
hot
so
what is that
you said Thomas Lisa Thomas where
Lisa
that's this way who are you why are you
Lisa Thomas
I'm gonna go bring more items inside
where am I
your camera oh energy drink
anymore yes yes
I'm just trying to find my way out now
scary
where's the way out here Lisa has a big
family
Lisa
sadness
you are the lucky winner of one million
US dollars
what is that this house is so big I
don't know where is the exit oh God
where's the exit to this house it's so
big follow me
the accident is on the low lowest ground
fluid
looking for hatchimal
wait where's the exit
oh my God
that's the accent oh there we go
Lisa Thomas is
it all makes sense now
okay do I even need this
eight nine Celsius right here
I'm in the hallway
I'm outside the room we were in wait 12
all right there okay
is this useful
no joke
oh
uh how do I use those much stickies I
did not
does someone know how to use that like
when to use them when I already know
where he is or
right Mouse
turn the lights off
she did something
it's eight right here
oh
oh she's touching it
what do I do with this much things yeah
boy am I purifying the house
I'm so scared
oh where's the Thomas
[Music]
yes what's up Lisa
ASA Thomas right in this book how you
doing
I'm pricing of do they only work one
time
you don't like temperatures are jumping
everywhere they're already used
crap
I'm gonna burn this house down now start
a fire today don't stop don't stop just
go in your own way
foreign
don't bring them back
give us a sign
is there anything I should be looking
out for from the truck Lisa Thomas Lisa
Thomas Lisa Thomas
Lisa Thomas
Lisa Thomas Lisa Thomas where are you
wait 30 minutes
Lisa Thomas where are you why are we so
bad at signing ghosts
wait so Thomas would you like a cup of
tea
would you like to share a cup of cake
would you tell me how do you drink your
tea
what happened what happened what
happened
oh I hear water what's happening what
happened what happened what happened
right now
it's very high it's at 10. Lisa is on
the move I know I know
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I'm gonna mute myself on Discord so
they don't hear me
um
I died gracefully and beautiful
I have to say that
clip I died gracefully
take a picture of me I don't know
well I hope you girls can clear the case
without me
let's try to follow them what's that
noise
he didn't get a turtle any any of the
other girls though huh oh no only me oh
it's happening again it's happening what
are they doing hide hide hi girls
is that gonna work
hiding there
foreign
[Music]
alive
oh God where can we hide oh my God it's
so dark I can't see anything oh my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's just irons
oh can we have a double death oh no oh
no well unless I'm doing a good job as
the camera girl oh you're next go down
wait a second is it yeah oh no we ain't
the ghost are we good
oh no wait what did you think wait I
can't tell the difference between ghosts
oh God oh God
I'm hearing things oh no am I being
haunted yeah
go back
[Music]
she was random can I still do something
though
I just want to know
good photo dirty water dead body
what could it be
do we even have any hints
I don't know of any at least
only hope hope hope is left but do we
have hope are you a ghost right yo ghost
uh where did Iris go Iris you dead
Iris we have fingerprints
okay
wow that does not help us much
welp
oh oh here's another accent huh
ooh spoopy oh
that's Iris let's follow Iris
Iris
you gotta have some conversations with
yourself for your stream's sake please
I I always feel free to talk to yourself
okay okay
ah no no no I'm not okay but let's okay
what am I supposed to do I'm really
scared about going inside we have uh one
evidence right now which is fingerprints
we would like you to get us some more
evidences please okay how am I gonna do
that how am I gonna do that how is she
gonna do that girls good or maybe ghost
scooter can help us as well let's try to
clear this with the ghost town I don't
know maybe use the Spirit Box try to
talk to it I think we're screwed however
where is the Spirit Box currently
think someone dropped it somewhere near
Kiara man I was probably mean I'm just
gonna voice join voice chat so I don't
have to keep pressing V okay okay who
cares at this point
yeah
I probably dropped it somewhere
over there okay okay okay go upstairs
[Music]
oh oh did I have it in my hand at that
point
okay coming in
[Music]
huh I'm in I'm in chat
oh the
ghosts
because of something in the game
oh God I think we're being haunted by
the ghost of Amelia Watson the host of
vacation
smells like stale french fries now
um
[Applause]
[Music]
are you dead yet
wow
[Laughter]
we got we got 10 bucks though we got 10
bucks it's like a 10 pity bugs
pity money here's some salt oh man wow
that was um
um we we did uh underwhelming really bad
in both cases
belly yeah with it so we got some uh we
got some moments there yeah we haven't
won yet which is not great but
uh I don't know
what they do
um
what do we say one more one more
question
maybe an easy one yeah
another awesome man
actually
yeah I have a lighter oh my God
I still have 175 dollars so I can buy
candles I can buy salt so much sticks
um oh God so much money wait a second
you have money
how much does Ena have 100 bucks
I only have 17. that's a lot of money
too I have like a 150 I can buy a bunch
of stuff what do I need to buy what
no no wait
um
um flashlight I'll buy two
I'll buy a flashlight too yeah
oh my God
um do we have a book thing
do we need a camera uh I'm sorry but we
have one yet um
we have photo camera we have video
camera we have a book we have a
thermometer we might
uh no
I don't know
yeah we have one should I buy a Spirit
Box
we have a Spirit Box okay maybe a
flashlight or a strong flashlight I I
put in a strong flashlight I can put in
another flashlight oh I see I can put it
on flashlight I'll do the flashlight
okay
um what else do you want
um
I have a thermometer
salt so I'll buy some salt yeah why not
it is soft yeah oh wait we already have
some salt
oh or is that the one that you just
bought let's look at maybe why is this
salt so expensive now we have two salts
it's robbery should never be that is it
iodized
can we do it never mind I don't have
enough for that okay that's it I think
we got everything
uh that's a golden oh that's a good one
easy map two that we have is a kinda
it was the president wants the high
school
oh dear
no no no no can we um like reset that
somehow I gotta leave and like yeah yeah
okay because then next one would be Iris
I think no
um g g has to leave now that's me do we
have different choices
Roadhouse or Tanglewood Street
yeah either of those is good
um all right I'm in well let's do this
one right three of a Roadhouse two-story
four-bedroom house with a basement
and I can't toggle the difficulty anyway
so it's gonna be an amateur just like
Baby Mario Motors all right put in our
stuff oh I have to put in the stuff
again okay one more of that
one strong flashlight and a thermometer
yeah not okay ready I am ready baby
ready
yay
[Music]
um let's see what what did we do bad
last time what can we improve
accordingly before starting the
investigation
yeah so this girl is called Helen Garcia
uh
alone so we get some alone time again
um
no did we
got an average Saturday below 25 let's
go take this yes
all right everyone take your items uh
I took that EMS thingy and the
flashlight and I'll take some sauce
okay I got a thermometer too so we can
spill it up next too
nice
open up
okay the Ghostbusters let's go
a beautiful house oh
well that Ivy's gonna be a pain in the
ass in about five years nice
neighborhood
this is the house she died in I think
that one time remember all those months
ago
that you girls talked about I don't even
remember that one specifically you
blocked it from your mind yeah it was a
traumatic voice he's blocked it
all righty and what are we doing uh this
thing here what was the name again
something Garcia ah Helen Garcia Helen
Helen Helen
helenga
oh my God oh my God Ellen Garcia where
are you
hello Helen
Helen Garcia oh another door
seat
I want Garcia
or something
what does the EMS thing say again
how high should it be
temperatures oh
okay so now I think it's 0.94
Helen Garcia you have a beautiful house
where are you
what what
together
what never mind that's when I have
something else I I have a fur moment to
firmative thermometer
but it says EMS
service
Emergency Medical Service
okay
yes as well or like em5
EMS
okay whatever I guess it's just the
temperature that matters I left his room
oh my God
oh nice chairs
in the bottom
low temperature and where there's a bone
here
where's the camera I don't have a camera
I just grabbed the camera I did catch it
in 4k just now though
of the bone that's like here
nice oh bone yeah is there a dog if
someone just ate some kfp
be good
uh hell Helen um
Helen Garcia is that her name no wait
let me mixing something up
well Helen Kellen I think that's right
can you write Helen
have you received the education to write
Ellen
draw us a picture Helen Helen Helen
Garcia Helen Garcia we don't want to
fail a third game so please help us out
here Helen Garcia where are you
I found it I found what
about him
in the kitchen
apparently I found it how low was it let
me try to go back where was the kitchen
second floor are we
oh down here is downstairs around here
where did I find the dining room okay
wait I'm gonna try this one right now
[Music]
oh you have one too oh my God
oh okay okay let's go
oh yeah it's really low
hold on should I put some salt here I
put some salt here
I promise
unstable
that oh now I have no more Ellen Garcia
oh guys please
please we have some more items that I
can use
well if it's cold there doesn't mean
she's always there it did say though
that she reacts to people being alone so
if we think she's there shouldn't
someone be there alone
video camera I guess no one set up a
video camera yet oh what is that thing
I'll take that and I'll take that
not freezing oh
how's this going alrighty
Spirit Box is this Spirit Box this is a
Spirit box right
sorry guys I'm just talking to the chat
don't worry
don't worry about me
yo
okay
I have my crucifix in hand
how are our sanity levels doing oh good
they're good okay girls everyone leave
this room right now talk to the ghost
I'll talk to the ghost okay
we can do it
I don't need a crucifix of a phoenix
hello
um
maybe yeah okay okay yeah it's got an
AOE so if I stay here here it will
protect me
maybe but how can she run into the
building
um
we're right outside the door uh Helen
guys
hello welcome to whole talk where are
you
Helen Garcia did you watch the newest
episode of oh the lights are switching
are you that's you forgot
who said who said fool me
Garcia
this is the famous Phoenix takanasi
Kiara I know you wanted autograph I want
one to Helen Garcia hello
[Music]
where are you Helen Garcia Ellen Garcia
Helen Garcia oh she wrote something
girls
why are there some crazy signs
it's like uh
conspiracy theory
okay I can't I think
so so we have we have low temperature
and some ghost riding can can we go now
you know low enough temperature to be
written in the book or do you have to
like it I think it does not low enough
someone said that
hello
hello Garcia
[Music]
what up did she walk into salt
she also walked in salt oh yeah please
join me now I don't want to be alone
anymore
should I have turned off the flashlight
Mouse click
we have
uh
ghost orb no fingerprints we do have
right and then we have ghost riding
and add this picture to I have the
picture of the bone yeah that doesn't
really help us
okay so did we not see fingerprint
somewhere
I don't think so maybe I'm mixing
something up okay
all right then uh well
um
yeah I put the video camera down but
I don't know I'll see if um
maybe I should reposition it though
I'll just carry it because then you can
tell me yeah
inside right if you see something
oh you're against the wall or something
right now
Helen has a very nice handwriting you
don't see anything right now
someone else
um okay
it's perfect
Helen Garcia put it down do you see
something now yeah
do all lights have to be off in order to
see a ghost orb
okay
Sofia hello Helen Garcia where are you
Ellen Garcia
Ellen Garcia Helen Garcia where are you
Helen Garcia Give Me A Sign
up
[Music]
Ellen Garcia
are you here Kevin Garcia
number nine
are you here Helen Garcia
give us a sign
ificant
okay Helen Garcia are you here am I
alone in here
hello I'm here okay
where are you
Helen Garcia
make content how do you like Japan
Helen Garcia where are you
Ellen Garcia
Luigi board I found a lower in the board
but what does it look like
a Ouija board
apparently the chat saw a Luigi boy
oh
you guys are talking about does that
help us
okay talk to us
that's the Ouija board how do we use it
I don't know we gotta talk to her just
just have to be alone
probably
um
Luigi board
Helen Garcia you like Louisiana Mario
banner I think girl Luigi is better
oh yeah
Helen Garcia where are you okay ah there
we go you look like caveman sliding over
fire
you've ever seen talk oh yeah uh can you
step one step back go down
okay
it's more
Helen Garcia how old are you
Helen Garcia
where are you
five zero zero
Helen guys where are you
does that mean on zeroth floor
Maybe
she she said she's zero years old Luna
Luna
yeah
we're trying to Bubble okay thank you
Helen guys I guess that's all she's
gonna tell us
oh
my God
why why is someone dead oh no oh no
I am not here I'm not here I just saw
someone die
the Christmas bro
we died
uh I think Iris died
can we open the door oh wait okay I can
open it Oh I thought it was cool
all right uh let's let's leave ladies
let's let's leave
I think we got some stuff okay
did we
what did we actually get
wait girls girls
yeah I'm still here I think I saw it
yeah I saw her die as well but I didn't
see the ghosts
okay that's two
oh no yeah you know stay with me you
know don't you dare die on me
oh
hey
I'm going to die
okay [\h__\h] again
or did I
no no no no
no no no
no no no no no
[Music]
oh
no
[Music]
windows what the [\h__\h] I don't have time
for you right now and what do I do I
have so many like evidences but like
nothing for my journal
like
wait but wait do I like maybe still know
what's up like wait a second
I guess I'm gonna make again oh my God
yeah so all job board the most common
way of accidentally summoning your ghost
is with ultra board so you may come and
go and be careful if you choose to use
one and two okay that doesn't tell me
anything
um hello hi ghosties
uh so Yokai when hunting you can only
hear when we were talking your Yokai
while I'm gonna increase his Gentry
box so it's probably not something that
has freezing temperatures because we
didn't have freezing temperatures yeah
Yokai yeah I just read that one yeah
when hunting a yoga can only hear voices
close to it
talking here Yokai will anger it
increases chance of attacking we didn't
talk yeah it's weird but I didn't talk
when it found me wait I could still
because the camera is on I could still
maybe try to see some ghost orbs but
[Music]
um
the girls were so fast it wiped out
three of us in like 30 seconds yeah
um I don't see any oh hey I just saw a a
fork fly around
oh Paranormal Activity maybe a
poltergeist then oh she's trying to eat
something
she's hungry
apologize can throw huge amount of
objects at once and Poltergeist is
almost ineffective in an empty room
Spirit boxes
noisy ghost riding
yeah we have ghost riding oh yeah
Contour
to move at faster speeds that makes
sense I mean it was not freezing but it
was a lower temperature and it was
hunting very fast
that's true that's true oh and if we all
died you girls all died in the same area
which was a colder area right
right
oh try new thing I think we didn't see
fingerprints though
what Spirit Box did let's see something
with Spirit Box I forgot what that is
that's the talking box oh did I have any
kind of like I I held it in my hand but
I don't really know how that stuff works
like did I have any reaction no Spirit
Box reaction from the funnel okay then
because I had it in my hand the whole
time I was talking so much with it so I
guess that's a nope maybe it is a hunter
[Music]
because it was moving object a great
space Oh yeah being more active will
make the only easier
I
shouldn't really risk going inside again
right I should just like guess it
there there are definitely
[Music]
oh
um
ah this is difficult
this is difficult so either handle or
Oni Maybe
you didn't go through no freezing
temperature no
Spirit Box EMF level five wouldn't we
have seen that uh if it was EMF level
five
I I guess
um did they change this game
I've never seen a hunter before
I I would say hunter
to attack often during cold weather
Aloha temperatures can cause the hunter
to move and faster speed it just kind of
makes a little bit sense
yeah you girls are dead but you can
still do the ghost type guessing right
so
Hunter
yeah this that the hunt was new right it
didn't uh exist before right
yeah because it likes to hunt too yeah
ghost riding there you go on to ghost
riding is the only evidence right that
we actually found
all right
man I don't remember them being so
tricky to interact with yeah I don't
remember that either we were in the
amateur right now too
yeah go back in I'm not going back in
there All My Friends Are Dead you have
one percent sanity Kiara squeeze it out
less drops yes between zero and two
percent nope
um I'm gonna close the door now
uh did you did everyone put in what they
wanted to put in
yeah there's no more Fork the fork is
gone
yeah okay I'm closing to finished eating
let's go first win and round of the
night oh come on baby yeah
please please please please please
please come on we need one win come on
please
a Revenant really
okay
isn't that what you guys said
[Music]
well that's disappointing what the hell
fingerprints Emma five Wario
well um I mean we found nothing but uh I
think that was still a lot of fun
yeah yeah
wait can you ask your Chad something
yeah hey kfp uh I was trying to remember
the name there's like a similar game to
phasmophobia that came out not too long
ago do you guys remember what it's
called kfp is it the Egyptian one
don't I don't think it is I think
there's another one
a ghost hunters corpse
yeah that's it it's not devour no no
devour is where you like you have to
collect goats I think Labyrinth right
they all seem to say no time to Corp
I think it is Ghost Hunt Court
oh we might as well try it out someday
and ditch faster for me because we ain't
finding any ghosts in fact
the game it's the game it's not us
well I hope you girls had fun and uh I
want to say thank you uh for
um Gathering today with us both Chad and
these ghost girl girls gorilla girls
yeah gorilla Squad yeah
hopefully hello live Council can join us
soon and then we'll have even more fun
together very soon yeah any closing
comments from you girls Iris how was
your first phasmophobia stream
it was fun but it's much harder than I
thought yeah
yeah
no I mean the second time it killed me
it just kind of came all of a sudden I
was like holy holy holy what the what
the beep like it just it just only
showed up all of a sudden I'm just like
what what's that I didn't really get
what was going on yeah yeah but yeah
their hands the ghost hands they look so
they look so dirty they look so dirty
want them to wash their hands okay and
I'll tell them
Iris aren't you uh tomorrow together
with me in the garlic phone call out yes
yeah yeah
as well yeah I know I haven't released a
schedule yet
oh so yeah tomorrow the next stream uh
will be me and Iris and uh two girls
from Whole Life Indonesia and two girls
from Whole Life Japan and I think six
people look alive yeah
yeah granny phone is always so much fun
so I'm looking forward to that uh thank
you enough for the amazing thumbnail
thank you Gua for joining in on the fun
and uh you know we basically played fast
before we are because of you I'm sorry
we didn't reach that new map that you
wanted to do
I mean always fine it's all right they
changed this game something happened
this game is different I haven't played
it in so long
um yeah it seemed a little bit different
but
um maybe we just suck at hunting ghosts
also yes
it's part of the fun you know yeah uh
uh are in the description in case you
haven't subscribed to them for whatever
reason they are in the description uh
thank you everyone for watching I'll
leave it here uh and uh read no super
Giants because I I want to try to go to
sleep early because this was a gorilla
only anyway
um oh yeah I'm gonna be doing some
Nautica in six hours yeah yeah please
wake for holo Council huh
yep that was my original plan big oof
there
wow wow wow thank you so much for the
impromptu collab
send them a little bit with this
collaboration
thank you and in German we
say ah
[Music]
what's up
thank you
foreign
[Music]