[Music]
oh
welcome welcome members
thank you for joining membership
let's start
[Music]
kiki hello
good morning good evening good day
wherever wherever you are
whenever wherever
[Music]
thank you for all the people who joined
in the membership right away
guys first of all have you seen
uh the new uh the new
memphis member emote which is
fried chicken the one that i'm holding
i was thinking by the way papa papa gave
this to me
thank you papa he gave me
a png of my chicken
that i'm holding right now um
i was thinking like people asked me um
to make a light stick
for my karaoke streams and i thought
that would be really cute
but how about we just treat the chicken
as a light stick so imagine
one day we'll be having a concert
maybe somewhere over the world maybe if
my dream comes true
and then i'll be on stage and you guys
will be in the audience
instead of light sticks you'll be
holding
chicken legs in your hands and waving
them around and then
i mean that's really cool because then
you have like a snack
for it for like during the concept
[Music]
of
yeah but that's what that paper is for
it's all good it's all good we will not
get our hands too dirty unless you also
eat the paper
and i don't think you guys like to eat
paper
yeah i think that it totally works as a
light stick we don't need
another light stick do we
don't you want to use that don't you
want to spam that chicken
when we do karaoke strips
soda
i think it's the perfect lipstick i
couldn't ask for any other line stick
korean johnny come picking up
the show it's just so fitting
actually i was thinking of this since
the beginning when i was
uh when i was thinking of what emotes to
do i was thinking of like
making a a chicken light stick just like
this one
so inside bgm is off oh god damn it
is this too loud
tell me earlier
well i mean it was early enough thank
you
is it fine now oh i hope it's not too
quiet
perfect volume nice
okay so now that i have introduced to
you the chicken emote chicken leg is it
a chicken
leg
chicken it's not a chicken wing this is
a chicken leg
is it a chicken tie i wonder what it is
drumstick drumstick drums yeah that's
not what i was looking for
the chicken drumstick emote now you the
members
are able to use this magnificent emote
so i think we can move on today
actually i haven't done any like normal
talking streams
uh up until now so i thought
today is the day i had a
long day and to relax
i thought maybe let's just talk
i hope that's not uh too boring for you
guys
and i'm actually like i
i'm weirdly nervous about doing
a talking only stream like usually i
would say i'm a good talker
but we we don't know each other that
well
yet do we so there's like not
not really so much that we
can talk about with each other yet i
think
uh so i was like really nervous about
doing a stream where we just talk
so therefore i think we'll just decide
on some topics
to give us a guideline of what we can
talk about
and the topics you will choose
easy isn't it talk about cali
i always talk about cali let's try to
not talk about cali today
okay so is there anything you guys
want me to talk about maybe something
that we can go into
deep but maybe nothing about cali or
piccolo
uh future streams
that is a topic we can talk about oh
wait this is
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
why do i change that again
[Music]
we're going to change that again center
here
lift okay
but that i guess that we can talk about
that here
[Music]
potato pc no i don't have a potato pc
potatoes will you play against impact
for now no unfortunately
anyway anime i haven't i actually i
haven't been
watching anime for a long time
so uh there is actually not much i could
talk about again like except for like
older anime
i guess
something now we can go deep into
how do you learn so many languages i
mean i guess we can talk about languages
oh if you guys want to hear about that
people always ask me about languages
minecraft holy and separate am i only
i mean that that ends with one question
yes we're doing it
that answers one answer yes we're doing
it
pokemon yeah i already got it it's
already there
your travels you mean like where i've
been to i've been to a lot of places
maybe maybe we can maybe maybe maybe
maybe i don't know how deep i want to go
into that
uh yeah actually i have talked about my
first impression of the holy yen members
in my japanese only stream so we could
do it here in english today
because you guys kind of missed out of
that out on that hello
first impression
[Music]
i i don't know what to say about
gangster impact i'm not playing it
i know all of you are playing it
rosa i did not try to get her yet
can you speak bird language
food talk about food german food
well that's a really wide topic food
ah who are you playing to follow not
gonna
rosa obviously and w
i wanna roll for w but she's not coming
yet right i haven't really been paying
that much attention to arc knights
recently
have you played catch an impact in your
free time no
no time i know everyone's playing it
it looks so nice i wanna play against
in fact but don't stream i'm gonna play
it on stream
oh what happened to your girlfriend
thank you for asking about my pen
some of you may know i have been looking
for my pen
for the longest time and uh it was uh
still absent
in the which collab i guess it was the
second
yeah in the second collab i still didn't
have it
my pen and then i needed it
for making emotes so i got really really
desperate and i kept looking all over my
room
and i looked under my bed i looked
everywhere i thought i looked everywhere
and
then i ordered a new pen
and one day after i ordered the new pen
i found the old pen
was it behind you here no no it was
it was it was in one of my bags because
i remembered once i found it i have a
ton of bags
i remember once i found it ah
recently i took my tablet outside
to another place to work with it in a
different place
and that's why i brought the pen with me
and then when i came back home
i took out the tablet but i didn't take
out the pen
god damn it hobbies music artist
i mean we kind of talked about hobbies
and music in my
debut stream
yeah i watched that the live um
announcement of
the live the live stream of the pokemon
news so i obviously
also watched the mb i watched the live
news thingy
live i watched it live
five favorite features about that i like
about myself about like
my looks you mean
[Music]
maybe maybe
i do want to watch a movie soon with you
guys but probably only members
how am i doing i always i already always
talk too much about how i'm doing i
always talk too openly about how i'm
doing
weird childhood stories eh you know how
my memory is
you guys know how good my memory is it's
horrible i don't remember anything from
my childhood
horrible i hate horror movies there's
nothing to talk about when it comes to
horror movies i don't know
anything about horror movies i watched
maybe one horror movie
what was it about
i don't even know i don't even know
animal crossing or lap life that's such
a weird choice you're giving me
it's a game and uh and i i guess well i
love like there's
probably a game for me too but it was
more like an
such a anime different weird choice
but i would choose animal crossing
your favorite idols mom
kind of talked about that before
[Music]
family is adorable thank you it was
drawn by yuna
on twitter she did a bunch of cute
artworks from
like me like fan nights he's so cute
everything she does is so cute
like the first one i retweeted it uh
when
when i saw that the first time i died oh
my god can we talk about you now
can we talk about you
caps lock art of me
okay there we go
caps lock well she'll be very happy
i like to make people happy she was so
yesterday she was so yesterday when she
was happy what
she was so happy when yesterday in the
minecraft
stream i mentioned her art
for like a second and then she was like
enjoyed that she was like
okey dokey
well then let's get started let's let's
see how how far we get
um and now i cannot cook i mean i can
cook some things
some some things but the things that i
can cook
that i can cook i think i have mustard
but it's not very much i can make
fried chicken
i can make french toast
i can make schnitzel it's a german food
austrian german food i can make
schnitzel
which is basically the same you make it
the same way the way you make
a fried chicken so not a big difference
um i can make
spaghetti boyonese
wait that's probably how you say english
i can make
spaghetti carbonara and spaghetti with
meat sauce i can make those from scratch
what else can i make i can i can make
curry
which is a thai curry and japanese curry
um yes i mean it's very italian birds
[Music]
um
the most favorite word my teacher
in italian classes used she would always
start her sentence with
aloha
[Music]
here i go again
how could i resist you
yeah oh that's such a good movie and
such a good song
yeah okay so future streams pokemon
um the most recent
pokemon game sorry and shield
obviously very fitting for me i have
played it privately
when it came out and but then the
the expansion pack came right guys
the the expansion pack
without what's it called
the what's it called
aisle of armor
and something with tundra
so i have not played that isle of armor
one i have not played that one
i also have not played obviously because
it's not out yet there's no
the snowy one i'm thinking i don't know
i kind of want to play it on stream
but would you want me to start from the
very very beginning
or would you want me to
like take the the game
safe that i used before
so we can just start with the dlc the
beginning
oh that's such a long journey you mean
from the very beginning are you sure
don't start over
use your old tip i thought that would be
smarter because most of you probably
already have seen
uh playthrough or or have played it
yourself
of the whole first you know the original
game
and uh yeah i thought it would be better
to just do the dlc
and yeah we have some other projects
going on too
all right well i mean i'm i still gotta
check
if i can even i think it should be fine
right
other whole live members played the new
pokemon too right
i saw it i think i'm pretty sure i saw
it they played sword and shield didn't
they
so it should be fine
i'm sure they know
okay then i think we have the permission
oh then maybe we started the dlc soon
after
she i'll check i'll check if i can just
use my old save
if not we'll start all over i hope
that's okay too
um tonight
[Music]
hi
hello
welcome welcome another is nice luck the
one where
you uh once your pokemon dies you're not
supposed to
revive it is that the one you mean
is that the did i get cause i heard up a
bunch of these modes
and they're really interesting they make
it so much more harder
i mean i guess we can do that
but that would be so sad my
my pokemon die a lot i my strategy for
games
is always make sacrifices because i
i don't take i didn't take death that
seriously probably because i die so
often
and i just revive so
the the concept of not being able to
revive
is um strange to me
very strange so hmm
i don't know if i can handle a nuzlocke
and accept it
when my pokemon are dead i i always just
let them
die when i'm in trouble
and just move on to the next pokemon the
problem is also that i
i'm the i'm the kind of a weak ass
pokemon player who does not really still
still doesn't really remember which type
is
effective against which type so
yeah i i just you know play very uh
bad
like oh yeah i can guess the things like
water is good against fire
fire is good against plants
plants is good against water okay that's
all i know that's all i know
oh wait i think electricity
is not good against
earth wait earth
plants plants
[Music]
but electricity is good against water
a ground ground is what i'm agreeing
yeah you know what i mean
electricity is
good against water right okay okay
uh
[Music]
it's dark what's wait don't tell me
what's good against darkness
huh there was a dark type right okay
what's good you can see i have
no idea i have no idea oh
is it is the light wait was there a
light type is a light type good again
fighting
bug in fact see this is something i
cannot remember because it doesn't make
sense for me
why or very ah very yeah that that
that i think i lowkey remember fairy is
good against
dark
what is what is good against fairy dough
mmm see i don't know
um you guys
still ah yeah right right right i think
once i get into the game i might
remember
some of them again but mostly i will
always forget them
that's why my pokemon always die
but i don't care because
i'm used to it that's just how life goes
for me you die
then you get back up again and you die
and you get back up again and you die
and you get back up again yay
but i will consider that
nozzle it would definitely make it much
more interesting and challenging
pokemon is just generally i guess too
easy
and like i guess if i would play it
privately
i would never give myself such a
challenge because i'm like what for
[Music]
how annoying but if uh
if we do it on stream i will maybe do it
yeah did you play kingdom hearts no
never what's your personal favorite
pokemon eh
moltres
is that a good answer is it maltress
is that a good answer
let's just go with that
all right all right and i think that
that's
uh now that is enough for the pokemon
topic but about our future streams
um i think okay so once we get
my stupid elgato working again
then i will continue fire emblem which
will take five million years
but at the same time i think we will
start
uh like when we get to a certain point
in fire emblem i think we will get
started with
xenoblade because i can't wait anymore
i want to play centerwave and in between
yeah i want to play mario kart
and some other games some yeah we also
have to continue
super mario 64. and once we're done with
super mario 64 we'll play super mario
extension
and then we'll play the third one was it
super mario
uh what's the third one is it
it is it all does say galaxy galaxy ah
obviously is what
amma is playing
yeah so i wanna play all of those
because i bought the game i gotta
make the most out of it
yeah but those are all like pretty long
games right
so in between yeah we're gonna have some
mario kart and then what else
i don't know i am minecraft yeah oh
guys yesterday was it yesterday in
minecraft after this dream ended
i wanted to be a good girl and did some
farming because while i'm streaming it
just takes too much time
um so i went to farm a little bit but
then i found
some super cool place with i uh
i i wrote it on twitter but i found a
cool place where we can do some farming
and we can do some exploring either it
has some like
uh tracks and some train tracks
so yeah i was really really really
curious i really had to
hold myself back so i went back to my
apartment in my
cave and then
enderman was there
i was like what the hell and he didn't
seem like he wanted to
get out uh so i was like okay
i'm gonna take my iron sword and i'm
gonna fight you
so it's i i attacked him
but he killed me
so i i panicked i went on twitter
and people gave me many solutions and
the easiest solution
i came up with i didn't come up with but
but you guys
told me was throwing
water at him and it worked so i went
quickly i made a bucket
and i ran to my little pond and outside
of my cave
and then i took the water and then i
came back and then i did a sploosh
and then he was gone
he thinks he's so strong but he's so
scared of water
ridiculous i sploshed him
it's all up on twitter it was really
funny
so then i was finally in peace and then
i continued
growing my farm and my farm is really
big now
it's okay not really really really big
but it has i have lots of wheat
now and um then
the the llama guy the llama guy can buy
the llama guy came by he was like man
and i was like
and uh i said welcome
i don't need anything from you but he
stayed there and then
the llama guy and the wandering merchant
the trader he bugged himself out
he disappeared became invisible
and now the llamas were like in my
wheat field and i put a fence around it
hoping that
now i can keep the llama the guys
apparently still there because like the
lead was like still like
push pulling them and uh they couldn't
get out of my
my field so i just fenced it in so they
can never
yeah yeah but he was still he's still
there because then i i right clicked
the the invisible area of where the lead
was uh pulling from
and i could trade with the invisible
merchant
yeah so he's actually there but he's
just invisible
i wonder if he's still invisible once i
open actually will
the llamas still be there when i fence
them
will the llama still be there when i
open up the game
no yep probably yeah
awesome so yeah i now have a prisoner
a lot of things happened even more
happened because after that
i went to do some uh i'm not fishing i i
went swimming i'm a really good swimmer
now i finally know how to swim
and i've killed a billion fish they're
all mine now
and then i went exploring looking for
um actually i'm not sure what i was
actually looking for i just went
walking walking walking and then i found
a village
a good village a big village it looks so
pretty and so fancy i also showed that
to you
on twitter and then i was like i gotta
keep this for later
but i went inside anyway and i took some
stuff
and uh but i i still left a lot of stuff
[Music]
i put up some torches here and there so
that they don't
get killed and well yeah it's a really
pretty village
uh-huh i was like i wanna live there
because like the houses are so pretty
that's like the prettiest village i've
ever seen
no i'm not talking about in real life
stuff it's minecraft stuff
i did not kill a million fishes in real
life
i did not uh whole i'm not holding a
hostage
llama and trader in real life no
and i did not kill the enderman with
water
in real life no i did not
obviously i'm talking about in-game
but i have to say that um you remember
that mini
mini mini mini village in the desert
that we found in minecraft
it had like some really awesome stuff in
the in the chests
but the new villas that i found it was
like huge but there was basically
nothing
in japanese he would say it was a mural
today
it was like really pretty i want to live
this anyway we're going to go there i
don't know what we can do there but
we're going to go there
and we're going to check out the the the
mine
that i found some people told me that
mines are a bit uh
dangerous for beginners so they can be
they can be
dangerous oh and that you can get lost
really easily
that's probably not good for me so i
gotta do the thing you got you gotta
remember
me guys because i will definitely forget
please remind me
that i should put torches on only one
side
of the the the the the
thing all righty
all right i'm really excited i want to
play minecraft maybe tomorrow i think
maybe tomorrow i'll play minecraft
[Music]
did you hear that did you um
what what do you usually do in those
mines do you just like explore
is there anything special i can get
there i guess like
i guess gold maybe i don't know
explore even the torch string is not
foolproof
we'll be alright diamonds golden apples
there
there are treasure chests oh oh
i want to find the treasure chest oh
it looked really big though the mind
from i mean i didn't really
look at it
i have a feeling it's really big because
and that's the one that i kept on
hearing
while i was mining for hours and hours
and i kept you know how we kept on
hearing some train tracks and i just
couldn't figure out where it came from
but now i finally found it
yay
[Music]
i can't wait to show you everything i
did
i would can you say i'm a good girl for
exploring on my on my free time i mean
probably partially it's also not so good
because i
took away some exciting sightings
and that we could have done but i feel
like if i would have
explored all that in on my stream i feel
like i wouldn't have found those things
because like it's kind of distracting
and i'm when i'm streaming like i'm kind
of out of the place
uh because i'm talking so much and then
i i just like
i have no patience no chill i just keep
running around
but when i did it off stream i was like
really chill
and i for for an hour i was listening to
piccola's bgm tanokitchi
so it was like really really nice and
then i turned it off after an hour
and then i just listened to the
beautiful minecraft
ambience music
it was just so relaxing and i i think i
think i understand
why people play this game now
yeah yeah well
yeah oh yeah but for future streams
besides those
games
[Music]
we recently got permission for a couple
of
new games and one of those
games that i was kind of interested in
that we could start and
if you guys want to see it
but it's a not the typical kind of game
that i would plan
for i probably will suck at it real hard
and yuka and laylee i probably said that
wrong
yuka and laylee
yeah i will suck at that game
but we got permission to play so i
thought of playing
it's uh how do you call these games
platformers is it a platformer
i think it's a platformer
a ukulele ah
ukulele the instrument
that's what their name is trying to
imply oh
they never knew
i never knew
i never noticed
like banjo-kazooie what
lama i mean i know the banjo but what's
kazooie supposed to be
kazoo
hey
wow you gave me two mine explosions
you called me and banjo
and kazuy is ukulele
and a banjo and a kazoo
is
many of the japanese friends did not
know
see it's not only me so if you call me
stupid you're calling them stupid too
and that's kind of rude
we have to be nice to each other in the
chat okay don't call me stupid
if you call me stupid then you're
calling them stupid too
much
[Music]
protect me japanese bros protect me
they're calling me stupid we're stupid
together
[Music]
m
but i think like hmm
that one is hard that i think that's not
so obvious
that's nothing to do with it that is
nothing to do with it oh well
wait was there any other game that i'm
planning to play soon
and i already know i'm playing soon oh
no no no
no no not not at the moment
xenoblade but that's about it
alright let's talk about languages
but wait i want to play a zelda game
sometime soon but wait which zelda games
are available for the switch
besides breath of the wild because i
feel like breath of the wild is kind of
too difficult
for me is it the only breath of the wild
no wait there was one more link's
awakening yeah but
you know i would love to play wind waker
well i guess yeah i guess link's
awakening would be fine too but i
actually i watched the whole playthrough
of links awakening by a certain youtuber
so i already know all about the story
and all that i kind of ruined it for
myself
hyrule warriors but that's like not
really an rpg right
that's like just fighting each other
right
all right wind waker yeah i mean i know
the story of wind waker and so on
but i never played this complaint i
would love to play wind waker
but it's not on on switch
right it's not on switch and right now i
only have a switch
why you guys can see an impact i cannot
play against an impact
no permission i would have played it
otherwise
so now i'm like more like oh which zelda
game am i going to play
f off the path traveler is on my wanting
to playlist
oh well anyway let's keep on moving wait
it's already it's already
44 minutes after i started streaming
how the hell did i do that okay
quick languages what do you want to know
what do you want to know you already
know i speak a lot of languages
what do you want what do you want to
when did you start learning japanese 10
years ago
but i was like fluent pretty quickly
advice for learning new languages and
speak speak the language every day
and try to learn something new every day
if you don't know a certain word
write it down right away and then try to
use it right away
how do you handle all the languages i
don't know it's not that many
it's not that funny the ones that i
really really speak fluently is only
english german and japanese and
german is my first language english
i learned over the years in bird school
so it's kind of kind of normal that i
can speak it and japanese i taught
myself with lots of passion lots of
motivation so it's not really
such a surprise that i can speak them
but italian i only learned for a little
while and i
yeah i mean i didn't give up on it i
graduated and i ended up with
basically no no knowledge i graduated a
burp school and uh yeah they
weren't really good at teaching us
italian because like it was ridiculous
uh the amount the amount of lessons we
had was like really
really small to begin with bird is yeah
i guess yeah i guess yeah bird is my
first language sure
excuse me i speak four languages bird is
my first language
german is my second language english is
my third language
and japanese is my fourth language
uh some people uh kept assuming
that japanese is my second language not
english that's not true i i i
i'm just i don't know is my english that
bad that you would think
english is my the language that i
learned after japanese
no
how about the birth yeah multi-language
your english is amazing thank you your
japanese is just that good
exactly thank you
thank you thank you so so much for
bottom left huh
did you have japanese friends i guess so
yeah it makes it much easier to
learn a language when you have someone
who speaks that language to
talk to right what what
i moved my thingy
[Music]
by the middle i'll accept it i mean
i don't think that i am as
how you say it loot as you are
um saying i am i
i i mean i get how you get that idea i
understand how you get that idea
but i'm actually
pretty shy
i'm actually pretty sure i am this is
like i talk and i talk
and i act as if i like like i make some
moves on cali and so on
but like actually like if it would come
to it
i i would i wouldn't know what to do
i'm just talking loudly and like trying
to act
cool and trying to act as if i know what
i'm talking about
but i have no idea okay i have no idea
but okay i understand why up until now
you would think i'm
bottom left i kind of get it
from the things i say okay
but yeah i'm not i'm not
i'm not that dark
but okay whatever you put me wherever
you want me to be
i'll take it
well we're talking about languages
though
knowing you're a shy person you're doing
pretty well stream i'm like shy
in uh certain situations like
for example if i if i am like
um if i meet
just someone on a like
for example if a friend introduces me to
their friend
i can like really interact well with
them and
uh i'm like good with um
trying to be nice and making
them like me i guess i know how to
hmm i know how to
read the room maybe i guess
uh how do i say i don't know um
i'm just good in doubt those situations
i guess but
when it's more about
you know about like the situations with
kelly if
if we were if we were to have a date
i would embarrass myself i would
not know what to do i would be quiet
as hell ah
yeah yeah so i'm like shy
only in certain moments you know that's
that's the type of person i have
don't so callie kind of has to take the
lead
if she wants to we'll get her there
i'm embarrassing let's move on travels
um
oh yeah you want to know where i've been
to ha
do i want to tell you
ah i've been to
i've been to do i want to tell you
i've been to japan
i've been to italy
i've been to germany
i've been to austria
i've been to
america i've been to
[Music]
brazil i've been to
africa i've been to
uh uh switzerland
i've been to
oh wait let me open a map of europe
europe i've been to the uk
i've been to the uk i've been to france
[Music]
i've been to spain i've been to spain
i've been to hungary i've been to
croatia i've been to
i feel like maybe i've been to poland
but i don't quite remember
i've been to s
kia however you say that
[Music]
i think for europe that's it
outside of europe i think that was it
too
yeah that's hard to remember
oh i would love to visit australia i
really want to visit australia
ah turkey yes i've been to turkey
singapore no space
yes
well that let's keep it at that
you forgot netherlands why i've never
been to the netherlands have i
ever no no no no no
yay anyway yeah that's uh
i like traveling i wanna i wanna really
visit australia
um i wanna visit canada
i wanna visit canada
i really want to visit canada
i heard the people i sound nice in
canada but australia
i i've seen like it's really expensive
to get to australia
it's so expensive so i feel like canada
is more like realistic
yeah so in europe i basically i've seen
so many
places in europe i want to go more
outside of europe
how about austria i said i've been to
austria
come to canada i'm coming just wait for
me
just let me fly over there it will take
a couple hours
don't go to australia why
australia is like beautiful
the underworld oh i've been to the
underworld like a million times man i've
died so many times
i've visited cali down there so many
times you know
oh my god it's already i should have
wanted to stream only one hour but we
didn't talk about much
let's talk about whole life ian first
impression uh
i'd already talked about this on my
japanese only stream
but you didn't miss out on it so let's
talk about that
and okay well so let's start with
cali when i
first met cali
when i first met all of them
the one that first uh really
struck me was cali
she was so funny from the beginning
and she used like really funny words
that just really cracked me up and
she was just so funny he's so funny i
was like
oh my god this chick is so funny
and i mean obviously i've met her the
first time
millions of years ago so i'm talking
about the time when i met her millions
of years ago obviously
when i first saw her i was like damn she
hot
then what a hot ass chick
oh my god
yes
i was like not only her personality got
me from the beginning but also her looks
like she just got the whole package
yeah you know the whole package
and she was also the first one that i
just uh tried to
you know get closer
and then she also helped me with so many
things as you probably know she did my
at the animation for my loading screen
she did the animation for
my debut book thingy
so i think just from the beginning on we
just where it meant to be
yeah and uh for the other girls
uh surprisingly uh for gouda
i i thought she was like
a quiet mysterious girl
she was always uh she for a long time
she was a mystery to me
and very quiet and she's so cute and
every once in a while
she would sing for us girls
anyway she's so beautiful yeah i really
enjoyed
hearing her things every now and then
but like generally she was always so
i don't know i thought she was a
quiet girl so that turns out she's not
[Music]
amelia she from the beginning
she seemed like someone
very friendly and it felt like
i mean obviously number one for me
mobius kelly i love her let's marry
but for amelia it was like
this is someone i want to be friends
with this is someone
i can rely on because she was really
like reliable
emil amelia is really reliable you can
always count on amelia
ina is like also you know she's quite
kind of like the quiet soothing type of
person and that was
very noticeable from the beginning very
sweet
sweet girl with the greatest talents
her art is amazing actually
i love her artwork so much and she's um
actually like you know
[Music]
when when she notices quite quickly when
i'm feeling down so she would like
message me privately like
if you want to talk about it i'm here
for you you know she's like the first
one
to message me in these situations
super sweet i love all of them all of
them
are just so sweet so cute they're like
my family and i'm really glad
that it is us five i'm really really
glad that we found each other
i'm really glad that we're in this
together i couldn't ask for any
any other girls any better people
there's no better people
really real family we're sisters
i love all of them so much and i'm so
proud we all made it i'm so glad we made
it
i'm so glad it wasn't anyone else it was
supposed to be us it was meant to be us
yay wholesome
yeah and i honestly like of course
there's going to be new generations
but like i'm kind of hoping that it will
take a while
because i'm just i wanted to be as
five as long as possible you know what i
mean
it's always exciting exciting to have a
new generation but i just
i just want to chill with those five i
don't want us to grow too fast
i just wanna have this small family
for a while before it just gets too big
you know
you know what i mean i mean if there's
gonna be a new generation i'm gonna
welcome them
with widely opened arms but for now
i wanna enjoy what we have
i love you all
can we not talk about food
can we not talk about food i don't have
so much
time i'm gonna talk maybe 30 minutes
more and then we're gonna get into super
chat
we love you too i was talking about my
generation members but i love you guys
too
yay generation one hello myth
yay five favorite things about myself
let me show you
uh wait how do we do this
[Music]
wait
gotta be careful
go here and come here
okay five five favorite favorite things
about myself
these feathers
they're so pretty i really like them and
they're really precious to me because i
only got two left
you could say i'm turning bold when it
comes to feathers i had much more
in the past but now i only got these two
and they keep me from dying so i don't
want to lose them
are you seeing these properly and then
number two this
beautiful sparkly eyes
it's like there's a universe in it
i can't really like get lost in my own
eyes
second this beautiful smooth
hair which is by the way washed with
gravy and blushing
my shampoo is gravy that's why it's so
shiny but i really like my shiny hair
and the gradient graded
gradation
it's so pretty i really love the color i
really love orange orange is really my
favorite color
but i feel like that the gradation makes
it even
even prettier that was free right okay
four that our glass
shape that no one can beat look at that
sexy shape oh
yes oh
oh ho ho
yes just yes was that for okay oh my god
there's so much more about
uh huh
there's so much to like in this area
like the belly button or those how do
you call that part
where the how do you call the part
above the skirt those dips
i guess but also um
this part this part
but that's like over five already i also
like this this
uh tape it says sheol kimchi in japanese
it means like don't use because if i use
it i turn
into a phoenix and i was asked to
refrain from that
i also really like my sleeves and i like
that badge on my chest
i like those buttons and i like that
zipper
i like those knees knees
i like my nails too
yeah i like a lot of these i don't like
this hat i like both of the hats
especially the one with the stars he's
such a cute hat
i want more hats i want more hats
and i like the ribbon e on my neck
you see it
oh i also like my teeth
[Music]
ah
i also like my my lashes
okay but that's way too much but also i
really like that chicken
looks so delicious wow
okay i like everything
okay now we go back to
the topics don't you agree with me guys
everything i just mentioned is a hundred
percent correct
and all the magic is done by my papa
[Music]
sexy kid
yes can only agree thanks for joining
membership
thank you
oh and let's talk about yoona's art of
me
for today's thumbnail i used using
yoona's arts the
if you want the twitter link to her
account it's in
my description of this stream
thank you for letting me use it so much
thank you thank you thank you
isn't it so adorable she already drew it
like a while ago
and and maybe
like some of you didn't see it or didn't
notice because
this is me in my pajamas maybe you
didn't recognize it first but now you
should give it even more love
and do you see those plushies from the
other members
that are so cute actually these um you
maybe have seen
them in all of our streams these icons
and enoch came up with them and now
we're just all using them i think that's
really cute and
you not made them into pleasures so
adorable oh my god everything's moving
everything's falling apart anyway i
really love that but she also made some
other fan art
i'll make wait can i like oh yeah i have
this one too
oh it's so big wow have you seen this
one this was the first one she drew of
me
uh wait no
she drew me in the
uh whole life japan idol outfit
did you see this
and i was like oh my god that's like
that was like one of my dreams like
i was thinking about oh i wonder if one
day i can wear that that outfit
uh when i saw that i was like how the
hell did she read my mind how did she do
that
it's so cute i really love that and she
like implemented
all kinds of elements from my original
outfit
like great bigger
like my colors obviously but you see
that belt and i'm also wearing
hey or the ribbon from my neck
or the feathers like she made them even
fancier those are not earrings by the
way and then
they're behind my ears and my hats
she made the that that uh that hat on
that i have on the left side she made it
into a little crown
so adorable i love it you're cute
ah she makes my dreams come true and
recently she was the one you probably
saw
she was the one who drew all the members
in my
outfit just like the kfp crew
this one i didn't save on this pc yet
but it's really cute i think all of you
saw it
yeah ah okay sorry for the fangirling
so i have the link to her twitter and my
description please check it out
she she might be drawing something
special for me right now and you
might be able to see it sometime soon
something new
it's so sweet she draws so much for me
you made me so happy thank you
yeah i guess that's yeah i'm just so
happy when i see you fat night
this makes me so happy thank you to
everyone
who who drew some artifact for me
bring on the tantra fan oh yeah
potential
more tensile fan art
i want to see them all i want to see
your talent then when i intro
i should definitely get that thing
started where i
especially now for a while we are not uh
supposed to show the chat on stream
so this window is kind of um empty here
and so i guess like a good idea would be
to have
fan nights in that window
[Music]
i hope you're everyone who drew
something i hope you're all fine with me
introducing
your artwork oh yeah and recently i had
recently yesterday i've started the taka
modi
hashtag and yes don't worry some people
thought i just did that without
permission i thought about it on stream
and right after the stream i asked her
if it would be fine and she said yes
and that's also what she said said on
twitter she was like you're in the women
what you want
in her usual sins and moments
it's all good it's all good yeah i would
never do something that she wouldn't
want me to do
i would never do something against her
will i will never do something that
doesn't make her happy all right
i love kelly i just want to make her
happy
yeah now the topics are all done i mean
we didn't really talk about food but
that's that
[Music]
what else do you want to talk about
is there anything anything you want to
talk about with me
[Music]
how long do you think it's going to take
me to finish mario 64 first i'm so bad
and it's gonna get even more difficult
right
i'm not sure if i can finish it i'm
gonna try to make a few more streams for
mario 64. i'm not even sure if i can
finish it it's kind of difficult
and the camera and the controls oh man
it's the worst it's the worst minecraft
collab
you mean with japan yeah when the collab
band is lifted definitely
but first we have to get all the other
members on
on minecraft and make a server i don't
know how to make a server but i wish i
hope we can use
the current world that i'm in with the
things that i have
i wonder if that works you guys kind of
said it works but
yeah collab and yeah we have a collab
and how much longer is it
yeah we we had our debut i think on the
12th
it's been one two two and a half weeks
uh wait one two it's two more
one and a half more weeks ah
what should i do guys
how do i how do i ask
[Music]
one and a half i think it's one and a
half weeks there
[Music]
ah
like even if i i'm gonna of course i can
ask from my side but if you ask from
my side then i kind of already have to
come up with a plan of what we could do
so like i can't just come and dm them
like hey do you want to do a collab with
me
i just kind of have to already lay out
what we could do and it has to sound
interesting enough for them to say yes
so it's not that easy ask and chat yeah
of course i'm going to ask
i also feel like wouldn't that be too
easy
if my first collab would be with piccolo
but wouldn't it be too easy
oh i feel like i should nah
i shouldn't get that so easy
yeah maybe some
other collapse before peccola senpai
would be better
so better yeah i wanna ask survivor
senpai
i think that's probably subaru senpai
i'm gonna probably ask super senpai
and marine senpai maybe maybe if she
wants i want to ask
shion senpai and nene senpai
those are probably the first people i'm
going to ask and then because inside
because of course i want to
collab with her but i feel like it's
maybe
too easy and too early i don't know i'm
not ready i'm not ready for it guys
i am not ready
can you imagine us actually collabing
and then i'm gonna be so like
starstruck i'm gonna be like
do whatever you wish with me
i feel like we need some more time to
warm up before we go like straight into
a collab
well let's see
i wonder if she likes me there's also
this thing about
you know wondering does she even want to
collab with me i don't want to force it
on to
that girl or whoever it is don't want to
force it on to them you know
so it's it's good to have some kind of
sign
from their side that they would be open
to do
it yeah
but it's so exciting i want to do lots
of collabs
can you laugh like pekora well
apparently i can apparently my love
already sounds like the crust
i'm not even trying i'm not trying i
i swear i'm not trying
i think i want i try to remember
if i laughed like this before i watched
hours and hours and hours of
her streams i tried to think of it but i
just can't remember
you have a reverse speculative really
oh wait
i'm trying to compare in my mind
stop laughing like that stop
laughing like that
[Music]
stop stop
i keep on laughing like that
i can't i can't stop myself it just
comes out like that
i can't
[Music]
but sometimes i laugh differently you
know
so you need to ask her first but did she
just say she's shy or did she
say she's shy and she wants us to ask
her
don't hold your lap okay i will laugh
as much as i can she wants
she said she wants us to ask she wants
to collab with me and really
but does that include me
does that include me i wonder
laughing german how the hell are you
laughing german
i wonder if they want to collab with me
i mean i would definitely be the easiest
to collab with because i can speak
japanese
i'll try my best i actually i'm so
nervous
about the collab band being lifted i'm
quite nervous about it
because it's like
yeah it's like now or never but also
like maybe later is better
you never know japanese chicken
dominance what the hell
teaching them english without source i
don't think i should be the one teaching
english it's not my first language
yes i have watched the new pokemon mv
i've watched it live on pokemon news
can you do a good voice impression no
how do you do a good voice impression
shock
that's all i got
did that sound a little bit like her
that was really good hell yeah
hell yeah nice
she got such a cute angel voice
it's so cute it's a cute baby angel boy
okay i can't get close to that
[Music]
angelic predator i don't understand the
whole apex predator thing i don't get it
what is it what does that even mean does
it mean someone who is good at playing
a packs but didn't she say that about
herself while
not playing apex
on top of the left top of the food chain
why is the why is the word apex in there
apex means but isn't that a game
apex had a meaning i thought oh my god
so many mind blowings here
i thought that was just the title of the
game that actually has a meaning
what okay i'll have to open my
dictionary one second
i still have caps lock unlock on can
someone undo my caps lock
apex
it really says that
i just thought it was a random made up
name for a game
okay so apex predator means
wait what does predator mean in i kind
of know the meaning but
bread that tie
makes sense now it makes so much sense
now
now i finally get it why she was saying
apex predator during a game that wasn't
even
apex i was so confused
ah cause she never did she ever play
apex in those dreams i don't think so
i was like what what no she didn't
even play i
packed so i don't get it
ah too good that's so funny
[Music]
interesting thanks guys you taught me a
lot of things today
like banjo kazooie and
yuka and lily in apex
bottom left moment excuse me why why why
why why why why why
why how is that a bottom left moment
just because i
didn't know that apex actually had
meaning doesn't mean i'm stupid
it just means that i lack lack maybe one
word in my vocabulary
but what languages do you speak huh what
language
language is do you speak to speak any
language besides english and
if yes can you do you know every
word in that language do you do you know
every word i don't think so i think
there's definitely one or two words that
you don't know in that language
and that does not make you stupid it
does not make you stupid
so you may call me stupid but not
because of that
bird used flame from
drinking stream for oktoberfest actually
guys you know
there's this one there's this one
traditional festival
coming up this year
that i am a bit scared of
i feel a bit in danger
when it comes to thanksgiving
um many people
have been misunderstanding what i am
i hope you guys will protect me when
people
will be coming after me
right before thanksgiving i
i need your protection i'm scared
i'm not a turkey and i'm not a chicken
i'm a phoenix
i cannot prove it right now because my
belt
does not allow me to transform
but i ask all of you for your protection
i'm scared
you can have the chicken that i'm
holding in my hands
you can have those drumsticks but don't
take my life
because i told you before i might be
an immortal phoenix but
that i'm only immortal when i
go up in flames and turn into ashes but
if you eat me and poop me out
i will not come back to life out of your
poop
no that's not how it works
i'll be gone forever so please don't eat
me
i'm not laughing i'm i'm very serious
and i'm very scared
i did not need to know of course you had
to know this because otherwise you would
have tried to eat me
thanksgiving is the scariest day of my
life
the scariest day second scariest is
halloween yeah
i'm really bad with horror movies and
horror games and all that stuff
so halloween is also quite scary
so we have a lot of scary days coming up
first halloween and
thanksgiving i don't wanna do this
anymore
[Music]
very spooky i'm just not
catching a break i hope i survive until
christmas
i really want to survive until christmas
and new year's eve
no there's nothing uh scary about
christmas no no no
just want to survive so can this
please
thank you okay guys
i think we've reached a good point to
start reading the super chats
uh tomorrow i'll be streaming at a
different time slot
around the time where i streamed
yesterday to stream some more minecraft
and then
unfortunately i'll probably be taking
a break over the weekend i kind of um
sunday there is a collab but i'm kind of
scared about the collab because like i
feel like
and on the weekend uh i i'm gonna have
some internet issues some really bad
internet issues
i'll probably be doing a memphis only
stream on saturday
to test out the internet i hope that's
okay i just really gotta test it i gotta
do
[Music]
and then the whole horrible internet
situation
will continue for at least another week
i don't know what to do i don't know
what to do
i hope i hope i can stream
but for a while you might be having
much worse uh disconnections
than my wife callie even has with my
streams
probably disconnecting much more yeah so
internet that's how you call it
i'll try my best if it gets too bad that
maybe i gotta
stream at my manager's place or so yeah
anyway ipax phoenix oh yeah apex phoenix
now that i know the word and finally
makes sense yay
so you better all come tomorrow because
tomorrow is the last
day for a while where i actually have
stable internet
and then i'll be taking three days off
or so
everyone come tomorrow to my minecraft
stream oh thanks for the super chat i'll
be reading them now
i'll go ahead and read them actually i
have to do a check
so let me set up everything
let's put up that and let's get rid of
[Music]
that everyone who's gonna leave now
thank you for coming i hope you enjoyed
the little talking stream
and we talked about a lot of things huh
eventually so i
originally only wanted to do one hour
but it was it was fun so i extended it i
can't get the right window there we go
thank you kiara it was great i'm happy
to hear that thanks guys
thanks and welcome to the membership
danke shoe and feeling dang time exactly
good night guys if you want to stay and
stay for the super chat it's probably
not going to take that much time so
you're welcome to stay we can do some
more chatting in the meantime
but if you don't want to stay that's
okay for me too
[Music]
wow
where where is it
[Music]
i shall stay thank you
wee wee wee
yeah sorry um this is going to take like
maybe five minutes or something
scrolling oh there we go that was fast
so it might be done quite early today
copy
ah i should do the thing again where i
need a noodle i made a
cough drop let's have some cough drop
cough drop licking asmr ha
everyone who left are missing out on
cough drop
licking asmr
i wonder if you can hear it though
no i'm an asmr can you hear that
probably not so much to hear
okay
ew i mean usually i would also be the
one who says you about these things
[Music]
one second i really can't do two things
at once i'm like
that's stupid
can you hear that i should get further
away from the
microphone
no i don't want you to hear that that's
disgusting
ah
how disgusting
closer no that's disgusting
someone oh my god i still have caps
and now we got it some
someone up for a super chat check
ah
you guys are weird
thank you
[Music]
okay give it a second they're checking
right now
uh in the meantime
let's talk about food
i think like recently i don't know
recently
today i don't have much of an appetite i
think i'm just gonna eat a sandwich my
favorite sandwich for
uh dinner
i also feel like the things that i eat
it's always the same i want to eat some
more different things
what is your favorite easy breakfast a
piece of bread
with nutella on top
i like i used to be the type okay here
comes
the discussion this is a very important
discussion that i used to have with
an ex-roommate she said
she's also she was a big fan of nutella
and she she insisted
that my habit of having
butter in between nutella and the bread
is weird she was like that's disgusting
and i was like no it's yummy and i used
to be the type of person who could not
eat
that i wouldn't i didn't think you guys
would be so
upset about that
i was a typhoon what you guys are
shocking me right now
i was the type who thought that it was
only delicious
with the butter in between but recently
uh i'm in a different place and the
butter here
is not very good so i stopped putting
the butter in between the nutella and
the bread and
it's good it's good okay i got used to
it i really like it this way too
also it's always just uh annoying like
when i toast
the bread it's like super hot right and
just putting nutella on it cool but if
you're gonna put
butter first then the butter melts and
of course it's still kind of there
but i kind of don't want the butter to
melt so i have to wait and wait and wait
until the bread is not cooked it is not
hot anymore
and then i put the butter on there but
then often the butter is like
that kind of butter that doesn't spread
very well on bread
it just stays a stupid block
that's so annoying so yes there are
always a struggle so recently
i have stopped eating it with butter and
just go straight put in the towel and
that's actually pretty good because if
the if the bread is still
fresh toast it and it's so warm and then
you put that nutella on top of it
then you have like a hot bread with
nutella and it's so delicious
okay so it's all good for me but you
guys why are you so shook about putting
butter between the damn
it's good have you ever tried it all of
you guys who say ew you haven't even
tried
it
it's not illegal
it's something healthier no
that is healthy
[Music]
that's my favorite but also sometimes
i'm in the mood for
cereals so that's also really really
easy breakfast
okay here we go
oh my god google what is you doing
[Music]
i'm not done with my cough drop but okay
you sure are you ready my friends for
some thank you showing time and
feeling dank time
are you ready
oh there's there's uh never mind
let's go
there we go oh this time it wasn't
someone else
is
finally got to see my favorite polyglot
phoenix what does that mean life
you're my favorite personality and whole
life right now
taking
[Music]
speak many languages ew oh
yes did you guys know in japanese
there's a really funny pun
that you can make when you say i'm
trilingual because that's be real
a bird is not a language don't tell
anyone
that i said that but okay so i'm
trilingual
and the japanese you pronounce it like
tori lingard and anyway you can make a
panel of that because bird is tori
in japanese so you could write tori in
kanji
and the rest in uh in katakana so it's
like
burt ha he's so funny
i love that pun yeah the japanese
people are riding it right now it's so
funny
but it only works in japanese
bird lingua it only lies in japanese
i'm glad you guys are appreciating that
okay
[Music]
the bridge that connects the yen and
japan fans together i'm looking forward
to future collabs
thank you i will do my best and actually
since we don't have so many donations i
think i can read more texts so let's
read the one
from below also looking for the top said
hi majestic feelings
hello do you have any plans for
halloween spooky stream you
are not a chicken after all right
um
i don't wanna i don't wanna do a spooky
stream
i'm not a chicken
[Music]
i don't wanna
don't say that don't want to do it
ah i shouldn't have read this
it's like i officially read it so it's
officially a challenge for me
you officially challenged me to do a
spooky stream for halloween
why would you do that this is why i
shouldn't read the super chat messages
shut up don't
already just mentioned yeah that's
something
that i can still handle but have you
guys seen the video that i retweeted
today
when in minecraft a pickaxe breaking
can scare the out of me
you know how it's gonna go when
when i'm gonna play a horror game or
watch a horror movie
anyway let's move on
[Music]
thank you i had fried chicken tonight in
front of you
i see how you would think of me as i'm
always holding fried chicken
thank you
on the scale of very likely to extremely
likely likely how likely
are you to use that minecraft thumbnail
on radius today
i saw it i appreciate it but
if i'm gonna use that i wonder how many
people are going to realize it's my
stream i'm gonna click on it
i i i politely have to turn it
down this time
yeah but thank you thank you that was
really cute though i really liked seeing
that
no worries i had a really long and hard
day as well so a nice and comfy relaxing
with you is all i need yay
how do you handle setbacks wait setbacks
means like
when something goes wrong uh
this is like asking me what was that
question before
what's the question before i said i have
no idea please tell me how i handle
stress
how do i calm down when it gets
distressed um
but a setback how do i
just um get back up again i don't know
how i do it i mean
i'm just i guess um
there's been times in my life where uh
people thought very strongly
that i couldn't do something and i would
i would be thinking that too
but i tried it anyway and then it worked
out
and i mean i don't want to brag but it
just really happened i didn't think it
would actually work
but i gave it a try and i i tried my
best
and it worked so i'm just um i just keep
trying again again
especially since that first time that
something so big happened to me
um i think that probably really changed
me a lot in when it comes to motivation
and setbacks i guess yeah
i'm a fighter if something goes wrong
i remember the time when things went
really well
surprisingly and
it just really shows that even if you
think it's impossible and everyone else
thinks impossible it's impossible
it's probably really quite difficult to
accomplish what you want to accomplish
actually you can do it if you try it the
right way
and if you try often enough and long
enough
you usually should be able to accomplish
it
phoenix mentality exactly
so i mean you probably can't go as far
as me to
uh you know try so hard that you will
die
that's probably too dangerous because
you can't revive yourself
so try to a certain extent but also
don't feel bad about setbacks because
facebook sometimes it's just not meant
to be that that happens too
second of all from setbacks i guess you
can learn
you learn how to change the way
um you you went at it
can't speak english yeah
you learn from setbacks see i'm trying
to
say something good here uh but i often
also have problems with those things so
don't worry everyone even even i even i
had a phoenix immortal phoenix who keeps
getting back up
i also have problems i also often lose
hope
um but then just sleep a night
over it and then often you can just try
again from zero
yeah thank you
i'm flip plays games thank you how about
you that new arc nice banner
i wanna get rosa she's so beautiful and
she has a really
cool range i really want to use her
ryan dankeshen who's your favorite
non-japan
or ian whole life member
you mean who's my favorite indonesian
remember
there's like only three members i'm not
gonna say who that's like kind of like
i feel like also i don't really
i wouldn't say i have a favorite from
the inner indonesia girls
ah but
[Music]
i don't think i have a favorite
no i don't really have a favorite it
doesn't mean i don't like them
but i also didn't um i didn't have some
so much opportunities to talk with
anyone
outside of holoyen to begin with
because uh we are only connected on
twitter
and as a as a kohai as a
uh what's it was the opposite of senior
uh and what was it
as a what what was it
junior yeah as a junior it's um
kind of hard to like contact someone
privately
first so
um actually muna senpai was so nice to
message me
so i was really happy about that but as
a junior it's just
i feel like i'm not in the position to
message my seniors first
so it's kind of hard to um you know
really get closer to them at least at
this point maybe after
the collab band is lifted it will be
much easier
um muna wanted to eat me
uh yeah somehow everyone wants to eat me
but i'll take it as long as i can get
friends with them
united states citizenship blah blah blah
can't read the rest because it's caught
up there dan kashing
cute anime girls are the best thank you
nicolas who else comes
your enthusiasm and exuberance another
word i did not know
it's awesome just keep being yourself as
for topics what are your favorite
non-anime films
oh um i like a lot of the rings
i like
i like the hobbit i like game of thrones
i like uh but that's not a film that's
not a movie
i like the great gatsby because it's a
so romantic but then so sad
other than that good movies what are
good movies
yeah we all like fantasy stuff
oh yeah pirates of the caribbean was fun
yeah but i wouldn't say it's my favorite
legit good taste oh thank you how about
like uh
the great gatsby probably um
it's like a very girly movie to like
hey watch a long lord of the rings
extended edition that's gonna take ages
but we can do that i haven't watched the
whole thing in a long time
only the roommate that i talked about
before oh my god she's crazy like
um we started i don't live with her now
but
she started what we we together started
re-watching
a lot of the rings and she told me
before she warned me that she knows the
movie very well and has seen it like a
million times
and then we start watching and she
literally
remembers the whole dialogue of all
the lord of the rings movies and next to
me
on the sofa she keeps on like
talking with the characters on screen
and i'm like
like at first it was funny but at some
point it's just annoying
but also amazing like how the hell do
you remember
the whole dialogue oh my gosh she would
always just look at me like
with her smug face and like say the
exact same
thing that they're saying like you shall
not
pass haha
that's the only thing that i remember
it was so funny she literally knew
everything i was like
what the hell is wrong with you i love
her though i love her
crazy crazy absolutely crazy
i like her i like her too i love her
all right let's move on
thank you would you consider doing
another oh yeah yeah we said we do we do
we do maybe i will
challenge you
um
it's almost a quite quiet time for me
uh g breakdown
any embarrassing names for your pokemon
on your original account
no i i usually kept them the same uh
like i never changed the names for the
pokemon
you're the secret brand of herbs and
spices of rainfall life and squat
together that's so sweet
thank you thank you those uh
secret blend of herbs and spices is just
my ashes kind of disgusting you
shouldn't try to eat it
i know there's a long list of games to
get free first but my favorite turn
based
oh rpg of all time is maybe mario titan
whiny um
actually my favorite a non-be trooper
youtuber is like a huge mario fan and he
played that and he also said like
it's uh the best rpg of all time so i
watched a playthrough of
him playing that yeah
yeah this is not like my favorite style
of game
you know i love those jrpgs with like
really
cute designs
do you watch any german youtubers well
i think if you check my uh the people
that i follow on twitter you definitely
find
one do you love 67 thank you shame
jay skirt danke should never thought i'd
find an idol who speak german and
japanese languages i've been most
interested in learning oh gonna enjoy
watching you give me something to do
you're the best character
up early to watch thank you thank you
i'm planning to do german
language streams on members only but
i'm not promising that you're going to
learn anything
from that
fox thank you so much
and you can say greetings in multiple
languages like a pub no that actually i
cannot do
it
[Music]
i'm not loot no i'm not be gamer for 11.
um i wish i had enough money to travel
as much as you have in your life but
i sadly can't seem to figure out where
all my money goes
honestly save your money please do it
traveling is like the most fun to do
with your life honestly traveling is the
best you can do
and then take some nice uh
pictures for into instagram
[Music]
i wanted to do some really deep talk
today but i feel like i didn't get that
deep today did i
i wanted to go deeper i want to go
really deep
it would be fun to have phoenix scented
candles we could light for whenever
you're streaming
that sounds like a cult
thank you soon be gamer 311
[Music]
yes we are allowed to collab with anyone
we want really
any uh uh how do you say any private
vegetables also no problem if we want to
do that
food point is
i had to explain the ibex predator to
cali on the stream collapse from two so
i guess you oh
really she didn't know either nice thank
you
aj fox thank you tony
i really love your chat gaming karaoke
here's some amount for delgado thank you
looking forward to the pokemon and maybe
roon factory five yeah maybe you can
tame and train chicken what
an original song by you oh maybe maybe
who knows that cashen
[Music]
i was so happy when you said the stream
is just chatting and what is my
favorites really
thank you hearing you talk about the
other hello live en members was so
wholesome thank you
keep all the awesome stuff keep up all
the awesome stuff you're doing
wonderfully
[Music]
i enjoy seeing you have fun and be happy
i also appreciate your fine sense for
yuri shiv's hair speaking of that you
know like sakura i heard of it uh
i heard of it isn't it yeah it's a
beauty anime yeah but i didn't watch it
can you stream in german during the eu
afternoon i'm not really planning a
german only stream for now just because
i feel like there's really not going to
be a big audience and anyone who can
speak german
can usually also speak english so i
don't think it makes so much sense
and i'm embarrassed speaking in german
for too long
thank and now let me refresh quickly
everything that will come after that
refresh i will not read thank you
and of course
then
[Music]
happy birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear take two
sorry i'm so um going fast right now aj
fox packaging i'm so glad that you stuck
it out and that we can all be here for
this stream you got my first membership
because you're a sweet and wholesome
person and i can't wait to have my
drumstick
stick isn't it amazing
dan kishan and welcome to the membership
thank you for joining me for your
lavendan
i mean cinnamon toast crunch if you mean
the one that i know like a cinnamon
crunchy thingy i really like that one
but that's not necessarily my favorite
hey
it keeps on changing like i can't eat
the same breakfast cereal the whole time
it has to change
[Music]
interesting thank you but you need to
get good butter
thank you shin two pin nine donkey shane
wallace warlord thank you shenzhen
jason visto thank you mary officially on
the marriage papers
you can keep staying with marty
eternally and neglect me i just want
your name
ah what no you cannot have my name what
the hell
thank you big creeper v dankeshen
if you're just
i would like to suggest you try the
resident evil series no
no no i don't want to play that no
no no no please no no
thank you i'll think about something
else that i could
that i could play that it's not too
scary but still scary but oh
no no no i don't want it to be too scary
and but we could also maybe watch a
horror movie together
and you can hear me scream all the time
quadrant at first thank you
in attack thank you very much
and i traded a new and improved
all righty i'll check it out thank you
[Music]
after the uh i see those that
came in after the refreshing so let me
read captain peppa's extinction
[Music]
grow strong little verb
and thank you to everyone who enjoyed
the membership
and again captain david jackson kitchen
thank you so much yay pink
okay i gotta go guys i'm sorry
sorry for the how do you say it why did
you say
crap how do you say do you say crunch
no thursday when they like go really
fast and
like rushed
i guess sorry for the rest ending
[Music]
i'll see you guys tomorrow i'll be
preparing the
thumbnail for minecraft and then you can
um wait just wait
for me and i'll be waiting for you
see you tomorrow and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
i love you wow
[Music]
bye bye thanks for coming guys i hope
it wasn't too boring
[Music]
tomorrow probably starting from
1pm japanese time
oh that was really good
[Music]
you