[Music]
things
this is
[Music]
foreign
this is
[Music]
foreign
you mean you mute us unmute you unmute
yeah uh hello
that's a couple kikirikis here
[Music]
a couple of cute kitty Keys hey good day
good morning good evening everybody
hello morning
hi guys welcome back to to babu's gate
it's a beet juice
yeah for saying that for just bringing
yeah the bag I know Bilbo I know Bilbo
Baggins you're the best I thought you
might be impressed by that reference
yeah just by saying Bilbo Baggins
oh
wait I need to clarify again why I
decided to stream today yes please um
the main reason because I had just been
I just went off of a tirade telling
everybody we don't need four povs but
here's the thing
um I realized if people go to my channel
and they're looking for a collab and
there's like randomly one missing they
miss a big chunk of the story so I feel
like I have to stream every single time
because people go to my channel and
they're like oh I want to watch all of
Kelly's Baldur's Gate and then they
click all of them and then they miss one
and then then they're confused you know
what what you could do for that I have a
solution
what let's say you stream part 1.2 but
not part three
then yeah make a playlist for Baldur's
Gate and then just put part three of
someone else in there oh truth
there are people who wouldn't wouldn't
check it out yeah and don't you do this
playlist for your game series sometimes
sometimes it depends I have a lot of
game series oh my God there's a bug on
my screen let me kill it oh it is
let the cats take them yeah more toys
for the cats how are you guys doing
we're doing well
3 P.M at my time zone
I was like oh oh well yeah all the
mushroom people are here yeah they're
really interested
can you impersonate Golem for me please
um
watch tater's brushes
[Music]
[Laughter]
that has potential good potential pretty
good that's a solid impression got him
got him oh
all right I'm getting kind of nutty I
like it
and then her stuff was kind of I have to
say before the stream started she was
kind of savage I love it I was not being
a Savage Girl boss mode all right go off
Queen that's what they say go off Queen
I don't know why it sounds so wrong to
hear you say that to me and me yeah
[Music]
at you
thank you yeah
get rich when we eventually get to
Baldur's Gate I have to play somewhere
where there's lots of people because
apparently there's an achievement where
you have to get a hundred coins from one
one time playing oh okay okay I just
realized I don't have your shoes on yeah
I just saw that too oh ew are those dogs
out for free free yeah I was just
looking at your feet actually please
stop I don't have shoes
it's like nice and far away just so it's
like basically a little tantalizing but
like not the full thing yeah okay I'm
happy yeah that's the imagination okay
you have to feel the Earth become one
with the earth oh no God it's healthy to
go uh Barefoot apparently yeah
and they get stabs on your feet yeah I'm
gonna put all the time
some glass and bleach oh yeah oh yeah
people is Barefoot gang yeah I am
Barefoot games but I think it's an Asian
thing because I always I never
understood wearing shoes in the house I
don't wear shoes in the house either
yeah I think that's an n a thing yeah in
Europe we don't wear shoes in our homes
I was raised to take my shoes off when I
came in the house so I don't know what
people are talking about when they say
that thank God it scares me I just see
it in American TV shows all the time and
it makes me feel so disgusted when
people go on their beds with their shoes
I've been told it's a TV thing is is it
not also reality
um
I couldn't help myself I see him I'll
just be fine with it though one thing uh
there was an update where cutscenes you
can listen in you can eavesdrop
automatically so we turned that on so
now it should be easier for everybody to
stay on track with what's going on yeah
and I was hoping it would be like that
yeah
will try to lead the way today although
I don't know where we're going but you
know maybe an innocent mind is the best
mind to go through this map I could say
so yeah yeah last time we were were we
done exploring the city I don't think so
not completely or where are we yeah
for the most part we were we talked to
the big guy who wanted us to go get them
wanted to come with us to kill someone
oh yeah where's the mushroom guy the
cute mushroom guy he's not cute
down here's our guy where's our Deuter
he is not our guy this one he's our guy
we have to hire him again
what do you say team leader
me
you want him to come with us yeah of
course I hired him last time but he
didn't stay so
um please
slimy slimy friends
what
he's icky why does he want to ask so
many questions again
did I just skip this
because we already did it wait how do I
get him to join again behind eh wasn't
he the one who joined yeah
we definitely saved at the end he did
hello what's going on buddy boy
oh
um we might need to kill the guy first
and then he might come with oh just be
the to see the dead body was already
part of us our team last time
specifically because she doesn't like
him it reveals it oh he cringed he made
him cringe narissa good
okay
who is he following before me because I
was like the only one who was willing to
take him in
oh ammonia but now he's done talking
with me oh wow oh wow maybe another time
yeah maybe another maybe it's not meant
to be okay do you really want a
sovereign named glut following you
around
not that bad yeah
well then let's continue do we go this
way this way I want kooky characters in
D do we have something on the map we
want to follow
um well if we keep going this way we'll
eventually come across probably the guys
that we're supposed to destroy okay
is here for battle battle I love battle
oh I don't think so we need to go back
to Camp which I don't mind doing we
might want a long rest soon because I
have no spell okay oh well I mean I'm
great we can do it now too yeah sure all
right go to camp
we're going to Camp Lads yeah yeah sure
yeah we have a mushroom camp
scratch
y
Shadow heart approves of me petting the
good boy oh oh good boy the good doggy
I don't know where I am I'm sitting in a
van of Darkness
um
okay it loaded finally oh
the leg
Shadow heart looks like she's missing
like her bottom legs when she sits like
that
oh yeah I guess see what you mean
a Starion put on some clothes Jesus
but you girls took it from him I'm
wearing his
give it back to him
well I'll give him I'll give him a set
of clothes oh okay he can have Michael's
I think Cali needs to give it to him
wait oh that's why we can't because he's
not in the party so he can't give him
yeah
[Music]
I see
Hello hello hello let me go look up my
keyboard mouse she's been kind of a hot
pose like wow I'm like spinning around
my character right now
not that I want to see but like I'm
gonna go look yeah you should as always
smoking
[Laughter]
hotkeys
yeah because I'm not using a controller
yep noise
inspectus tea
I wish when you were a tiefling you
could change your tail color because the
skin colored tail looks very odd
um yeah that would be kind of neat yeah
it's just kind of you know it's just
kind of fleshy you know
well I mean it Blends in with your skin
you look at Carla she has it too and
hers yeah but she's red so it doesn't
look weird it doesn't look weird it
looks it looks cool yeah you look a
little bit like uh
what's it called
the the Minecraft little thing that
everybody wanted to collect
Minecraft animal
what yeah
we look like an axolotl I don't know why
I found them
Axolotl everybody all rested yeah I
think they don't want really want to
talk to us what you call the Syrian over
he brings his book though while he's
walking oh yeah now where did he put it
[Laughter]
I need a dancing mode thank you
when you dance
I know Carla randomly does dances
sometimes yeah you do that yeah teach us
Carla teach us you just gotta feel it oh
yeah I'm getting down
yeah I'm feeling it yes
no emotes yet oh breathing strongly
okay get away from me let's leave
go to bed wait they're giving me money
we're missing
heard it
one goal they're they're picking up what
you're putting down nurisa keep it up
for us
you're gonna be sharing some of that pot
right of course we all share an
inventory anyway hold on a sec
sipping on the coffee hoping I can sleep
tonight
good luck
okay another player is currently
choosing camp supplies Ah that's what
that message was yeah all right good
night oh man
what's happening
not again
every freaking time
oh
why me because we bone down I swear yeah
because he likes you the best bro I
could totally kill you I could snap you
like a twig my man well
it is always hungry
where is the choice to kick him in the
Neds
not for a long time please let me kick
him in the oh that would be funny melee
attack
see um I see how long did you have you
it's been since so that's why you were
so quick to kill the girl Hunter to keep
your secret
I'm not some monster okay prove it I
feed on animals this is really uncomfy
because you're in your tidy way whatever
I
can bless the clean looking yeah
I'm too weak he's thirsty okay if I just
had a little nice color I like it
everything clearer finds better I'm sure
Cali has plenty of blood to give I am a
big brutish ogre you sure you want this
ogre blood
it's really yucky it tastes like swamp
one
Secrets half revealed
I don't care how much you need you're
not drinking my blood why didn't you
tell me bro okay okay joking I'm joking
I'm not gonna do them dirty
yeah he's like a boy
trust me oh yeah I'm gonna give him my
blood become bloodless and we're not
even gonna use him on the team
he tried to bite me how can I trust you
I do I believe you oh we had a nice time
in the woods
you could
he's really taking what he can get
the taker
fine but a drop more than you need and
I'll kill you go too far I'll drive a
steak through your chest all right no
not a drop more than you need all right
all right now do it
dude's so shady Kelly said soon today
for him look only because big brutish
ogre is hilarious okay trust me
oh
my strip juice get a room a Shrek juice
Crystal I need to persuade him that
that's enough
what if he kills me bro if that was a
one
I wish it would have been a one that
would have been yeah it would have been
super funny
done something
does that mean
S no way that was oh shut up
this is really weird in his underwear
yeah
what if you like keep letting him drink
more and more like does he kill you
melee attacks his words not mistake and
drive it into his
house
that's weird something this is a really
weird pose
this is a gift you know
yes he will kill you oh boy watch as he
stalks off
just a freak what a little freaky baby
man ready to hunt oh I'm a freaky baby
man I mean yeah the baby gives me a
freaky baby man Vibes
I I like I prefer to call a Starion a
boy failure boy failure
that's pretty good yeah
you guys need anything else here can we
do it yeah we need it did let's get back
to this do you guys know what they call
Shadow heart on the internet yes and I
will not repeat it please
is it lewd uh
it is a bad one why are you Snickers no
it's not it's just gross
they call they call it sharks
[Laughter]
no it's not it's
uh do you know what A Shard is
well I could I could put a few things
together in my brain yeah but surely
they mean Shadow heart charts right no
let's just say let's just say they mean
that
did a quick rest there's a fight that's
really strong that I need that's down
here can we go to there first yeah
um what is it there's a weapon down here
that I have to collect three pieces of
it to staff oh yeah
can we go to the seller night Outpost
sounds like those isn't that where we
came from oh yes okay yeah it's still in
the underdark but we're gonna go out a
different direction
okey dokey is W okay uh cell night
cell cellulite
cellulite I only see under dark mic on
it
lower and lower right
oh I see
okay okay and then we cellulite
cellulite opening wait wait Point
Outpost I'm on my way cellulite Temple
of cellulite here we go and there's
gonna be a big fight
like right there oh okay party time I'm
ready I'm ready to go crazy with my
ladies okay big fight okay girls let's
go oh there's like a lot of uh statues
that are petrified oh oh no oh boy
I wonder if first they were afraid and
then they were petrified
and kept thinking
oh surprise I'm surprised I'm surprised
too
laugh for me chat
don't believe me
you're funny Kiara thank you hey that's
that's fake no it doesn't it's a real
laugh a fake laugh would be hot
it's a real laugh
it was a little fake
buddy
that looks like from monster Inc
oh yeah
oh that's a lot of teeth oh my God it's
a big Mike Wazowski all right
now oh
no
it's Dorne
I probably should have done a little
quick save before
well might as well do it now wrong okay
living Library
it's good to fight this when we after
like we just rest because this is a high
place is he our enemy too Dawn yeah oh
where's my Dash are the unpetrified ones
also our enemies now oh my God yep
seems to be the case let's get out of
here
um
oh boy
same stuff spectator
I wonder if it's better to kill the
smaller ones first
um
I mean it depends what you like I like
it I like to kill whoever I managed to
kill in one hit usually
um my whole team because then that's
less people attacking oh big electric
shock yeah shock em
I need to summon my pets again I keep on
forgetting
and then and I hit him now a lot of
movements so I'll just do a little
camera right here really bothers me
yeah
hey can I backstab them
I'm gonna do a frenzy
I like the thought of the backstab yes
do it yeah yeah like bloodborne well
he's distracted
oh
you became a good guy
can we not fight him no we should fight
this guy uh is he mean the big dude yeah
I should try and move it's a waste of
frenzy no can't I move on my mobile
oh no dang it I can't be very useful
because you're scared
oh Mario is scared of nothing that's
unrealistic come on now
enraged bro what are we throwing yikes
yikes 14. I guess
oh he's back yeah hit me
Bust It Down narissa Bust It Down
come back
yeah it dodged Oliver once earlier
surely I can do something
it's not my turn yet you've got yeah all
right I'm still learning the ways of the
keyboard mouse
uh yeah you girls will have to finish
him probably yep we got this
problem
s
come out with him
kill them yes kill them I need them to
die okay leave it to me oh really quick
oh you could talk to them first I think
they have information
we don't need that information anyway
just kill them yeah all right
oh
yeah jump into my cloud of daggers
what a big dummy
lacerator
Mario big hill
I'm talking today
oh my God
Frenzy
she's really mad
[Music]
hmm
oh okay nice guys
oh sucks the critically miss you big
dumb dumb
die
yay what's he holding
let's see one of them should have let's
hear something that I need there's
afraid to draw wood
he's smoking
how about this dude
in the cloud of daggers he's got a ton
of stuff I'll take everything yeah
oh wait let me anyone he wants cup of
ice
[Music]
hold on a sec I have a pendant and The
Spectator eyes
uh something that looks like what
ice
looking ice oh memories last pendant
which is a lightning blast
there's something called a blast pendant
um
if somebody wants that gloves of Heroes
that's it apparently the pendant the
blast pendant oh at least chat says yeah
it's the memory I am going to Blink it
if that's okay yeah get it okay memory
chart
huh
okay
is that all you needed people that's all
I needed I need two more pieces okay we
can keep exploring I'll bring it out
when we when we get close okay maybe
we'll go okay you're done see what we
find
follow me
yeah follow Liara
oh rope
something I'll leave it for you though
what is this
there's a trap oh you know what
oh it's a basic poison all right oh
oh okay we are
oopsy
what do we do about this noxception oh
my God it says one damage it's not so
bad oh my God and the fumes we walk down
thank you for it bye
[Laughter]
I didn't want to watch Oreo pick and
take it we're good do you guys want a
short rest yeah maybe yeah let me get
down there first yeah because you're
gonna need it
happening
good luck Bagel okay
okay
knocked down right when we were short
resting great oh is it gonna come out or
what I wouldn't mind fighting it I
fought a vegan fight him
easy
can't control no sit down oh I was
waiting for that oh it ran away
I'm right uh yeah
take him
I don't know about that uh guys I'm just
a Bard I'm just a lowly Bard and come on
you can you can jump oh 20
step Mamma Mia
I'm Gonna Save him yeah
a spicy spicy indeed spicy boo
take this
zero fire
that was strong
not very helpful for Far Away
hi yeah
you need to switch games with narissa
ideally I know right yeah I got a tank
somebody
throw a potion on you if you need it
oh nice wait did you hit him no why
would you go back
you're good
we got it Avengers
guy everybody knows bards are just the
tanks just don't panic yeah exactly yeah
exactly perfect mm-hmm
now let's see can I uh kill him I had a
fence
a critical Miss yikes that doesn't feel
good 50 only Lindsay
friendies
God damn it I keep frenzying right
before you guys kill him
son of a stop being strong oh
there's some cool armor in there what
guzzler's Garb it's armor who can wear
this
armor
I am what what level
just ten it looks pretty good but I
don't know Gail can absorb it Cali but
Cali doesn't want it but I'm a Berserker
yeah it's not armor it's clothing
there's a difference apparently I don't
I yeah I keep on forgetting that I'm
wearing clothing it's not armor oh you
can wear it it's close yeah all right
I'll put them on somebody unlock this
heavy chest
oh I'll try I'll give it a hand
hey cool
that's pretty neat
okay let's see him oh
my Nike damn
I really fail wow I'm gonna use
inspiration
you open in the chest
there we go nice oh
wait did you open it
mine now
[Laughter]
nothing so special it's drow studded
armor or leather armor which is 12. rare
light armor
um basilisk oil antidote and a creased
paper
that if red says dark mother Weaver of
Destiny offer us a blessing to slay your
foes may they be strangled by the
threads of fate and died red in your
image love will be praised
okay nice voice good
okay oh wow this armor looks kind of
almost identical to the armor Liara is
wearing oh really yeah look I just put
it on for a minute this place is scary
oh we're gonna storm it right yeah yes
clearly wait wait wait wait wait wait
shoot the mushrooms first they'll
explode okay yeah yeah
well no problem we can do that
uh the not the toadstools right not not
them just the torch stock
Chihuahua
oh you guys want to see a secret place
yeah oh yeah okay
okay we're gonna jump on these shrooms
oh
wait is that safe
save games
over here for a second
second
yeah yeah nice
you got it
Z
okay
yeah okay oh there's this girl
oh wow wow what does Debbie doing here
he's got a helmet helmet of autonomy
after you she says kind of sucks he's in
the ground there you go bye
I'm not gonna take it I'll take it
oh oh a the festering code
Chasm sounds fun oh there's a lot of
people around here who look like they
might kill us and my health is kind of
low mm-hmm
oh yeah there are some freaky dudes we
can short Rush okay yeah we can do that
you also throw a potion on you oh yeah
all right Allison's buddy
nice yes cool friend real buddies all
right shall we go there then come on
wait before mad
look here
are they are we gonna fight them
I mean my guess is okay to go down there
that's all I'll say okay
Wow
since I handle it
and talk I guess
they look like murlocs he might as well
yeah yeah they're fish people cute yeah
they're just doing a little dance they
don't feel like nice to go guys
the things they're saying aren't very
calm and polite
maybe not
I'm so dirty
she's a shower
stinky
oh blood
Bowl
I'm made of blood
in place
manifest their gods through sheer belief
oh that's they are willing it into
existence wow that's powerful Magic
I hope you can convince him otherwise
I'm no one's off and get your bearings
one heavy stomach
oh I have
investigation proficiency
um actually ball is the god of murder
not bowel
I will say that then
cutlets
you're not the god of murder you just
don't want to be
he's a little ugly guy
if it's blood you want I can make
another offer I can oh what is it here's
my teammate
just gave her blood to a vampire it's
probably chill him
uh I can kill many more you know oh the
merciful
okay I'll oh favorable Beginnings Plus
four I'll try that I have only one life
but I can kill many more in your name I
guess
good luck 20. oh wow 20. I can't even
give you guidance on this yeah you gotta
really be persuasive good luck
inspiration
uh I don't is it worth it uh should I
really try you can also just kill him
yeah we can just yeah
no I won't we're gonna slurp you up
wow
he's gonna get blood he's gonna get
The High Ground
it's gonna be great
and all my friends use again
oh yeah you went right where I wanted to
put my daggers
[Music]
nice oh my God
one day ah what the I got electrocuted
the water there's water on the ground I
want to get out of there
bro
it is a little wet
um
Essie
Cali is also in the electrocution uh
Arrow I feel like I didn't get
electrocuted though
I'm chilling hopefully it'll stay like
that
yeah
oh my fisherman let's party
look at one of them is dead
hey
don't hit the bear
is my cuddy buddy yeah
need something to hug at night I'm sorry
was that supposed to hurt moriope
oh I can't wait to kill this little
blood Goblin guy and do it yeah very
high
oh more open thirst for blood
the Mori ope is the one that's thirsting
for murder right now I'm just saying
yes I should hit Raven will help you
okay please
him
oh yeah he hated that ooh it made him
really upset
shove him
oh wow nice wow nice nice one
it's so much for your God
yeah who's your god now wait everyone
else I see no God here other than me
I actually named this stream Mario fit
is gone
oh wow boom
and the Bear
ah
you're doing your best
huh
okay camera camera
I'm stuck like oh my camera okay oh you
go last fish oh I'm not down he knocked
me I sweat me off my feet
welcome
nah let's do a reckless attack
on him
oh
it's all right I forget oh huh what
happened
on the ground
uh
only like where where is the rest
there's only three left and they're all
archers so they're gonna be up to you
Liara hard to reach man hard to reach
how are you gonna get him
well first birth goes
I don't know
yeah there's rope netting
From Below yeah definitely not right 85
that's not bad
and then where's the other one can't
even see
there's one here all right oh first here
oh
oh oh oh oh oh thank you uh-huh yeah I
think that one's maybe easier to reach
for you actually
good luck oh nice good luck yeah you can
review you can reach him go Bagels
bagel
get them rough Em Up Rock Em Sock Em die
I missed
ah okay I'm behind him now
I slept on people's eyes
and
it's finished
you're welcome okay
to this guy oh it's nerissa
we're not that's okay I can't blame you
I'd lose yeah
go let's go
how far
can I shoot from here I doubt it
Target too far yeah they're pointing out
your bird can fly further than it can
walk if you pick the fly it can go
pretty far uh yeah uh yeah bird already
too late now
okay
here we go again
wow that's the spoils these guys had
nothing in there bro
money in the in the chest up here where
I am wait this guy this guy
this guy had a sickle of ball
oh that sounds kind of nice I'm not
gonna lie
we already opened it
is this a pearl oh nice oh don't forget
we can level by the way oh yeah when did
that happen literally didn't realize
that level up never mind
assistance to make decisions
Ranger level five
fast movement extra attack
I get an extra attack nice
oh darling
oh boy they'll never see him Oreos
[Music]
I love that freaking song so much
catchy if I hear it once it'll be stuck
in my head the entire day it's karaoke
[Music]
well that's a big sea monster bones
what's all over here
I'll take it nothing much ooh fish
Barrel
Chasm is a Chasm okay I made my level up
Choice I'm ready
cool
I guess we go and enter that big
foreboding place
if there's if there's fish collect the
fish because we can use that for food
yeah I'm true there was a dude holding
fish
hurry up I use dig on the dirt Mound I
think we get a chest we got that so much
crap in my inventory again
give me the fish
I found a message in a bottle that reads
Dad sorry I stopped writing we ran out
of paper on the road I got this from The
Druids maybe that's why they're so mad
at us I hope that this can find you
zevilar says you got lost and that our
old house is gone but I read a book that
says all Rivers find their way into the
sticks when you get it can you write me
back in Baldur's Gate or maybe come
visit I'll write again when I can get
more paper Donnie oh Donnie knows what
the river sticks to me why do I have a
second bear and this one wears armor I'm
so comfortable
that's kind of cool
evolved it's a Pokemon yeah oh there's
so much gold here
um
that's called the Ecstasy of murder
cool good food collection
any other goodies
little little gold pieces on the ground
what would you find in the heavy chest
baby
um some money and some potions I got a
potion of giant strength you might be
interested
she already has giant strings that is
true
in my own game in my own game I got Gail
a spell where he can actually make you
big oh wow I didn't know that was like
big well I haven't tried it yet but I'm
like whoa some people may really like
this oh come on this is the first thing
that I thought so I thought I'd share
with the class
oh some people certainly like that
see here you get what I mean I get what
you mean totally I had to say my
memories of the internet Remind Me of
anything do you guys not sometimes think
when you were at a concert and you're
sitting in one of the back seats that
you don't see what's going on on the
stage wouldn't you wish especially for
YouTubers where technology basically
permits anything nowadays to just size
them up like 100 times to be a giant
woman on stage yes yeah that on stage so
even when you're really far away you can
see them really well isn't that an idea
of a genius or what that's super smart
actually
it's brilliant they people should pay
you money for that idea thank you I
already brought it up to management
actually
it's good oh my God brought it up to
Japanese management when I was in Japan
and they just laughed at me
so funny
hip squeaks but I'm serious about this
okay
very serious I just want to make it
experience better not go like sorry
don't go there
like holograms on the you know you don't
see those like mushrooms
cyberpunky cities with like Holograms
and stuff
or some
or something yeah like big holographic
women that's what I imagine oh yeah
like some kind of like Blade Runner
yeah Blade Runner yeah which one do we
go
yeah there's a big doorway that we I
mean it's up to you but you know there
was a big doorway over there if you want
to go to it
oh doorway out here okay yes yes it
looks good looks good oh this is cool
too it's just like a little is that a
fishing Hamlet Village looks like Oh
wrong way sorry this way oh what the
I'm being targeted
by who I don't know carrot
but it's
oh my God
oh oh my bird stuck uh oh no I'll just
I'll just re-summond them
about to get shot
this area is yeah bye
[Music]
did you cast your news that was a spell
for the whole party
people can shoot that thing the Arcane
Tower
yeah
probably the arcave tower
all right then
[Music]
here Cali
yeah I gave you a movement bub
blesome yeah
the third magical turret dude
wait enter turn baseball so he doesn't
you know so he doesn't yeah constantly
there you go I'm trying to shoot at the
ready
can I just rail him
oh he's 30.
there must be some way to hurt him I I
can't ah
no it's too sturdy yeah
oh nice
there's another one up there there's
another one okay I have I have a spell
left
can I get to it I have to wait for my
next turn though okay
wow people are freaking hero mm-hmm
there's some cool chest over there
hero bee boo who's the real hero
I'm not gonna try and hit something that
I can't kill
so I'll chill right here
one more health potion
stay alive Kelly
mm-hmm near our tank we need you
trying to get my health back
I'll chill in this corner because that
turret I don't think I can beat it yeah
I need to wait till my next turn to get
close enough thanks
for the heels but it doesn't see me yet
so it should be okay
careful friends
[Music]
go get him yeah Target is hamstrings
make sure he can't run yeah
oh hell yeah
what was in the chest
we're about to find out what's in that
bad boy let me lock pick it oh it's 15.
you did it you succeed
I just want to see I want to look at it
that's a big heart you know yes no
Sky breaker
yeah but I mean it's cool but I don't
feel like I would use this any of you
guys like hammers
yeah he could use it yeah she's not
stronger than what I have
for throwing I mean that's true but I
have a lot of things I can throw keep in
mind
save games
you never really came in clutch there
that was cool right
yeah okay oh we're at the Arcane Tower
oh
[Music]
is this
shall we try wait the the
tentacle guy told us to find mushrooms
here here yum yeah
oh
add inside inside the Arcane Tower
oh yeah oh wait can I enter turn mode
there's another there's another thing oh
a turret yeah
make them pay oh
maybe we should all get in first then oh
yeah you can just go through there all
right why use the door when there's
windows
it's mine
people really taking one for the team
there
hey
I'll I'll offer myself as a Target as
well
yeah
uh there's one on the other side but I
am now out of a spell so I can't oh well
actually
behind it maybe I can use shocking grass
hold on let me sneak
hopefully you won't you see me oh okay
leave me alone see me oh boy
oh Jesus
that's fine
you want potion
uh sure yeah I'm gonna throw it on you
you don't need it yeah
you don't need it we're good oh we're
good oh thank you oh
swag do we do a short rest no I healed
you because I'm so cool like that
kill the rest so that no one that one
that the one can Thrive
so is there a mushroom supposed to be in
here
yeah somewhere I don't see a mushroom in
I can feel its magic
nice view mundane that's a hell of nice
for sure
pretty eh please I'm gonna go there
with the pretty trees
huh
that just transforms
what happened to the church oh the stuff
turned into stuff oh oh
the stuff turned into stuff
bad stuff in the good stuff
I got what did I get I don't know
different stuff uh
well I got
a bomb
nice oh a light bomb I got some school I
got some shoes
yeah stuff neat
hmm But no mushrooms
she's lying what
people's lying
like lying about what I don't know stuff
what
biboo you're not streaming your
perspective you can't lie
that's what I got right yeah yeah
that's right I trust bibo more than chat
over here
I got a scroll of Mage Armor some shoes
sounds legit
sounds legit well there's no mushrooms
here what guys come here I'm here oh
wait
oh yeah I thought that was an entrance
what
it's an elevator I don't know I haven't
seen this before but it seems like it
there's addition
Yara I feel like we're already so high
up so it's like some kind of magical
it's a tower Contraption now to get it
to get it to work
the Jinx who owe me a soda
I think I do we perhaps need those uh
like pieces
to fix it that I saw somewhere on it
I picked up some like
mechanical pieces
I know another Contraption of some sort
and don't think so man
you need to power it from the ground
floor eh
are we not on the ground floor no no
look at the balcony just below us yeah
you can see we're like really high up
hey come over here
see you see oh
well
that's a way to go oh
um all right
down the mushrooms okay
out oh a little bit painful
say something only again is there
machines in here too that shoot us no no
no
but this place looks broken shins
pretty blue Barrel there's mushrooms in
there so um
moldy cheese it's rotten cheese wheel
we love our mushrooms yeah
nice retrospective
I can't redo
I just found a book that feels like
retrospective
I found some mushrooms some timis spores
what's the name of the mushroom that
we're looking for I don't know but I
know we need the weird tongue one I
picked up the weird tongue oh so we have
it okay yeah
we got the fetch Quest
[Music]
called mushroom
is that just Somewhere Over the Rainbow
I come to you I want to follow our
leader okay but you want to jump down
the balcony or what
do you your your call boss I will die we
will not live
[Music]
feather fall can I use this do it
is true
let's try it
[Music]
oh
I lived okay just aim for a spot try to
jump down
oh look at these looser flowers Peter
Pan
jumping
okay
what else is there to find
I don't know how much is this
shiny it's like a sakura tree but with
blue lightings don't it ruins your magic
you ruined I don't have magic oh yeah
that's my magic feels yeah but we have
magic so if you grab it and we're around
you you'll throw it away
um you can send it to Camp
I got a scroll of haste I opened up the
building oh all right
oh
uh-huh
yeah a nice person there's a hole
a hole but people who go in there
oh I'm too big of course yeah
but I am maybe but familiars can't go we
learned that before right so
really I wonder how you're supposed to
be able to oh is it the Misty step
they all have Arma now
you can go yeah
yeah rat can't go oh yeah because you're
actually shape shift Hmm this is where
we can fix the elevator
ready
[Music]
disorders and mind
I found Lawless candle and Lackey light
cellulite
last one
of that up it's in my inventory if you
want to see it I don't know what it does
though
what's inside hey
songs
slow man
y'all sound tired AF well you know it's
just 6 a.m for some people yeah six
seven sorry what's the time it just
turned seven for me good morning it's 9
A.M now oh nine a.m yours
so that's luxury
I sleep into like 11 every day what do
you mean
okay power generator oh combined items
what does it want
I don't know
where did that thing go
what could it want
[Music]
um
a blue flower ah the blue the flat wow
did somebody pick up the blue flower
yeah I picked it up yeah put it in there
yeah
stick it in there
I sent it to Camp no can we get another
one another one outside yes quick
there's another one wait go to camp and
then grab it if there's not one there's
another one out here okay Google grab it
okay no enemies around so you know safe
and sound
right here oh
magic oh fire
magic okay I need my magic erupt violent
and Powerful
why did we send the magician out there
to get the no magic flowers
without magic
free maybe don't you feel free
I don't care
what's your powers I don't care magic
Cannot Be Tamed
not even by you
oh you have no magic I'll just Bonk
yeah it's okay and the moment you get
the flower off of you your magic works
again so you're good
all good
pretty flower Inferno iron I'm so shiny
right now yeah drop that bad boy in
there
[Music]
Lord
oh everyone you made it nice one you did
it
I'm gonna go it's powered by anti-magic
well we were already at the top and the
mid level so how does this I I don't
know if we were at the top level oh oh
it deactivated the oh and it activates
the lamps cute
so is there a top top yeah they're still
yeah we haven't been there or there oh
there's two levels exciting
nice scene is there something waiting
for us up there
I have no idea so we're gonna find out
together such a cool Tower Rory wants
treasure treasure okay we can go up this
way
that I follow a little earlier we are
woohoo
you're my golden stuff oh more real but
you're so slow
she's so slow because the camera is so
slow for me it's so glowing how do you
guys see the upper level I can't see
can we get much higher
one more
oh this is new or is everyone we're
hitting the Ascend button yeah
I see oh
Ascend oh decent I see that's how it
works
tender
Sendo
and what's an anal guys
hello I don't know what's good
oopsies I thought all of you guys
for you I come in peace
that's not true let me persuade you
little speed
we can be cool are you in trouble okay
we'll just end am i b but I'm going to
descend
like yeah yeah
if I can descend here let me press the
button so what's an annual a-n-n-a-o
it's a kind of book I don't know what it
means though specifically
can't be cool anymore apparently I see
red dots up there are you in a fight
it would appear so
would you like it doesn't have
let's go you did not want it for me oh
yeah sure
I found something cool don't make much
sense of them but you're fine for all
primer to Aid you we need to get the
Yankees
[Music]
that's okay
the disc doesn't oh animated armors
using ranged attack yeah I'm kind of
getting slam jammed over here yeah maybe
Lee yeah
you were powered up and like went kind
of nutty okay oh
the battle has commenced even though
we're on the ground run
bee boo
you can always reload I guess yeah
oh Mario these guys are really really
tanky
we've got a lot of shiny armor
animated armor WoW
wow
oh because that's like visible to them
oh messed up yeah I'm dead
Supreme load the game
um f let's not go to that level yeah
yeah slowly I'm sorry I thought you guys
were at the very that's okay yeah it's
understandable like I I would have
thought so too if people didn't we do
need to prepare for whatever that is
though I tried to be nice to them they
were not having it so I don't know what
the proper response is for them I don't
know if you can ever be friends with
them they're just rude
yeah they're very mean and inconsiderate
and think they're embarrassing you can
find books in the tower to give them
commands
oh really
yeah so maybe in that second level
or that level right before rather yeah
okay this is the floor you guys were on
yes yeah
gotcha okay
Glory
let's be on my way chips
there are books and then
there are more books
this is pretty cool yeah oh there's
controls full of speak with dead on
death and Resurrection
but then strange place for a button
strange place for a button especially
one that doesn't work the wooden chest
wait that was I put it on your face oh
yeah she's lying there oh whoopsies
I didn't do anything it's too dark to
see
turn on some lights
oh a history of the city of Ballers
great as told with a Bard's flare oh
Lord
place
oral history is a favorite yeah
mysterious
[Music]
serious button oh there's another chest
over there oh what's in there nothing uh
somebody probably already took it
no it's okay
oh yeah there was a ring
um a magic ring a Mages ring so I'm
wearing it now
okay where's the the disc that you found
before
it's in my inventory
um didn't we get the dialogue again
I just skipped it okay okay
Cara what do you want to do let's go up
um we need to read all the wait wait say
first and let's read all the books that
we picked up I read a bunch of things in
this room
yeah I I picked up a ton of books so
okay let's see there's one up here
um
I don't think this one helps the one
that I have
just Baldur's Gate history lesson
[Music]
okay
I spy wanna take a bath
like just like a bath before taking one
together yeah never mind I'm good
a fish hour
[Music]
you really you really set me up for it
I did
so what what about the books who has the
books um I read all my books I only
picked up like five I didn't get
anything books on the ground that I read
there I couldn't pick them up but
there's like a gear icon so I read them
um read them yeah
yeah
oh and there's a paper here
the silent stretches and I'm all alone
please can I hold your hands just for a
while oh
sweet oh wow what's this
oh wonderful art of your ciphers
Anki origin and come to such archaic
lightings what is this pick it up how do
I pick it up you can use it to decipher
things I think
oh
moriope doesn't know how to read
my head Cannon
fitting so if we can use it apparently
for something but oh
I have a hide-bound journal that says
one favor one faithful servant that is
all I summon no more no less than the
malice do ordin ever had or indeed the
mother of lust herself the yachlo was
quite a sight in all its forms I'd read
of its foul order but I found it
intoxicating like rose water so it
smashed a few artifacts his head a
master the archmade should have revered
me for such a Conjuring instead he
threatened to curse me to make me a
dryer yet my time will come soon I will
return to menzo baranzen and his
sorcerer then the archmage will worship
me I will be served but I don't see how
that helps speaking in riddles to me
yeah yeah sometimes mysterious
they're saying the books wouldn't have
been in the bookcases they'll just be
sitting around and we have to pick them
up and one person has to hold all of
them oh okay
I'm Gonna Leave it to you guys because I
don't know what to do
and I'm not smart same
I'm just a Bard man
are they all on this floor
or elsewhere to
because
I also found books on different floors
sort by newest good idea
latest
one person has to read them that person
needs to be the one to talk to the
construct so whoever read them you got
to go up first what is the book guys
what is the book name
yes tell us tell us or else
give us the answer now let's stop can we
save it and see if there's stuff now
yeah okay save
oh not that kind of saved
him anyway go up and see what happens
hello
oh boy
oh
you know these words oh we know these
words
found in this very Tower I see
uh
uh I guess chat yes this one is new
oh yeah for me
nothing seals
oh
he likes me Amanda
um
oh no do you remember what it said uh
oh
I remember this one yeah yeah oh number
three I read this one
can we hold hands oh
robots
this is kind of neat
yes please
[Laughter]
gears are gonna spin you up into a
smoothie mm-hmm
so much
[Music]
I haven't been hugged in 10 years it's
like me flirting with TTS yesterday
can we all go up now are we good are you
safe are there more things that we can
say to him
maybe each of the different commands are
like you get different dialogue with
them
um
okay
tick okay okay let's save
Mario but save game
where's it going okay oh yes if you guys
are going I'll go
hey is he showing you a book who is this
oh he put a
Kimpton down nice
uh Guiding Light it's a ring uncommon
it has a light can trip should we talk
to the other ones too they don't seem
like they want Africa yeah this one
doesn't want to talk
um
I can throw a hammer give me that
you could also send further I suppose
space wait wait wait we can go to the
basement now yeah
wait is there even anything any further
up wait let's let's talk to people first
always find out ladder
he doesn't seem to want to chat no
which is a shame because he seems cool
well nothing up here
okay I think basement it is
oh my basement thing is gone
it's gone there's only a defense it came
back oh okay oh
basement where does that go it was all
maybe it only takes one of us at a time
it won't let me
oh wait wait you guys go first I think I
have to be yeah because you're
perceiving it or so I don't know
[Music]
okay go first
there is a kick-ass staff on the top
floor somebody says
I I like staffs
yes I don't know where though I'm
already all the way on the basement
because he's
if y'all want to want to find that um oh
there's a staff of Arcane blessing is
that what they're talking about that
might be it
hey but you can still use them when
they're whenever you feel like you can't
do anything else
that's a good point I did pick up some
some daggers
um
it's pretty cool yeah
it's always nice to have some Scrolls
for backup classroom
what'd you find in the chest View
I got a ring that gains resistance to
lightning damage which is good because I
do lightning damage
yes
maybe you should give the ring to the
people you keep on
[Music]
all right I get the this I see I see how
it is
see what you guys think of me all right
I understand oh that's a connection over
here shortcut found whoops
wow
well what else was there in the basement
you know oh I'm not sure I don't want to
split the party too much
before
not wherever or yeah I'll be right there
keep living
on my way
wow beautiful ah hi nerissa hello
we found the staff right is that it
was it was it the staff of what did you
say Arcane blessing right
uh uh I don't know because that's what I
found out to be apparently there's still
something left at the top
and yeah talk to the construct again now
some people are saying that's the 1B
boom okay the staff is great for clerics
okay
lyrics
the clerks I think it is
[Music]
did anyone pick out the top floor
well we're all on the top floor no no
there's one more above it
yeah let's go up
sounds good and uh
up
and up
I'm on my way I'm just taking the longer
path up
[Music]
at the chair near the table on the top
chair
and ascend
Ascend not Ascend again
there's a stairway
here
um oh it doesn't
lead anywhere else apart from just up
here
other
[Music]
um
what I heard there was a staff up here
up here
there's a great stool
great stool
oh is it this this stool that says stool
of giant strength or whatever saying to
talk to the main guy again
the robot there's a story oh that's a
funny stool yeah Little Giant strength
what is that maybe somebody with giant
shrink faster okay oh to you
yeah
yeah breaking it didn't break break it's
closed Molly has to smash maybe yes oh
yeah
oh
giant strength
who uses clothes who wants it let's go
to the club
what kind of weapon is it I wonder is it
magical uh it is
it is magical it does two to five damage
splinters of giant smart increases
strength to 19.
[Music]
yeah
yeah oh no
yeah it's cute it's cute
a bonk stick all right let's get out of
here then I guess
it's good offhand keep it you get a bow
that profits from strength later oh okay
Coolio
kind of cool
uh which level do we want to go to to
basement I'm in the basement okay
insanely good club they say
yes
send wait no I wanted to go to
I'll figure this out moriope is not good
with directions
oh there's more tongues here tongue of
magic wait did you guys did you guys
abandon moriope up there I mean I don't
see the basement
it's only visible no I don't want to be
I don't want to be a burden yeah
is so cute oh that's the kind thing to
say thank you people let's get out of
here okay we'll meet you on the ground
floor
yeah are we lost Dad no no we're fine
you always say it's just me and you
just me and you
Kitty
here we are in the moment
[Laughter]
thank you I am the prettiest of all I'm
so beautiful I know this
is there a way is there anywhere to go
from here or was it this was this like a
dead end
um
pretty dead to me yeah yeah
don't know if we can make any jumps here
we could just teleport back to we could
go to back to mushroom Place yeah the
mycenae colony okay nice idea let's do
that
oh yeah
cool apparently the big robot also has a
special weapon but yeah
you have to kill him
I don't want it yeah wait do we give the
the mushroom to to whoever asked for it
yeah yeah
yeah the main guy right give it to that
guy
was it the the leader who asked for it
yeah successful
um
[Applause]
lines
impressed by them
drink the entire
Drive
[Music]
enjoy yeah
the acidic liquid tightens your throat
oh burning on the way down you didn't
even ask him what it was gonna do do you
know what's gonna do to you
as the potion
you may find yourself acting
irrational irrationally try and stay
focused act up sounds like you're drunk
the world
's inches
finer boundaries
fluid a trap trap like a creature
suspended in Amber
oh should I saving throw yeah I mean
yeah yeah probably otherwise you might
die
all right I think it'll be fine look at
all those bonuses give me my blush
actually no I want it yeah it's less
yeah why not
hey you didn't even lived another day
dark holes bite at the edges of your
vision
therefore you cannot draw you in
attack of spasms seizes
fighting the potion even harder than you
are fear peace is your mind like knives
of ice well the mushroom is to get rid
of the tadpole right
um
protects me I guess
oh
look at your bonuses you're fine
just barely
yay
okay don't take the mushrooms The Edge
not today Squidward not today
against itself
which is
lashing out against that I could go for
some food right now good morning for you
in your mind pancakes breakfast oh yeah
some of you make them for me I want to
make French toast
I think I'm I'm not French
I'm
sick
oh so it didn't kill it no of course not
because that would be too easy too early
too easy
yeah yeah you can you can smooth your a
tentacle guy
you have a technical moment I'll leave
that to you Mori open no I'm good I
already have my my love
[Laughter]
although
I may have another solution
albeit a temporary one
it goes as well as you could expect a
ring of Mind shielding
that prevents Elder brains from noticing
my presence it will not remove the lava
but it will limit its influence
both positive and negative I would offer
it as a gift but in truth that's nice he
wants to make a deal priceless
I take it as it's free I become your
consort
uh how about I
tell you about
I'll tell you a story every Last Detail
what can you tell me you got a pinky
promise first
um oh I see performance
give a dramatic
agree to mine so there is a ship and we
were on it good luck
and we crashed it was on fire and there
were brain people and
experience
and then step things
what a story mark
he liked that of course he's entertained
well Sasuke we are streamers after all
and we have stories all the time
you know he's our audience oh I'm
poisoned now though
oh yeah wow you gotta throw up that
potion
you have an advantage on saving those
against charms if anybody wants it oh
they can have it the ring gnome ring of
my shielding I'm gonna I'm gonna go full
brain brain worms this run time ah I
love Charmed
your mom likes it too ah yeah let's go
that's why she that's why she chose as
her Reaper name to be Andorra
yeah
I'm Charmed right his
face
I don't remember an Endora what
it was definitely from charm right it's
just like another misunderstanding with
like you know Golden Girls
never mind
it seems we had another misunderstanding
okay
the second time this has happened with
you
you don't worry but maybe your mom still
likes Trump maybe ask her sometime yeah
I'll ask her it seems like a show she'd
like
um
when will anybody ever understand my my
TV series uh I think I like I grew up
watching Charmed with my mom too who was
your favorite mom you know I don't
remember the names too well because it's
been a really obnoxiously long time but
the one who died
the one who ah okay you're like well I
don't know I don't know I mean that's
too late to spoil it like just yeah the
show is so old but true yeah yeah I
didn't like Prue at all it's because I
liked her actor
oh yeah she was very hot yeah yeah yeah
I would agree with that I like the girl
who replaces her later
um Paige
I like the opening because it's a Smith
song
um ah yeah how soon is now but I didn't
know that
for a long time
so I was like oh my God what a based
show it seems like they kind of lost
rights to it because when you watch the
show now on like Amazon Prime or
whatever they replaced the music with
something similar that that wouldn't
surprise me the Smiths are kind of
oh they're drama baby
um more seem is a character
oh that's it yeah he's a singer
he's the character he's he's the singer
he's a he's a character do you know that
expression Chihuahua yeah yeah I know
yeah yeah yeah yeah character
I have a weird weapon in my inventory
the bull walls arms I didn't know I
picked that up and it's like his pincers
like a cancer
I'll throw them if you don't know what
else to do with them oh yeah
sell sell it crap crap crap why did I
say cancer
in my in German it's like the same word
cancer and crab
okay
um oh there's another Trader down below
okay I'll go find them
here I'll leave you Mario pay come with
me missing pets thank you narissa
okay I'm actually uh done to anyone oh
very well let me go clean out this guy
let's see what he's got Marissa uh is
your character just you
eh yeah you're self-insert yeah
mine's a self-insert too
English one to one
yeah
you mean the personality or both
Valen
can you describe I haven't seen him yes
I've met him which is a lie
you describe him
gold blue tunic
domicistic
show me your wares really quick that's
what I'm in here for I need to sell some
things
maybe we can help her too though
she's yeah looking for someone right
it seems like um
let's see I'm at this ring I don't want
that Cali is
catnaw nah who am I Callie's I'm sorry I
I don't know about that self insert
you're I find you way more Charming
outside of this game
what no this is literally what I'm like
no
but have you seen a Syrian like he's
like you know wow yeah that's a good
point actually this this older character
is more attractive
oh my God he's just being real this
I don't mind it so much I really don't I
don't need anything this is huge this
Amulet of unworthy grants resistance to
slashing damage grants vulnerability to
bludgeoning damage that's really
interesting
oh even the the little why was I well
guys
everybody likes my music oh I want to
play too yeah join me
very well wait what song are you playing
I'm doing I'm doing the power
I think they're bullying me
[Music]
let me talk to him
they're yelling
[Music]
wow ooh do they hate you
oh you're not good
you're not even so nerissa to play music
yum
oh yeah I can hear it Vivo I know you're
doing your best it's quite pretty
I'm sorry I actually want to attack you
sorry it's angry
yeah I love how he moves oh he's so
angry so mad he's so upset
want to go
he's not playing girl stop playing
I won't improve if I don't practice
exactly I don't know if this is a skill
you can improve on
oh no he's so upset don't listen to him
poor performance
are you okay
[Music]
they're just haters don't worry about it
he treats me good now doesn't care
anymore
that we want to find right
down my arm really quick
not my arm or my club
combined
oh my God are you actually putting on
clothes well yeah I mean oh my gosh wow
wait that look good
what did that the clothing you just had
on put that on the game oh yeah no I
definitely will I need it to be swamp
green okay ice team okay Shrek calm down
yeah are you friends with right now or
why are you so
me oh no it's because a Starion took my
blood oh yeah still okay
bloodless till next long rest
there we go now I'm nice and ogary oh
yeah you can dye your clothes let's go
fashionista baby give me some money
and I got a necklace of restoration
which means if I have heal spells now if
I put it on
okay pretty cool nice
I'll put that on next time we see a dead
dude
come on Gamers oh
Gamers where do we go next
this way yeah
[Music]
and then I'll let you lead but we should
go out this way oh yeah ah this is where
we started out anyway today
yeah okay we teleported out of here
immediately oh we could go
ah let's go this way
I think because that way there's a quest
over there that the final balance
it's a cute Pumbaa that we have on our
team
that
okay
[Music]
will it go away
Marissa does not care I'm fine I'm just
a Bard man
you are working on becoming more of a
tank day by day mm-hmm
oh there's a lot of bombs let's go
I'll help you shoot them yeah there's no
no no no no no no oh my God you guys are
crazy there's no biggies
you gotta look in there there's a man oh
oh oh oh oh
um
oh my God
nice
well
[Music]
what are you doing here
get it she's
I must hmm
yeah
for you oh
nice thank you
um
Michael Bay filmed right there oh
invisibility oh hey he's fine
yes
hey and all the fire is gone what night
embarrassingly I'm picking up stuff oh
there's some Scrolls
but they're proving hard to pick up for
some reason oh there's something there
there he is
but this
is
I just want to see what's in there
only I can open it the money and grease
but I've got enough grease freeze is
pretty good oh yeah if you have like
fire bolt or whatever there's some
candles here why is there so many
candles these crazy stuff babies someone
was doing some prayer
they look pretty yeah yeah it's the
scary the scary God candle oh smallest
candle
but that's
oh
I suppose is everything here yeah okay
then we completed that question does she
want to talk all right let's also save
because of wow that luck
is that really lucky I don't know what
you mean there is uh I killed that guy
so many times
I tried that too
great doing great job Kiara's just
perfect is what it is
alrighty are you lucky we'll take it
yeah I wonder if the if they want to
talk to us again about the quest or um
they will but they'll they'll stay there
so if you wanted we could do the next
Quest where we need to kill the durger
and then just go back and report all
those at the same time yes
is the quest item still there or did it
go boom says Chad
Quest items wasn't he the quest Adam
a guy
it looks like
nothing it may have gone boom boom Oh
well
not bring this flower I'll get it during
my birthday
you were a magic debuffing us
sent to Camp okay
maybe this way
[Music]
which Quest are we going for I don't see
anything on the map
um we remember in our last playthrough
we were talking to the guy the the the
big mushroom Sovereign and he wanted us
to kill someone we need to find a place
that we need to kill the jurgers I uh
was that like a dwarf also
yeah it's just keep walking around we'll
eventually run into something oh there's
a village
bloodborne
all up or down well now I went up I'm
probably down it looks like we're just
going back to the my Synod Colony now
sorry
there's some something to go down here
and dead body executed
he's got a cool short sword of First
Blood yeah get that little guy
is that good for someone
looks powerful let's do this and then I
can throw
give me that club I can throw it
oh there's more oh there's more depth
let's go dead people dead bodies
everywhere
oh wait who has talking today I have the
thing with the dead please the dead body
what's that
I'm very curious
all right I got it now let me say hello
oh
okay
let me see
hey you can move faster now increased by
three meters
up there
oh I can
see if I can talk to this guy okay eh
could you not talk to the other one
um I'm using a scroll oh okay
[Music]
that's too bad what
eh
bad a fish they should tell me that
before I talk to them yeah wait I'll try
one too cast spell it better have
something to say
they glow green if you can talk to them
a corpse too damaged Ah that's what
happened okay okay oh well then again
I guess yeah that's a bit of a rip-off
it's a rip-off y'all
hey did you waste the scroll for that I
don't know I think it was a scroll but
I'm not sure I just used a necklace yeah
I have a necklace so I can use as well
yeah but I can only use it once
oh well
there will be more chances to speak to
the dead that was cool though
those are you guys okay there's a
waypoint
oh oh really take a team yeah there's a
waypoint and a yummy looking witch's
stew
and it looks like somebody forgot about
their cooking which is something I'd
never do never
getting about it
yeah I'm blind I'm sorry
[Music]
oh
ancient sigil I'll need it well
they say it's better after a couple days
a corpse is glowing green I could have
talked to him uh
but rest
they got cool stuff
we talked to you oh whoa whoa
uh-oh I wanted to talk to that course
hey look we're chill right steps are too
loud
oh we're chilling half orc intimidation
I'm hungry for a fight but you're fairly
immorsal this is your next move
character back down or bleed
use my half work and I like it add a
bonus
bardic inspiration thank you narissa but
that's the guy we agreed to kill okay
yeah
yeah let's just pretend like we're
friends for now let me sneak up on him
and beat him up
fine
I'll let you live hi idiot spoil my hunt
and you're dead
[Music]
what are you doing here
told you hunting
slave ran away okay no need to be rude
I'm a little slow
respect the leather
all the boss is in Moonrise they'll have
friends hide oh the moonrise Towers
maybe I could help
she really kills someone for a pair of
boots someone helping a slave catcher
would you really kill someone for a pair
of boots
wow maybe I could help
you don't even know what you'd be up
against slaves and protection
my whole crew is pretty strong yeah
can't get past those Rock flowers
jumped off a cliff laughing ah let's go
sounds like fun
she'll make a run for it eventually
then I'll get a
I don't like him yeah free I'm not
helping a slave catcher your problems
are your own I'm leaving
suppose I'll just eat you then oh
okay you can give it a try all right
let's kill him all righty oh he's got
some bunnies Oh I thought the way that I
went about it was real nice but okay oh
oh
make a new save
um you can do save
yeah we can make a save
that should be fun uh we'll just take it
reanimated course oh I have no spell
slots yeah I have none either oh no and
I've been silenced oh no oh
weak
[Music]
yeah these guys suck I mean anything oh
my God
best be on my way
um
yeah okay
[Music]
I'll get a second one why
he's very unlucky the game really wants
us to reload yeah
but I don't wanna that's so lame I can
attack twice though wow
that is nice a difficult situation that
we find ourselves in now we can kill him
should be fun
do a big old ax swing you know we have
like a bear not a bear we have a Pumbaa
bomba yeah yeah
I'm playing this music
fine these guys eat yeah saying
yeah there's four of us and there's a
lot of them
oh they Blinded Me
that was cool
and then
got it what
is Battle Tunes am I not done what is
what is this intern ah huh
ice
oh come on I was I was listening to that
man he didn't like that wanna hate her
yeah it sucks
let's see
frenzy it seems need a long rest for
that I'm assuming oh attack together
yeah together
come on these guys are a little beefy
but that's okay
just show them
yeah you jerk yeah well the way he gets
back up
actually impressive
wow
he really's got a death wish
they are very replaceable
definitely a long rest is an order after
this yeah
for sure I want to talk to that big body
beneath my shoes
yeah let's go yeah
pretty good that's really good actually
yeah that's fine let's go
can you stop trying to Blind me thank
you he knows you're strong
you can feel it mm-hmm
you know how strong you are that's all
I'm not strong I don't have any spells
don't
um
true true
what's happening oh I was just checking
something
[Music]
hit him hard
free leaving it to you girl all right no
problem
we got it together
let's see that's very healthy this
dude's about to die I know this one's
healthy and this one's healthy this
guy's about to die
[Music]
getting the good POV
oh
[Music]
whoa there excuse you but keep doing it
I wonder how they come up with all these
phrases
I'm playing a lot of DNB
did you guys see the voice actors
playing DND I did no what that's so cool
yeah
asterian voice actor so what are they
doing
um
pretty cool actually I like him getting
distracted by Gail's boots when he
failed a role
cute
okay something knocked down there
leave him alone
I guess I put ice down when I used oh I
see okay
that's why I didn't want to walk out
okay well
that was my reason
oh
no no
still alive
speaking of Pumbaa did I tell you guys
about the Roomba incident
no
Roomba yeah so my cat ghost cat
sometimes you know he poops outside of
his litter box on accident yeah I have a
Roomba you use your room bro okay it
automatically goes at 9 00 a.m every day
and I had been sleeping
wait it did it like suck up some fresh
poop
no it did the opposite it smeared it all
over
that was bad that's the Roomba incident
those guys are still pretty small you
can't make such big ghost poops right
that was pretty big
smeared all over the carpet in the floor
I had to get a new carpet
but the carpet is a big yikes yeah it's
pretty rough it's okay he's just he's
just a wee little lad yeah it wasn't his
fault I can't be mad at my cats for any
accidents either no it's the room
for not sensing the poo poo yeah
added a smelling sensor to the remote
exactly that's a piece of dookie maybe
let's not go hard
kind of thing I actually really activate
my room but I had one like it's still in
its box since like like years
damn
good I don't know I I know that like
resetting it is kind of annoying when
like you change something in your room
and so I felt like I will start using it
when I'm 100 set on the furniture's
position in my apartment all right but I
should really activate it I didn't
change Furniture in a while if your cats
hate that Roomba they're going to make
plans to destroy it I.E leaving
droppings around
I know that chunky wonky will be very
scared of the Roomba because she's
scared of my my hair dryer and
everything else that makes loud sounds
you know monkey
man
she'll have to get used to it
what the hell oh two dudes get rid of
these dudes double demon
destroy them this guy refused to die I
had him on death's doorstep
[Music]
don't think a Roomba is like yeah yeah I
guess not but like
um
it moves around and chunky monkey gets
scared probably oh googly eyes on it
that's a great idea Chad what ah yeah
give him some googly eyes
yeah you like that
yeah for real
so Cali has your apartment been taken
over by like fur yet yeah yes but I have
a really good vacuum it's a Dyson that
has like a green light on it that shines
on the ground and it shows all the dust
particles and all the hair whoa
it's good I recommend it
um
not sponsored by the way that's what
makes such cool things I really want the
hair dryer from Dyson
yeah the one that we saw Kelly good yeah
Hotel fancy
good good stuff
okay
lame yeah
and a silly
here I think why is he so tanky
quit being tanky you should have used
the rage can I hit him hit him
[Applause]
oh yeah the dumb dwarf dude yeah
why what's there's the large guy right
here
yeah then there's another one up but if
we go up there then we'll get
electrocuted
oh it's like that I see the guys
we're gonna stick them out anyway uh
shall try to go up
oh
it continues
what happened
yeah I'm just confused
somehow
I thought we were done and yet there's
more now I just three dudes up here okay
okay
[Music]
I'll fetus dude right here
oh I can shoot again but that probably
yeah I thought so okay
dwarf
wow sickness
yucky well I can do that too though
where he moves up
oh
yeah I get the other guy
no two we got a corner in
I get two attacks now that I'm level
five oh that's what's going on
interesting yeah
pretty cool yeah
toys
oh
I can't hit him twice oh well
yeah I'm not tired do I seem tired
I'm just chilling yeah well there is
this Bard has this really chill music
that plays everyone it's like yeah I'm
getting the chit chat mode with you
ladies when I hear it
get him
yeah yeah you want one more
[Music]
I'm gonna jump over here
oh man go go you want someone man yeah
fisticuffs
[Music]
ready
that should work
Here Comes why was Arrow yes yeah
[Music]
one more but yeah for I only have 36
percentage
and now it's on 16 never mind Hey I just
moved two more steps
is that because of Hunter's Mark that's
cracked yeah I use it all the time it
pops a bit
outside
are you okay you poisoned all right
that's fine six I'm not done you're not
ignore me you piece of garbage
finally
you hold it
he's got oh this is cool exterminator's
ax because may I take this you guys take
it yeah yeah let's loot the bodies
okay thanks I'm gonna equip it now
because it's better than my current
weapon
excuse me
from the stew it looked delicious
actually
[Music]
exterminator Stacks sheds hard to do a
car
exterminates
Gloria water oh there's a letter
I wonder if they've got treasure back
here no it doesn't seem like it
imploring the recipient to be cautious
around the far shore of the Evan Lake as
durgar of Ruma to be probably in the
area
we might want to do a long rest yeah
this one dead dive if possible okay
first yeah okay
let me see I would be curious what he's
in I'll take that
I'd like to recast this I'm clicking on
the cast spell button and it's not it
seems like it's blacked out but chat
said that I can recast it
oh
believe in itself examine
just believe
make it happen it only works against
bugs plants or oh you have to sleep I
see oh okay
oh it's a separate button I see never
mind can't Target Undead I see
it's quote unquote Undead so maybe we
could reanimate it but that's about it
anyway let's go have a long rest
cool before we accidentally run into
another fight I suppose yeah
okay time to chill hey doggy why are you
holding that weird flower oh wait you're
already there okay
cam oh
wait the dog has the flower
he was glowing for a second but then it
went away oh maybe he ate it or
something Gail wants probably some
something to eat again it's being
ignored as little as I do yeah
given you're enabling him
yeah give him something nice
whoa uh crack but I like having Misty's
step but I don't want to give him this
one
does it only let you choose from your
own inventory yeah it's fine there you
go Gail
thank you oh he's embedded oh look at
him look at yeah
you're gonna go crazy guys yay he liked
that yeah he was into that
congrats Gail
you're so dirty
Oh it sounded positive at first
listen I need to speak to you to all of
you you'll be unconscionable of me to
remain silent
uh go on you're among friends
that
to know who I was
to know who I really am he's a dark
wizard wow you are so dude
I bet you guys all are too yeah we can't
see it on moriope it's an early age
could not only control The Weave but
compose it
much like a
poet such was my skill that it earned me
the attention of the mother of magic
herself
the lady of mysteries
the goddess mistra there he goes off
herself to me and she became my teacher
in time she became my muse
oh yes
oh yes this company body
Wow
first thing bastard
he's great
mystra Keeps Us in check if a goddess
can't satisfy him what could ever
satisfy his cross right every time the
glory opens with her more open Mario
everybody in the game the origin
characters do not like that oh
um
ryopa is God
more than God
my methods
pouted he found it
please
Jenny smiled and told me to be contented
inconceivable as it seems to me now I
shared a bed with a goddess
wow greedy um
we come now to the Crux of my Folly
correct shall I share the story behind
it or would you rather head straight to
it sworded for nothing
fine now finale yep yeah suffice it to
say I obtained an obscure and ancient
book
that had locked away inside a much
coveted prize was a fragment of Primal
weave locked out of time
what if I thought
what if
after all this time
I could return this lost part of herself
to the goddess
this is a short version
Oh my God
[Music]
fable
book took it into my study
as for what happened next
here
place your hand over my heart
oh it's gonna suck you inside of his
body he's gonna slurp you up okay well I
guess you guys will be without your your
hot Bard for the rest of the playthrough
you feel the tadpole quiver oh something
else is quivering too
don't let him in don't
[Laughter]
resist the swirling massive black
history trying to snatch his weave
Unstoppable as it digs through oh it's
part of you intense
I want to do
it
thanks for the moment I absorbed the
fragment wasn't enough to kill me
outright
was only the beginning damn wow
that armor looks good on you yeah he's
blight this is the score yeah
as long as I absorb traces of the weave
from potent enough sources remains quiet
we had ever to fully destabilize however
feel nice hair
it does cool story bro you will die
will erupt oh I don't know the exact
magnitude of the eruption but given my
studies of nethery's magic
I'd say even a fragment as small as the
one I carry at a levelless city the
size of water heaps
my chance upon a king's collection of
magical artifacts around the corner we
might cross paths with a miracle round
the bend
then again
we might not yeah all of this
it must feel like a betrayal
say the word we're not parting ways with
Gail he's okay yeah hi Gail I like him
yeah
that is yeah this is all right great
relief
stand with me but then one of us has to
not be on the team we can do my best
Gail is the most charismatic news
but if you do not give up hope neither
shall I
I'll fight
I'll resistance
no I would volunteer as not being on a
team so that I actually survive
because literally
just sent him yeah yeah okay very nice
nice okay good solution
oh good morning oh how do you feel yeah
I'm fine you feel a little woozy my neck
hurts how you think I feel be grateful
I'm not a true neck always hurt
s when you might wake up as a family's
got a large chest you know my good self
I carrying that around the vampires
but few of their powers
is that how you could stand the Sun and
your drawbacks I should know about I
have no idea
the sun would have turned me to sinners
until the crash when I woke up bathed in
its you know he's skipping arm day I
think the rest of his body is pretty
toned like in comparison
weird
[Music]
they Bend so weird
in blood
uh if I can help just ask we're in this
together
you're such a sweetheart wow you're
being sarcastic
what if I grabbed your nipples and
twisted oh
to get you to shut up would you leave my
party
I think it would be funny
what do you mean I'm just being honest
first thing I noticed is God I'm staring
at me those things are staring at me
clothes on this poor man
okay we'll talk to biboo about that
because
she can have clothes just
we can you can put some other clothes on
him
the real issue is we have to then
somehow take our one of us off the team
we can close him yeah let's just keep
them naked yeah good
you guys that we have come to a complete
ah oh
you good I hope someone in cam still
wishes to speak who wants to speak
uh Starion again oh it's a serious oh my
God go ahead Molly go on
what does he want you gotta help her boy
all right I'll be nice to him I'll be
nice to him just for me which is this
yeah oh wow I I could probably read that
because I'm a tiefling oh wow that is
true that is a good point I'm gonna take
a look what are you doing oh I'm saying
hey what's up sorry I'll leave you alone
this is
this person we're traveling companions
now if you don't yeah
piss off oh yeah I should kill him for a
stag that wow hey
stop it I should tell you that
that's what I get for being respectful
next time I'm gonna be a mom he doesn't
like you anymore let's go you said he
was your master
I'm I'm done with this whole you don't
have to tell me anything you don't want
to I'm gonna pry into his life
with all the minds layers too because
now I know I have to strangle him if I
want to tell me anything was it the
nipple twisting thing I'm sorry I said
that man
it wasn't very cool song is a vampire
the patriarch of his coven and a monster
obsessed with power maybe political
power maybe yeah I'm very sorry for that
no I'm not I don't care I don't give a
but I would like this 200 years ago see
where this goes you know I'd love to get
to the scene where I can you know knee
him in the
I'll lead you there along the way okay
thanks I'll lead you to the right
direction cool
a vampire's soon oh wait one of us will
have to leave the party for that
I'll do it no choice
they speak our bodies react
it's all part of the deal yeah don't
don't worry about it you know don't
worry about it
sometimes I'm taking notes I'll just
torture ourselves before you ever taken
notes
whatever his scary vampire dude a
starian slave yes I have a bad memory
free now enjoy that freedom quiet the
sob story what's your point
[Laughter]
I won't take it for granted the Mind
flares aren't the only monsters out
there
they're not even the only ones hunting
us
all I'm asking is that you keep your
eyes open
and watch out for anything lurking in
the shadows like you trying to drink my
blood yeah I'll watch your back keep me
safe and I'll do the same oh no my
friend if vampires come looking for you
you're on your own
I'll watch your back I'm moriope what's
more could I
why are you always sarcastic
a piece of
kill him
oh my God there's literally so many why
do you insist on exhuming the pump wow
but then he immediately answers
I'm joking
so mean betas are cool too
don't worry about it don't worry about
it or a b-a-i-t-e-r
be lost
I'm not being mean I'm just trying to
get into the moriopic character well
Kiara if you want to get into the Omega
verb
oh yeah what's an Omega version never
mind I'll tell you later
can we stop talking to him I'm like
puppet
[Music]
and I just skipped the dialogue yeah
yeah just basically worry about
dialogue because people get mad when I
skip dialogue but like okay I wouldn't
be mad there's a cleric with this I
wanna fight
yeah I feel you yeah yeah we gotta we
gotta we gotta sleep and kill things I
won't lie we'll skip all the dialogue
like do I do I hate not hearing his
voice actor absolutely yes
but at the same time
it's fine you know yeah
he has a very Charming voice yeah he
does
and he looks beautiful what the hell oh
baby
it's still alive
no I didn't rescue you people rescued
you
beckoned him closer with animal handling
yeah bonus plus five it should be fine
girls Okay Google wrong stream this this
Olive bear should have gone to mumei's
3D showcase yeah right the Cub tilts his
head
let's not trusty it's so cute
such a piece of food from your bag
hungry
hungry I like like that oh
macaroon walk onto the food there you go
toss the food
eat the food
keep it in front what if it bites my
hand off wouldn't that be hilarious yeah
do it for the meme it'll be hilarious it
says his foot lands on a dry twig
no that's scary
oh
but if I toss the food at him what if it
hits him in the face we gotta try again
sometime dang it will it will he just be
gone forever I'm sure he'll come back
oh
baby we'll be back okay surely
all right let's get out of here yep too
bad okay
it's okay we're fine he comes back he
comes back he's better
hey what is this over here
there's a boat yeah can we take
it and go somewhere
I don't know
should have ate the food
yeah
that's bored I say yes
oh you guys went back oh yeah
outside of the camp
goodbye
oh
did we get on the phone without moving
I also don't see a baby girl no I'm
there okay it's okay we'll we'll get a
waypoint and then you can just teleport
to us easy peasy oh it looks so cool
the boat looks so nice
wow
can we find the one piece
you know
where where is the one piece oh no
uh
Pete what are you doing we have
permission to our conversation by
pressing the ear
oh
boy do you want to fight where's Geck
who are you
um
your parasite stares briefly then goes
still hopefully they don't get in the
fight
oh
how desperate is this to make an ally of
a Top-Sider well I will tell you what
the sergeant told Geck until you have
the boots you will not cross eh
come back empty-handed again
all the boots what boots
oh
[Music]
but Molly oh Molly wow
I'll go and find something else
we need you without you yeah you can
probably win
did we did we say did we save after we I
don't know I can't remember the last
time we saved me neither
we'll just kill him fast and I got I got
another shot of you this is dead okay
now we just have the ones on the other
ship
one two three four five
you got all your spells
that's true well I mean if they're gonna
survive it's cool
could we jump over to the boat like
I think so we're all kind of long
distance Shooters anyway but
it's fine thank you
there is an auto save after camp
that
that is true
I wouldn't mind like
yeah
but I don't want to do fights without
worry open yeah we need our country open
load or save
okay
anyways
we'll see this one campsite load game
friends fighting for their lives Mori
out here shopping
grocery list hmm
yes spicy mushroom
no we can't get the owl bear we can't
it's from waking up
that's fine waking up is when it say
it's okay we'll get them next time yeah
it is what it is we have to accept it
sometimes
exactly
I bet we don't have them right all right
now
okay I'm gonna follow you guys because I
don't know where the boat is
all right we can kill him yeah yeah yeah
nice boats nicely that's cool too
let's sail into the darkness with me
without my shoes yeah
no ogre Left Behind where's Geck okay
okay we could lie
in the name of the absolute
um
[Music]
so barefoot
full armor but no shoes
all right
no reason to get your horns in a Twist
oh there well come on
let's get you to shore someone's
floating in the background
so busted
you continue forward and sign up okay we
avoided a fight no thank you
okay
you can always beat them up wow under
their Grim Forge
abandoned refugee
oh
see oh
no wow whoa trying alone on the boat wow
I'm scared wow my toenails are so long
what where do you see your toenails
because she doesn't have shoes
I'm seeing something different from you
I don't see feet
well now I'm in the other part of the
cutscene but it was just for a moment I
was looking overhead
right into those nasty toenails
you gotta clip those bad boys no I see
your nails
oh yeah oh
the guy is with us we got a welcoming
party wait what hey
are we seeing the same thing right now
no
what other private moments or set your
dialogue to public
fit it out there's no voice acting
um I don't hear anything are we spread
it out Sergeant finally choked true Soul
Nails neck oh okay
a ring on a fat finger you're
me he pay up that's the trouble he got
the gold on him oh no the game is good
this conversation's muggy oh no I'm the
whole time I've just been seeing nice
shots of the scenery
there's a conversation going on with no
dialogue
is plugged apparently
[Music]
it's a it's a popular glitch okay wow
can you like explain what's happening um
we're gonna fight okay nice I
get my find oh never mind they said
never mind
here for fun okay okay
basically there's there's a true soul up
there if you're so near I think oh
um
so we can kill these people if you want
to that could be a kind but I don't know
um I don't think it'll aggro the whole
Camp because they're far away but let's
maybe oh you guys got the Waypoint then
yeah quick save yeah your call Kiara you
want to find these two people down here
you easily kill them no I think now I we
should explore first okay okay what is
this place
this is the the Grim Forge
executed rounds is this a boat yeah
there's colorful spiders
[Music]
if you loot his body though it'll aggro
everyone
wow cuties
interesting first we explore then we
kill that sounds fun
what's happening they've been raised by
locals not a clue loyal to them
uh and I got Adam
and tried to destroy that you're an
animal Master chatter
and I shall add the bardic inspiration
yes oh how ah there it is okay
okay let's go 10 yeah
let's just say that's so easy but
we have lots ridiculous
with critical failures it doesn't even
add the bonuses huh yeah if you get a 20
or a one it doesn't add
[Music]
um
the largest spider versus the other
three
[Music]
[Applause]
wait oh bullying if you leave the
conversation I have animal talking on
maybe they'll say something different
hmm
Kiara
I'll I'll let me see what happened
okay this mean girl spider yeah for
real oh my god
that is some kind of cult going on
you can't sit with us at the spider
Table
Santa was a betrayer
we will miss her
oh no we missed some context here
so oh well hey we didn't kill this
fighter dude we did nothing yeah we
didn't
the dead spider
nice
okay what else
besides dead people you can go up the
stairway if you want
fix it
oh they're in love
straight to the Shadows
since we won't move a pebble a pebble
moles
[Music]
supposed to be in the water oh okay
um
how might I get one of my own I heard
the true Soul was trapped shouldn't you
be healthy hold out your hands you heard
the man let's see him maybe because the
scene is full of bugs get it spiders or
bugs
why
no were you
okay look
my drinking hands busy
yeah
[Music]
spiders aren't bugs yeah they are
yeah they're arachnids they're not okay
I don't care a bug is a bug if it's in
my house I don't want it there it's a
bug it's an understandable have a nice
day
someone finished that one off please
two HP is oh oh boy oh they're gonna
call their homies is that an elevator
whoa
I think we got him
you killed this place
is that the wrong person oh God
oh
mama
you might be holding some gold yeah yeah
look there's casualties in War I got
people
or you see there's gold there's there's
a bun
just keep your hands oh simply oh yeah
there's a dude watching he sees us oh
hey man what's going we didn't kill this
guy he's just
he was chilling
oh
we didn't do that there was an auto save
that scares me
oh
it's probably fine
we go that way
it seems like a bit of a dead end over
there
okay should we kill more people
oh there's a path
my perception check
okay okay
sorry I don't know what I found
um
secret room maybe yeah I got us some
Golds uh lots of gold like 115 gold big
gold cool
let's just find nice nice chest
is a natural war criminal looks
interesting only on accident
but
it was an Ali
we forgive you he definitely doesn't and
his family doesn't but we forgive you
there's two guys over here we could kill
them too because they're Witnesses
mm-hmm yeah sound good you aren't
exactly aggro but if you guys want to
fight them I don't mind I think these
guys suck it'll be fun to kill him
yeah no they're beating people up for no
reason
yeah
kill him someone only the guards are
allowed to do that and this one
yeah try it
perhaps people now forget that attack
yeah yeah violence let's go violence
okay don't hit
oh nice blessed whoa that was cool that
was what I was trying to do like the
other guy
it's five against one buddy what are you
gonna do
oh he's dead he's super dead
oh God good stuff oh
okay in my inventory you can just take a
look in there
just killed under the
year slavers and people they're like
your people right
right oh
respect oh respect it's all about the
respect
I'm gonna see what they're holding yes
what are people's friends holding uh yes
anyway what's in your pockets
potato potato
invisibility
when you enter the door I wonder
probably
open up let's give it a try knock knock
have you guys ever tried knocking on the
door before are you lock picking it yup
it's open now
let's go
a
blue yum yums rotten fish rotten we
don't need that
yeah
build religion check everyone failed
like a bagel way before killing enough
Bagel you know what this place is
yeah you got the religion killing people
for sure
you're right we're Shadow Hearts
Open Door
what secret room let's go more secret
tunnels oh another door
I want a lock pick oh it doesn't look
big it's open whoa
that stuff looks like an ambush
oh what is that
jelly what are those ogre jelly
[Music]
dmca
what's alive
uh it's up it's upward someone has to
end their turn so we can all move up
extend it I guess because yeah oh
90 all in one spot all hit buttons
cool time to press it oh he's dead
they're all dead I know they're not
there's still one left I think
yeah up here
okay
for now
get him yes not enough movement oh oh
wait well yeah okay that's all I could
do
Dash
oh
we're getting there
I just wanted to shove them
oh good yeah
multiplayer sweet squeeze that jelly
from your eyes
it's nice when you don't have to control
everyone in your garden on my way
nice
yeah
yeah nice take everything take it dang
it everything
there's some Scrolls here Scroll of fly
it's rare I'm gonna take it yeah I
already have one
special arrows kiwawa might be able to
use yes
I give them to you they're she'll be in
your inventory
the queef
it's in here I am honored I shall make
best use of them
my inventory is such a mess
right you can sort it into lots of
Scrolls I don't know if I'll ever use
yeah we should we should use them more
and oh there's also still oh no we took
the chest okay is that what the arrow
were where the arrows were it looks as
though we can climb further if you'd
like to climb
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh
candle
oh wow
how far can we get
big question well it seems that since we
can jump that's pretty cool
I may need to be eaten you want me to
throw you yes please
I gotcha
bro
there you go
[Music]
buddy
doing okay
the back looks a little broken could
help hey where are we
good no idea
this is a flesh wound oh yeah no
backbreaking it's fine I'm more flexible
now cool
yeah like a surgical operation yeah
there's a little a little person a
little oh
friends family friend no friends I don't
know but I see things that we should
take like the camp supplies let's see if
there were skills I swear to eye in hand
one more step she reminds me of b-boy
yeah fashion scent fills the air the
barrel is filled with smoke powder oh no
the scent is
it contaminated somehow
oh much gonna pull a Walter White and
blow the whole place up
careful
[Music]
hold on there's something different oh
does she know now shoot your face before
I melt it clean off I know what you are
and you say it I think I saw this in a
video but if you say conversation
do you want me okay okay come get me
hold on don't make any don't make any
decisions
yeah don't make any decisions yet yeah
go go steal some bee boo steal it
can I steal it super funny can I detect
her thoughts though
oh my God
so much for the Perfect Crime
um
come on let us at least roll for it
right live to see it
oh she's mad yeah okay
that I feel like she she had a reason to
be mad and we could have like cleared it
up
yeah is she like a good person is she
good she looks like a a deep gnome so
probably she's also probably a slave
here is he temporary hostile can we
disengage no we can do only non-lethal
damage from non-lethal oh yeah
yeah I don't remember how it works you
need to go to your passives and turn it
on when it's your turn it's on I'm not
gonna use any spells I'm just gonna Bonk
her yeah
is it on now guys chat I think it is
uh but then yeah only melee only melee
okay technically a war crime does that
mean we're gonna go shoot or no shooting
I turned it I think it needs to be a
melee right I think only one person
needs to turn it on yeah it's on for all
of us
for all of us okay one person touch it
once and then yeah
uh
so melee does that mean what does that
mean what do I so if you if you shoot it
with an arrow I think she'll still die
okay what what about main hand attack
that's a melee so yeah okay to get close
get close and
do a Stampy stamp is she okay not in
this game in real DND it's melee only
gotcha uh-huh
[Music]
she's not dead right yeah nope she's
knocked out she's wrong
can we like be friendly with her when
she wakes up or so she might be able to
wake up that'd be gold why is there
you know I sleep here it's just been
waiting until she wakes up
do you also see like
like a dark version of herself standing
on the stone
no was that Kiara do you also see a dark
version of her standing on the stone
above her
I think it's a bun
it might be a bug I don't do anything
like that okay
I have this bomb that does 50 to 120
damage
Moon powder vial yeah I have a nuke now
can I take what she's holding yeah even
looter oh Rune powder vial looks really
cool
high damage
I wonder when she wakes up I don't I've
never experienced some waking up but
then again usually when I realize I've
done that I just kill them
ah loot attack nah
no way can we throw a potion at them
yeah nice idea I don't know if that
really works well it's always good it's
not a temporary right it'll wake up
eventually yeah
you'll need the nuke
fresh elving
yay
before she wakes up close
it's a fight oh my God
kidding oh she's still knocked out
interesting okay
now I thought for sure we'd be able to
like negotiate with her no they're like
hey look real sorry about all that
you guys want to lay on the stone bed
with me yeah sounds fun girl talk
a spa
I love this one
wow yeah comfortable
lady I got a sleepover
loves her ladies
new episode of girls talk
um so
um what do you think of that a Starion
guy like oh my God he's kind of like you
know you know yeah but what about Gail
though like he's also like pretty nine
he's yeah he's pretty okay yeah and then
there's will like oh my God actually
yeah I can't choose but I'm guessing is
already taken it's so unfair aren't you
taking uh like carlak she's like you
know I guess so
stop being so beautiful and leave the
boys to the rest of us yeah Wario pay is
sorry attractiveness
I am born with it I'll give it to you if
I could man I'm so jealous
when you're sleeping I might just like
rip out one of your hairs and then make
a concoction and then I'm Gonna Leave
become more like serious
there are ways to make fashion belts
Drake yard
trachea is uh throat where you breathe
oh that's so you're problematic
um
it's so hot yeah I know oh I said it
baby
okay we were turning
I suppose yeah we couldn't talk to her
man it's okay but at least she's alive
maybe they passed it
now I think we're gonna need that we can
use that for later hey
guys to put my hands on everything
oh
oh the stupid door
that is a sparkly thing back there
behind the door open yeah that's I think
just the perception thingy oh
open sesame
ow yeah
can't throw too heavy oh that's too bad
I'll add so much silverware I know we
could sell it for money
um
all right
wine oh I found some camp supplies at
least yum
nice
good job Liara hey we can get drunk
later but I hope there's nothing yes
why night for the girls you can drag it
oh yeah
oh yeah what's left here of this place a
lot we need we we need to go the other
way up the stairs okay lead the way okay
don't worry about the rock it's okay
fish Barrel
fish Barrel okay fish and wine We Dine
tonight I hope that this boat isn't
supposed to be yeah is that not how you
park a boat no it's bugged I don't know
that boat was there when I was there too
oh no there's a different boat that's
not supposed to be in there it's a
little deeper in
all right
okay Merchant if you yeah moving around
I see take all those goodies and grab
some gold and some minerals come into
her Shadow let all that is
oh
smooth face well no one's aggroved
they're a shark they must be no they do
not give a wow oh you killed our
Brethren's sick yeah we hate them
cool you probably had a reason and I
doubt I'll find pressure
and then mouth off what should I be
looking at the Rock whatever you want
all of it if I may be so bold
take a look tell me what you see and be
thorough there's so much echo in here
nice oh I see you're right
oh
I will proceed wow they're really big
what
wait huh because these Halls are so big
yeah it's so big I mean yeah wow
ceilings very highest feelings indeed no
crystals oh
the hottest of flames smooth the stone
and left sulfuric crystals behind nice
the fires of the hells have touched
grimfort
foreign
I guess I could use more time as you
need
I wish I had more skills but okay
investigate
it's whatever you can I'll add people
guidance yeah
oh it's just five anyway
when you don't need it since Stone
breaks at various sizes clutter the
corridor mini split clean lean too yet
some walls remain fully intact
I see no Quake brought these rocks down
smashed through in an instant who did it
some something big charged through here
something very big bigger than Mori
happy what do you think
that must be big
I shall try to assist
the statue okay wait
yeah
curves and golden edges stand out
against the weathered masonry behind it
two Styles two Iris the statue was
carved from newer Stone and erected by
Lake comers to this ancient Fortress
Zoomers anything standing out consumers
erected the statue
I am now ready to report my observations
incredible
an entire history region from dirt and
debris
from the stone by Disciples of Shah I
love how he talks
Untold
a new tribe revives it fresh walls fresh
sculptures until a great hell Beast
charges topping the walls and crushing
the people oh oh OMG fantastic
that explains the infernal play I found
a place perhaps you might have use of it
yes thank you
there is more still to find he's nice
let's not kill him okay okay he seems
jokes he seems chill now we can
try it once again I'll just just a
little bit quick
okay I'll sniff around a little bit but
not too much yes
[Music]
oh
I did want to sneak
I I was gonna sell these potions
we did it she did we don't worry about
it
okay
oh infernal alloy the ridges in this
metal glow faintly drawing your gaze the
longer you watch its hellish positions
the harder it is to remember who and
where you are but this is not like the
infernal iron right yeah we need
infernal iron but I don't know what we
can do with the alloy hmm we'll keep it
until it
becomes useful
we shall
okay
[Music]
people who's watching a cutscene
um
unintentional cutscene I just wanted to
say hello to the cows
and they started talking
oh
actually elf
cloaks in darkness
ten Masters ago and ten more
but I remember that was the work
and the blood
there was the Thorns Army
there was the Heron Beast
broke them
the Catholic Thorne's name I can't wait
till we meet Catherine Thorne
his voice actors so good
uh yeah impressive memory damn how do
they remind remember so much how old are
they
outlived my mother oh mother's brother
and many mothers Beyond oh he's done
cursed to see many Die oh
how sounds cool
I saw tusks and flesh
smelled fire and eggs
eggs
smelly omelette
I know not so I say not
um
so if you not know do not speak sing
by the Shadows
Shadows
okay so I have no one else to tell this
about so I'm going to tell you guys you
guys know portal right yeah yeah oh
Patrick thorm the voice actor is
Cave Johnson
the same guy who voices him so JK
Simmons
who's Cave Johnson never mind character
from Portal 2
I played all the portals even portal
free he's he's the one who goes on the
lemon rant in Portal ah lemons I
remember some lemons yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah that guy that guy
what's this eye doing here
um it will call reinforcements if we get
in a fight oh
yeah I was so close to getting into that
chest
oh no one who's there when I tried to
open it then this lady just showed up eh
go away good try
um
whoa dark just to see our male armor
medium armor
not for me I suppose but there's some
cool armor here with the shadow heart
they're all clad in the same dark
oh interesting yeah the deadbeat armor
portal free favorite game
portal free is real
oh
Bijou is also mindless intelligence we
we're not very smart
I
uh okay you see nothing special
velvet tunics
it's endearing though
let's focus on the problems at hand
oh man
oh but the armor that I picked up was
green and the others are and you got a
special one wow
stole
wasn't anything exceedingly useful but
you did it let's go yeah
really wanted to steal from that
Travelers yes I don't know anyway I'm
back on my way
that Rubble needs clearing and my
patience is hanging and that's what the
animals are for
yeah maybe it just looks like a World of
Warcraft character right now all right
yeah that was the armor I found yeah
getting cramps in my arm trying to whip
the druken in beasts
now get to the training he's a nasty
little guy I'm gonna I want to beep him
up
kill him I mean
split you from head to home okay
wait what
again they want you dead too uh be
careful maybe we save because uh you can
get tossed off the edge here yeah same
game thank you Mario babe yeah
I turned cancel back on oh I think
you're just super mad you got it I guess
I'll just save them with violence make
sure that non-lethals off yeah we can
lethal the guys but the non-lethal the
animals oh okay yeah possibly
nice idea yeah
um what was that
with animal safety you can save them you
gotta talk to them yeah but you have to
talk to them before talking to the guys
oh it didn't give me an option to tell
them it I just entered a cutscene when I
walked is
lag uh
kill the sphere thing all right I'll get
it yeah hopefully
well let's see if you were Excalibur two
damn kind of oh he's moving away no come
back
piece of garbage
he's back
come on surely I can use something
important is ever easy
yeah
what no way
hmm
come back this ball just
making
you guys keep coming I'll be keep keep
going I'll be right back oh okay okay
it's very close to being dead we should
we should take it to our doggo and let
doggo play with it as a ball yeah this
idea I don't want a frenzy because I
keep wanting to save my friends yeah use
it too often oh that guy frenzied
oh okay well maybe
that many enemies okay
well that wasn't on you
oh no
no
well we can make them pay for it what I
want to take the death seriously with
this beautiful tune is playing
the poor cows they're free now yeah it's
a good point Chad and they're free
man
I have no mercy because
he can't go really far right now but
later yeah you know he's mad he's mad
because those are animal Brethren yeah
they look like him just bigger yeah
that's no good
[Music]
yeah that's what you get
let's go
did you have to like
killed the
people before they killed the cows or
something
you gotta talk to him
well you know should happen you got a
sweet talk to people first well it is
what it is sweet
sweet talking
sounds like sleep talking yeah I've
returned at the perfect time welcome
back the animals have died but not by by
our hands yeah
we did our best So Sad Piano we tried to
save them there's not much we could have
done
these guys are Chumps I'm not gonna
waste a frenzy on them yeah
[Music]
but I'll gladly tank your hits if you
are so bold
yeah Pumbaa
the piano nice one and then I can do
another Chad friends eat strike
let's go
that's what you get
for animal cruelty you little yeah
why is this one hiding in the corner
says he's a coward baby yeah
and here we go
no traps please everything wait they're
red but can we can still loot them right
yeah because no one's around to watch
good good good oh this dude has a ton of
stuff
please
good stuff
I mean yeah I would say so he's got like
fish a fish good good things yeah and
some rings
about the aminals
animals the animals aminals
aminals aminals aminals
the aminals
[Laughter]
definitely trying to figure out how you
were saying it wrong because I was like
it's not right but what's what's the
matter with it what's wrong with it
it sounds correct to me no Miss
girlington
all right
where would you like to go next
question uh wherever anniversary is
going I guess they're sorry
[Music]
uh
it doesn't let me lock
picked should do it
show me your inside
lent me an Insight over your inside
yeah I want to see what's in it oh
oh plus one there's plus one
uh but I don't necessarily need it uh
someone else can take it you could sell
it
Maybe
actually maybe you want Mario pay with
like a nice new crossbow uh wait I will
who my computer is a mess Let Me sort by
new or hammer
uh okay I'll put it in your inventory
uh
it's Anya it's I took your soul coin
instead no I can't give it back here
find it it's a green crossbow Green Oh
light crossbow plus one yeah plus one
yeah this is better than what I have
thanks
yeah no magic for you Gail this is mine
thank you you're welcome
and anything else here oh no right oh
wait it actually goes down here
it looks like it
there's just a chest I'm looting it
right now oh okay then we shall stay all
right on The High Ground
yeah I have The High Ground
[Music]
if this was my solo playthrough I would
read every single book very well
his chest down there it's on there too
can we even get down there oh wait can I
do again wait everyone come here and
maybe I can feather fall oh it looks
like there's a place we can probably
climb down to oh
because we can climb back up yeah look
at the bed down there that looks kind of
cool
[Applause]
but wouldn't it be more fun to jump down
okay yeah all right baby
if you say so I believe okay
[Music]
wow
it's a minute
RPG stable mimic
welcome
oh you wanna rock and roll let's go
I'm still so fine he wants to eat food
he's gonna turn you into a tasty snack
please I'm just a widow guys oh there's
three of them you might be good
family
I'm surprised wow
pretty surprising are they strong I
wonder
I'll frenzy if they're strong they've
got 40 health
okay Frenzy
20.
and that's not my turn
maybe they're not that spelled mm-hmm
what a reckless attack
acerate
don't push them down they have great
items oh
okay
yeah because they are chest it's really
they're holding some goodies right um
yeah I want the goodies
who's oh it's my turn oh my god I'm an
idiot here we go no problem can't reach
the dead that's okay I'll just shoot
shooty sploady
thingy
no wait where did you what
I swear to God man I'm gonna lose I'm
about to lose
oh it's fine you guys can
still getting used to the mouse and
keyboard it would see yeah
jump down here with us join us and wow
we've got feather fall
um Oh I thought you meant jump down into
the electricity no
I would not wish that oh yeah it's good
for me to have high ground up here for
now you guys got to tell me what's in
the chest though
I want to know it's just curiosity I
don't need it I just want to know
[Applause]
I know now I shall jump down broken
I want to look and see just what's in
there um there's wondrous gloves they're
in my inventory I got a hand ax plus one
if anybody won
that could be good for throwing
oh it's in this one do they all have
good items
but 20 is kind of high
oh you can try
um
oh okay that's just a week
no open up
oh the opening is also 20.
wait I can do it I can open it
I got 21.
this better be something good
oh it's a scroll of evidence
and the Magical scroll
but wait for the rest of us is that okay
also by the way guys I used one
inspiration sorry about that but it was
going to be a critical failure and I
didn't want to see what we did no
problem
um
it's about the kefaric form
can't be known an alliance between the
Harpers and the emerald Enclave United
We may end forms Reign of Terror
okay interesting
now you have toilet paper excuse me
oh this is a bug right
the mimic looks alive to me
hey no he's super dead for me yeah it's
definitely it's real for me
it's real okay is this where it ends
yeah go up here oh
oh big blimeys well you can climb
obviously well already in use because
you've got those long toenails on your
Stompers
[Laughter]
really dig in
I really dig into the Rock you know get
there use more open I can't get there
why
just why can't Mario begin oh
[Music]
what
all right your turn Mario babe There You
Go moriope is just a little slow
you need a hand
I'm okay wearing the wink on next you
lead me
is there still something interesting
here yeah there is
no from
this might be useful who's that well we
can go down here okay
okay we go down
whatever you want to do
and then why don't you go see what all
those people are doing okay
what are you doing
what the hell what kind of party's
popping off I
think there's a party
[Music]
why don't you talk to them yeah twisters
lost in the hot air
their nose right save my pee
my people yeah for Bubble
okay we can eavesdrop I'm sure my role
will be satisfactory mm-hmm
forget
it they kill Phil on the spot I won't
let you do it yeah we gotta give it to
them
so yeah okay yeah go ahead
she's
she's I mean we did knock her out but
she's alive I wonder if that option
wouldn't be available if we killed her
they'll die in that tunnel
possibly you have the powder my Belgium
would die back there blow up that wall
I'm begging you
all right okay
imagine being like nah I'm not cave in
Forever
we'll save you justice all right do your
best Dave
all right you can blow that and
blow it wait we got two powders right I
have a vial it's something called a
hold on a sec this is called Rune powder
vial the Rune powder inside explodes
when ignited damaging everything in the
vicinity
[Applause]
or the barrel
what does the barrel say the barrel the
barrel they're talking about the thing
we took from philamine yeah so the the
barrel well we have two we have one
barrel
yeah I looted this from her from her
unconscious box
I would like to save the new for fun
okay possible
does less damage
look at you as the Lyle baby okay okay
is that right here
the rubble a fragmented voice clutches
is that your mind are you okay
yes you know she all right she's just
going through it the voice is in her
head you know
okay
are you
what happened here
passage trap
s trust bugs hmm get me out oh wow he's
really
communicating with me you only make out
a bit of rubble and few moving figures
hmm all right let's get them out I guess
hmm
okay try to focus
really quick add a bonus yeah
let's try
no nice
yeah did I run out the bonus no
may I please roll one more time yeah
yeah let me add my guide thanks oh thank
you okay
didn't know how to add it there thanks
yeah there we go okay we're good
let's see another resolves into an image
feverishly
yeah well two others lie dead at near's
feet
flesh scorched by powerful Magic
oh he really wants to be let out and the
Gnomes ain't doing well how okay I
guess well what if we accidentally blow
him up
he's probably fine blow him up
everyone's using vile because it's less
powerful
yeah use your vial okay and do you
just let's see maybe is there an option
to use an item uh after we do this by
the way I have somewhere to take you
guys okay okay okay
sneeze frustration okay I want to help
it let me see if I can just use the item
um
try it out someone says drop bile on the
ground and shoot it with fire let's okay
let's save first yeah yeah good idea
you just drag it out of the inventory
and put it on the ground uh-huh okay I
can't ogre smash your way through no
clean up
clean upstairs
just throw it I mean I guess there's
that too
bro
lit on the ground
hold on I know I have where's thorough
oh come on please I know I'm not
knitting yeah
gosh you can just drag and drop
inventory too okay
here we go uh the vial yeah but can we
tell them to walk go away
before hopefully they'll get the vibe
you want to go chat with them
just a quick check if it's possible to
explode it yeah okay but you good I
dragged it I dragged the item to it okay
they'll go away when they notice drop it
on the floor and they'll Run Okay drag
it to the ground gotcha
okay no problem I'll peel Your Balls
Like Potatoes if you don't move wow that
sounds awful
step a bit Yeah okay yes
all as well
back there
whoa oh oh looking rocks they come and
they go
um who is she
finally oh hi near me
oh is he a bad guy he's a true soul
I just stand there on unshocked un that
doesn't bothered
it's not how I would react
finish this lace I don't care for the
weak truth
like you
um
and yet you came to my a yeah
yeah exactly the absolute paid you to
try nears faith
thrin Liara is unimpressed
indeed is a true soul
let the absolute sad all right all right
oh
you so much just touched me I'll tear
you from live to limb yes yeah it guides
my hand come at me bro oh I can't wait
to kill him it's gonna be red he must
have a nice item to drop this true Soul
has betrayed what the I want his
cloak that one is closed yeah
oh that's a lot of people whoa good luck
we'll take them
we can take them perfect time to frenzy
yeah yeah perfect time to Frenzy
all right
[Music]
who's this guy oh see over there
time
[Music]
Let's Get Down buddy
I I I'm the closest to the boss so I'll
go for him I guess
Pro tip don't end your move standing
close to Lava yeah that seems smart
[Music]
let's see how strong they are without
their leader
oh my gosh good damage
destroy him
oh
okay
maybe I'll throw another one
because
okay that was weak no match for us
easy
a true Soul yeah the absolutely though
I'm curious what he owns yeah yeah we'll
shoot him we'll loot him after we kill
all these other people Reckless attack
on this guy go go Power Ranger yeah
NASA okay my turn
I'm made from history I've been large
we just need to take his body
I really wanted to cloak yeah I'm gonna
I'm gonna pick up his body and take it
to Camp exactly
mind mastering my my my board
um oh no it became an enemy yeah oh wow
be careful
okay
no problem these guys are Chumps yeah
total Chumps on easy mode yeah
sorry baby
okay
great as many as you want
as your little people heart desires
mm-hmm
okay oh
you're so excited more slaves
[Music]
wow that was awesome nice that was very
cool yeah I'm gonna go over here and try
to eat these two now yeah
all right
I just can't I can't force myself
maybe he'll come back to his senses
yeah I don't want to hurt him
[Music]
whoa there with the burns
no your master oh it's okay
it's me now
and it was a shield
okay isn't that sweet
yeah his butt smells kind of bad but
it's kind of funky yeah
oh I can't attack right now okay it's
right in your face
the lava looks so good
right oh yeah I just line up right there
frenzied strike
yeah
and then
a lacerating strike actually it's a
bleed
hey he's dead knife
he has a size
Big D I'm gonna take that
the wearer Bears looks like a scythe
like it
okay and I got one more shot
um
Corsair Greymon
all right wow
very cool
recessed
um
all these guys are bad guys yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
yeah when they're all clumped together
like chumps
how the am I surviving this I don't
know but keep doing it
um
oh my God
seems like Lee hours of Phoenix too yeah
I don't even care about attacking with
my boar right now I just want to save
Wawa
do your best
difficult terrain lava yeah a bit
difficult this terrain to be you have
like like incredible lava walking
loafers
Jesus Oh Carla would be proud of me okay
get out of there can I jump out of lava
please
hell man oh yeah yeah oh my God
all right who else needs to be killed
okay let's go there's just two more left
one is in the tent and yeah the other's
up there
uh I could get him actually now
[Music]
okay okay okay you wanna make it
difficult
smells like fried chicken yeah oh no
easy mode yeah imagine we're on easy
mode and it only took me down like 40 HP
or so imagine this on like non-easy mode
falling into the lava you're dead
yikes
that's pretty yucky
easy mode lava is gentle in tactician
you die right away
I see I believe it
thank God
you're so close to the lava too be
careful that's fine I don't care
yeah well one HP ghetto
okay all right who's the last mother f
word oh he's up there
one more
oh yeah
brimming with potent magic oh worms so
we have a mind flare specimen a thousand
gold
a dagger plus one a sort of Screams
this is I'm gonna take them oh oh oh we
can all I I need everything and then we
can spread these okay
it seems
spiky Lantern flickers with him a thick
layer of dust coats the bottom of the
lantern
oh Dusty
um
investigation
let's add bonus
thank you nerissa for inspiring me
not that you needed it
wow
what's so special about it it wasn't
magic magic lantern oh we have to look
even closer at it okay
Magic
oh this is Pixie Dust Pixies
did he like imprison a pixie inside of
it oh
[Music]
yeah I have some weapons I have uh
georgel's great sword uh a shining
staver of skulls and um a new bow
so Kiara we can't access your inventory
for some reason will you send me those
boots
yes I I was trying to put it on you
directly but wait I can't I'll pull it
down I love you inventory finally you
will wear shoes finally no more naked
feet um
Corey okay can you pick up near's body
and bring it back to Camp later
yeah I can literally won his body Force
um just trust trust me on this trust me
yeah it's a trophy we're gonna put him
in the camp
pick up
oh
he's right here thank you okay I need to
bring you guys somewhere
else
really quick let me oh really thanks
really quick I need to send some stuff
back
us and to Camp I need to send some
things to camp
oh yeah I'm over encumbered right now
very sorry okay let's see
I need this many goblin scimitars send
the camp
okay let's have a whole body I'm holding
yeah
only level five
oh cap of rats send the body to camp
uh we could but we can also just keep it
too does this count as armor this cap
yeah
it's really cool I don't know if it'll
not work with my build sadly but oh my
God looks interesting
it's not armor okay I'm Gonna Keep It on
actually yeah I'm Gonna Keep It on thank
you
let me send a couple more things really
quick camp
okay now you may lead the way okay come
with me everyone well first someone
talked the Gnomes Maybe
they better be thankful
oh it's okay okay
all right come with me
all right one sec just a moment I am
walking very slow because I have many
many items
um you all got Misty steps
and you do not have that probably
somewhere
I have a scroll of fly does that work
too yeah that works
Cali if you need something I have a
scroll of a knife don't worry okay okay
okay fly over here
call The Fly
there's no target come here so they have
space Oh
yeah there's a there's a war Pig
Yeah but it's more fun if you get to do
it yourself the first time don't you
think let's see girl will fly no Target
cool I disagree with that wow
put it on yourself
I see thank you and then you get like a
fly option
can't get here oh why option yeah like a
skill on the right side I think thank
you thank you thank you
we can fly oh cool I'm flying I Can Fly
wow what oh another Waypoint I'm a real
boy oh nice the ancient Forge
whoa cool so they're special or around
here you can find if you look hard
enough and then you can also find molds
and uh like over here right this this is
mold like
asbestos no you can find molds to make
armor is there Carlos
medium maybe oh what there's someone
here
they're mad we're here they don't want
us to be here ah no problem I'm gonna
make quick business with them yeah make
quick work of them
big dum-dums actually I'm gonna climb up
the rope in a second so get ready
yeah big jerks
actually I could fly up there
well then we keep on missing
you're gonna have to come down
eventually
yeah
oh there's one here too oh he's coming
down for to meet us as in meet us with
his sword meet and greet yeah critical
Miss dummy
tea
there's moriope
oh
my elf oh yeah right my health was
pretty low I forgot about that
well well
only five
kill him somebody kill him see yeah you
got it
[Music]
oh whoopsies
I didn't think it would throw him up
there the river
that's the song hmm
yeah can we do a short rest after this
maybe yeah sure
because I'm out of spells now yeah
and we're getting closer to four hours
so once we find it yeah
mmm this is probably a good place to end
it we got the Waypoint so we can come
back here whenever cool definitely
push them yeah he's dead sorry
well he's still there he's just down
there ah
he's actually not even alive okay
he just broke his back at school
okay
nice nice
homework
[Music]
quiet broken legs for you
honestly imagine this game are so
insanely beautiful and detailed
sometimes I just I know right go away
with my camera and look at everything
because it's incredible it looks amazing
what is that like my God sorry am I are
we still fighting
yeah you're still alive
why are you still alive
get him I need a burst I don't know like
a balloon
I'll just I'll just try to hit normally
this time
come on there we go yeah okay before we
long rest let's go get some stuff oh
stuff
yeah come down where the body fell I
already picked up a mold so if one
nobody else wants to pick up this other
mold here
it's a medium armor I believe yeah yeah
um
yeah I definitely won't be able to hold
that oh wow
uh don't die guys I wonder what this
could be
frail
almost yeah it's mythrall close enough
that I just I think I heard that before
from Lord of the Rings all right or
there's one what does it do there's one
well we can use it for these moles yeah
I'll leave it to you guys okay
well that's a good point to uh we get
out of the lava area and then we can go
long rest and then save and uh start
over
not start over is call it a day imagine
all right
yeah we messed something up let's
restart
to me
oh
nerissa needs sleep
understandable I have a stream earlier
than usual tomorrow too so yeah some
sleep will be good f-zero
f099 I wanna play that too tomorrow it
looks super fun right yeah I've heard of
it surprisingly chill blade in the fires
because Andre as it actually seems to be
really like Smooth in terms of like
servers even though there's like 99
people racing with you
they have their dedicated servers so it
actually
like works
cool I'm excited to test it out oh this
is a chest Arrow
a stinky cloud scroll dinky cloud
yeah I want that
uh we need to use some Scrolls a bit
more or I guess we could just smell them
no no
okay no okay
in my solo playthrough I use the Scrolls
a bit more
yeah oh if we save them
um I might expect one into Wizards yeah
I I might be doing that too later
um
okay I might do I want to split with
Rogue and uh wizard wow okay
yeah learning spells just seems useful
you know
I want to see yeah
well this is
good shall we go to the camp then yeah
let's go to camp
big smash
oh naked lady lying down on the ground
oh
oh did he suck her
blood mintra she's like naked naked
I think I see he's haunting us it's a
glitch
I definitely don't have nudity on but
she has a leaves on her
on her okay she's leafed perfect only on
the lower part
I think it's wrong on my screen it's fun
yeah yeah she's she's leave
cute sure
I just feel like I turn the camera oh
it's fine Callie it's fine go talk to
our favorite NPCs when in doubt
challenge just think about if it should
ever the pp game that fails played and
it was okay if that's okay then new
standards are being set it's a very good
boy
you make a good point
why is she here
um
she just glitches around sometimes
she'll haunt the camp I do want to put
on the ground this freaking dude yeah
right
get him on the ground
[Music]
oh at least he's not naked wait he took
his box
what's his body here oh what
what does Volo upset about us trying to
loot a guy that we brought here what the
whoa Lola is a bit special
I mean I'll I'll pick him up and take
him somewhere else damn no no no it's
fine
yeah right
oh I love how they make camps for each
like specific area that you're in right
this is so much love to detail attention
to detail I love it
but once you take it Easy by the Talon
there's no telling how he's going to
convince you no brainworms
he's not enlightened
no he doesn't want them
let me see where did I put that guy
it was in my inventory a second ago
I was
he mentioned dark just this year's oh
and we've come across I didn't I didn't
realize you were watching sorry Kiara
what I'm not watching anything I mean
I'm watching you yeah that's what I mean
I was skipping text because I didn't
realize you were watching it oh no no
it's fine
no problem actually hold on I know how
did we steal them how exactly
but I felt like I do yeah but the
artifact has a will in its own what the
Volo Jesus
what it likely won't let why is he so
mad I'm so mad he's able to leave if you
let him perform eye surgery now
get eye surgery
we have specimens uh close yeah I picked
it up on the sword Coast
you guys won't care if I lose this body
here will ya I don't think we can take
his clothes but we need his by now
something from him later so just leave
leave him in like the your traveler's
pack my Travelers oh even my chest
put him in my traveler's chest
nice chill rotting body yeah it doesn't
look like he's holding anything right
now so I don't know
it's actually can't take his clothes we
can take mentors that doesn't make any
sense that that seems a little uh no so
it's because mythra is uh a companion
oh you can recruit her if you do certain
meet certain requirements near is not
so that's why I'm in thara is special
and you can take her clothes and
underwear okay I get it well I'm glad to
stuff his body in my chat
the chill dead body in there we hope it
does not need to explain
all right people I'm gonna do a surgery
yep all right let's see don't you just
bolo yeah
definitely seems like a trustworthy dude
hi Rings toys
quit the shouting
bling bling
oh
well is it a good conversation
that's it for now
oh my God he needs time apparently
yeah just a bit longer
thank you so much after the next long
ride I'm afraid the expectations are
very okay I'll get surgery next time
okay
um surgery kind of scares me I don't
really want to see that
understandable it's pretty gnarly yeah
freaky freaky freaky
why doesn't it move oh I have another
absolute Tempest if the wearer Bears the
absolute brand they deal one additional
Thunder damage with thunder damage
spells and attacks are you still trying
to raise them up eh
just a little conversation right
yeah I'm just I'm just chatting and
giving the nib now it's a little more
screen time yeah yeah yeah because you
know I'm not streaming my perspective so
it's fine
my game crashed oh what
an error has occurred and the game has
quit unexpectedly okay let's let's long
rest so let's end the day yeah I guess
yeah but what about you Allah
no no there's a freaking
that's fun
no it's annoying an error occur that may
be caused by problems in your game
installation
next time you launch the game sure
oh
wait
yeah just just wait we'll just wait eh
no I mean is it it's fine
it's fine it's fine uh
so I don't want you to miss out on it eh
okay wait
um it's just two bad fighting
each other yeah they really hate each
other's guts
uh kind of hot though yeah I agree but
it's now I want them downloading content
for some reason
really slowly
don't worry about me anyway okay then uh
beeboo continue
okay uh Let Them Fight
girl fight girl cat five cat fight cat
fight me
dunkers movie yeah they fight sometimes
that's cute
yeah yeah yeah I love kitty fights not
intense ones
and just playful
oh they're gonna fight
yeah
ah she's one of those either one did you
know blazel is only 23.
a youngling I know a baby
oh wait
we all saw this coming
guys if you want to see what's happening
watch Cali stream
mm-hmm
I am viewing the scene
uh
sorry frog lady the new update caused it
would listen to me someone else yeah
because it happened the moment I clicked
on listening into the conversation brain
I hope you're all good people
not Lisa promise
uh not a threat that's a promise
we need her we need her
oh
Kiana you're being so cute I'm gonna
stop watching my stream
[Laughter]
[Music]
ladies
whoa
yeah let's not pit two band
against each other girls
yeah we have plenty of of bad in
this entire party in four of us and then
you guys yum
enough girl fights to go around
okay well that was the end of that and
it looks like it did heal up kiwawa as
well yeah that was inhabiting her body
yeah yeah yeah so that's good let's
let's close the game yeah
good time today good time respect even
though you girls were tired yeah yeah
good job
is a good good old time with you guys as
per the usual it's always a good time
yeah anything you want to promote or
talk about what are your next dreams
happening
um
I have a stream tonight I'm going to be
watching perfect blue with my members
and then uh Monday uh around similar
time to when this stream started this
morning uh I have a collaboration with
onigiri on Twitch oh so are you cooking
she's cooking I'm directing her how to
cook a dish of my choosing
yeah so please look forward to it yeah
I just want to say again uh stream my
album and my new MB pineapple do it
please
also there's a Korean version of do you
up now if you're curious so cool I
didn't even know you could sing in
Korean like that sounds so good I
learned Korean over the past
um yeah first half of the year uh I took
private lessons so now I'm pretty decent
I might say
you're amazing korean's so freaking hard
good job I'm proud of you Kiara
yes okay what's up what's up what else
um let's see for for Mori
um I'm gonna be streaming um I'm gonna
be streaming f099 uh pretty early my
time 9 A.M my time
um and yeah come hang out I heard that
there aren't custom lobbies but that's
okay well I'll try and get in a death
match together anyway
um and then I'll do that for a couple
hours and then
Molly's taking again a really little
small vacation but I think they'll do a
members only stream that night while I
sip some champagne and just chat with
you and champagne that'll be fun yeah
some champagne I think a little sippy um
and then yeah that'll be that day and
then the following day is endurance
karaoke until the big 2 million 300.
um I have I'm preparing a lot of songs
at the end I was just singing tequila
all the time
with other whole of them names yeah
it was good yeah so that's what's up
with Maury how about you baby
uh
I have achieve in six hours oh good
night before that hopefully good night
first now and then um we're playing
armored Core and hopefully we can finish
New Game Plus so we can PVP maybe with
Molly sometime yeah we're finished with
it yeah
brain empty take a nap
take a nap
yeah by the way uh seems like next week
there will be no Baldur's Gate which is
actually surprisingly the first week
since we started where we're not doing
anything together yeah you've made good
progress yeah oh we really we really are
we're almost done with act one kind of
not really kind of but yeah somewhat wow
[Music]
everyone what's up for today
everybody take care of yourselves and we
look forward to seeing you again next
time yes hi everybody and we'll catch
you later
bye
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
thank you