[Music]
n
what is
up hey guys I'm pomu
welcome what is
[Music]
up oh sorry I was checking
Discord hi guys
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello H hello hello hello
hello what's up
YouTuber H I don't know going insane I
mean I'm going
insane I'm already
[Music]
[Laughter]
there
[Music]
um hi po hello did you sleep well for
once
I'm just going to say
yeah I'm just going to say absolutely oh
my gosh like a
baby by baby I mean like you know they
wake up every two hours and scream and
cry uh hion chat good to see you all
hello
hello hello hello
hello posted your image in a Five Guys
billboard oh my God gosh I've always
wanted to be on a five guys thank you
wait really did you take a
picture I've always wanted to be in a
five
guys like you know how I've always you
always see like a Sonic drawing you
always see I don't know sans's
undertale maybe Minecraft Steve but do
you ever see a PO rain puff no you
don't you guys you don't know Five Guys
and go thanks for the five gifted oh my
gosh Five
Guys you guys don't know Five Guys it's
F it's it's it's a hamburger
place and they have like a a Bolton
board where you can
draw and
[Music]
wait what are you guys thinking
about I know six guys wow look at that
guy right there
friend flexing on us
gosh wow we six six guys you know I know
like I know probably more than six
guys cuz I'm in nii
Sanji I know
like however many guys there are in nii
Sanji
more than six
yeah yeah I I gosh now it's my turn to
flex back way to show
off I have to go out in style I have to
go out putting you in your place you
need to
know can you name every guy
[Music]
uh Minecraft Steve
um hold on I'm sweating uh Jack Jack
Black
um Solid Snake the only five guys I need
to know is solid liquid solid is naked
and oot so true hey pmo thanks for the
one time you stopped with stopped by
with your magic carpet it was cool to
give me a ride yeah oh that's a guy I
know that's a guy I know that's a guy I
know rainb thanks for the
Rainbo U Metal Gear otu Metal Gear hi
rainow Phantom
hello hello hello hello today I'm going
to be talking with people I feel like I
should probably get
started
um let
[Music]
me
um sorry messaging people I should have
messaged before
[Music]
stream You Know Jack Black's real name
though it's got to be Jack
Black okay I'm only checking this one
last time Jack Black's real name
oh what
it's his name is
Jacob Thomas Jacob
Black yo we did it we did it we found
someone who changed their name for
[Music]
Hollywood we did
it I've been Jack Black this whole time
shut up rayc I literally met you at the
meet and greet I saw your
face I saw your face and it was Jack
Black he's not lying you guys he's
actually Jack Black isn't that
[Music]
crazy thank you guys for the super thank
you I use your sign we cross cards as
tokens let's
go let's
[Music]
go P at Jack Black
real if I ever meet Jack Black I will
find a way to tell you guys
okay I will be like you must tell
everybody I met Jack Black I don't know
how oh thank you thank you
Matt
I don't I don't know how I would meet
him but I would find a
away thank you for everything you've
done for us tomorrow's my birthday I
will be hitting Boomer status never
asked for a happy birthday due to social
anxiety but since the last time can I
have one for the road of course happy
birthday Matt krer I hope you have a
wonderful Boomer
time
Boomer
status I hit Boomer status as soon as I
Left the
Womb maybe pmo is Jack Black no when the
N TM movie is
made Jack Black must play me in the
flashbacks Jack Black must play me in
the
[Music]
flashbacks so that's why I'll meet him
you know
thank you for not outing me we met at
series anime impulse m city pomu Ryan
Reynolds wow you guys you guys didn't
even notice Ryan Reynolds walking around
wearing the
headband that's
crazy all right guys I'm going to be
doing a Totum Mai today Collins yeah
yeah yeah yeah this is where I sit in VC
and people
come people people come to me they line
up to kiss my
feet so get in line everybody the
headband was the perfect disguise
honestly every maybe every Hollywood
actor should look into
[Music]
it stop no you guys stop I was in they
come line up to talk to
me stop
it can I come
no
no where do I stand the lines over
there you can uh wait your wait your
turn Jack Black and flashback doing
original song hell
[Music]
yeah
the electric
fairy of
a that's what he
do speaking of I have a music video
coming out later today um in about two
hours we'll we'll be still doing Totum
machis
so so uh um we'll do a watch along we'll
take a little break and do a watch along
of it and I'll talk a little bit about
it and then we'll um
then we'll get back to people coming in
yeah yeah yeah you might remember when I
mentioned buying a Wakka
machine it's scheduled to come in today
or within the next day let's go oh my
gosh speaking of games that are going
out of
service you
guys Groove
coaster my favorite rhythm
game
gr coaster is going out of
service oh my gosh it's going offline I
think it's in like a couple months from
now I have to go back to Japan and play
it as much as I
can I'm so I mean it's been around for a
really long time we've had a really good
run with it but I'm just so sad thank
you for the super chats you guys thank
you of course when people are talking
and stuff I won't be able to
um uh I won't be able to read your
messages or anything so much um I have
been reading them off stream though and
everybody's comments and stuff like that
so thank you guys even if some people
are just like you won't see this but I
still wanted to leave a message no I saw
it I saw it I saw your message even you
say I won't see the message I saw your
message so so don't even say that
because I saw
it
[Music]
thanks for the oh that's basically an
aono thank
[Music]
you oh wait did I oh my gosh I missed an
AA sua I'm so sorry wait I'm trying to
get to it oh my gosh real thank you I
don't know what to write here I thought
you were head MTV tuber but after your
love for MGS series I come to love
you I am still head
empty but thank
you um what was I going to say oh you
guys before I jump into to gosh this is
just turning into a normal chitchatting
stream I bought something I wish I could
take a picture or rather I did take a
picture and I post it in the Discord I
wish I could show you guys but
um uh I just got it
I
got
a very good
[Music]
condition Metal Gear standy oh my gosh
it's taller than me I mean obviously I'm
only 9 cm but it's of of mgs2 and it
looks so good I'm looking at it right
now it looks so awesome
oh my gosh I posted in the Discord I was
like you guys look at my metal gears
dendy it's like 20 years old but it
looks so amazing oh my gosh it's in such
good condition and
snake yep I that that I I I splurged a
little I kind of went crazy but you know
Cy than thank
you it's going to be scary at night no
he's protecting me actually actually
you're you're probably right I will
probably get spooked by
it I will probably get spooked by it not
going to lie also Kwan I sang the song
for you but um thank you so much for the
AKA Dono thank
you all right
guys I'm in Discord now oh let me set up
fugie real
[Music]
quick
uh
here um FY fie
ignore ignore
that
[Music]
okay okie
doie I don't know who was planning to
come I told everybody like if they you
know if they wanted to stream or if they
couldn't make it that's totally okay no
pressure so don't be like sending anyone
like why didn't you why didn't
you go to P to ma it's
okay this is no
pressure it's no pressure it's no
pressure or
anything um so I'm going
to
uh I'm going to at everybody oh gosh I'm
scared at every
everyone I'm starting the tosu I'm going
until 1 p.m. yes
see cuz I'm crazy and want to finish
Pokemon
[Music]
L
[Laughter]
send uh
one at a time please I'm
[Music]
anxious food time thanks for the
raid thank you thank you thank you hello
hi guys thank you so much for the
raid
um if I just sit here the whole time if
no one comes that's okay too you know
what then maybe I can just
uh maybe then I can just hang out with
you
[Laughter]
guys thanks for the Super Chat wish you
the best in your future never thank you
07 oh oh did somebody say they're
comfortable
alone yeah too bad I'm here to ruin it
what's up p p oh man this guy come on
Pai you know you missed me a yes I
missed I missed our intriguing
conversations about anime and swords
anime and folded swords yeah I like wa
your Pai has become cooler than he used
to be you think so yeah it sound it
sounds more Metal Gear
now used to be a bit nerdio now it's got
like that energy he's got I I've grown a
confidence you know
Kel why is he say it like that that's
what it sounds like when you're doing it
now it used to be like proper um
confidence now but now you're going like
full like confidence now and I'm like
damn piz are beast now oh my God it's a
glow of yeah oh [\h__\h] I can't wait for
the fan
art of who of
bomai cool Pai went like full like mode
you know when they say studied the blade
and it was like really going into their
parents yard and just flinging around no
he actually studied the the blade he's
like that's yeah that's what I would to
believe he had like the glow up he had
like that Sigma male grind set he had
like a tournament Arc for like a good
month yeah yeah yeah now he's come back
stronger than ever oh my gosh wow I
think I'm I'm going to stand him now
let's go
Pai honestly yeah sounds like a beast
you guys he went to the mountains yeah
everybody take this as a lesson you can
you too can be stronger if you're like
Pai exactly you just got to do
100 me how how far was it 100 push-ups
100 sit-ups 100 squats and then run a
certain distance I forgot it's like I'm
good it's like 10 I don't remember I
know right I can't remember the full
stats I'm good how are you doing pom pom
I'm good I'm just uh here yeah does it
feel real yet cuz it doesn't feel real
to me
nope that's the weirdest thing I've seen
like so many people getting sad recently
and I've been like n it hasn't set in
yet it probably won't set in until like
after the streams are done tomorrow yeah
I think so too I think though like I'm
just uh trying to party it up exactly
that's the thing while you're still here
just go nuts yeah have fun with as many
people as you can thank for thank you
for doing like two days of parties with
everyone from Ian I was so excited to
see that I mean I'm taking up two days
of space I feel
like nah everybody's going to be happy
to be here
anyway that's good I'm not going to be
happy no I'm just
kidding well if you're not you only have
to suffer it for another 48
hours oh God I know right it's going to
I think the weirdest thing is not going
to be
streaming yeah yeah even if I take like
a break more than a week it gets real
weird yeah I know get to that point
where you wake up in the morning you're
like what am I streaming to oh oh I'm
not nothing yeah then the emptiness sets
in yeah then you're like oh what should
I do with my life am I wasting my life
oh God wait who I'm not at that point
maybe I should be studying the
blade fuan you need to take a a page out
of pai's book I'll give you my knowledge
yo oh give me your knowledge instill it
upon me sh
gone no not the shoting
gun how many siblings did you kill to
Power It Up po
marai um let's not talk about it oh is
that why there are no more fairies wait
wait there's no no more
fairies I haven't seen any what s know's
a k
fairy true how bu I feel like that's
like a different species of fairy
right
no she doesn't have
wings
oh and outside of or outside of nii
Sanji there's um there's Maya my friend
Maya she's a fairy there's fairies
there's fairies you're just okay so you
haven't gone full icha yet I don't
murder fairies I I murder
robots heit um I'm only half I'm
good I have a human brain I
swear I'm trying to become a cyborg
now oh [\h__\h] um um we can go steal some
limbs from other people mine mine being
used currently okay what what about how
like but like if you decommission them
like H you could reverse engineer them
yeah send them my way you know
oh my gosh I'm going to make a Mech out
of your body I'm going to be 9 cm and
I'm going to be actually can I just
crawl through your ear and pilot your
through your brain like that one episode
of SpongeBob where Plankton is you know
that would be like the most horror
inspired version of Ratatouille I've
ever
heard just inside my brain slapping the
different parts to make me move yeah
yeah yeah um we could build you a robot
instead okay I'll take a your leftover
scrap yeah I can I can definitely make
you like a full-on like o you know what
we could do we could get like a gunpla
um thing we could build that together
and just get some moving bits out of my
arms oh yeah yeah yeah then no one has
to die right it will be the perfect size
for your fairy form yeah no one has to
die
yeah why did you sound disappointed
but no one has to die that doesn't no
one's going to
die yeah but this is less fun to slap so
true
true um we can make you like a fake
brain to Pilot the Gundam or the
mecca okay that's fun
too I'm not sure if I like the idea of
pom with a Mech that's
terrifying what I I I'd be
responsible I have only played Minecraft
with you a few few times
but it has never gone well for
[Laughter]
me oh okay come on we were a good team
we did balers gate together remember I
mean we didn't finish but like yeah we
were we we finished a lot of things
though like Boulders gate was a lot of
fun but I mean we also we had like our
njy blessed moments where we did that
priest game yeah yeah yeah yeah we had
all our nii chuni moments where we
played like different games and stuff
yeah yeah that was yeah you did murder a
squirrel I forgot about that
no dude you kicked it into a tree and it
exploded I mean I didn't know that was
going to happen it was
involuntarily
manslaughter no I guess so I'm glad we
at least got to talk to it before you
murdered it yeah it was also kind of an
[\h__\h] so he was he was very spoiled
yeah you know what maybe he was a
druid oh maybe I didn't even think about
the fact he was hanging out in the Druid
area maybe you just killed like a druid
oh
God that's why he was so like confident
about everything he was like I'm a druid
and nothing will hurt me oh God the
fairy murdered me you know since we uh
going back to our little board game crew
um oh I love that I know we didn't never
got to play doap Pong Kingdom but I know
ya really wanted to play it too so you
guys should play it with her it's not
going to feel right no I'll be watching
cuz that game is
whack yeah I was so excited for that one
we tried to get that together like a
good what month and a half ago yeah it
was like a bunch of weird timing on
everybody's part so yeah everybody was
just taking holidays at the wrong times
yeah yeah it's okay though it
happen but she'll be there to watch it
yeah and I won't feel the rage I'll be
watching you guys rage it's kind of
great actually I'm not going to rage I'm
going to crush everyone oh oh oh that's
a kind of confidence that sounds like
someone who's going to rage no I never
rageing games I just I mean even that
Monopoly game where everything went
wrong it was just like it's fine don't
worry about it fuing Monopoly everything
always goes
wrong we had the worst Monopoly
r
you had the worst luck you ended up like
in jail all the time you were broke all
the time hey the jail ended up becoming
my home like it was the sanctuary
actually I was I going to say then who
was it you started like beating in jail
prison [\h__\h] I don't
remember yeah who was my prison [\h__\h] I
can't remember I think we played with
Ros and me too but I don't think it was
oh it was Shu it was Shu
apparently no oh yeah the Eiffel Tower
sorry
Shu sorry
Shu yeah was prison rules man I was
having to drink pee like it was pretty
tough in there but um it felt better
than being out in that cruel
world yeah Monopoly is a terrifying
world yeah we eventually made some
toilet wine instead of all the pee yeah
yeah yeah was
[Music]
good oh [\h__\h] she was in chat apparently
oh ni
Sho Oh
No Good Times wonderful times for us
yeah thanks for always being so fun and
collab SW you always will go along with
whatever stupid [\h__\h] is
happening it's always fun genuinely
think I learned a lot of that from you
no way yeah you already to get emotional
here I mean like I I started off doing
like a bit of tuny thing but I mean I
think one of the big moments that locked
it in for me that we can really be crazy
here was um Friday the 13th and we found
you just dancing and singing by
[Laughter]
yourself I love that everyone always
post that clip they love it it's so good
I was
just yeah we all found it one by one and
we were just like what is she doing
there was no one else around so it was
just you
yeah I mean I'm having a good
time but even even before I joined
nijisanji I think one of the first
streams I ever saw of nijisanji Yen was
you doing P's day at court oh was
amazing yeah that was fun it was so good
silly
streams silly streams that look like
they took a lot of work that one did I
think that one was my most that I put
the most effort into probably it was so
good but again you're you're always
amazing in collabs and honestly the way
you just yes and everybody and like go
along with the tuny flow or the serious
times unless you get angry and want to
murder people which also works too yeah
it's it's depends on the type of day I
flip a coin you know
true but no yeah I thank you for always
going along with me I had so much fun
thank you for being here thanks fuan
I'm going to leave before I get
emotional so other people can come in
but I hope you have a wonderful rest of
your day and good luck with everything
and I can't wait to play games with you
tomorrow yeah we'll play
Lots yeah thank you thanks for being
first thank you have a lovely day byebye
pomu bye-bye
fan there he
goes I didn't I didn't I mean yeah like
I said fu Chan is always so much fun to
collab with because you know it's always
fun to get have people that go along
with your stupid Antics and fuan was
always so
like yeah okay something stupid is going
[Music]
on it's not over yet
fuan still got all the games
tomorrow um but yeah if anyone's W
[Music]
oh
I wanted to say hi before going to bed
yeah yeah yeah I was going to say it's
it's like so wait it's so late for you
oh my gosh I'm so it's early it's 5:30 I
know I'm sorry I wanted to say hi no I
wanted to say hi and I just wanted to
say that you were so fun to be around
and I feel like we probably hung out
more offline than online right because
so to yeah yeah like we went to the
amusement park and then good food and it
was so much fun meeting and the mid
Cafe was so much fun yeah I don't know
about other people but for me like at
least like for now it hasn't like really
come to me yet no I don't know it's not
really feeling real yet and also that
but like I just I just know that we're
going to meet
again like hang out again eat good food
again talk like you know like yeah like
we've always been good friends you know
like you've always like had like this
very I don't know just this this
friendly I don't just just something
that you have that really Sparkles and
then it like it has a special place in
my heart and like I don't know Fu like
we haven't really talked like a huge
like a whole whole time but like I feel
really close to you and I love you so so
much and I just wanted to say that I
love you Bo I love you no I think it's
because we've gotten so many Wacky
Adventures Together like you know yeah
just because yeah we didn't get to talk
much on stream you know cuz like you
said the time zones and everything but
yeah yeah but we've always had really
lot of fun hanging out and you know
we'll hang out again so
yeah I want to go to fujiu I know me too
me too me too me too me too me too I
kind of want to go to the haunted house
like the really scary one I've never
been but like I'll go if like someone
else goes with me let's go with we got a
group we got to get a group we can get a
group and we'll go yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah we can do it we can do it
yeah and I loved it when you helped me
out with biohazard Resident Evil with
the the crying baby
you oh my gosh thank you so much for
that remember that that was so long ago
it was was it that long ago oh my gosh
it feels like it was yesterday last
year it was somewhere last that was so
fun though you like you gamed through it
you did it I was so scared you were so
determined to beat the game I needed
your help so
much thank you for
helping of course and I love your
singing no
you you're singing hello no I love H he
hello you're coming with us yeah Oh's
here yeah she's here she said oh she
said not the haunted hospital
yes have I ever shown you the picture of
AO fana and I that we took at the
haunted
hospital no you can take pictures yeah
they take a picture at the very
beginning of it okay I I'll find it and
I'll send it to you yeah send it wao
it's so funny is it that bad
what the haunted hospital yeah well I
think when we went it was still like
kind of close to like like they were
still doing a lot of covid prevention
stuff so there weren't so many people
inside it the hospital like live action
like or like live actors oh like yeah
people scaring you yeah there was less
people so I think now probably it's
going to be scarier which is so
[Music]
scary I hate haunted the house remember
the one that we went like the smaller
one yes yes it was so fun I scared of
that one as well so I probably will just
die
inside we go it's okay do you know how
long the haunted house is at
fujiu isn't it like an hour it's an hour
long holy [\h__\h] no I died in that 20
minute one and remember the guy in the
the reception he was making fun of me
yeah he was like it's okay girl
six-year-old can get through you can too
thumbs up I was like Fu
you we made it it was fine it was good
good
time okay well at least we have
something in the future we have we made
PL yeah we made the plan so if you Chad
if you guys here like you guys got a bug
if it's just like hey we haven't heard
about you going to the haunted house if
fujiu
yet well we got to make it happen yes
we'll make it happen and it's not over
yet because we have the game tomorrow
yeah wait are you gonna be able to make
it are you yeah yeah yeah of course no
no I'm not going to make it no I'm going
to sleep through it no of course of
course I'm going to make it of course
it's so early oh gosh no it's not sorry
time zones no no no anything for you I'm
so excited
y also I don't know before I go I just
want to say that like you know like
auditions are like so hard mm like it's
difficult like auditioning for vtuber
companies so agency it's so tough and
then I like kind of gave up like in the
middle but then like when I saw love
light like when I saw you guys like
debut and like pave the way through the
community I was like I want to be here I
want to be an Ian and that's I'm here
because like you debuted as the first
wave and I just want to say thank you
for bringing me here because I am having
so much fun here and I'll keep it that
way
even after you're gone I love you so
much pomu big peee
energy thank you you're killing it um
and you're also maybe killing yourself
with your cooking but that's
okay don't burn your house down okay
I'll bring you some the next time we
meet okay okay that's the real you guys
that's the real reason I'm graduating
I'm about to
die okay I'm going to going to go now
before you go tell me your favorite food
and I'll make it the next time I see you
oh
um uh oh gosh um I don't know she's
thinking like what can she not mess up
in pizza pizza pizza mhm okay you got it
for pineapples yeah yeah yeah yeah yes
let's go and durian and the durian wait
no no no wait what
the durian Pizza no oh go she's going to
put the durian on I got you fomo I love
you thank
you I'm going to die I'm going to
die oh my
gosh like Kota said it doesn't like fanu
also said doesn't really feel like it's
said again it feels like more like it's
my birthday people are calling in for my
birthday you
know ah
okay we'll go to
Fuji we're going to get a big group of
people and go to Fuji and do the all the
roller coasters especially the one that
was not open last time we went thanks
for the love these streamlabs reactions
I'll miss them oh um uh uh uh tuna asked
if I could share them I will share the
sound files for my notifications so you
guys
can I guess use them for your I don't
know your phone or
whatever whatever you want to do with
it so yeah I will have those for you
guys I'll probably post them maybe under
like the community tab on YouTube so
just keep an eye out for it hey [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
gosh [\h__\h]
sound oh my God happy birthday oh thanks
what's up my God what the
[\h__\h] I don't know what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I
left you everything in
Minecraft I
know I'll I'll remember to finish it
okay make it look good I know you will
but what do you want me to do on the
inside you don't need to do anything
it's okay
do I should I
like I don't know should I put seats in
there or something or lights there's
lights there's lots of Lights you can
put seeds I guess you know he uploaded
another
tutorial the the like the monument or
whatever the hell it was called I was
like yo this guy is so crazy I saw that
and I was like [\h__\h] oh the Mazo I'm
probably going to have to make it you're
going to have to make I I think he said
this one was his like most difficult
one oh my
God it looks really good
though oh my God put pomu
coffin no I'll put it right in the
middle I'm already in the sanctum you
can't oh I mean in the middle Oh I
thought they meant in the middle of the
sanctum oh yeah I'm in the middle of the
sanctum
yeah okay yeah I'll uh I'll cover it
with glass and make it a whole uh
exhibit
okay yeah you can decorate the outside
of
it cuz I like it's it's basically it
digs underground
and uh yeah but you can decorate the
outside okay
okay yeah make charge people to go see
me
okay I'll put a a chest in the front
make me like a real freak Show you know
come see the MiFi body what if I what if
I do what I did with the moon Temple
thing oh actually that's per okay I'm
going to let you in on a secret it
underneath the sanctum is a huge uh um
Lush cave like go when you go in you'll
see you'll see when you go see my grave
you'll see what I mean
okay you'll see what I
mean I was going to do that I was going
to have it open and drop to like the end
of the edge of the
world but um I didn't have enough time
and I'm also didn't want I was
[Music]
lazy it's lazy I don't know you have to
you have to stay on Minecraft though
because you and like a sometimes Willie
you guys are like the only ones left I
know I'm going to what the hell nii
Sanji you need to hire more Minecraft
people I'm going to try and build more
exciting things so that people will want
to come online
yay by the time people come online
they're like I feel like playing
Minecraft today and I've built like a
million new things oh yeah yeah yeah
they'll be like oh my gosh this place is
so awesome oh wow oh my God me while I'm
like week after
week one day I'll finish this know me
too did you are you are you trying to
become
God yes we'll see what happens oo but
I'm inquiring oh he's praying he's
making
sacrifices higher being higher power
yeah I got to see what can be done what
do I have to do who do I have to
sacrifice maybe you're the sacrifice oh
uh I was going to say Willie but oh I
could do that
too yeah yeah probably him
right yeah I'll let you know
okay cool all right I feel like you're
not even leaving I know me neither
sometimes that's why I have nothing to
say Dad
okay
like I think I did all my all my crying
during the during the hop concert oh
yeah you you're saying you like couldn't
unmute or whatever yeah all those tears
came out already so I guess I have none
left that's fine or You' always been a
little dead inside
so yeah I'm surprised I cried at all me
too
actually I like that
laugh all right pomu Bieber puff it's
like my favorite clip ever Beaver is
such a little [\h__\h] he's like I like that
laugh
[Laughter]
laugh oh my God
go
yeah well good luck being God I
guess
um yeah
yeah see you
sometime sometime I yeah sometime in
future maybe yeah I guess I I don't know
what will we what what would we
do I
don't
oh you know just to piss you off maybe
I'll maybe I'll print out um an old uh
membership thing that I
have
what no way
wait
[Music]
what I feel like I can I can talk about
it cuz you're
[Laughter]
leaving wait
what
right
here I knew it
[Laughter]
was oh my God this is an ancient Relic
holy [\h__\h] I don't know why I still have
it you
still saying stop oh my God number
20 oh my God I got delet it people are
looking at
it guys stop
they they're going to steal it your
business they're going to steal it
they're going to make it their
own you guys I can't show it I'm so
sorry
[Music]
um it's okay
um well you
know um that's probably worth like a
bajillion dollars now
so
probably I'll I'll profit off of your um
graduation but I have to wait until you
actually leave then it'll be worth more
okay okay yeah yeah yeah so true so
true well then thanks ukie for being my
Minecraft partner in crime and also just
being you know a [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
affectionate yeah you you two
um um get out of
here [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you I hope you never
come back
you I won't [\h__\h] and I will slam the
door on my way
out bye
[\h__\h] oh my
God
what a what a hoot that
guy can never be
[Laughter]
[Music]
normal I wonder I don't know who's going
to come in next should I keep a list so
I like see who has all hold on I'm going
to keep a list just so I can remember
who who has all been
here
rain bubble R PB R bubble
r m i love you Ru you're going to be the
only moo left bro I'm sorry I couldn't
finish Metal Gear Solid 3 before I suck
at St no shut up shut
up there was one SE section when I was
literally just running away tanking
bullets for like 20 minutes straight I
can't I can't play that game like he
wants me to play it I'm just kidding no
I don't are you having fun with it at
least I am having so much fun I'm doing
this one more than two surprisingly
because there's no rose in
it she's so awesome
though what you she's so terrible I love
her the way she's like always just like
yeah but what about me and it's just
like rose I'm literally eating bullets
right now what the hell can you call me
later or the what was it the those were
okay until they had that one
conversation and it was like
you you don't understand the suffering I
went through when I went to your room he
was like you went to my room yes it
wasn't even as worse as when you hit me
I was like he hit her and then she was
like no your room is empty just like
your heart and I was like rules what the
[\h__\h] it was so bad at so many different
levels I it's so awesome not the hitting
part but the fact that she was just like
you w just like your room had nothing in
it like what is wrong with Ryden it was
it was empty like your heart and I was
like what the hell is this girl on so
funny I love them they're my favorite
toxic couble ever I just can't I'm kind
of glad that I have the mask though the
riding mask for
metal let's go he actually he looks so
good too so funny he
looks he
looks
yes oh oh there was there was the thing
is there was one scene where I I left a
snake naked by
accident by by accident and I put the
ren Mas yes and I put the Riden mask on
and there was a cot scene and every time
that snake spoke his lips didn't move it
looks so
uncanny it so
bad because of like the difference in
skin tone like the
it looks so un
like it's like a [\h__\h] skin walker
like he [\h__\h] like skin R and put you're
so bad E Yeah by on accident you guys
you can accidentally take off someone's
clothes it's true I was asking the same
thing that he was asking like over the
coding I was like why didn't they let
the pant op you know the pants option
too hello
no if they did it with the shirt might
as well just do the full job the whole
thing I think honestly it would be
better because it's like you don't need
to stealth you then just have to shock
them you know like you just run up on
them and they'll be like w throw throw
your pains in their faces and just run
in yeah yeah yeah ex nice strategy yeah
okay Kojima write that
down we're making your job for free
canot
believe it's been so fun thank you for
introducing me to the game I can't no at
first I really thought it was going to
be like okay uhhuh but now I'm just
like the brain
rot
the I'm playing all the games and I just
like instantly do a bunch of reference
from metal gear and I'm like oh I know
it's so evil because the game is so easy
to reference it's like I know I think
when I played it too I was so like you
know I didn't know anything about the
story so I was like oh I'm just going to
play this like stealthy military game
it's going to be whatever but instead
found the jam I know it was literally
like you know I mean I know it's been
such like a critically acclaimed game
for ever but I just had no idea I didn't
even know about it yeah I didn't know
about it either yeah but man I'm so
happy enjoying it then enjoying it how
many games do I have left though after
three okay that depends on you because I
recommend I recommend doing four and
peace Walker that's it those only only
those two yeah but if you but then you
could be like oh my gosh I still want to
play like the game play for five I think
you'll like a lot the story is kind of
whatever but I think you'll really like
the game play for
five wait was five the one that no yeah
was five the one that was like with a
weird ending like with a rushed ending
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh okay oh yeah and
rising of course sorry guys I I always
forget about Rising cuz I played it
first so I like forget about it it and
the people are playing it man oh and
peace Walker does have co-ops so you
could play with
a
oh well if she waits for me though cuz
I'm pretty behind that's okay she still
has to play wait for four I'll go to
Columbia and I'll bring my PS3 and then
you can play four please I don't own one
okay I'm so happy I got to play this in
my in my other PlayStation if not I
would have been probably been putting it
off for a while M I know cuz it's such a
pain in the butt I know yeah such a nice
game thank you P yeah wait are you
playing the master collection or yes oh
okay okay yeah yeah yeah good good I I
ended I ended up buying like two copies
though remember cuz I bought the I
bought the PlayStation 2
collection oh yeah that's right that's
right yeah yeah and then things happened
and I was like okay fine I'm going to
buy the other collection then you memory
card man I'm so
sorry I I would feel so unmotivated too
by that like I mean yeah it was a pain
in the ass but it's fine I guess I get
to like display it you play metal yeah
collection she's a true gamer
guys yeah I get to be a
[Laughter]
poser how is your day been going what do
you do today
um I'm just I'm just here I'm
chilling yeah oh hold on do you wake up
right before stream no sorry let me just
message this person I'm so sorry it's
okay solid disc rainow I think I had
another coach chat I don't remember
which one was it it was a clown one cuz
I am so good at stealth yeah you guys
have no one seen me trying to clear that
it's either I Tangled the bullets or CH
tell me you don't need to kill anybody
and I'm like wait the clown key who's
the clown oh was it silly snake yeah I
think Chad just calls me silly snake oh
you're silly snake yeah like you don't
need to kill anybody I'm like the key
word is
need yeah and I want to she enjoys all
the killing you guys differ I enjoy all
the
[Laughter]
[Music]
killing oh my gosh yeah you me a Viv
we're all going to have to do metal gear
talk yes without spoiling the rest of
them though oh I know okay I'll we'll
wait I'll do my best we'll wait then
please I'll do my best to do three as
fast as I can no no no you're okay don't
don't rush it just take it in enjoy it
because it's such an awesome
game you just finished beating the
fear yeah and then I got lost in the
forest for like that's the other thing
oh my Lord my chat has so much patience
man I ended up going in circles in the
same sector like at least like three
times and I was like why can't I reach
the the objective where am I and Chad is
like bro are you perhaps an
idiot rain Kash idiot
IDI it's like that oh man oh man and
while I get lost doing a circle for
three times I just tanked bullets it's
so incredibly annoying to watch me play
those games but I'm enjoying it so much
that's the worst part of it they suffer
and I'm just there laughing that's you
know what then if they're suffering they
should take some pain medicine you know
that's fine yeah different kind of
enjoyment everybody yeah exactly this is
a stream for the for the M's all right M
if you want to raise your hand yeah
right
now the next SP is really cool I think
you like it the
four people are poking me about four
though cuz they're like I feel the the
characters that you're going to like the
most will probably be in three and not
in four but you'll probably but they
were like if you enjoy the killing
you'll probably enjoy four more like
gameplay wise and I like the game playay
for four like goes up so much more too
it's so easy so so much easier really
wait how so what do you mean it's just
better controls and like um the the uh
the camouflage it's like if you lay on
the ground or like lean against a wall
it automatically
changes oh that's so cool yeah it's way
more modern yeah oh they won't let you
you wear the stinky outfit or the
chocolate cookie
one Chate you say the chocolate dookie
one chocol oh
Cookie I'm going to miss those
but no five five has definitely the
guest or the best game play it's like I
feel like you will do so well in it
because it almost is like
Apex let's go what the hell yeah the
Apex with a controller though oh I am so
bad at shooting with that's another
thing good luck you would expect me be
like okay she sucks at stealth she tanks
bullets but I guess her aim will be okay
oh no no it's not she's got I if I could
do it you could do it I'm just stubborn
that's the only thing that I have on my
side
stubborn man man well thank you for
playing them I'm still glad yeah that I
got to play them that you were there at
least for
like at least half of the whole series I
would say yeah I'm so lucky you I still
remember remember in I was it Metal Gear
so one or too there was like a key was
for a codc that was in the I probably
for wine mhm that was in the cover of
like the disc and I was like I don't see
it where is it and then I had to like
send pictures to you and you were like
R right there right I was like oh yeah
the Merill codec yeah like 30 minutes po
where is the
codec so good oh I'm so glad you're
enjoying them I've always like know I
was scared because it's just like I'm so
like brain rotted with this series and I
felt I was like oh my gosh what if they
play it and they like yeah and they hate
it you know so I feel it's hard to hate
in Metal Gear
no yeah I think so too it's so funny so
awesome cuz I I I was talking like
literally like 10 minutes ago with chat
about it cuz they were like we didn't
think you were going to were going to
like metal gear and I was like why
didn't you think I was going to like it
and they were like you know it's it's a
stealth game you know oh I hate Ste G oh
my God no same and I'm so bad at it but
then I was like I mean it all just comes
down to preference for example for me
silen heill is still my favorite series
but it's just because I prefer horror
games but if you don't like horror and
if you end up liking Metal Gear more
that's way like that's 100%
understandable I see where you're
standing oh my gosh there's one part I
think you're going to love in this game
then oh my gosh what do you mean it's
like it's it's horror esque it's so
awesome you're going to love it oh my
gosh I can't wait for you maybe I
haven't been I haven't been there right
no no no no not yet it's oh you're going
to love it oh my gosh it's like my
favorite part of the game it's so cool I
can't wait I'll be watching I'll be
watching please DM me if I end up
getting into the part please okay yeah
yeah yeah I will I will promise me you
[\h__\h] I I promise I promise no spoilers
chat no spoilers yeah no spoilers they
have
been quite decent with spoilers
really yeah I think yeah that's good
that's good that's goodone going to
haunt your asses from the grave in my
chat if you spoil anything I swear to
God she'll give me the secret
mod no cuz I will okay I'll I'll still
mod for Metal
Gear just tell me which link and all I'm
not even I'm not even lying I will still
mod for
you what what else am I going to do
don't do even cuz I will I will actually
do it okay okay send me whenever you
want the link and I swear to God to add
you to the list so just become a silent
one she's going to be watching you all
you guys will never Escape my
sights thank you
R I'm going to miss you so much I miss
you
too the only thing that I regret
probably the only one is that we didn't
get to collab one one enough sorry
I'm a little bit socially awkward when
it comes to that me too it's a theia I
know you
guys I thought you were going to say
also I thought you were going to say the
thing I regret is the Latina joke but
it's just no well
no no cuz at the end of the day he ends
up being a memory that I can look back
and it's linked to you and then I end up
laughing about it despite the horrors
behind it but vanta suddenly like
stealing it too like what the hell this
guy get out of here everybody most of
the people are now linking it to him and
I was like hello
no he can have it it's okay if you're
going to no please not there's one of
the things that you cannot put in like
in your in your well pleas do not right
it okay okay vanto you're not allowed to
have it it's mine it's mine and ru's
joke only okay Ru my woman Ru my woman
it's a stream it's official it's
official official clip
it okay I'll see will you be playing
tomorrow no hello ma'am oh wait on your
over at yours yeah of course oh okay I
sign out for everything I was like
yes okay then I'll see you tomorrow yes
I'll see you tomorrow then P I'm not
going to steal anybody's time anymore
okay take
care
byebye uh give me one
[Music]
second
uh R mo mo we have so many jokes
together I'm so
happy she should is is she's going to be
the only moo left so take good
care
um
[Music]
uh I have someone coming in I think it's
actually my
only non nii sanjian person I wasn't
sure if they would be able to make it
but they
are
[Music]
oh my
god look look what I
did the pictures are so
sad it's like it's like I I'm um is it's
our beautiful memories in pictures yeah
oh my gosh oh my gosh so
[Music]
smart
can we just cry for 10 minutes
okay I can't cry whenever I'm with you
because I'm always
smiling shut up don't be so
cute but that's one thing about you
you're like always smiling and always
laughing even when you're
sad I it's a coping mechanism no
pomu how you doing after 67 minutes of
being told goodbye I don't know so
weird I'm okay it feels like you know
when people call in for your birthday it
feels like that yeah yeah feels like my
birthday you you're not grasping reality
no it's not real maybe it's not real
maybe it's not real maybe I'll wake up
do you do you feel like sometimes you
hope you wish Maybe
maybe it was not
real that's such a sad question
sorry sometimes just because I'm having
so much fun yeah it's it it's honestly
like I really really really respect the
decision itself because obviously you're
like you're leaving behind such a such a
big Legacy and and you you built so much
up in in nii sanjian and being being
like you know we're both we're both
first generations of our
branches and I don't know about you
maybe you felt like a lot
of obligation and such similar feelings
for staying possibly oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah I can't imagine like the kind of
pressure that you guys felt like you
know you're you're you're technically my
Senpai you
know like so yeah how how how long after
did you debut again after us oh it was a
it was a good amount of it was like good
amount of time maybe like almost a year
I think yeah but you guys were like the
first like from like a big company you
guys were like the first how to say like
not Rivals but the first something to
challenge us you know right right but I
don't think I
ever just because I don't know I I never
really felt like that from the beginning
I never saw you guys as someone I have
to be like seeing see as a rival or so
it was never like that also because I
don't know did you how how how long did
it take for you to DM me cuz I remember
you dm' me with like that mumi picture
and you were like I I offer you a mumi
and I'm like sorry momoi isn't even my
Oshi I'm
sorry I like
M who doesn't like
true I don't know I I think I think I
was always so nervous to DM because I
you know I didn't want to seem like I
was like you know intruding or
anything no I was so happy to have a
friend like
you and I think it's great that we can
we could see each other as friends even
though for like the longest time we
couldn't collab I know we were we were
Romeo Juliet yeah for so long seems yeah
that seems like a long long long ago
past I know yeah it was ages ago yeah
now everybody's collabing it's like so
happy and free it feels so good yeah
freedom feels good beautiful
Freedom so I I don't know I feel like
you're really really strong for making
this
decision I'm sure it took you a long
time to figure it out but I do think
that leaving at a from my point of view
like a high point rather than a low
point is probably a good thing yeah no I
think so too like thank you no thank you
for you know every time I've talked to
you about it you know you listened and
you gave such great advice Kiara is so
thoughtful you guys like am I yes you're
so thoughtful and hardworking and you
always were like you know you were
thinking with such good perspectives and
giving
yeah oh really I don't I don't even
remember what I ever said to you no you
were always so so awesome that's all I
can think you're still awesome you're so
I'm just honored that you trust me and
you know you want to like talk to me in
the first place about such
things I'm I'm I'm honored thank you for
for seeing me as a friend to talk to to
I can't wait for us to meet yeah like
that's one thing that I am kind of mad
about we couldn't meet at all in this
time you know people were saying uh cuz
I think cuz I was in Japan and you were
somewhere else in a snowy snowy Place
yeah people were like oh she's she must
be in Japan right now they're going to
meet it was no no we
tried yeah we did try but I saw that
video I was watching it and I think I
was showing it to narissa too your uh
what was it alas no Antarctica yeah yeah
yeah other other side of the
world well it's pretty [\h__\h] cold in
Alaska too no
yeah but yeah you went to Antarctica and
I was I was watching that I was like
holy [\h__\h] this girl her dedication to
her craft as always is incredible you're
so unique your brain is so creative and
it's it's like you're you're such a
genius like it's it's such a sorry cat
hair in my
mouth it's such a such a like how can
you I I think losing you is really a big
loss because you were such a mastermind
and I see you from an outside pu
partially outside POV I see you being
like besties with everyone I feel like
you're connecting everyone in nii sanen
and you're like a bridge for everybody
so I'm I'm sure they will all do greatly
even when you're gone but it's still I
feel like all a big big piece of the
puzzle the one of the biggest puzzle
pieces will be missing one of the
biggest pillars of n szi Ian um but is I
think if that's what you want if that's
what you need then so so it shall be and
they're surely all supporting you and I
don't think you ever need to feel guilty
even even even if the pomis are crying
don't cry pomi don't
cry you're the best you're the bestest
you you are thank you for thank you for
you know Paving way for all of us no no
no I think we were I mean you know when
when I debuted I was told uh or we were
saying you know cuu sampa paved
everything and I think that was true but
then all of us I think we all had a part
uh myth paved their own paths and then I
think also you girls you paved a big a
big part you also had a a big influence
in the in the Ian sphere especially
so you did a great job in your time and
you did everything you could you did
everything in your power and I wish you
could have done more but you did
everything in your power that's for
sure thank you so big
respect you know the good thing is at
least frog bird isn't graduating so
true so I can still collab with frog bir
right yeah yeah of course that guy his
schedule's Wide Open No thank God like
it's probably more important to me
because if if froggy waa doesn't have a
man to like have sexy time with then she
gets she gets really moody and she's
trying to like kill me she she haunts me
every day I'd prefer not to think of
frog B having any sort of sexy times
with anyone what frog boy is very very
sexual frog okay okay you think so he
frogit has insane amounts of Sexual
Energy I mean come on oh my gosh maybe
maybe I'm just refusing to see him like
that wow is this how everyone else feels
too well I I wouldn't see froggy waa
like that either you know cuz I guess I
don't know what what is frog bird to you
pomu who is frog bird to you um he's
like a menace he's like you know he's
he's um he's just some guy that kind of
showed up on my at my
house and borrows your VR equipment
yeah no frog bird frog bird is hot
oh not from my PO oh sorry frogy Wawa
said that you guys not Kiara yeah frogy
don't misunderstand
[Music]
please yeah so frog bird M please hit up
frog Wawa anytime when you feel like it
I hope he hears it FR frog bird are you
around I'm telling him right now hey hey
hey froggy was asking for you okay like
you haven't called her and like you know
visit her yeah go go over there she's
waiting for you on her lily pads oh
she's got the lily pads ready frog Brey
you need to get over there now oh my
gosh everything's really wet and steamy
over there I hear
meowing
it's chunky wonky she also wants to meet
you you're welcome anytime in Austria if
you ever want to come by not if when I
will come yeah okay okay okay my Kito
Kos will will welcome
you thanks for taking the time K I know
you are about to go your the funny thing
is the funny thing is I thought you were
doing even more Collins on your last
stream because like uh I I we talked
directly but also uh my manager gave me
a time and a day from like your
management side and they said
20f oh I think they're confused yeah I
think they were confused so I and that
confused me so I was like oh I guess
she's doing another toachi so I won't be
calling in on this one so I was just
chilling in my bed and then you were
like oh if you still want to call in or
not it doesn't it's okay and I'm
like oh [\h__\h] I'm so sorry oh no you
probably not ready that I'm so sorry no
no I'm always ready no no I'm never I'm
always ready to talk to you but I'm
never ready to say goodbye to you
no it's not goodbye though also cuz like
you know you're one of the very few
people in this like Ian vtuber vtu
sphere that understand the whole like
especially hello project and like AK AKB
uh Idol things culture so that's the one
I think the biggest reason why I
connected so much with you and was
really happy to have someone to talk
about that with you and we were able to
sing together I made you sing a song
that you probably didn't even know but I
forced you I wanted to it's okay I
learned
more it was so fun oh my gosh I love the
gift of us dancing and we're so in sync
like people use it all the time oh yeah
it's so cute there were a lot of cute
gifts and screenshots from that there
was so many so fun I've had so much fun
during that stream yeah me too me too
also the recent ones I thank God that we
could still collab a little bit more
before it's too late
yeah yeah Pomo you will be missed
[Music]
greatly and um man and it breaks my
heart to see people leave not only for
myself cuz at least I can like talk to
you but like you know seeing seeing Ich
so
Mama
P give them big kisses and big hugs
before you go it's the hardest part for
sure I hope you're doing okay too me
yeah them you you me yeah you I hope
you're doing okay and just in general
okay oh I'm okay
he starting my break today more or
less yay yeah get lots of rest I think
you should um leave something behind
that for the Pachi like I don't know
like your your spit or your breath
bottle I was going to say maybe hair
like yeah hair yeah fing some strands
fingernails yeah leave something behind
oh guys what you would what would you
prefer it'll be like I'll leave enough
it kind of be like Exodia you know but
of body what's
Exodia you the Yu-Gi-Oh card oh [\h__\h] I
sorry I don't okay so there's there's
this there's this like one creature
called Exodia you have to collect his
body parts and if you collect all his
all of his body parts then you
automatically win the
game oh oh so you get like a card you
get a card that says like exodia's left
arm and then exodia's right arm then
exodia's Left Foot exodia's Right Foot
and then oh okay okay I only know like
one
Yu-Gi-Oh meme thing I don't know
anything about Yu-Gi-Oh the only thing I
know and I already kind of forgot is the
thing something where he the dude is
like because in the anime he just does
it like that he plays something and then
the other one is like you can't do that
and and he does it like anyway what was
that you have no idea what I'm talking
about I have no idea what you're talking
about I already had to explain my joke
of green pot of Green Oh pot of
green that's the only one I know wait
you play Yu-Gi-Oh I used to yeah oh my
God I would do I would do like
tournaments what tournaments yeah when I
was a kid I would go to the bookstore
and do Yu-Gi-Oh tournaments oh is is the
the the the the duel also from Yu-Gi-Oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah ah okay then I
know two memes she knows two memes two
wow she's go she so
cultured yo I the only like
animeish card game that I ever played
was uh Wick cross woss oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah and I I keep on seeing nii Sanji
doing like stuff with Ruru and I'm
like
[\h__\h] it should have been
me it should have been me wait were you
really that into it I um I I started
getting into it for the anime ever since
the first season came out oh yeah that's
right this was an anime yeah the anime
is like holy [\h__\h] it's like uh Madoka
Maga with cards oh really because it
looks cute and you think you're getting
into something cute and wholesome
typical of that like magical girl
whatever uh genre and then you get into
it and and you notice it's dark as [\h__\h]
and people die what yeah it's a card
game it's really really dark there's who
so if you want to be surprised by a dark
as [\h__\h] uh magical card game with cute
girls okay I'll look into it go yeah and
then I tried to I I I bought some card
sets uh and card mats and all that but I
had no one to play it with because no
one here plays we I wish it was more
more you know worldwide like Yu-Gi-Oh
yeah yeah Yu-Gi-Oh has like a choke cold
yeah also I played magic did you ever
play Magic no I never played magic magic
are ging you
nerd what you're nerd don't go me nerd
you're a nerd you who is the bigger nerd
I think you are the bigger nerd you
think me okay chat chat who's the bigger
nerd it probably depends do you still
like watch anime actively I haven't in a
bit I but I a little bit Yeah okay mean
not me so
[Laughter]
pomu also you have the you're kind of a
superior Idol otak only because you you
know all the [\h__\h] chance and yo I saw
so many videos of the nja Sanji Ian fans
like screaming and buing the chance you
taught them and that's also a legacy
you're leaving behind no one else could
have ever like spread this kind of deep
deep Idol culture culture uh overseas
like you no one ever has had such a huge
impact with with that in particular so
that's actually kind of insane point you
taught so many who would have never
known about it and they're so passionate
about it and it gets like it it gets cuz
like I've I've seen in I don't know
maybe in American conventions it's
generally a bit better but I've heard it
isn't just in European conventions I've
experienced when it comes to like you
know people performing concerts and all
that the audience is usually like
relatively quiet maybe they clap at the
end of a song but you know they don't
really cheer much in the middle of a
song uh so having something to like with
a lot of confidence scream out loud and
chant I think helps a lot for the
audience they have something to do and
it's just so [\h__\h] hype you know I
don't go as hard as you guys do I I just
you know hello project chance are kind
of basic guess kind of Bas it's okay
though that's okay hey hey you said it
first yeah yeah but we have to remember
the names of a million girls in the
hello project I mean okay AKB too but
but still but yeah but we we we we we do
we do dance choreography copy copy oh
the food copy yeah cop we do that pretty
intensely I don't know about you but we
need to focus on the dance
totally yeah no but yeah that's
incredible you're
incredible I hope I hope the N sanan
fans when they go to conventions they
will continue to scream their [\h__\h]
lungs out please I hope so too I hope I
hope it spreads I hope everybody starts
just screaming at all the concerts
spread the virus guys spread the virus
virus continue pumu Legacy I think she
would be really really
happy I
would I still don't know how to do it I
will really oh my god well I guess I
guess one could just to make up their
own chant right yeah you could yeah
that's how a lot of them start they just
make them up no I'll just make up my own
yeah make up one for your original songs
there you go yeah well W you never made
one for me did you well you made one for
hinoni did I make one I think I a little
bit you you sang didn't we sing didn't
you sing like yeah I sang it didn't you
sing my song yeah yeah and then or I
sang it and you chanted to it I don't
remember anymore oh wait no I thought I
sang it you sang it right yeah no
I know you I know you made videos for
the for your songs though oh yeah yeah
yeah I did try I kept it simple you know
kfp chicken brain one brain cell I
needed to keep it
simple sorry if K to dunk on you there
literal Chicken
brain honestly I this it's crazy how
they remember so much yeah how do they
how do you guys remember remember all of
that I don't sometimes chat is crazy
they'll remember like the tiniest things
that I've said like months and months
ago and I'm like how do you remember I
don't even know what I had for breakfast
like crazy yeah yeah I'll give that
point to kfp toodle they also remember a
lot yeah just not just not the
chance come on kfp do better drill
starting from tomorrow yeah do your reps
do your do your mix reps come
on yeah
oh man so I hope that we can still meet
I hope this doesn't mean that we'll
never meet you know meet you
IRL cuz I met some others and they all
told me about
you and I'm I'm like tell me more about
pom tell
[Laughter]
me yeah the usual room you'll have to
turn the usual room into the rep's room
for a little bit a okay okay yeah I
might do that
thank you Ki thank you for taking time I
hope you have a wonderful break and rest
a lot thank you well I hope you rest a
lot too I hope you get to like enjoy
your time away even if it may be weird
in the beginning like I can't imagine I
feel like you'll be like wait what the
[\h__\h] I'm not going to stream today what
am I supposed to do I'm already thinking
about it because even when I'm bored I'm
just like oh I'll just stream what do I
do if I'm bored
yeah there'll be lots of time on your
hands so use it wisely I
will thank you k I love you I wish you I
wish you best of luck in your future so
much luck so much luck I will go out
personally outside and uh find a four
fourleaf clover oo for you oh my God yes
and then I'll burn it because because
that's our Phoenix ritual oh don't worry
okay it it's on
purpose yeah so best of luck thank you
and I hope I hope you find a path that
makes you happy in the in the future
too and no one will ever forget you ever
you're
Unforgettable um I I'll I'll do my best
congratulations on your legacy promo and
big respect for for everything you've
done so far the time you invested into
this channel into this job and every day
you spend working so
hard big respect you are amazing pom
you're the most amazing fairy I love you
I love
you I'll talk to you later oh really
okay
[Laughter]
yeah of course I'll I'll be around I'll
be around just for you just whenever you
know you if you ever want to send a
message
whatever goodbye byebye
[Music]
K
yippee let me get back into the collab
um let me okay so we have about half
hour until my music video debuts let me
uh I was going to write a
uh
um
mama let me write the I was going to do
this earlier
text yeah like like I said like um I
always just when I'm bored I'll stream I
don't know what to do now I love
streaming though it's so much fun
no I what do I do I have to I have to be
productive with my
time I can't just I can't just go on the
internet and make jokes anymore oh my
gosh I can't if I'm not the joke anymore
oh my God what am I do what am I doing
with my life big love for Pomeranian
thank you
Kiara thank you for coming I'm so happy
I'm so
[Music]
happy second was H Kota right kot
K oh oh oh and then
ukie and then
[Music]
Ki
right oh rainbow I'm so stupid my brain
you guys sorry I did not get a lot of
sleep last night I was like I don't
think I knew there was someone else
sorry Ru I'm sorry it's not that I
forgot you is that I'm an
idiot this is why I'm making a list
because I'm so bad at
thinking I got
like
and hello Miss rainow hello
Anna hello
hello how are you doing I'm
good how about you
good I'm saying sad
sad well I'm not happy oh uh sorry about
that are you ever
happy
no it's true when you posted your
schedule and you were like every day
sucks life is
pain it's because I couldn't stop making
mistake it was so
annoying I still have one it says
January 22nd January 28th no way wait
that's next week she you're trying to
kick me out
already I know
sorry I don't know what day it is I just
know it's a sad day no it's not the last
day
yet oh
no I can't cry sorry I'm too shy I was
like oh my God are you actually cry I
thought I was about to be amazed I was
about to be like what I can't express
emo
I no it's fine you he um um this know
why I'm always so awkward with you this
is like our remember when we had that
one-on-one collab together and we were
so
awkward like the one time and it was so
awkward it was so
awward I don't know
why I don't know I think I'm just so
awkward and you're awkward and we're
just
like I think I'm the problem you you
think
so yeah
yeah I mean I don't know I I I always um
you know I feel like offline we're
pretty good you know we
are I don't know what it is about being
online we just kind
of I mean yeah we did a lot lot of
things I think we do more things offline
than we do
online to
karaoke yeah several times Wendy's at
like I don't know 1100 p.m. or something
it was our our New Year's
Wendy's the stinky sauce that someone
left behind did you talk about that did
you talk about that no I didn't
actually we can talk about it now I
think it was like on the last year of
2023 right yeah literally like on New
Year's Eve after after our dinner we
went to Wendy's because I was so tired
but I wanted to stream I was like I need
coffee so and nothing was open cuz it
was New Year's Eve it was like 10 p.m.
900 p.m. 10 p.m. so Wendy's was open and
we go in and there's like this table
next to us that is so disgusting it's
Rak like they left their sauce
everywhere we went to the floor and the
whole like the whole room smelled really
bad and I was like there's nobody like
there were a lot of people sitting there
actually but nobody was like really
bothered by it but I was so bothered by
I was like this is like a sour hangy
smell and I don't appreciate I was
trying to like look like who is eating
like fermented Wendy's Burger I know and
you ended up cleaning it the guy the
Wendy's employee guy actually came to
the floor and he was literally taking
out the trash but he didn't take the
trash that like somebody left behind
yeah he didn't clean up the table and
then we were scared that they thought it
was our trash so we were like it cleaned
it up and then the smell went away and
that was my last memory of
[Laughter]
2023 was so funny yeah that was that was
a time that was silly
yeah I think like we both drank like I
think it was matcha right you had the
matcha drink
what did I have I had I think I don't
know if I had the coffee or bubble tea I
don't
remember I think you had something with
caffeine and I think like we were
gaslighting ourselves into think we were
like shaking or something oh yeah we
were like the caffeine's hitting us guys
in our hands we're like we're like
jiggling I wasn't sure but I was very
excited cuz I was like oh my gosh I like
we ate so much at the dinner and so that
I was like I need to wake up to stream
the countdown and then you know what end
I ended up missing the countdown cuz I'm
an idiot what happened I got I got
distracted by something and I just
didn't I didn't by the time I I think I
was trying to set up a clock and then by
the time I by the time I set it up I it
was already New
Year oh but you were streaming yeah yeah
yeah oh but I I didn't even get to do a
countdown your problem yeah yeah it is
my problem I mean at least you weren't
on a
train I was like am I going to make it
back home into for the countdown and
then I didn't and I was just I was on a
train oh so we both had really you know
really great ways to start the new year
I know like this guy beside me was like
almost falling asleep on me and I was
like Oh no you're going to fall asleep
on me into the new year
house know oh like that means it can't
get any worse it can only you know go go
up from here I hope so what's your New
Year's resolution I didn't make
one I don't
know
ow wait what's
yours okay I told I told a couple of my
friends this and they all laughed at me
so now I have
PTSD okay my
my New Year's resolution is to do better
self-care so I started it by changing my
Wi-Fi password to I love myself one two
three how often do you have to put in
your Wi-Fi password I don't think it
works if like you only have to put it in
once you're not well you can change it I
can I change it every
year he I knew he would come out of the
culprits it says it's a step in the
right direction
everybody I think it's beautiful screw K
kco that guy's opinion doesn't matter
yeah thank
you new new year new me new year new
Wi-Fi
exactly oh my God and I'm so excited for
your fairy of aimers oh gosh I'm so
nervous I saw the trailer or like like I
saw like a snippet somewhere yeah so
good like oh my God a full
animation I was wondering what you were
doing cuz I saw you Tweeting a couple of
days and you're like I'm so sorry I
didn't sleep and I like what she going
to like I didn't animate it but I feel
bad when I'm just like gosh I'm so tired
I'm like wait but the people worked on
it they're the ones who were tired
they're the one doing all the work but
you have to direct everything that's a
lot of work too this was fun though I
learned a lot actually so I'm really
glad that I did it even though it was
hell I'm it was fun it's always hell up
until it's uploaded I
know yeah yeah yeah oh excited I sound
excited I promise she's so excited
exited you
guys either there or you'll die everyone
oh that's my New Year's resolution for
everyone to watch my music video or
die that's a good one yeah all right
guys we came up with it actually an know
what do you think my New Year's
resolution should
[Music]
be like in terms of what anything
anything I think your New Year's
resolution should be to explore new
things and experience this is his this
is my PR answer okay um I know just do
whatever you want you're you're you're
fairy free I'm fairy
free yeah what are you going to
do this year is um I have a few travel
plans but that's all can I go back to
antic oh I wish oh my God
actually I heard AA almost died and I
anticipated it I remember she was
leaving I looked at it and I was like I
love you so much you're one of my
bestest
friends I thought you guys wouldn't come
back you thought I come on have more
faith in me I wouldn't let her die I
mean we did almost get lost and like
froze to death in the middle of the
water but terrifying it was so fun and
you would have hated it but it was so
fun I know
it was so beautiful you caught like such
beautiful sceneries thanks
yeah I love the footage I got so cool
did you live in egloo or anything what
the [\h__\h] we were on a
boat I don't know I don't know what up
in
Antarctica there was an option well they
wouldn't they couldn't do it because the
weather was so bad but there was like an
option to Camp outside you had to dig
your own hole and then you like out in
the snow and then you like had to pile
yourself in and
stuff wait so you camp outside by
putting yourself in the snow
yeah and there's nothing over your head
no I guess not I didn't do it so oh yeah
I wouldn't have liked
it frozen tomb yeah exactly the Frozen
womb where is one place you'd like to go
this year this year
yeah I want to go to your house so I can
use your Wi-Fi
password you're welcome in my house
anytime
yay I'm you know I I'm going to change
my Wi-Fi password I'm so SI of this no
no I have to use it if I come over and
it's it's I love myself one two three
right yeah yes okay I see I remembered
it that's how important it is if I go
there and it's not that I will
literally I I don't know what I'll do I
will freak
out okay I'll keep it just for you come
visit me yay okay I'll come
visit yeah yay thanks for coming Anna
thank you Pomo I wrote so many cheesy
messages for you like at least three
times so I feel like anyway I love you
and I'll miss you a
lot
really yeah yay I love you too and uh
thanks for all the fun times thank you
for all the fun times too even though I
never joined a Minecraft collab that's
okay I don't
care are you going to play tomorrow
or Minecraft no the games tomorrow
no no okay I'll see you around I'm just
GNA oh you meant in your collabs Sor
right yes yeah Oh I thought you me like
my own streams or something I need to
start phrasing this question better
because everyone thinks
sorry I was like huh I'm going to be
there D okay I'll see you tomorrow then
I'll see you tomorrow good byebye thank
you byebye
byebye
yay oh my gosh now there's an actual
list of people oh my gosh I'm
scared
[Music]
uh we're going to have the next person
come in and then
uh and then uh we'll do the music video
hey what's up k conle I'm good just you
know I can't believe you're
leaving stop
this so would you believe it if I cried
or would you be like nah this shit's
fake I'd say it's fake I say it's fake
as hell okay at least at least you know
me well enough to know that you
know yeah what's up
man um well low key I I didn't plan
anything to say um I just want I just
want to hang out I do I do want to say
you know I appreciate everything you've
done for all of us you know you like
behind the scenes you do a lot more than
people know um like advocating for us
and like I don't know you set an example
for a lot of things and so I really
appreciate you kind of doing it you know
putting your foot forward and you really
you really take on the Senpai role like
for everyone like you do it's crazy and
so without you we're definitely losing a
big part of our like you know liver kind
of community we have in the Discord and
everything so it's gonna be it's going
to be hard to you know go on without you
but I know I post you're going to you're
I know the things you're going to miss
the most like my Mount Fuji pictures you
know yeah yeah exactly myig my big
contribution to the
Discord well you you know what I mean
you know what I mean oh my gosh yeah
yeah no you you too though I mean I
think everybody kind of comes together
with a lot of stuff so yeah yeah yeah
it's been nice to see everyone you know
recently come together and like hang out
and all that stuff it's been very very
fun Hangouts has been popping everyone's
been playing Final Fantasy I know I'm
I'm so happy my God it's such an odd
time too it was just like the most
random thing and was like let's hang out
how did start I I don't know I wasn't
there for the start me Millie and finana
have been trying to get everyone into
Final Fantasy for like damn near a year
and then all of the sudden like we got
ukie on oh it was because AA got on
Final Fantasy that was started yeah she
did it and then everyone else was like
oh my God ay likes it maybe I'll like it
cuz you know [\h__\h] [\h__\h] kelin he a little
bit crazy I was like you know I kind of
agree with you so then ay was playing
and everyone started hopping on and then
V was showing her around and it became
this whole big thing and now everyone's
playing shout out to
[Music]
AA
n well you know I'm glad then that you
guys have like a good you know I know I
wasn't interested in it sorry but good I
mean you've been busy too yeah you got
to be all like on 100% you know for the
pomchis for your last week you can't be
you can't be hanging out wasting your
energy yeah on Final Fantasy you guys
I'm paying attention to you thanks you
guys are denying me pre ious times with
my with my you know nii Sanji gen mates
and everyone and now now I've missed out
on all those precious memories because
I'm taking care of you crying
[Laughter]
babies it's all your [\h__\h] I love how all
the memes on Twitter about you
graduating and people being sad you're
just [\h__\h] retweeting them and you're
like bro stop being dramatic basically
it's so
funny no I get it they're just silly I
like to be
silly yeah I'm playing Gaia Online
instead what the hell what the [\h__\h] I've
haven't heard that for so long oh my God
that ancient Relic I think a still plays
really
mhm I never actually played Guy online I
just heard about it no it was it was
like some ancient [\h__\h] to me I'm like
damn it's not even that ancient it's
just like I don't know it's pretty
ancient at this point yeah I feel like I
was playing Webkins when that [\h__\h] was a
thing you know what I'm
saying like I didn't really do the Gaia
Online do you know like the thing with
Gaia now the
economy no so the economy is like so
[\h__\h] in that game like even the most
cheap item will cost like a million
dollars wait why I don't know like they
just something happened with it I need I
need someone to do a deep dive video on
it like come on where are all these like
YouTube channels that like those do do a
into the rabbit hole on Guy online yeah
come on I need to know what happened
with the inflation I'm going to DM him
gu online next video
please I have 20 plus trillion gold holy
[\h__\h] wait I I think it's cuz like all
the vet players like still play and so
they've had like what like [\h__\h] 10
years or some [\h__\h] to get all this money
I have like I have like good items if I
sold them I would probably be like I
would be maybe the richest person not
really but you know a started the
inflation yeah well AA I have 40.5 octo
dilian cookies and Cookie
Clicker oh my gosh yo can we talk about
this guys listen every time I ever see
Pomo status on Discord it's like playing
cookie cooker for like 5 days or
something it's like never like 20
minutes it's always like like 15 hours 5
days 24 hours a
week I'm like your CPU was crying
that might be why my computer's dying
actually you just always have it open
yeah I just leave it open overnight and
then I it's open right now I have it I'm
actually playing it no I see I see for
four 15 hours it's been open yeah oh
yeah I turned off my computer I let it
rest a couple days ago yeah yeah yeah
you know you give it a break just like
when you go on breaks you just leave
your computer on that's crazy too your
computer is a trooper it is I think the
video card is actually the problem I
have to get a new one maybe I would
literally be scared my computer would
like explode when I was away and then I
like my house would be on fire oh I
never thought about it like
that the one time I had my power supply
unit like combust what yeah I got some
like shitty pre-built it was like one of
those sites where you can like build it
but they do it like at too much of a
discount like it was a little too good
to be true and I guess they cheap out on
the specs that like normally you don't
consider so like the power supply the
motherboard I remember one day like I
turned on my computer and I just heard
this like loud bang and this kind of
spark and like it kind of glow glue red
for a little bit and then it like fried
the [\h__\h] out of my computer oh my God
wait was it salvageable or like did you
have to get a whole it [\h__\h] up
everything the CPU broke the graphics
card broke oh my God that's one thing
like with computers you can't like cheap
out on stuff like you got to yeah I mean
I was kind of new to gaming PCs at the
time so I didn't really know so after
that I was like oh hell no I'm never
doing that again I was like if I get a
pre-build I'm just going to get I'm
going to like you know you know sell my
my kidneys and get like a good one at
least yeah damn oh that sucks so much oh
my God I'm so sorry and then I remember
I emailed them and I was like hello and
they were like they were like tough [\h__\h]
I was like what you mean it was under a
year I had a warranty I was pissed I was
pissed I was so mad that's so [\h__\h] oh
my God I was so mad but yeah just you
know I hopefully your PC doesn't explode
don't think it's a common occurrence but
it can happen you know I'm like staring
at it now like oh my God am I seeing
smoke coming out of the top no like I
kind of have a fear of that now I'm not
going to lie like I to that sounds
traumatizing like I don't put it on my
desk anymore I put it on the floor and I
put it kind of far away so in case it
goes boom boom like I'm just going to
lose a leg and not my [\h__\h] face you
know is it the wait no I was going to
say is it the same computer but you said
everything was oh no no I'm never buying
a computer from that company again oh my
God God never again I think I could have
gotten a better computer off of like
Craigslist that was like used for the
past 10 years I saw a comment earlier
that said you got the temu the teu
computer yeah I got I got a computer
from temu like dead ass I I did one of
those and it was an American company but
that's the equivalent that's a good a
good comparison I got one from like wish
or something it was
crazy crazy it's so bad wow yeah so you
know be careful if you guys buy
computers you don't get ones with shitty
power supply units kill kco don't be
like him yeah or maybe I just have
really bad luck I don't know either way
you know traumatizing so it was pretty
that's pretty scary yeah did it like
smell like did it like actually
burn it kind of did it like I like
turned it on and then I heard like a
couple like it was like some loud
clicking it was like almost kind of like
Sparks and I was like what the [\h__\h] and
then I just heard of boom and then like
the It kind of glue red and I had like a
glass um a glass like side on it cuz the
the case looked really nice but I guess
the internal parts were dog [\h__\h] and so
the glass like broke um oh my God that's
so scary and then there was like a
little bit of smoke and then um it kind
of it smelled really like weird and so I
freaked the [\h__\h] out I like um I turned
off like the power strip it was plugged
into and then unplugged it and I kind of
like watched it for like the next hour
with fear and and then when I realized
it was kind of chilling I you know I
didn't know what to do I was like I'm
not pouring water on this [\h__\h] I didn't
have a fire extinguisher cuz my dumb ass
didn't think my computer would explode
so I was just kind of watching it like
uh and then when I realized it was like
chilling I I I was kind of just
depressed that it was broken after that
I yeah well k um I have to get going
soon cuz my music sorry I didn't I don't
mean to rush your you you're good guys
watch the the the the music video if you
don't um you'll die like Anna said just
like Anna said wow oh my gosh my New
Year's resolution your New Year's
resolution if you don't watch it you're
you're
dead um what was I going to say um yeah
I'm glad that you could talk out this
trauma in my in our final conversation
together I got you thanks for being my
my therapist I appreciate it you're
welcome I'll send you the Bell later you
know yeah yeah I got you all right bye
bye K thanks oh wait oh never mind
I was going to ask if he's going to play
games tomorrow with us but I think he is
I think most people oh what what what
are you going to play games tomorrow oh
yeah I'll be there for crab game okay
I'll see you tomorrow okay bye
bye Okie
doie all righty guys let me get the
music video up I'll put I'll post the
link um and everything oh gosh I'm so
nervous oh my stomach hurts so
bad I'm so
nervous um here's the link but don't
leave this stream as well well it'll you
can leave if you want if you don't want
to listen to me talking I probably won't
talk too much I'll probably just be
like uh we have two minutes before it
starts though oh that's me you probably
heard for a second thank you guys for
all the super chats by the way oh wait
uh
watch Fairy of
Aki Aki verse here premiere
[Music]
Pomo original
song
yay pin
[Music]
message and
uh starting in 60 seconds is there's a
two-minute countdown
[Music]
so
uh let me turn off the music and I'm
going to turn it off so you guys can't
hear uh and uh oh gosh I'm so nervous oh
my gosh I still have a tab open that
says Jack Black's real
name oh and let me oh wait hold on let
me set up this too the redirect back to
here just in case you guys forget to
come back don't forget to come back
guys wait oh uh here save save okay
perfect I think we're good to go oh my
gosh my stomach hurts so bad I'm so
nervous
uh the premiere will begin shortly
guys there's one part I'm excited to see
you guys' reactions to
[Laughter]
it cuz everyone that I well I don't
think anyone has seen it actually yeah
thank you um but people that I've shown
screenshots too oh my gosh ah it's
counting
down two times two speed everybody
playback speed times two everyone that
I've shown it to though they've been
kind of like what the
hell what the hell is
this oh my God wait why does it say only
25 seconds left I I put two minutes on
this thing wait
what wait it says it's only 10 seconds
left what the
hell why was it so fast I put a
two-minute countdown on
it okay that was so fast mine is at 5
Seconds mine's starting oh my God it's
starting oh my gosh you guys might have
seen this this part it's the
[Music]
same oh it's
buffering
YouTube YouTube oh my God I have to redo
it you
[Music]
know
okay why did it buffer for
me I'm just counting
down
no actually I really want to see how
this one part looks
because
God
Bento I'm coming out of your TV Soko
Style
yeah I filmed all of this this is all my
footage you can tell how old it is
because of the niif Fest Stu
of
UB big pee
[Music]
energy
yay
here it
comes believe
[Laughter]
me we thought that for that the part
with the different art styles it kind of
gave like a visual novel
vibe
the book off sign makes me laugh every
time
buffering it's okay you can watch it
over and over
again oh my God it buffered for
me buffer hype let's
go yeah by
[Laughter]
stars
that's the part I wanted you guys to
[Laughter]
see actually that's my Monday
sign now you guys have to go to all
these spots
pilgrimage that was our baby
[Laughter]
girl Manan was so
funny he'd be like thank you pomu this
is my first time
ever he'd be like this is my first time
ever being able to wear a maid outfit
and a sailor fuku outfit I tried to also
do an O outfit but we couldn't find one
in a
size he was so excited he was like oh my
gosh he was like i' I've never have had
an opportunity to wear a made outfit
before and now I
do
[Music]
yay
yay that's what you were cooking that's
what I was cooking
yay thank you guys I hope you like the
music video
very um I think some people might ask
this so I'll just I'll just answer it
now unfortunately I can't get it on
Spotify so
um was like who did the
[Laughter]
dance um unfortunately it won't be on
Spotify so uh um you'll just have to
stream it from YouTube directly but
yeah turn the music back
on everybody worked so so hard thank you
fobu no thank you that was awesome fobu
big p energy forever thank you thank you
for the behind of me
um uh what was I going to say
oh it took so long a lot of it took so
long because of the real life footage
but I was really really determined to
hot dog thank you I was really really
determined to have it
[Music]
um uh
so um it took so long to get that kind
of
approval
um uh so that first delayed it and then
and and then um the people I was working
with they had their own schedules too
you know and so then because they were
had stuff that they were working on it
got delayed because of that and then I
started working on stuff and then would
get delayed because of me and so it was
like kind of like you know part of me I
was just like oh my gosh I wonder if
I'll ever be able to if I if I'll ever
be able to uh Premiere this but in the
end it worked out and I think the I
think I think it's a pretty you know all
things considered I think it's a
um a pretty awesome uh music video so I
hope you guys liked it
too I tried to like make it a bunch of
different like I don't know like Styles
and mediums that's why I had like the
live action and
the that MV was very pomu course I got
Electric Fair vum
thank
you um I wanted it to have like I wanted
like you know the pixel art um I like
the mushroom did the you know the
um the uh pixel part for that exactly
exactly how I described that I wanted it
um so awesome and then uh Leah did like
the storyboarding and she is so entirely
cracked she's so awesome
why are you so cool stop
no she like came up with so much of the
concept like originally I only mostly
had the chorus of what I wanted to do
but she helped flesh out um like the in
between stuff she was really awesome and
then we like got into a meeting and
we're just like oh what if this happens
and oh for this part let's what if we
did this and you know we were kind of we
she was so awesome to bounce ideas off
of and then um
yeah every we
we and then two two days ago hold on let
me
see let me see when I posted this
because it was absolute torture
um thank
you thank you so much thank you thank
you wait I can't I'm trying to find it
but I can't find it oh there it is L
live Electric Fair AC I kneel to the MV
team be promo thank
you
um
uh um where let me see I'm trying to see
[Music]
uh there was like just so much stuff
that needed to get fixed last minute
like on the 15th they were telling us to
change some things and then I'm trying
to
see uh
uh I think it was either the it was the
16th pretty sure it was the 16th when
Manan came back to me and was just like
you need to change one of the background
scenes I was like
huh what do you mean by
that what do you what do you mean by
that so we had to scramble
again to
um
to uh get that fixed it was so I felt so
terrible even asking for it you know I'm
tired but I can't imagine how the team
was because they had to go in and change
[Music]
[Laughter]
everything so
um uh there was a lot of last minute
changes and things but um everyone was
so amazing and so awesome and they all
pulled through they're typing in the
Discord now yeaw
Yeehaw oh
[Music]
man and if you notice the animation was
done by the same person that does my
ending screen animation I really I I was
really happy to be able to work with him
so thank you guys OT oh it's got it
everyone I'd be miserable for you any
day pomu shut the hell
up shut the hell up I was I was trying
so much I'd be like please if we need to
cut anything if we need to cut anything
that's fine I just want to get it out if
if if we're cutting something for the
sake of your health that's okay you know
we can change things for the sake of
your for the sake of your health
please oh yeah
they're all posting in the Discord so
funny o o u yay sorry that it's like the
day before my
graduation hot dog hot dog thank you
sorry that's like the day before my
graduation but um you know if you ever
want
to uh oh my
gosh
is hold on let me this there we go thank
you oh my gosh wait I'm trying to find
your thing it's very old that was
amazing thank you for the music video
was so worth the wait everything was
perfectly poo and so much fun to watch
thank you Manan
p a thank you ducky thanks for the 10
[Music]
gifting it's a really nice parting gift
so we can remember you yeah if you ever
are feeling down you can watch it and
it's really high energy and fun and you
can go to the different spots in Akiba
and have like a little bit of a
pilgrimage you can be like oh my gosh my
pomu Pape here pomu stood
here and so you can have a
little a little moment go to AKA you can
go to AKA and be like I remember this
scene because it was in pom's music
[Music]
video
yeah
so um thank you guys I wouldn't have
been able to make it without you guys so
thank you so
much oh my
[Music]
god dog
H
H making tweets now in a little bit okay
I'll retweet them I I'll I'll retweet
your tweets
hey I want to go back to Akiva now
because I know it would feel so much
more magical my fairy was here
yeah so much
[Music]
fun it's finally
out all righty let's get back to the to
machis though because I will be
streaming Pokemon later I want to be
able to get through as many people or
everybody if possible um if I have to
push Pokemon a little bit that's okay
too sorry it's kind of like a really
late time but we're going to beat the
Elite 4 yes we are we're going to get
that screenshot that I said I was going
to share with you guys through other
people hell no I would feel so shitty if
I didn't beat my challenge so I'm going
to beat my
challenge
yeah I can stream as much as I want
until I'm gone and so I
will okay
um uh who what let me see let me find
the
order
D TI thank you oh I'm sorry did I say
your name wrong D DAV titanium pyro
thank you for the 20on gift by the way
thank you so
[Music]
much I'm trying to find it where is
it Gail Force thank you for the 10
gifted as well I'm a little late oh find
no it's I who found
[Music]
you you thought that you could fight the
Elite 4 without getting through me pomu
rain puff huh huh oh this not called the
elite D
dopo in order to delete the Elite 4 you
need a d now it is time for you to check
what is what is Pokemon type
matchup what beats bug type a fire a
fire uh
[\h__\h] you know what thinking about it
that was probably one of the easiest
ones bug types are so uh are so horribly
weak huh yeah my my my my bug
fables TI your uh gym my my bug fables
themed gym usually doesn't you know they
usually don't win so it's pretty uh oh
you should do a challenge it's a rough
time h a challenge actually that would
be kind of sick wait doio I can hear my
voice he my voice uh can you mhm okay
all right so
okay I got it if you take out your ear
uhuh phones you won't be able to hear
yourself right what so I'll no so yeah
no if you take out your earphones from
your ears you won't be able to hear
yourself um I'll just scream really
really really loudly so that you can
hear me from like the earphones that are
like you know away from your
[Music]
ears
okay hello it's awful to say goodbye
ah oh sh says don't be this is a stream
oh okay hold on I I'll fix it um I'll
maybe maybe I'll be right back actually
while I fix this okay all right okay see
you in a bit see you all right skip my
turn oh bye bye okay I'll be back what
just happened what did he mean by
that what did he mean by the by
the what did he mean by the uh um you
know thank you for Thea rock forit thank
you so much inclusion of iral footage
all the style mashing together pixel
game session oh po dancing during the
solo Oh D during the the dancing hold on
I'm trying to find the list of people so
I can
um ping whoever's next but uh
the the during the dancing um oh thank
you
sho
um oh I'll say it after hi
Willie hello I am Willie oh God you're
you're on the uke train too I don't know
I think I'm more team Willie team Willie
willly is kind of a classic isn't it
right
yeah how you doing good what's up with
you what's up uh a little bit tired I I
I just I played like a visual no for
like 7 hours on stream I'm a little bit
tired but oh wait what' you play yeah a
date with death how was it oh did you
die or M it's up to you to find out I
guess there's multiple endings how
mysterious yeah it was pretty good I
enjoyed it it was cute was pretty nice
but yeah so if I sound a little tired
I'm sorry I talked I talked for 7 hours
straight so you didn't expect me or I
didn't expect you to be the visual novel
type me
neither me me neither I guess I guess
you figure something out about yourself
every day wow oh my God you surprise
yourself you know yeah okay let's
[Laughter]
go well yeah well did you play a lot of
visual novels yourself I used to a lot
yeah anything that
rings a bell to me anything at
all what do you mean like what that you
would know yeah maybe oh you probably
like clad M okay
yeah no Stein's gate
at all I I have not played the Stein
gate visual novel you've watched the
anime though yeah of course of course
okay okay okay I I've I have not played
the visual novel either but I've been
told thousands of times to play the
visual novel I know I need to even
though I watch the well now I have
plenty of time on my hands so that's
true that's true you'll get to do more
things hell
yeah yeah oh school days yeah I played
that
[Music]
one
I'm not very experienced with visual
novels I play like maybe four total
what's the four what's the four name
them off name name what you play
um I
played um are they
naughty maybe I don't know um I I I
played um what's it called I played the
the nekopara game with crisis that was
pretty nice oh you're right I played I
played the um I just played a date with
death which was pretty nice I enjoyed
that one it's pretty cute um I
played um oh
god oh
freck I forgot what you only remember
the ones you've done on
stream yeah well the other one's like
maybe I should not see on stream that's
all I'm going to say oh type it type it
type it I'll I'll tell you if it's bad
or not if it's bad yeah I mean well
you're saying I mean if you don't want
to say it on stream I'm going to assume
it's
[Music]
bad no not that actually I did play that
one you play Dramatical Murder okay
maybe like two hours of it okay okay
that that one's one um I think I played
like that oh that's Niel par is like so
you know it's not bad at
all okay okay yeah I played like the
first two I think that's it if I
remember correctly not more than that
okay yeah yeah see that's so whatever
you know it's not that bad okay know
that's like so
normal not naana saying it's for the
week what yeah you should here I'll give
you um I'll give you it's a it's a game
it's a RPG visual novels called monster
girl Quest if you lose the battles you
get vored by the
girls Viv if you're listening what the
[\h__\h] uh sure man shoot in my way I let's
go there's three of them they're really
good happens they're good what they're
actually really good oh if you win well
I mean can't say on
stream uh okay that's fine that's fine
you know some things are better
Untold that's okay it looks like lot
that goes on there's a lot that goes on
in that
game okay okay very eventful I I'll I'll
remember that I'll remember that I do I
do think like I should play more visual
novels though they're fine yeah kind of
like uh what you call it not much
popular genre nowadays um some some like
some kind of make it out like being
popular for a little while it's hard to
stream them though it's hard to stream
visual novels yeah God yeah it's really
really hard do you have to be short or
like really really funny um but yeah
it's it's really difficult yeah that's
why like the neopar like the the boys
one was is good cuz it's like yes it's
perfect it's like per it's perfect
length of like gameplay yeah exactly
just a short stream it's so good yeah
it's kind of quirky so yeah it's good
it's good and it's
free it's free yeah two I like free
visual novels they're great it shouldn't
be free should be you're right though it
should not be free it's it's astonishing
that it is fore but look I know
huh we'll take it
what is that what's
what what the
[\h__\h] a just posted like seven oh my God
holy [\h__\h] she posted like seven links to
AI sunium
[Laughter]
files you should play that one actually
yeah I should play that one I got to
play is is it safe for work yeah she she
she and finina both streamed it
huh oh that's a popular artist
though wil soon play it this is this is
like aa's metal gear she's trying to get
everyone to play AI somnium files damn
bro we never talked about Metal Gear
Metal Gear we is that crazy hell I know
we've always made like we've always made
not a single [\h__\h] time in like since
my debut we never sat down and talked
about Metal Gear for a single [\h__\h] we
just randomly throw references at each
other randomly out of nowhere but we
never sat down and actually talked about
that's crazy I know it's so crazy what
the
[\h__\h] well just sometimes yeah like make
a joke and then move on that's it yeah
just say one thing and move on but never
actually add in a serious conversation
everyone's just spamming their favorite
their favorite games yeah doio was
spamming bug fables sh was spamming frog
detective yeah there it
is yeah you could have joined me a Viv
raymon yeah I'm trying to beat one on
hard difficulty right now I think you
watched a little bit if I remember oh
yeah yeah yeah I remember I was heart
stuck on great
Fox that was [\h__\h] painful I think it
took me like 3 hours to beat him oh my
God you have to learn his pattern like
perfectly otherwise like you get three
shot and you get killed it's insane it's
really [\h__\h] hard but I really wanted
it's like no no radar
you get three shot by everything it's
really hard hard yeah it is that I might
do middle gear too um and honestly I
played only the intro mdle 2 yep I'm a
fake fan wait what I've only played the
intro mdle 2 yeah wait were you one of
those who is just like oh it's not a
snake so I don't want to play anymore no
I love Ryden I actually love Ryden I
don't know I just I played it and I was
like oh okay cool and I don't know why I
never picked it up again wait you know
the story though right yeah I do I do
okay okay yeah yeah of
damn you have to experience the story
Willie what are you doing I know I was
thinking about playing it on stream for
the first time because I was like okay I
got to play it for real for real I
actually have to play middle gear too I
have to do it I'm a fake fan I'm sorry
okay you're talking middle Gear Solid
right yeah Sol sorry not m 2 okay yeah
yeah the M Solid 2 I have to play M
Solid 2 I my God I have to actually beat
it I never did but I played the [\h__\h] out
of three I think I beat three like four
times three times okay I love three I
know oh Viv what the hell four I think
four is underrated I think so too I love
I think people hate on it too much
because they're like oh but cut scene
cut scene yeah but it's good ass [\h__\h]
cut scene I don't get I get like the
issues that it has you know like I can
I'm I'm not a fan who's going to always
be like this is perfect this is perfect
whatever whatever but like I love four I
think some people have issues with like
how four kind of like Chang the story a
little bit but I I don't hate it like I
kind of I like it I I think I no
spoilers V is still playing I'm not
trying to spoil uh I think it's a great
conclusion I so do I know it feels
satisfying it's like it really does the
N of the N of form I'm like you know
what I'm okay with this it's fine no I
think it feels good mhm it does feel
good it's like satisfying you're like
okay that's it it's wrapped up andar
Rising is after Metal Gear Rising it's
like the the best character
assassination of Ryden ever it's so
funny really you don't like how they
portrayed Ryden in
no I say I mean it in like affectionate
because like it's really it's really
starts in four where he like you know in
two he's like I'm going to become yeah
I'm going to become my own person I'm
going to be you know I'm going to throw
away this fate that was decided for me
and then he's just like you know what
never mind I think I am going to be Jack
like what the hell
man I like ah [\h__\h] it's so hard to talk
about middle gear solid four ring
without spoiling but you know if if you
know you know right like it's like you
go from that the conclusion it's like
Rising it's like what the [\h__\h] happed
what are you [\h__\h] thinking why are
you doing this what are you doing that's
why I mean it's character assassination
but it's awesome everything just it the
book just closed you close the book that
was it that was done you're done you
move on and that's it that's that's the
character but no they're like no no
let's let's bring him back for more it's
so awesome I mean four is I mean I mean
Rising is great though too so fun
yeah yeah I like a lot of things for
four um I think people like to to poop
on it a lot I think it's kind of
unjustified I think maybe once people
can start playing it again maybe like
more easily they'll be less poopy maybe
like they have bad memories about it
because maybe they played it once and
didn't like it but I think if like the
ending yeah I think if you played it
back like it's just it hits it different
oh it really does oh my God I don't
think if I played it as a kid I would
have been like so you know impactful
about it but like it's just so good it
really is I'm currently be playing
through five oh oh oh yeah I saw you
were playing like on your new steam deck
yeah yeah yeah um I'm doing a pacifist
run on it wow I beat like three h sorry
three I beat five like three times now
uh I just for me it's like I know people
like to you know criticize five for a
lot of things that I'm sure people are
tired of hearing about but I I I think
like the game play is peak in that one
personally um I really like the gam play
the it's really really really fun oh
hell yeah five gameplay is so awesome it
is so awesome you really feel like you
can pretty much make your own build and
like if you if you're a lethal character
you know kind of player boom you can
make a lethal build if you're more
passive player boom you can do it um
like they took every you played Peace
Walker right yes a yeah they took
everything from Peace Walker and just
like made it into the best that it could
be like it's just oh so good never
Walker either what the hell oh my gosh
you're missing out on the best boss
fight ever really yes wait do you know
it like do you know what like um I think
or anything yes I think so I think so I
think so I'm pretty sure really you have
to finish okay now you you AA rayu VI
when you guys all like when everyone
gets to Peace Walker you guys need to
play together together on one stream no
yeah you can do
co-op wait it's still up yes I played
with my I played like literally last
week wait wait on on on PC or like on
the the master collection the okay or
not sorry not the master collection the
um um the HD Collection oh oh so the old
PS3 one yeah yeah yeah okay yeah cuz
that's the one I have yeah oh wow it's
is still online what the [\h__\h] yes that's
insane so you guys all have to do co-op
together and beat it that'd be so
awesome oh you know what that'd be
actually awesome I'd love to do that
yeah you guys should get
together maybe maybe also play a little
bit of uh portable UPS I think I played
that one more than than
um than that yeah sorry I'm tired no
it's okay I portable Ops is
rough yeah yeah it's I mean yeah I was
going to say wow but it's on the PSP but
I just remembered so is peace Walker um
on they're discussing the timeline V or
uh Peace Walker ground
zeros did you play ground zeros yeah of
course I played the [\h__\h] out of it when
it came out how the hell did you how the
hell did you play that and not play
Peace Walker you don't understand the
story I don't know I I listen I at the
at that time I had played four three and
one when ground zeros came out four
three and one yeah yeah oh my God wait
not in that order right no no no not in
that order I played three first I think
three was my first time playing m gear
I'm pretty sure I think that like when
people you know mention that five is
their favorite even story-wise I think
it's only because they played five
first M yeah yeah I think that they
didn't play the like maybe they like I
don't know it's not that the other games
have a Nostalgia factor for me cuz I
didn't play them as a kid but like I
think it's just that they and and
honestly and because five was like so
Innovative for the
time I put Peace Walker Ground Zero 5
and Shu just said tosu
order true okay next up is com next up
is peace Walker you
guys but um yeah I'd love to I'd love to
yeah but like uh I don't know I think
that's why because it's just so it's
felt like such a groundbreaking kind of
game with like the mechanics and
everything and the playing it's just so
awesome the fox engine is [\h__\h] goated
God it's so good I know it's so [\h__\h]
good it runs like butter like I've never
had a single [\h__\h] like like I've
never had an issue with running M gear 5
it runs absolutely [\h__\h] beautifully
you could run it like on Windows 95
awesome it's so
good man so they're calling us nerds
yeah what about it okay yeah I like a
thing so what God I like talking about
thing I like with other people that like
the thing I like it's cool that you can
play it so well on the stream deck too
yeah no it it's like perfect like 144
FPS like like I I have the latest Steam
deck whatever it's called the the no
wait the OLED is yeah it runs
beautifully it's it's perfectly like 144
FPS like refresh rate and everything it
yeah it's it's insane I play middle Gear
S 5 on the plane oh my God that that's
crazy that that's [\h__\h] insane to
think about like yeah that's pretty
impressive I sit down and I just play it
and it works and I say I've said this
before on stream like multiple times but
I think the most impressive thing about
five is it looks like a game that came
out like yesterday it's just
so up it still looks good it's so good I
was watching like well I got to a
certain point of the game I'm not going
to spoil um where certain character um
dies um which I will not say um and the
cut scene is like 10 minutes long and I
was like this is this is this is [\h__\h]
Cinema holy [\h__\h] it's it's still like
every single scene is captivating and
I'm looking at it like I'm not bored for
a second watching that cut scene it
still looks so good the game looks so
good it's like almost 10 years old it's
kind of baffling Willie did do you
regret your words and deeds my words and
deeds your Deeds actions whatever the
what whatever the quote was
oh um okay well it's like my third time
rep playing so like I know about things
that you got to do yeah like you're not
supposed to know about if you're it's if
it's like your first time playing so I
guess yes or
no yes or
no yeah kind of when you saw quiet you
didn't you didn't you know regret
anything no but what was done was done
the deed was done you know what I'm
talking about right I think I'm not
sure I'm trying to understand
like you can't even type it cuz no one's
going to see it [\h__\h] okay so no no it's
not a spoiler so when the game came out
and like people saw quiet they were just
like why why does she have any clothes
onima and and then and then it was yeah
the lore explained why well coima made a
tweet he was just like you have to play
the game then you will regret your words
and actions or
whatever [\h__\h] did he really tweet that
yeah it's a
meme holy [\h__\h] The Mastermind that it
again he really said play the [\h__\h]
game you'll figure it out stop being mad
that's why she has no clothes on idiot
it's not cuz I'm
horny dummy oh words and deeds sorry
words and
[Music]
deeds man I I really want to talk about
like a a Twist but I can't cuz it's
[\h__\h] major spoiler we should yeah we
got to talk more Metal Gear or you know
you'll have more people to talk Metal
Gear soon so ABS that's true that's true
you caused a ripple I hope you know that
you un ironically let's
go well you know yeah I remember when
you're in your debut with the metal gear
reference I was like oh [\h__\h] here we
go here we go I'm going to talk so much
about Metal Gear with this doesn't talk
about gear
I don't think we've ever I think this is
actually our first time talking one on
one it is no holy [\h__\h] that's true that
is our this is our first time talking
one-onone oh unless unless it's
Minecraft I don't know actually I don't
count Minecraft okay I don't count
Minecraft either then the first time
talking in six [\h__\h] months holy [\h__\h]
sorry I'm not a very good Senpai I'm
very I I well you guys are always in
Hangouts I don't join Hangouts very
often so no no I don't blame you it's
like I don't know uh it just you know it
just goes that way I don't know what to
say I'm glad I'm glad we did at least
once though that's awesome always wanted
to Y little bit yay we got to talk a
little bit about Metal GE cross that off
the list talk about Metal Gear with
Willie there you go
[Laughter]
boom but I don't want to take too much
of your time I think I've taken a lot as
much as I like to talk about M with you
um I will keep in mind I know I'm not
maybe I'm not a true true fan because I
haven't beat two um but I will okay I
promise I will beat it yeah did you seey
I got yes I'm [\h__\h] jealous I love yo
shawa so much and I'm very very jealous
but I'm very glad that you have it cuz
you deserve it for sure you're a true
fan you're you're a true patriot you did
it thank you of course um I'm saluting
you but you can't see yeah I can't see
it I'm doing it too don't worry okay
it's very mutual
thanks Willie thank you very much have a
great rest of your stream will I see you
tomorrow in games yes you can bet your
ass I'm playing those games I don't know
if you revealed yet so I won't say them
oh I said them already it's okay okay
okay yeah you can bet your ass I'll be
that okay yay I'll see you tomorrow then
thank you take care by
byebye
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay oh yay we got to talk about Metal
Gear together
finally so funny I can't believe I was
like wait a second oh I think doio is
going to come back let me add him uh
dopo you good what a weirdo said what
weirdo
uh
yeah
M come on
in
[Music]
oh it is time for the Pokemon battle
hello hello hello maybe not a Pokemon
battle anyway anyway this is part two
part two rematch yeah yeah an absolute
rematch welcome back I beat you the
first round I took all your money now
are you
stronger I caught a new Pokemon hello hi
go my new Pokemon this one is also a bug
huh what do you have to say against my
new bug type Pokemon
[Music]
Fire I knew you were going to pick fire
you're as readable as a book and and
your pokon very easy book painted right
no way no my Pokmon is both a a a bun
and a
fire he absorbed fire exactly it is an
absorption special ability so now it's
my turn all right now you must face my
attack poison
sting oh it wasn't very effective
what why why
not I don't know um I mean it's like a
ghost went right through
it uh I I I forgot it's it's Chandelure
like six of them right yeah all six like
and all they know is fire
fire oh wait you can't are you're you're
fire uh oh wait I think of
able oh no the poison stings will
eventually win looks like I win now I'll
get all my money back nice man now I
can't be pomu anymore I have to be
domu
a man you know what they say I never
choke cuz I'm like Gary
[Music]
Oak see I I I started to um think about
all of my new dop isms and I decided to
like start my own business where I'll
just get like a bunch of cookies and
I'll put a bunch of my little words
inside of these cookies so when people
open up these cookies they're going to
be like wow this is really unfortunate I
I wish I didn't have to know this
knowledge so I call it unfortunate
cookies unfortunate you know I I got one
of those before actually it was trying
to sell me
crypto what what somebody picked my idea
already yeah I'm sorry and they're using
it to and they're using it to sell
crypto yeah really sorry a man then that
is actually way more unfortunate okay so
if that's unfortunate then mine is kind
of like a mild what's what's like the
mild form between fortunate and
unfortunate it's like
in inconvenient inconvenient
inconvenient yeah yeah just like just
like today I've been very inconvenient
with my with my um uh echoing um but the
thing is is I found out that it's
because I wasn't using my correct dopo
skin on the totachi Colin I was using
this one that had like a little glass
and it turned out that when I spoke into
the glass it just echoed but now I'm
just my normal self and now I'm not
really echoing or anything like that
anymore I've unequipped my special
ability wait I didn't even know you
could do you can change like features
like that with
[Music]
Fuki no I made it up
oh no I I made it up actually so
congratulations you have just un
unknowingly opened up an inconvenient
cookie I got told congratulations got
Bamboozled I got damn doled damn doled
you know I you know pom a lot of the
times when I'm thinking about like all
of my favorite like nii Sanji uh Ian
memories ever since I debuted um nice to
your word debut write that down write
that down yeah yeah yeah hold on hold
hold on hold on I I need to write in my
book hold on uh wait
debut
actually starts with the letter
D even though it's probably like a
French word probably what's wrong with
that cool uh no because uh nothing
nothing nothing nothing it's just that
uh one time one time I was like talk I
was like um thinking about like the
classes to pick for like um credits and
stuff and uh one of them was like French
and I was like oo nice French nice I
might be able to learn something about
France and then I saw like the words and
I was like wo ah none of these nice yeah
this is this is this is well no there
was some words that starts with d in
France I think yeah let's see French
dwords I can't think of anything off the
top my off the top of my head yeah ooh
let's see it says um Dairy
air oh oh Dairy air oh that's that's way
better than the one I found what is you
f uh diabet
diabete
which is which is pretty awful um maybe
I should maybe it's maybe it's like an
inconvenient French cookie that's
telling me that I need to check my sugar
this is really inconvenient actually
yeah you can use that wait do you know
19 in French no like are you talking
about the Android from Dragon Ball nice
Ste word hold
on Dragon starts with d um sorry go on
in
French yeah yeah yeah but not not like
the Android right the the actual yeah
the actual letter number it starts with
the letter
D
oh d
d so close oh my god really Dam one try
one more time one more time
uh
[Music]
no it's dick noof
what's that that's 19 in
French oh why why would they do that
that's kind of that's kind of uh not d
word it's a d
word yeah
but they don't sound like words they
sound like sounds just put together
that's so rude to the French no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no don't
don't cancel me on the P wait is this is
this going to be saved she says you're
streaming are you actually streaming
yeah I am yeah yeah
oh hi hi French view I'm not in Hangouts
I'm in collab VC oh okay well I mean but
but are are are are there any french
pomis May probably oh okay well I'm
sorry to all the French pomis out there
I'm sorry that I didn't know 19 in in
French and I'm sorry that it's really
confusing Maybe
maybe I should have taken French in in
um in school and then I would have
understood what what was it called Dick
snuff yeah dick
snuff it's it's it's not like a D's it's
not like a d joke is it no I'm telling
you the real truth yeah
[Music]
oh is is you know a long time ago I took
like a Spanish class and one of the
teachers was like oh we're like the the
um the Council of the Council of
Spanish decided to change one of the
letters so that it's now an a consonant
instead of a vowel or something like
that maybe they should do the same thing
with dick snuff they should like yeah
they should get like a council a council
of all the French speakers in the world
and they can like put it to a vote maybe
they can change it to like d cuz I think
D is a little bit more I think D is a
little bit more like like um television
friendly I think so too yeah it's yeah I
think more recognizable like you know
it's better branding probably for the
number 19 I think we should maybe uh
propose that to the French
Council yeah I mean like I think the
worst part about it is that imagine if
like you were like an evil scientist and
you were like creating like evil
Androids to like take over the world
right so you have like Android 17 cool
guy Android 18 well oh we're going to
give we're we're going to make this
character like top 10 famous female
anime characters of all time and then we
have Android dick nuff and not not
really oh sorry I think it's actually
dick
narf that's that's even worse now it
sounds like a Garfield
character that's wow wow oo everyone in
chat was saying that I was pronouncing
it wrong so it's I think I I remembered
it's dick narf
sorry what
it's it's it's like a combination of
Like A Garfield character and a Pokemon
at the same time oh oh oh wait oh yeah
what's the typing of Dick snarf oh um I
don't know French
oh oh oh get Bond Bond help us how to
how please here I actually I think it's
this hold
[Music]
on wait is that how you write it yeah
that's why would they do
that okay well um well while we get
while we get uh Zally on the scene to
explain why this is how it is pomu I was
thinking about like all the stuff about
like like how to say goodbye forever to
you cuz like it's it's awful right it's
like what are the final words you're
supposed to say to somebody when you
know that you'll never ever ever see
them again oh my God what what do you
mean we might see each other again we
you're going to be really embarrassed if
you say something really final and then
we meet up again well yeah but also when
was the last time Ash saw Charizard or
Ash saw cater or I mean Ash saw
Butterfree he let Butterfree go yeah he
left Butterfree go and it was it was it
was the saddest thing pom you're that
Butterfree I'm the Butterfree is it
because I'm a fairy that's kind of
offensive I'm not a
bug are you sure you're like bug sized
right that's why I always thought that
bug fables would always been like your
kind of game in in your music video you
were even like fighting a
slime like that's kind of bug fables
esque you kind of lost against the Slime
though yeah the Slime took like 70% of
your HP oh sorry PP kind of embarrassing
I did hey hey hey I it was um I was in
an area that I shouldn't have gone into
yet and um
I also did my special move and I won
it's fun yeah but you still lost like
70% of your HP and you were in the
middle of a force and what if you f f
another
slime it wouldn't it wouldn't go
too probably it probably eat me eaten by
slime that's so embarrassing that that
would really be hakashi eaten by slime
here lies pom rain puff digested by
slime oh my God and then the Slime would
be walking around and you'd be able to
see me in there and people would point
and laugh and be like haha then she got
eaten by a slime yeah who does that
that's like I I can't even think of a
single person out there who's ever been
beaten by a slime I know I actually I
know what you know somebody who's beaten
by a slime oh I
mean in a different game oh in a
different game oh okay okay gotcha
gotcha gotcha different kind of game
yeah okay so I'm I'm going over the
script that I wrote before so it says
pom I don't know how to say this but
I'm going to miss you I think I think
that's basically it like I was trying to
think of all these like really fancy
words and all these fancy paragraphs of
things to say but I like yeah yeah it
was too much writing too many words and
I'm like yeah P I'm just going to miss
pomu it's going to it's going to suck
without you pomu I don't know how we're
going to handle it what you'll be
fine really why how can you be so sure
because I know huh yeah you do do you
have telepathic abilities um I have
futuristic abilities actually well I
mean nocx came from the future and they
were still around so technically I you
know it'd be a time Paradox if you guys
weren't fine oh oh wait that's actually
pretty
comforting yeah yeah that is pretty
comforting I like sunny I like fuan I
like Alvin I like ukie they're all cool
people and they're from the future a m
MH oh that's a little bit of comfort um
but speaking of comfort you know um when
when I started out and debuted oh [\h__\h]
that's a nice d word you already wrote
that down you're right I did write that
down oh wow this is getting kind of
embarrassing yeah for you yeah sorry
okay
um uh well maybe embarrassing for me but
like not as much as embarrassing as U
saying that diig snarf is the number for
19 um so yeah a lot of my memories
favorite memories from nii Sanji um you
know a lot of them had you and them like
my first ever collab in VR was with
Among Us you were there oh my God wait
was that the first time we collabed yeah
that was the first first first ever I
think it was actually one of my first
ever collabs too it was insane and and
then and then and then enko and dice I
was really nervous and then enko Dice
and now it's like my thing you know I
never even had the whole d stand for
whatever before nko di I just came from
that yeah yeah yeah yeah I I had no
other personality nko dice happened and
now and now I have a personality tra and
people aren't sick of it yet it's insane
no way I thought that always was a thing
no no no no no no no no that actually
was the first first time ever like I was
thinking wowow what am I going to do
like I I I I didn't think of like
anything prepared I didn't have anything
prepared when I went up against um like
ey or scarl or anything and I was like
oh man I want to make an impression how
do I make an impression and then I
looked at like
ooh what can what what can what can dop
you stand for and I was like damn that's
a lot of letters in DOP you I'm just
going to I'm just going to like take the
d yeah simplifying the D and then I
Googled dword and I was like oh my God
this is it so powerful it never ended oh
my God no that's the best way to do
stuff is like in promptu because
sometimes like things will just come to
you like in the moment and it ends up
being like frog bir you know frog bir oh
frog bird was just something that came
out of nowhere yeah oh
oh and he's like so beloved
M yeah he gave me some really good
advice about eating dirt oh I remember
that yeah I was I saw him say that yeah
yeah I I'm not really sure if he's um
you know licensed or whatever but he
told me to eat dirt um but speaking of
dirt like you know I guess what's kind
of cool about like Words is that um you
can find different words from different
languages like I didn't know about Dick
snarf until today so now I can so now if
I ever run out of dwords in the English
dictionary I could always go to the
French dictionary and be like wow I
wonder what kind of words the French
dictionary has in store they must be
really really really when you run out of
yeah when you run out of dwords in the
English Al uh dictionary you just go to
the French dictionary and then you know
continue
on um right right right right right I
was going to say dopo you're a master at
improv so never you know don't stop
being uh so uh what what's a d
word uh dick narf yeah don't stop being
dick narf okay yeah yeah I yeah I'll
take I'll take that to my grave okay I'm
going to write that on your grave this
guy was Dick's
[Laughter]
narf no not my secret identity no
imagine you dox me like oh doy beyond
the
grave thanks for dropping by doia I'm
getting kicked out yeah sorry that's
okay that's okay thank you so much pom
your laughs and everything gave me so
much confidence and so many amazing
memories and I'll keep them Forward
Forever cuz you know they're really
important to me so I'm going to miss you
pomu byebye thanks doio bye-bye
bye-bye yay that was doio I actually got
to go to the bathroom real quick I'm
sorry there's a lot of people waiting V
you can come in if you want you can talk
talk to everybody um I'll be right back
we can talk about mgs4 oh my gosh I'll
be I'll be right back um uh hold on I'm
going to put on my thing one second I'm
going to put
um my my little picture that says I'm
going to the
bathroom where's my bathroom picture oh
here looks like it's wearing sunglasses
okay I'll be right
back I'll be right
[Music]
back
no hello pom
cheese what's up it's your girl VI today
we're going to be spilling my spaghetti
thank God she's going to go to the
washroom what the heck what am I uh you
guys got any jokes do I have a joke
um um let me think let me think I have
no jokes uh um why was the car car
tired um anyone
anyone uh knock knock yeah yeah why uh
because it was
exhausted what who who who T that who T
stupid punch line before I got
[Music]
there all right you guys are pretty good
you guys are all pretending to laugh
that was not a funny joke but I
appreciate it please don't throw a
tomato at me I I I didn't come in here
trying to oh um yeah anyways you guys
having fun you guys are
[Music]
uh freaking out about the Aki
burst music video it's so
good I don't know if I can tell the
story but um I I definitely uh
snuck to Akiba to to see the
Akers
ad
um that might I have been uh uh yeah
yeah but you know what no no regrets no
regrets I I pretty much point at the
sign
and and I had to take a selfie with
it uh I I wanted to go and look at all
the you know books May cafes and all the
anime among
manga and make way too much eye contact
with the maids that are out in the
streets they don't want to look at
me they didn't look at
me they they had no interest in me but I
I was interested in
[Laughter]
them they're so
cute they're clothes their outfits are
so pretty I'm like oh my god um but you
know no no didn't have any a flyer they
were like uh H she doesn't seem
interested but no it's me I'm interested
I'm very
interested I'm like you know they would
have gotone me to I I would have opened
up my wallet free you'll be like here's
my credit
card and all my cash oh you can probably
sell my coat for money
too um yeah you know I was willing to
sell like my armor my
helmet I I was very like uh what is it
enamored
why is she going to the washroom for so
long why am I supposed
to
intermission
intermission yeah I would have simed
hard that uburst is a very very scary
place it's a very scary place for your
wallet you I barely made it out of there
alive cuz you know there's different
like themed made
cafes I got to call a Kodak I got to
call
where's mein where's our where's our
little proverb where's our like you know
where's our relationship
drama we just got to listen
in like hello
please all right we got to talk about
movies right no I don't care I'm going
to talk about all the cool make cafes
that I saw there's different
themes I saw like h
what is it I saw like a like a gun
made and I forgot what the style is
called but they have like the
Jersey um and it's kind of like casual
but cool they've got like the the
replicas yeah the gun Maids like with
like they have like assault like assault
rifle
replicas and stuff cuz I'm sure those
things probably weigh like 100
lb now it's suck to carry around well
you s food but there's like there's like
battle maides and like gun
Maes and all these different themes and
I was like oh my
God
I I do make money my
money hello please why are you doing
this to
me oh I I I actually wasn't able to go
and check it out but I saw the
advertisements and I was just way too
excited I was like oh my
gosh what do they do there do they like
point the
gun but like like do they teach me how
to clean a gun or like to like reload or
something I don't know there was so many
I had so many
questions you know but I was like if you
threaten me that's
okay please tell me she's back I I'm I
see you move you're just m
how dare
you hello
[Music]
BBY they this is this the worst codak
call that they had to experience what do
you what do you
[Music]
mean sorry I was feeding my cat a a okay
no that's okay that's okay I oh that's
even
cuter no you were up late at night I
know
he oopsie no I was watching you
play and then you watching me and then
you got the the end of act three and I
was like oh I can go to sleep and then
you were like I'm going to keep playing
and I was like but this is the best
part look I I I eventually went to sleep
I don't I don't know where you ended off
on actually I okay uh do I talk about
where it ended off at uh I basically
ended off um
getting don't don't listen ru support
box that's okay that's okay no I I wait
no it's not is it a spoiler Shadow Moses
it's a spoiler yeah okay okay sorry no I
got my emotional support box yippe
yeah I'm yeah oh my gosh I just I just
wanted to say thank you I remember uh
watching you play a little bit of metag
gear and I was like oh I I I always
thought those games were like super hard
MH you know I'm like I don't I don't
know if they're meant for me but see you
enjoy them so much I'm like oh maybe I
can check them out maybe I'll have fun
with them too so yeah thank you for
introducing me to the series oh my gosh
let's
go let's go oh my gosh wait so you
actually played because of
me um I started it it's been a while
since I had to uh you know find a PS3
and everything like that and and also
like start and and find a copy of middle
Gear Solid
yeah but yeah Big inspiration I was like
she's having so much fun with it this
looks like it's so fun maybe it's not as
like scary because no I I typically I'm
like I am so bad at stealth you know oh
I know me too I hate stealth don't worry
oh my gosh how are you liking four so
far I wait emotional damage I don't
know I'm going to tell you it doesn't
stop I'm so scared there's so much like
it only gets it only gets worse from
here no no cuz I cuz I see all I I see
all the Death flags and I'm like uh uh
just kidding right right R koima please
please it's just it's just a little
funny little joke right it's just a
simulation the the ending is really good
though it's really good you'll like it
so much you and like it's not an ending
either that will make you feel bad you
know like an when you end three you just
feel so empty and terrible and awful so
but the ending of four is like so it's
good it's it makes you feel good okay I
that that that's a really big promise
there because I I I think I still have
like half the game to go through you
still have what I still have so much of
the game to go through for Metal Gear
cell for I'm sorry I couldn't finish it
no what do you mean what are you talking
about oh my gosh you and raino said the
same thing it's okay it's okay we made
it through a oh well I I we could talk
about one two and three and and there's
still L and reu yeah oh my gosh no I I
I'm at the point where like because
everyone's been playing
now I can talk to people about like up
to three so I'm like bottling over with
emotions from 4 so I'm just like I want
to throw up all over you right now and
but I can't because you're not done but
that's okay we'll talk later we can you
finish it I'll just
will give me that I mean no do I want
the vomit um word vomit I'll give you
all the
bi frog
B why why frog
ver I I feel like human B seems fairy
human B seems kind of um dangerous you
know oh maybe it's like it's kind of
it's like more magical than anything
it'll be okay you know like in some
anime when they throw up it's like
rainbows it's kind of like that okay
okay okay safe you might even be able to
bottle it up and sell it like people
think it's kind of
nice oh my God thank you you're you're
like helping me you know go through
through retirement I'm just going to
sell bottles of a fairy pile yeah that's
my new business it's a new business
everybody see it's the fairy economy the
fairy
economy unlimited yeah so um you know
I'm not going to help you with that
Venture you can you know get your own um
fairies for that but
like okay okay so cool cool that's cool
no I I I knew I knew no no of course not
of course I mean mine is like kind of
exclusive
so I I'll just keep it I'll keep it with
my appendix okay right next to it right
next to in a cute little jar append oh
your appendix is in a
jar yeah W yeah it
exploded way back when I was like eight
and you got to keep it
yeah what we kept it for a while but
then we moved and then got chucked oh
I'm so sad it was part of my
body they threw away your appendix wait
so there's like an appendix literally in
the wild right now like in a jar it
could be anywhere um yeah yeah maybe you
can clone me with it you know it's all
part of the the nii purse oh my gosh
wait you can oh my God wait we could put
your appendix in the little plastic
sheet just like big
boss oh
no
just call me
big and fill it with Nano machines yeah
yeah yeah yeah so it keeps it
alive okay okay fair enough that's cool
yeah wow nice L on font
VV oh no oh
[Laughter]
no that's a scary fate I don't know
about that just I know set it on fire
it's okay I'm okay with that ooh
barbecue ooh with like what
bile marinade M oh it's like
spicy is that how it is you can't get me
to talk about weird ass Foods lately
because I've been on a dungeon mishy
binge and I'm I'm like obsessed with
thinking about it oh wait like watching
or reading like watching it it's so good
you should check it out I
will I've been i' I've been wanting to
now I have so much time I'll be able to
watch so much anime we can we can watch
all the animes yeah yippe yay uh but I
guess mostly I just wanted to say thank
you
Palo no thank you it's been so much fun
haven't we've haven't been a we got to
meet a little bit um for during ni Fest
so I'm really happy about that I'm
really happy about like what we talked
about and everything and um super yeah
yeah yeah I'm I don't know I'm really
thankful that you were so kind and
considerate towards me even though we
only had like a short little meet and
I'm like what the heck you didn't have
to be so kind to me what did I do I
didn't do anything you're so
nice you gave me a fry oh I give give
you my
fry all the fries no you you understand
because you're also you know we got we
got that same lifestyle you know
we you you you we are you you are my
Kindred we are the ois son at heart
thank you for being an O son
otaku if you ever want to hang out again
and stuff
100% you still have to take me to a maid
Cafe I
know I want to go so bad okay next
time I feel like you got to teach me all
like the rules and the matters and all
that kind of stuff and your what it's
fine you just go have fun times no
worries you just kind of look at the
girl you go look at girls yeah I want to
look at the girl I want to spill my
spaghetti and all I can say is like
thank you so much in English and they'll
look at me going like
huh yeah no they'll think it's cute
they'll be like oh so cute and I'll be
like no you're cute yeah we're
just constantly just giggling and you're
cute you're cute you're
cute yeah will be more ogan than anyone
else in that Cafe yeah they would be
scared of us kind of
energy we'll be put on a watch list
don't let them back
[Laughter]
in want to watch L and just be like
please no no no not them again not them
again they see us like they hear us
coming up the stairs there's like an
aura that's just like takes over the
cafe and like it's just this dark Aura
and you just
hear I can see
that they're like no shut shut shut the
blinds we're closed we're closed sorry
she's not going to well to she's not
in you didn't announce it on Twitter
we're like jiggling the handle of the
door like let us
in got I've got my backpack full of
books and just shopping
[Laughter]
[Music]
bags yeah we definitely have to go
though not maybe be a little bit like
that we could be like a fraction like
that uh I'll I'll try to calm myself
I'll try to wear like um normal
clothes whatever that may
be normal clothes yeah we'll fit in
we'll F in brush my hair we'll be like
oh you're going to brush your hair okay
I'll also brush my hair yeah yeah I know
I know well I'll use deodorant and
shower the night before Oh my gosh I
don't know if I'm I'm into that much of
a commitment to shower but I'll you
know we got to do it for or or dust and
stuff and like perfume you know I think
both works you know just like a mix I
think they prefer a natural musk you
know kind
of oh yeah so that they'll remember us
our pheromones yeah the pheromones like
it'll be like projecting like it'll be
really attractive I think that's how
they'll know that we're coming just like
up like the first floor they'll be like
oh they're there they're here mhm
everyone will evacuate because they know
we're so important not cuz of our smell
oh yeah we are yeah our VIP smell yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah you guys we were so normal together
when we were we are no no no we were we
were I think we are still normal I think
everyone else would believe that we are
yeah yeah we we we shopped for normal
clothes M actually we went to that one
we went to that one store we were like
this is so cute oh my gosh and then we
like turned around it was like a ballet
store oh
yeah we were like oh oops oh yeah
they're like oh okay well I mean there
there was some other normal stores like
the ones where all they sold was like
boy like emo band T-shirts and oh yeah
was it cargo pants you guys I was trying
to find them and I got lost in a floor
that only sold linger I didn't want to
leave I was in heaven I was like maybe I
should ditch these guys this is like oh
my God
that was yeah yeah and I
was like what I don't see this I was
like there's only lingerie here guys
where are
you but um yeah it was fun yeah it was I
had a lot of fun thank you for showing
me around yeah we got a little bit lost
sometimes but it was fun it was okay we
we still found a lot of cool stuff MH
and saw a lot of cool things I'm sorry
for the mossberger
no no I look the only reason why I could
have backed you up on saying like that
was like the best was because I had it
like a long long time ago and I was like
oh my God I remember I've I hate that
it's not available in like North America
I
know I tried to get them I tried to get
them to try the the teraki rice bum
Burger but we went to two Moss burgers
and both of them sold out because it's
that delicious everyone wanted it
they were sold out there was stores like
hundred there's like hundreds of people
there and I was like how is so popular
it was so busy it was crazy yeah yeah no
love for freshness Burger I've only been
to freshness Burger once oh wait what's
freshness Burger it's a it's like just
another burger place but I've only gone
once before I don't know what what are
they known for the freshness
Burger I feel like the rice from the
rice burger from from Moss is is
definitely like the it's so good so
addictive it's so good it is yum yum I
put it I'm thinking about it literally
right now exactly I'm like that would be
nice to have have that yeah your hair is
white like
rice oh is are are you trying to say
that that's why I like rice or I mean
I'm just saying like you know if I ate
it would it taste like rice you know um
you could try you know uh I I feel like
every girl kind of goes through like an
eating hair phase
right oh oh my okay thank you I E this
part it's like a it's like a bun right
here oh it is a bun it's a literal
bun oh my God
help how is it taste is it rice like
how's it taste yeah it's rice like for
real okay well I don't know about that
but
okay
thank you viie um I hope we can hang out
more me too thank you pomu you are so
inspirational you're so creative I feel
like I don't know I this is mostly like
the first time I ever got to talk to
you uh like on stream yeah oneon-one on
stream yeah oneon-one yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah you have so many cool creative
streams I love all like the Valentine's
Day
the court the showers and everything
like that I'm like she's so smart how do
she how dides she come up with these the
drive you know I don't know I'm like
it's like I got like a Brain Blast
moment I'm like this is so Galaxy
brain I I'm like in so so
inspired thank
you I give all my creativity to
you uhoh go
forward uh-oh
uh that's a that's a tall
order nah just have fun with it you know
I just have fun streaming and you
know yeah yeah you always burning up my
days with your streams and your laughter
and all the banter all the fun that you
have with the pachis I'm like
dang I thought I was having a bad day
but no this is a pretty good one no what
the heck no
it's such a good atmosphere
here we just have fun we're just silly
we're silly Bunch you know and um I just
want to say thanks for singing all like
uh the Emo
songs and the anime
songs yeah the emo s like finally
someone that gets the Hot Topic child
inside me that got left behind hell
yeah
we'll go back to karaoke we'll sing
we'll sing all the songs together yeah
yeah yeah yeah we got we got start like
our Myspace band and I know play the
triangle oh okay nice good start I'll do
uh oh we can Workshop this what else do
they Kazo I have kazoo all right all
right all right okay okay I have a
tomatone too so yeah we could oh my gosh
this is shaping really well okay nice
nice nice nice what a good do it
yeah we're Twan
band triangle a oh I have uh my omnic
cord okay this is I don't know I think
um it probably could be like a new age
emo band you know because we don't
really have guitars or drums or anything
that normal bands have we have like
everything oh that's true yeah we're New
Age we're cooler exactly they they're
not ready for it yet you know we're
still
cooking yeah exactly but thank you so
much P thank you thank you thank you B I
know you only been here for a little bit
I'm sorry we couldn't talk more but I
hope that you have a really fun time in
nii Sanji and I hope you um you know
continue doing what you're doing you're
doing you're doing so well you're
killing it yeah and thank you so much
for playing like we feel company with me
m yeah yeah yeah and on the clubs and
everything like that I really appreciate
it everyone has yeah yeah warm welcomes
from everyone so yeah thank you will you
be able to join tomorrow
or yes yes yeah I wrote it down my
calendar no no I I put it on a sticky
note in front of my monitor
cuz I'm young at heart and I like to
write things down cuz that's what young
people do I put on oh my gosh I'm too
and I also do that yeah oh my gosh it is
what a young person does yes it is it is
yeah that's that's how I get my
reminders you know exactly exactly like
what's the phone I don't
know landline I have to use the internet
okay I don't have a
phone so
true yeah we're we're hello fellow young
people
yeah I got to you know you feed your cat
I feed my neop pet you know it's like
the same thing mhm mhm I got hacked in
theet so oh no I got hacked on Gaia no
way I want to try and log back into my
guia
account oh my God I'm going to try that
you're a promy maybe that's my New
Year's resolution is to get back into my
guy online account I uh no I had a Kiki
Kitty I had I had um I had the winged
anklets I think I'm pretty sure I had a
a
Halo what you you're what you're oh my
God you would be like a a gajillionaire
and Guy aren't you I know I I well I
don't know how much money I have now
probably not a lot not in this
economy you're a what the heck you're a
pomy a
what promy I think that's what they
called them right like the really cool
kids on GAA what they had a name yeah I
don't know I only role played in one
place ooh I see I I I think my the
account that I got hacked in was was uh
was my role I I think I tried to role
play oh
no but I gave myself a really stupid
name so yeah I'm honestly I'm glad that
it got hacked that it saved me a lot oh
my gosh I just had like a oh my God I
just had like a flashback I used to okay
so there was this one item that would
turn you into it like it would take over
your entire like Avatar box you know
like where you display everything oh and
it would make it a giant ugly frog I
just remember going around in like the
Gaia towns with that frog and I would
role play as the Frog oh my god I've
been doing this
[Laughter]
forever oh my God you were the Frog all
right no I huh you know what that kind
of adds something
I can't believe it I just remembered
that no way oh my God the
origins I was trying to put on a robe
and wizard hat and I still fa to do
it she puts on her robe and wizard hat
everybody don't mess
with that is an actual okay you that is
like an actual Boomer meme like that
is
what is that of you that gets
it you know hey hey hey hey I'm just as
you're just as guilty as I am right now
no no no
no oh my gosh thank you viie I'll talk
to you later we'll we'll hang out again
and everything yeah definitely Pinky
Promise yeah pinky promise we have to
talk about mgs4 once you're done yes and
I'll well I I'll we got to Wrangle
everyone else for Peace Walker yes yes
yes you guys will love it it's so
awesome yes we will the final fight is
so awesome oh my gosh I'm excited yeah
all the boss fights are so good anyways
wait I'm getting off
topy yeah yeah thank you thank you
byebye byebye
oh my gosh I can't believe I just had
that memory that's so
crazy of the Frog and Guy online
Wow Let's see I'm going to tag the next
person everyone starting to make like
a a lineup now so I don't want to go
take too long especially
oh V hi
hey uh I I think I should change my
uh I needed that ice breaker oh okay
that was a pretty good one maybe do you
are I think you're obsessed with this
image actually I think I might be
because there's this and then there was
Millie's
TSU I think I think you need you have a
problem
maybe God I I I I might as well just
cover um uh oh [\h__\h] got I got to cover
it now it's so de yeah why didn't you do
you crisis should have done that song At
the Hop concert instead I I couldn't
convince them they were like go is the
way and I was like you know what I won't
fight you guys on it okay but your go
you guys' go was so
awesome thank you it was a lot of fun I
I really liked it so I'm glad glad you
liked it too yeah so fun I was like I
was going
bang oh yeah my raft oh my
God yeah I was literally like everybody
was like oh my gosh you did such a good
job singing and I was like I mean yeah I
sang I I guess you could consider that
okay we're staying as kaneki so I can't
change it I don't know what's wrong all
right sorry I guess this is the mood
that I'm going to be in please don't
think that I'm depressed or sad I mean I
am kind of sad I mean sort of but but
you know I'm why are you sad are you
okay do you to talk about it no no I'm
I'm I'm okay I I'm just I'm just sad
that you're leaving I feel like I feel
like I didn't get to talk to you as much
as I wanted to and
I was just thinking about this I feel
like the the most the most I talked to
you was actually in person in Japan I
know that's what I'm saying like I feel
like with some people I've mostly talked
with them like in person it's kind of
crazy yeah I I was just thinking about
that I was just like wow huh it's it's
it's unfortunate I wanted to I wanted to
talk more but it's it is it is life you
know it happens and honestly I I I do
treasure the time that we spend in Japan
so I I don't so F I'm not totally mad
yes I I I want to go back so badly I
want to go back to can I yeah we went to
uba a little bit I got to take vanta to
the um what was it the Square Enix
Cafe yeah yeah and then I and then I oh
my God I I I I bit the I bit this it
wasn't styrofoam
but consider it tastes like Styrofoam we
okay so like we got like these specialty
drinks and um
who else was with us um um I think it
was Ren
and was it Sally yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yes renan's alley oh
my God and um and uh the monaka like I
told the story like how I went to the
Ace Attorney Cafe and it was not like a
little wafer cookie it was actual
styrofoam and I bit into I was like holy
[\h__\h] I'm eating styrofoam right now but
so I was like I was like hey guys be
careful like it might be styrofoam and
like r fit into it thought it was
thought it was got it
styrofoam that sh it tastes like
Styrofoam I it was like you're supposed
to dip it in the drink I know that now
but boy oh boy do not eat the the the
Square Enix Cafe Dragon Quest themed
drink chips by themselves or do I mean
if you want something if you want like a
kind of semi styrofoam
experience yeah like you know maybe
styrofoam is good to you you know like
I'm I'm not judging but if you're not
into styrofoam then I I wouldn't
recommend
it if you if you see monaka on the menu
it's the little Waf for cookies it's not
Styrofoam you
guys I need to know for the future I got
to pay attention now I don't know what
they could be serving me in Japan
anymore that's true I got to be on the
lookout I think it's like those um those
Japanese like a variety shows it's like
is it cake is it
styrofoam oh my gosh
oh my God that sounds like so much fun
oh I'm G to I want to do something like
that now that's a great idea oh my gosh
is it styrofoam oh wait wait wait I
thought you meant the is a cake oh god
oh you know is a is a cake probably
makes more
[Laughter]
sense yeah yeah gosh I'm always going to
think of mossberger now because of you
hell yeah or I'm always going to think
of you when I have
mossberger the off the many many times
you have
mossberger yeah I I definitely want to
go back that place was freaking great
hell yeah see a Believer everybody a
Believer truly don't don't talk down on
mossberger no mossberger slander here
that place is god
tier yeah it was fun I'm glad even
though it was just for a little bit
because of niif Fest and I think we only
got to hang out that one day honestly
but pretty much yeah it was fun to yeah
hang out yeah I mean you know there was
still like the the karaoke and uh
everything else so that was crazy oh my
god when when when mine was was going
crazy and you were going crazy I I your
chance were I was just like wow this is
this is
great yeah was funny this is what they
mean by big pomu energy I was like I get
it now I get it I
understand I just like to scream and
shout I mean that's respectable I think
I think that's what you should do
especially when especially when you're
supporting your friends you know m
so I think we should Scream and Shout uh
for you in support of this decision that
you're making people don't know who you
are hold on I'm going to there's the
name right there sorry it was kind of
small you guys don't be fooled by the by
the profile
picture no I'm I'm act I'm actually
kanaki
guys oh get out of my
[Music]
stream leave wait I can make the name
bigger let's make it wait you can yeah
40 pixels instead let's go oh oh that
worked that worked actually nice oh my
God okay P they're just like who is this
guy on your stream pom like who's this
guy is he he he in like some some
stranger did you leave
again yeah who the hell is
this there we go that worked nice but uh
really I just I just want to say uh cuz
h I don't again I don't want to take up
your time uh too much of your time
but just thank you for you know your
your presence in and nii I I I really
think uh I don't I don't want to take
this as like a it feels weird to say
passing on the torch almost like you're
dying you're not going anywhere Senpai
is Senpai is furthering her
education so I don't want to say it like
that but you know the the the energy you
left behind is is really going to affect
everyone I think I I am I I've certainly
got a fire lit under me so I I really
hope you know who you've touched even
though even though we like I said we we
haven't interacted much but I you've
affected me a lot I hope you know that
and I really appreciate you wow thanks I
know I've been a pretty bad Senpai like
especially for like you know crisis and
um Triple T you know like I haven't had
so much chances to talk with you guys so
um it's busy yeah but you know um I see
I see your fans and there you guys are
making like good your own good great
communities you know like everybody is
very passionate like about uh you know
their ooshi and yeah you guys are
killing it so um you know thanks for
joining and enjoy enjoy your streaming
life you know it's so fun of course this
is great I mean we we only have our
communities because of the foundation
that you set um but before I before I do
go I know this I'm probably the shortest
person on but um I I do I do have
something for you I was actually
supposed to draw this uh tonight uh but
I my my my ability to read schedules and
understand time zones is awful so uh I
was like oh wait her TSU is today and
not tomorrow so oh no wait you can still
stream oh no no no no no I mean I'll
just I'll just I'll just draw like your
other outfit or something okay all right
if you want you don't have to I I will
will I will okay here you go I I I
dropped it I dropped it in your
[Laughter]
DMs oh I like scuff pomu
PNG thank thank you I I I worked I
worked really hard on it so like yours
was another case I I feel like I'm just
getting better at this drawing thing
yours was too good at first I had I had
to change it up in order for it to be
properly scuffed yeah it did not look
like this at first I had to like take
away some details I really like tone it
down for you oh it's huge oh my
god oh is it oh God is it no no it's
okay I'll put it here right
there there you go it's all like weirdly
cropped aw it's right behind me like
it's oh my God actually this is a little
terrifying it's just going to murder
me maybe I should have like changed the
eyes or something to make it a bit cuter
but it's so it's okay no yeah it's
perfect it's perfect just the way very
nice thank you thank you uh thank so
much vanta for this lovely birthday
present I I I do what I can and I and
what I do but thank you so much P me
some by thank
you see you later oh are you going to be
playing games tomorrow or I definitely
will I I my day is free it's clear
tomorrow I'll see you tomorrow then all
right Osa bye-bye
byebye yay oh my gosh I got an art what
is this it's it's it's just I feel like
he draws better than I do what the hell
where's the scuff part looks so good
actually
a when I was doing the meet and greets
my handler was like making fun of my the
way I talk she would be
like she like when people were leaving
she would be like Pomo says bo boy and
was like I don't sound like
[Laughter]
that I don't what do you mean she's like
yes you do you sound like that Buu I was
like
[Music]
what oh my gosh you guys will never
guess who's
[Music]
next uhoh I have to brace myself though
I think I'll be
okay hi sister God
hi hi sisters hi sisters
oh I can hello hi P
aror I'm not ready for this me
[Music]
neither why was vanta so short like
everyone else before him was like so
much longer and I was like oh okay I got
I got time to like emotionally prepare
for this but then vant was like you know
he was just so fast and I was like wait
hold up why do I have to be right after
him it was getting so fast and or like
so long before V I was like oh okay this
is pretty good pacing for me to
emotionally prepare but then vantis was
like okay well that I I don't want to
take anyone's time and I was like no
wait no it's okay we're just we're just
chitchatting we're just hanging out yeah
yeah as we always do mm
m and we have your music video was so
Good by the way thank you oh my gosh and
you had your cover come out too I know
everybody's releasing stuff everyone I
know all of Lite actually all release
something oh my God you're right yeah in
the past couple of weeks we're so insane
or week I
know it's crazy yeah let's
go yeah we still have lunch lady
tomorrow tomorrow too oh yeah that's
right I'm not going to lie I thought I
was going to save all the sappy stuff
for tomorrow but maybe this is the one
where I
do if you want to save it for tomorrow
that's okay too it's up to you are you
sure well no I I think I can I should
probably get it over with today okay all
right I'm already on the verge of tear
so wait
really you
[Music]
are it's okay it's okay I'm I'm good I'm
good I'm good wait actually no I'm okay
I'm
okay you can go here I'm going to put on
my sunglasses so you can't see
anything this is when I'm
[Laughter]
crying I'm already
crying oh God I don't even know how to
start
this I thought I was going to be all
happy and the first half but God damn it
oh we can we can keep talking about
other stuff whatever uh if you want to I
don't know um um um how's Final Fantasy
going oh it's it's been fun um
everyone's hopping on it and it's uh I
actually started to uh get back into it
as well cuz uh I kind of like took a
long Hiatus from that game oh really I
think ever since we've debuted you've
been playing
it yeah I still continued uh well not
not religiously but yeah no I always
remember you would be like sorry I can't
do something at this time I'm doing a
raid oh yeah and like the first year I
was still doing that stuff but then I I
uh quit because um it was too hard to
maintain both schedules at the same time
yeah yeah mhm so so I I decided to quit
um even though it was something I really
enjoyed and all but no but now you can
play with everybody else you can stream
and play I know we've been getting on
really late at night like every day just
like playing XIV and stuff together I
saw you guys last night hanging out I
was like I know I was up until like 500
a.m. I know I saw you guys I was like oh
my gosh AA and finana are both in
Hangouts I should go hang out oh wait
they're probably playing
Final
Fantasy yeah we were up really late and
ay was like man I'm so tired but I don't
finish she that's exactly how she would
say it too
yeah it was funny cuz she said she got
off but then vanta joined the cult and
then she was like wait does this mean I
have to get back on now oh my God that
girl yeah that was really
funny n the Final Fantasy grind Never
Dies yeah I'm
[Music]
excited it's good
though yeah why is it so awkward I don't
know what to say I feel like if I say
anything
like I don't know
like what do I like I don't know like I
I don't want to like say the sappy stuff
you know but then I'm like what do I
talk about like I don't know that's me
too I'm like debating on it too but I'm
also like I feel like I should before
tomorrow cuz I think tomorrow I kind of
want to end it
[Music]
happy yeah me too me
too I I'm not going to lie I've been
crying for
days like starting from last week I have
just been crying a
lot just thinking about it cuz like even
though like I knew for a really long
time um I don't know it just kind of
hits different when it gets closer to
the date you
know
yeah it it like yeah for me I I don't
know like I think it was all of December
when I was just like dreading I was like
oh my God but yeah I felt I think I felt
worse before the announcement than after
I don't know like I still feel really
bad after the announcement I feel like
you know I see so many people that are
sad and I'm like no
no I don't know it's just
a it's a weird
feeling I
know
H sorry if I'm like if I sound so weird
all of a sudden no me too I sound awful
when I cry oh my God my voice gets so
terrible
no I'm not going to lie like during the
announcement uh stream that was when I I
I was crying in bed like all
morning like hearing you cry made me cry
so much harder and it was just so
much
yeah also
um I guess maybe I should get it out now
but I uh I I wrote a little something
because um I'm not really good at these
kinds of stuff when it's just like on
the fly so I pre-wrote some things just
so I could get most of it out obviously
I could say so much more than what I
have today
but this pretty much kind of sums it all
but there's so much more I could add to
it
so okay I'm I'm I'm prepar I'm prepping
myself all right I'm ready you ready yep
okay
okay um sorry if it sounds so scripted
but no oh did you chat GPT this
no I could never I don't even know how
to use
it that would be kind of funny though I
could do a chat GPT version of it I
don't know but this one was this comes
from the F our heart yeah this one comes
from the C
okay okay oh God if I break if I break
in the middle I'm so sorry
okay okay
um oh god
um okay
um homu you are one of my first few
friends that I made here alongside with
Aira and even though
I came in feeling very anxious and
inexperienced you showed me that
everything was going to be okay and you
gave me so much confidence to move past
my
fears
and it's going to be really tough or
really rough knowing that I won't be
able to stream with you or
continue any fun 3D
[Music]
projects
sorry we we any concerts
anymore and
um I'm going to do my best to continue
everything you've left us
behind you know like all of the chance
and all your joyful energy that a lot of
us can't naturally
do and I'm definitely going to miss you
a lot
and I'll always be think of thinking of
you every
[Music]
day I never thought that my own genate
and friend would graduate
but realizing now you were defin L my
Oshi during these times and I never
really understood the concept of Oshi
before M Sanji but you naturally just
became one for me when I needed
inspiration or
motivation and um I also just want to
say thank you for always being so
positive and for all of the hard work
you put in for
us I know that often times when we we
stream together we usually are really
playfully you know typically fighting
each other out of love but in all
serious outside all in all of
seriousness outside of
streaming I'm glad that I could have
someone I feel so comfortable with to be
able to have those special moments
without any discomfort with each other
afterwards I'm usually too nice or
polite towards other people that I'm not
really close with or familiar with but
you are one of the few people and and
that I consider to be a really close
friend where I can just be open and
comfortable with myself and I just
really appreciate you for that and I
hope that wherever you go you'll always
continue to smile
and I hope that we can still keep in
touch to you know
just check on each other or you know we
maybe we could hang out again or go on
another trip together just for
fun and
um I just really I'm I'm never going to
forget all of the memories we made
together you know
streaming you know like I'm on
observation t or Outlast those those
were really fun times that I had with
you and
even though I I don't stream Minecraft
as much but the only memories I've had
of Minecraft were actually mostly with
you I mostly just played it cuz I I also
really enjoyed playing Minecraft with
you um honestly I don't know if I if I
could have gotten into it without you
so
um yeah I'm I'm just now I'm improving
off of my pre-written message now but
but yeah I'm just it's really sad that
this is going to you know affect me a
lot but I'll do my best to continue to
be very strong
and I just want to say that even though
we have to continue La without you it
I'm always going to think that laite was
or is the three of us no matter
what yeah
well I'm going to I'm going to miss you
a
lot yeah I'll miss you guys I know we
collabed so much you were like my horror
game
buddy I know like the one person I think
of always is you I know and I'm so sad
when you were like do you want to play
Exit 8 together and I was like it's like
a 20 minute
game
oh yeah that's okay
though
yeah I yeah wait I don't know I I was
going to write something for for you and
ala I just felt like I don't know I
don't know how to put it into words it's
okay um but and we don't expect anything
or you know you don't have to no
pressure
anything yeah and then I was really
happy that we got to do that
New York trip together and
yeah my my first time traveling
independently yeah yeah I I've never
traveled alone before but having you
there made it feel easier to do cuz I
was still kind of anxious and nervous
about being alone but at the same time I
had you there you know just to spend it
with cuz I didn't really know anyone
else that liked honai or whatever
so yeah but it was still really fun and
I'm glad that it was you that
came we've done so like so much silly
stuff like you know I I can't even think
of like a favorite moment because
everything every collab is like always
so or just using out there's always like
there's always like one memorable moment
I know there's always something that is
just so crazy
I can already think of one right now
when you got so mad at me in Crab
G I still remember we still quote it we
I will I will mucking murder
you yeah I know people that's my nii
clip that I
think I think you know people probably
like might be like or sometime they
might be like oh I wonder if they like
you know get along but it's always like
you know we are always just being so
silly like the anger is never like
legitimate it's always just like us
being so silly
so yeah it was really funny I remembered
when yeah cuz like a lot of people were
like do they get a l
afterwards and me and pom are just
sitting here like oh my god did we
really affect them that
much did we really scare them that much
like la la
la
yeah I mean if that really was the case
would I have been like coming back you
know like
continuously but no worries guys it's
all it's always just a
bit it's usually always this and not
just us too it's up for everyone else
everyone has their own bits but we all
get along very well
mhm yeah no you are always like the
person that you know like we I it was
always like the most
like I don't know how to say it like the
most sibling kind of like but no you no
you I don't think I have this kind of
relationship but you know I kind of like
bicker and I mess around with other
people but no one else but like with you
it feels different like yeah it feels
different like I sometimes bully others
or I get bullied by others too and stuff
but it's not ever the same when it comes
to us I know we get so serious about it
even though like we're not serious but
we're like we get so serious about it
and then afterwards we realized how
stupid it sounded yeah exactly like how
pointless the conversation was and we
were just bickering for no reason and
then at that moment we're just like why
are we still talking about this
I know it's like a competition it is
yeah I think that's the thing we're both
very competitive and so we're just like
no this we won't and we're both stubborn
so we won't let it go
yeah you're the only person who who
literally makes me act like
that I know right I think you are also
the one that test for that me too
it's so much fun
yeah I'm sorry that I have to go early
oh yeah no it's it's okay you have your
own reasons and that's totally fine and
I very much respect anything that you
do but we can still hang out you know
I'm always just course yeah yeah we
should maybe a second Antarctic a
trip we we can go to I don't know Alaska
Alaska you heard it here
everybody yeah I don't know that was
just a random place I thought of but it
doesn't have to be that we can go see
the Northern
Lights oh yeah that would be really nice
I've never seen it before me neither I
only have seen it from Polar
Express like the
movie yeah like when they're on the
train and the girl start singing and
then the Northern Lights just come out
I've never seen the Polar
Express what isn't that the scary movie
no it's a Christmas movie I know but
they look so scary oh the
everybody like the character models yeah
I don't know they just look there's that
one kid that's like a nerd that's just
like I know who you're talking
about
I mean yeah I kind of agree the CG is
kind of scary a little or like I guess
uncanny isny yeah yeah but you should
watch it I think it's funny and
iconic okay I think what the iconic
scene from for me especially is the hot
chocolate song okay on the train no idea
that one is the best wait did you ever
do a watch you didn't do a watch along
right no I didn't okay you should do a
watchong and then I'll watch your watch
along really yeah yeah I'll watch it
with you technically I'll watch your
watch along oh I guess I
should I could just also watch it with
everyone else too for anyone who hasn't
seen it oh po Express watch along okay
now there we go everybody we're set so
then everyone can watch it yeah and
watch it alongside with you
yay yeah that's crazy you've never
watched it though main character did not
deserve the ending what does he die oh
don't spil oh we have to watch it I
forgot the actually don't remember song
changed me what's theoc song yeah it's
it's it's like their iconic like song Oh
everyone
dies the whole train
explodes I actually don't remember what
happens at the end Tom Hanks is in that
movie isn't he I think so
yeah I think so I don't know it's been a
while there's a video game for it
what what
the a video game wait Polar Express you
have to play it I stream
it oh my God
wait on the on the the GameCube oh
that's
old W is a fake fan oh my God wait why
clearly the hot chocolate song did not
change her life because
she would be all over this oh my God
this the graphics look like that one
game called uh
bully oh my God it actually looks like
Bully right I
know
I'm looking at the pictures right now
and it just looks like bullies righted
three out of 10
holy wait seriously why cuz it's
probably
shovelware
oh oh my God oh my God yeah the reviews
are oh my God it's an old game so it's
it's
okay wow that's so funny someone said a
I liked it oh no a what's the game play
like I
wonder uh I don't know just looks like
those old like PS game like gameplay
mechanics or
whatever yeah I think I think ew there's
some there's some like playthrough that
are you watching it no I'm just looking
at some of the thumbnails for
it what the hell is this lady in the
basket so creepy oh I see it too I see
what you're talking talking about wait I
don't know if that's a lady oh just
kidding wait that might be Tom Hanks
what sorry Tom Hanks in the basket is it
this
picture um
yes
that's I think that's
him why is he so old I think wait let me
double check wait I lied I lied don't
don't listen to me oh just okay never
mind don't listen to me that wasn't him
I think he has a health bar I think you
have to I think you have to kill him you
have to kill the old
man who is this character actually what
the
heck o are they even part of the
movie is this even the same
movie I think I'm thinking of a
different movie that might be
why like a different Christmas movie
like The Christmas Carol or
something I think oh I have no idea I
don't know I don't remember even rainow
said it looks like Bully that's so
funny oh yeah yeah oh yeah I was
definitely mistaking it for Christmas
Carol
sorry because I it looks like the oh it
does like the ghost yeah yeah yeah yeah
like it looks like when he's like
wearing like the pajamas and stuff yeah
no I think that's what this character is
wearing the the pajamas I don't know
what the hell is going on but I don't
know who that is supposed to be I'm
going to watch this playthrough tonight
maybe wait the play like the game play
yeah why
not okay I'll watch it too
then I'm curious cuz it I want to know
why it's not so or rated so low I mean
it's an old game so it's like whatever
right
right so
funny did wait how long have I been here
I don't want to take up too much time no
you're good you got a long list of
people so I want to make sure you're
able to complete Pokemon on oh you have
3 hours before I play Pokemon oh wait
you have 3 hours left oh shoot okay all
right then I guess I'll finish up then
but we're still going to talk tomorrow
yeah we'll talk tomorrow still I still
feel relieved that I can still talk more
tomorrow yeah yeah I I'm glad we could
get the sappy stuff and tomorrow'll just
have fun normal time with lunch
lady I can't believe we're playing lunch
lady again oh my God yeah I
know and they have that one map that
just literally is the fast High School
let's go I'm so
excited yeah I'm excited
and not just that too but I think I'm
also in the other uh games that you're
doing as well okay y so I'll be there a
little early yeah yeah I made sure to
open the entire day for you
yay thank you f thank you for you know
thank you being such an awesome gen mate
and you know thank you for you know um
you how do I say this
you are so much stronger than you may
think and you are
so you are such an individual you like
there is no one else like you like it is
so funny your mannerisms your everything
like you are a true one-of a kind fish
so you know just keep being yourself
because you're just you're just a little
fish you know you
you you are you like I said I I I the
things that come out of your mouth I
just don't
understand that's okay I always intend
it to be that way always what does that
mean so it's a conscious
effort yeah I've always I've always
purposefully done
that oh my God I mean sometimes
sometimes there sometimes I actually am
very genuine about my reaction to things
like I don't know some things I don't I
think I'm just living half under a rock
sometimes so half of the things
I like think about I I don't know how to
like piece it together and stuff
so I don't know I feel like I don't know
how half the world works
but no that's okay
yeah just keep it that way you know just
uh
yeah stay stay stay exactly the stay
exactly the
same I will
try no solar Under The
Rock You
true maybe that's why I didn't know what
a solar was after all she's living under
a rock yeah all I saw was just
darkness whatever the opposite of solar
is um lunar
lunar
wait but is it really a lunar if it's
just complete pitch black
what is it really a lunar if it's just
pitch black but solar okay solar is the
Sun so the opposite of the sun would be
the lunar or the moon yeah but you can
still see the
moon wait so you're thinking of just
lightness and
darkness yeah
right see I don't really I don't know
how
[Laughter]
to this is this is this is poetic this
is the perfect way to end this I don't
think we can continue any longer this is
it
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyways
yep see you tomorrow Fina okay I'll see
you in broad daylight solar yep in the
broad daylight solar where I can see
you
[Laughter]
yes okay okay I'll leave it to the next
person then the [\h__\h] who the [\h__\h] is the
next person I don't know I don't know
who Mike
is wait I think I know who is it just
take away the first
letter is it I oh is it wait I don't
remember seeing him type though oh wait
oh he's
here oh I was like who is
Mike I thought they were I thought they
were referencing the Mike
Smile I thought someone's name or
nickname here was named mik or
something it was either Mike or mik and
I was
like oh my God I was I I thought you
knew I was going to be like oh can you
tag the next person yeah I didn't
actually know who that was I thought
that's said M or something I'm like who
the [\h__\h] is M
Mike
Mike yeah if you guys don't know uh
there's like a queue and the people who
are repeating the queue is just it's
like I know everyone has unique you uh
nicknames yeah like the next the one
after is Necco made and then there's a
toilet paper on Emoji like just it's so
messed up yeah I don't know any of
these nice okay I will I will take my
leave now but okay I'll see you oh I'll
still keep watching the stream but I'll
see you physically again tomorrow
okay see you
tomorrow see you tomorrow bye-bye
byebye bye-bye bye
bye love you
fish that was
finor the first one to make me
cry but yeah little fish okay let's get
through these I'm not trying to rush
anybody you know if I have to push my
stream that's okay I I I intentionally
started my stream with also the
intention or the possibility of pushing
it back 1 hour so um you can come
on
in but
yeah whoa
whoa hi aomu how's it going hi I
Mike Mike oh yeah I saw the fact that
you thought they were talking about Mike
mazow I'm like is that what I've been
demoted to I didn't I didn't know for
some reason my brain could did not
process that just putting an M mon ink
reference putting an m in front of your
name just changes
everything that reminds me of the whole
thing with like oh spell yes what
happens if you put an e in front of it
how would you pronounce it and they just
go e yes
e the man of sex no why you so close to
when we got to say goodbye and you still
won't let that go hell
no why I think you inside of nen has
been the one that quotes it the most
okay maybe aside from Vox and fulger oh
yeah I mean Vox will probably take any
opportunity to say it don't give me
really much of an option but you you
take the quite the opportunity to make
me remember it too yeah I like it why I
don't know I just think it's funny
that's fair yeah I don't know where that
name even came from it was some stupid
meme that Vox posted a around debut of
some I think it was a Team Fortress
screenshot where he just saw a user with
that name through a wall and then he
pasted me
over
H I thought it was like I don't know I
thought it was like something you did or
something no I have done nothing to
deserve that name
wow you know what maybe I shouldn't have
been saying that this whole time you
haven't proven yourself
worthy whoa okay you're not wrong but
you don't going to be so loud about oh
now you're offended
huh anyway have you been
Ike uh slowly but surely recovering I'm
only left to coughing oh
no I'm almost back but I'm still trying
to rest as much as possible but I set an
alarm so that I would be able to wake up
in time for
this I'm sorry you can uh you you we'll
we make it quick and you can go back to
bed no no no no no it's fine my sleep
schedule is ruined anyway so what's this
so
true felt that yeah like I've just sort
of been like reminiscing like a about
like a bunch of things like leading up
to this day even though like we like you
let some of us know like a little bit
like early just like hey this is
happening so it was easy to sort of like
prep yourself but you're never really
sure how you're going to take it once
like everything actually goes live yeah
like even when I was telling you guys I
was like this doesn't feel legit like it
just you know yeah like it still doesn't
really feel real
because like as someone that was there
at like lazza light's debut and just
like saw this like like the like quote
unquote official beginning of nien and
it just sort of feels like things are
always going to be the same M when
you're like at at some place like that
and then be just somehow ending up here
in one way or another it's just like oh
yeah like the people that were here like
they're going to be here forever like
they they founded the thing like of
course but then reality sinks in you're
just going to got to be like damn no I
don't know if I'm making sense anymore
like it's 1 a.m. no no I'm sorry no I
get what you mean though I get it it's
like yeah it's
just it's kind of like when I made my
announcement like I I said like it's
it's scary because I am so comfortable
here you know like I'm having to step
out of my comfort zone I'm having to
leave this you know community
that that has been so you know awesome
and yeah I don't know it's one it's one
of those things like that the cliche say
saying something something glad that it
over happened or whatever what the fck
something something glad that it over
happened
you don't know
kid
[Laughter]
2024 something something glad that it
over
happened listen I am bad at words when
I've just woken up no that's so
[Laughter]
iconic yeah don't cry that it ended
smile because it happened yeah that's
the thing yeah that's the one exactly
got it nailed it you said that you
actually you you you said that oh my God
me yeah attribute that people are going
to quote me incorrectly in the future
just like
sunzu yeah EXA novelist by the
way yeah aren't you supposed to be like
you know you're supposed to um work work
better under pressure even the fastest
computer needs a boot up sequence ooh
wow guys don't be so hard on
it yeah yeah like there's just like so
much cool stuff that You' done that I
always like just what what's the word
I'm looking for I I don't know I guess
respect it because like you know when
you have respect and admiration for
people from afar like even when you get
closer to them like by happen St or
whatever that it sort of becomes a more
like different kind of respect and
admiration I guess because like it just
friendship does
that but I guess part of it that that
never really goes away in one way or
another because there was always like so
much cool stuff you did that just made
me like flabbergasted like especially
like the anarctica like seeing that
finally like come together it was just
like I don't know how you think of these
things like I'm just genuinely in awe at
the creativity on display I don't know I
don't I feel like it's not creativity
it's just me being like I think I'm just
going to go do the thing like I don't
know like I don't know I'm I'm inspired
by the world around me you know I
actually I um when we were there we
got we um we sent postcards back to
ourselves and that's great I got I got
mine the other day and mine says my mom
said anime was just a phase but anime
brought me to the end of the
world that's so inspiring but also so
kind of like huh at the same time
imagine the post the postal worker being
like what the hell does this
mean God imagine the weird kind of weird
stuff that they see flowing through I
know I can't imagine oh my God you got
to see all my figures and just like oh
here's another one for Mr Eveland
again his cultured
taste they're judging you they're
judging your
wifeu H as they're entitled to but I I I
sh take up too much time I just wrote
down a few things that I wanted to get
off my chest before before I
procrastinate and lose the chance
forever oh okay okay
uh and when I first got here like one of
the the first collabs that I ever had
not the first one I think it was the
second one was a phasmophobia collab
that I had with you and fana and box oh
my God yes that was so long ago yeah
that was ages ago but like it was so
scary there in the beginning because
like it was still that sort of Star
Struck like and still being you know
thrown into the deep end not really
figuring out what to do so I just wanted
to say thank you for like that
invitation and being like so nice nice
and introductory and accommodating and
everything showing us dumb boys the
ropes with the drooling man babies that
we
are I you you you you you're pretty put
together Vox on the other hand you know
I
mean I don't know about that you got to
be broken in at least a few places to
end up here that's fair that's true yeah
like you made it all feel very natural
and so thank you for that and thank you
for letting me like you you were also
one of the first people that I got to
mix in here so that was also oh my God
yes you have helped me so much Ike like
I only I no I only did it twice I know
that's more than once that's more than
zero times you have helped so much I was
more than happy to it was a lot of fun
unfortunately the one one of the ones
that I mixed was Ian which is kind of
ironic now now isn't
it
yay
man but yeah thank you for always being
kind think for always doing like cool
things like uh like the group projects
like the virtual to live uh like for the
first anniversary like
the which was like such a cool thing
like at this point I know that it's a
Goose house song but I can't stop
imagining us whenever I hear it at this
point yeah I'm kind of the same which is
maybe
bad it's okay like you see it as a head
Cannon yeah yeah
yeah and just anything else like cool
and creative that you've always like
done and impressed us with like the
courtrooms the singing God knows for
like ages actually like I'm a little bit
sad that one thing that I imagined like
ages ago isn't going to come to fruition
now because like there was one thing
that I wanted to do that would include
God knows in one way and I was like this
has got to be
pomu uh I gu I guess I'll just pass the
mantle to like I'll ask lalite to put on
bows in the future yeah yeah wait you'll
be there in spirit I will I'll be
watching and also thank you for making
kagami such yell your name at the top of
his lungs during one of kosian that was
peak in every sense of the word I didn't
even do anything thank you
AI don't don't worry about it it was the
big pee PE energy influencing the
AI yeah there we go but yeah just you're
very cool pomy thanks for letting me get
to know a cool person like you and
please stay cool in the future I know
you will yeah thanks yeah I'm really
glad that I can meet you too I um we got
to talk more yeah for sure you got to
talk we we have you have anime tastes
and I need to know more about
them oh that that is a risky risky
slope but I feel like feel like we're a
little bit on the same wavelength I
remember when we shared like o Taco
Collections and I was like oh wait a
minute you watch that I think so too
that's why I'm like I think we need to
talk a little bit bit more yeah for sure
for sure also we need to yell about too
more yes oh my God The Zo into Toby Fox
collaboration yes oh my God it was so it
was so funny because it's like it's it's
such so very like um Toho in the
beginning and then just
undertale you can yeah you can really
just kind of like feel the switch Yeah
Yeah but that that's what's so great
about okay we're going to get
sidetracked we keep talking about that I
know but we'll hang out more yeah for
sure for sure just you if you're ever in
the neck of neck of the woods around
Sweden just like feel free to stop by
there's not a whole lot here but I'll
figure something out I want to I don't I
don't you'll have to tell me what to do
what what I should do in Sweden I've
never been I I don't know bring a fun
person because it's not fun
there damn on don't the tourism people
are not going to be hiring you no they
are not
thank you Ike thanks for taking the time
I know you're not feeling well but
thanks for no it's okay I was more than
happy to and thank you for having me and
you know just just fly safe to whatever
neck of the woods you decide to go to
next I know you'll do great there I
don't know whatever Planet I decide to
take over next ooh okay spicy I like
that P ification in the world now p
ification in the universe exactly we're
expanding mhm dam is expanding
all right I'll see you around hopefully
sometime in the future yeah thanks I
thank you for your help and everything
you've done and yeah it was it was my
pleasure stay cool pomu byebye you
byebye oh my god guy does that every
time oh my gosh Ike evand that guy Mike
Mike
Mand no yeah I I feel like I should have
thanked him even more for helping me
with my covers and mixing and stuff ah
that guy he's so nice that's I
think come to Sweden we
have Sho Sho screen capture comment
resting glitch face and
posted you said it
off I think one thing about like I don't
know being the first wave like we've
seen I mean this is obvious we've seen
everybody come in you know so it's like
um I haven't there's obviously some
people that I've talked with more than
others or collabed more with others or
but I don't know like it's weird hearing
how people will like you know come in
and be like oh I was so you know when I
came in we were nervous and unsure and
anxious and everything but it was just
the three of us supporting each
other so
um yeah it's kind of it's interesting
when people are like yeah we came in and
you guys are so
nice I guess that's good that it's uh
good we left that kind of impression
um
man next
[Music]
person
uh uh uh pomu rain puff of nii Sanji
Ian's first wave lalite the Fairy of
uburst the One
D hey what's up hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey what is that Bo I don't know I don't
know what to say uh I I I know what to
say yeah
um thank
you uh uh yeah okay I'll try not to be
too awkward cuz I'm really awkward with
stuff like this I know me too don't
worry that's why I'm just trying people
have been like should I say something
sappy and I'm like um we we're just
hanging out you know we're just we're
just chilling yeah like I thought about
writing something down and then I was
like uh I'm I'm I'm really bad at that
so I'm just going to come in and be like
hey pmu what's up how's the weather oh
I'm fine thank you and
you um my my favorite color is is blue
what but you're Green Oh my favorite
color is green uh green
yeah um but yeah um I
guess uh I guess I should talk about uh
what I think of pomu rainpop M uh
well I mean you don't have to I mean
well no no no no I want to I want to
like this is this is
no
I how do I put it
uh I I I I watched laite
debut uh I when I first when I first saw
you guys I was like who this is this is
insane like because I had also known
about nii Sanji before and I was like
holy crap you know Ian has has a well
there's an Ian Branch now oh my God and
then when I when I saw you debut it was
just like who I I know like this person
with this kind of energy I know she's
going to she's going to do big things
she's going to really my do a lot of
stuff big Pomo energy yeah literally big
Pomo energy and and you did like you did
like from then until until now like like
you you really have have done so much
like not just for like fans but like for
ien and for nii Sanji itself like like
you were the Forefront for for a lot of
stuff like you really you really showed
everyone your love for nii Sanji so I I
hope you know that everyone in nii Sanji
loves you just as much
[Music]
no everybody has been so I it's it's you
know I don't think we could have done
you know everything if everyone wasn't
as you know driven and fun and you know
as we all are like it's you know it's a
collective effort like everybody makes
me want to do more and you know
everybody cuz everybody is always like
working hard and doing so much and it's
you know it's just been a lot of fun
like you know everyone hanging out
and yeah but I mean I I I think a lot of
people
can really like really really attribute
you to like being a lot of their
inspiration I know for me to like um
when when I first joined nii I was
really like I was really not sure how to
fit in um cuz you know how debut goes
like you join and it's really scary and
you're like oh god what the hell am I
supposed to do yeah yeah um
but yeah like I when I
would like watch your streams or like
when I would bump into you in Minecraft
or something or whatever and just I
think I think the biggest thing that I
took from you in those moments was like
to just kind
of no matter how the flow is going to
just kind of keep having fun with it
like keep keep uh just just keep keep
the keep the big pomu energy keep the
big positive energy yeah I mean once you
lose the fun of it like you've lost
everything you know yeah then it's you
know then it's just a
CHS so no but I think everyone is you
know
it's not to say that we're always we're
always super happy gol lucky he you know
like I wish it was like that I wish but
I think everyone is pretty good at being
positive and you know kind of keeping
like that like yeah we got this
mentality and it just it makes it way
easier to want to continue you know so
yeah and yeah well for that mentality
too I feel like well I can't speak for
everyone else but for me like like I
said like you were you were the one who
really taught me like
that um I don't know just just keeping
that kind of mentality kind of like that
happy go-lucky kind of vibe
like
is it's just it's it's all about the fun
like don't like like you really taught
me to not forget the fun because there
have been a lot of times I feel like
I've almost forgot the fun of this and
and then you'll you'll like uh I I'll
hear you talking about like oh I I love
this so much I love streaming I love nja
Sanji and then that kind of reminds me
too I'm like I I love this too I love
doing this too so it's like you you
really were a big part in reminding me
to to keep loving what I do so I I I'm
really really thankful for
you I don't know I mean I think
I think you know someone can say that
you know someone can say
like someone can say any someone can say
anything you know but it's up to you to
kind of take that you know and Implement
that you know like you know someone can
just say like oh you know go be happy
but like it's up to you to right to do
it yourself you know to take charge of
that and make it an actual thing that
you believe in so yeah you know
man I'm going to miss you
P oh no what will we do without the
fairy of acus yeah be
F oh man I really I could sit here and
gush so much about how much you've done
for all of us but like I just I hope I I
really do hope wherever you go off to
like what whatever you do I hope there's
nothing but like joy and positivity to
come your way and and I I hope you never
forget that you know uh like we we
always we always got your back we're
always like cheering you on no matter no
matter from where you know yeah and me
too for you guys of
course
you what is happening no I don't know I
oh upon you my big PP energy oh my god
dude honestly okay another thing too
that
really really helped me kind of fit in
like was the the chant you know because
yeah you I I I remember when NOC di
debuted like everyone was doing that and
I was like oh my God I want to do this
too so I literally Googled the whole
thing and I tried to memorize the all
the all the lyrics and I was like okay
I'm going to have this down and I
memorized it in like a night and yeah
you were one of the first people to like
really kind of grab on to it yeah yeah
and and it helped me like um I don't
know attach attach better to to other
people to kind of like it it it kind of
was the one of the first things that I
was able to share with with other people
in the branch it it like it wasn't mine
but you like gave something to be able
to like bond with
everyone like you did that a lot
actually there were a lot of things you
gave to us like in the branch that
helped people bond with each other so
like no
we're H I'm just I'm just I'm really
grateful for you so yeah I mean I'm I'm
not good at like happy stuff but no it's
okay me neither yeah but no I'm just
yeah just just really seriously thank
you yeah no thank you Al
you guys' been so fun it's been a lot of
fun so yeah I'll never forget there was
like a because of the chant there was a
I'll never forget this specific
animation it's you mean Sunny yes all
doing the CH
together yeah it I think that's like
when it started to really pop off and it
was so fun yeah yeah what would okay I I
have a question for you for someone
who's not very well versed
in like that kind of stuffff like do you
have any any like uh pointers or tips to
get more like into that kind of
culture I I wish I could like recommend
like a like a tutorial
Channel I don't think back then there
were really any like I just learned from
watching Idol shows and stuff like that
uhhuh uh but yeah cuz I've always been
really curious because like I I hear you
talk about stuff like that a lot and I'm
like what is a good way to get into it
oh yeah I did do an idle call teaching
stream wait really yeah I
forgot wait I'm so curious wait hold on
idol call yeah it's like Idols 101 or
something wait what is
this I see like this thumbnail is so
funny I see like a bunch of hands coming
from like your back and there's a bunch
of
paper
ha oh my
God yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
crazy oh my God so um maybe that'll help
a little if you if you need any more
help uh Myan will can help you too yeah
oh my God M yeah but I don't know uh
well I won't go for too too long cuz I I
feel like I'm like repeating myself at
this point but um yeah no like thank you
for for everything you've given for us
like not just like not just like in
terms of like projects or anything but
like in terms of the things you gave us
that let us bond with each other like
it's it's it's really really really
special to all of us the things that
you've given to Ian thank
you I don't know how to respond I don't
know I feel like like you know I don't
know I
feel that everyone everyone has had
their impact and so yeah yeah but no
listen yours was big man come
on I don't know take the compliment boo
okay I take the compliment okay thank
you oh god well then I will will you be
joining tomorrow or I will I will be
there yes then I will see you tomorrow
yeah I will see you there take care and
again wherever the wind blows wh HCK
anywhere
wind thanks Alvin yeah take care have a
good one see you tomorrow see you
tomorrow
byebye
ad ad a
brain I don't know I'm sorry I'm so take
the taking the
compliments but I appreciate that you
know he would think that highly of
me let's get in the next
person oh you're so
fast uh bonjour bour how are you doing I
hope your day was good so far yeah
everybody it's B
doggy hi everyone so so loud what no
you're you're you're perfect oh okay oh
wow thank you I mean you're toast oh
yeah I'm a I'm a french toast
today yes you are how are you
Bond I'm I'm doing okay I'm doing okay I
hope you do too hey I was listening uh
the thoughts with
doio and you you speak a lot of French
actually I I didn't know about that yeah
um what um yeah we
[Laughter]
we wee yeah I actually I took French for
like three years in school oh already
mhm for three years gosh yeah so well
it's like you're fluent
now basically I mean it's not that harsh
like so impressive that's crazy yeah
yeah you could say anything to me right
now and I would be able to
respond oh
[Music]
um we oh my God she
knows she does know
friendship
yeah wow oh my God all right well well
we we learn things every day
see that was that was like baby
talk oh my God gosh we should we should
have did some some French that's
together oh my God we should have oh oh
gosh too bad too bad we can't do it s
why did we not do
it my God what everyone knows s like I
don't know I'm really curious I actually
have no idea
why everyone knows about it even even
fresh people doesn't use it I I I I'm
just very confused oh you don't use it
I believe we don't anymore anymore oh
what do you use
now
M what you use m m it mean [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I me
[Laughter]
mad yeah yeah oh my God you're doing
you're doing great great yeah know the
slang
gosh that's even even worse oh hey are
you teaching me bad
words um
no no no no I'm I'm taking you know
teaching you how to sound native oh you
guys I have to sound
native yeah yeah yeah you're doing
you're doing
[Music]
great
see my God wa are you can you actually
talk like for for real IFR that's like
all I know
friends okay okay gosh she I don't know
you got to be confused like does she
actually know does she actually don't
know I I don't know I didn't know
anymore no I know I know Dix narf and
it's 19 in French if you didn't know I
mean disf right what oh you actually say
disf no no it's Di
Nerf I went to France I told them oh my
bad yeah I mean you know I I live viam
never mind yeah I
know what is that that's met
gear oh I
see I see I see haven't played it yeah I
could
[Music]
tell Pand you're a little
freaky what me I'm freaky yeah yeah you
you made some freaky stuff in
Minecraft oh what did you see yeah I
saw
oh um did you see with the normal T your
back
um
both
oh yeah I
saw um
yeah do you want to explain that before
um before I go or anything
or I mean there might be some people in
the chat that don't know so you might
want to you know you could like say hey
this is yeah I kind of foren this day
and I was like you know what how can I
how can I you know clone B and you know
I thought I would try some experiment in
my in my basement
to you
know get ADN of fairies and and clone
them so maybe you
know you guys he has like a whole freaky
basement he's captured finana he's
captured me like there's some weird [\h__\h]
going on
there weird was it m some weird Med
going on on
there oh my God you're using perect
well you know I'm going to continue my
experimentation okay maybe we can you
know revive p in in Minecraft eventually
yeah maybe but yeah we'll be we'll be
working on this on this on Minecraft
okay we'll be keeping up the server okay
good yeah you got to you got to work
with uh you know Willie and a and um
ukie you guys got to keep the Minecraft
server alive all right got it got it
we'll do that
okay thanks Bond I know we haven't
really talked much but um it was fun
yeah of course of course what fun what
fun yeah well last you know uh I wanted
to say something
oh um so you know when you think of BU
you think of P ener right
mm and you know I have a a re line I
kind of find out and I thought it's
suits you very very well okay okay okay
are you ready I
think hey are you pee cuz you're in my
heart
what oh okay let me do it again hey are
you are you pee cuz you're in my
heart what um thank you very much for
thank you but Dy I'll use
that yeah you're welcome okay see you
tomorrow see you
tomorrow well guys um I guess you can
use that right for your
own
um uh
Rising uh
opportunities are you pe cuz you're in
my heart where's the other
pee I don't know wait he said like
um
what oh you're in
[Music]
my oh like urine like
pee oh my
[Music]
God I can't believe you just said that
to me me I can't believe he just said
that to
me and we all just made him feel
crazy before
he it was actually a
[Laughter]
joke oh my gosh you have it here see see
see see I'll type it out for you R you P
cuz you're in my heart it sounds like
you're in
but it's urine like
P that is so awful anyways thanks B next
[Music]
person don't pin
it you can't you do not have mod powers
to pin
it I don't know if this person if oh
she's she said
wait wait oh hello hello
hello hi
M how are you I'm good oh my God you're
so right it's time for me to cry sexily
on stream yeah you practice you practice
Yeah here I
[Music]
go sorry you're supposed to cry sorry
keep
going
I'll miss
you what
is are you in the bathroom like What's
happen no it's it's my sexy
voice oh I'm going to miss you my sexy
partner in crime you know what I always
missed out I always was sad when you
guys did the big full girls off collab
that I didn't get to do a sexy
introduction I know maybe we could do it
next time can I do it one right now yeah
oh yeah I forgot you're
leaving oh my God hater on the chat
hater on the chat and hater on the VCT
text whatever you're just jealous I
could do a sexy voice I'm sorry girl
boss
feminism anyway go go go pomu okay can
you go first so I can have an examp
okay hello
everybody it's your sexy girlfriend
experience streamer with 40 no sorry 51%
chat agreement I got that that's
yesterday
[Music]
parfit okay go that's
it it's my name is p rainbow
n first wave last night oh yes oh yeah
I'm I'm I'm so honored to have the
sexiest member of N
and in
here yes oh yes
yes oh my God you did it
[Laughter]
I was sexy you sound like frog bir no no
no it was good it was good
okay how are you how are you how are you
feeling so so so puff
so sorry I had sexy long days I'm all
puffed up man oh arome I can't wait to
Puff you too in bed or I don't know what
does that um I don't
know anyway how are you feeling Miss
Ruff you feeling sexy yeah I'm so sexy
now I've never felt sexier in my life oh
my God it's so awesome cuz I'm also
feeling sexy so I think we should kiss
or something
[Music]
okay by the way this is paid content
everybody there's $5 for everyone in the
chat who's watching right now no this is
so the first 30 seconds are free oh okay
subscribe to uh pomu only headbands
afterwards no pomu Hub P pom pom Hub was
right
there sorry pomu
[Laughter]
hub
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes yeah I'm trying not to be sad
because um I cried when you announced it
and you were there and it's going to be
redundant if I cry more so don't cry to
be sexy you're too sexy to cry girl I
know but remember the time where we did
a sexy collab when we were both sexy and
we were so sexy you mean every collab oh
yeah like the sexy lethal company where
we go inside and explore each other and
you honked at me I I honked at you I
watched you I watched you get wet in the
lake oh yeah slowly and all you did was
look at me so
tenderly and
hel
oh my God sorry um you know with great
sexiness comes with responsibility and I
I see on VC text like some I have some
haters
on like it's okay to hate you know just
saying they're really they're really
hating on you I
know it's okay don't worry everybody
who's in the VCT tex I'll be here for 10
more years so you're going to see more
of me she'll actually be a grandma with
the
grandma
oh can I give you $5 to stop y yeah chat
give me $5 to
stop jealousy isn't pretty guys yeah
come on yeah
anyway how are you feeling pomu I feel
like we got into tangent oh my god when
you brought up the lethal I you know
we've collabed like so many times but I
feel like you're still going oh my God
I'm on I'm on my sexy mode today okay
okay this is It's A coping mechanis ISM
you guys um I feel like the lethal
company collab was so like our lethal
company collabs in general have been so
funny I know it's really I know it's
really fun because you're around I like
I I I no I laughed crying when you fell
into the
lake I think it was the first time too
that we played Lethal company so I'm
just like and then it happened again
time and and I I fell it and you left
and then you fell
in what can we say we like water we like
getting wet we like getting wet exactly
I'm wearing a white T-shirt oh my God oh
my God hold on me I'm wearing pink
T-shirt what color are your pink what
you say um hold on let me check it's
black oh my God mine are pink oh my God
we're like we kind of like swap you want
swap underwear next time we meet yeah
really it'll be so hot do you do you
like laces or oh yeah I love laces yeah
oh yes yeah I don't like it but I'll
wear it for you clothes wait I thought
you owned l
oh why' you ask then I don't know and
we're just trying to be sexy to each
other guys is it working is this like a
real sexy stream now
yeah raise your hand put the heart
side the
[Laughter]
heart do you guys feel uncomfortable cuz
I know some of you
are this is a normal this is Milat
normal yeah this is me on VC Hangouts
every day that's why this is actually
how she talks to all of us we're used to
it Yep this is my real voice
everybody this is why when you leave
I'll take care of a for you hey hey
what or triple marriage three-way
marriage oh
yeah just remember you're always welcome
to my sofa bed if you ever come in my
place don't a sexy one don't you live in
A's basement yes I'm pretty much you
know
offering her
house I'll come over okay I'll see you
and um I just want you to know that I
love you love
you oh my God this is so Steam on my arm
it's starting to smell or
something oh I mean uh
it's a good it's a good smell girl smell
I know girl
smell why am I doing this
undergraduation thinking I was like wow
I'm going to be this is the last memory
I'll have of you on
stream now there's going to be more
tomorrow yeah more tomorrow yeah I
already cried a lot during the last time
when you were there so I I lost all my
tears and I know it's not going to be
just like it's not going to be over for
us you know uh we're going to meet up
more anywhere just call me wherever you
want and I'll be there just let me know
6 months in advance so I could save up
money on a flight okay and apply for
Visa just in case cuz you know I don't
have baa I I'm
like Canadian yeah why know yeah with my
accent it's like very difficult to um go
to like a other places with the VISA so
oh my God you're pulling out everything
today I
know yeah if anyone uh in in the chat
who wants me to uh you know
marry let me
know I'm I'm just here I'm not here for
pom's graduation I'm here to look for
someone on my life yeah this is actually
the dating Show part two
yeah oh my go that was so
funny man you're so crazy you're so
crazy
crazy crazy for you
she oh miss you really though I'll
really miss you yeah I'll miss you too
it it will feel different here but at
the same time you're always going to be
in my heart and my coochie and my I
don't know what I'm saying mostly my
heart and my
head I think only in I think just I
think you got the other part wrong yeah
I think it's supposed to be my heart and
my head but for some reason I thought of
my coochi but I don't think you're
thinking at all yeah I don't
think I don't know if you're thinking at
all oh my God yeah I don't think so
either but yeah I'll miss everything and
I'm you know I'm still looking forward
to to the time that we're going to
karaoke you again and we're going to
hear you like dance Hear Me
dance girl are you are you okay okay
what is happened I had a long day
today I did some physical work like
lifting boxes sexily so sexily oh my
gosh
yeah wait was it what was on the
calendar
oh touching grass yeah were you touching
grass yeah it was it was yeah yeah yeah
I thought you going to say the place I
was like please don't say no no no no no
no no that's why it's all funny cuz yeah
yesterday I didn't even know I put the
address on the calendar until Al pointed
out like girl you put the address of
you're going on the calendar I was like
oh my god I didn't even see it I just
saw that you good okay good good good oh
my God okay well damn I should have seen
it I would have come
over yeah you could help me lift some
sexy boxes too if you want
yeah anyway oh my God I got we got
tangent I just want to say I love you
pumu and this is not going to be over
for us um
unfortunately I think we're we're now
friends for life so um you can't yeah
you can't get rid of me I'm sorry it's
just how it works yeah oh boy we're
we're like we're like trauma bonded no
blood bonded yeah blood bonded uh lip
bonded bonded
bonded can't wait to kiss you in
different parts of the world I think
that's going to be our
goal that's the goal okay
we need to take um I always wanted to
have like those um you know those cuz I
I never have a like anyone in my life to
have like kisses and couple selfies with
oh so would you be interested in going
different parts of the world and we
could take thanks for coming on to my
stream Millie it was so nice you know
I've had so much fun with you and okay I
tried
[Music]
yeah goodbye everybody I I guess that's
no just want a couple kiss you know no
we can kiss Millie we can kiss really
with tongue cuz is
a a is not really into tongue so I don't
really have a tongue so like you know
I'm going to have to wait really yeah
did you just cut your tongue or what
happening yeah it's
like I lips are fine okay no tongue yeah
cool can I get the upper lip or can I go
on the upper lip or I mean sure I think
it
yay I'm happy this is all I wanted
everyone I just want her to kiss me yay
thank you thank
you for having me I'll see you whenever
see you tomorrow oh yeah it's not end
yet I forgot yeah it's not the end yet
to
sleep go sleep see on crab game bye
bye guys I do have a tongue but if she
asks me one more time to tongue I'm
going to cut it
off thanks
Millie Millie parf
everybody let's see who do we have left
one two three four five six seven eight
nine 10 okay we can get through 10 in
two hours we got this this is easy next
up you are up
buddy oh
hello yino hey
hey I shouldn't have sign up right after
middle you have very big shoes to fill
honestly um but yeah um I don't really
plan much I played a little but we're
just here to talk just here to talk yeah
just vibing how are you doing buddy just
chilling yeah watching a pmer rain puff
stream yeah I know that gosh I think
there's only like two more left oh shoot
oh man got to watch it while they were
there or your BS are staying right yeah
yeah MH oh do the sexy voice shoot
it's what the people want no I I
can't I'll stop I'll stop
wow yeah this this one's this one's
because you're going
away I didn't ask for it they
did don't put it on me oh true true well
I don't I don't know what are the pumi
going to do you know oh I guess wait
should I be should I give extra fan
service then while I'm
here I mean up to you really okay you
have to maybe when maybe when it's you
know when I have no one in call to judge
my actions like immediately you know
what I
mean I mean is it not fan service when
you have a whole music video release oh
my gosh the of a bir
Akers is it is it is it AK akur yeah
akur Aki Bur yeah like AKA AK Akiba AK
yeah yeah yeah oh my gosh when I saw the
music video the part where the it was
the the what is it the the ad on the at
the station oh yeah yeah that's my
favorite scene yeah we went and I took
that when I was there really quickly and
sneak
yeah the ad and the the dancing those
two are favorite Manan
is yeah he was very excited about he was
just so much like oh my gosh I I Loki
think manan's passion is dancing I've
I've seen I've seen him dance I've seen
him dance really yeah he's just like
just waiting around he'll just start
dancing he's so goofy that guy he is he
is yeah he was very he was so excited he
was just like this is and when we were
recording he would be like um actually
he learned learned how to do like some
of the W gay I sent him videos and so he
learned he stayed up the whole he was
like I stayed up the whole night
learning how to do
it I know it was so nice and go um when
he was just like what should I do when
like you know for the other parts I was
like well I asked him to do the the um
rajio Tyson or the rajio tyo I was like
yeah I want you to do that um he was
like why I was like I don't know I was
just and then um and then uh he was like
am I doing a good job for the other
stuff like what should what do you want
me to do and I was like anything just do
anything he was like
okay he was so funny and after he was
done he would be like did I did I do a
good job I was like do you want me to
change anything I was like no it was
perfect my it was it
was yeah yeah man manage us on fan
service mhm we we got those
before you go I I was I originally asked
if I could do it oh uhhuh yeah but he
was like um me I think he wanted to wear
the main dress he did he did
yeah I think he wanted to dress up and
dance around but afterwards after every
take he would be like I'm so hot I can't
[Laughter]
breathe oh yeah I bet it was yeah yeah
oh man when are you going to do that
shoe
[Music]
oh
h i mean I've done it in VR
already you know like I met I met froger
actually oh yeah yes I saw that yeah I I
went to say say hi to frog bird and I
was I wanted to learn some W from frog
bird wow but yeah frog bird didn't
didn't teach as well as you did I think
oh damn yeah yeah wait did you recently
get VR
or um I recently got full body oh oh my
God so that was like
exclusive or have you used it before or
that in well that that in the luxium
second anniversary yeah ah okay okay
okay yeah yeah yeah
nice yeah but yeah that was the first
time I I I uh I did the with the w I
think yeah cuz you you and sunny were
moving you were grooving oh oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah s had a gun yeah yeah he did I
kind of want one now
what you you have your jiujitsu you
don't need a
gun I mean could you summon a gun I'm a
Valor player Oh summon in a gun o I
don't know I mean it's not it's not very
like
jiujitsu that's fair for for a gun yeah
ju is more like Souls of like dead
bodies and
stuff MH you could possess someone that
has a gun take his gun oh my God it's
like when I'm when I'm playing a video
game of
and I'm controlling a character in a
video game but real life mhm yeah
exactly oh my gosh oh my God valerin and
IRL
valerin and I and they make did your son
move
around what would his what would his
wait do they have ults in in valerant oh
yeah yeah
yeah he'll fly around he'll fly around
yeah he'll learn how to fly around and
like yeah it's like it's like Merc from
OverWatch it'll just fly around how do
we always talk about valerant when
you're around um I think it's just me
this is all me it's your brain rot oh my
gosh yeah but I still remember the one
time you made an account just to play on
my birthday the hopon account I did yeah
you you own the hopon account I actually
yeah
yeah I don't even I don't even know how
to get logged back into that oh
but you're you saying that you'll have
some free time afterwards like you know
if you stop streaming and you know if
you want to
you if you want to hop kind a little if
you are if you are if you are willing to
I am always well not always but if I'm
open I am open okay um I'll think I'll
think about it um yeah you know I never
did it before when I had free time mhm
um uh so you know uh but it's something
that I might consider when I have free
time now
oh okay since I don't have Minecraft
anymore oh I mean you could have
everything you know you're free you can
do whatever true yeah yeah you're you
also you don't have to play valerant all
the
time I I mean I no I don't I don't do it
all the
no yeah
[Laughter]
yeah oh Sho but yeah before I go
mhm I want to give you this one thing oh
I have one thing to give you give yes
but I want you to not open it until the
end of the stream oh
[Music]
okay there you go oh okay it's even
censored oh my wait so I don't open that
don't open it until the end end of the
stream okay is it something that I can
show SL say on stream okay yeah oh I
don't even know what it is oh my God
but I I wanted to organize a little
something I just want to give that to
you oh thank
you just open at the end okay oh my gosh
what oh my God okay you guys have to
can't you can't let me forget can't let
me get Pokemon
obsessed you can over here doing Pokemon
if you
want yeah thank uh thank you for having
the opportunity yeah best best best
Senpai no
any other
way shut up but like for real I'm glad
that you're part of wave one like I
wouldn't have it any other way myself so
yeah it's been a lot of fun thanks you
mhm see you
tomorrow see you
tomorrow later
later shoot oh my gosh I'm so curious
what this is what the
hell
the person who's been posting
the the
the what's it called the the list of
people is next
ah um it's so weird like you know some
people I don't know I just um maybe it's
like kind of like how Ike said when you
become better friends with someone like
it's it's weird hearing like the the
admiration like the or like the you know
the oh you done this and that I don't
know it just feels weird like it just
right now I just want to or I just feel
so comfortable like just chitchatting
and you know even if it's just dumb
mundane stuff it just F seems kind of
fun you
know that way oh the next
person let me ask if she's
ready oops that's not
[Music]
her I think I think I tagged the right
person Discord cuts off their names oh
yeah I did oh my God you made she made
the picture that her Discord Banner oh
my God e
e okay um I'm I'm so not ready to be
here what is your Fogie I this I oh my
God I'm be so honest this whole entire
like two weeks I've been like we are so
back it's so [\h__\h] over Who We Are so
bad it is so [\h__\h] over and even right
now my brain is like yeah I'm like
listening and everyone's like laughing
I'm like haha and then like someone
cries and I'm like it's so
over like I was so scared to go after
Millie because I thought she was going
to cry and then I was like it's over for
me but she didn't she didn't she was
strong yay but finana C I think fana is
the only person that cried I don't know
if I can promise the same that's okay
and you were like oh my God having so
much fun doing mundane chitchatting I
wrote like a really long you can no no
no no no you can say you can say it's
okay I'm sorry I'm about to break oh my
[Music]
God I just can't believe this is
happening
sorry
x what is that guy I have to close I
have to it's because of
you know what that means I know that
guy oh my God okay I wrote a lie I'm
sorry I don't I'm going to do my best
not to cry I made it like silly I wrote
LOL in it time try to to remind myself
that to be okay I do that too I write
LOL in places that I want to laugh to
break up the dit all right
this is so
embarrassing this is more embarrassing
than sad I think
no um wait I'm going to I'm going to put
music on for me too because I feel like
if I don't have a bgm for myself I'm
just going to be sad do you want me to
do
it GNA do that for for three
pages it's okay unless you want to no
you can go it's okay all
right maybe I'll put on a sad song what
what's wrong with you okay I'll put on a
sad song um Beyond hold on let me I'm
putting on a sadder song than you oh my
God I don't even have that many sad
songs I have
a
no I have to find it though I'm going to
I'm going to do my best to make this
happy wait where did I
um I know maybe it's in my likes one
second this is the Ambiance you
[Music]
guys is that what you put on no okay
should I okay I will oh I put on like an
actual sad song is that not a sad song
it's called like sorrow and
whatever you're right sorrow and sadness
from Naruto Sadness and Sorrow Sadness
and Sorrow oh it is about being sad
you're so right it's literally the
epitome of sad
yeah anyways okay I wrote so much I'm so
sorry but I knew the second I got in
here I'd be
like tomorrow tomorrow so I wrote stuff
down because I knew the second I got in
here I would regret I would regret I
would regret it for the rest of my life
okay oh dear
po Jesus
Christ
okay maybe I won't cry cuz I'm so I'm
cringing at myself but it's fine okay
dear po I really cannot believe that
this oh God I'm going to this is one of
the last times that we're probably ever
going to talk on stream it's funny that
although we've been together for a
really long time it also feels like it's
only been or it feels like it's been no
time at all it really truly feels like
yesterday that you told the two of us
that 2024 early 2024 would be when we
would be saying goodbye to each other
and at the time it really felt like it
was forever so I really didn't think too
hard about it well I did I thought a lot
about it actually it took me like a week
to reply to you I apologize profusely
because I I couldn't take it in but
little did I know everything came a lot
quicker than any of us could have
imagined um I even wrote here I'm not
even really I'm not ready to talk but so
I hope you don't mind that I wrote all
of this down and it's going to sound
like I'm reading off a script but it's
okay I haven't been able to process for
since as long as you told us and I
probably will not be able to process it
for a long time
afterwards um first I want to say thank
you I remember when in the first ever
meeting that we ever had together with
bana um and we were seeing each other
for the first time we learned that we're
going to have a debut song together and
I remember when staff told us that mafu
mafu was going to produce the song I
screamed yep but I tried to hit the mute
button and then I messaged you
afterwards and I was like pomu did I
mute fast enough and you were like no
LOL so it was really
embarrassing and then it happened again
with
Achi and you're were like h no LOL we
all heard it but it's probably okay
yay I remember the first time we ever
saw each other and you told me something
along the lines of that I looked like I
was the main character
or something and I said hell
no I was so nervous to debut and I was
so nervous but hearing you tell me
something that something like I'm the
main character or whatever it gave me so
much more confidence and I thought to
myself like yeah you know what maybe
this is my moment like yeah and it gave
me a lot of strength to do my best in
the upcoming weeks before we debuted and
during the debut and even until now you
know cuz it's even stuck to me until
this moment
but thinking back on it now I'm glad
that I disagreed with you at that moment
because I feel like one of the best
parts about laite is that we all bounce
off of each other so perfectly well when
the three of us are together it just
feels really natural and things just
always have slotted right into place
I've never felt so comfortable with two
other people in my life and I really
can't thank sta sonon enough for looking
at the three of us during our audition
phases of being like yeah these three
put them
together I don't think they knew what
they were doing at the time but maybe
they did know maybe this was a prophecy
thata was like these three toss them in
there the greatest
foresight that was probably the greatest
decision that they've ever made I mean
they make so many great decisions with
all of the Waves here but for me
personally that was the best decision
that they've ever made in their whole
entire life so thank you
tazian but to be 100% honest with you
pomu I am not ready to say goodbye to
you I I don't think I'll ever be ready
to say goodbye I've spent so many hours
trying to think about how I'm going to
say goodbye or what I should say to you
but it really truly feels like nothing
will be enough um there isn't anything
that I can do or anything that I could
even say to convey to you how much you
mean to me and everyone around you but
to be honest I I really wish that we had
more time together like I'm I'm a
selfish [\h__\h] so I'm going to tell you
all this
but I'm sad I get really sad when I
think about how there's no more songs
that we can sing together there's no
more games that we can play together and
there's you know like the games to come
we can't play and there are so many more
future events that we won't get to
experience
together as the same as before obviously
we'll get to experience things together
in the future hopefully but it won't be
the same but for me personally I really
wish that I could have seen you sing on
stage a lot more I feel like in my life
I've never seen anyone feel more at home
on stage performing than when I watch
you uh when I watched you during your 3D
I was so inspired to try so much harder
I remember you doing your best you were
always practicing the Coro in your hotel
room or when we had free time in the
studio you were always practicing and
you were always so peculiar particular
not peculiar I mean you
are but you were always so particular
about every move and you were always
trying to make sure that the next time
was better than the last and I remember
sitting there watching you and being
like yeah like this girl was born to be
on the stage and I hope that wherever
life takes you next you know you get to
stand on a bigger and even brighter
stage and I hope that I can be in the
crowd cheering you on because now I know
how to cheer idols on properly thanks to
you and seeing you get to perform a nja
Fest this year one last
time was really really special for me at
the moment I a lot of people nobody knew
except for us and here but getting to
watch that live stream meant so much to
me and probably means so much more to
everybody else as well now
but um P brain PFF you have such a
ginormous heart you know even though
things are so difficult for you right
now you always reach out and ask how I'm
doing or if I'm feeling all right thank
you I've never met anyone so silly or
with so many wild insane project ideas
like you I can't believe we went to the
end of the [\h__\h] world just to sing a
song from an anime is literally so crazy
did you get your postcard I did yeah you
know you know what I wrote on it right I
don't think so I wrote on my postcard
things in life may be tough but nothing
will be tougher than crossing the Drake
Passage and I'm like taking that
personally right now but maybe I should
have wrote bracket except po rain Puff's
graduation because I would take living
on the Drake Passage every day no over
this remember the Drake
[Laughter]
Passage but like I wrote here maybe I'm
also crazy LOL cuz I said yeah let's go
yeah you did at the time when you asked
us there was like this feeling in my
head where I was like I should go no
matter what like I remember reading it
this the time line and being like that's
a little crazy but in my mind but there
was like a gut feeling that I had where
I was like if I don't go on right now I
feel like I'm going to regret it forever
so I said yes right on the spot because
I had this like feeling and I'm really
glad that I decided to go because I feel
like I would have regretted it if I
hadn't had I don't know there was like a
spiritual Force pushing
me and I find myself to be like a pretty
shy I know it's hard to imagine everyone
but in person you know I find myself to
be kind of shy and like closed when it's
with people in person but in never in my
life have I been so vulnerable around
people like I have with you and finana
like when we're doing
3D or I wrote here I literally can't
imagine puking in front of anybody and
dying and I literally can't imagine
puking in front of anybody else without
dying of embarrassment and like never
wanting to see them ever again but pomu
you didn't laugh I wish you had and you
weren't like grossed out or anything the
only thing you said was what do I do I
go get you water do I go get you food
like how are you an Angel and then I
wrote hahaa
haaha but you are just like immediately
focused on what you could do to help me
instead of be like girl ew I'm like are
you an angel what the
hell it's the contrast between how
someone can be so insane but so sweet
and the most caring person in the world
at the same time that's why I love all
about you pomu I love everything about
you it's hard not to love everything
about the pomu rain
puff except one thing I'm sorry tier
that I'm going to give you a critique
okay but I wish that you could
understand a little bit more how special
you are to everybody I even throughout
today's stream I want you to understand
that you aren't just some anime girl
who's graduating and you aren't just
some other vtuber you make so many
people smile every single day by being
your true genuine self and that is the
most beautiful thing that one person can
do like I want you to know that you are
so much more than just another blip in
somebody's life like you say you have
changed so many people's lives by being
here and by being yourself you know
having something to look forward to
every single day is a huge motivational
factor for so many people to get up and
you you have been that motivation for so
many of us you are so special pomu and
you are literally one of a kind and I
don't ever ever want you to forget that
ever and don't ever doubt that because
it's
true that's my critique take the
compliment take the compliment is my
critique I guess don't brush it
off
okay um I want to say thank you again
for making n Sanji and what it is today
um thank you for bringing so many silly
ideas and creative projects into our
lives you literally changed our debut
song into something that just can't be
sung anymore more without the C sounded
in it's a requirement and we'll forever
stay a requirement and if any new
members join and ask what the hell we're
doing parentheses which they better not
cuz they should already know end quote
then I'll be happy to brag to them about
how my amazing wave mate has left her
Everlasting mark on what I would
honestly call at this point niis Sanji
Ian's theme
song I I have experienced so many of my
firsts with you and finana we debuted
together I went to my first ever made
Cafe with you and I got to see you mix
in person for the first time which is
the first time I ever saw anybody mix in
person my first time ever singing an
original song was with you my first time
ever being a guest at a convention was
you was with you it really honestly
still feels like yesterday when be Mario
came onto the stream and we surprised
you and when I was thinking about so
many of my favorite memories one of them
that came to mind was that collab that
we did when we played devour with finana
and rosam me and we were on the cowboy
map and we were decoding FNAF lore like
[\h__\h] crazy from literally nothing
that had to do with FNAF and it was not
even it was just symbols on the ground
that [\h__\h] was
[Laughter]
insane um personal anecdote sorry but
going to Fu Highland with friends has
always been a dream of mine ever since I
was really really young I went there
with my parents when I was a really
small dragon and I remember standing in
line with my dad and one day I thought
I'd love to come back here with friends
when I'm older and I would love to
travel travel around with my friends and
as I got older I didn't think it was
something that could happen because I
leared about the
money and you know it's difficult to
just say yeah let's go to Japan guys and
pack it up and go over there but I was
able to go there with you and finana and
I was able to experience the park
together like it was my dream when I was
a child and I got to see you freak out
over fujian in
person core memory that I will never
forget like the girl who was in front of
us and her mask flew onto her face so
funny oh
yeah thank you pomu for introducing us
to what it's like to love something so
deeply and literally buy every single
thing that you can from said series I'm
really glad I was able to dive a little
bit into Metal Gear before You' left and
I'm so thankful that you stayed up every
single time I finished a game just to
join into my stream so we could talk
about the story and the games U getting
to hear you talk about something you
love so much is really a joy for me and
for all the pomchis I'm sure and it'll
be memories that none of us will ever
forget and I'm pretty sure when ever any
of us see snake ever the first thing
we'll think about is
you you know I personally have also been
like pretty deep into series before but
after meeting you it shown me that
there's still a lot more insane lengths
that people can go to and it makes me
feel really at home when I'm talking to
you about things that we really like
yeah I've almost never had friends
around me in my life until I met you who
had these kinds of burning passions to
buy so many things from one series so
thank you seeing your collection ins
saying things that you buy and how deep
Your Love Goes is really so refreshing
and so fun for me and I can't thank you
enough for being I wrote here you are
such a cute otaku ELO because I didn't
know how else to describe it but that's
I think the best way to describe how you
are
yay so sorry complimenting me spending
lots of money but like honestly L that's
what money is for money is made to spend
on things that you like like what is the
point of saving money forever if you
can't indulge in the things that make
you actually happy so
[Music]
true uh thank you pomu for being a part
of Nan you've done so much for everyone
around you and it inspires so many to be
their honest selves after you're gone
it's going to honestly feel like there's
a huge hole where you once stood and I
don't think that hole will ever go away
but I also think that that's a very good
thing because I wouldn't ever want the
existence of pom rain puff um member of
first wave laite to ever disappear from
this world ever and to be completely
honest I don't think anyone in this
branch is ever going to let that
disappear because we all love you so so
so dearly I remember during your debut
stream you said that you wanted to make
lots and lots and lots and lots and lots
and lots and lots and lots and lots of
people love and know nii Sanji and you
[\h__\h] did that [\h__\h] like you my God
you you don't even know how awesome you
are I'm going to
scream I'm going to miss you so bad like
I still don't know how I'm going to
process all this to be honest but I wish
you I wish nothing more for than for you
to be healthy and happy here going on
the strongest fa in the world thank you
for all the fun memories I'm going to do
my best to stay silly and be a little
more crazy and think of you every step
of the way thank you for inspiring me to
be my true self um when I had debuted I
hid away aspects of myself because I was
scared and I was lowkey embarrassed
bracket cuz how could I not be to share
who I truly was but by embracing
yourself for who you are and being true
to your cringe self is how I promise to
live my life from here on out thanks to
you I love you so much Pulu thank you
for all the
memories end script end
scene sorry that was so long
[Music]
no sorry I'm
snotty I'm not making it out of the told
to about
you I'm not going to make it out of here
without crying but thank you Fu I love
you a lot and the words that I write
they're not they're like only maybe like
0.00001% of how much I love you and I
know they're still tomorrow
but it's it's it's hard yeah
but in the end the only thing that I
want for your happiness and you to be
healthy and strong and happy and that's
all I
want and I will miss you
but my selfishness of wanting you to
stay here is like beaten out so bad by
my want of you to be happy and for you
to be able to explore things that you
want to do in your
life and I will be cheering you on
forever me too to you
I don't even know what to say man I'm
sorry
[Music]
no I I don't think I could have debuted
with anyone else here like it just felt
so yeah I know you mean so
perfect like I know that people outside
will agree and say yeah but I feel like
even more than that like the three of us
mhm like unless you are the three of us
you probably don't understand but it's
just it was Destiny that's like the best
that's the closest thing that I can say
is just it had to have been the three of
us or
else I don't know I can't imagine a
world without I don't know I think in
any timeline it would be the three of us
yeah I think so
[Music]
too yeah I don't know we've just we've
done so much stuff together and we've
gone through so much stuff together and
we've accomplished so much stuff
together
yeah and
um yeah it's
like you know we'll still see each other
yeah it's just
yeah what the dog doing I'm so sorry
shut but
yeah what the fair doing that's my other
favorite po
[Laughter]
memory it just yeah I just feels so
weird like that it won't be it'll be you
know I'm going
to um you know when people are
like oh they'll still be able to talk to
each other they'll still be able to do
with whatever like why why are they so
emotional or like you know whatever ever
but it's like it's different when you
know when you graduate school do you
talk to those people every single day
you still you know like
people it's it's hard when you know
you're not constantly together and with
this like we've been able to
always be able to hang out and talk and
it's just been so much fun
um but yeah
yeah but I think I think we oh my God
this dog needs to shut up
Bute U those are my inner thoughts
um but I think you know I think we the
three of us have really established how
much we care about each other
and you know I think you said it earlier
on stream like you have talked to a lot
of people in person more and I'm
definitely the type of person who is
able to communicate with people better
in person and I feel like the three of
us are all that way like like I
definitely feel like I'm able to
communicate way better and I feel like
if you know our friendship is so strong
that even past this like we'll be able
to see each other still and we'll
probably still be able to make as much
time as we need to be with each other
yeah
yeah this dog is my comedic relief sorry
I needed something so I wouldn't die of
crying but yeah I don't want to take too
much time cuz I want you to be able to
beat Pokmon hell
yeah but we still have tomorrow tomorrow
is the real last day but um yeah I just
wanted to tell you even like a 0. 1% of
how much I care about you I don't think
I'll ever be able to tell you how much I
care about you I love you so much I
didn't think I could ever love someone
this much until I met you PA boo it's
crazy I you
I'm not good at expressing myself
usually it's okay me either it's hard it
is but yeah thank you no thank you I got
to stop crying where's the
dog the dog is gone the cling is so
bad but I will let you go I'm sorry that
I said so many words to you no it's fine
but yeah just make sure that I don't
know just take the compliment stop like
making yourself seem so much more
insignificant that you are pomu you've
seen so many of your you know Idols
graduate I was going to write this but I
thought maybe it was too harsh but
you've seen so many of your Idols
graduate and I know maybe for you I
don't know but it's hard every time I
can only imagine but for a lot of the
people who are watching you I'm pretty
sure this is you know their first
experience with their Idol leing I mean
I don't know if we want to call each
other
Idol but they oi I guess is the better
word this is probably the first time for
a lot of people to see their Oshi leave
and you know if you can remember the
first time that you saw your Oshi leave
this is what they're feeling right now
and it's a really foreign and like scary
feeling for a lot of people but you know
you would probably not want your Oshi to
be like Oh I'm nothing like you would be
like you're everything to me that's how
everyone feels about you so I hope you
can keep that in mind and remember that
so many people love you so much and we
want you to remember that you are so
[Music]
awesome am I
dead
hello no I'm muted okay sorry my
internet has been really wonky like
lately so I was like oh God I said all
of that and then Discord is going to
goom but I just want you to remember
that that you oh my God I'm going to cry
so much tomorrow but during lunch lady
we
can't I'm going to cry when I'm a worm
for
you I'm going to be the most dehydrated
worm in the world no you'll be so extra
slimy I'm going to be so dehydrated then
I'm going to have to suck up all of the
moisture from my tears on the ground and
then rehydrate my worm
cellana saying I'm going to cry a lunch
lady too no it's a lunch
lady you're going to be crying and then
you'll hear the lunch lady
[Laughter]
[Music]
go okay sorry I talked so long but yeah
that's all I want you to remember that's
all I want you to remember is that you
are very loved and don't ever think for
a second that you are not because you
are the strongest fairy in the world and
probably everyone's favorite fairy in
the whole world and I will now go
because I don't know how to wrap this up
okay I'll see you later tomorrow for
lunch lady and crab and goose okay I
love you PA love you
[Music]
byebye she's still apologizing stop
apologizing I think if there's anybody
that I would want um to take up the
whole time it would be
laite
man
[Music]
same to you no no more sorries
okay but I am
[Music]
sorry I'm sorry for
going
no sorry I'm going to block you I'm
going to you going to take away my
Discord privileges h on Halloween 2
years ago and I did it to you yeah don't
be sorry don't feel guilty Senpai is
furthering her career I mean her
education don't feel guilty for leaving
everybody supports you and we only want
what's best for you don't
apologize oh my
God I'm sorry to the next person that
comes in I'm going to be
so I'll be all feel better give me a
minute oh
no oh more people are added to the list
okay no it's only it's fine I want to be
able to talk to
everybody let me at the next
[Music]
person thank you
sho
dog
oh oh my God how am I even supposed to
go up after
L I'm sorry I said I'm like I was like
I'm sorry to the next person oh my
God what was it
mean honestly that made me cry earlier
too I like I wasn't crying I was like
listening to you guys I was like
[Music]
no how are you
rosor I'm good I don't want to take up
too much time cuz I know there's a lot
of
people want to finish
Pokemon so I'm trying to be really
really quick it's okay I don't know
honestly like I was going to write
something too but then I was like I
don't think I'd be able to say it and
then I was like trying to write
something and I started crying too I
can't I can't do it so I don't know I'm
just here to to clown you know yeah
we're here to
clown here yeah I'll give you a nose
don't worry oh thanks yeah okay all
right um um I feel like not to see a
joke um okay okay um oh crap I didn't
prepare one
um hey pom you're very
special
sorry she you y out so
loud sorry
that was awesome she a clown thanks I'm
a
[Laughter]
clown yeah she's I'm very special you
guys didn't hear her she's very
special to all of
us feel like everything I I try to think
of I try to not get sad and then I end
up sad and then I'm
like man but your Envy for Fairy black
Keepers was so awesome thank your your
manisan is actually my
oi he's my Oshi too he's so baby girl so
awesome my Manan is girl failure with
with the men pregnant Emoji I hope I
hope he doesn't hear
that no it's okay I I I tell him all the
time the men pregnant Emoji Manis on
girl failing oh yeah he started that or
like well he didn't start that everyone
gave him that emoji right yeah yeah so
girl failure yours is so awesome though
yeah he's pretty baby
[Music]
girl I'm I'm sorry I'm so sad right now
and I I said I would come up here and
and not be sad but it's way harder in
the moment and I feel like I have a lot
that I want to say but
it's okay man it's okay yeah I mean it's
it's hard to say even I like you know I
have I I feel the same way towards you
I'm just like I could I
could I could gush about you forever you
know like I could you know say
everything wonderful about you because
you are everything why are you
complimenting me I'm here to compliment
you because it's also my last
chance well oh my God why am I I set I
wouldn't cry why am I
crying I literally promised myself I
wouldn't so now I
feel well I mean you know we we we still
have to hang out Lots together and and
and get more yummy food together and and
and go camping we got to go camping yeah
we do yeah we got to go hike M
Fuji I will
I will put my life in your trust and go
camping with you and it's going to be
awesome yeah we got to go lick more
delicious
buildings
what
yeah yeah together
together man okay I'm I'm I'm probably
going to leave cuz I'm just crying
but it's okay no don't feel like you
have to stay or anything I want to it's
just I feel like I'm just here and I
can't stop crying now but you know in
the end everyone became P pul ification
happened we're all pul we're all P
You're P I'm
p no I mean I guess
canonically um I was your boss at
work yeah until we both we both quit our
jobs so you know oh now you can be my
big
boss
yeah let's go I wish I knew enough about
M gear to say more than
death no you know that you know the
other
thing um the other thing that OT is
gay that's all I know for real that's
all
I that's all I
know oh that's not what I was
thinking oh L
yes you're right maybe I know more than
I think I do I hope AA heard
that oh my
God that's honestly actually all you
need to know about the whole series
though Big Boss L and also G or the
three so that's actually all ofal
SC I will play it one day for you oh
I'll think about you and I'll play it
for
you okay I'll think about those three
things but uh thanks for everything p
and I'm trying so hard not to like I
just wiped away all my tears I feel like
I'm on the bridge of crying again
but you've done I mean everyone has
already said everything so I feel like I
can't say
anything that no one has said yet but
anda's right I feel like you should stop
doubting yourself because you've done so
much and you've accomplished so much and
it's it's not you know it's not a small
you know you you've done so much for
everyone and you've spread so much joy
and so much happiness so I feel like you
know you deserve to be proud and happy
about
that just all I say thank you thank you
po I'll see you tomorrow see you
tomorrow let's play LS together and talk
LS together then also
yeah yeah and we'll we'll still hang out
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and if you if you want I'll I'll I'll be
outside your window my God yeah don't
threaten me with a good
time see you later Rosen R bye po byebye
all that's left is the clown
knows hold on put it up
here oh no I'll put it on you guys we're
clowning
together
yay oh is this person let's see are you
ready wait hold on uh
[Music]
yes this guy
oh
well what the big
pomus hello
Claus oh my God girl I'm I'm
so sorry I'm I'm like I'm also try to
like recuperate I'm
sorry oh my God oh my God yeah I'm I'm
so nervous too I
I I think I was also like too scared
because I was like do do I should I have
prepared a letter to no a whole
speech no oh my
god um but yes I I man I I I don't know
how else to really say but you know I
feel like everything that's been said
already I could not have been said
better of you know I think you've truly
done so much and if anything even if
I've only been here a short time I feel
I know we didn't get to hang out I I
[Music]
know I I think I remember when when I
posted in Discord letting everybody know
that I was going to be leaving I told
everybody basically like a month earlier
and you were like man I just got
here oh my God I Had My Moments and I
was like
what I know I felt so bad I was like oh
[\h__\h] sorry sorry Triple T my
bad yeah but I mean it's it's been fun
it's been real it's been yeah been
cool I don't even know what to say I I
don't know either at this
point it's like everything's been said
and done but it's like I I still think
you have truly left a legacy and I think
everyone everyone knows that and feels
that to their core and even now I still
feel as
though I myself want to push myself to
work as hard as I can because the impact
that you have had and you know it's it
would be a disservice for me to not also
put in the amount of effort that you
have as well because I feel like with
everything that you've done you've truly
given 120% of yourself you've really
done things that not many would ever
possibly dream of
and
it's it it is a tremendous task so you
know I I truly do thank you for all that
you've done and you know best of luck
with everything that you
do I feel I feel like I say anything
else I'm just going to start
crying I was like I was like listening I
was like oh my gosh I think this is the
most serious I've ever heard you
damn that is damn that's
crazy I I it's so hard I I can't be
serious I if I'm serious I'll start
crying if I'm goofy then I'm no I'm the
same way I just clowned through it
man the the the funny haa will will
persevere yeah yeah yeah laugh through
the pain oh my God laugh through the
pain oh my God but yes shant Chandelure
through Elite Four yes to the end yes I
will TR J thank you God I'm
so oh my God girl I I I feel like I need
to like there's so much that I want to
say like in private but like I
get I'm sorry that uh um I couldn't be
around more to um so hold on oh my God
it's okay you've you've done so much and
sing akub burst through I'm so happy
that you
have you have gifted us the power of
money everyone is going off about it in
the
Discord they're like oh my God that's
M he he is arm man yeah I'll I'll send
you guys the green screen you can all uh
please oh my
God you guys can have that for
your our oi for real
yeah oh my
God yeah oh my God I also don't want to
give too much time there's a lot of
people I I feel like if I go anymore I'm
going to start crying
again oh my
god um all I got to say is kick ass
Claude you got it sir thank thank you
boss love can bloom on the
battlefield I I actually that's I that's
funny though I did manage to buy the old
Legacy Collection for PS3 because of you
I'm doing I'm this in your [\h__\h] name
let's go I will see it through to the
end let's [\h__\h] go sens
07 thank you so much pomu you're you're
you're the goat keep in touch thanks
love you to death byebye bye see you
tomorrow see you tomorrow good Lu with
Pokemon thank
you man that guy's such a
clown the only reason I could hold it
together was because I was watching his
fugie put it back on you guys
though we're
[Music]
matching clown Mino stop it keeps
getting worse and
worse let's see the next person see if
she's
available there's still quite a few
people one two oh hop in whenever you're
ready
oh hello oh my God hi hi
hi oh let me turn you up there you go oh
sorry I'm also I should probably sit up
that's the polite thing to do sorry I
was slouching you're okay my back the
street I'm sitting like an L yes perfect
very good very good yes oh yeah an
L practicing I'm trying I'm trying
really hard not to
cry it's like
you know that that Meme that guy sitting
in like the classroom where he's like
his the veins are like on his neck and
his and he's like squinching really hard
that's like me right now I'm trying
really hard not just not to cry I can
already see someone photoshopping like
your hat on to to that good don't give
them don't give them
idea how are you holding up you've been
talking for a while are you feeling okay
is you have water and food and stuff
yeah I'm good I'm good okay very good
very good I mean I don't know what to
tell you that there isn't hasn't already
been said man it's like I don't know I
remember when you told us that you're
leaving a little while back I bro was
I'm not going to lie I genely thought
you were joking I'm like H that's funny
wait
what it's just I just generally didn't
see it
coming it doesn't help that when I like
posted the announcement I was like hey
guys I'm leaving you're so casual about
it
and like I think like Petra is the first
to respond and you're just like I'm like
what do you mean I said
like I was like hold up wait what was
that supposed to [\h__\h] mean I'm sorry
it has to be a joke right I didn't know
how to say it so
seriously I mean well that's kind of
like that's very on brand of you you
know something I've always admired about
you how like you can handle things that
are serious or sometimes sad with like
your brand of humor which makes the pill
so much easier to swallow honestly and
like it takes a lot of like mental
fortitude and mental strength to be able
to make something like that palatable
you know so like I know there's a lot
that I admire about y honestly it's like
it's like I don't know what can I say I
mean people like you are just kind of a
like I consider you like a a once in a
lifetime kind of person as in like I
only get to meet people
like
I'm not sad I'm not
sad okay clown clown clown yeah clown
clown
clown okay okay we're good but uh people
like you basically occur once in a
lifetime I don't get to meet people like
you very often and I think that people
like you um you're just a very rare
person to find and so I consider it a
one of the highest honors to have been
able to be in the same brand as
you okay we're
fine we're fine we're fine I'm not sad
I'm not sad at all um it's like I don't
know you you set the standard in
innovation in the Ian streaming scene
honestly I mean not to say that others
aren't also Innovative but you've
changed it and contributed to it
contributed to it in ways that that's
distinctly you and I feel like you
really push the scene to be where it is
today and that's that's just so
admirable and just so [\h__\h] cool
honestly and I I hope you can rest easy
knowing that you're basically impossible
to forget I listen I don't have a stem I
don't have a stem degree or anything but
like I hereby clinically diagnose you
with um with uh being an icon the legend
the moment and that kind of thing it's
it's it's going to be hard to forget
what you've done for not just nii
sanjian but the EnV to being scene as a
whole you know and so it's physically
impossible to forget all the
contributions you've done for everyone
and everything over the past few years
and you have every right to be proud and
honestly if I were you i' would be
insufferable you have so many bragging
rights you can brag forever
honestly you have so many [\h__\h]
bragging rights I implore you please
brag please please like when you get the
chance to I implo you to do so because
not many people have been able to pull
off what you've what you've done
honestly and so like you have every
every right to be extremely unbearable
and how much you going to brag about it
so please do
so it's I I'm trying I'm sorry if I'm
I'm shotgun really fast I I don't want
to eat up too much of your time and
there's a lot of people in line um it's
also like you're also just a good friend
to many but you're also an inspiration
to countless more honestly and and I
kind of
okay
okay um I also just admire you because
you know the the old 9 to-5 office work
isn't for everyone you know and you
inspired me a lot to break out of that
and pursue something I actually care
[Music]
about and um you know there's more to
life than just quote unquote getting by
and sometimes finding happiness means
that you have to like you know make the
big steps take the big moves to get what
you want and work hard for it right mhm
and so um thank you for being such an
inspiration in that way as well and I'm
sad you're leaving but I know that your
next call to happiness and the next
chapter of your life is just taking you
elsewhere from here and I respect that
and and I admire you for taking that
step as well but you're such an
inspiration to everyone and we'll all do
our best to take care of the Ian branch
in your absence and uh remember your
legacy here of course I'll I promise to
keep people on the Minecraft server I'll
I'll harass people start off and okay
yeah I'll make sure I'll I'll make you
the lead stripper at my strip club in
Minecraft okay oh my God it's an honor
of course of course I'll have I'll
always have Diamond Stacks right next to
you okay
just a thank you a I know um yeah we're
we're also Kindred Spirits in the in the
working
field and you know I
know I know for sure that the you
know
um how do I say like I I saw like your
your I saw like clips of you talking
about how you know everyone in Ian is so
special and I 100% agree with that you
know like you you have carved your you
know your community and you have such a
loyal fan base and um it's like I've
told to everyone else too like
without without not even just my fans
but without everyone how how like
encouraging everyone is in Ian it would
be really difficult to want to pursue so
many different kinds of projects
and and you know um push towards you
know more creativity or just anything
like you know if if everyone was wasn't
as incredible as they were and you're
you were 100% a part of that a you are
so funny you always put 100% into what
you do like you know even just like as
an example from the other day when we
were doing VR chat and you were like I'm
going to be this character and you were
like role playing 100% is so funny like
girl you're you are you're you're a dork
affectionate uh only you're allowed to
call me that okay only only you can
okay and just thank you Po and just like
on a personal level just to be fully
transparent and honest on on the
timeline right here when I joined Ian I
was thoroughly intimidated because I
respect you and what you do so much I
was like oh my God it's [\h__\h] Pur rain
puff holy [\h__\h] I you hop in V see the
Luna on I was oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and then like lo and behold you're
the most down to earth most relaxed
layback chill person in the entire world
like you're also a dork though like
[Applause]
I this ain't about
me listen I think we're both Kindred
office ladies and also Kindred dorks at
this point I think I think we I think
we're on that level now I guess
so no but you're just so welcoming it
made me feel at home immediately and
that kind of thing and it's like even
though I've always been a bit shy to
approach some members you've always been
very receptive and always chill to talk
to whenever you're available and you're
easily available as well and so I I
appreciate that and oh no I
just one of my greatest regrets now is I
I didn't manage to squeeze you into a d
and d game yet oh
yeah yeah it's okay though uh do I have
your permission to write you in as a
final boss of course oh my God I'd be
honored the honor is all mine no I
remember when you um when you put us
when you like what you did like the
character sheets of all of us and
everything too oh yeah that was a while
ago it was a long time ago yeah but yeah
I got you right not what I classed you
as but I hope I got you right I think I
remember feeling like it was
correct good good that's all I'm not
very well versed in D and D stuff so I
couldn't tell you the specifics but
listen I know there may be some people
watching us right now but don't let them
know but it's it's some nerd [\h__\h] of
course it's complex it's like it's it's
like Giga nerd [\h__\h] so like yeah it's
hard it's hard to get get a grasp on
even I be I barely have a grasp on it on
the DM
so but I don't want to eat up too much
of your time and I feel like I I very
clogged up your stream so I'll I'll let
you go thank you I am thank for coming
thank you I I one day I'll I'll come
find you I'll I'll I'll get out of jail
I'm on Pro right now make sure I stay
out of jail and I'll give you a proper
hug I know oh my gosh we still haven't
met yeah dang it we'll find a time for
we'll find a time we'll find a way we
will We Will We Will um yeah cuz I have
that Pomchi that I sculpted a while back
I never got to give it to you yes oh my
gosh okay we have to have it happen then
of course of course we'll start
arranging we'll start planning for it
then yeah are you available to play
tomorrow or
oh yeah I've uh I I'm technically on the
clock but they don't know that so it's
okay it's okay if I just if I just if I
I work from home tomorrow they're not
going to notice it's okay if you have to
hop in and out you know do you know
whatever no I'll just tell them that
like my arm fell off or something it's
okay it'll be fine yeah it's the
plague I was like oh oh sorry guys got
the plague he is I'm so sorry sorry
about that yeah
I'm going to miss you but you take care
and I'll see you tomorrow thank you for
your time thanks I see you tomorrow okay
love you bye byee love
[Music]
you oh I forgot the
right I think I think next is Vox it's
just a it's just a British flag Emoji
what does this mean
[Music]
I think it's
him um I'm going to add him yeah it's
box
okay if he's still
[Music]
around that guy British that British guy
oh be right there no
problem
lra and Shu have been keeping track of
the list of
people
British the British guy was just the
British flag was
like I guess there's there's just him
right so
[Music]
funny a man how are you guys holding up
are we okay we're good everything's
fine
I'm doing
okay I have
tea and
coffee we are not okay we're crying
we're a mess yo
what I guess it's good that I'm not a
mess because I have to if I can't keep
myself together then the stream is just
going to be a poop shoot you
know
someone has to keep it together a little
bit dehydrating through my eyes make
sure you drink enough water we in
shambles how is he even awake right now
that's why I was that's why I was like I
wonder if he's even still
here but he
typed oh my my gosh my throat is
starting to get like I have a cough
doesn't it like hurts when I not when I
talk I'm
okay also be sure to have enough sodium
yeah get some crackers or something
we're here for you girl thank
you thank you thank you Murphy accept
love and praise
loser
[Music]
thanks I don't know how to ever do it oh
hello
hello hello hi Vox Mr M
Lord hello I'm quite sleep deprived at
the moment uh I don't know you don't
have to be here long it's okay what what
do you put this nose on me for cuz
everyone gets one we're clowning oh my
my God I'm
clowning I feel like a feel like a feel
like a clown right now I don't mind I'm
not particularly tired but what I am is
confused although this is true um for
essentially every day yeah um why are we
confused
well things are constantly happening
aren't they yeah
yeah I mean that's yeah things don't
stop happening they don't they don't
they start coming and they don't stop
coming you know I don't want to think
about how they don't stop coming
listen it's really difficult to know
what to say in a situation like this
because I feel like I don't know I feel
like whenever when when all of us got
like you know we we got the message we
found out that you were that you were
moving on it was like it was like
what was like
huh I would say a good I would say that
I'd say I don't know for me it was like
that's a good thing because I know that
you like you know you're moving on for
for a good reason and that you have like
really thought about it it's just I
don't know I'm sat here and I'm
still even after like anime impulse like
with the big emotional Diamond City
Lights with the chant that like
practically knocked the speakers out
like I'm surprised that those
microphones still function properly um
it still kind of has hasn't really set
in yet like I feel like with um because
because with uh with with mister for
example like I knew a long time in
advance before he before he graduated it
kind of felt like I accepted it and I
had like made my peace with it a long
time before for me I'm not I I don't
know if I don't know if I'm ready for
this it's it feels it feels so new and
it feels so weird and I know that like
we um after like the and I'll get on to
it but like after the Shakespeare collab
like we didn't really collab all that
much yeah but it's still you know I I
feel I feel like especially kind of
early on um I really looked up to the
way that you were able to be so creative
with your streams constantly and I
always thought like man how did she do
it it was always so like inspiring for
me especially stuff like um well just
like like all of the OBS Wizardry that
you've been able to do and like always
putting putting stuff together and
having all of these scenes play out and
stuff and with theater kids right and so
when it came to like my when it came to
like the the date stream that I did
where it was like all of these different
scenes and stuff it was like yeah you
can do all of this and I always really
respect you for like being able to push
those boundaries and trying to find like
okay well we've done this before how
about we do it in this way how about we
do it in that way and it's difficult to
come up with I don't know I I sound very
vague at the moment it's because I don't
know I don't know left from right up
from down or now you're good you're good
I tried to say tried to say North from
South I said nth from South
that's get some sleep man I don't know
now it's like I'm not tired I'm just
confused like I said but it's like and
also I will say it's like when we did um
when we did that uh that that
Shakespeare collab that was like I would
say that was like a really formative
moment for me um because that was like
so early uh after like I was still like
fresh new face and and like lilite like
I I still to this day kind of feel I get
like a little bit Star Struck sometimes
I'm like no way it's weird I'm never
going to get used to it it's like it's
like lelite especially being like when I
first found out about nii I was doing my
research of like H this looks cool it
was like lelite were the first ones I
was like looking at I was like man these
guys are really funny this is really
cool and now it's I I I I never really
got used to it I feel like I got used to
it with it with like everybody else but
never with lelite and so a member of
lelite um graduating
especially um one who I did that the
fact that our our our one-on-one collab
was learning well not learning fully but
like performing the entirety of much to
do about nothing with that was so crazy
after after we watched like the film
adaptation and we're like making notes
of like what the hell is going on
that was an absurd amount of prep for a
collab like that was was so dumb it was
like yeah I me it was lot of fun I i'
never done anything like that before you
know even like I guess like even as a
theater kid still though it was I I
don't know it was cool it was like a
really neat I I I knew for sure that you
would be down for it and it was really
cool that you like kind of were like
yeah let's do it and we were just oh
yeah oh and and coming up with all of
the like that morning um like before we
started like setting up all of the stuff
like in OBS the different how do I
differentiate the characters uh name
tags and I was making these little name
tags like swap between and okay I'm I
can't remember what all the characters
and that called
Horatio um oh
yeah I think that was it I remember
Horatio and that's about it I I might be
wrong maybe the orig I I don't even
remember the any names I'll be honest I
remember we had a post credit scene with
a dream works like dance sequence to and
I'm a believer that was my favorite part
personally
absolutely we we really shreked it
[Music]
up that we did that we did um so I don't
know it's um like I said like it still
hasn't really set in so it kind of feels
like I'm not having the proper emotional
reaction to it like I can remember it um
like like like back stage anime impulse
like like with the tiger chant I
remember a load of people
like like a load of people load of
people are crying and I was and I was
like it's I think it I think it just
hasn't set in yet and I feel like it
will like there's going to there's going
to be some point where I'm like man a
member of Lite is moving on and I don't
want I don't want to make you feel bad
it's just wild to have so much history
and the but a good thing as well that
you feel confident in you know moving on
to the next chapter of your life after
having done
so much um for for everyone who came who
came after you
like uh like I think also getting
involved in the song project like I
always mess up the
pronun getting don't worry everyone
trips over even me everyone literally is
like it's a tricky one it was wonderful
for me especially because like I've
always struggled with um you know uh
nihongo and uh PR pronoun even with
lyrics and romaji it always takes me a
good and it did with that one like a
good six to seven attempts at every
single line of me being
like I've been killing it honestly
recently with all the covers and stuff
though like I appreciate it the Cody one
was so awesome thank you but I feel like
that all kind of kicked off with with
oton naru and like finding room to
include everybody and like giving
everybody you know kind of equal footing
and all of these different lines to do
and it felt like even though I was even
though it was um even though it was
tough like getting given these lines
that was tough to pronounce it really
kind of forced me to learn something and
then I can't really imagine a better
sort of event you know everybody being
involved in this one song and a song
that is just so uplifting that's Our
Song now we've claimed it it belongs to
us uh and every time I hear that song
I'm going to be like ah there they are
yeah that's us I think so for me too
it's going to bring like I'll hear it
like just the very beginning notes and
be like man the rush of memories and all
the good moments
yeah you know you know you know
something that's something that's funny
is that like you've mentioned that you
that you want to like kind of go back to
go back to school or or whatever it is
you're going to do next um I I I I
personally think like it's it's a really
nice idea and I'm I'm really excited for
you honestly thanks the thought of
actually the thought of actually like
graduating hasn't really crossed my mind
but sometimes I do like wonder what it
would be like if I if like I wasn't it
if I wasn't here you know what I would
like to be doing and also trying to
remember what it's like when you don't
have the sort of like that sort of
pressure with the job because there is
like a fair amount of just stuff you
have stuff you get used to when you do
this I think especially like being hyper
aware of what people are saying about
you online and just really being exposed
to this much internet you know it's like
you get hooked up you got an IV drip of
pure data just being fed straight into
your blood and it's and it's it's a lot
you know and I think especially when I
spend um spend more time around normal
people it's kind of crazy just how like
I don't know just just how ordinary like
that most people's lives are and how
they're so not concerned about all of
the things that like chronically online
people get worried about and it's just
really bizarre to get used to and it's
like oh oh this guy is just the only
thing going on in his mind is what he's
going to have for dinner tonight oh I
can't remember the last time my my like
my thoughts were that linear everything
everything just goes through a filter of
like what is what is this what is that
what what what implication does this
have for this so so I just I don't know
I'm really looking forward to um to
hearing about what you managed to get up
to in you know kind of without a lot of
like all of the thoughts that go on when
when you're in this position because it
can be a lot and I don't think anyone
who who signs up for this is really
prepared for how how that makes you feel
so I just it's it's an exciting prospect
to think of like a really fresh start
you know something that's truly in a in
an entirely different space I just I
don't know I think it's a really
wonderful idea and so you know no I I
haven't even really thought about that I
don't know I really love streaming so to
me it's kind of like when I wake up and
I'm like oh what am I streaming today oh
nothing I don't it's I I
can't honestly
fathom I know I will eventually but I
can't fathom like having Normie normal
not Normie but like you know those kind
of like daily thoughts currently I'm
just like I don't even I don't even know
but you know
yeah no yeah it is weird yeah it's like
yeah because it's sort of this I mean I
mean I I I had a thought and then I had
another thought and now and now neither
of them makes sense it's like um how
well really you know the whole thing
about um about streaming is that it kind
of like takes over not just your work
life but also your personal life as well
so something that I kind of found is
that I almost I like I almost can't
really listen to music anymore because
every time I listen to music it like it
immediately becomes like ooh what would
a song cover of this one sound like oh
maybe I should do this one for a karaoke
or oh maybe this one would suit this
like idea for a scene I've got or
something like that and then suddenly
it's like immediately when I listen to
music I'm thinking about work and it's
like man that separation is really is
really difficult to find and I kind of I
don't know if I
ever if I ever um was I think I think I
I I think I think like you like if I
ever was to leave I don't think that it
would that I think that like for me
that's enough internet for one lifetime
I think I would I think I would just dip
and go and like live in the woods or
something like that because it's like
definitely given that a thought
yes you want to go from all the way
online to as far offline as you can
possibly go like I I want I want to I
want to go camping I want to go to the
mountains I want to live my Kiki
delivery service dream
exactly Oh
that's oh God that's
brilliant like my jibbly dream that's
what you know I always think that's like
the ideal lifestyle you know
just actually becomes a gorilla yeah
that's what I would do yeah you can
actually become a gorilla go to the
jungle and swing from Vine to vine and
then I realize how tiring that is and
how and how tough that is on the arms
and then I would just kind of like sit
in the middle of the Jungle and be like
man how did I get here no you have to
have a you have to have like a a group
group of gorillas accept you as their
own oh that's brilliant I mean the
problem the problem with that I mean you
know the thing about gorillas and sort
of like monkeys and apes in general is
that like if you breathe wrong they'll
get really mad and like might tear your
head off or something like that so it's
a risk I would do it for the for like
the comedy Factor but I like I'd be a
bit worried especially chimpanzees like
they're so they're so aggressive so
easily agitated it's really scary not
someone just saying I think you die Vox
yeah I probably would i' go to the
gorillas and I would be like hey guys
how's it going my fellow
[Laughter]
gorillas just's it going tear you apart
like a doll like a stuff this is
reminded me of a meme I so the Lo the
the the gorilla he literally has a
reference for everything at the Lost
16-year-old before turning them into a
red paste what the hell
yeah yeah it was this hypothetical
someone posted a gorilla versus six
16-year-olds with baseball bats who wins
and uh and then and then they responded
with this
image what the hell
St the gorilla would look at me he would
stay he would say stand he would say
stand proud and I would then become the
red paste but if anything I feel like
you know with my color palette I think
red paste makes sense if if you get by a
gorilla would you be like a sort of a
sort of like a a blue greeny paste or
like a a blonde paste probably like a
greeny paste yeah probably a a green
paste yeah that's brilliant and then you
and then you could be and then and then
you could be putting someone's
paintbrush and they could and they could
paint it's a lovely exclusive color you
know oh yeah
like well Vox it was a pleasure I got to
get through the other people before my
next stream of course yeah I don't want
to talk your off but but you also need
to go to sleep so no I okay yeah I
probably do you should I I'm I'm really
grateful to have gotten the chance to
talk to you again and uh I just know
that whatever future awaits you like
you've brought so much creativity and so
much energy and passion and really you
know there's only it's really it's
really strange cuz I think that you're
especially unique in like in like a lot
of ways and
the and what you've brought I don't
think anyone else could really bring so
I feel like you know there's going to be
a big hole that's going to take a lot of
that's going to take a lot of filling
but we'll be all right and I just want
you to know that like wherever you go
I'm sure we'll have a pomu sized hole
ready to be filled and it's um so yeah I
just I I'm I'm sure that you're going to
have a wonderful time and uh I can't
wait to hear about what you do cuz I'm
sure it's going to be fascinating and
kind of scary
probably thanks Fox yeah I think
probably terrifying but we'll see very
good I'm ready to wreak havoc wreak
havoc wherever you go all right I'll see
you soon and as always uh don't look
directly into the bright lights because
that's hell that's hell know you're
there all right see you good night
Vox Mr my Lord everybody that
guy
um Mr my
Lord next person oh my gosh just
realized I have a half hour if I have to
extend that's totally okay cuz I still
have 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 eight
people we's see if this person's still
around and if
they're
oh
hello B Master
hello hi Hi how are how are you even
though you've been talking for six and a
half hours I'm good how are
you I've been playing League of Legends
of course you
have we never got to play one League
game before you left Aster I'm going to
be honest we've never would have played
a league
[Laughter]
game I understand I'm sorry I'm sorry I
don't even I don't know even if AA asked
me I don't think I would be playing a
league game what has she
tried I don't think so
God damn
ITA maybe one day when you guys meet
somewhere who knows who
knows I S I think this might be our
first time like talking one-on-one
in like a stream
right it is the the the only time we've
interacted with each other was through
Discord text yeah or uh a Discord VC or
that one time in Minecraft that one time
in Minecraft that's so crazy
yeah I'm sorry I didn't get to hang out
with you or talk to you at all I'm just
super shy no me too don't worry I am too
I that's my fault as like a senpai you
know but um I also like I don't mean
this in like a negative way I feel like
we have really different interests like
you are league and Apex and I I always
I'm like I can't do those things so yeah
yeah teach their own I understand yeah
no but you got you got your thing you
you're and you're really good at it so
you
know well I always silently lurk here
and there on your streams and what you
do I'm pretty I'm pretty aware of what
everyone does Prett pretty much but oh
my God uh I did want to say one thing
okay uh though I never really talked to
you uh I've I actually got introduced to
nii Sanji because of you uh so before I
even got in here I I actually watch
quite a bit of you and I still
remember um the stream that actually got
me into nii Sanji that uh that you were
uh doing it was with Al uhhuh um do you
remember that stream you did where or
maybe it was A's stream I forgot which
stream it was but it's basically you
took over A's Minecraft
stream oh yes how could I forget yeah
and then and then you went all demonic I
laughed so hard it was it was really
funny see all that and how you kept role
playing it was awesome like all the
effects oh that that wasn't role play
what it it was Role Play right you were
just pretending right no no I was
actually I was 100%
serious so so all those signs with
please AA play Minecraft with me in
blood yeah that was just like paint
right I I've sacrificed
you know I sacrificed people to take
their blood and write that in her
[Music]
room
oh yeah you
know you know just normal fairy things
don't worry about
it my okay uh
anyways yeah uh you you introduc me nii
Sanji and you know I watched a lot and
it's crazy to be here with you but I
never actually got to do anything with
you and it sad and uh I'm sorry no what
no don't even be no I I think you know
we uh we are such a huge group and um
you know some people are you know like
you and you'll play Apex with people
like you and fan you got your little you
got your group and everything
like um it's yeah and I like I said I'm
I'm extremely shocked and I'm really bad
it's an it's not an excuse obviously
because um I should be better about it
it's just hard for me to reach out to
people and I think for me I was like I
don't really know what to reach out to
you about you know but you like you know
the arcadians are
are a super loyal bunch I have I have I
have lurked in your streams sometimes so
no way yeah so I'm not and I'm not just
saying that um just kind of like oh
what's you know what's what's he up to
you know and stuff so
[Music]
um but yeah uh it's it's like I I feel
bad but I don't want you to feel bad
it's my it's not it should have been on
me to reach out more so I'm really sorry
about that um but I know that you're
you're you literally you're you're doing
it you're you're doing it well I'm I I'm
trying yeah as long as you're having fun
you know that's that's the most
important thing is to just you know have
fun enjoy your community and you know if
it's not fun then that's like don't let
it become like a chore or anything just
kind of do what makes you happy and then
people will you know come to you because
of that because they see that you're
passionate and happy about
it
how you how you so positive I need some
of
that I need the pomu
energy I give you Pomo
energy I felt that at the at the hop
concert I I I felt a little bit
emotional uh it's actually really hard
for me to be emotional but that that
like it hit hit my heartstrings and then
seeing that clip of uh Gino fiber yeah
it's crazy
uh yeah and seeing all that I also want
to say I forgot to say this too but
thank you for going out of your comfort
zone and singing with us in
U I mean I didn't really do much I was
just I was like a background singer no
but I mean like you know I you're and
your your singing has really improved so
much with your covers and everything so
just keep at it I will actually do plan
to do one in the future uh you're
definitely
one of the few people that inspire me to
pursue the singing stuff like obviously
including like Ren so Ren and you and
like others but especially during hop
concert uh you know you just love
singing so much and I aspire to at least
get to an ounce of that level I don't
know singing is so fun I never actually
thought I would get into singing it is
so much fun like seriously just have fun
with it just that's honestly ly for
everything it's just like if you don't
enjoy it like there's no point in doing
it there's not enough time for True for
you to like feel forcing yourself to do
something you
know I I will do my best thank you for
inspiring me yeah keep
out you're super creative always
positive even through you know
difficulties hardworking I know you're
gonna do amazing stuff in your next
chapter forever we going to do we're all
going to miss you of course yeah was
been a lot of fun
so it's not going to be the same no
it'll be
[Music]
[Laughter]
fun oh I really appreciate you coming
today thank you yeah oh uh I forgot to
mention to um before I peace out cuz I
know you don't have that much time yeah
sorry it's okay I got to leave to too uh
I actually cannot make it to the crab
game tomorrow cuz I'll be out with
family but so I wanted this to be my
last time I talk to you oh oh yeah oh my
gosh a
no it's okay no oh my gosh well then
even more so thank you for making the
time to come by and yeah like yeah I
know we didn't talk so much
but I really appreciate it I mean this
entire composition means a lot I'll take
it to heart uh you inspire everybody
here so we we'll take a page out of all
your
books my books are sloppily written I
don't read but I'll read just for
you okay yes read my I I don't know my
it's a it's a
cookbook I will cook so there's not very
many words in it you're
okay yeah there's some fanfic in there
also love a it was so good anation so
good thank you go watch
everybody yeah it was awesome talking to
you have a good one we see you later a
thank you I'm going to miss
you
byebye
bye ah I feel I feel so bad like I said
I I should
I I should have been better about
reaching
out I'm sorry
Aster I'm so
sorry but
uh um okay uh next person okay I'm
definitely going to have to push back
the stream but that's
okay we'll see how far we get before I
um I push it back sorry
guys let's see if this person's
around if she's here
[Music]
don't say sorry oh okay I'm not sorry
it's a gorilla stream
anyway
[Music]
Petra who drew this your
fugie me oh my God it's so
cute it was inspired by your drawing
really oh no oh no
it looks like my mouth is like really
wide open and I have one big tooth
yeah wait I like it more
now wait it's kind of
awesome oh my God thank you this is a
collab art collab art collab from the
pomy the pompy oh my God it's an
honor P how are
you I'm good how are you I'm
good I've just been watching your to
yeah just kind of vibe are you are you
doing okay yeah I'm okay few hours I
know yeah I won't I won't take up too
much of your time I know you have like a
bunch of people still waiting it's okay
wanted the chat yeah I was really happy
to chat
I think I'm gonna miss
you I think you're also one of the
people that like I've talked to most out
like outside but you have always helped
me so much petrick I'm eternally
grateful I next time we meet I am I'm
taking you out girl you're going to get
you want a drink I'll buy you a drink if
you want if you want pizza I'll buy you
Pizza I'm just really happy that you
know I could help you with anything and
that you trust me enough to help help
you you know like when you came to me
with the cata video as well like is it
okay for me to like work on something
this important I was like oh my God no
you help me so much thank you multiple
times oh my gosh I wish I could do
anything to repay you no okay then you
have to come and hang out with
me that's that's the repayment and I'll
pay for all your things no oh not that
part
yeah yeah I feel like we've had a lot of
like really fun times off stream
actually I know I know he do so much
more off stream I
know oh my God singing I was like
looking back at our videos the other day
and we were like singing in that that
Ferris wheel yeah we were singing so
loud and you you guys didn't realize we
were already back at like where we
started so everyone could hear us
screaming at the top of our
leg so funny yeah and and the Cave the
Cave the Cave we never got to go to I
sometimes it still comes up in my
recommendations when I look for
restaurants and I'm like no no way not
that one they're going to know not that
one they're going to know I know I'm
going to show up and they're going to
they're going to kick me out like have a
picture of you on their wall and they're
like don't let this pengu
this penguin is
blacklisted yeah oh my God I saw your
music video as well yeah I I was getting
like emotional cuz I really love this oh
my God yeah when you first sent it to me
as well when I was adding the subs for
your 3D I was like this song is so cute
it's so
awesome yeah and so like I was you know
like I I learned this I learned to know
the song really well from like you know
making the video I was like singing
along I I was no it was so awesome I
singing along and like getting emotional
and then
the I don't even know what to call
it m son
yeah M I was like what I really wanted
something that no one would
expect no that was the that was the
best best best part
yeah no
no I could not that was so perfect and I
saw I saw people were debating in like
in in the server which
M no it's my M son the greatest okay
okay okay I my head Cannon is that it's
actually all of our mon son together
together yeah they're each doing a
different part
yeah I have like a photo of our Min son
looking like The
Avengers like they're standing there
like they're oh yeah yeah a in the
Discord saying can we please go to the
cave no no a you don't you had to be
there we walked down like the most
sketchy like it was so scary actually it
was SP yeah it wasn't even the main
street of kabako like the main street is
still okay but the that the side alley
was that was nauy yeah it was freaky I'm
like shaking my head right now just
realize no one can see I'll shake it for
you
yeah cute oh my God yeah this was the
kabuko back alley restaurant
am I don't
know she said after anartica cave is
nothing oh my God yeah I'm so I was so
happy to see all your pictures from
Antarctica as well and all the
penguins than you for visiting my
relatives even if they were stinky oh
gosh Petra they were really really
smelly I keep tell I keep trying to
educate them on hygiene and they just
stand in their poo all day they don't
know I think it's because they don't get
visitors very often they don't think
about it you know yeah I keep trying to
tell them but they don't listen I'm
sorry I thought they would be like I
don't know like oh my gosh someone's
coming to f us oh it's pet okay wait
wait I need you to I need you to confirm
though do I smell nice oh yeah yeah yeah
you guys Petra smells nice I've SM every
time she kind of gets close to me I'm
wait what
wait
yeah okay um um she smells
sometimes [\h__\h] oh wait sorry I thought I
muted on
Discord
hey
not hey hey hey hey hey hey I was I
needed you to I needed you to you know
um deny the allegations because now
everyone's like pomu said Penguins stink
a lot and I'm I'm I've try to you know
I'm like I'm not like the other Penguins
maybe you should do a shower stream and
prove that you are bathing so that they
well then then it's impossible for you
to be stinky I've actually even thinking
of trying to do another another bath
stream so maybe I will yeah oh God it's
so hard
though yeah I know it's kind of a pain
in the butt to set up I know I feel like
I'm going to break something yeah
yeah I don't want to take up too much of
your time though cuz you've already been
streaming for so long so I just wanted
to say you know I feel like everyone's
been saying this but you really are just
such an
inspiration and you're like I just feel
like you're such an like such a special
existence and you know no one will ever
be like pomu pomu is the one and only
pomu we might all be pomu but you are
the pomu
and sorry I'm so awkward I'm bad with
words but you know when I when I
auditioned for Nan G en um I honestly
never really watched English
streamers I just like nii Sanji and you
know I so essentially I think lalite
were the first like English streamers or
vtubers I ever watched
properly and you guys kind of are like
you guys were the you guys set the
standard for you know what me and I
guess the rest of us really would
do and I I'm just so thankful that it
was you and lalite
because I think you guys really changed
the trajectory
of you know nian Gan or even like
English B tubing guys had a part in you
know changing that scene and changing my
life as well and I just wanted to say
how grateful I am and
and it just I'm so bad with the words
but I just really wanted you to know how
important you are to me and you know
just as a friend as well I feel like
every time I hang out with you it's so
fun and I feel like we I don't know I
feel like we're always laughing about
something something yeah we're always
doing we're always feel sometimes we're
in a big group and the two of us are
just laughing over something that no one
else noticed I
know it's all he like the two of us and
like so true I was just looking back at
my pictures and I just I took a photo of
the Bobba we were drinking mhm and you
took a photo of me taking you take the
photo I still have it and and then as
retaliation I took a photo of you just
holding the I have like this really
blurry picture of you that I don't know
why I
took I I just never deleted it because I
was like ah this is a nice
memory we're going to keep that photo
forever I'm going to keep every photo I
have for you forever and ever and print
them out and stick them on my walls and
kiss them before bed every night I'm my
gosh you going to make my face into like
a wallpaper on your wall sure yeah okay
I'll do the same too and we should get
those we should get those you know they
have like those couple things where if
one of the couples is holding it like it
lights up or like makes a oh yeah yeah
so every time you're touching the wall
it'll light up on my side and then I'll
touch the wall okay okay
okay you're going to be like why is it
lighting up all the time what is she
doing or you're going to wonder that
because I you know oh my God oh my gosh
the batteries are going to run out and
then you're going to be like because
I've I've been touching it for so long
and then you're going to be like why is
she never touching it again who all
right all right it's I'm going to look
one up right now okay I'm the link okay
gotcha awesome okay I got the link
awesome yeah okay okay but you you know
you promised you would come hang out
with me again yeah you know even though
I won't be able to talk to you on stream
anymore I know we're going to be able to
talk offline and hang out so yeah I'm
just really going to miss having you in
mean I feel like you're know truly an
Irreplaceable existence so I really like
how Vox said we going to leave a Pomo
shaped
hole I just like imagine like like your
up cut out of your body with like the
ribbon and everything just like in the
middle of the office you know that
Juno M manga oh my God yeah this hole
was made for me that's my God
no but I I really feel what he was I
feel like there's a PMA shaped hole in
my heart already no but you know if I
feel a little bit better knowing we can
still hang out whenever you come visit
me which you will right yes okay it's a
promise
okay thank you you break the promise you
have to drink a th000 needles oh how do
you drink needles I don't know that's
what they say in Japanese oh okay thank
you P thank you for everything thank you
so so so so much
thank you I love you so much we'll hang
out more yeah byebye
[Music]
byebye little
pet I'm starting to get hungry so going
to have to get some food uh don't worry
I have just stuff that I can like easily
make um probably at the end of the
stream I'll get some food and eat it and
then start the next stream so
um okay next person
[Music]
oh yeah I'm so glad that like I I pushed
for that I don't to collab so that we
could talk during that time because oh
my gosh so many people want to talk to
you
yeah I man i' I've been listening like
since I woke up and I'm just like I've
cried so many times just listening oh my
gosh we're just we're just we're just
being clowns we're clown we're having
fun clown yeah I'll give you a nose too
oh uh the squeaky
nose
yeah oh my gosh it look so
[Laughter]
good oh I am the joke now
I'm the
Joker
oh say bye I can't believe tomorrow is
the last day I
know I know the times for the games
aren't so good for you if you can't make
it it's totally okay I know no I'm I'm
putting an a lot which one did I sign up
for again I
forgot it's okay you can come to any
single one of them whatever well I will
definitely be awake by crab game 100%
okay we'll do that at least the C crab
game yeah
yeah I'm glad we got to talk so much
though
recently yeah I'm really glad like I
think especially recently I've been like
bothering you
extra you've been like sending me videos
and I haven't been able to it no it's
okay I know you're busy too you
know and I'm really glad that we were
able to hang out in Japan as well yeah
so yeah you're so
awesome yeah and I'm still going to keep
bothering you even after so yeah you're
not going to escape I don't want to
escape yeah well no I know I know we'll
keep talking so I'm I I feel I feel very
comfortable you know like and
yeah it just yeah it's sad that we could
never dance or I
know but oh no I really wanted to dance
and said by so badly I know me
too one one day when I get the when I
get my 3D reveal I'm going to I'm going
to go on stage and I'm going to think of
you while I'm
dancing yes think of me if you need like
a a backup dancer that is like um maybe
like Kuroko you could have me oh my gosh
oh my gosh time to ask
my they'll never know it's me
they'll never know they'll never know
they'll never know oh my gosh
wait
[Music]
wait are you okay I'm okay all right all
right I notes it down I notes It
Down
Yay yeah no I I think I I replied to you
a tweet about it but
like I I hope I'll be able to like you
know keep the the eye idle love within
at least Ian from here on out as well I
know I probably would do as well as you
do but like I'm going to do my best okay
and I never dies down yeah yes if
anybody if there's anybody that I trust
it's
you oh my God yeah and yeah no you're
okay it's okay
yeah no I I like I said and you are the
hardest the hardest working you you are
always cooking you're always working
so I know yeah know I'm really glad that
we were able to do the the duet song for
from the from the a
cafe I'm so glad and we have to go to
make cup C together how did how were we
in Japan and not I know we were going to
go yeah the timing was just
so but next time for
sure for sure next time we have to
yeah yeah I know I know for sure that
this is you know it's the last that will
be together on stream but not you know
together in general yeah second last
yeah yeah second last yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah second last second last yeah
not yet not yet you're the that soon
well last time we'll be oneon-one you
know
yeah I'll keep sending you Idol videos
what's it called oh yeah I'll keep
sending you on as well you know I'll
keep bothering you every every other
day maybe even every day you'll be in
stream and I'll be like mine stop I must
show you this sorry I don't have a
stream so I
I I need attention now
yeah no please anytime I'll always reply
as soon as I possibly can as soon as I
see it yeah yeah and like you know I've
kind of I've kind of told my my audience
that you're going to be in my next cover
oh oh yeah I wasn't sure if I should say
anything or no no no you're the I think
you're the only person that I've
actually like been saying that is
definitely part of it oh my God and it's
such an awesome song I can't wait oh my
gosh yeah I just I was like no you know
when when I reached out to you to sing
the song and I was just like oh I'm
planning to release it here and then you
told me I was like no yeah actually
Maran was one of the first like before I
told everybody in Ian I told Marine kind
of earlier because not just because of
it but I was also like yeah I don't know
I yeah yeah but so like even though I've
had so long to like kind of
kind of get over it not really but like
you know like get become become
like understand and get past it all it's
still
like no you know yesterday yesterday I
was on YouTube and it like recommended
me Eon by you and I was like no I keep
getting comments people are just like
why is this video being recommended to
me think cuz everyone keeps going and
watching it probably probably but
I was literally outside eating eating
sushi I'm not kidding I was out eating
sushi and I was just looking through my
phone and it pops up and I was
like out in public not the salty
Sushi oh
[Music]
no
yeah no I'm so excited for that cover
I'm so excited for all the more covers
and your and original songs and
everything that you'll be doing so yeah
I'm super excited you know yeah PA said
by you were the first person to hear it
I know even though it's just a little
little tiny bit of
it I I um I'm very excited to um become
just a fan of yours you
know I can you know I can finally just
be like the true fan that I want to be
in be in your stream and be like oh my
god with everybody
else I will you know what you will be
the first person to to listen to the
final version of my next original t my I
promise I
promising I can't wait yeah you guys
already from what I've heard it's so
perfect you're not even ready my gosh
you know I promised M stand by that I
would want like I was like I want to try
make a danad the fairy of Ayers oh yeah
and she was like yeah but then it ended
up not being able to make take one
inside it's okay if you ever want to
cover it and do a dance you can totally
do that yeah only if you want
to is it still okay for me to make a
dance for it you know yeah of
course thank you I'll take this as your
written um written permission for stuff
it's a verbal yes I am verbally per
[Laughter]
saying Mark the time stamp
heck yeah oh my God but you still have a
lot of people to go through and I know
you're getting I I heard that you're
getting hungry sorry no no no no don't
be sorry like what's it called I just
want you to know that you're like very
very very very very loved and within
like not like all of Ian not just Ian
but like probably like everybody out
there like they we all look up to you I
looked up to you like from the beginning
you were the first like Ian member that
I ever watched like I watched your debut
as well
and I was I was like oh my gosh she
likes Idol too and so like when I joined
I really wanted to do something about
like Idol related with you and I'm so
happy we were able to so I'm really
thankful about that and I'm still so sad
you're going to go but it's okay because
I could still talk to you yeah we could
still talk all the time no worries yeah
honestly if I wasn't if I wasn't able to
talk to you I'll be crying even hot
right
now yeah go delete my account I'm just
kidding
no I will I will hunt you down I'll like
literally sniff you out can you imagine
how evil that would be that would be
evil that you told me where you're going
to be you told me where you're going to
be you if you delete your account I will
fly over there just to search you
out oh my gosh don't threaten me with a
good time
oh
might de's going to implement all the
torture um stream stuff that she oh my
gosh yeah but yeah I I wish you luck
with your um with your with your
studies as well you know thank you like
yeah yeah yeah we
do made Cafe 100% okay
yeah yeah and I'll do the idle calls and
um in my future songs and stuff thinking
while thinking of you as well so yeah I
got to put 200% into it yeah oh my gosh
I can't wait thank you thanks for droing
by thank you byebye
[Music]
byebye we still have uh one two three
four five people left five people left
sorry guys I'm gon to oh let me go to my
other stream real quick here I'll tag
the other person
[Music]
R uh wait I was
oh
POG hello oh God hello hello is this the
CL of
r
[Laughter]
can't
tell oh God hello oh god I'm laughing
already I
know I can't tell sometimes if you're
talking or if you're
laughing all I turn it off turn it off
hello pom hello I no I couldn't tell
that you turned it
off wait is it still on no no no oh good
hello pumu hello
lucar hello p rain p p rain p p r p rain
P roll me some off roll me some
more why is that voice the best thing
[Laughter]
ever I don't even know how I found it I
don't I prob like watched a I watched um
a clip of someone using okay
way yeah ma' well how are you so far I'm
all right I'm all right been 27 people I
know
crazy yeah almost all of
Ian almost yeah but yeah like I don't
know you hopefully you're not tired at
all you have a stream after this I know
I got to drink a little bit more
coffee no I'm feeling good I think uh
I'm getting tired of talking to people I
can't wait to talk to myself myself when
I am
stream no I'm no but I'm happy to still
talk sorry that sound sorry for coming
so late though no it's okay I was
actually I just woke up I have uh I have
three Australians in a row I figured
that uh oh yeah son
is
yeah um so have you cried yet yeah
anyone cried yet cried today um finana
cried Al
cried um that makes sense though uh I
think Rosie cried a little bit um AA
cried oh no Mar cried a little
bit
oh oh no no honestly I I don't really
know what but it's notop pumu um I
thought you were going to say I don't
know what to
say well you know I know what I know
what to say oh okay you're pretty good
at this like like you know when hell no
what are you talking about no I feel
like you're pretty good about about like
saying things about
people huh what what do you mean I like
barely any I don't even say anything
sometimes I don't know I feel like you
anytime I've seen like you talk about
someone you say pretty good things I'm
an action type guy you know what I mean
like that oh I show it through action
all right well get on with it okay oh
well um chat GPT helped me out oh yeah
yeah yeah there you go oh but seriously
though I think uh you know we we we
played a lot uh when we first
debuted I think I think the one thing I
really wanted to say mhm is although I I
bullied you a lot in games you know we
both bullied each other you know I I
threw a lot of things at you like most
of the time mhm yeah I I still I still
really appreciated that you know like
all of you guys back then like played
with me you like dealt with me so I
really do appreciate that no it was a
lot of fun I felt like I had a brother
that I never had no no no I'm glad as
well yeah it was fun yeah but you know
it was it was really fun so honestly
like if I look back in like two years
ago I would say my God oh my my alarm
went off good
morning but yeah like you know like
basically around the 3month marck of
when I
debuted you you guys like collabing with
me you know like
Sho especially with Minecraft stuff M
yeah it it you know it really it really
helped me really helped solidify with
like how I want to be on on stream you
know like
how what I needed to do to be
comfortable on
stream you guys like basically just I'm
really bad at this no it's okay just
just know playing with me really helps
me see that you got to get back into
Minecraft
man I play every now and then yeah in
secret in secret hey I get on the server
a lot and I don't see you there
but you won't be on after this I know
that's why more people needs to get
on I want to go I want to like wait like
a couple months or so or something and
like go watch someone's stream of the
server and kind of like see what has
changed is that anything you haven't
finished
yet anything that you wanted want to
make no I the sanctum isn't totally
finished but I think ukie will take care
of it we'll finish that
yeah but you got to go fix you know I
can think of something oh yeah
okay you know like after this maybe no
this year you have to do something at
Halloween at Halloween Town you have to
Halloween
Town if I saw now it is a lot of time
yeah you made that whole big area you
and you can get more people to make some
stuff and you
know I feel like this is the year you
can do
it yeah well since since you asked for
it yeah that's what I want finished a
Halloween a Halloween event few months
that's what you'll watch okay yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's what I'll watch and
I'll be like holy [\h__\h] they added so
much to Halloween Town it's so awesome
yeah that's what I want to see okay I
can do that M but you never really
actually you know you know changing the
topic
mhm what do you what do you have planned
like after you leave after this I heard
about well something you can say on
stream oh yeah well I'm going to go um
you know I got to go P do pulation other
places
uh I you know Earth is just too small I
have to take over the entire galaxy yeah
oh outside oh my God yeah
I must infect
[Music]
everything I I heard you're um like
going to school for something yeah I'm
going to school that's about it yeah
luck with without L Pomo okay thanks I
actually I I finalized some of my stuff
like last night
so oh my gosh oh you really oh okay
that's good that's good yeah yeah I I I
heard about what it was so good luck
with that that'll be really fun that'll
be fun yeah I hope so it's it's not for
so long but um you know it it's still
going to be a trip though yeah yeah I
think it'll be still good experience and
I'll learn I'll expand my
brain that'll be good that'll be good
yes that'll be good yeah didn't you say
you were hungry oh oh was that I was
just going to say you know thanks for
always going along with whatever crazy
stuff um you you you were like one of
the people that if we were like doing
something dumb you would always like you
know follow up and we would just be
stupid so I mean I I'm dumb by default I
know so it was so easy it
works also it was it was really fun it
was really fun thanks for inviting me to
that um that VR chat dating thing so
that frog BT could be born oh frog B no
but that's all you though no you were
the one that made the Cara didn't you
show up at the stream the I didn't I did
I did I did but my internet actually
went out oh no okay I was like wait I I
was talking to people I didn't want to
like disturb you like I don't know like
you were talking to someone else at the
time no it's okay but thanks for
dropping by say hi no no no it's okay
it's okay I was just there saying folk f
as the whale whatever folk yeah like
that do it as the
narrator
wait wait hold on I hold up
wait hold on okay no
[Laughter]
worries no
okay okay I won laugh anymore i't speak
normally speak
[Music]
[Laughter]
normally
turn it off turn it
[Music]
off turn
it
okay thanks for coming
Luka thank you thank you thank you pom
okay see you later we wish you all the
best listen as the first girl in nii and
the first boy nii salute you oh [\h__\h]
really oh my gosh all righty I salute
you good luck good luck to your future
endeavors
thanksa and let's hang out more when we
can yeah see
you goodbye P
byee my God this is our last time
talking on stream wait are you going to
are you going to play games tomorrow oh
no no tomorrow oh yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah that guy oh my God the fact that
the the thing when he it's like normal
talking and then it's when he starts to
laugh and it becomes so scary it's so
funny oh my gosh it's so
funny oh let's see get in here my
man thanks for the thank you so
much
oh hello hello
hi hey how's it going what's going on in
you oh just we're Clowning Around
clowning you too you gonna
[Music]
honk I don't know why I just learn like
I knew that you were good at voice
acting but I don't know why in the past
couple of days I've learned that you're
good at sound effects as
well oh am I I don't know yeah I just I
make funny sounds with my my voice and
my nose sometimes yeah yeah so do you
you're pretty good hey you're pretty
good no I always like really appreciate
like you go into little bits and
characters on streams sometimes one
thing I really enjoyed about your
streams ever since you debuted really
it's because I'm um I don't know I think
I have an identity crisis I can't stay
with one character the Eternal drama kid
always got to be in character yeah man I
feel that I never went to drama class
kind of feel like I missed out like I
would have enjoyed that I think you
would have really liked it I think so
yeah we did that thing with Vox you were
there weren't you where wait were you
[\h__\h] we had like an improv class on
vox's Channel at one point I think I was
supposed to be there uh maybe you didn't
end up coming in yet yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah that was so much fun want to do
more stuff like that yeah you guys
should I know Vox would be down for sure
oh hell yeah hell's yes
yeah yeah role play yeah um how's it
going how you holding up long stream
yeah I'm good I'm good yeah good having
fun with everybody yeah
yeah what's up this is nice this is nice
isn't
it this is good this is good isn't it
yeah yeah I don't know what to say I
don't know either we speak through metal
gear qu yeah that's the only way I know
how to speak to
yeah never really knew how to talk to
you like since we met really I think
this is is this the first time we're
talking one-on-one on stream or um I'm
sure there's been like small moments
like that maybe small moments yeah yeah
damn no yeah I don't know I always like
kind of kept my distance a little bit
you I don't know you seem like such
a I don't know like I just you kind of
like
[Music]
a I don't know wasn't the
man I just I look up to you a lot you're
a great role model and a great
Senpai and you know I just I feel like I
can't approach you what what the hell
but everyone says I'm so approachable oh
my God was it a lie well well you are
it's just that I'm not good at talking
to people usually that's the main thing
that's fair me too I wish could have
done more stuff with you in nii did I
traumatize you talked
more no not at all nothing like that I
just you know I just look up to you a
lot Shy Boy to
a I don't know it's like talking to like
a like a famous historical figure or
something the p rain puff I don't know
what to
say I don't know I mean I don't know
you're
I don't know I mean I don't even know
what to say yeah nether I'm a historical
figure
guys yeah you're going to go down in nii
history oh my God you done so much for
us you know I'm like rud off you've done
so many like huge products um projects
rather that um you really uplift all of
us like when times were tough you you
were really thinking about all of us m
no I think but like I mean you're just
you're you're you're you're so iconic
too everybody knows
VF
no
nah I'm just I'm just a worm I'm just a
bug I'm just a worm what the hell oh no
it's two people that can't take
compliments no you you should take the
compliments cuz you really do so
much I think you just have a lot of
Praise I well um thank
you thank you yeah I thank you for
everything no no I'm really looking
forward to your future stuff your future
projects too based on what you have
hinted
at I I don't know what you mean but I
know I know I know in my head yeah all
right yeah I mean I would I hope that I
can make some stuff happen
yeah you know good for us yeah thank you
well um I guess I'll head out now
okay why was this so awkward I I I wish
I wish I could express myself better but
you you mean a lot to me and I'm sure to
everyone else here as
well thanks son thanks for being such a
champ with the
shenanigans
I know what you mean no I'm you know
that
was that that moment in that
cab
when I said something strange and
embarrassed myself wonder what I wonder
what you said I don't know so weird yeah
it was it was a really humiliating thing
for me at the start but in the end I was
just glad that I could have something to
connect you
with even though it was really
embarrassing oh my God we really did
traumatize of you
guys yeah I'm glad that people were able
to laugh about
it yeah thanks
Sunny thank you okay goodbye see you
later home with my woman Sun
my well I was not expecting
it oh
[\h__\h] hey um there's you got to get in
line now Sunny Brisco there's a lot of
other people that say that have called
me their woman
now a that guy he's shy
boy yeah our woman oh thank you sh he's
posting that every time I say say thank
you sho I feel like I'm saying like donu
you know like thank
you he's so sweet that
guy I don't know why that was so awkward
but H Sunny is so he's so funny he's a
he's a funny guy it's it's so funny like
how different he can be like here and
then on his stream you
know but um no all righty next
[Music]
up
oh oh my God it was so sexy for a
second
scarla hello sen um my my fairy my my
lady my woman my
beautiful beautiful Fair magical
princess how are you wow am I still
deserving of this title yes you are so
beautiful Your your gorgeous sunglasses
your volumptuous
nose the thighs oh oh my we are we are
together in thighs we are together in
thighs how you doing how you holding
them you want to go get a snack go go
get a snack I'm okay I'm
okay okay make sure you eat bro before
you're other stream yeah how are you
doing I'm good just been lurking for
remember during the times I I was like I
remember when you were stalking me in
Minecraft like one of the first times I
went on the server like what's am I
doing hey when are you going to get back
on um
Minecraft I've been
debating maybe I don't know how you
don't get motion sickness I get motion
sickness so bad I know a lot of people
do say that especially about yeah yeah I
know that's why I'm like props to you
don't
it's okay I will not I want to try
though just a little bit
MH but I'm so sorry I lost the little
what's the little blue babies in
Minecraft oh um the the the blue babies
that's what they're called actually
they're a a lot no I don't remember
their
names the the the thingies you give them
the H I don't remember oh Al alyss those
things give them the I'm sorry I lost
him no forever ago it's okay is that why
you stopped
playing no bro I was traumatized I'm
like Scaro where'd you go I couldn't
find him any
Scaro
scar where' you go I was so traumatized
for
days whenever I saw another I couldn't
forget him and I'm like is he the one no
he's not I think no Rand I've sometimes
like found some in the wild so I we he
we might have found him and we don't
even I don't even know can't even
recognize my own son I don't deserve to
have
him and thank you for my the chunka My
Sword I remember when you did the
scavenger hun for Al Luna I remember the
thank you for the Chun it was very
useful in times of struggle oh I'm glad
so glad that it got some use oh Scarlet
I wish we could have like
collabed more or talked more in
general no
worries I'm so shy and you're so shy bro
I I feel it's like when you bu in like
freaking little introvert beings it's
like hard sometimes for but like I've
watched so many of your streams you're
always so crazy I don't even need to
tell you that everyone will tell you
that you're always so crazy oh you're
crazy bro oh my God bro I would watch
all your streams when I was at school
like I'll just be lurking your Minecraft
streams while I'm at my internship and
I'll like maybe comment one time I'm
okay that's enough just watch and your
karaoke are my favorite you have the
bestest karaoke ever I look forward to
them all the time I watch all the read
broadcast you are
amazing man you you so creative and you
killed it during the hop
concert bro no also bro thank you so
much for dealing with me
I'm so sorry I don't take care of my
voice and I got freaking
bronchitis thank you for dealing with me
no I felt so bad yeah yeah that's right
cuz you couldn't participate with the
but no I really appreciate that why are
you going to apologize for getting
bronchitis girl you've had like throat
issues for so long now I get so worried
about you sometimes I don't know what to
do about it at this point I'm like this
is like see this crock this is just how
it is now this is just how it is oh my
God it's kind of sexy though I like the
raspiness oh is it
okay oh my
go but thank you you've always been such
a heartwarming Senpai always available
with open arms and you're just amazing
you're so talented you're crav you're
like bro freaking I Loop your singing
all the time your karaoke are bomb your
freaking fairy aiar is beautiful oh my
God thank
you how do to even get an ounce of the
talent and creativity you you have bro
no I think you have it though you're
always you're always trying new things
on stream you're doing I I I look to you
and I'm just like damn how did she come
up with that no no no he the Pomo I just
have got you got that fairy in you got
that Pomo in you got that got that fairy
always got the pomu energy inside to
keep you going through the
times are you holding up good yeah I'm
okay I'm having
fun have fun with school by The
Institute of Mystics is
boring I'm Legit ditching today and
tomorrow do you have any advice for me
uh don't ditch class like me I would
ditch class be like I'm going to
stream so um don't ditch class actually
go
um um study find better I don't know I
never found good study methods ever I
just I just try my hardest and hope for
the best know I'm I'm I'm really bad
because I'm one of those people that
will like cram or like like remember
things for a test and then forget all of
it you know bro I would study so hard
and then like as soon as the test would
come I would be
like what is this about mind blank brain
exactly I wish you the best on all you
do and all of your endeavors and I know
you're going to kill it okay thank you
Skyla of course I don't want to take too
much cuz I know you haven't eaten I know
you had a push back stream like kick me
out whenever okay I should probably go
eat soon now but good go eat you know
what you know what good go eat go eat
something go eat I'll go eat okay um
thank you thank you SC thank thank you
thank you P Sun F you're amazing God Dam
it's it's not going to be the same with
that I know I said you going to go
you're amazing you're a pillar you are
like the icons of the universe oh I I
hope you know that and you you don't
think you're a little speck you're the
biggest [\h__\h] Speck and no one can
forget you okay okay thank you I love
you go eat I love you go eat go eat go
eat go eat okay thank you thank you
mommy by thank you're welcome
bye oh she's so cute oh man
scar I'll eat after
the next two people we have two people
left okay two people left thank you oh
let me type down scarla
sorry 28 oh 29
28 I wish that um uh some people yeah we
I don't think everybody is coming that's
totally okay like I said I
um uh I didn't like uh some people had
to like go to sleep and obviously time
zones and things like that so it's no
problem at all if not everyone could
come or even tomorrow as well you know
so uh um yeah and I you know as much as
I would have loved to talk to everybody
you know it is what it is
so we're at 30 what are you talking
about oh
I said 27 28
[Music]
nine
30 oh my God
okay um oh yeah thank you
sh don't worry about the don't worry
about the Sho reminded me about the link
too from Ike who oh my
God hello he wi almost
having West
Virginia why I just been I had no other
reason oh
okay you know how to make an entrance
what is up do I'm good I'm good I just
wanted to come by and um give you know
say my goodbyes I think we're still
doing something together somewhat soon
like the whole collab thingy yeah yeah
yeah but I won't be able to talk to you
as much so I wanted to come by oh no
worries yeah thanks for dropping
by of course and um I I know that you've
probably I mean there's been 29 other
people before me I was looking at your
counting and it was like 27 28 27
stop stop I don't know how to count I'm
a fairy what do you want for me so I
know you mentioned that you wanted to
like you know make pursue continue educ
a after this and maybe starting to learn
how to count is a good place to begin
damn
yo oh it
hurts sorry sorry sorry all right all
right but I wanted to say then we love
you and you know I I I've mentioned this
before but I'm not want to to say that
oh I know this person since kindergarten
you know pomu and I go all the way back
I Tau her how to tie her shoes damn
thanks for that by the way
of course no worries and don't worry
about the $10 million I lend to you
though by the way that's you can keep
that I completely forgot about that so
you know yeah yeah yeah and the
Lamborghini and I crashed that it's all
yours oh no no that's no worries I got
20 of them okay but
I but I I do want to say that you know
even before getting into nanji laulai
was probably the the wave to me that I
was the most nervous to speak to uh um
and and thus you know we haven't been
able to to bond as much but I think the
reasoning behind that in particular was
because I saw you guys um as as very
instrumental not not just to nii Sanji
and um but for Ving in general like I
think in my mind at least in my personal
opinion when when when you say V tubing
I think it's very synonymous with with
Pomo and with you and and with like I am
I am
pom that is you correct you're so smart
I don't maybe I don't need to go back to
school hold on we love you're a genius
but yeah I I wrote a little list of
things I wanted to say and literally one
of them I'm reading them right now is
say that you want to be like pomu when
you grow up so I just want to
say are are you sure I don't know about
that man maybe just a little bit you
know like some parts just the maybe the
Minecraft expertise and everything else
maybe not so much okay fine that's fine
you can yeah but but I also want to say
and I want to thank you for for like you
are also one of the reasons and I never
told you this before but you and and
luxium and notics and a lot of the
Senpai are reasons why I decide to step
up and and go out of my comfort zone and
right like literally at the end of the
week this week I'm going to be doing a
hand cam with I eat water with a fork oh
wait I think I remember when you
mentioned doing that we were like what
the you were like this sounds like a fun
stream and we were all like what the
hell is wrong with you know so
everybody's everybody's been doing you
know like like lore videos and music and
[\h__\h] and going to you know
Alaska y but I got to start somewhere
you know you're going to eat water with
a
fork but okay that being said
uh I hope you know that I appreciate you
we do too um and and I I've just being
able to see you from for I've been here
for a year and two months which is not
long in comparison to other people but
uh you you you mean so much to us and I
know that wherever the roads take you
you will be
so successful and you will be vibrant in
whatever you choose to do um and I I I
assure you
that should you learn counting I know
that you'll pick it up eventually I know
that's you'll get there I'll get there
I'll get there when I and when I do I'm
going to send you
literally to 100 [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
that's big that's big boy numbers I'm
going to write it I'm going to mail it
to the nii Sanji office as a fan letter
to to you to start with like smaller
ones first but that's a really big goal
I'm
really triple digits a little you know
you're reaching a little bit Yeah and
then you'll get it and you'll be it'll
only be numbers and you'll be like she
did it man she did it I could just
imagine like reading that letter in
front of my parents and they're going to
be like why are you crying and then they
grab the letter from me and they just
see one two three it's like sloppily
written like a kindergartener wrote it
like this man laughing a [\h__\h] crying
at [\h__\h]
numbers I hope you get several fan
letters now of people writing one I
[\h__\h] hate you
I instead of like heartfelt messages
it's just [\h__\h] numbers yeah okay uh
but I love you and I'm proud of you I I
think that you are a a wonderful content
creator and you make everybody's smile
and I think even with this like I've
been seeing people approach your
thoughts and everything the way that you
like when when somebody cries you just
manage to to put a smile on their face
instantly and and cheer them up it's the
sweetest thing really um but yeah we
thank you so much for having me and
thanks for dropping by I love you thank
you so much pomu thank you so
much okay I'll leave you to it get some
enjoy your Pokemon bye-bye I'll see you
[Music]
tomorrow
man yay all right we got one last person
think actually um I got a package today
uh from
staffan with like the with more Goods
it's so crazy because my room is my room
is filled with I mean there's I mean I
saw
the was it a counting book shut the hell
up
man no but my room is like filled with
you know I like look up and I see my
birthday merch and I see the the acrylic
stand that went to space and I see the
shikishi aami Drew of me and I see my
pomu Pape and my newi and like the
acrylic stand my mama made like my room
is filled with so many uh so many things
and I I have more now because I got like
the the San Rio goods
and the um some other Goods but I also
got two fan letters
that uh where did I put them I think I
oh there they are
uh hold
on I got two fan letters that um were
from like they were from a while
ago um I know that I think there will be
quite a few more next package perhaps
but like one of them is from
August and um it's so cute it's in such
a cute little envelope with like a
flower sticker and um I think the name
is are they Carly or Carl thank you so
much for
writing
um uh it was they were like looking
forward to your new
outfit so let just pretend that I saw
this
before before the outfit and I got it
and then the other one um it made me so
sad um thank you salty zero I got your
letter um I'm sorry for the future
letters I won't uh be able to tell you
if I got them or not but
um uh I'm sure I will get all of them
just so that I don't want you to feel
like oh my God I wonder if she got my
letter or not I will um I will let's
just say yes I got your letter so just
just know that I will have gotten it um
but this one made me
feel
um
yeah just uh
[Music]
yeah what you wrote made me be
like but thank you thank you for writing
everybody I still will keep these
forever
um the one plus onek plus letters on
Kudo so true so
true
um uh yeah it was just saying like you
know if the that they were really
comforted that I like stream and that
they can watch me
and you guys say um you guys say like
don't apologize but how can I not when I
read
that okay let's get the last person
[Music]
in and then we'll open up whatever ik it
run oh my God all of you guys have like
the
matching it's so funny oh oh yeah from
drinking it's kind of appropriate I got
a green tea right here in honor of the
green fairy we
go how's your day been long probably
yeah a little long but it's okay okay
it's been fun yeah yeah that's good
that's good well
uh I can't believe I can't believe that
it's yeah today and tomorrow last last
days it feel surreal it does it's like
again doesn't feel real I think I I
don't even know I think maybe like
Saturday it'll feel
real that's when it'll hit you
yeah yeah but uh but I hope I hope for
the most part you're happy and I I think
that everybody is really you know
everybody's really uh told you how they
feel about you uh including including
all of your audience as well so um I I
don't feel like there's too much left to
say you
know it's okay we're just kind of
hanging out too you know whatever yeah
we can kind of chill yeah um but hey I I
was going to say that uh when I first
joined nii Sanji um I really appreciate
ated the happy and positive vibes that
you kind of gave off at the start oh I
felt like uh I felt like Al Luna we kind
of like it it was really appreciated you
know like um I don't know it's uh it was
kind of kind of nerve-wracking for I
know for um a lot of people in Aluna
joining nii Sanji and just meeting
everybody and stuff like I I didn't
really know anybody but uh you know
Aluna was they're just like oh my god
I've been watching people for this long
and I'm just like oh they're so cool
though like they're so
nice you know but uh but yeah you were
yeah you were always uh you know from
the very beginning just very um just
positive about the whole experience and
um I would say you've um you know you've
helped remind me while I've been here
that the you know the the whole reason
that I'm here is to have fun you know
yeah exactly and just yeah exact and
just like not not take things too
seriously because you shouldn't I feel
like especially on internet I
know I mean we're creatures of the
internet like this is yeah exact oh my
God and we we got to we got to not make
that such a thing we got to touch grass
and I will say I'm happy that I got the
chance to touch grass with you while
being in
thean I know you actually made me
leave let's
go oh my gosh touch
grass yep yep oh
terrifying oh it wasn't that bad no it
was fine we got to hang out um yeah it
was cool yeah no you were always like so
chill so it was a lot of fun every time
we you know hung out and stuff so yeah
and thank you for thank you for uh was
that one time when uh when you had to
like find a restaurant for me that I
could actually eat
at we and we and we all ended up going
to like one place I what did I even get
I got something like like chips or
something I can't remember oh wait was
it the Korean place no yeah yeah was it
oh God was it that place I'm not sure
there was a SE that's been several times
that we had would had to look for a
place for you yeah I'm so difficult no
it's okay that actually it's so funny
because that happened to me again I have
I had another friend who was vegetarian
and um it was always like they were like
don't oh just go eat wherever you wanted
I was like you're going to starve shut
up I know at one point I'm just like oh
gosh you guys we've been through like
we've looked at like six different
restaurants now let's just go anywhere
please I think that's what it was I
think actually we were at Tokyo Dome
City and we were like circling the place
like three times being like you want to
have this oh but it has this you want
have that oh no I don't think
so and actually I think a thank you
isn't it the thing you got even like was
it like there's something in it it was
like called veggie but there was like
some sort of meat in it I'm so
sorry it it happened I just pick out
this I don't really mind too much but uh
it's difficult finding restaurants but
yeah no it was good it was a lot of fun
and uh yeah and I remember uh at the
start of nii Sanji and me joining as
well um some of my first impressions of
everybody were uh you remember Minecraft
the Minecraft server and just being like
introduced into that I felt like I was
joining you know like a cult or
something oh yeah I do it was really
that was really chaotic I do remember
that yeah yeah that's just like some of
my earliest memories is uh is like you
and Luca trolling me in Minecraft so
thank
you honestly it did um it did help me
kind of like uh you know really get that
sense of community as funny as it sounds
like we we show affection through
bullying I
guess the hazing is real the the
trolling it's okay I'm used to it I'm
used to
it no but it was good that's the I mean
that's the whole reason that I um that I
decided to try you know joining nii
Sanji in the first place to have a
community and a group of friends and um
and um yeah I would consider consider
you one of my one of my good friends so
thank you very much yeah thank you red
man I can't wait to see I and I'm I'm
manifesting this I cannot wait to see
you do a [\h__\h] 3d concert I we all
want to see it we all need to see it oh
my gosh I would love that manifesting so
Stan
please one day one day crossing fingers
yeah it was amazing to see uh to see
your 3D as well niif Fest I'm so
good wait did you I I remember when you
guys were doing the tour and I was still
um in rehearsal did you did did you see
me yeah yeah we were walking through we
were walking through the hall and we
were like writing on walls and stuff and
then I kind of just like I stopped
walking and just saw you performing on
the stage like for your sound check and
I was just like I just stopped and I was
just standing and staring I was like no
it was so good I was so proud of you and
and it was inspiring me so much and then
and then my manager came over and was
just like Ren you got you got to move
with the group and I'm like
oh that happened a couple
times yeah you did amazing and I hope
that uh whatever you do in the future I
hope that singing is a part of it
because you are so insanely talented
with um singing and uh even even dancing
and stuff like like you're a natural
born performer in my eyes so I hope you
continue it thank you whatever for thank
you yeah no I can't wait to see what all
you do so
um yeah I'll be watching from the
Shadows I'll be watching oh my
gosh she'll be lurking but no I mean it
means a lot to for to hear from you cuz
I know you're like so you know you're
you're a real musician I'm just I'm just
pomu I just sing karaoke and mess up
words you're not just pomu you're pomu
you are pomu okay and that's that's a
big thing that's that's that's a big
thing so thank you so much for
everything and I I will see you in crab
game tomorrow okay yeah I'll see you in
crab game
then yeah but um I I I I got nothing
else to say I'm going to go touch grass
bye touch grass bye Ren thanks for
dropping
by
yay thank You Ren thank you everybody
who dropped by thank you
guys
I think that's everyone that um can make
it so
cool that was crazy oh gosh thank you
for
the this is some birthday gift you're
leaving oh gosh bike shorts Senai happy
birthday thank you so much found you
through shorts oh my gosh I've been a
fan for years but graveyard shift job
that's like oh oh you know so I have big
regrets not joining live stream no if
you can't join oh my gosh no
no oh a asra sent another message is so
nice um okay shoe shoe has the link okay
I'm going to open it now and then I'm
going to go eat and then we're going to
beat Pokemon baby yeah we're going to
beat
Pokemon okay it's a secret
PowerPoint what is this oh my
God Dragon thank you
wait what is
[Music]
this wait hold on how do I
uh uh to make sure oh there we go okay
hold
on what is
[Music]
this it's a power
boy
a PowerPoint by nii Sanji n wait I can
he said I could show this on stream
right he said that right oh
[Music]
gosh yeah he did okay I just wanted to
make sure yeah okay okay I just want to
make
sure oh
no oh
no how
oh
God
no
no oh my
God it's playing all the
videos oh
[Music]
God the hell oh I see it I was like who
the hell is tuny old man I should have
known I'm
dummy a oh be
couldn't um he couldn't make it but he
oh was able to write here oh thank
[Music]
you no blue shut up so
sad oh my
God oh my
God
what is this oh God I killed you in the
crab
game holy
[\h__\h] I can't even read these I'll read
them off stream I'm
too dream guy so
[Laughter]
true
yay he's so cool is that what that said
m
[Music]
so it's decorated so
cute
[Music]
b
v
Vox what is
this oh my gosh oh my
God jump scare go touch
grass oh oh there's a video message
from K damn oh my gosh I I'll watch it
later oh there's a second
page oh my God it's so
[Music]
cute thank you oh my gosh I love your
drawing so much I'm so
happy
[Music]
oh my God the the
cat oh my God this is so cute why did
you guys put it
together oh and
meoo thank
[Music]
you what is what is
this oh zawa
zawa what is happening
oh oh there's
more oh we're down here too we're Frozen
though this is so
ominous hidden behind the Frog
[Music]
bir
no I couldn't make it either thank you
[Music]
guys I tried to sketch one of my must oh
my gosh it's so
cute wait what the hell Petra you drew
this you should draw
more what the
hell
oh my
[Music]
God oh my gosh so cute thank you
guys dumb
collabs
[Music]
oh my God this goes so hard what the
[Laughter]
hell oh my God you even got the
background like this
similar this goes so
hard hey
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] the
legendary the title you never even
[Music]
wanted oh there's oh my God there's so
many oh I think that's
it thank you guys oh my
[Music]
God I'll go back and read it
all wait I need my
glasses I need my sunglasses so you
don't see my
tears oh when did you guys put this
together what the
[Music]
hell actually hold on I'm going to
download
it so I always have
it has
PDF I don't
[Music]
have oh download I also have to have it
as a PowerPoint so I can see the sick
[Music]
transitions that was so awesome thank
you guys thank
[Music]
you I didn't expect that oh my
god oh I should get out of
[Laughter]
[Music]
VC thank you
guys
[Music]
thank you
sh I had so much fun today thank you
guys for all talking with me I still
have a little bit of streaming left to
do cuz CU we still have to beat Pokemon
I'm so determined even though I got no
sleep last night I have
coffee and then tomorrow will be a long
day too I don't want to stop streaming
though
because I want to keep going until we're
[Music]
over yeah we got to finish the
fight that was so sweet of you guys
thank you so
much oh
it's like my own little scrapbook oh my
God you guys wrote hags in my
[Music]
earbook
man you guys are always like man you
need to know how maybe it's because of
this like I don't know you guys are
always like you need to know how
influential you are how much you mean to
people and this and that
but honestly it's like
I I don't know I feel that way towards
all of you guys towards everyone in Ian
towards every every friend I've made
outside of
nian towards you know the
Pomchi I said it in my in my
announcement but like my life has
actually been changed
like
and I don't know I'm just really
grateful because
like
because um you know I was able to I I I
don't have to walk on my boss's back
anymore
I I I don't know why am I so lucky like
anyone could have been the first wave
you know like
I I got so so lucky people say like you
you you were so awesome as the first
wave but only cuz I got lucky with
it
[Music]
but but every day I get to have so much
fun why it's it's not
fair I want to so that's why I try my
hardest to also make every everyday fun
for you guys
because because you know I get to have
so much fun I only I want to give
everything that I that you guys give
me um and and then some I just never
feel like that I can
um do I have to join voice
no no I'm just saying I just I don't I
mean I just wish that I could always
give you guys more because I you know
maybe if you guys think it's enough to
me it just doesn't feel like enough
because it's just how how grateful I am
so like like I wish like you know I I
put out a music video and I'm like God I
wish I could go like I wish I could jump
out of each of your computer screens and
like vacuum your floors and wash your
dishes for you guys you know
like like I don't
know then then I would actually be doing
an act of favor back to you you
know or
something
[Music]
uh I don't know like I guess it's you
know when I think it really hit home
when when a is just like you you've had
your Idols graduate and they mean so
much to you but I don't I don't know I I
can't I
can't I can't see myself meaning that
much to anybody else but I don't know so
many people say it I'm too
hardheaded
[Music]
um even though I can experience it with
my own you know with my own Idol
or with like you know even just
YouTubers or streamers that I like to
watch
it just doesn't feel like I deserve it
or
anything but
um sorry I'm crying as if it's the last
day as if I don't have a stream that I'm
five minutes late
for um but
um
yeah I mean maybe I'm an idiot
for giving up something that I love so
much um and leaving here I don't know
like leading up to this I've always I've
thought I thought time like so many
times I was like am I doing the right
thing am I making
mistake
um cuz you know I I I do have so much
fun I I really really love streaming and
hanging out with you guys
[Music]
but
um you
knowa I just hope that you
guys never forget um not only how fun
this was but also just
uh um you know to always be true to
yourself and always remain silly do the
clown nose stays on
okay let's go wipe some
[Laughter]
butt why why did I say that the other
day let's wipe ass
everybody let's go beat the Elite
[Laughter]
yeah I have no idea if we'll be able to
defeat the Elite for
but
um
yeah oh one last silly meme before
graduation
yeah get up thanks you all right I'm
going to take like a 10minute uh food
break and then we'll jump right into it
thank you for the super thank you thank
you for all the super chats you
guys thank you
um oh there
hello thank you for dropping
bye
um yes okay time to wipe ass I sure hope
so or otherwise this stream is going to
be a complete waste of time but we're no
no no no no we're going to do it we're
going to do it Ruda thank you for the AA
Za let's go out wiping ass
yeah okay tomorrow's the last day
tomorrow K thank you for the
Hupa okay all right I will see you guys
then um if I see you if not if you're
going to bed please go to bed if I see
you um maybe I will wipe ass who knows
um I I don't know
but we're going to we're going to go
down kicking screaming crying throwing
up [\h__\h] pissing
[Laughter]
everything we'll go down without a or we
won't go down without a
foot
yeah uh
okay all right I'll see you guys then
thank
you thank you guys I'm seeing Oh I'm
seeing some like aad donos thank you so
much I really really really really
really really really really really
really appreciate it um a aatam akamine
thank
you thank you so
much um for the aono okay if I missed
one I'm so sorry there's it's it's
unless I hear
it uh it's hard for me to catch I think
there was one earlier in the Stream too
thank you guys I really really
appreciate
it I've been reading all the messages
offline so and now I have more to read
because I have the whole Kudo board and
I have this PowerPoint and I have the
letters that will be coming
[Music]
in it's a little
overwhelming I've never felt this before
this this power oh but you guys are very
powerful sasuga my
pachis
I love you guys see you in a bit ult be
byebye byebye byebye and thank you for
the music video to stream stream Fair
vyers thank you
[Music]
bye-bye oh
bye-bye
[Music]