oh
uh
[Music]
okay
uh
[Music]
okay
hello
[Laughter]
how is the volume now everyone can you
hear
with with me in comparison to the others
how is it hello
hi
can i have some food please i'm dying i
just gave you some steak
oh thank you oh thank you you haven't
been sorry
hello hello
thank you for the steaks i was waiting
for this
yeah all right put them away i don't
need them anymore
i'm making a weapon oh wait where is
this girl
do a wheelchair in her house i'm just
getting
my house
if you guys have weapons we and you have
like any xp
i have some stones here you guys can use
and you go into this basement and you
can
enchant your weapons uh if you guys
haven't done it yet
hang on a sec yeah i tried it earlier
today let's put them up in there
whoa wait did you enchant your uh
irons my what your iron sword or
diamonds oh yeah yeah yeah no my iron
sword i didn't make a diamond sword i'm
too scared to lose it
i can just mine more times excuse me
oh yeah i borrowed some lapis lizzy
oh hey is this the good one
[Applause]
[Music]
do you maybe first of all want to tell
the viewers what the hell we're doing
yeah what's happening here
even i don't know even i have no idea
[Music]
and then we're going to the never
together and all going to die
yay
i'm trying to adjust my i've never been
there before what's it what's it like
what kind of things happen with lava
bring a bed and then sleep in the never
because it gives you like
it gives you a buff that makes you
stronger for like uh 20 minutes
really okay cool yeah i'll do that i'm
level one i can't enchant anything
yeah where is my bed it must be in the
house huh i'll make one wait
do you wanna chat something girl i can
do it for you
uh yeah wait why
27. it doesn't take away it takes away
your level though
it just takes a little bit oh okay here
will you eight nine twenty seven
yes you enchant my bow for me
is that i have pirates speak on my game
so everything is pirate language
so um that's cool i want that
okay girl they're both unbreaking so oh
wait i thought i thought it had never
ending bolts i thought that was never
it's random i think
or maybe like no one's higher
okay i'm going to give you guys a piece
of gold armor because cara says i'm
breaking you know what
if you guys know me all right would you
guys rather have pants
boots or a hat golden oh i want a hat
a golden snapbook yes it depends on the
person
yeah it's per player it changes on
purple air okay
you have to unlock please yeah yeah yeah
i have on the minute you can't have the
boots because it has a curse of binding
and i don't want i think i should wear
them because i don't know i don't know
if you could take them off your pants
i'm just pretending this game is all
about pretending so i'm pretending it's
a golden snapback
oh i know this is hamilton oh my
goodness do you steal this
you know want a gold hat it's got the
curse of vanishing i don't know what
that is
like harry potter right yeah
okay i thought you were still in chains
where are you oh
[Laughter]
does anybody want shiny pants oh i do
are they free
yeah i'll take them like shiny pants yes
i'm very behind in this game because i
don't have time to play games
so please yeah it's also been a while we
got you
know people need the hat the hat will
disappear on death but it's okay
thanks cool are you okay
shiny pants again
is everyone okay what's going on
having a crisis over there uh-oh
i don't know hello gouda what's going on
hello hello i don't know i hear
screaming there's a skrillington over
there he's just
oh he has an enchanted bow he might
start shooting at us that's the cave
where i wanted to live
oh no sir yeah watch it yeah make a shot
make a shot yeah come on yeah i dare you
ha ha you're a coward
he's a coward a coward's scrolling oh
come on come
uh angry in your voice yeah really get
him hey you mother f
word no more cursing guys no more
cursing from me
i'm not gonna do an announcement yeah
being called yeah no he doesn't i'll get
him oh no i'm using the wrong weapon
hang on i don't mean to use
uh oh oh no i just threw it with my
pickaxe away
where'd it go it's gone i lost it
it's gone forever i got him i killed him
you have an arrow in your head watson oh
you have an arrow in your knee and in
your hand i hate that
wait why do you need to pick us up i
found this mine stuff
it's in my hand we're mining again
in the nether apparently there's a lot
of gold
ah okay never okay i have a question
um so i i had how do i hold things in
two hands and how do i switch
between them that there's an enterprise
what's the button uh you wanna you can
scroll through your
your hot bar like the stuff on the
bottom yes is that what you mean
yeah but i uh you guys are holding
things in two hands right
oh yeah yeah so if you if you press e
and then you see there's like a little
square on the right side next to your
feet
that's like a equip if you can hold that
hand again
hand i like the way you were saying it
before you like hand
oh really i didn't notice my left hand
oh my left hand apparently you can just
press f to switch them
okay between the two hands okay um i
only have one slot and it has a sword in
it
um yeah and then you can you can use
your hot bar on the bottom and you can
scroll through other stuff okay yeah you
got it sorry i pressed what
i have no memory you're doing it you got
it but i
hang on oh the idiot idiot i got it okay
and you want to switch your hands
you can press f oh sick okay
understood understood got it okay so
i was i wanted to uh say an announcement
really quick yeah
the apollo rail is now complete
well done
it took us so long is that what i'm
saying
on your roof the thing on your roof
looks amazing on it hey why is there a
tennis racket on there
[Music]
oh i see it now i see it now that you
said it i see it now that you said what
it is
the combine is faster
how do i build this portal i have
obsidian in my hand do i just complete
it
uh i think yeah oh yes where did you get
the obsidian
from i mined it with a diamond pickaxe
that i made
yeah is this how we will access the
nether
what did you have what is that is that
okay if we leave it there
oh well if it doesn't complete itself
then we can get rid of it
where's the music do i make it one block
taller i'm making baby cows hold on
okay i got i got the music
[Music]
i need one more thing uh this is kelly
kelly love game high naruto okay
[Music]
hopefully this is okay now maybe oh i
gotta remove that block i think
wait so oh my goodness guys for the
support
so now i just do this yeah and then just
remove that
diamond pickaxe i don't wanna go get
okay oh my mine's closed my house is
right here
okay oh bgm off yeah bgm is off i'm
playing um
i'm playing the minecraft soundtrack
from the internet
because i don't i don't like when it's
just just sometimes
yeah when the music is sometimes so much
we don't even we don't even need
i
hey where do you guys get your shields
iron and wood oh okay cool i'm going to
do that real quick
let me see wait let me just
do i even have a house i guess it's over
here
i don't really think you got to build
one
yeah i guess so huh i was thinking about
i was thinking about flying like
this area up here this look this
mountain
what do you guys think should i flatten
it out so we have more room to build
yeah should you see over here wait what
mountain
i'm gonna flatten this out this big
mountain what are you doing kelly
i'm looking for my chest i know i had
one i mean yeah
do it like you only have the pain
where's my chest i guess it was over by
the nether i would choose to live in the
middle okay
would you mind if i if i created a
shield first
no problem thank you yes you need a
shield
yes i will create the shield where was
my house again um
i think it's gone oh yes my chest is
here but i have no house because the
creeper blew it up and then i got tired
and didn't get a new one okay cool
here we are i'm gonna build you a
temporary house oh just live with
me i would keep you safe i'm good
i'm gonna fail here i know that i have
iron
[Music]
let's see can i make shields out of
anything else by chance
oh i need i need arrows for my bow wait
oh i got some arrows
i have feathers you can use too oh
wow you know you made like a farm down
wait how do you like you make it
i'll make it
and iron something maybe iron nugget i
don't know
i give up this is too much i can't oh
[Music]
gosh i miss i really miss playing video
games i
just i'm not good at them anymore gosh
back in the day i was so good
you did oh i couldn't go with myself
i don't know i took it again it's not a
tennis race
look behind you oh yeah okay
thank you sorry you had to make that for
me someday i'll make my own
you have a pickaxe in your hand and your
sword and the other
yeah okay okay okay
and and sports what do we need and food
sword pickaxe food
uh calorie need a bag i have one i have
a bed i have it i took it from my house
first okay okay okay
don't forget your beds okay you want you
want feathers
i have ten shots and then i'm screwed
that's not a lot
that's fine whoa there you go
you have sticks yeah one second
where do you get the feathers i forget
how you get feathers skeletons
are chickens you kill chicken oh chicken
okay i need to kill chicken ah i need to
kill you
uh do you have um pointy rock pointy
rock
yard that's a natural item because that
sounds like that
rock i don't know what that is it's a
flint
oh oh yeah i have a bunch of flint here
who is mr pierce
i like him thank you yeah
have you seen bradley and his family
kelly no i haven't can you introduce me
yes on this side thank you i want to
meet them
how do you make it you have dogs
how do you get that what hang on hello
cute cute it's interesting actually
because every
every time that i call an animal or for
example a dog or a cat a default name i
always call them bubba
but because because watson has a dog
named bubba everyone will
everyone will think that i'm talking i'm
talking about that bubba
when i see you okay hello bubba
yo they look at you like you're the mom
i want something
i'm not really get me like that
[Music]
yeah he's dumb he's too tall hello uh
he's gonna chase you forever
uh he can't get in the three-way he
can't get in the the door so if you uh
i don't know he's gone no he's right
here but he can't get
you gotta get him to stand in front of
the door cause he's only he's three
blocks tall so he can't pass under a two
block
oh you're good no the
under buddy
i feel like it's gonna die no
yeah something sounds strange there is
water on the wall
over there why is that how do i harvest
my my
my crops uh with an empty hand you would
just touch it
just you know which reminds me i need to
put the weed
this is my home from now on this is my
home
hang on i'm just going to i'm going to
come out yeah
an extra carrot i could have some dirt
yeah for my carrot form
okay thank you you're welcome
i also have beef if you don't have any
beets or melon i have melon
i have beer roots okay oh wait what
beetroot beer this is fun has someone
claimed
this this is my swimming pool this is my
swimming pool now
has someone claimed this area i think
it's mine now
okay this is mine i got a swimming pool
yeah it's it's in here already for me
i think he's gone
you scared him off i think i did
my home is perfect well not yet but it
will be
sorry i'm just very excited let me know
when you guys are ready to go by the way
i don't want to hold us back oh i think
i just accidentally
opened the uh open lookie africa uh no
not yet i have the rest
okay okay oh wait it's just the one
block right yeah well done yeah close
the pool
get prepared probably should make a
couple pickaxes huh
oh yeah we need that maybe we should
craft some materials yeah
i will help shortly just a moment it is
dummy
yeah it is dummy oh oh there's a gap in
the wall
what's on this side that goes outside
evil witchery of disappearing my house
is big
but it will be big
[Music]
hey do i have iron nope
but i need flint and steel for i've
never used that for anything
um
i thought i knew that but i i don't
remember there's something
something another is there water in the
nether no
no no lots of lava
let's just make a lava boat that sounds
funny that's what we use the strata
board you guys know about the striders
no what's that oh yeah
the striders are for you right um
that sounds cool you can you can walk on
uh
lava with riders what my renovation is
done for today
yeah so if you see striders we can uh we
gotta get some stuff but then we'll be
able to ride them they're funny-looking
and then look at my pool everyone isn't
my pool wonderful
anyway this is my house congrats on the
new home thank you
whose house is this what is this is this
a farm this is not very safe cali
huh that's very it's my very safe house
it's it will be
i'll i will format it later when we're
not visiting the nether i don't want to
hold us all back from visiting the
nether
you need a bunch of time
[Music]
i did but it broke i was making a house
this sounds really cool thank you
hooray wow
okay all right you should go close to
ready
yup i'm ready yes i just need to i'm
just going to drop these rocks off who
has a llama
what the heck someone has a llama
you stole it from the merchant no
i evolved it
sounds like you stole it
wait that's fine i i don't have a
problem with it
i want a donkey um yes i will go to the
gate
okay what is this top building it's my
farm the farm what is this
a blast oven
wait wait wait i need to make out does
anybody have a pickaxe lying around that
i can have
maybe yeah i have like uh we need a
texture
um nice hey you
sorry i just feel like breaking things
anyway
oh yes now my chest is protected thank
you for whoever put
that protection around my chest i think
i stole your llama
huh i think people are saying that i
accidentally tamed your llama so i think
my llama
did i say yeah i'm an inna my ben okay
how do i start yelling he's looking at
me
oh i just rolled on it
it how do i make him spit consistency is
important don't hit it
no a little tap on the butt little
template
all right are we ready i'm ready portal
now i'm ready
let's go ghost rider's ready too i'm
gonna put in the last vlog
hopefully this is my en history here yay
[Music]
let's fix this up it's happening it's
happening here we go think i know what
you need you need that little
uh thing that makes sip and then it's
there what
oh what what zip huh flint and steel
anybody have flint and steel i do here
let me drop it
i will oh it's in my box just what do we
what do we like right click with it and
then it like does like a chat
you gotta light it on fire here yeah
i'm useful for something here there you
go
okay i have
[Music]
what happens in here
the fun all the fun fun okay in one of
your chests i'll put it in one of your
chests okay
okay how do you hold up a shield by the
way
right click oh okay you gotta do that
like if somebody's shooting arrows at
you you have to you can't you have to
block and you walk really slow with it
up
oh okay it's not just like a passive
thing you have to yeah
oh okay gotcha
chad says do not leave the flint because
we might need it to get back oh
oh okay oh okay it's in the wait i get
it again
can you imagine if we could never return
i'm gonna bring the rest of the obsidian
with me just in case we need to make
like another portal or something
we can do that right it'll like lead out
to somewhere else
huh shoes yeah
shoes yeah i noticed i'm missing your
shoes
i can make your shoes i might have some
just kidding i have nothing
i cannot buy stuff we need you wait can
you have your bed
yeah i have one okay are we supposed to
sleep in the nether really yep yeah we
have to save it just
in case uh we die oh okay
that doesn't sound right in my brain
yeah
what do you know about minecraft i don't
know that much about minecraft but
that's something someone's telling me
that there might be a little bit of
trickery going on yeah i have a weird
feeling right now i don't like the way
that you guys are saying
[Music]
like i don't like it we have some cheeky
people thank you
today are you guys trying to mess with
us
why would we find another together
come on okay and we wouldn't want to do
that for everyone we just want it to go
well
yeah i don't like that i don't buy it
you guys have to sleep first
i'm only sleeping in the nether if you
guys are sleeping in another i won't do
it first
i'm totally sleeping in the never i
brought my bed
all right it's another
slumber party i'm coming
[Music]
all right who wants to go first you can
do the honors
no no no all right i got this
let's go all right all right all right
let's go first you guys
don't worry about it there you go
[Music]
catch you on the flip side
oh it looks just like home hey buddy how
you doing
that's we can ride them if we have uh we
need a saddle and then we can sleep
yeah we need a stick i feel right at
home this is nice i should have brought
a saddle
that looks like mordor oh
i don't know a lot about the nothing oh
[Music]
what's this block
looks so fun down there look at all the
friends waiting with weapons
can we go play with them is that is that
good can we use that for something
basalt coordinates
[Music]
i think like one block and another is
like eight in the world or something
like that
it's like multiplied yeah oh that's not
great i don't like that ooh
gold i'm going for exactly i'm pressing
um i think something to just to keep in
mind i i'm not a minecraft
uh encyclopedia but you see these pig
people down here uh-huh yes
they uh don't touch them they won't hurt
you if you don't hurt them okay
oh cool okay yeah just like my homies
well they'll see me and know that it's
fine but
i want this gold oh my god
what it's fine huh be careful
okay
everyone wait my the lavas
i think we're up pretty high there wait
who is up there
watson is that you yeah what are you
doing
i want to get the gold and the ceiling
there's gold oh that's i guess that is
gold huh
you guys will go pick it up
so there's pig people right that uh
won't hurt you but there are other types
of characters that will hurt you
yes hello
but the sick people will hurt you if you
are close to them and uh mine some gold
i think oh yes
if you're far away then they don't care
but if you do it like somewhere close to
them they will follow you until you
die there's more gold we should go down
this way okay just lead the way
okay wait i'm sorry hi
you're making friends here yeah boy he's
cute in here
i like him i want him as a pet can we
bring him back
yeah can we bring him yeah make it make
a little how do we get down there
oh wait you need a stick and a mushroom
maybe build a stairway
it's hard build the stairway down it's
okay we'll figure it out
um it's kind of dark here
adventure
[Music]
okay oh look at that cool guy look at
him the white
the white oh oh oh oh oh oh
what is that okay maybe we should go the
other way
oh yeah i think so maybe okay
i knew this would be happening i knew it
when i saw him i knew it
kind of guessed apparently they're
called guests just
yes
this music is nice is anybody else here
i
what is that lava slime
oh we're so high up should we sleep
somewhere
is that huh should we set a spawn point
how do we get anywhere
everything's so vertically okay
parkour everybody yeah that should be
easy
where the red rock is what
oh oh there's a guy up there with a
sword there's oh wait
look at this dude
it's a slime i really like this place
yeah you guys be careful tina's going
the other way you guys
if you want to come back oh okay um i'll
follow the group
we can all do no say we can all dig down
on this but is there going to be like a
gap underneath if we go down
straight down does everybody know to
hold [\h__\h] be
oh no i didn't know that thank you yeah
yeah prevent you from falling
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna dig it down
over here
okay you're digging down oh boy okay
i'm doing two blocks at a time yeah two
blocks it's good two blocks
okay okay oh my god ghostwriter please
look at them we're gonna go out here
we're gonna say we could
let's take a straight line
i'll just follow you guys
oh true that guy looks cool it's mining
time
okay what are you guys doing deja vu
yay careful not that you suddenly fall
down that is very
possible oh hiya fellas
oh this music is amazing wow hey guys
how are you doing
where'd you guys go uh we're mining
inside here
wow
[Music]
that was scary i'm a phoenix i have food
does anybody need food
water is useless in the desert well that
makes sense doesn't it
how do we put out fire if we
[Laughter]
don't get caught on fire oh no they're
friendly right they're finally different
like that yes
friendly oh they're friendly until
they're not
exactly this gold is far enough away
from them for me to mine
no don't take it don't take it no but
they're not even that close
science they're coming up
hello just let them leave you be nice to
them in here
they don't want any trouble
coming out excuse me should we set a
spawn point guys gotta protect his
dublin i want my
goal follow that yeah we'll find enough
gold somewhere else don't worry
there's other people over here we should
set us one point guys well this
this area is kind of nice if we if we
want to just make this the
the place to spawn at no bed that says
no bed why i have one
oh yeah be my guest they
what happens when you sleep you get a 20
uh armor buff you're lying speed boost
you're lying what happens
get out of here
go what are we looking for in another
what do you do here
yeah well uh i think we're looking for
materials
what kind of materials i want soul sand
oh oh she's doing it yeah i do wonder
what vm oh man
amelia's gone them off wait where which
way do we come down angry
oh wait strider okay this is the way we
came from oh there's the bed
no don't don't let them out oh oh oh i'm
sorry i didn't know i didn't know
wait okay this is the way we came from
yeah look for the little lava board put
i put a lantern here so that we know
yeah we go
[Music]
so what are we going to do i didn't even
get oh i got gold nuggets oh
where are my mining you want to go down
here there's stuff down here if you want
to go here okay no
[Music]
who's going to be the uh i mean who's
going to be the uh the tesla i mean the
who's gonna
kiara who's gonna
kiara you sleep now i mean i legit wanna
see what happens
go to bed all right we'll we'll pick you
up from home
okay wait let me get a good angle ina i
only trust you with my stuff
i don't like what i'm hearing from chad
about sleeping in another sword
uh that's why chad kept saying set a
spawn point okay that makes sense they
want us all to die all right i see
i understand now potatoes it's not gonna
happen and
one more two take off 14
hello i got it all thank you are you
guys ready
to watch this he's blocking my kid out
of the way oh god this
isn't gonna be good yeah he's he really
is
i'm ready all right go kyoto i'm doing
it
it was nice knowing you all goodbye
[Music]
wow fireworks
that's one way to get somewhere but wow
are you okay
so you you are going to try you are
going to try and make me do that see
even even the pigs are like what is
happening
this
does not scare me so i'm i can do i can
do it again and again
i gotta stamp out the flames oh [\h__\h] i
have the gold armor
wow give it to me look at me oh wait
where are you
all right here oh wait the door they
really look like that
is right
i think that was worth it right that was
totally worth it yeah we
got an easy way down
thank you
torches yeah follow the torches
it's the big floaty thing oh
this
[Music]
i want this for my home
my new home in the cave a fortress a
biome
ah
[Music]
can we fight it okay yeah oh i don't
have a
bull is it is it
is i think it's just randomly shooting
or is it oh i think that it knows that
we're here so it's gonna try and
actively
kill us
well we can go this way uh maybe we can
i'm not
close enough and do your worst
yeah let's go this way up the stairs
i got yours it's like a pig hut hey guys
our friends
can we kill that thing you can deflect
the fire you can attack the ball when it
shoots it and it shoots it back at the
guy
does anybody want to try this battle
time
i shall give it a shot so you have a lot
of health because you might catch on
fire
i'm in full health
i'm on fire now no what
well oh well if i'm gonna die anyway i
might as well give it a try
aim at me
yay it works nice we need this died so
easily what the heck
i
oh are those the glowstone thingies
oh yeah there's a forest over there
let's go that way i think we can build
it
first cool oh there's a way yeah we can
build a bridge here
a bird yeah
you guys are good at that team
seriously wow i'm impressed
it's nice that this stuff comes apart so
easily you have to hold shift right
so much goal yes hold shift hold
i got you
so what happens can we make another
nether portal does it exit out somewhere
on the other side
but it'll probably be really far away
from where we came from
like super far really pretty one is wow
in the outer world right
beautiful now what how do we get down
build some stairs here if we hold shift
we can't fall right
right okay that's what i thought that's
what i thought kelly
oh were you wrong uh i don't know maybe
you might just
get more wrong this is it's possible see
hold on no no no
this far away enough from the piglets to
to get the gold
guys is the btf the music is so loud for
me there's like music and game and it's
like wow that's like special
special
wait what is this hell's wart
red grass oh [\h__\h] oh wait i have pirate
game hold on don't listen to what i'm
saying
i like i like can i if i take this stone
can i take it back to the to the real
world
i want my walls to be this color yeah we
should we should probably try to go back
after we collect some of this stuff
because like uh if we collect too much
and die it'll
just be like a waste a big waste yeah
so collect as much stuff now and then
we'll go back for like a few minutes
another i met another floatie
pump what is that is that a lightsaber
oh yeah it's live it's floating wait i'm
shooting down where is he
there what's that sound you hear that
literally yeah
a
yeah yeah don't be a coward i say as i
run away
coward
you're gonna be quicker than that buddy
i want a garden with these plants
here are these ones
wait i thought they saw a fortress i'm
gonna go to the fortress wait this is
wood
or trees oh what a cutie hello who are
you
are these villagers oh
is that pumbaa
it looks like there are other people
here they don't look uh nefarious or
mean
maybe they're other explorers i i have a
sneaking suspicion that the pumbaa is
not so friendly
but we shall see
[Music]
chad says they are hostile so maybe we
shouldn't go say hi
oh
we just built a bridge to get a little
one dominance all right cool i'll help
i'm behind you
okay oh wait they're fast hold on there
are a lot of people
hold on wait wait wait wait wait i don't
shoot first
there's so many of them it's fine we'll
be okay well it's easy see they're all
equipped with swords
so if we taunt them and we get them to
come at us then we just knock out the
bridge
hey [\h__\h] boys
come over and fight us and you want to
fight
oh we can give gold to them and maybe
they'll be friendly yeah let's try i
have a bunch of gold
i'll go hello
huh i was i was ready that i was ready
to shoot that's fine enough
ready to start blasting i'm going to
raise back up i'll be back up
okay yeah we're here to help i don't
have a i don't have a bow and arrow
though so i'm going to have to melee oh
wait that's
really far hold on i'm not prepared you
believe
are those the ones that won't attack it
oh
i put on the binding booths does anybody
want iron boots
uh yes i could go take it swear um
crossbow wait can i have that who's
attacking no no try to trade him what is
that
oh
[Music]
i'm glad that things ended peacefully
but i'm more i'm warning you
don't mess around with us i'm ready to
start swinging
thanks chad i'm no coward
i also want to try the kacha i want to
do the kacha the gold kacha yeah
[Music]
do i just throw it at him huh thank you
what do we do with it
try to give it to him but right click on
him right okay
[Applause]
it okay all right we're good
wait i'm going to try this guide to
machine i want to when i open it
when i did the right it held up it held
up a shield instead
when i right clicked so i left clicked
and it hit him with it
okay i wanna do gold i didn't give you
one here
yeah the the piglet took it right away
from me
oh i see they try to pick it up okay so
how do i
hold it in your right hand and right
click on them stop
okay now give me something good
he gave me a meatball
i have something too
[\h__\h] maybe we should build a portal here
oh that's cool
you gave me a meatball what am i
supposed to do
what did he give me oh
i don't know i got something
he's running away water bottle
he gave me something
[Music]
did not drop the harpoon though or what
is it the crossbow
water bottle i got a water bottle what
does it do
gotcha don't you run away
oh wait you little hey what does this do
wait hold on
that's right
thank you chad thank you wait do we know
how to get back i can throw this spicy
meatball
easy oh yeah here's our bridge okay our
bridge is here i'll put
uh here
hey so the meatballs uh it's like
throwing heartburn
when you throw the the the the spicy
meatball they give you it makes fire
uh oh uh-oh
hang on it's fine i got him
hey flying split come here let's play
i'm ready to party
look at this wide open tournament i will
fight you nothing in hand-to-hand combat
come here
coward bring it squid well you judge me
i'm just getting the way back for us
really quick securing it
okay coming back yeah
he's afraid of us
which one this one
[Music]
that's fine that's mine i gave it to him
i gave it to him
give me something
hello oh little one hello little one
the noises they make are so interesting
hey come back
it's so cute hello
what are you doing you're too young to
hold a weapon
hello how do i get the soul sand
maybe it's a different biome
[Music]
something um oh you got some
yeah i got it uh for gold i don't think
that was uh
sorry i can go look for more gold if you
guys want to do that
i don't think we could take the gold
from here what are these
is that good sorry my scythe swinging
tutor instincts were kicking in when i
saw the little one i got something
really great
apparently i got something amazing what
did you get
ten spectral arrows and the chats
pog what do those do can you shoot those
arrows you can't see the person you shot
that's all it was
oh it's like walking through the wall oh
we probably can't mine these gold darn
it yeah
we can um i'm addicted
we can find gold on the way back give me
something it's build gold yeah
my
crimson roots i like them and gives you
it's like some uh what is it worth the
world stuff i like it
yeah okay i want to save my
actually i don't have to save my gold if
anybody say anybody want to go again i
have three left
i have some i wanna i'm gonna milk them
for what they got let's see what you got
give me some stuff wait how you want to
go again
i got another piece of gold we gotta
come over here
there you go over here over here
thank you gold dealer did you just
there you go amma is the dealer for
everything thank you he robbed me
he wrote anything oh it's this guy no
tell him
do they all aggro if you attack one
yes i think so yep oh okay let's not do
that
what did he give me yeah enough did you
take my item that he gave me oh
do you guys see this huh you guys gotta
come see this
oh guys gotta come see this
[Music]
what what does the chicken do in the
nether oh i got
um
i
[Music]
can we keep them hi you want to come
back to the real world
you guys want to build a portal here and
see where it goes yeah
we're friends i like your gold sword
little one
oh
this is nonsense all right again
anybody has who has the flint yeah the
minneapolis
do the orange yes i will do
let's oops
sorry my bird brain is uh not being
activated three two one go oh
we're in some sort of cave oh oh
[Laughter]
like an exciting outside area that we
never saw before like a nice
new bike oh wait wow why are there
torture
oh i put it i put it just now wait are
we back at the real world
is that uh deep in the ground that's up
and down right right where we come
where it comes out i feel like
it's how long it's not gonna be like
before they glow
or unless they're sand all right hey
guys should we sleep now
[Music]
like that kind of blue i have one what
is
good should we set a respawn point i
wonder
santa oh never mind
we are we might be underwater hey
everybody get ready to uh
swim i brought a door just in case
[Music]
something i have experienced before oh
sorry i took here
wait where's the face oh there's watson
it's gonna be the ocean
making me feel like it's going to be
ocean yes okay maybe we should go back
what could possibly go wrong no i can
also be a
pyramid or something like that i died in
one before
whiskey pyramids we should build a
pyramid how cool would that be
yeah let's actually we're down we should
be pretty close to the surface actually
right now
yeah yeah yeah i'm struggling hold on a
minute
i can't play this game um it's okay
ah no no i'm sorry i was trying to mine
the stairs
all right it's just a scratch it's like
sorry
i'll be
oh i think we're close to getting out
santa's
yeah yeah yeah no we're fine it's okay
that definitely wasn't my fault
it's okay ah we did it
whoa where are we
all right i need to i need to keep
mining so i might hit you
oh the desert cactus
no wonder it took us so long looks like
dystopia like we came out in the
dystopian future
can we take it i should have brought my
diamond pickaxe
fireman's stick oh gold hey
we can't i only have can we can we go in
this portal is it like continue in the
lava right
what's in the chest i took it there was
a shovel and a hoe
yeah yeah yeah yeah for water yeah it
doesn't give me the gold
i can't it's too high up hold on i'll
build away uh
oh nice there's a village
but this one is too long i think we got
a
oh yeah one two three four oh no no it's
fine it should be
wait a second no it has to be and i'll
see what yeah yeah
we just have to get rid of these two
blocks we're not gonna be able to save
it but we can remove it and then replace
it does anybody else have an opinion
i have crying obsidian i gotta go see if
this is the village i think
crying obsidian is different though oh
apparently we screwed it up
oh oh really oh there is yeah we can no
we can still
we just
i don't think so is this one that i have
in my hand different amelia
you can't mine it oh oops
we don't have enough obsidian to make a
new one i have
three oh okay okay
three three six eleven wait how much do
we need in total it's four
by what is it wait
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven
twelve three extent some people are
saying it doesn't work the one that i
have
oh just kidding oh the bright obsidian
doesn't work
no which way did you guys go uh
i know the way the way tool
let's just leave this place yeah yeah
wait okay we can come back to it to
retrieve it which way did you go
yeah where is it there's a temple over
there temple
hold on did you guys empty the chest yet
i'm going to empty it what am i doing
here guys do the water
mine the what where are you guys
you don't need the corners oh
yeah but i only have five blocks and
kiara here how many did you have three
three oh uh but they're not the glowy
ones right it's just regular obsidian
it says obsidian okay is it trap
you might be able to build it then let
me try
all right we already have them here in
the floor so if we do
you guys said we don't need the corners
so does anybody
[Music]
we just need to lure a creeper over here
wait a rabbit oh yeah
accurate the creeper doesn't blow up
obsidian i tried
oh oh come here two bottom tops
why are you in the desert onto oh i see
what you come here out
come here come here you guys mean
okay i can just do here then
okay so like this
no i have to oh okay i see i see
i'll replace this with sand like this
and then go on
no yes this is right that's right
this seems like a difficult problem
like a puzzle huh well then it is okay
i'll
do a mock one okay this is one two three
oh and then we don't do the corners so
we do like not the middle
mine
[Music]
and
isn't that too then yeah kind of short
okay
one longer one longer or higher one
higher longer yeah
perfect holy
yes
okay okay all right now i just replace
this side so one two three four five six
seven eight right guys yes
should be the one is this this is long
enough he's fine they said chad says yes
um yeah this looks okay imagine if this
was one higher on the ground then it
would make sense
sounds good i have the coordinates don't
worry we have the right amount
all right kyra i'm waiting for you i i
think i seen it i'm coming
no we already tried to use this one that
we built but we can't mind the obsidian
so we have to try again because it's not
tall enough
yeah and we don't have a diamond pickaxe
with this because i didn't bring one
because i was scared i was going to lose
it
oh yeah see him but i don't mind i'll
bring it with us if we get back home
because like i have more diamonds it's
fine
[Music]
almost there are you oh he's getting it
thank you i'm not a pyramid nice
where i want to see oh wait that's just
a bunny
and give us your coordinates good uh
i've been trying to say i'm in a pyramid
could you hear me
yeah i was trying to look for gouda but
then i got lost
a cat yeah oh yeah there are cats yeah
but that's a bunny just a bunny there
are cats though in the desert
cats i am a paleontologist
that's a dinosaur person though right
yes yep ah
i feel a paleontologist okay oh my god
the wizard is like endless
yeah who discovers mummies what are they
called historians
mummy mummy excavators
i'm an excavator that's a truck isn't it
what
uh probably i mean they stole it though
um what should we do we gotta wait for
you guys
we're we're still in another portal we
don't know
oh hold on who's coming hi and i saw
what i thought was a um
he got us here hi kiara
[Music]
yes
now let's try with the flint yeah
it worked wow but now we're gonna
help each other
hello me too me too let me in huh
okay looks good oh hey we're going back
in
yep yeah hey the little one is still
here
are we in the same place as before
yeah we only went up i just didn't want
to go back down like some dudes
so we came back in from the same same
gate okay look at these guys jump in
here
oh that oh this is the same hello
yeah torches in here remember you close
and it ends up
i'm coming well they look happy to see
me
whoa whoa the groundwork lights on the
ground lights on fire when you jump sir
oh that's what cali's looking at hello
cute okay
all right well i know the way back to
the home in the cave in the cave okay
okay the cave we uh we uh we started
[Music]
bye guys thanks for being so chill
they weren't bad dudes all right i'm
ready to fight there's another pumbaa
i'm ready too oh
he's running away all right i'll let you
go
[Music]
all right there's a bridge here we'll
follow this bridge
okay okay i'mma is so reliable honestly
out
it's like oh somebody would go back up
this way
she is the detective okay
eye attention to detail watson yeah
and then be careful on these stairs easy
to fall
wow one at a time
bridge like we're like following the
mother bird
so i made the birds too nice
[Laughter]
oh yeah this is where kiara blew up
sorry
there you go
because his name is the little strider
fella hi he's our little landmark
you shall not get he's lost oh
i did not get any gold because i gave it
all to the gata
okay i think it's fun too i was going to
get more gold to give to them what i
found this hole
goodbye friend i hope i'll see you again
soon why
i wish i could pat you on my head but
i'd
good job guys success and we did not i
mean the only person who died is me
right
and i died on purpose yeah exactly
wow we're making like progress how many
times have we died
last time too many and there's another
man
[Music]
golden sword benjamin
it's not the one that's mad at me right
i don't think so
enemies here don't seem as big of a deal
after coming back from the nether
i can't die right now i got so much no
you leave ina alone i'll kill you
i got it you got it do you want to sleep
or do you want all i'm good for is
hitting things
um well i got more guys there's
i did it
[Music]
purple purple i got purple wood
nice yeah
oh did you kill them nope they're just
walking around they're chilling
yeah i should be able to darn it stem oh
whatever that is i'm sorry but for my
house
purple door i'm working on my house now
no you can oh yes you can i'm done okay
oh nice side outside
those are there's a phantom holy sleep
yeah phantoms
what what mushroom wait
maybe we should sleep one night just
yeah good idea
let me explain my bed all right i'm in
my bed just a moment
here for now
[Music]
good morning good morning this morning
though oh they're burning they're
burning haha
okay my house i'm scared
okay guys i'm gonna take the i'm gonna
go get us that strider i'm gonna go
bring him home
oh yeah yeah bring stuff to like capture
those dudes
it's a good idea and the mushroom and
stick
what flavor mushroom does he eat though
oh
i have a bunch of mushrooms i got a blue
one
a brown one and a red one
depends on more flavor than this red
these are blue
mushrooms uh you got a blue one
the one do you have one of them
i have one yeah that's what he eats
apparently
okay hang on so i don't i don't know who
i guess he dies if he's outside of the
lava oh
you know i'm in in there i mean that's
still pretty good can you i wonder if
you can make a little pen
hold on right or something
all right i brought some fence wait well
would it catch on fire in there
you put it down uh i don't know
outside of the uh portal
oh yeah that's good yeah i bring some
materials
no no beds no beds okay
just like furnace and crafting tables
ah no i didn't mean to do that i can't i
can't oh i can't stand
hang on oh how do i get up i'm not
getting up there's so many
okay high ceiling because i am tall oh
cali's house to be yes i'm working on my
house
welcome ina i'm still landscaping it yes
my pool
do you like it it was here when i found
it this is for your organ not you
all right i'm ready to go back again
yeah we go back in i don't know uh
stream in like 45 see it's our members
well we can just build a house in there
and then we can like stay pretty close
yeah yeah it's just like a square house
cool yeah in another yeah yeah yeah
sounds fun let's do it
yeah wait i mean do you have that
mushroom oh yeah i got it
like that not what
yeah my god
[Music]
three hits
uh
need the mushroom for crafting yeah
here you go
hey yo welcome i'm going back in
did you make our little face here like
wait here ina's got a crafting table i
can use this one
okay here uh i want to use these blocks
hold on
there you go i want to help
pick a guess polish
uh is it the usual
what you will call it the usual like
horse armor
okay i guess yeah
hi y'all buddy
yeah they're having a nice little bath
it's like an onsen for them
yeah they're just chilling with the hot
springs
later losers we should make a hot spring
hold on he's dying
coming should we hit him wait what is he
doing no
why is he purple oh he's
him already no
he he's just a little anemic that's all
he's fine he doesn't need a nap
and uh it's cold
how do you
now i see okay i get i understand why
you're standing there
i have a fence if you want to build him
a little paddock
maybe we can build him a path hey go
a lava path yeah look
oh i see what you mean can you walk on
magma rock
no he's waiting for us for all of us
he's at our back
you can but it hurts a bit see easy way
easy way down now
what kiada yes we're trying to make it
oh okay okay it's okay it's okay
you're fine look now we can easily sail
hey our trusty seed we can perfect it
later
but for now yeah thanks for your service
buddy
he's cute i know right maybe we can
connect over here too
the rest of the roof with it cool
[Music]
that's too bad
oh where'd homie go
that looks like a knife house damn did
he leave where'd he go
where'd the strider go oh he fell
he fell oh no is it my fault
is he dead
oh
[Music]
sorry my my keyboard is in japanese okay
hold on back to the game
okay all right he's down he's landing
wait but how are we going to get him up
here i'm going to be running oh fancy
[Music]
i want to be the hero yes beer here
hold on i'm going to i should have
brought you here
oh my god i haven't had more of this
wood that we can use
nice
our neighbors are here our neighbors say
hi
oh um i have a pickaxe do you want mine
no oh yes thank you
thanks a lot is it okay thanks yeah i
think it's a little bit
different i want to use that rock for it
oh wait i picked it up hold on here here
does anybody have any wood yeah yeah
thank you
oh wait okay here yeah i need i need a
um
i
oh yeah you do the sign yeah where'd he
go
right below okay so as long as you make
your way down nice and easy you'll be
fine all right i'll go save our friend
oh that looks cool hang on
okay um this is gonna take some brain
power but i got it
done oh
oh i think we can only give the gold to
the villagers i guess not these random
pigs yeah
i tried
oh you tried to give it to me anything
hang on and this is
there's probably a roundabout way to go
let's just keep moving this way
maybe i can make some stairs wait hold
on just kidding
no i can't yeah there are no stairs that
will be made here uh it's okay
i'm gonna move to i'm gonna move this
way until hang on
it's fine we got it whenever i can build
actual stairs i do this
making progress hey you could be a
architect
oh thank you architect
watson yeah amelia
oh i didn't die i just came out to get
some wood
where where is everyone in the indiana
saving our friends
i'm back cali and gouda are making their
way to save
strider yes is that his name
that's what he's called you can name him
if you want though i like that it's okay
here we keep stretching him i'm not
going
all right i'm gonna make a joke right up
let me get it on camera
okay let's see
getting getting closer i bet i can put
uh you made that jump
yeah brave
i know i got to save our homie
should i extend the i have two more
chests should i put it
uh just a minute
wait where'd he go is he moving is he on
the move
i mean
he can't be far okay he didn't go that
far
yeah yeah yeah yeah you think he could
did he open
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello i come in peace i wonder
i wonder if there's another village
that's closer whoa i guess that one we
found is the closest one
yeah no
i found him we know i hit him it's like
a village
i'm riding on him but i'm i'm on fire
i'm on fire
yeah i died well it was a valiant ether
but i found
him i found him oh i'm back here too
can someone go pick up my stuff i'm here
i'm here
come on thanks good all right something
i know also where am i oh wait what
happened
yeah i caught on fire i found them but
then i caught on fire
oh i don't know where i am
uh you're probably oh [\h__\h]
are you okay gooda we're fine we're fine
we're fine
did you die we play calm we're calm
we're calm we're cool collected we're
comical collecting assistance
are you okay oh we're fine did you die
because of me
no no no no we didn't panic we're good
we're good i'm scared i don't want to go
down
sounds good this area is familiar i
don't know where i am but there's a
village i'm going to go look in it
a village yeah
go to a high place and look for the h
and that's the entrance to the tunnel
and you can just take a minecart in
there from uh
the emergency exit i need to okay thank
you
do you see the h okay uh i'm in a
village hold on a sec i need i i can't
get to a high place right now hang on
one second
i'm good i'm good i'm with strider and i
got cali stuff
thank you you gotta you're gonna have to
where are you yeah how are you gonna get
can he jump i see a house
i i this is house
i don't know how i'm gonna do this can
we swim up lava probably
not right so it is all my fault
i'm sorry everything no no no no no no
no down there
i think he'll be there probably wait i
should have my pickaxe here
yes yes yes yes
hi friends you cannot look like a face
listen you gotta move you can walk
around
sure nothing in there
get out of here okay um assistance
is required in the netherlands i'm okay
are you okay i'm okay with your
coordinates
i'm right outside i can see all your
names um
um there's a gas do you see
oh oh they're on fire
oh wow i'm on fire you guys take out the
gas
which one but it like went away i see it
um it's
gone right here oh what's here is that
one around this corner
i think so it's getting closer to the
pig village because there was the path
that went
sort of in this direction over there
she's down there well i'm i'm i'm i can
see your guys's names i'm like
uh right down here well i'm so scared i
don't like hiding
oh no you're fine i see watson's tennis
racket
i
i don't think our friend will leave i
think we can leave him here so i'm just
gonna
yeah just park him there it's his
parking spot
yes that's a really far far a parking
spot hello can you guys clear my uh
headspace here
why are you good yup oh wait it's good
okay yeah yeah
and we got a house we got a panic room
and
i'll be back soon away
oh wait i could have written on the
strider but he's so fast i don't trust
myself
well if you guys want to play gotcha
before we go i got i brought a bunch of
gold
i brought some gold too that sounds fun
but read up there's a lot well
we'll wait for cali to get back oh
thanks guys
does anybody have a chest that i can put
cali's stuff in oh there's a bunch of
guys thank you
for doing that by the way i will make it
up to you oh no worries
yeah it's okay i'll put it in uh what
did you have
um i just want my nether stuff like uh
to build my house with cool things like
uh
there were some i feel so stupid why
didn't i put that
stuff in chest before i get the second
time yes
i'm silly i'll come help in just a
second i'm on my way
um
building a nice path to the gotcha
i'm here thank you everyone
wow it looks something there but you
have a really cute face
thank you gouda which one is it
perfect yeah yeah yeah i don't know if i
missed anything i think you got
everything thank you
looks right to me baked potatoes yeah
i'm hungry
yeah so strider is down there where we
left him he won't really go anywhere
oh okay oh i wonder
um yeah i guess there's not much we can
do about that huh
darn it i wanted to rescue you i can
come back
when i don't have anything um yeah yeah
nice i think you can build like
staircases
we'll get him something to walk up oh
yeah yeah
he looks like that outside of lava right
so we can just build him a really really
long
long staircase yeah yeah yeah
we have enough rocks
that's a that's a project for another
time i suppose huh yeah
yeah we'll save them later oh go go
let's go
where are you kara i'm where are you
guys yeah
oh okay
oh i just okay i just left let me put
some stuff away i'll come back
well right before the ah yeah i want to
go put some stuff away too actually oh
callie
you should put your arms on yeah oh
that's right oh that came off huh
i'll continue to mine the path to the
village sorry i lost the gold snapback
hello oh yeah do you need some gold
armor so they don't
[Music]
yes this way that's fine let's go
yeah i'm just gonna put my things in my
chest real quick crying obsidian no
oh yeah it's gone huh oh well
i know i used it i panicked and i used
it oh it's okay
oh that was yours yeah oh my god i'm so
sorry it's okay you're good
thanks for getting my more i am in your
business
you don't have to it's okay we have a
craft table at the home panicked
it's all good no it's not that far what
does it do
anyway i don't know it's purple
yeah it is very beautiful but do i
really want to wing
all my gold at the gacha again do i have
i have gold for you
i have like a ton more at home oh my god
oh wait we're playing
amelia the gold woman
here i want to play me too let's go
let's go oh why i don't need this
railroad
goal it is like i thought it was the
stairs
uh make this
[Music]
i have no i don't have any back
no is it called rock or rack
rack yes wreck like quack
yeah yeah another wreck are you guys
should i take the pig village path
uh yes yes yeah okay i'll follow the
torches
nice shiny swords you got there buddy
oops
[Music]
oh so i guess nether spawn points can be
used instead of beds i didn't know about
that
we used the crying obsidian to make
those
bright the bright one the crying one
um it's okay we'll find some more
almost killed me oh we can mine it back
with our
diamond pickaxe i brought mine wait
where is it yeah yeah
yeah almost died
almost died some of them have gold armor
[Music]
you know are you building this is this
where the ender dragon is i'm just
making it so we don't have to know it's
a good idea
this is not where he is where's the
ender dragon i want to see him
[Music]
maybe it's for another time how do you
summon him
what do you gotta say then we have to
find that gate thing and then like
complete it
and then like you gotta go find him
i'm ready to gotcha knock on his door
boom
i think we have to be like all diamond
everything to do that right
and no no no no i mean like for our own
safety
i like this basically uh uh i watched
like
20 hours of uh uh and and
uh rta yes
and the dragon rta so i know how to do
it
but we are not we're
why you kind of make a different kind of
portal
ender pearls and there's a few ways to
get the ender pearls but it takes a long
time
oh
right eventually i like your sword was
that
oh are you able to move sir sir you look
like you're having a hard time down
there
ready are you okay do you need help
getting back up sir
see it yeah thank you oh i hear it oh i
hear him hello
you know huh i'm okay well there he is
oh i see it let's break our bridge i
think he's gone oh he's right there
jellyfish in the sky come here uh that
would be the safe choice
go do it girl i don't think i don't
think i can make that shot i can't make
this shot he's so
we can get a little closer no it's so
far away i don't think i can make that
there's our other portal too nice
let me shoot him out in the open well
here we are
no he's too far up where are all the
villagers there were so many here before
they died what what i don't know
there's some homies over here maybe
they're sleeping maybe it's night time
for them yeah
where's their house they're training the
little one
uh no but i can make one i think
well then
run away right i have one
put it right here put it right here by
the bridge
[Music]
gold gotcha
thanks amelia for the free gold yeah big
ups
three and you get three thanks oh you
picked yeah sorry
uh-oh he doesn't he really doesn't like
me oh he's a
girl why is that why oh god i'm gonna
die it's fine i'll help
ah that was a close one i wonder why
he's acting oh yeah i have one heart
we'll see what happens
wait do you need food yeah who's that
girl
yeah i'm matt how are you kelly
yeah i am sorry
i didn't bring any food i thought we
were just gonna do gotcha so i didn't
bring any food
i actually don't have any gold anymore i
wonder what happened is the man on fire
boy you in the gold pants
here come back sorry amelia i think that
when you gave me the gold you
accidentally picked it up again
i don't have anything huh yes give me
something
are you okay i'm okay
thank you thank you thank you big ups
thank you
i don't know that's a boy
[Music]
where are the villagers yeah it's
probably just dead dudes huh
i see one he has a gold helmet come here
oh he's running away
come here are you scared of me oi here
look
ah no he's hurt he's aggro
i died oh my god kelly i'll grab your
gold
wow
oh my god oh i'll take the steak
yeah take the steak
alley bed again yeah oh my god no
i was just gonna give him gold and then
he turned on me
i think i think if you're holding gold
they'll attack you because they're the
they're not the villagers it was a
villager though it was a regular dude he
wasn't like a zombie-like guy or
anything
not a single good thing came out of this
one i did something with
him looks rich yeah let's see if it
gives me anything
uh what was that a block what the [\h__\h]
uh you're doing something good not
a single good thing i did something
weird with my keyboard
string i think it's the end for your boy
on this one here
i'm gonna get yeah we should we should
probably call it soon because cali's got
a stream
yeah time to wrap it up
wait did did anyone find any of the
trader
gotcha trader i thought i did
but he started blasting nice okay i
didn't drop
anything actually that's good because
then i can
take the catcher home and don't waste it
all right we can go back i'm going back
okay okay let's go
i'm in that same village too i got lost
again
[Laughter]
tried to swim in lava i doubt that game
somehow i doubt that she tried to swim
in the water
all right i'm i'm good with another i'm
ready to go home
kelly are you still in the village yeah
i'm trying to i'm looking for watson's
uh tennis racket
i can't find it oh okay okay okay a big
one a big scope
no it's a magnifying glass terrace
rocket
oh my god
wait where did you die kiana because in
the lava
yeah yeah i know but like wait
so clearly this is the wrong direction
got it okay
are we gonna do operation find kelly
sorry i will find it don't worry i'm
getting up high
what did they do you know okay so listen
i wasn't
i wasn't wearing any gold armor and
apparently that's a thing that's
you need to wear a piece of gold
ah it all makes sense now
yes
oh you don't have to i'll make some i
promise i'll start minding my own stuff
i don't want you guys to have to do
everything for me
no no no help we help yes we help each
other we help
yes team we are one
we are one thanks guys i want to be good
at video games
maybe someday
let's see what's inside gosh where is
watson's tennis racket
there's watson that's the real question
where's watson yeah we're night and gold
hold on
where's waldo where's watson where in
the world is
what's wrong with is watson
hold on i'm coming wow that's steak
what oh i do okay
wow minecraft is so pretty another come
back i see an incredibly tall building
so this must be the right way
like ridiculously tall one black
building yeah
oh no
wait how did you drown she drowned in
front of my house i just kind of watched
it
you what what was i supposed to do
okay hopefully our house will survive
i'm in the basement fine okay
all right i shall wait for you all here
big stretch today's remember stream is
going to be a sleepy stream
sleepy it's okay it'll be fun
all right we're all here yay
you can do the the ending right here by
the tennis racket
yeah sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i know i
know it's a mining
i'm not a mining i'm a magnifying
magnifying glass
yeah it's a beautiful magnificent on it
you guys will see
yeah it's a beautiful magnifying glass
it looks just like a mustache record
wait where are we meeting us
do you want to do a minecraft stream
with me where we build a huge chess
field oh
[Laughter]
ah yes the chest feels to always
commemorate that legendary chest stream
professional chest i'll hear cali i
think this is your stuff
all right whole thing oh oh yeah thank
you hold on
oh thanks for this thank you i'm sorry
i'm in a weird view right now all right
good here i have a present for you too
a present for me let's go over here turn
look at this oh crossbow
you should enchant that oh
okay she's got it oh uh cara i have a
present for you too
go
oh you don't have to wait what
nice good old
betsy you can because you can draw it
and then you can just have it drawn and
then you can shoot it
oh baby
the one and only now i want to give you
a present too so here you go
yay purple doors
yeah i said i just changed my door to
the purple one thank you
it matches my color
yeah i'm sorry color i'm in santa claus
cute thank you i appreciate that i love
you
guys okay okay
oh yeah come on what do you want for
christmas little girl
um you i still haven't i have two crying
obsidian you guys i still have it
bottom left
left let's fill my house and then make
my house next
oh maybe she wants me to hold some way
she wants me as a friend
flowers you just got friends don't care
that's okay i just want i just want a
friendship that's all
i keep friendship friendship forever and
ever
[Laughter]
it's magnifying glass i'm sorry i know
it now i understand now
yep yep yep wait like ah there we go
yay oh
we didn't yeah take a screenshot
previously i want to take one now
no yeah i'll take off i'm like i'll take
off like oh i don't have spots in my
inventory
unfortunately what's that huh yeah
there's a skeleton over here there's a
skeleton over here
yeah i was trying to shoot him down
photo op time
hey yay give me a second
give me a second how do i make the cats
go away
does someone know how to take the man
look at you wait i need to see
one there you go this is fine
yay
[Applause]
hey successful another trip
[Music]
[Applause]
nice
yeah thank you for watching yeah
[Music]
me and gouda are planning on playing uh
minecraft together next week so tune in
for that
[Applause]
i'll be there yay it's gonna be fun so
yeah come to that
i'm having another whole japan
collaboration
[Music]
schedule for me will be out uh tomorrow
or the day after tomorrow yeah
new week yeah almost here we go
all right okay thank you everybody for
watching
bye see ya
[Music]
i guess i i should turn off the i'll
stop the stream then
goodbye oh hey hey i'm gonna mute this
goodbye
sorry bye
you