[Music]
stop talking about important things
enough cease don't do it
what about that one thing we know we
forgot to talk about the important thing
that nobody
knows you know the one buddy
what about what i have for breakfast
everyone wants to know that
everyone wants to know hi
hello guys hi hi we're here we're live
we managed to do it somehow by the skin
of our teeth we're here
hello hello hello
do you like all the e's
all right let's do a let's do a volume
check first let's go down the line first
ena give us
give us some vocals
oh [\h__\h] that's louder than usual all
right
no no no it's good it's a good thing let
me fix you
let me fix you you know all right
again hello this is ina
all right good stuff good stuff perfect
next up
agura hit us with some vocals
perfect next up oh no
hit us with some vocals
help me there is currently a five meter
big
uh fly in my room trying to kill me five
five meters a circle
my cats are already on it my cats are
trying to kill it let's go
yeah let's go
all right and last amelia give us some
vocals
[Music]
such a star such a star
all right it really is yeah
all right should be okay now guys
welcome to the very first session of
myth breakers
oh man i'm i'm sweating with
anticipation i'm very nervous
i want to do much are you motivated um
baby listen i probably shouldn't have
admitted that i'm a bit nervous
as the gm um never never show the
players your fear
don't don't let them see it or maybe
it's a trick maybe it's a trick to make
you think that i'm afraid but but you're
the ones who should be afraid
no i think you should hear me i'm going
to shake your trailer
please don't do that close to dying but
we'll be fine well that's it's all good
in the neighborhood because we're going
to go into the end of the prologue
you guys where i kind of describe to you
um
what has happened after your situations
you see because things are actually a
bit out of time order
you guys oh oh yeah you see you did not
all arrive at the bar in chronological
order believe it or not
yeah interesting you did not
explain who was first interestingly
enough
me me uh actually
interestingly enough um the first to
arrive was the ones that we left off on
scout doc nice and scout's sister were
the first to arrive at the bar
interesting yep they were the very first
to arrive there
well well let's go ahead and do a little
a little flash back to the past as you
guys are driving down the road together
and eventually
are able to buy the skin of your teeth
find out where the bar is and only
because
doc nice is a little bit better with
directions than you are
thank god yeah thankfully scout you guys
were able to find the bar
and when you arrive scout i want you to
go ahead and
do um a perception check for me
okay let me tell you how to do that go
to the chat
right and you have to type a slash
forward slash okay roll uh-huh
roll and then what is your
wits plus composure scott do you
remember
no i don't have that sheet pulled up
right now ah grab that sheet
go grab that sheet i'm sorry i knew i
forgot something
it's okay no worries we're chilling
we are chilling i typed e a bunch of
times in the
the roll 20 chat because the the link to
join the session was in there and even
though you had to hover over it to show
it
i just i got a bad feeling
so i typed a bunch of e's
okay i got it all right what are we
rolling uh perception check which is
wits plus composure widths plus
composure
okay is there space after roll yes
there's a space it's slash roll space
yes four four d ten
okay four d ten greater than symbol
do you know what the greater than symbol
is it's like a sideways v
it's opening up to the left
it looks like this i'm going to do an
8d10
great uh greater than we don't okay
listen for d10
for d10 greater than eight i will type
it for you looks like this
i got zero successes yes it is eating
the bigger number okay let's see how
many successes you get
okay so forward slash rolled for d10
greater than and then go right and yeah
okay perception yeah i got the bar by
the boat mathematics
um that's a capital that's a capital d
uh so use a lower case d
and then put in eight okay
wait there's an eight at the end yeah
you want it to be greater than eight
because that will count all of your
successes eight nine and ten
and it'll tell you how many successes
you got
it was anything over eight counts
exactly okay roll four slash roll
four d ten greater than
eight yes essentially exactly what i
rolled just now
okay one success yay okay nice job yeah
you did it first roll the game wow
technically the first fill was the four
which is fitting somehow
um since it's my campaign and four is a
great number but um this is good
this is a good start guys uh get ready
for these kinds of successes
um so you get one success
to basically perceive that this is a bar
this is the site that you see before you
interestingly enough waiting out front
of the bar is um
a slightly sledged over figure that you
can't really see in the dark looks a
little shady but as you approach
you realize that standing in front of
the bar is a nice
old woman oh geez i'm getting flashbacks
too
i'm not old no tiara you're not there
yet
you're not dead
so wait we're in the car still or we
pulled up we where where are we we're
pulled up to the front of the bar
you pulled right up to the bar the front
of the bar and there's a
little slouched over old woman standing
out front of the door
all right where do i park this thing
you could probably do it right here says
doc nice this looks this looks fine no
one's no one's around no
no police or anything should be okay
there's no police or anything i don't
know anything i don't know the first
thing about
meters and toes and things and whatever
i mean
the doc what are we doing here doc i
don't know what i'm supposed to be doing
here
i guess we could look for a parking
meter excuse me i will go look for one
you i don't know go make yourself
acquainted
figure out if this is the right place
and i will search for a parking lot
go talk to them go meet them maybe all
right
let's see what happens and uh if
anything bad happens just uh
just yell i won't be able to help very
much you're much stronger than me but
i will i will uh scream
maybe go get the papers
okay
all right um
well all right then i'm hopping out the
car i'm gonna hop out of the truck
and i'm gonna well to be quite honest i
don't want to get out of the truck
because i'm not used to this kind of
area i don't know i've never been in the
city before so
yeah i guess that's true not exactly i
feel like i'd be uh gripping the
steering wheel
uh quite a bit tighter than usual
waiting for
doc to return what i'm gonna be brave
oh right scout do what you're right
i'm gonna be brave all right
i'm gonna tighten my belt buckle and i'm
gonna step out of the vehicle
and approach the old
lady okay as soon as you start
approaching her she looks up at you and
says
oh hello there youngin how are you today
is it morning or night time it's the sun
is starting to come
up okay
uh fine morning
uh okay howdy ma'am
uh where's your finest uh establishment
for personal refresh
where's your bathroom oh
the bathroom ah let's see well all the
shops are closed right now so i think
the best
idea would be to go in the street
party you like some cookies i just made
a fresh batch
would you like some hey sister
lock the doors for me thank you ma'am
have a nice day ma'am
oh well goodbye then this is
man are there any man ma'am are there
any bushes around here you got any
natural greenery it doesn't seem to be
much well here in this concrete jungle
gym
that's right so no i'd say no you have
to pee in the street i think but you
could go behind your car that might be a
nice idea
ma'am thank you ma'am have a nice day
man
as soon as you turn around doc nice
returns and says whoa whoa whoa what's
what's going on why are you getting back
in the car
i need a restroom
doc okay well surely we can persuade her
excuse me hello ma'am hi uh we we came
from the countryside and we
really came a long way um so
would you let us into your establishment
um you want to enter here
she says well why didn't you say so
she offered me cookies how am i supposed
to know she owns this place well yeah
she's a woman of course she's gonna
offer you cookies
i'll be right back doc
i don't mean to remind you of the trauma
we just experienced but the last old
lady that we just
happened to be a half disintegrated pile
of mush on the bottom of a man eating
mine if you know what i mean
i know what you mean but listen it's
it's the only chance that we have it's
the only chance we have to go to the
bathless i have to go to the bathroom
too
no lie you're a fella though you can
just open the car
door just do whatever you please
actually i'd probably have some jar
some old dried up moonshine jars in the
back you could have just said something
honestly have you been drinking old
crinkles moonshine
no those are all right let's get to the
bathroom right now i've had an i've had
enough of you i've been in the car
far too long as soon as you say that the
old woman comes out
um and she looks at you guys says you
want to enter this place right and she
pulls out a shotgun
and points it at you yeah baby now
all right ma'am
uh
you can't enter here
[Music]
i suggest you leave
ma'am i'm not sure you're uh i'm not
sure uh now listen i'm not from around
these parts but i'm i'm i'm
thinking that there's a concealing carry
law that you must not be abiding by now
and
we don't i don't mean any trouble or or
any that's a nice shotgun though where'd
you get that from where'd you get that
mighty fine barrel from
i got some shells in the back if you if
you need any listen i really just need
to use your
your your restroom that's all i'm asking
for man there's no need for any
any violence or anything uh oh
my shotgun well you said i don't shoot
you
[Laughter]
ma'am i just happen to think of
something i'm always down for a
challenge if i can out shoot your shot
you let us you let me and my fine
friends into your establishment so
we can use your self-relief facilities
yes well sure sounds like a nice idea
how about we do that
all right sounds nice
all right so she she goes she goes ahead
and uh
grabs another shotgun and hands it to
you
she has a lot of shotguns and she hands
it not her special one now go ahead and
do a firearms roll
scout audrey lloyd okay
[Music]
roll mm-hmm and it's gonna be
firearms plus strength unless you have
fighting finesse
uh firearms plus strength
well that's not looking good for me i
first should have
three all right
um that should be fine you know what for
for the sake of right now um since we're
early in the game i'll let you choose
between strength and dexterity
if you like
um i'll go straight
sticks so that's not exactly much better
so do a
you do a forward slash roll 3d 10
greater than eight
three d ten greater than eight
oh oh oh oh
so you go ahead and you shoot at a trash
can nearby
and it narrowly misses and kind of
ricochets off the ground and hits
someone's window
your little crash but no sound
thankfully might have been
you got pretty lucky maybe there was no
one in there
granny grabs her shotgun and says okay
my turn
um while granny's aiming up the shotgun
do you mind if i
uh give the old woman a bit of a pat
down the secret
super sneaky pat down in search of the
key or is the door open can i give the
door a push and see if it's actually
open and she's bluffing
well thankfully thankfully for you uh
scout as soon as she shoots off this
shot that kind of is pretty mediocre for
how badass this grandma seems
um all of a sudden you hear a voice in
the distance
say wait wait wait hold up what is going
on here
why are you guys fighting stop stop stop
stop that right now
scout roll a perception check perception
check
i remember how to do this okay forward
slash roll uh-huh
four d ten greater than
eight yeah good yes that's correct
learning here we go
all right so re-roll okay do a slash
roll
one d10 because you reroll tens we don't
do exploding dice here because it's more
intense this way
greater than eight do you do greater
than eight every time greater than eight
every time
all right so with one success um
you realize that two people are kind of
waddling towards you
one of them looks to be a janitor of
some kind carrying a pizza box
and along with him is a severely wounded
other human being
i thought i smelt
you smell barn you'll be all right go
ahead and roll a perception check
me you will be all right
noodle enters the scene
all right so that is seven eight
ten greater than eight
one six one before your eyes yule
you see a merry band of misfits there
looks to be two
uh country bumpkin ladies and the doctor
a doctor uh who looks like uh he's very
confused and not sure if he should be
there or not
and also bodily burns yes severe bodily
burns and then
the one of the country girls with
incredible abs is holding a shotgun as
is the old woman vic seems to know at
least one of them
uh
[Music]
the older woman yes i'm acquainted i am
why did i pull off a
cowboy voice there i'm i'm i'm
acquainted with
her she's a co-worker of sorts this is
the bar
that that i told you about that is the
safe haven of
of sorts yeah i don't really know what's
going on here but
listen listen bertha it's okay they look
to be friends
are you guys are you guys here because
you're here to join the team
listen fella i'm not sure who you are
but i think you ought to try and keep
your old lady on a leash she's gonna
blow someone's head off with this
shotgun oh
it's okay bertha doesn't mean any harm
she's very she's very kind
she's just protecting the the land she's
always been the bouncer here
bouncer yeah you know someone
someone who who uh protects the the
front of the listen anyway we don't have
time for this uh this person's dying
also i wanna eat pizza so uh let us know
nice uh the doc immediately looks at you
and says oh goodness gracious me let's
get inside and i can help you
yes yes i know help is what you want
let's go
oh well why didn't you say so go right
inside bertha says and smiles
the entire time crazy old vet
crazy old bat um as you all are entering
the bar
um three other figures approach
in the distance
[Music]
basically um you um
wait a minute hold on a sec well so
there's not three figures in the
distance it's wattato with the dogs
and the merchant sales kid um so
you know this kid has been like sticking
around you for a while
um and was a great friend of your dads
and sold your dad's stuff so you
you don't have a complete reason to
distrust this kid
um he does tell you you smell funny a
lot yeah what's with your friend
you still smell funny anyway we're here
um
bertha went ahead uh i went ahead of you
guys um
she was one of the people that met with
you in the market but
she went back earlier to guard the the
homestead and you stuck around with the
merchant kid
um and he just kind of says ah looks
like uh berth is going a little crazy
again today
geez she needs to calm down anyway it
looks like someone else got in trouble
instead of us so we're all good
let's go watoto um let's go
yeah and basically what you perceive
with your dope perception role watson
is that this place is um it's a large
brick building
a large square brick brick building very
unassuming
hole in the wall style bar um
that you would see just maybe in the
shittiest area of town
um extremely unassuming um
there's a there's a sign out front that
says
the little whiskey happy hour which is a
little
strange oh yeah i see that yeah
you get the feeling though this place is
like one of those places that's really
dank and dirty and nasty
but the drinks are super good yeah
all right so you guys enter the bar
now we're gonna do a bit of a time skip
and we don't see what goes on inside the
bar but you guys have kind of
made yourselves comfortable there
they've offered you a place to stay
and rest mostly the focus has been on
healing yule's wounds
and telling you guys to sit tight and
the next day
the next evening um vic
of course has to leave he says he has
some business one final job
as a janitor to do
and wouldn't get uh give this white toto
fella a wash down he smells like he's
been rolling around
smell good for mushroom growth
i don't know i can't really tell what
the bandage is over my face
thanks zane is a sweet offer
yeah thankfully due to the the handiwork
of
doc nice um you've actually healed up
decently well and this is a one time
thing that's gonna happen for you
but all of your lethal damage aggro
damage is now converted to bashing
damage
yes that's like the two two
you still didn't want to turn into
yes it's all turned to bashing it's the
only time this is going to happen
is because you know doc nice is really
good
it's the only time thanks doc yeah doc
just gives you a thumbs up
doc is there for you um vic is returning
from
his final job and he's brought
someone with him
[Music]
another person go ahead
and roll perception tiara as you
approach the bar
uh it's um
forward slash roll and then wits plus
composure
greater than eight which
composure free three tens yes
greater than eight like that yeah
um you can't really tell anything about
this place but
here you're going towards it it's a bar
that's about all that you can tell
um from this place everything is very
confusing right now tiara you've been
through a lot
um so you know you're definitely feeling
a little winded
a little tired so you're not totally
able to take it all in
um but here we are it's a bar um
now i'm gonna show you guys uh tiara's
tiara's image because kusatori worked
hard on the art for it
i finished it tomorrow yes
there she is that's why my brain is so
empty right now
look at those thighs whoa whoa didn't
mean to zoom in there
this is who rolls up to the bar this is
he rolls up
to the bar goddamn yay that's
oh look at look at your cute owl
the owl has seen some [\h__\h] this all has
some [\h__\h]
look at those big eyes they've seen
everything really
yeah yeah so cute
so this is who rolls up this is who
rolls up to
the bar with vic um
and enters the bar you do hate him but
he's bringing you to the bar
he says he's got there's something nice
for you guys there
um nice for you at least a chance uh to
start again
to be safe um and so here you're going
to the bar now you enter the bar and now
everyone is in the bar holy [\h__\h]
wow you guys have made it
already in here into the bar that's
right now
i'm going to show you guys the inside
but first i need to hide this
okay can i roll to pet yara's jars bird
can you guys see the new place okay but
what if wow
who has its own will maybe who doesn't
like to be pet by strangers
um let's see um
who who contests the rose strongly
all right with five million d10s
i i want to roll um
um plus um oh who doesn't have a sheet
though it sure doesn't okay i'm gonna
make one up all right
you're gonna roll three as well let's
make this even
okay all three ten greater than eight
oops
wait oh i did something whoopsie oh okay
okay ooh he's gonna pick your eyes out
oh
[Music]
um so here's how it plays out watso
you kind of make your way up to ooh and
you get one hand
on the bird before it's chaos absolutely
like hell has broken out inside the bar
um
flapping around all over the place um
you're getting pecked all over
watertown
take one bashing damage
take one bashing damage it's one slash
in your health bar
okay that's what you get adam who the
hell are you
[Music]
don't touch my bird alan i don't even
know who you are anna
yeah you better be you know
oh my goodness all of the commotion has
has kind of brought a bit of a ruckus
up onto the bar um vic and some of the
others are just chilling on the couches
they've kind of done their job and
they're kind of sick of you guys already
um so you guys are kind of left to fend
for yourself
in the main area of the bar um
and as all of this commotion happens um
a woman
steps into the middle of the bar she
looks to be perhaps the bar master of
some sort
um and says
excuse me what's going on here what's
all that commotion that terrible racket
oh
well it looks like you all are here
finally
welcome welcome to the homestead
the homestead part of me can i
put my hand up oh sure
what's the homestead
everyone kind of laughs um and
uh she says it's the name of this bar
you're in it hon
welcome
i couldn't see the sign on the
i mean she kind of likes to hear you say
that because that seems to be
the plan at least in some way or shape
or form
um and she kind of gives you a nod and a
wink and says
uh glad to hear that um little little
troll goblin person uh thank you for for
joining
little stinky warty mushroom man
[Laughter]
can you um all right how about you all
introduce
yourselves well hold on i should
introduce myself first i've
i've brought you all here uh without any
real explanation so let me explain to
you what this place is
sorry you all are very tired i hope that
you've been able to rest a bit on the
couches
um basically the homestead bar is a
quaint
hole in the wall style crawl of a place
with not even really a single customer
here but
but you see this is a special bar it's a
bar for people who know
like you guys you know something yeah
something that other
normal people don't right yeah
people have seen what uh what lies
behind the curtain
and uh and also for those very
discoveries themselves so
you four have seen some truly
frightening things and you will continue
to see them there is no doubt about that
but this bar serves as a peaceful ground
between both
uh supernaturals and people like you
hunters
hunters hunters precisely fish
i would call it a falconer but if you
call it a hunter here i don't that's
fine
but hunters are a bit different you see
oh
how so well
hunters basically exist to hunt
supernaturals but in our case we don't
do that no no no
we do not strive to harm supernaturals
not this cell um
they are still our enemies but unlike
other cells we strive to maintain peace
and equity between our species and thus
this bar came to life it was started by
my mother
about uh 35 years ago
35 years ago she started this bar and i
am now continuing
running it um
i am i don't i don't mean to interrupt
you but
see i just came i just came from out of
town and
uh you see i've experienced a mind with
teeth
stomach acid and um i don't mean to be
rude but um
your life story wouldn't happen to have
something to do with that would it now
oh my man eating mines and
and and walls with teeth
and i mean you can look at my friend
over there on the couch he's
practically well i think he's always
been ugly but he's even more ugly now
because he's been eating away at the
stomach acid and i just
oh what the hell is this place i see i
see
it looks as though you encountered
something very strange possibly some
kind of anomaly that can't be classified
but
but nonetheless supernatural nonetheless
something strange that needs
investigation see that's what we do
here we investigate and we make sure
that the common public will never have
to encounter those kinds of things
we keep them out of reality everyone
this is a hunter cell after all you you
have a brother
you got a mouse in your pocket a mouse a
little
little farm rat in your pocket we no no
all of you strangers together i don't
like
but it worked so well 35 years ago my
mother was able to assemble a team just
like this and they all worked together
and
and they solved they solved uh
supernatural crimes and and helped with
diplomatic things and and oh gosh
i didn't really foresee this i'm sorry
i've been terribly rude to you all
please excuse me i i think
maybe you should get to know each other
a little bit better first but
but first let me set let me say what i
can offer you
before you make any decisions if you
stay
here you'll be safe from other
supernaturals and not only that but we
pay you money
real money and and ourselves
yes real money you can get real american
dollars here
for the work that you do right
and um and we also have other benefits
as a hunter cell
um specifically this bar the bar that we
have here the drinks that i make
specifically power you up in a in a
special way
you see um the drinks that i make here
um have often been called experience
drinks they basically power you up after
a mission
so when you come here and tell me your
stories uh i make you something special
and you can hone your skills
i was going to say it's like shield
juice from fortnite dude
on the shelf in the background sorry
what is
fortnite is that a game you play here
oh my gosh um but basically
she kind of continues and says i know
that this is all very
it's a lot so let me at least i can show
you around
i can show you around the place but
first introductions are necessary so how
about
you all go about and uh introduce
yourselves possibly
potentially would you be okay with that
let's all calm down a minute here oh
gosh i really [\h__\h]
up i don't know sharing
my name with strangers i would prefer to
wait a little bit and get to know you
all first anna before
i tell you about me how's them say all
right bird lady
bird lady you guys have no respect for
people like me i see
interesting anna i mean
she does have a point we
we just got to know each other but i
guess
at least the name is okay
well that's fine if you're not gonna
give me a name then i just i just won't
interact with you then i guess if you're
not giving me anything to go
off of them ma'am that's fine with me
i don't really i didn't really come here
to interact with anyone
anyway adam well all right fair enough
howdy everybody my name is scout and i'm
from a little town called belt buckle my
parents
are well my parents are
being chased down by the police for
possible murder i just merely escaped
mine
that had walls with teeth and stomach
acid and
[Music]
uh yeah that's pretty much it nice to
meet you i hope we can get along
or not do you have any special skills
special skills i am the finest actually
i'm happy you mentioned that
i happen to be the finest blacksmith in
all of belt buckle
uh i can craft you well if you can get
me the right material i can craft
i can make anything out of anything
actually i can grab you the finest
weapon you've ever seen as long as it
doesn't shoot projectiles i've got
blades on the mind i've studied the
blade and
boy just the sound of the sound of the
sorry i'm thinking about my blacksmith
my black my blacksmith what is it called
this
little forest i'm thinking about the
forge back home and
i just really love my forge anyway yeah
i forged some really nice weapons and
that's all i gotta say thank you
wow you know we actually have a forge
here
in the basement do you really we do
that's you
go take a look at that man well
certainly as soon as we all introduce
each other i'll show you to downstairs
and you can check it out
okay yeah who is who's next for
introductions here
we've got a lovely start from scout
who's next
well don't don't jump at once at once
i don't know what that means ma'am but i
think you and i are going to get along
just fine
slowly put my hand up high um
i'm i'm you you'll be all right
you can call me just you oh you just
just
stay you'll be all right
you i'll well i mean we i mean i will be
[Laughter]
sorry i do get that a lot but the name's
you
um i'm just i'm just a normal student
here
at the local university i
almost died but um i get i guess
i'll um look forward to working with you
all i don't know what's going on but
yeah i don't have that many special cars
or anything
i mean i can drive
and drive you lack a stick shift what do
you like automatic
automatic mechanic man mannequin kick
i'm sorry man i'm not very good with my
words
i can i can i can drive almost almost
anything my
i guess my professor kind of sent me a
lot of places and
i needed to learn on the fly and eat
yeah
you will teach my total drive ah
i'm not sure if you can reach the pedals
but
i guess i guess we can try yeah i don't
think you'll be able to get that stink
out of your car from being quite honest
with you your upholstery would never
forgive you
ah i'll drive i'll just add some febreze
i'll be fine
nice to meet you nice to meet you nice
to meet you
all oh very nice to meet you yule i i
hear that you um
you know quite a thing or two about
science as well is that true
ah yeah it's my uh
one of my specialties but uh i don't
know how
how helpful that would be but yeah
as well just a few things any skill is a
good skill i would say
very useful that's great to hear well
welcome i hope that you'll choose to
stay with us
um now who's next uh how about you
a small stinky one thank you
i am watoto i came from wato town i live
in trailer with ma
and
nice to meet you bird lady oh
you make bomb oh
what kind of no he's kind of cute if you
plug your nose
wow um i mean i think you'll get used to
this smell
you'll get used to it well
um i see that you have two friends with
you as well hello doggies oh
ah dougie yes doggy one doggy too
the dogs are very ferocious looking by
the way everyone
no no no no sweet sweet dog sweet dog
i try petting one of them
and pet the dog all right um do the dogs
contest watertown
no no no doggies like it yeah
they like yeah they like petty okay cool
it looks like they
they like your pets i'm very smart adam
wow um well okay welcome wattato i hope
that um
you can enjoy or at least find something
to do
with us i'm sure that it'll be very
useful we have um
we have a crafting room if you'd be
interested in crafting your mushroom
magic mushroom bombs there
if you'd like a total found worm
would like a bite maybe oh hungry
maybe later
save that worm save it for later for a
snack
a little midnight snack all right
well uh thank you very much for that
introduction
watato um nice to meet you we also have
a shower
we have one shower it's in the basement
um
and you can certainly use it uh if you'd
like
finally um we have one more one more
person to introduce
this isn't the one i wanted this isn't
the music i wanted
go ahead uh well
i guess i have no choice uh it works
hello i am i come from
a different country and a different
continent i don't really think we will
have that much business with each other
that i will tell you more than that but
um i do use guns and i
uh well i have a lot of bird friends
um one of them sitting on my shoulder
is but don't even think about touching
him he's
very precious to me and we are
on a mission
if you give me the worm if you give up
i think he might like you a bit more and
we can try again i don't know
okay that's so cute
what do you give her the worm
no no not yet
what are you waiting for i'll save it
later
thank you for the cooperation um
nice to meet you i don't know about the
others but you seem like a
decent weird person
thank you bird
it's so cute all right um that
sounds wow sounds good so you say that
you're an expert in using firearms tiara
so you can find it yes i um have been
taught by my brother how to use all
kinds of
uh guns and rifles and yeah
um i i would say i am quite
useful when it comes to fighting
although i prefer to
not fight and just defend myself
whenever necessary
i would like to stay out of trouble anna
ah i see
that's great well i'm sure that um i'm
sure that we can help you perhaps in
some way with this mission that you're
trying to go on
or at least provide you some protection
while you try to carry it out
and a job it is a job after all you will
be paid so
and uh and we have a place for for
training if you would like to
to fire off your weapons i actually
have this i just picked up this other
job with lots of
birds and that actually was pretty nice
because you know
i like birds uh so i think i'm fine
thank you
ah well i respect your decision
but i just think that you're going to be
in some grave danger
also a gentle reminder that when you did
return there was
there was nobody there anymore um but
i'm sure she will come back anna sure if
you want to go check again later you
most certainly may
um but um yeah
um essentially um she says well we can
at least offer you a home
in the meantime if if you would
well of course the home food and shelter
is all free
um for your services and we will pay you
as well this is a very
highly funded project you see oh
well that sounds a bit more interesting
then
may i ask how much we're talking here
well it depends on the job how much
you'll be paid
um if you choose to go for a higher
paying job then
naturally you'll make more money that
kind of thing
um in fact we can talk about that
situation after i give you a tour of the
place
would you be interested in at least
seeing what we have to offer here
yes please before your eyes sure let's
have a look
all right well here's the first floor
where we are
right now looks like this
oh this is the first floor of the bar as
you can see it's a rather uh it's kind
of like a
dank you know dinky little place
let me see um change up the music a bit
um but basically the main floor is here
and then of course you've got naturally
the bathroom
the entrance and the back room where
people typically go to not do work um
that kind of thing
um and that's basically all that you've
got but there is a secret
here uh let me show you she says
as she um shows you to the stairs
there's a hidden stairwell you guys a
hidden stairwell
behind the bar top
um and she takes you there
and let me show you what that place
looks like as you guys go down to the
subfloor
wow it's like a hotel
yeah a little bit i mean there's
considerably more effort put into this
area
uh than the kids market area why are you
selling here man
oh you oh kid kid is the merchant
actually the little the little merchant
boy
yeah who actually walks down there with
you guys looks at you all and says
you all smell funny anyway i have uh i
have
dogs uh like you like your dogs actually
he looks
he looks at watertow's dog and says this
is my dog home wrecker
and he lets his dog come out in front of
you guys
he's like a boy he's a good boy just a
big golden retriever
oh yeah and he says
yes a good boy you guys can pat him if
he wants he really likes pets anyway i
sell guns and drugs so if you guys want
anything like that just come and talk to
me my market's right over here and i
will help you
all right guys do you have rifles too
sure do
i got anything anything you want banana
oh wowie andy yeah
yeah i mean definitely i got some in my
pocket it's got some lint on it
but oh and what total have
uh yeah sure this one's free just make
sure you buy a watch or something later
okay okay cool thank you
yeah no problem anyway i'm i'm gonna go
uh i'm gonna go back into my hole
see ya later
zane um and it looks like as you guys
enter the common area you can see that
the kid just kind of jumps into his
his stall area um and off to the right
now this is uh the ladies speaking who
still hasn't introduced herself to her
herself to you guys by the way um she
kind of motions off to the side and says
garage and forge is this way
it's very well equipped you'll find
yourself very satisfied with it i'm sure
it's some high grade stuff
um next to the combat training room
which is perfect for practicing firing
off your weapons etc
especially after having one of my drinks
you'll find that you're very skilled
afterwards
and of course oh sure i can make you
something a bit later
but um okay for now you guys will need
to choose your rooms as well
uh they're decently sized they've got
the essentials in there but you can
customize how you'd like
oh we wanted to build antenna
you're going to build an antenna
exciting we can do a roll for that a bit
later
sounds fun it sounds fun i'm excited to
see what kind of antenna
and then she says finally we have a
crafting room um watertow you may want
to take room a if you want to be close
to the crafting room
yes please yeah sure and a simple
computer lab as well in the common area
is full of nice couches and uh places to
relax and hang out
a big old tv um it just looks like a
cool hideout
basically you can envision it how you
like but essentially whatever you
envision a cool hideout to look like
well this probably ticks all the boxes
it is quite cool it looks
decently comfortable
yeah what's better than my dorm
yeah that's better than trailer
definitely definitely and um finally
finally um she kind of says we should
make introductions of ourselves
first um so i will now introduce to you
the members of the homestead bar
here you guys can see oh no and i have a
bigger i have a bigger
image for everyone here i just did
little black and white images i did
these last night
oh oh awesome
yeah so these are the characters oh wow
they're hands yes
what are your hands too oh my gosh i got
the watches yeah
so we've got a kid the merchant just
sketchy
kid that sells merch everyone's got
popped collars here for some reason
um the lady finally introduces herself
as
madame m the bar owner um
but a lot of the other members um just
call her mama because she's the mama of
the bar
i guess
[Laughter]
you can call her madame m you can call
her madam you can call her m you can
call her mama anything works
really and she is the one who kind of
runs the show here as the
as the lead bartender and the owner of
the place
um then of course you all you all met
bertha yes
good old bertha has been here for for
many years 35 years in fact
35 years wait it's first thought
and still a terrible shot
had to do it to him
had to do it to him um so yeah bertha
is the bouncer for this place she's been
the bouncer for 35 years
and then of course well you all know vic
vic recruited a lot of you he doesn't
really
do much we do more to help him than he
does to help us but at least he got us
you guys do we really need him i am
so sick of him i don't know he kind of
saved my life
so he was so useless in my situation
already are we do we know the same vic
i don't i think so there's only one
thing correct
i wish i would have been surprised if
there's multiple though
and there's only one of me come on there
could only ever be
one of me look at my hair look at it no
one else can do this
no one else can do this he starts
flipping his hair
what do you think ladies boy they sure
do make them differently up in the city
don't they
hello miss are you from the country
yes there are many things i can show you
here if you would be interested in city
life i am well acquainted with this uh
this area
if you'd be interested i'll i'll think
about it thank you mr pop's caller
wait really whoa you'll think about it
don't make me change my mind i'm not
never mind never mind
sorry anyway i'm gonna go back onto my
couch and uh just go chill on my phone
for a bit huh instagram whoo
bye guys
useless as ever you want to borrow some
little man
little little little man here
he sprays a little cologne kelowna
oh i thought that'll smell good now
right ladies
what is this the words yeah
um yeah you actually think guatato
smells worse now
to be so that smell reminds me of my
home country
oh you like bird lady huh it's it feels
familiar
ah i'm good calms my nerves sada
oh on a piece is there any windows
down here no but there's there's a
ventilation system though
you can you can open a little thing in
the wall to ventilate the air but it
will take some time
probably several hours
yeah so um anyway
i hope that you guys have made
yourselves acquainted with the
establishment
and now i want to explain one more thing
to you all before we get to
the job offers that i'm going to give
you if you would
like to accept them perhaps um okay
i have one last thing to talk to you
about it's um
it's the bar and my experience drinks
um essentially well right now
um i'm sure that you all have been
through many crazy things and i wouldn't
like to give you
um different drinks or anything like
that i think i'd like to give you a
welcome drink
if if you would like um
but um so basically all of you will get
the same amount of experience from this
welcome drink you get it for having
pasta i guess
your uh i guess first
experience in this world of darkness
so i hope that you will accept it
seems like a basic manner that's right
so i'll make one for you
and explain the system here so
all right all right so you guys sit at
the bar
at the bar counter and she starts making
you drinks and as she's making you those
drinks i'm going to explain to you all
uh in gm in gm mode how experience works
in this game
so basically uh i've formatted it to be
um
a special a special perk i guess of
being at the bar
is that you get to get experience points
this way so essentially
the way that you get experience points
is you get uh
beats you earn these things called beats
okay
um and a player earns beats for his
character in many ways
so when your character has gained five
beats
they convert to one experience which can
be used to develop your character's
abilities
i will put all of this in the discord so
you guys can have it on your own time
you'll be expected to update your
character sheets on your own
but let me know when you do um
now essentially let me explain beats for
beats
you gain beats when your character
fulfills one of the criteria below
okay so number one if your character
fulfills an aspiration
take a beat at the end of the game
session replace the aspiration so if
your character has a goal
right and they fulfill that goal you get
one beat
at the end of the session okay next
number two
um let's see each uh let's see what is
this
each condition has criteria for
resolution so when resolving a condition
a condition take a beat uh for example
um
in some of the tutorials some of you may
have gotten a little a little twisted
um some in some kind of mental way um
which is me applying a condition to you
um conditions can range from being good
or bad
um but when you resolve that condition
um
then you get a beat okay so for example
i think
actually um you'll be all right
when you went to the party and you were
inspired
right yeah um i would give you a beat
for that
i think it's more it's supposed to be
more for negative ones but i'd do it
anyway for positive ones as well if you
get some kind of condition
uh you will get one beat number three um
let's see what is this
um any time that you fail a roll you may
opt to make it a dramatic failure and
take a beat
okay that means that means
that if you fail a roll you can choose
to make it extra bad
a really bad situation but you will get
a beat for it
okay let's see and if your character
takes lethal damage um then you take a
beat
in one of the rightmost health boxes so
when you're taking lethal damage
towards the the end like towards the
part where it gets yeah bye
then you'll take one beat um
and let's see then at the end of any
game session take a beat that's one you
get for free anyway
all right and those are the ones those
are the ones that are
in the book essentially except for two
that i omitted um
and finally one home brew one
is good role playing if you role played
well
in the session i give you a beat
oh boy it's like a gold star yeah
yeah exactly so good role playing and
then i also have one more
homebrew one um if you accomplish the
mission
not just your personal aspiration if you
accomplished the mission
like brownie points oh nice yeah exactly
yep and those those are the beats that
you can get
um and essentially uh you can get you
can use them to get experience
so essentially um you can get
like a merit skill um or attribute
they all cost different experience
points okay
um i've kind of okay i've kind of uh
tweaked how many beats you need for each
point of experience
uh to fit the length of this game
um essentially it's three just because
we're only gonna have five to six
sessions so
usually i believe it would be five i
think it's five let me see
let me check
um yeah if you gain five beats you get
an experience point but because this is
a shorter campaign we're doing three
um so i will take a screenshot of all
this and send to you guys that explain
in more detail but that's essentially
how your characters level up in this
universe
so at the end of each mission you will
come to the bar
and tell your story to the madam and she
will make you a special drink that
levels you up
okay that's pretty cool this is actually
gonna be
telling retelling the whole like
everything that happened like no not
really
no no you just you just kind of assume
that your character does but i will be
asking you questions like did you do
this did you do this
etc um okay yeah so basically that's how
experience works
but all of you right now uh drinking
this special drink um the special drink
that is being made for you
is worth five beats
yeah which means you guys get about one
and a half experience points
uh that you can expend later but we
aren't gonna do that during the session
um we will do that off screen
just because we need to move along um
but uh yeah that's essentially how
experience works so yay
welcome to the bar welcome to the
homestead we hope that you enjoy your
stay with us
thank you thank you thank you
the drink is ultra tasty
what color is it uh it's a different
color for all of you
very cool yeah everyone gets a different
color for example
eels is purple scallops is blue tiars is
orange and white
yellow green greenish yellow green
yellow
oh it's not really my color but okay
yellow drinks the color of your eyes no
i don't think about it when you drink
the drinks you get this feeling as
though
your body is being connected to another
world where someone else is
calling the shots for you but it's only
for a moment
it's only for a second that you feel
that connection to the the other world
so this is what happens when you accept
drinks from strangers
yeah might be might be with that being
said
uh the madame takes this opportunity to
explain to you
that um she does have some jobs some
some test runs that you guys can
try out and if you don't like it no
problem you'll still be paid and you can
you can leave the hunter cell
and it's fine though you you may not
want to because the world is going to be
very dangerous for you but
but i understand i understand why you'd
want to so
i will let you choose between two recent
job
tips that we've gotten if you all would
be interested
in looking over them she says as you all
kind of
drink your drinks yes
all right now i'll go ahead and prepare
those job proposals for you
um as the madam places these scraps of
paper
on the bar top here's the first one
that you guys get
i can't read one of y'all's gonna have
to read this
for me would someone like to read it or
would you like me to read it
could you please read it for us
certainly
all right so here we've got upscale
party at crimson manor
see attached invitation this is a tip
that we received a little while ago
through one of our
contacts she looks over at vic
all right here's what it says look i
know you humans don't care all that much
about our quote unquote
petty vampire politics but the thought
of letting those malkavian buffoons ruin
everything we've worked for for the past
millennia
it irks me the romanos need to be
exposed
we'll make it worth your while really
worth your while a fresh organization
like yours could use some contacts
more details when you get to the
establishment
from a friend i hope
that's the tip that we got and the
invitation that came along with it
very mysterious utter a bit mysterious i
would say indeed
all right here's the invitation and
there are
actually interestingly enough five of
them five invitations
crimson ten minutes
well actually you can choose anyone you
want to come with you
from our crew or you can choose to just
go alone with you with your own selves
yeah you guys can choose to not take
anyone it's fine
um but yes essentially the crimson manor
charity ball
is the event it's hosted by the romano
family your attendance is humbly
requested the romano family's yearly
charity ball
a 10 course meal auction event and art
exhibit will be held
dress code please dress in formal attire
please bring your invitation to the door
to enter no guests may be permitted
what total wear suit
formal attire
a bit of a fancy one i thought i was
getting married
[Laughter]
oh congratulations watato
we just met but congrats on your
marriage can i come
everyone invited yeah yeah so
that is the first mission that we have
available for you you may choose that
one or
here is the other option this other one
is a bit
more high profile because it involves
some famous people
well i mean technically both of them do
but these people are a little less under
the radar
so we received this as um a bit of a um
a tip from someone who works at this
mansion
the tamason mansion you guys have all
heard of tamason before
it's basically the biggest company in
the world anyone who's anyone gets their
packages from tamason
but basically there are strange noises
from the basement of tamazon
the address i'm not going to show on the
internet it's a secret
now here's the tip that you've been
given i've been working at the tamason's
place for two weeks now and i'm
convinced there's some strange
otherworldly activity going on in that
place
the owners an old clockmaker and his
business tycoon wife refused to admit to
it
but something terrible happened there i
know it first
child labor could very well be anything
you think of
oh my god first the delivery man
ironic then my friend from the cleaning
agency
people keep disappearing and you gotta
figure out why
i don't wanna be next and a kind of
supplement that
for anyone who doesn't know who this
famous couple is
there is in fact a newspaper article
about them
trouble in paradise oh
madam slams it on the table my total no
i heard in the alley whispers no
wizard or lizard oh i heard
wizard i heard lizard
wizard lizards wizard lizards
wizard lizards could be a combination
um i wouldn't be surprised
the news article says trouble in
paradise
accusations continue to fly as tensions
rise between multi-billion dollar
company at temazon and their competitors
claims of sabotage have risen over the
past few months and the number of
unexplainable warehouse fires has only
increased
however the public has recently begun
raising their eyebrows at a new equally
mysterious prospect
the private lives of the tamason family
known for remaining
quiet and under the radar recent missing
persons reports have led to the media
talking ex
taking exceptional interest in the
family's affairs though they refuse to
comment on these accusations
the mansion itself is situated on a high
hill for all to see and yet the couple
seldom leaves their home
what kinds of lives do these mysterious
billionaires lead we receive no comment
and then it stops there because i don't
feel like unfolding the newspaper
[Laughter]
interesting i don't know
i think the ball sounds nice
yeah i wouldn't mind dressing up nice
full once it has been a while
black tie event i'm not a fan of parties
but
if everyone wants to go i guess
um yeah they can set you up some formal
wear
if you'd be interested perhaps you can
pick some up on the way
i would love to take a look i didn't
bring many clothes from
my home country yeah
new shoes i wouldn't suppose madam you'd
be willing to
fund our adventure quest mission
today oh well of course
yeah i mean that's why we exist as an
agency
an agency okay yeah
i mean we do strive to eventually become
much bigger than just a cell
we'd like to become something of a
compact even a much bigger larger scale
but
um it just depends on how things turn
out for now
let's just see if you all can can get
situated into the role
so when is this party
the party is actually in uh in two days
however
um it's a bit of a long drive
oh i i uh can anyone
here even drive anna i can
oh okay well
all right all right what can you do
called
[Music]
ah can i roll for shotgun
uh sure
it's either we roll for shotgun or i'm
riding in the middle i'm sitting on the
console
oh my god would you like to roll for
shotgun
toto yes yes contest all right okay
you're going to fight each other by
rolling your initiative mod this is
usually used for fighting in combat to
determine who's first
but we're going to use it in this
situation it's good to learn to use it
anyway so
in order to roll initiative mod you roll
it's a little different
one d10 plus
what your initiative mod if you look on
your sheet you'll find the initiative
mod
wait roll 1 d10 okay initiative
initiative mod
looks like this don't do the greater
than eight for this one this is the only
time you'll never use it
oh no i didn't fill mine out for
initiative month oh
it's okay look at the bottom all right
one second
[Music]
oh there's dirty plus composure i see it
dexterity plus composure is your
initiative mod
one you'll need this for combat so good
that we're figuring this out now
oh boy this isn't gonna look good for me
okay one d10
oh you gotta do a slush roll do slash
roll it's okay
all right it's okay little round of rock
paper scissors
no it's uh it's slash roll 1d10
plus uh let's see your initiative mod is
three
all right it looks like this i'll type
it into the chat one sec
i'll type it into the display that was
the wrong that was the wrong rule i put
here because i have it copied all then
oh it's okay it's five
there we go looks like this
copy paste yeah oh
i did it again it's okay
okay all right 13. nice all right now
it's scout's turn
it's like i'm riding in the middle okay
roll one dude let's go
oh no no oh it looks like walter
gets around in the middle can't stop me
i thought i'll stick head out window
yeah
[Music]
all right and i guess in the background
yeah oh gosh
all right sure thing yule uh roll let's
see how you can approach this depends on
how you want to approach it do you want
to intimidate
do you want to persuade or do you want
to physically subdue them um
[Music]
think hard about the fight you'll be
picking your slade
per slade all right so go ahead and roll
uh let's see your manipulation plus
persuasion or your presence plus
persuasion i'll allow either one
okay wait come again
uh roll your manipulation plus
persuasion
or your presence plus persuasion
all right that's that's a three okay
roll three it's a 3d 10 right
yes the 10 greater than eight
yes okay
oh no
what a shame what a shame
wanna rock paper scissors to see who
gets to drive i don't want to sit in the
back
or in the middle i'm driving i'm driving
no
no no questions
can't read can't drive sorry yeah
yeah we gotta have we gotta read the
wrote son sorry scout
wow all right fine
that's right that's very astute it's
very smart
it's true all right so with that being
said um
the madame says well i think this will
be a good chance for you guys to get to
know each other
um individually so i think just the four
of you going on this adventure will be
nice
um everyone else will be staying back
here um at least for now
if anything suspicious happens or
anything goes wrong someone will be sent
to help you
um but for now let's just see if you
four can can handle the situation
all right yeah so i'll take you to the
ground
let's go to the garage i
i guess let's let's go yeah
so you guys go to the garage and
everyone
role perception
uh roll seven eight
ten perception
was uh wits and composure
got a lot of ones sure did but
thankfully this is new world of darkness
rather chronicles of darkness okay
cool so everyone got one success except
for tiara so
let's see scout yule and watato you go
down to the garage and you see a van
tiara you go down to the garage and you
see a shitty van
it kind of sucks wow it's not great
are you sure that we can really make it
with this
[Music]
um it looks
like it's in a really bad condition is
that all you have
it looks nice
let's start up we can get there
yeah unfortunately this really is all
that we have for now we
we haven't gotten a lot of funding yet
because we haven't been able to complete
any jobs
and i spent uh all the budget on uh
setting up the underground area to be
especially
uh good for you all for example the
forge the training room the crafting
room etc
all the money went into that and we
really couldn't afford to get a nice car
but it runs rest assured it does run um
kid did some maintenance on it so it
should be fine
okay that that seems fine then
well i mean that's supposed to be all
right if you got any paint laying around
we can add a little spice touch to it
splash some color on it why total paint
mushroom on van
all right well
i guess it's something yeah certainly
i mean i don't know are we trying to go
undercover
or whatever
well it depends you're going to meet our
contact uh
decently far from the manor so you
should have time to switch out
uh your situation i suppose and perhaps
the contact can take you to the point
um so i suppose you don't have to worry
too much
if it makes you happy then i recommend
painting the car
you do have about you have several hours
before departure
so ah
okay i guess you can paint mushrooms
what do you
will be fine i total
sure go ahead
i want you to roll your dexterity and
expression oh oh
okay oh okay
i don't have anything oh well it's like
a minus one
eight yes like two two d ten greater
than eight
yes okay oh
you paint the mushrooms they don't look
great water toe but you painted
mushrooms
that's also tried you had the spirit
you're at the spirit
it surely won't draw the wrong kind of
attention now no
i mean i'm sure if he's parked at the
back alley or something it
should fit right in maybe
maybe i can go on ahead of everybody and
kind of scout out the area
oh like your name scout
oh yeah i just can take my motorcycle
i've got my motorbike in the back of my
my ford that should be out front of the
bar can't watch i'll talk
no absolutely not okay
it's not cause you don't want to ride
the van or anything right
no i'm just thinking that we don't know
what we're getting
ourselves into now do we and i think
exactly
might be smart too would you know what
what are we getting ourselves into maybe
uh are we expecting some combat some
battles
yes well that's why we have a couple
hours to prepare so essentially um we
don't know too much about
the mission and you should be briefed
further on it when you meet up with the
contact but
this is more of a um an undercover uh
mission to find information and expose
a certain vampire family who has kind of
gotten a monopoly on
a certain industry that we are not
briefed on
and allowed to talk about at this moment
in time
but um essentially it's vampire politics
um
i don't think that there will be any
combat here um
but you may need to be stealthy and you
need to prepare in case there is a
scuffle
all right okay i have some basic weapons
for you all if you would like
i think you have any should be helpful
right now yeah
you got any what kind of ores you got in
your forge man you got any
any any anti-vampire
ores um not quite yet
we just have the basics for now but do
well and perhaps we can stalk some in
the forge
do you have some garlic that can maybe
make some
garlic chemical crease or something
oh gosh i could ask bertha for some
garlic from the kitchen but
i don't really think it quite works like
that with vampires
oh i thought vampires and garlic were a
thing yeah
a common misconception uh
decently common misconception but there
are other ways i suppose um
the truth is i actually don't really
know much about
too too much about supernaturals myself
to be honest only what my mother told me
so um i'm a little a little
lost i suppose i'm really just an
investor to be completely honest i just
i just had a lot of money to put into
the project
that's kind of it i'm not an expert but
but i think i think that if you go in
there
and meet up with the contact they can
help you and um and brief you further
i suppose i can give you supplies
and a place to stay all right
yeah all right can i go for something
now
oh sure if you'd like to certainly we
have um all the basic materials so
go for it if you can make it in five
hours
five hours easy yeah
yeah we'll go ahead and set the
departure time at five hours it should
be light outside by then so go ahead and
uh
i suppose scout you can forge something
and the others if you'd like to pick a
basic weapon
i can show them to you again i'm not
talking about it
sure uh so i still have a gun from
before but like uh do i need like
a certain amount of of uh
ammo or does it just is it like eternal
ammo
how how like how does it work
you should be fine basically in this
game especially
um i don't really count the ammo
situation
just because the way that battles often
end up going
there's not a million turns anyway i
don't like there to be a million turns
because it really drags out the game
um so i don't really uh
focus too much on ammo um in this game
so you're fine
don't worry it's pretty much infinite
all right
then i would uh uh lately i would
just like to maybe um have
maybe perhaps um a knife to add to my
gun okay sure you can have a knife
thank you yeah we have a basic knife
i'm not sure what weapons i could use
i'm not very
good with physical activities
i see i see but you still may want to
defend yourself in some way i'm sure if
you're
if you're alone and separated from the
others so
um you could have a basic gun or a basic
knife if you'd like
like i i guess i guess knife would be
okay
sure let me grab one let me grab my
hunter book actually it's right here and
i can
literally read them to you
[Music]
i got it the weapons compendium but
you basically will have uh you'll have
some very basic ones because this is
just the start of the journey
we don't have a ton of funding though it
do be like that
all right let's
do see have a taser perhaps i don't look
a taster
that's a nice idea that's the worst
bottle that's a work gun
i do have a taser we do have a taser oh
nice taser all right
let's see someone might want to pick a
taser out of could be useful oh i'll
take the taser
i think i can use it sounds my total
want to build sonar antenna
ah okay the sonar gun you want to build
that
can i uh you can but uh for both of you
both you and scout you only get
one chance to make it because you only
have this limited time
oh okay yeah can i can i modify
the taser to be like lethal
um sure let's see yeah that might
be possible um all right yeah let's try
that so first let's start off with
scout's roll to forge something
okay scout go ahead and roll uh
to create a weapon do you know what you
want to make
vampires um
i don't know much about vampires
right um something sharp though
all right sure maybe some blues with
something sharp
okay sounds good sounds good
let's see you can make um
maybe
aggressive light weapon okay maybe a
dagger
yeah a girthy dagger yeah girthy dagger
okey dokey scout so go ahead and do a
roll
likes on
like a cat's tongue all right gotcha you
know what i mean you ever seen the cats
telling before it's got spikes that
you know what i mean so like when it
plunges into the into the victim
it's gonna when i pull out it's gonna
shred whatever comes out with
it it's a good idea all right scout if
you want to forge a basic dagger you'll
need two successes if you want one with
spikes on it you'll need three
um so let's go ahead and do that forging
roll forward slash
roll and let's see last time i believe
we did your crafts plus
dexterity or wits i'll let you choose
which one
um
uh crafts please
okay crafts plus two three four
wait what's the other one either wits or
dexterity
okay we'll do dexterity okay
okay and do you have a specialty in
crafts by channel weapon creation
okay so that's seven seven dice would
you like to expend willpower or do you
want to just do the seven dice roll
you don't have any money you have what
you you gained one will power back
after a night okay okay i don't think i
have very much then
all right yeah you really don't i think
you have two now
all right i'm just gonna i'll stick with
this then all right so
seven yes forward slash roll
seven d10 greater than eight
come on baby give me a girthy dagger
let's see what we got here damn it oh
well with two successes at the very
least you're able to get a regular
dagger so that's the good news
oh this is not what i want can i try
again um unfortunately time is up
sadly but you can you can later
possibly roll to modify it in the future
do i still have my pickaxe
um let's see because that's also a sharp
and pointy weapon and
it's pretty fantastic you do still have
your pickaxe there would be no reason
for you to not have it anymore so
very awesome alright so now we just have
a dagger and
10 10 10. sss pickaxe
all right so let's see with that dagger
that you have
it does let's see oh that's pretty good
one lethal damage
so that's pretty nice i just remember
that the dagger yeah
if you use it i think i think the the
pickaxe also has it
mm-hmm pickaxe says something right
picks that pickaxe has two
dude okay plus two lethal yes ma'am
all right good stuff nice now that's
scout situation next up
let's see um tiara did you want to
choose a weapon or
do anything else with yours uh
well i wonder if i can somehow upgrade
it
okay let's see i wouldn't know how
uh yeah i guess i still have crafts you
do
okay um let's see with your current gun
i believe it's uh one lethal yes
okay so you can maybe get it i don't
know actually
all right if it's a basic gun let's go
with what um so you can
get it up to two if you roll let's see
wait no this is not the one i wanted
um you can get it up to two if you go
ahead and roll a crafts roll
um let's see crafts and either dexterity
or wits
and you get let's go ahead and put it at
two successes to be generous this time
it is the beginning after all
uh slash room
okay i want some success i failed all
right
okay no problem well you still do have a
gun so that's the good news
can i um
okay kiara not tiara speaking kiara
doesn't know much about guns but
um is there a specific type of gun that
works well
for vampires oh
[Music]
oh i got nothing in there ah you can you
can try if you want
is that is that me trying to find
something how can i not ask the lady a
question maybe
uh you can ask her but she doesn't seem
to have any answers unfortunately
i see so i i i won't
i won't know does anyone have a cult and
wants to try
i do not sorry damn it i have to
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
unfortunately it can't work that way i
wish
all right three d10 okay 3d 10.
okay oh yeah
you think maybe um the way to um
to kill vampires is to use uh
nanobots that the government's been
putting um in people's cereals
that's right that's probably the way to
do it yeah
okay um well uh
in that case i uh tiara will just
go with the um blade that
i have and the gun that i have all right
but but one question do we perhaps
um lady do you happen to have a
um walkie-talkies or something like that
anna
oh sure yeah i thought you'd never ask
yeah sure here you go
for all of us please thank you yeah no
problem
over yeah doesn't hurt to ask
here you go yes
hello hello
wow you guys are quick learners
[Laughter]
learners all right now finally we've got
both wazato and yule you guys wanted to
do some things let's go ahead and start
off with yule you want to modify the
laser
taser sorry laser taser
laser tastes laser tissue
okay nice so go ahead and roll your
crafts plus
intelligence or wits actually no sorry
wits or dexterity excuse me that's what
we've been doing so far
okay yeah it's seven
wait i have a specialty in crafts called
crafting sense
does that mean oh crafters sense is um
is a merit
actually ah okay but you do have a
specialty so we can go ahead and tweak
that a little bit later but
you should still get one dot we can
rename it to something else
learning okay it'll have to be related
to this this role though
so um we'll do it a bit later uh
yeah maybe i could make it like yeah
okay some modification or something yeah
modification yeah
okay whoa all right reroll that 10
1 d10 roll it one more time
okay so with three successes your taser
now does lethal damage
that's good that's good yeah and it can
shoot from real far away
oh yeah really decently far away
i would say um maybe like
one how do i how do i say this i don't
know measuring systems
maybe five yardsticks is maximum uh
yeah um it's decently far how many vicks
is that
how many vicks okay let me see imagining
vic laying on the ground
oh let's see maybe we can shoot
oh my god it's maybe two and a half
can we test it on them i'm kidding
horrifying absolutely horrifying vic
looks at you in horror
and then goes back to instagram
yeah yeah sure sure uh
can i have a speaker do you have a
speaker
uh what kind of microphone
ox oh sdx
uh sure yeah here you go you mean like
speakers to bump music or like yes okay
yeah sure this is a stealth mission
i thought i'll make a sound gun
sorry can i roll to make my sound good
sure do the same thing crafts plus
dexterity
or wits
yes oh
wow okay you make the sound gun watertow
you make the sound gun and let's see
this sound gun
right now it only does uh one lethal
damage this is still lethal though
that's a that's a good gun
okay hey good stuff uh
sorry can i ask one more thing sure uh i
actually i have a specialty
and gunslinger firearms and that
only applies to revolvers and
therefore it was useless last time but
and can my gun be a revolver
would you like to trade in the gun you
have for a revolver yes
yes
all right
okey dokey you trading your gun for a
revolver
thank you that is a very useful ada all
right now this particular
revolver is interesting because um it
will do
two damage but you don't get to roll
tens again
so normally how when you do a roll
you'll re-roll a 10
right for your roll you can't reroll
tens with this gun
that's the only special thing about it
it's too lethal damage that's good
um but if you get a 10 you can't re-roll
it
ah that's what you mean okay okay okay
but then i also get to use my specialty
so
yes there's some special stuff added to
that okay
let's go yay let's go
all right good stuff so you guys are all
prepped and ready to go
you pile into the car and it's time to
set off on your journey
all right get in okay you're going on
control radio all right all right
you got the radio toto
all right and so um the madame waves you
off
and you guys are sent on your way
on a long journey where are we going to
get the formal wear
on the contact oh yeah on the way
probably either that or the contact will
give it to you but you guys could
you guys could go to the store to get
some form of wear if you'd like
to steal ducks
but they gave you money water so you
don't need to steal
all right so you guys are out on the
open road
[Music]
well shall we sing country roads
everyone around it's a song from my
country
i'm good okay i thought you weren't from
around here tiara
yes oh wait you know country roads as
well anna
i think everyone everyone knows no water
roads
i totally
[Music]
oh that's all i remember it sounds like
it kind of sounds like country worlds
not very original oh no
maybe it's just great grandpa wrote that
song oh
well he surely got away with words
it's poetic it's easy to remember
definitely thank you
most definitely it's the wasato anthem
all right so you guys uh begin your
drive
and interestingly enough um this crimson
manor is actually quite a ways away
it's a good five six hour drive
honestly so you guys have to spend a lot
of time together in the car
punch buggy and i reach over and i punch
total in the arm
you punch me back
self-defense sorry
[Music]
i thought i don't need to be
uh the closest
closest stop is 10 kilometers from here
should have brought my old moonshine
bottles you could use that
oh my total can hold my god
all right buckle up
all right you'll roll to drive
oh yeah okay what do i roll slash roll
drive plus dexterity
all right i have aggressive driving does
that count here
probably not right um are you trying to
harm other cars
ah no no no no probably not okay
six ten eight
what's with all my ones maybe if you go
fast enough you can catch some air on
these hills
yeah exactly all right i got a success
you got to re-roll that 110 though all
right that's right
roll
okay okay with one success you're able
to drive normally
you'll oh yeah 10 kilometers is a long
way
can i roll and see if we can pull over
and get some ice cream at the gas
station
okay sure roll perception scout if
you're trying to kill him
i'm hungry wait roll
d or d10 i've already forgotten board
yep 10 years 40 10 greater than eight is
that your width
plus composure no i think i missed a
wait
yes it is 4d 10 okay greater than eight
okay this is for gas station stop for
ice cream maybe you can also pee
water oh right
one success all right with your one
success
scout you kind of look out the window
and you scan the horizon
um you can't read any of these fancy
newfangled signs scout unfortunately
but but um you do
there's a picture of food on it though
right picture of food
well you've seen a couple signs like
that but as you'll mention next rest
stop is about 10 kilometers away right
um so as as you're kind of scanning the
horizon
um you actually don't notice um
anything in particular scout any place
to stop and get ice cream
except except suddenly you get real
lucky
and on the side of the road there is
what looks to be
some kind of ice cream stall question
mark oh
please are in jesus has has heard my
prayers for ice cream
no bathroom though it doesn't look like
there's a bathroom it's way too small
anything's a bathroom if you believe in
it all right let's
pull this baby over
you could go in the forest
yes forest it is
actually can i be right back i actually
do want to go get some ice cream over
here everything
okay guys small break small break break
time
break time guys okay intermission we'll
be back
shortly yay
[Music]
we're continuing the story we were about
to stop at an ice cream stall
don't you think an ice cream sauce in
the middle of nowhere is
suspicious you know now that you mention
it
the middle of the highway that is pretty
darn suspicious but not at uh suspicious
enough to get in the middle of me and my
cookie dough ice cream
yeah can i roll perception sure
excuse me scout um what is
cookie dough ice cream adam
it's it's hold on roll
perception
well cookie dough ice cream is like
cream and sugar and pieces of cookie
dough and chocolate and it's real nice
you've never had it before
no they have ice cream we have ice cream
but
only um two tastes of ice cream
they are earth taste and water taste ice
cream
ice and dirt yes pretty much sounds
pretty miserable
you get used to it i know but i would
love to try
the ice cream of your country
well perhaps you don't have to share
some cookie dough ice cream with me
right now
i i i i
i am i i i take that as a yes
ah well i i have no choice
i guess anna um yeah you're
forcing me to try so i
like an arm wrestle for it if that make
you more comfortable it'd be a fair
fight that way
we're gonna have a three-way arm wrestle
for this how does that work
i i i would like to um um wrestle
for a little taste indeed
okay should we let ina
perception check first sure oh i did
just yeah success
yeah one success so basically all you're
able to um
kind of perceive for right here uh yule
is that
um it's it looks
a little all right it looks a little
sketchy a little bit
but it's only because it's rather old um
the woman that's selling ice cream there
looks rather friendly
um and there are some kids walking up to
the the ice cream stall and they're
getting ice cream and then leaving and
going into the forest
to play it that sounds
alarming
does seem a little strange do you sell
mushroom ice cream
oh you want to ask what to tell you're
going to have to get out of the car
oh can i drive drive through
you faster oh you guys can try to drive
through
i mean this through drive through all
right pull up to the
ice cream stall sure
okay you pull up to the ice cream stall
all right and uh do you roll down the
window
sure yes okay on on
hello is anyone there howdy travelers
you guys from around here no i don't
no no oh
but you sell ice cream here
oh well yeah we have all kinds of ice
cream
i'm just wondering what about you know
well yeah of course from bell buckle you
ever heard of it
but bill buckle can't say that i have
all right actually how it is
oh well i'm sure i'm sure it's a fine
place let's see what flavors i got
here do you also have somewhere elsian
dirt flavor
as well somewhere else in dirt um
i'm sorry i only have somewhere elsie an
ice flavor
i would love to also take uh somewhere
elsian ice flavor please thank you wow
i'm surprised you have it here anna yeah
i mean it's
it's a pretty rare favorite i would say
of some of the folks around these parts
we got cookie dough as well we got let's
see
um we got banana we got chocolate chip
we got
caramel we got
sticky green mush um let me see
um we have we have special promotional
shrek flavor
for the new movie oh that's pretty close
yeah somebody once told me that these
are pretty good
oh yeah i have a shrek then
[Music]
all right well in here here you go
okay um anyone else well
you want what did you want some cookie
dough
ma'am is that one please ma'am okay how
about you driving ma'am
ah no i'm i'll pass this time thank you
oh okay uh let's tell you a treat
ladies
okay uh let's see let's go with uh five
dollars total
ultra cheap okay dollars what kind of
cheap roadside scam robbery ice cream
media are you running lady
oh no it's okay i paid
oh okay well if you just so thank you
for the five dollars
um you got a permit to be running this
thing the sales inspector know you're
doing this
well technically i mean it's just a
family owned
business it's a health inspector is
a masked master ghost
by the government no
huh emily own business is best
oh okay i'll give you tip
six dollars in total wow
six dollars no no no no no no sorry
one dollar oh okay one dollar is fine
too
it kind of got my hopes up there a
little bit but oh okay
i'll take it thank you all right what
what toto has to buy a tux so
oh yeah six dollar tux i heard those
look pretty good
all right well thank you here we come
all right i'm gonna go ahead and prepare
your ice cream then
all right um you'll roll perception
me okay uh
bro
hey tiara are you still fixing the arm
wrestle
yes i i wouldn't mind trying and
all right let's see i can go ahead and
do a quick
arm wrestle first fire arms
can i can i um no shooting in the car
nope arm wrestling is a straight
strength check
i would not be fine
you just roll your strength only your
strength
we'll do a quick arm wrestle then we'll
get to euler's perception
but how do you do it it's just
strength
[Laughter]
we drop it on the floor right or
something happens i mean none of us get
it
alright we don't get it well thankfully
there are no ones or anything like that
here
um and uh it seems like it's okay
um if one of you wants to take a beat to
make it a dramatic failure i'll let you
that's a good place can you dramatically
fail as
in she breaks my arm then i might be
useless for the rest of the game but
okay let's get to it
[Music]
all right my arm yet fair fight
okay so neither of you win it looks like
uh
a very pathetic struggle between two
people who are not exceptionally strong
in this moment
this makes it even better because i have
a playlist the playlist of like raging
banjo's place
[Laughter]
well in your eyes it's a really epic
fight but in our eyes it's just like
something really strong
looks like a tie guess we're all eating
ice cream anyway
i will just stick to my um somewhere
else in ice
taste ice cream but but but maybe
another time you can
share the cookie dough ice cream with me
thing thank you
can i try it
need water ice cream maybe i mean what
totally paid for
oh yeah you need to pay for it you're
asking for an arm wrestle
oh uh okay
yeah all right um before you guys do
your arm wrestle
however you'll you make an astonishing
discovery
oh i did you did you got uh two
successes to make a
decently astonishing discovery and that
is that the car has stopped running
you want to go fix the car watertown can
i give it a try first
sure you know i don't know a little
thing about cars
all right i step out of the car and i
pop the hood check it out all right fix
it
sure thing first let's roll perception
one more time you'll have to kind of
perceive what's going on with the car
just in the first place at a glance with
two successes oh
nice okay great um you'll this is
uh not great uh what has happened here
because you're realizing that uh the car
itself
is uh it's it's really it's bad it's
it's not um
it's it's old it is super old um and it
looks like
uh the engine is completely
uh throttled like it is
burnt out entirely this thing looks like
if you continued driving it you'd be
driving a bomb
oh
were they trying to kill us with this
ala unbelievable
okay well what are we doing now anna
what do we do
what would you like to do do you have
any ideas to fix this
uh what does
one single mushroom but i don't know if
mushroom can do anything
can i at least try to maybe maybe scout
anything i can go out into the woods and
see if i can collect some stuff to make
some kind of
some fix and do it here so
perhaps we can also ask the ice shop
lady
for some help nice job lady you have
engine
you got yourself an engine practice oh
and
wait what happened is your car broken
down
uh yes it seems like we're having a bit
of a
trouble oh goodness me oh my goodness
gracious
oh no this is bad because well the
closest um
the closest area uh where you could
possibly
get your car repaired is 10 kilometers
away but
but there is um there's a hotel that's
only about half a mile from here
um perhaps you could push the car
up there and maybe call someone we don't
have a phone here sadly
my house is in the woods
what but but we have phones don't we
otto
we have walkie-talkies can our
walkie-talkies reach back to madame
um unfortunately they cannot sadly all
right
it's only between you guys she didn't
keep a walkie-talkie
uh we don't have phones none of you
mentioned ringing phones when we were
getting ready to
go equipment no no no no no no no not
this one
you gotta remember gotta remember to say
i bring my phone and my flashlight etc
is the is the ice cream cart is it odd
is it does it have a
uh is it push cart or does it got like a
motor on
the ice cream cart
um it does not have a motor on it you
just push it i think
i would say so i wish i could be more
helpful
okay
and connect uh to radio
and make a announcement
okay okay who are you trying to make the
announcement to wathato
everyone call for help no call for help
okay ben broke all right sounds good
so let's use it maybe you can use it to
like blast us forward like a slingshot
right because it's a zombie boom
it's true what what do you think this is
frequency so it will pierce through
whatever it's trying to push that's
fantastic this is
this is a killing gun
wait what does it do you still stuff i
scrambled the brain very good
are you sure you want to make an
announcement with something like that
okay maybe not i mean i think it's a
great idea just the execution
maybe maybe i don't know i wish i could
be a little like
i really wish i could be more helpful
i guess we have no choice but to push
the car out of
all right i guess and guess we push
all right i'll i'll steer
oh you're gonna get down push
push door
all right you guys are gonna push the
van together
yes yeah all right i want everyone to
make a strength and athletics roll for
me
hmm
oh
you guys can reroll those tens by the
way
so er i roll another three it's a one
d10
another a one d10 because you're like
right okay yeah
oh the suspense
oh okay roll it again nice oh
four four four wow wow
so that's four successes plus the next
thing
do another one roll it again
okay so let's see what we got here
all right so watto with one success you
know you're pretty short you're pretty
stout
um you're doing your best though you're
giving it your all and you are
contributing so that's the good news
watoto
um as for the real
the real power
[Laughter]
participation trophy honorable mention
um scout you've done things like this
before
you've had some car breakdowns on the
farm you've
you've had a little bit of experience
with this so uh
you know how this works and you push the
car with ease
um however however
tiara is uh the real heavy lifter here
the real heavy lifter she just carried a
car
she just picks up the car carries it she
gets behind the car and just pushes
and pushes and pushes and is an
unstoppable force
with this truck and it's very obvious
you guys can all see tiara is real
strong
oh wow this is easy anara my tattoo
small leg can't keep
up yeah it gets to a point watson so
where
with tiara pushing the car at one point
you're holding on to one of the doors
and it just kind of picks you up and you
kind of like float as she continues
pushing the car
honestly if you if you want guys you can
just get into the car and i'll do the
workout huh
okay get in car okay
happily accepted
thanks tiara
and push and push and push
and push and push
push and push
[Music]
you guys have been going for about half
a mile you do find the hotel that the
ice cream lady was talking about
um and it's actually more of um
well it's less of a hotel
more of a motel truck stop oh okay
that way
they might have they might just have
pool it's scotty's motel
all right yep
you guys roll up at scotty's motel
all right
try to check to see where where
the check-in is and parking and stuff
uh sure if you'd like to no problem at
this point it's gotten to be night
oh okay yeah so it's decently late you
guys kind of were rolling the car
down the street as the sun was setting
um
watertow and yule chilling in the car
scout and tiara push in the car
tiara doing most of the work however oh
it's too dark yule you have no idea
where to check in it's just a whole
bunch of rooms
where is this all right go ahead and
roll perception water
perception wits plus composure
all right and re-roll that one 1d10
okay well you got one success with one
success watson so you're able to sniff
out
a little a little doorway a little slidy
glass door
that works as a window to you suppose
the quote-unquote
lobby of this place you couldn't really
call it a lobby it really looks more
like a drive-through window
more than anything
so you find that there's a very tired
very tired looking uh older woman
maybe in her 40s looks really really
exhausted and not happy to be there
you want me to do the talking what the
door uh
two rooms please
sorry what can you say that again uh
two two rooms yeah
all right hold on you guys have any
money
you don't look like people who have any
that's rude um
yeah which
50 should be enough all right oh thank
goodness
two rooms all right wait wait wait wait
wait we have to split
i don't know hot ice cream
we're lady
you do have a little money from your
bird job
how much do i have about 50. 50.
okay how much is one room for one night
anna could you tell me the exact rate
and not [\h__\h] around now
25. do i look like i'm [\h__\h] around
does it include breakfast anna we don't
have a kitchen here
oh um okay i guess we can order some
uh ubereats or something out of that's
fine
there's a convenience store nine and a
half kilometers away
not i see okay i also have another
question do you perhaps know how to fix
a car
or do you have anyone around here who
knows how to do that
you can use the phone call the repair
company they're nine and a half
kilometers away
come in the morning everything's nine
and a half kilometers
i think that will do it and we'll take
the rooms and we'll use your phone
if that's okay at all all right use the
phone i'm getting ready to close up in
30 minutes to make it quick
all right okay um does anyone
want to uh do the talking on the phone i
i am not good with strangers i don't
know
uh and i'm kind of mad at all this
happening this the car that they gave us
was crap and they expect us to go on
this mission
it's unbelievable so i'm done for today
anna
all right or maybe better if uh you all
did that
since you all seem to have
the knowledge
all right what total can assist in case
i get stuck
okay all right all right
okay i go i guess i go and use use the
phone
is there like a phone book or the
numbers
yeah so basically the the front desk
lady lets you borrow the phone so you
can make one call
it's free don't worry about it no no no
cost or anything you just need to dial a
number and she gives you a phone book
all right and uh looking through the
phone book you can determine pretty
easily that
the place that she's talking about you
know not a whole bunch of repair
companies round these parts
right so you do find the number and you
give them a call
ring ring ring ring ring howdy thank you
for calling
randall's repair service how can we be
of assistance we're about to close up so
can you make it quick
all right so uh we have our van that
that that broke down um would it be
possible to
send someone here to fix it in the
morning
we're at uh scotty's motel
oh huh yes sir bob we sure can do that
if you wouldn't mind wait until about
tomorrow around lunch time unless uh
unless lunch break runs a little long
yeah i'm feeling tacos maybe tomorrow
we can bring you something oh
actually um hey you guys want tacos
tomorrow
yes what's a taco taco
taco please
looking forward to it all right i'll eat
all of them okay
if you could get some for us i'll i'll
pay extra
oh wow that's mitochondria thank you
all right see you tomorrow have a good
evening
hang up
um they said they'll come by around
lunchtime tomorrow
along with some food
wow thank you you did great
so uh who's going to share a room with
watoto huh
i i wouldn't really drink a rocker
her it's very comforting i think i can
dream better
if i'm in the same room mother all right
all right so you guys enter you guys
enter the motel
okay and we've got the separation as
such
uh yule and scout are together and so
are wato
and tiara
the walls are kind of in my speech
impediment okay
oh okay oh okay
all right so how does your evening play
out scout and yule what do you guys kind
of do
to waste some time here
all right um
is there a tv that's either a tv or a
really oh there's a tv
it is a thief somehow it is a tv a tv
that looks like a microwave
hey they got channels back on the farm
we never had any channels all i watched
was the vhs's
oh all right look for the remote
there's an exception oh a perception
do you want a roller should i i think i
have higher
oh i haven't i'll roll okay wait
all right oh wow okay reroll that 10.
i'm really searching for that remote now
either that or we lift the bathroom
mirror and there's a secret hole behind
the mirror that leads to another
dimension
all right so interestingly enough um
you'll
you look all around um the entire room
you can't find the dang remote however
your intuition tells you to check the
couch
a teeny tiny little uh remote poking up
in between the cushions
of the couch
all right i dig in and pull out the
remote
you also find many other things like a
couple of bags of doritos
um and a couple of boxes as well
completely unopened
is that a needle shirt
maybe not might be best not to
ah let's just uh sit back and
sit back and relax and eat some doritos
and pepsi
you feel me it feels like a breeze
is there a draft in here
with your perception check with your
perception check being so good
you will i will say um it's not that the
window is closed
it's that straight up the windows are
damn broken straight up they're broken
dude like somebody threw a baseball in
there and there's like a hole the size
of someone's fist
just indoor
it's coming from behind the mirror in
the bed
all right i guess i'll try uh
try to put the curtains over the over
the whole
scout you can no just chill or just look
around
can i roll the check behind the mirror
please sure
roll perception please come on
jesus okay uh what is it again
it's wits plus composure which which was
jokes
all right 40 10. well thank you
for the 10 greater than eight come on
let's go all right re-roll that ten
1d 10. they wondered
[Music]
aha all right with two successes scout
you march up to the mirror because you
know some funny business is going
on you reach to see if you can open
that mirror and oh my god you can
you open that mirror and you discover
another world
like what the world of cockroach society
as 50 cockroaches escape from behind the
mirror
as you have discovered their nest
oh my god they can fly
oh my days
[Music]
they can fly anybody hungry
my my owl we got roaches
can i maybe uh get out of the room and
go to the other room
sure you guys can all go to the same
room if you want
all right getting out of this room it's
over it's over it's gone it's not
nope nope nope nope
all right you head on over to the other
room
uh tiara and wasato how have you guys
been spending your evening
take apart tv
okay all right want to tell to take
apart the tv
roll your crafts and dexterity
okay
all right we roll that ten nice parts
okay with two successes you discover
the decent amount of parts um inside the
tv that could be useful
maybe only about half you'd need to do
something like build an engine or
something like that but
but you do get some good parts uh water
for future creations i'll give you a
little bonus
uh if you're creating something however
you have dismantled this place's tv so
let's hope they don't catch you
put brain back together and make it look
normal
roll crafts again
i hope you have some duct tape
well you did it i mean yeah you
succeeded it looks kind of shitty a
little sketchy
but no one's gonna notice until they try
and turn it on and then it falls apart
um should be enough to cover your tracks
for a while
okay yeah we've got some good parts
in the in the meantime um
like super super hungry and therefore uh
trying to eat uh my
jacket so i
i want to ask wato something
do you do you perhaps still have that
worm oh yes worm
is on my hand right here if if you
wouldn't
mind would you like to share your worm
with
my bird adam oh okay
i want worm
sure absolutely if if you guys both
consent to that then sure
wait well what kind of worm are we
talking are we talking about the same
worm here
we know i mean if you consent to
allowing no if
listen to me if you consent to allowing
wha if
you consent to allowing uh uh to eat the
worm that's what i meant
get given the okay the the two double
thumbs up
okay the worm the worm on my hand yeah
yeah that worm that worm definitely that
[\h__\h] worm
uh uh excitingly flies over
to uh la toto's hand
lands on it and aggressively packs
at your hand accidentally
ending up in wounding your hand as well
i am so sorry i'm so sorry i
i i i am so sorry does it hurt ara
should i blow on it to make it better
okay
[Laughter]
um i'm gonna go teach them to do some
tricks or something
i think the the delicious snacks right
thank you thank you thank you thank you
uh my bird is so so grateful to you and
i thank you for your girlfriend
scout as you and you'll exit the room
i want both of you to roll perception
okay
oh no you you
it looks like we all have to uh share
the room
can i do it just watch us yeah yeah yeah
yeah
roll roll first go for it
come on
okay scout with your one success you
hear something strange
huh you hear something from outside it
sounds it could be the cockroaches they
might be the hissing variety i'm not
really sure
it could be there's a history yes there
sure
is there are many varieties but it does
sound actually like um
like a car engine revving up and driving
away
wait what run out and
let's go take a look find the closest
window or a door and see
see where all right it's coming you go
and look outside and you realize that
your van isn't there anymore
what uh-huh instead there are some very
bold tire tracks
leading out of the parking lot and
onto the road my mushroom then
i thought i thought the engine was broke
could it be
well anybody want to build a tandem
bicycle
[Music]
has tv parts wait well total there's
another tv in our room maybe we can take
that
one oh i think with the parts i can just
upgrade the gun i don't know
about bike
[Laughter]
everything is going wrong
have an idea uh can we steal
someone else's car yeah
it's not a bad idea can we check to see
if there's
another car in the parking lot all right
sure roll perception
all right uh
oh please
uh-huh one success no other cars in the
parking lot
this motel is empty except for you guys
[Music]
look on the bright side guys tomorrow we
still get tacos
i have idea
okay i i will um i could
uh perhaps send my verb
uh off to look for a car in the distance
and then
show us where it is tomorrow ah
[Music]
that's a good idea go ahead and roll
your animal ken
and i have a special
specialization an animal can do i get
like one more dice how was that what's
your specialization
verb communication okay yes you do get
one plus one
uh one dice okay so animal can plus one
and what was the other one sorry
uh animal ken and let's see wits in this
situation
it's okay so that's six
wrong you're thinking on your feet
okay okay and re-roll that tent
um
okay three successes that is that is an
exceptional success
very good okay so you tell uh to go and
search for the car
and uh off who flies into the night and
you guys have a little time to wait
i was chilling in the parking lot
watoto look for a change under the rug
all right go ahead and roll your
perception latito
no change to be found not your lucky day
unfortunately
thankfully though thankfully you guys
don't have to wait too long
ooh who is back
with your very good success role tells
you
that um the location of tells you the
location of the van
it's not far from here actually ah
it's stopped in a junkyard a
junkyard well it seems like they
in order to drive it away they must have
repaired it somehow so
we if we go pick it up then
[Music]
i think should we do that now at our in
the morning at all
i feel like they do it now they're going
to sleep for parts if we're not careful
well then is it too dark for us to go
need to find flashlights or anything
would you like to search for flashlights
and we also search for a shopping cart
on the side of the road
yeah okay sure um let's see
wato i'll have you search for a shopping
cart on the side of the road but you're
going to need
at least two successes because that's uh
that's something quite clear
to find out here in the wilderness the
other is just real perception
and um we'll see if you can find
flashlights
one success oh one success watson all
right
um unfortunately there's no shopping
cart
um on the street
sadly okay okay
i got two successes all right with two
successes
okay you'll um you actually do manage to
find with two successes you find two
flashlights
all right uh you got to be careful
because you found them
in uh in that um little entry
room you weren't supposed to go in there
but no one's in there and it's not
locked
so
interestingly enough watson you actually
do see a shopping cart but it's not
unmanned
there's a person pushing it oh
and it's full of things
you wanna jump in uh maybe we speak to
him first
[Laughter]
looks like a homeless man oh walking
down the street i speak to him
yeah okay so what do you say
hello hello oh hello there
little man
what do you want what you got there you
got the parts or something
but odds and ends just just some
just some stuff mostly mostly trash my
things my things
can i have that card ah
why would i give you my card
whatever needs it
[Laughter]
what you offer uh
i got a powder
like a strong powder can i drop my
shoulder and do a
football takedown
um you may certainly try
if toto doesn't mind go ahead and roll
your strength and athletics scout
hopefully i don't miss i'm looking away
come on banjos
all right re-roll that den
okay whoa roll your athletics and
dexterity oh
oh i meant the guy pushed in the car and
not working
never mind never mind yes
i thought you were trying
okay
all right that's one success uh you
managed to tackle him to the ground
you guys are having a scuffle on the
ground right now
what the hell are you all doing allah
we should go look i could
help but honestly why are you attacking
a homeless guy that is just
oh wow we have the shopping cart then we
can get in and
you can push us and we go fast my toto's
got a plan all right
but we could also just follow my bird
and go to the junkyard and get our
goddamn car back
but with the cart we go faster
we can start walking while you guys deal
with that because yeah
yeah you and me let let's just go uh
yeah
you guys you guys do yeah anybody got
some rope without a witness here we're
gonna have to take a look
see you later roll perception scout
reception give us some rope
you're coming with me mister
[Music]
with two successes scout you do find
that this homeless man had some rope in
the shopping cart
oh no
what are you doing tie him up i'm gonna
tie him up i'm gonna do the
little cowboy tyler the old cowboy style
you're gonna do the special cowboy tie
okay
i want you to roll your crafts and
dexterity
oh you're in for buddy you got me some
high crash rolling
sorry sorry we'll bring the cart back
yeah we just need to borrow it
all right oh oh we rolled in we rolled
that 10.
oh my goodness
[Music]
wow okay
all right you really tie him up good and
he tries to
muffle speaking something he's really
wriggling around but gosh your cowboy
tie has really
really got him in a in a bit of a
situation right now in a bit of a pickle
um he eventually stops trying to
struggle and just starts
chilling after a while but but yeah you
really tied that dude up
scout i can roll him down the hill i'm
sure someone will find him eventually
and we can be on our way no no no
it's okay we're taking
they choose violence every day when they
wake up
i thought i was sorry one total he gives
the man visa candy
he doesn't throw
thank you though what did it look like
this
[Music]
search cart for parts
all right you want to search the cart
yeah sure role perception
as you guys have successfully gotten the
card um you don't find anything useful
there just trash
it's all trash to you oh
a total empty cart for now and neat
piles and uh
we can take cart okay as we walk all
right
okay great so now you guys have a
shopping cart
whoa does driving include shopping carts
um yes at a minus one penalty
uh should i drop the shopping cart
sure roll drive minus one all right
let's see
all right so let's uh
just is it also success or not
um or just try it oh just uh drive plus
dexterity
minus one oh drive plus sixty
five eighty ten
this okay well success
all right so you managed to drive the
shopping cart handily who's in the
shopping cart
watoto's bottom shotgun
all right who's who's right in uh
scout can go in the uh child seat in the
front in the uh
you know i feel like you play better in
the child's seat
okay scout take the main basket
kiara i guess you can just run along
okay oh i got the visual
it's a visual running into the night the
darkness in a shopping cart
all right buckle up there's no buckles
but
yeah i have some straps here
following instructions uh you're able to
figure out
uh the exact path that leads to the
junkyard it's actually really not that
far from here
and you guys see it looming ahead in the
darkness the moon
faintly shining over it on all the uh
the crumpled and
and uh twisted uh parts of different
cars
and uh and metals and trash
is there silver do they have silver
um probably some probably something is
made of silver
you're sure that there are many
different materials here but most of it
is junk
most of it is really truly junk
so here can you look around to see if
there's anyone suspicious around
sure everyone rolls conception
everyone full perception here
at this junkyard oh my goodness
oh wow
okay reroll that then
oh oh
all right how about you scout rolling
all right by the way i just want to say
in in case you plan to have someone
ambush us i have dangerous sense so so i
would be able to detect that perhaps
just yeah yep i know about your danger
sense no worries okay
all right okay
scout you perceive nothing you're too
invested in this uh this journey you're
taking in the shopping cart
it's fun it's the most fun you've had in
a while
almost as fun as donuts and paws ford
that's right almost as fun as notice and
fast forward
um and let's see as for both yule and
tiara
you guys see that this is um it's a
nasty looking junkyard that's kind of
all
there is to it um just like any other
basic one that you would envision
um you're
when you look at this junkyard you don't
only see a junkyard you see something
like
like a maze um a place of endless
potential this this place is i mean
especially to you because you're
interested in crafting things but
but to you this place it looks like um
like another world no this is not no it
went to the digging with other
music it's okay it's fine anyway um yeah
it looks basically like another world
to you um entirely and it's full of
potential
um entire entirely
treasured
[Music]
you also are kind of getting a sense
this place is shady as hell
and you also get a sense that there's
like
this place isn't run by anyone at least
not now it almost seems abandoned in a
sense
okay wow looks nice
yeah paradise for crafters
if you can find the right materials but
a lot of it is junk watson so you're
able to recognize that it's mostly junk
am i am i able to roll like a survival
skill
because i have foraging in in that
i don't know if it would be useful or if
you have an idea of what you'd like to
do
with it then we can make it work
can i look for for silver maybe
okay sure if you want to specifically
look for silver
in order to distinguish it from the
other metals i would need you to roll a
crafts and
either intelligence or wit's role
i'll do uh uh crafts and wits okay
because you're thinking on the fly right
now so
okay we roll that ten silver baby
okay two successes that's pretty good
um let's see you find a couple things
that are made
of silver but only in chunks no big
blocks of silver or anything like that
that you could easily just pick up
you'd need to gather it in chunks and it
would take a long time but it does exist
here in little bits and pieces
all right i mean i know i know tiara was
looking for some
and and i'm sure she's got a plan for it
so maybe she can use it
i'm not sure because like okay speaking
in it as kiara to
gm we uh we don't know yet right that
that silva would be useful against
vampires we don't have that knowledge so
i don't know
why we would be looking for it that's
why i kind of left it
at that right well i mean you guys asked
about garlic before as well so i mean
you guys can go off of stereotypes that
you know about
about supernaturals if you'd like to but
i can't give you any concrete answers
without knowledge of occult
oh okay okay
[Music]
all right
i mean if you gather little by little
i'll probably uh increase the amount of
silver that you get by the amount of
time that you're here in this junkyard
and how deep you go into it deep enough
to find this stupid van so we can get
back on
oh yeah we should find the van and let's
talk
maybe a tux
yeah all right so at this point um
ooh kind of like um seems to settle back
down on your shoulder wait i have an
idea who's got the car keys
i i do does it have an alarm button
oh it does that's it it does
okay smart smart press the alarm button
okay you guys are gonna have to listen
for me but
okay here's what you hear
we
okay you walk towards the car but you do
realize it is it is very far away
decently far yeah it's gonna be about a
five minute walk
to the car get in the car
i go it's a big vast junkyard like
what's the perceived another world
this place is well we better get walking
yup you guys start walking walking
through the junkyard
this place you don't have any junkyard
dogs do you
oh
oh yeah better better that way yeah yeah
yeah okay
yeah no casualties today yeah okay
all right so eventually you guys do
reach the van
you managed to make your way to it there
it is anna
all right what do you do
i walk around and check if it's been
tampered with if it's fine
the mushroom is running
you wiped off the mushroom no the
mushroom's still there thankfully
oh this is on the other side
all right you will do check to see if
the car is working
yes okay you check to see
and it looks like ah the car is working
just fine
it actually is running better than
before strangely enough
all right now
tiara you sense something is off here
oh no you sense you're being watched
everyone i had a feeling i sensed
something
i think someone is perhaps watching us
anna
be careful can i
do a perception check sure
whoever would like to do perception go
ahead and roll
oh yeah i'll do one too yeah
oh [\h__\h] oh guys
whenever it says danger i just roam
we roll those two tens yeah 2d 10.
are we all rolling and roll again yeah
whoever wants to perceive
all right okay let's see what we got
here
i got two okay re-roll that ten
scout
i'm smelling some butt kicking you guys
uh got some really good ones here
all right let's start with uh wasato who
got um one success
and yeah wazato's one success so watso
uh you have no idea what they're talking
about but it is oddly quiet here
um and it is a little suspicious seeming
next up we've got
um let's see tiara
uh as you perceived earlier there is
something
dangerous afoot here something strange
something peculiar
but the feeling was specifically being
watched
right um now it's not only that but
you're hearing something off in the
distance
you in particular are able to hear
something kind of moving
something big moving like a lot moving
next up it said one of those big things
that
yeah i don't know the word for it in
english big government robot
the bag it's a squatch
i don't know what that is
a burger a burglar
a bagel it's
it's it's in the picture uh that we see
oh the crane crazy not the crane
ah you definitely hear something that
sounds similar to that a lot of metal
scraping
um scout you especially hear a lot of
metal movement um that does not sound
natural
but yeah but you're you're still able to
kind of
kind of hear that and what you perceive
you're pretty loud then it's pretty it's
pretty loud not enough for water here
apparently
not enough for watching thinks it's day
quiet um
but yeah scout you actually can see
things moving in the distance
it almost looks like piles of trash and
garbage are moving
off in the distance uh-huh
um and now we go on to
you'll you'll be all right
uh you'll you perceive all of this but
then in addition to that
um you can see atop one of the faraway
mountains
there's a hooded figure standing on top
of the garbage and it looks as though
something is pointing at you guys
something that looks like
a gun a gun a squatch
a scratch with a gun oh my gosh
guys i think we have to duck get into
the car
immediately let's go okay let's drive
drive get the car right you all get in
the car and as soon as you do
you begin to hear fire hitting
the van
guns all right
now you'll you can roll to drive drive
all right well your drive plus dexterity
next 36. oh please
get out of here let's
okay we roll that 10. get out of here
can i can we tattoo a roll to use sound
gun
against the enemy okay sure the enemy is
real far away but i suppose with the
high pitched frequencies you could give
it a try
okay all right go ahead and roll let's
see
we'll have you do weapon not weaponry
sorry firearms
um and let's go ahead and do a dexterity
for this one
oh you're mess
you fire off the gun and as yule is
pulling
a sick maneuver by the way um
yule is really gunning it you guys are
going super fast
winding through the maze of the junkyard
and safely avoiding the bullets however
with you doing that watso
you fire off the sound gun um and it
summons two dogs
oh nice doggie it summons two dogs and
they chase you
oh it seems like they liked it
they liked the sound that you made and
then you realized what's it so that you
had accidentally had it switched to nice
sound for doggies
oh okay sorry sorry what
sorry next time i'll get them next time
so you guys are wasting off uh through
the junkyard
all right um however you'll you notice
something immediately
as you're winding through the junkyard
you're realizing that this isn't the
same path that you took to get in here
oh in fact it's almost as though the
junkyard has been changing around you
guys
the maze has been warping with you
inside of it oh no i'm getting
flashbacks
oh no you're familiar with the scout
um maybe let's just
keep that keep the pedal to the floor
let's do to get out of it
well it involved a pickaxe and a whole
lot of luck
so i'm not sure it's gonna help us this
time around
all right um can i try driving
up the trunk oh you wanna drive up the
jungle okay
go ahead your drive roll at a minus two
okay
uh come on
jesus nice okay
all right let's see what we got here
with two successes
you'll you push your foot down
on the gas and you grind against the
metal with all your might
and you are able to very slowly climb up
the mountain of junk
slowly but surely now you can feel that
the gun the gunfire is getting closer to
you because you have significantly
slowed down
you get to the top of a pile of junk um
and you realize that uh the junk has
spread out for miles and miles
around you it seems as though it goes on
forever in each direction
what should we do
hey maybe you can use your your sound
gun wait
never mind
all right i can't forget i was thinking
i keep thinking it's a big boom gun
you could use it to blast away the junk
but it's put it i'll put it on the mean
setting
up doggies follow you up the junk
oh no all right you i want you to roll a
perception check really quick for me
one success okay with one success you
are able to discern what looks to be
some kind of exit it's far off in the
distance but it's kind of off to the
west
and you can kind of see a path that
looks like it might lead to that exit
okay start driving down that pathway
okay
go ahead and roll another drive roll for
me okay let's see
uh
yeah oh whoops
you begin to go down the hill but
unfortunately for you
going down the hill is not quite as easy
as it was
going up the hill and uh your car does a
bit of a tumble a little sideways roll
um and everyone you all take one bashing
damage
everyone as the van
tumbles down through the garbage and you
continue you still continue driving
onward after that but you can hear over
the loudspeakers
someone calls out to all of you and says
the hunt is on my cute little humans
keep her up this is going to be a fun
game
uh a game
can we fight well
the thought crosses your mind you could
get out and fight if you want but this
seems to be a sniper
so however you'd like to handle that is
up to you but
before that yule you realize that as
you're barreling through the junkyard
as you are putting your putting
the pedal to the metal um suddenly
you realize that things do not look the
same anymore
it doesn't look like no in a junkyard
anymore
rather where are we at it looks as
though you've entered
something of a different maze as
suddenly
greenery begins to sprout up in between
the metal
around you
you begin to see leaves and thorns
suddenly poke their way
through the scraps through all the scrap
iron around you
and you realize you're a very different
place now
ah we still we still gotta go west
but where's west ah i can't i
i will let my boob fly into the sky and
look for
west okay
okay all right can i roll my thingy
yes roll your animal can what was that
again wait wait wait wait wait wait
a lot of a lot of dices
uh was it six i think it was
wait it was
animal can plus one and wits right
yes okay if this is bush's though can we
just drive right through it with the
with this truck going
but there's junk between the uh oh
well now at this point after you've
driven to a certain point it does become
all thorns and bushes
wow can you drive through then would you
like to try
she said that with the smile i don't
trust it i don't
all right roll your drive again and
tiara this is to communicate with ooh
yes yeah okay ooh who flies off
okay who show us the way
with one success with one success uh
yule
you try to barrel into the uh
into the grass and leaves and thorns
around you
um and it's almost like hitting a brick
wall
even worse actually because the thorns
are kind of trying to poke into the van
uh back up becca we're following the
path
it's a very very narrow maze it has
become for your van
well nothing like a little challenge
what if we got on top of the hedges and
we ran
but the car oh we gotta get the car to
get to our
destination gotta get it out of here but
if the pathway is getting slimmer and
slimmer who's to say that we're
able to actually get the van out of this
maze where there's a path i can drive
all right i like your confidence
okay almost as long as one bow
oh yes my favorite almost as though the
thorns and bushes could hear you in some
kind of way the scenery begins to change
the thorns and grass on your sides begin
to grow
upward
do you have further to start fire with
anybody got a match
i take the gasoline out of the car
there's gasoline in the car that's a
starter there it is
got anything to start something
did not start a fire i don't know
oh what what happened with ooh yeah my
name has not returned
what about the success it was successful
however the thorns have grown
over the ceiling and you can hear that
your owl is trying to return to you
tiara but cannot through the thorns
can watoto check if he has a lighter
sure um role perception
to see if you forgot a lighter
[Laughter]
you had a lighter for some reason what's
a toe
it was in there amongst all the pocket
lint
nastiness remnants of shrek ice cream
sticky and disgusting but you have a
lighter
okay now we can try to start a fire
okay all right
do we take do we use the gasoline or
what to do gasoline and mouth
sure um to spit gasoline
um you know what you don't even need a
roll for that i'm just gonna let you do
it
oh okay you spit gasoline
now who will light it up will you also
light it up watertall
okay okay i'll i'll try
all right so in order to pull off the
entire maneuver
let's see um you're trying to burn the
grass
so let's go ahead and have you do um
dexterity to aim properly
and let's see
oh god i hope what that doesn't miss
then i want you to i want you to use
uh your
your survival okay yes
oh yeah
oh my god holy [\h__\h] let me roll that 10.
reroll that 10.
that is a critical success
now you get the feeling that this wasn't
supposed to happen
you get the feeling that the powers that
be that would not allow you to do this
however because you are so
powerful because your idea uh was so
effective
you can hear the thorns and the vines
and the grass shrieking
against the power of your gasoline and
fire
as they kind of pull back not like
normal vines and thorns would burn no
much different than that almost like
like a magical substance is being burnt
in it the smell is just
indescribable something something
magical
yet disgusting and foul
almost dripping dripping with uh
with red hot um
sort of almost like a mineral almost
like you're burning minerals at
scout's forge or something like that
almost as though the thorns and leaves
were made of something similar to iron
they shriek and pull back as though they
are alive
and a waypoint does open up for you
um a waypoint that leads to a place
that looks decently safe
oh you find this place
a decent safe haven
it's about to go mushroom
okay you guys drive up to the spot and
it looks like um
it has sufficient covering sufficient
covering from the outside world
um from being hunted or anything like
that it looks like um
this is the safe area for you all now
watertow has found this
oh his critical success thank you
thank you it's my birthday maybe
uh you see ooh is trying to work through
the thorns and leaves and you can you
can barely see who's this
but you think you may be able to make
contact again very shortly
you're kind of struggling through the
brush but for now
ladies this is where we have to end for
today
okay yeah we gotta we gotta stop here
for now
all right all right yes you're safe for
now save for now
this is where we end session one two
because
that was quite a ride
[Music]
but what about the tackles i know right
that's the biggest disappointment
well maybe maybe next time yeah yeah
yeah this is a very interesting very
interesting
mission indeed i must say
um yeah i'm looking forward to seeing
how you all resolve it
and i know in the beginning we had to do
a lot of setup normally by now we would
finish
the entire mission but because we had to
do setup introduction and whatnot that
took about like an hour
15 minutes or so um so it's like an
exceptional one-time thing
um but we worked through it pretty fast
and you guys made some great progress
and you all you all ended up being able
to role play very very well with each
other
yeah i was really surprised and everyone
kind of did their part
during the session and it all worked out
very well and was very balanced so
everyone claps all around you did
fantastic
thank you callie yeah thank you guys
uh yes you guys will get beats and
experience
um let's see you guys don't get
uh the special drinks this time around
um but that's okay i'll still give you
uh beats and experience of course and we
can talk about how you're going to spend
that off stream okay yes
so we'll go ahead and talk about that a
little bit later
um but don't worry you guys definitely
get experience from this from this
session
as well not just the mission
yay and i will outline for that that for
you guys and then at the beginning of
the next session
i'll show the audience um how
you guys did um in detail like how many
beats everyone got etc
and um we can tell everyone how you
decided to spend your experience
yay all righty yeah yeah yeah awesome
that was fun fun fun yeah i'm glad you
guys had fun
my favorite parts were we're seeing you
guys like interact with each other and
have like little rp's and stuff like
that it was
very delightful to listen to
yeah everyone's characters are very
wholesome and fun
i will say you guys made some very fun
characters so
and next time yeah next time the next
session will be on someone else's
channel
so please stay tuned everyone yeah oh
and we'll okay you guys tomorrow for um
minecraft yeah ender dragon
yeah finally it's happening
oh so excited wow i'm very much looking
forward to it i wish i could have done
more to prepare
but i will i will be practicing shooting
my arrows so i can be of some use to you
guys
we'll get him down in one minute we are
so strong we got the power we can take
him
down in an instant i believe in us have
confidence that's right yeah you get
chiari you got everyone diamond armor
didn't you
yeah with some nice stats and we got a
lot of
uh enchanted bows and we got a lot of
arrows spectral arrows we got we got
golden apples in cooperation with
uh uh our our dear inna
taco bell thank you for helping out
james
[Music]
fingers crossed i want to ask gouda
one thing because previously i think i
asked gouda
if if we even know where the portal is
and good i was like yeah yeah yeah but
did you
did you not actually mean the fortress
no i usually get the i get fortresses
and like where you get the blaze rods
mixed up i haven't found a fortress
okay and we need to use the under pearls
we gotta toss them in the pearls to find
the [\h__\h]
the stronghold yeah we have to find a
stronghold all right
a lot of a lot of ender pearls so should
be no problem
cool yeah hold on have a little journey
in the beginning a little walk
through the park and then then we go in
okay i'll do my best i'll fight really
hard for you guys let's fight together
yeah let's do it exciting
so please look forward to it you guys
anyway um
we are hollow myth and hope that you
have a fantastic day
what should we say is the sign off word
everyone
ultimately okay
ready on it's three two one oatsmith
okay
yeah okay all right here we go yay three
two one ultimate
bye everyone
peace
you