[Music]
Y
OGOG
[Music]
Everyone, Koko Azuki and Kikkeriki
Kikerikikiki Kikerikī So today's
Amogester is our guest Chiara-
chan Yay, yay, hello to
all the KFP members too
Kikkerikki Koazuki Azuki-
senpai, after all, we're home  It's stuttering, it's
stuttering, it's stuttering, it's
true, I don't think it's going to fit in. It's okay, it's
not going to work, it's streaming, but I'm watching OBS, it's amazing, it's
moving smoothly, but the camera's
book is really stuttering, I feel like it's
true.
Yeah,
oh well, I guess it's better if I stand up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,\hit'll be fine if I fix it, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,\hoh, papa, I'm sorry, papa, while I'm at it, I'd like to\htalk a little bit about what we're going to do today.
Chiara-chan is here right now
with me. I made a few adjustments to the camera.
Today, I'm going to go to Geo Guesser.
Thank you, Overseas World Tour Ost.
So, today we have
Chiara-chan, who is originally from Austria, visiting us. Let's take a look
at Austria.  I'm really
looking forward to traveling around Australia. Traveling In Australia.
Hey, I'm really sorry.
What's going on with what I just said?
Hey everyone, that's right today.  I'm
sorry, but I
'm not from Australia. I'm from Austria, not Australia. Thank you. I'm sorry, but I'm not from Australia. I'm from Austria. Thank
you.
So, Australia and
Austria are similar, but what's
wrong with this? Just like Chiara-chan, if you
mistake Austria for Australia, it's
like they don't exist after all.Well, I
wonder what it is in particular, but Japanese people
often get them confused.Australia.  If I
say that I'm from
Australia, I'm always told that
it's amazing Australia, so that's true, but it's a completely different place.Australia is a
big island near Japan, and Austria is
in the middle of Europe, so it's a German train.  Austria is a speaking country,
and I'm from Mozart, and there
's no sea, so it's true that it's landlocked to begin with.It's
connected to many other countries.Can I
ask you to give me some information about Austria today
?  I
want to know.I want to know.I
want to know.It's about the size of Austria's
Hokkaido, but it's about the size of Hokkaido in Japan.So,
everyone, please remember that it's about the same size as Hokkaido.It
's a bit embarrassing when you receive it.  I
want to know how big it is. It's
tiny.
But it's fine, but Hokkaido is big. It's about that
size, and 60
% of it is in the Alps, making it a mountainous country.
Yes, there is a rich natural environment.
And yes, as Kia-chan said earlier, the capital
is Mozart, the capital of music, and a place called Jesus, which is frozen.  Yes, that
's right. Yeah, that
's right. Everyone has heard of it. Yes, I've heard it. Both Mozart
's songs and Utobe's songs are famous
and I think everyone knows them, but they were made in this country.  That
's what I mean. Yes, no, it's a great country.
Molt is my friend.
Kira-chan was my friend.
Yes, I've lived a long time because I'm not a mayor.
But, you know, Molt was my best friend. Yes, he was my best friend. He
was strong and strong.  The Japanese
language is German, so
today I think we'll see a lot of German on signs and
in many places.In
fact, I wonder what German
dialects are being used.  That's right.If you live
in a different place, the
words you say may be different.It's like the Kansai dialect.There
's a dialect in Japan, but there's also a dialect in Austria.Yeah,
I went to school a little bit.
At times, I wonder what it was, when I went to the same school as these
kids from the really rural areas, and
when they started talking, I couldn't understand what they were saying.
So yes, it's the same thing. In different countries,
there are dialects.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, but with this, I
can easily tell which one is German and which is Australian.
If you listen to me, I'll talk about the pronunciation, the
intonation, the intonation, oh
yeah, oh yeah, that's right. Well, you'll have to try saying it before you can
understand it. But you all can speak English pretty well,
right? That's right, this is
seriously that Australian thing.  Not only that,
but I think it's quite the same in Germany, and
in most countries in the center of Europe, I
think everyone can speak English, and in addition to their own native language, they can
definitely speak English, and they also study English.
Yes, yes, at that school, the
teaching methods are good. Well, everyone can
speak English, German, and English.
That's amazing. The
education in Austria is amazing. Yes, I
couldn't do it after Germany.  Yes, I'm sure you'll be able to
communicate in English if you go to that pickpocket.I've
been looking into that
Sachertorte with that sweet.I've
been looking into the Sachertorte blood in Austria.Yes, yes, yes, yes,
eat it.  Well, even in Japan, I
think there are quite a few shops that put a lot of effort into desserts, but I've
never had it before, but it's
chocolate, isn't it?  Oh yeah, it's a
chocolate cake with some sort of apricot jam in the middle.Apricot jam, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it,
but I'd like to try this authentic food someday.I
definitely want to try it, like when I lived in Japan.It's
kind of temporary.  That 7-Eleven was
serving Zahatre as a dessert,
and I was really happy to buy it.
There was a time when they were selling something, but
Starbucks' Harte was 100% different,
so maybe they've
changed it a lot to make it more palatable to Japanese people.I see.It
seems like things aren't going well today.  I
feel like I'm going around in circles, but I'm just hoping it'll get better.
Can you all hear me?
Chiara, I'm already feeling sick
and stuttering today. Don't worry, I'm starting to stutter. I have
n't changed any settings.  It's okay, husband,
it's okay, it's better than standing there,
okay, Depachika. Yes, I'm sure I'll go to Depachika,
and maybe I'll be able to find Haru
next time. Oh, I see. Well, that's the case today. Well, I
'd like to go around Austria with Chiara-chan on Geo Guesser.
Chiara-chan.  Thank
you, thank you. Where are you going
? I want to start.
Then, the game
start start Kira -chan has seen the same screen.  It's
like, no, I
tried the Austrian version, but it
's really annoying every time, so it's a little boring.But
everyone, it's the first time I've seen that Japanese person,
so I waited a long time and
looked at this bus station.  Look, what's this
written on Shimoda? Oh, I
don't know, but if you try hard, you'll see this. The
bus running in the city goes back once,
goes back once, and that person at this bus station is reflected.
Who do you think they are? I don't know what kind of people they are.
Yeah,
they're great. No, these two are famous comedians from Oria.
Oh, they're comedians. It's funny.
For a comedian, it's amazing to see them wearing suits. They
make me feel royal.
Why, yeah, yeah, I'm making fun of that old story about Austria.
But that guy on the left looks like a tsukkomi and the one on the right looks like an
idiot. Actually,
he's a famous comedian. Yeah, it's pretty funny. Yeah, it's funny,
mind you.  After all, it
's about that land, or rather, Austria.What makes you laugh?Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, what kind of bus is this?
But there's a Chinese restaurant here.There's a
Chinese restaurant, and it looks like it's pretty good.
There's a lot of culture from all over the world, there's a subway,
there's a subway, there's a subway,
uuuu, that blue, blue, that's coming soon, I can see the
mark here, I can see this
station, I don't really understand it,
but I can
understand it, it's left, right, left and right.  That's
right. Look to the right. Is this the entrance? Go back and go back once.
Yes, yes, but I've never covered that hard gas.
Where in Vienna is it? But where is this subway? Is this the
city of Vienna? Where in Vienna is it?
Where is it running? Well, it
runs
everywhere, so it's a subway. I'm looking for numbers everywhere, but it
's not written down, so I
can see the subway.
It looks like a bus, but if you go a little to the right, you
'll find it.  This or that park on the bottom left looks like a park. I
wonder if there's a park here or there. No, that's so difficult. That's right, that's wrong.
This is an ordinary train. It's difficult to wait for an
ordinary train. There is no subway near the ordinary train.  It
's not running, it's not moving right now, use the mouse,
go up a little, go to the top
left, and on the left, there's a U there. To the left, a little
further to the left, this is the subway mark. This is the subway mark. The
underground mark in Suria is U.  It's written
there, yeah, so if you look for it, this is
where you started, it's the last stop, it's the starting point, it
's not the last stop, it's not the beginning, but yeah, there's nothing beyond this, you're
going down there, you're going down there.
Okay, I'm probably going to go to the bottom. Hmm,
but this probably is
n't the center, and I think it's not that U2, so
wait, there are quite a lot of U's.
Uu, yeah, yeah, yeah, somewhere, somewhere,
etc.  You
shouldn't use it.If you
could give me some hints in the comments, Is there a danger?That's true.But
not everyone knows
about Austria.Also, this
is a really important hint.This subway station is
just  Let's go around a little more, let's go around, let's
go. Well, we've come all the way here, so when we
come to this big road, it's that one.
No, it'll be helpful if we can understand the medicine.
There's Meguro food and all kinds of things in that Tokyo.
Well, it's easy for me to understand, but I
think it's okay, I think it's okay, I think it's
okay, this is a roundabout, and I think it's
okay. Should I go left? Should I go left? I'll go left.
Maybe I can go anywhere.
Okay, senpai.  As I'm spinning around like this, I
can't remember where it all started,
but somehow this time there's a station, so it
's like a school next to the station, and that's my first objective.  I'm
running, yeah, sorry once.
Look behind me, there's that blue building. Yeah,
write down the address of Austria.
It's the 22nd ward, the 22nd ward, the 22nd ward.
So, open the map one more time. Yes.  There
should be 22 of them, so
zoom out once and stay a little above the river. Uno
[Music]
192019 That's not it. I do
n't think Unku is here in the first place.  But all these numbers
are like this. What's wrong with 2222? Hmm,
maybe it's
across the river or across the street, 22.
But yeah, yeah, if you
check all the subway stations around there, you'll be fine.  I
don't remember if this is the way this is.
No, I don't think it's that far away.
There's a possibility that it's a little closer.
Ah, Huapa. Oh
yeah.
Ordinary trains also pass by.  That's right, that's right
. That means regular trains are also passing through.
Ordinary trains have this mark. Ordinary trains. Oh
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. Come
here, come on, you're
wrong about Leopolda.
Hmm, this is it.  It said 22.
Well, 2022, 22. It's
not that close, but it
wasn't green either, and that liquid looks pretty big. Hey, I
tried picking it up here and there.
A little bit to the right, there
's a subway line here, down, down, down there.The
first station I
started with was Air Air.
Hey, that's what it felt like, right?
I remember it so well.
It's still different, but around here, I'm
not bald. Yes, I'm bald. There it is, it's there, it's there. Owazuki-
senpai's  In the free game, the
regular train is like this,
right? That's right. Haha,
once I got home, I was home, and
if I could go back like that, I
wouldn't have been here.  I just came here and
there was that bus station. I heard there was a school on the left and
right. Yeah, there was a fukushire. Oh, it's
not here, it says Fukushire Maria Freedon.
There's also a Chinese restaurant, but it's the same.  Looks like it's here or here.
Go back and look at it once. I
want to know the name of this school. Ah, it's the name of the school. Ah,
I can't read it. Ah, I wonder if it's wrong. It's not there. It's
a little further away. It's here. The name is
written on it.  It says ``Nesukure.'' Eh, I'm
graffitiing
it. What's the name of that? It looks like this.
Where did you enter the school? There
's a school in the bottom left corner of this one, right here.
There's a restaurant nearby, I
think. It's called Usendofstrasse, which looks like this. It's in the back. It
looks like this. It's here. It looks like this. Yes, it's not
right. This is not a school. It's not a school. This is not a school.  It's
not a school.
[Music]
Pou, this is the name of the school, the name of the school, the
name of the school, it's in that town, it's
here, it's the supermarket, it's all different.  Oh, it
's a hospital, I want a hospital,
but it's around here, after
all, there
's a house, there's a Chinese restaurant here,
and I wonder if
there's a name for this town somewhere.  That's right,
this
is here, this is here, this is here, this is
here, this is the address, this is the address of this house,
wow, that's how the name is written.I see,
yes, this is like this, so 1
1 this 12 this mopo 1
[Music]  ]
Oh yeah, I wonder where 44 is. I
can't see it, and I can't even see the name of the house,
but there's a road in front of it. Is it
here? This road,
this road. Oh, this looks like this.  Yes, that means
Is this a road? Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a
road. Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a road. Yes, this is a road. It's not for cars. It's not for cars, but
if there is a road, it looks like it's around here or around
here. Do you want to go? 12341223, around here.  I
feel like that, but maybe that car is
n't on the right road, so it's one step ahead on the map.Yes,
this is small, so the road to the right of this small one is
small, so
there's a road behind it.  Is this this? This is this? Yes,
this is this road. This is that big road. It's a big road.
Okay, so it's
a little more this way, yes yes yes,
this way. It's
amazing how you do things in such detail. I've never done it in such detail.
Okay, this is the bicycle path.Okay, no, okay, let's
do it here.Let's go.Let's go.Let's
go with Chiara as the first guest.I'm a
professional, so I'm a professional.  There
may be a possibility of a way, but what do you think? It's
okay, it's okay, let's go, okay, let's go, let's go, then let's go.
Is this a bad result for my seniors? No, I want to get 5,000
points. I want to get 5,000 points in Austria, so
Ki-chan is going to be 5 ahead of me. Let's do my
best. But Kia-chan has
given me a lot of amazing information, and I've
arrived here.  The subway is also the
center of Winn.
That number should be K. Okay, then I'd
like to go next.
Mt. Nekie, oh, it's so beautiful. It's a beautiful mountain that's
spreading out, but I think I'll move on to N.
Hey, Igi-chan, it's nice. It's beautiful. It's
nice here.  I feel like I've been there before, too.Ah, I
feel like there's a place there.Ah,
Siamgas, the name of the place, Siamgas.My name.It's
so detailed, I don't know.Oh, it does
n't have an address written down, no, it
doesn't.  What kind of shop is this? I wonder
if it's a shop that makes windows. Okay, yeah, but
here, the house is beautiful and the house is cute. It's quite
Australian.
Yeah, Europe
is full of people. It's all the way north.  I
've heard that there's a good chance you'll only get a 90% win,
but even then, it might be a little outside the win, or it might be right
next to that, and it's faster than this.
What's the road like? Yeah, it certainly
looks like a highway.
Yes, the cityscape is beautiful. Please come and visit us. Come
on! It's a
really beautiful place. But
what about this road? The road is so big. Oh
yeah. Oh yeah.  I know, it's
somewhere around Salzburg. Salzburg.
Maybe Hallein is nearby. I've
heard of all the towns I've heard of.
Salzburgsalt is actually Salzburg inside Salzburg. I
see, Salzburg is inside Salzburg.
For example, that Salzbrok is
like Kansai,
and Osaka in there is also
called Salzburg.It's Salzburg in Salzburg.I
don't know, but it feels like that.Yeah, yeah, that's what it sounds like,
but this
is Salzburg.  What is it? It's
not a city, it's a countryside. It's difficult to live in the countryside. It's so bad that
Salzburg is coming. It's so
bad. It's so well-known, but it looks like it's
all place names.  I wonder which
one is the center
?Open the map once in the city.Let
's go to Salzburg.Okay, just a little above where you can
see the Hallein.Eh, a little above,
up, left and right.After this, now,
where the mouse was, there is the Hallein.  It's
down, down, down, right, left, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, ah, ta
for you.
Which way does 2.1km go?
Wait, wait, Oba was the closest.
0.7km Oh yeah, that's right.
There's Over Am, so which one is Over Im?
Ah, right, left, left, Kokkoshi So,
wait here.  When I turn in this direction, what
direction is it? It's over here, so there's Oberam in the west-west direction.
Even if I'm a senior, it's pretty close. It
's 700 meters around here. Wait, wait, there
was no high-speed buck here just now.  Ah,
it's delicious, it's delicious, it's
delicious, I wonder if it's
all going well. It's delicious. It might be somewhere. Yeah, it's going fast. I wonder
if it's around here. I do
n't know, but it would be nice if there was a river. Is there a river
?  Can you see the river?
Hmm, it would be
nice if I could go through the expressway. Wait a minute, go home once, and then go to the other side.  If you look at the name and the name of the road, you
might think it would help, so just go south a little bit and
look at the river, Ahahaline, here from here, Haline
, here, that, that, that, that, that, that, that border, border,
border,
border, border, hain, somewhere.  I
wonder
if there's a border, so I wonder
if there's a border. Is
there a border?  Isn't
that the
address posted on that building?
Oh, I see, the river is there, but wait, it's on the bridge right now,
right between Ober and Hein.
Karakawa oh
oh, this isn't this big skin,
it's different, it's different, it's different, it's different,
it's a
small one.  Maybe there
's this tiny skin-like thing, but it
looks like this, but wait a minute, but how is it facing?  I
want you to look at the address of the Hallein building over here. It's the address, right? The address is
right here. It's on the side of this building. I
wonder if it's
right here.  Oh, wait a minute, read it. Hey,
read it. Hey, I can't read it. Maybe it's Hamata.
Hamas 6, that's mahama.
Chis, this is this, but wait, a, but that's fine. Oh, wait, a
store is here. Oh, store.
Ario, there's a penis.  It
's a pretty big road, so
it's a big river, oh
it's true, it's true, you already know it.
Oh,
this roundabout, this map, this signboard, yes,
Efra, it's big, it's big, somewhere,
wait, it's just like here, yes, yes,
yes
[Music]
Jesus, it's dangerous, oh, this is Hamas, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's Hamas, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's Hamas, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's
Hamas.  I've been
passing through here, and the
vertical line is here. That's
what it is. I got it. Now that I know, I'm
falling back. That's not true. The
tension is
rising. Wait, one home is here, and another
here.  It looks like something like this.That parking lot
is here.Oh, this is something like the
parking lot of this restaurant.By
the way, this is a restaurant called Booth Pavilion.It's
called Sausé's Pavilion.I do
n't know what Pavilion is.  It's like eating a revived person. Yes, it's
not all-you-can-eat, but it's a special store. It's a
special store, but it says Meku. It has the
name of another store written on it.
It's a super supermarket.
It's like a supermarket, but
it might have changed.  No, from this photo, that's
right, it's surprisingly different. I
think this is probably this house. I
crossed the river a little while ago. Here, this is this.
This river is  Well, that's it, oh
, okay, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, 5,000 points Tayoshiwa, I did it, 5,000 points, 00 meters, I
want to get it, great,
0 This is fine, this is fine.  I
came to a place called Salzburg, a place called Salzburg, and
it
was a beautiful place.
Salzburg
is Salzburg in Salzburg Salzburg is Salzburg, but this is
Salzburg, and this is where Salto
was born, and that's where famous songs
were born.
Azeno
Ge, so yes, yes, yes, it's
easy to understand.By the way, the correct pronunciation is
Salzburg, Salzburg
yay, yay, morelano,
leak, no,
morelan, no, no, I feel like great
songs will be created here.It's true,
yay, then I'd like to move on to the next one.
Let's go, it's gonna be Un again. This time it's
gonna be Un. This bus is
running on Un. Is the
bus red or not? But wait, wait, I
don't know. Maybe it's wrong. But,
wait, there's a station station.  Hey, what did you use? Oh, what's the
name? I can't see the name. There
's a bus, and there's a station. Yeah,
this is a big station. This is an amazing station building. It's
cool. Hey, it's pretty normal. This one looks pretty
normal.  If it's not written there, it
's not written.
Uh, this is where the
destination of that train is written. It's
just the destination. Is it written in here?
Yeah, yeah, here, this, ah, hae,
Hadestrov. People center, Hadestrov.  No Hades
Dorf, Hadesdorf.
There's also a station called Hadesdorf Hades Station. It's Ade
Station on the First Subway Railway.
Hmm, where is Hadestorf?
Let's find out. Let's find out. There's a big
thing to the east over here.  This is it, oh, that
soccer team. Oh, it might
be a stadium. Yeah, Gapi. Well, I
don't know anything about soccer,
but Gapi is famous. It's an
Austrian team. It's a professional soccer
team from Osua. Yeah, if I knew soccer, this would
be it.  I might even know where it
is. Is there anyone who knows it
? Do you like it?
Stadion Ariane
Stadion Yeah, this was Un.
That's right. The team name. The team name. I see.
Rapid Un. I'm sure.  I've heard that word before,
so it's huge. It's like a stadium where soccer is played. Well, it's a big
deal. But there are a lot of things, but if you go here, you can
go to Linz.
Linz in Win.  No, outside of Wynn,
outside of Linz,
right? Yes, I'm sorry. Please look to the left.
Yes, this is the cat's blue 14th ward.
14th ward. This is Wynn's 14th ward, KK bra. Yeah, can we
go there? How about Wynn in the 14th ward?  I wonder
how many wards there are from 1 to 23.
23 It's the same as Tokyo, but it's mostly made of that
stuff. It's a bowl, it's a bowl, but
I honestly don't know. 14 Where is it?
14 It looks pretty cool.  12345678 Are
n't you going around in circles? There
's always a name in that number for 14, but you can
look it up. I'm going to look it
up.
Tee,
Marin Ad Serin
[Music]
Fabrif Ed or somewhere, just now,
this one was 22, right, that
's only 22, 2321, this one,
2021222, that's right, that's the only one, so
that's either over there or on this side.
Yes, that's right, Penten, ah, the stadium,
right there, wait, wait, over there, over here,
left, right, right, right here, it's a lie,
oh, it's a huge stadium, it's here, it's
Kapitsu, it's where it says Kapitukapits, it's
here, it might be Debichertov or that big station.
It's this station, it's
amazing, it's so big, it's amazing, this place is so
famous. I don't know where it came from, but I
feel like it's somewhere around here. Let's go.
Well, let's go home once again. This is where it's at.
Well, that means this road here, here,
here, oh,
oh, it starts there. I see, it's a bit like this.
This road coming in here
is certainly a complicated road. It's a complicated road, and the
back here is also a terminus.
Rota Yes, yes, it's here. Zero, zero, bring out 0. I wonder if it's behind me.
Ah, come in. Come in here.
Wow, I wonder if I can do 0.
Hey, it's written here too, so let me pull. Oh,
sure, let's go on top of this.  It's true that the road is
getting closer. I wonder how long it will take to
get there. I'm already on the way to this road
. Well, this is about it. It
's detailed work. It's detailed work.
But this is it.
Or really, let's go, let's go, we can't go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Even lower, but 5000 points yay
yay yay yay yay if you ignore that 1 it
's 0m If you ignore that 1 it's 0 That's right, it's
0, right? 0, if you ignore it
Well then, let's go to the next one.
But I've
never seen a map of Australia so detailed.
Really, where is this place? There's something that looks like a castle over here,
but
there are so many mountains here. It's so cool.
This is so cool.  What about this house that everyone lives in
? Yes, it's
running a market. Let's
take a look at the Makibiun building. What is it?
Yes, it's 2020. 2020 Ward is the 20th ward.
This is a Panya-like
role. I
know.  Of course I knew, I know,
20, but 21 was over here earlier, so I wonder
if it's this way, or maybe it's closer.Let's
go and look around a little more.Yes,
yes, yes.Yes, yes, yes, it
doesn't necessarily mean it's close.  It doesn't matter if the numbers are
close together.There
are so many amazing markets.Hmm,
but there are also quite a lot of shops.However, there seems to
be a station near the station.  It seems like it's going to happen, right now, just
go straight, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, that's the tram, that's the tram,
this is the tram.In Japan, it's called the tram.In
Austria, it's Tarentan,
or Ostrava.A tram or a tram.A tram or a Subban.Which one?  That
means there's a station, right?
Well, there's a station for this car. No, it's not
really a pharmacy. This is a pharmacy.
Yes, there are a lot of stylish buildings.  There
's a possibility that there are people living above the pharmacy, and there's a shop on the first floor, and
a lot of people call this their home. Hey, I
don't have any smoke, but I think the station is here. This is the
side of the
train.  The station of the tram is likely to get off the place where you get off. That
big
size is a big difference here,
here is a huge bell, there is a certain left, so that is going to
go back once.  Go back, go
back, go back, go back one more time, go back too far,
go too far, left and right,
it's there too, yeah, that left, right
there, right there, here, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right for
you, but what do you
say?  Oh, yeah,
wait a minute, write that down. There's a
place called Valentineplatz. It
's very detailed. It's very detailed. I
wonder if there are quite a lot of areas where trams run.
Yes, there are quite a few.  Maybe it's just that it's hard to
narrow it down, but there's already a lot of stuff.
Oh, this is what I saw from the back earlier. Oh, I
understand.
Also, the bus station
is the bus station, right, right, right, right, right, this is the
bus station.  I feel like there's a main streetcar to the right of the main streetcar.
It's over here.
No, let's move on. Kukuma, the bear is the bear, the
bear is protecting the eggs. It's true, they have the eggs. What's
that? No, no, no.
No, ah, happy to the right, straight ahead, right there,
right there, Brittaplatz, hmm,
hmm, I wonder where it is around 20, but just now, it
's 2020, right? 20
wards, 20 wards, 20 wards, 20 wards, it
's still 20 wards.  I identified
it once, oh, it came, ah, Igasus, U2, ah, U6, U66,
Gastayu 6, yu 6, you know, you know,
oh, it's running from the other side of that river, oh, it's
running from the other side of the river, so it's the 20th ward,
right here on the river.  Even if it's nearby, I found a beech. Eh,
just hover over the mouse, upper left, yeah, yeah.
This is pretty okay. This area is Brigitte.
So it's Yuyu here. Let's
look for Yuigashi, right? But Yunoyu
Yuu  It was warm, it was warm, it was on the left, in the middle right now,
in the middle,
yay, yay, yay, yay.
Which way did it come from? Well, this is far away. It
was quite a big intersection.  Brigetta Platz Buri Getta
Platz There's a park next to that park
Brigetta Platz This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, that's the bear's name, that's
written there, that's this, that's right, that's
right, this has a bear's name on it, it's sitting there, it's
sitting, it's sitting, it's a
bear.  This
is the big intersection from earlier. It's probably here. It
came from here. Wow, how did it come? How
did it get to the river? There was a market on the river too, right? Market. Ah, there
it was. Hey,
how did it come once? Backing up, it
came a long way, so yeah.
20  The river doesn't pass through it, so it's not there.Maybe,
but did you go to some strange parking lot?I
'll go back once.Yes, yes, here it is.This is the place.I
want to know the address.The address is, uh,
in the 20th ward, half way across the street.  Yes,
that's
likely. That's right. It's
not around here. I
can't find the toothless idiot. How did he come here?
It's all the way south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, south-south, all the way.
What does that
mean? What does that mean?
Wait a minute, that Hanofa mark,
that Hanofa mark,
there's that Hanofa gas, there's Make and
Leave Maketo, that's right, that's right, so let's go
straight here.  I came here and came out on this huge road.
This is amazing. It looks like a triangle. It looks like a triangle.
Is this a parking lot? Oh, what's going on? Is
this a road?  This kind of road is good,
but it's like this
middle of the road, right? It's like this, right? This is it, right? There's
a run, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it. It's
a bit tingling from here, but this
road is this way.  I'm sure
there's a
store building here, right? There's a market, right? There's a
market on the left, and
there's a corner where you turn backwards. Oh yeah,
this is a dead end.  Oh, it's
not a dead end, because that car won't take it here or there. Yeah, yeah, I
think it's pretty much right now. Not really,
but there's already quite a lot. I wonder if there's quite a lot there. Should I
go? There's one around here.
No, there's 1cm
left here, right here, right
here, right here, yes, that's what I think, so let's
go.
It's good, no,
but this is luck,
so Wow, that's steadily
shrinking, that's amazing, I did it, then I
'll go to zero, will it be the last 5, the last, I'll go next, Kia-
chan At the end, next, next,
this is bad.  Isn't it on the expressway
?
Wow, Wow,
Linz, well, it's 3kg,
but it's 33kg, right? I'm going to Linz, but this is 33kg.  I can
go to Daramen.Which way should I go
? Hey, I'm passing by on the highway.My senior can drive.I
have a license to drive, but my
mom can't drive.Eventually,
everyone in Austria has a car, but it
's not as good as America.  Oh, that's right. I
don't think many people who live in that city have it, but other than that, I think
there are quite a few people who do. But
this is CA7, that
park where you can go to that Checek and Papa Park.  I can go to the park
Eh, it's A7, right? It's A7, right
? A7 It's huge. This road is huge. It's like a national highway.
Yeah, yeah, that's right. A6A6A
4 minutes
Ugh, it's pretty good. I found the nose ah7.
But that's A7.  It's not just 7, it's
different. It's different. This is Cebu.
It's a normal A4. It's from Lindt. That
's it. Oh yeah, it's so far.
Linds A7 A7
is A7. Where is it from where to where?
Linz It's so good that it goes through and comes out, so it's probably 1 here. It's here that I read Nortelinz. That's right, if I hit the book
randomly, it's
this way. It's
3 kg up to Linz.
3 kg.  Yes, yes, yes, wait 3kg But
there was a sign here, so I went 3km south
and I could go here.It's amazing to think of south, but I
can't think of anything like this, it's
not somewhere here.Wow, that's 3kg.
Wow, that's what this sign is all about. What's so weird about this sign
? This sign is 1 kg. 1
kg ahead is Prague, Hrasta,
Lens Centrum, Linz's Chushin, and Zatsu.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, right now, now there
is a fairly [ __ ] strass right now.  It's
so difficult to get out of here, but there's a little bit of a road over here. There's this road. Yeah, yeah, that's right. It doesn't look like this. It looks like this. But it's a super
difficult high-speed drive to get zero with this.  I feel like the whole world
is difficult, so this is
it. I'm not used to it from there.
I think it's a convergence, so I get cranky. You know, the
way the map is drawn, you know, when you get closer,
something's off.  Ah, ah, we're
not joining, we're not merging, it's here, ah, here, ah, here, a
lie, fraud, fraud, oh yeah, oh yeah, fraud, lie, it
's complicated, I've been fooled, I've been fooled,
but here we part like this, oh
here, right, but we're just about to
be together.
Right, now that I think about it, I still feel like I was spawned in a good place.I can really see this, so we're going to be together, yeah, a little bit higher, a little bit higher, over here or that.I think it's from that right side.  The coming road has
come to a complete end. It's true that this is also a
swamp. I can
see it on the map.
This is the biggest one right now. This is the biggest one right now. Yeah, yeah, I see.
[Music]
Oh, I'm going to fall into the swamp of zero.  Well, well,
that university definitely had
it, so we have no choice but to identify it with the professional knowledge of that senior
. But if you think about it normally, it's
around here, this cut here, right
here.  I think it's fine
. Let's try this A7 and make it A7. Do you
believe that? It wasn't
0 because of me earlier, so I'll
leave it to you now. Let's go. Okay, let
's go to Austria.  Let's go to the 5th place,
guess what?
Don't be silly. What's the
point of this? Don't get
too close. Wow,
fraud was right. Da double,
fraud fraud in the fraud fraud. The
yeah, from
far, far away.  I think it was better to see it.I
guess it's a bit
difficult to understand, but it
was Linz, right here, away from Un,
between Zazbrok and Un.  It's
been an hour since we said we're satisfied with this, so
I guess we'll go to about 5 locations today.It's
interesting.When
I was playing free games, it was
n't zero, it was 3,
like 500m.  But I was completely satisfied with it.That's why it
might have been boring.I
don't think so.It's completely different when you do it like this.It's quite
difficult to master, right?It's
true that you'll be very satisfied if you get it right.But Kia-chan
was with you today.  So, here's what I saw in Un. There are such
things as the 1st to 23rd arrondissements,
there are subway signs,
and so on. I learned a lot today. I
can go sightseeing in Austria with just one person. Wait
a little longer.  I'd really like to know more about it,
but I still don't know. I went
there today. What's Winn and Linz
? Linz Linz, right? Linz and Salz, right?
Burg Salzburg.
Maybe somewhere else, maybe Innsburg.
Yes, but that's right, that's right, Innsberg
Innsberg Only on the left side here,
there is a possibility that it will appear, but
where do we all go by plane?
Even in Austria, this airport is
not used.  Even if everyone who is not used is going to go, it
's Win, right here, here, where is the airport, what is the
area, that's it, those who fly from overseas are sure to go to
Un, yeah, yeah, right now, from Tokyo,
Narita or Haneda to Win, I'm sure.  I
saw in a book that there was a plane that could fly over here that was being revived.It was advertised because I
wanted to stay there.It's
where Yoya-chan was born and raised,
so I'm really interested in that.If I
went to Australia, I'd come here.
There are some places you should go,
other than Winn, of course
[Music] There
are many places in Wintown, but
to put it more roughly, I
definitely want you to go to Salz Block.  There
are a lot of really beautiful ponds around Salzbruck, and
in lieu of the lack of the sea, there
are a lot of ponds because everyone swims in those beautiful ponds.
There are a lot of famous ponds, and I think it's good to go and see them, and
just enjoy the view, and
there are 3 mountain ranges in the Alps, so I just
went to Salzburg and got a feel for the mountains.
Look, but yes, Oria, is it cold? It
gets quite hot in the summer, for example,
30°35°, but it's quite hot.
Sometimes I go up there,
but I
don't get that stuffy bug, so yeah.  Oh, that's great, Japan is so humid,
and it's quite cold in the winter, and the
snow piles up and the rice fields are pretty thick. Those
European people who come on skis love it, and they
often come to Austria for those winter
vacations.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's pretty true.
You
can go skiing in a lot of different places.
But it's pretty popular around Salzburg. I
think it's really popular, too. I
went skiing there last year, too.
There's a famous place.It's famous.Austria is an
international
sport.Austrian athletes are quite good at sports.That's
right, they're strong.On the other hand, ours
only really do snow sports in the winter.  I do
n't go swimming or anything like that.No, I don't
think there are that many of them.No, I don't think there are too many of them.But even now, I still hear stories that make me want to go to Salzburg.And of course, when I hear music, I think that's true, no matter where you are.  Salzburg
has a famous music festival every year.Music
anywhere is fine.It
's the place where The Sound of Music was set.Yo, that's
Sazburg, that's Sazburg.No
, I really like Sambu music.  I
've seen it many times, and I've also taken part in it.There
's a tour.That's right, that Third Meek tour
shows you all the places, and it's really nice.It's nice to have tours like that,
so you can
learn more about Austria.  It's small,
so if you're going to go there, you wo
n't just have to go to Un, you'll have to take that train, and it's
easy to get to a lot of things, yeah, yeah,
yeah, you can get to Salzburg from Un, in probably 23 hours, two and a half hours, three hours.  There
are quite a few places where you can go, yes,
yes, yes, you can go there, but it's not as good as the Shinkansen,
but yeah, yeah, you
can still see the scenery and feel like you can
go on and on.  Hey Chiara-chan, I
asked you to attend to me. I
have my passport. I have it, but it's been a long time
since I can't travel, so I haven't used it at all. I want to use it.
Yes, I want to use it. I
want to use it. Please do it this winter. I'm
really thinking about it.  Well, I guess I'll ask
Chiara to show me around. I'll
be waiting for you. I'm really happy. You
can stay at my house or
at a hotel, either way, it's
cold, cold, cold in winter.  It's ok to ask,
but it's cold, but it's beautiful. That Christmas
market. Ah, Christmas. It's Christmas
time. I want to go there.
Oh, come on, come on Austria.
Kihara-chan has been using Osaka dialect and Kyoto dialect too much for a while now.  I
thought that
was amazing as we talked, but I used to live in Osaka,
so that's amazing.
Well, I've already told you so much
about Austria today, and I'd like to
thank you for showing me around.  Thank you so much. Please come and
play with me again.
Thank you to everyone at KFP for listening. It's
been a while since I last
saw you, but thank you for showing me the fun part. I'm
sure you'll enjoy playing
with people who know more about it.  Anyway, it was interesting to learn about the place, so I
hope I can do it again next time.I wasn't
able to go to Germany today, but Unki-
chan and I were talking about going to Germany,
so I hope we can do it again next time.  I
thought I'd like to go to Germany as well.I
don't know much about Germany, but I
think if we work together, we'll find it somehow.Today, the
two of us managed to get close to each other, so
next time.  Let's aim for 0m. Let's say
yes. Thank you everyone. I
think I'll end today here. Kira-chan,
thank you.
Will you go? Yes,
yes, then let's go!
Bye-bye-bye
[Music]
Yo DET