[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
oh
that was probably uh advertisement that
you guys heard when I opened YouTube
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh well
foreign
[Music]
key
you chickens freaking out at every
little sound
what
freaky I know the shot is gone
no
why
come on
okay you know what we'll we'll play uh
like the cool people do a player in full
screen anyway
are sure
ah
there we go
again Stay Stay don't go away don't go
away
don't go away
my whole screen's realigned whenever I
open the game
well I have it on full screen because
when I do a window mode
and then I do the smallest solution it's
still stretching over two of my screens
can you explain that to me
oh my God help
oh
like when I when I do ah
when I do window
oh wait now it's okay
I mean I was too small
um
wait
that's too small what's a good size this
is okay that's better
resolution was crazy big earlier
oh
what no this is normal this is normal
this is okay
all righty
I like it when it takes up less than my
whole screen
I mean it's not as immersive but you
know
enable hyper chat there we go beautiful
okay well we still won't have anything
on this OBS screen though uh
sometimes I have chat in the game on the
same screen sometimes sometimes not only
three minutes left ah [\h__\h] okay
Elena had fun with this game too really
did she okay that makes me feel happy
um this game has been around for a bit
and I remember it
uh when crony was playing it and like
when it came out I feel like everybody
was playing it and then I didn't play it
because I thought it's a nice fellow
game probably I'll play it at some point
but everybody was playing it it was like
flavor of the month game
and then crony played it as kind of like
her debut game right you know and it
made sense because the time and all that
like I feel like the style kind of Suits
her too
um you watch so many playoffs really I
feel like like and I know that there is
like some drama and that there's time
going back and all that to fix things uh
to make things work I know that I
watched like tiny bits pieces uh that I
don't really know what's going on but
yeah the place don't [\h__\h] spoiler not
even hint at anything because apparently
that really ruins everything don't don't
please don't
foreign
basically Sims right because we control
this actions I mean even the angles kind
of
oh
whoa
click on an interactive object to use it
okay look at the painting oh
wow
okay more paintings don't care about
them
oh it's pretty I like the game door
locked door locked and they're all
locked
what
I should add to mine is that too quiet
guys
yeah right
flower I know that floor pattern
a little louder can I ah
can I turn it up
probably not
no no sound options okay I'll turn it up
for you guys here
there was a vault
blind show what ah
I'm looking for sound settings okay
[Laughter]
continue
you're really making me try all these
doors
walk the baby even though they're lost
sorry Neighbors
what that that
walked baby
I hear meow not just a baby what [\h__\h]
forgot my keys
ah in the plant oh
my recess fake rock I I collected the
road I should give it a road a rock I
should give it to
to the top to open your inventory aha
fake rock but that's not the key
or is it in the rock
wait
there we go oh
oh okay
I guess no I just need to use them to
get in okay click outside to select that
item to exit okay
it's locked uh-uh click and drag
inventory items
like this
all right oh here it goes here it starts
here
hey babe I'm home
love you so uh probably already that I'm
doing wrong
I I don't know the story though let's
find out
hey there hi Keith
[Music]
I didn't hear you it's like Sims best
nine ever guess who made dessert let me
know when you're in the mood I'm in the
mood now
whoa that looks better
I I I'm in the mood for dessert now
what's the reason for such a special
evening it's a good time to get wowed by
this dessert one second what'd you make
[Music]
the knife is dangerous somebody gonna
use the knife to kill someone
ow
it's fixed babe
someone look at her brother yeah
can I hide in there
go in
close
yeah
like in Thief simulator
hard to see can I see a bit more
oh well I'll probably be fine pause it
yeah
I I have to tell you something babe
I'm coming out of the closet
is a chocolate uh cake thingy what do
you call them
is it my inventory no you should sit
down and eat it
ah
don't read it
I wasn't expecting a storm tonight there
we go sit
thanks is that water in a cup could put
it at least in a glass man
romantic
kind of spooky though the rain
[Music]
apartment though let's eat
yum yum yum
oh her cup became empty wow amazing
[Music]
very romantic yeah
yeah beautiful
oh oh that's probably that's probably
not good
so someone's gonna come in now and kill
us right probably something like that
how how would I even
should we talk while we do this
okay so when is the dessert not just
dessert
I have something to share uh-huh are you
pregnant when is this my birthday just
open it
oh
that from suddenly
wow okay I opened
so
oh yeah that's what I thought
she is prego
I'm pregnant we're having a baby
yay wow yeah wow
so
the footsteps how are you feeling over
there
scary footsteps
um has it already been 12 minutes
what why Dahlia
ah the name
what what does he think it's going to be
great I have no idea how to raise a kid
are you sure
[Music]
um
it's gonna be great you'll make the lady
feel uncertain
you know decent the baby that we make is
gonna be amazing absolutely it won't be
so
so loved yeah
straight
I love you
happy and cut
mmm
yeah we don't need to say any more than
that thank you we're doing it
sweet I have an idea oh that was easy
don't laugh I solved it but do you want
to dance with me on a chocolate eh but
dancing goddammit
ah
dancing really that's so that's that's
cheesy
that's a little cheesy but okay
absolutely I'm a gentleman you lead I
know how it's a relationship
but you know somebody's gonna come in
and kill us right
[Music]
spooky
interesting about this atmosphere I
couldn't see her butt
from above it looks funny
looks like boobs lady
[Music]
I'm spoiler I'm just assuming because I
I know that you know you have to fix
something right I saw some screenshots
also of them on the grounds handcuffed
or so
oh well you know it's not just the two
of us dancing now
I just don't know how that's why oh [\h__\h]
what what shotgun oh I'm with the police
turn around please oh what me yes you
and it's behind your back let's go what
still not real police
I'm here
no that's not police behind your back
please don't help me
take the knife
okay
with another [\h__\h] idiots
this is misunderstanding
that can't be right shut up
you know what this is now where's your
father's watch my father please you must
be thinking of someone else ah no
playing dumb tell me where the watch is
I'm not lying please please don't hurt
us honey tell him he can't help you just
you and me hi what watches and we all go
our separate ways I'm telling you I
don't know about any what sure I'll do
anything bad right I don't know
please
okay
uh torturing me sure okay
[Music]
uh what the [\h__\h]
hey
oh God
he remember Europe what just happened
although only I remember because if he
remembers couldn't he call actual police
down maybe he'll get some help oh maybe
I mean maybe that's really police hi
what the [\h__\h]
but will she believed that I don't mean
so he remembers
I don't think we should talk about what
he remembers because you know how would
she why would she believe it
um let's ask about the past oh
ask Kyle that's such a random thing to
ask you see your significant other the
first time
and then in the evening and then you ask
how did your father die that's so random
but all of this is really random That's
So Random it's too direct but okay
how'd your father die so Random
well that's a fun conversation topic
right
he had a heart attack really it was
awful
I don't wanna even ask that I don't
doubt my wife yet
I'm still with her on this
um
did you ever own a pocket watch pocket
watch
no not that I remember
can you first try this very valuable at
least like after the first talking about
time the cop comes in is it possible to
first try it in the second try
because that's I see that as the first
try
no is it literally impossible like it
wanted to do it at least a couple times
you need a lot of info okay
would be boring if it was solvable in 12
minutes right
uh what did you just say
um and did you say something about the
pocket watch where'd you hide the watch
stop with that
you kill your father
excuse me uh no
that's a fun question though
I know I know it's so rude like [\h__\h]
that
ah you've been lying to me all this time
what about your past about your father
what we need information you're talking
about we need information
um can I even go into the other rooms
imagine if I was murdered
[Music]
in the next few minutes a Gob is going
to knock on a door what are you talking
about trust me bro I I saw it in my
imagination yeah trust me I'm very
trustworthy right now do not open the
door come on it could be anyone
do you have a hole there that you can
look for and also he even announced
himself when he was knocking I think
right so don't open when you hear that
okay just don't open
oh yeah leaving apartment that would be
isn't that the most genius the best
the best solution come on let's just
leave before he shows up come on are you
that scared of my cooking he's gonna
hurt us
[\h__\h] that's just a dessert
and baking is easier than cooking
I'm asking you please just let's go come
downstairs you won't huh because all
that programmed is this room huh I'm not
going downstairs of course not um
then I guess I'll let you cook
um
he's gonna accuse you of killing
killing what
we gotta give it to her straight
you're crazy dude
this is no I'm serious please don't open
that door at least we don't have time to
eat okay that's what I know
what if I kill the cop with the knife um
okay whatever she's stupid
um
I'll leave the conversation I'll take
the knife
I'm ready
I like extra locket
closet oh yeah I should hide here that's
also an idea but it's not gonna go
anywhere I suppose can I use a toilet
I'm nervous
but I'm nervous I gotta do the nervous
pee
oh he doesn't use it
can I not use it
the footsteps
the bathroom doors don't have the picky
holes I guess [\h__\h] okay I'm ready I have
a knife
kill him
what is this one
oh
[Music]
small apartment but I like it it's cozy
I like small apartments
and they look out the windows see
Windows getting closer well the cop is
also getting closer
oh maybe there's something here pocket
watch
oh [\h__\h] it's so dark wait I can turn on
the light can I not
yeah
gotta get that fixed before one of us
gets really good
of course there's no pocket watch but
damn wait you two are able to store all
your belong like clothes and all that in
that one [\h__\h]
thingy hey what the [\h__\h] what's that
sound
maybe in the ventilation code
check the ventilation Chris that's cool
just my hands
[\h__\h] how about the knife
what do you mean what flower
flower
no don't lay on the bed I was gonna make
you ah
[Music]
oh
it's like a [\h__\h] minute until he
would have come probably
oh let's kill him that's him isn't it
yeah that's what I told you [\h__\h] just
let's stay quiet
open the door
this can't be
Champion don't open the door I'm with
the police
what me what you dance behind your back
let's go hold scale
how do I use
oh wait
oh
[Music]
ding
maybe could I would work better if I
backstab him is that possible I still
think I should pick up the knife oh baby
there's maybe an encountered thingy can
I open those the drawer no
there's something in here
fuse no okay let's talk tell me more
[\h__\h]
no no I didn't hear you come in and it's
saved our lives
forever shut up
shut up
oh I I don't know
yeah yeah
talk to me talk to me
[\h__\h] talk
okay
[Music]
um
is it the same questions
okay I can't ask these anymore I guess
or I out asked them but maybe the watch
so I know you have a watch I just
watch what are you talking about
ask aggressively
babe stop lying to me where's the watch
you want to watch your tone Tony what
before you hit it oh [\h__\h] off hey we're
done here
I mean this apartment is really small
like there's not many places to look
in the next few minutes a cop is going
to knock on a door what are you talking
about trust me
uh look I can't explain right now just
trust me and don't open the door don't
open the door please please don't open
it please don't open the door I won't
oh
wait this is somebody convinced her for
real for real it's not open the door
but wait how did he get in last time
didn't he uh open the door himself I
don't think we opened it
[Music]
um
I'm stuck in a Time Loop so there's a
cop and a time yes yes geez yeah
nobody's ever gonna believe that proof
the day is restarting ah I can tell her
I know that she's gonna tell me she's uh
Prego and that she's gonna give me a
jumper of the baby that says Dahlia I'll
prove it
allow me
uh let's see don't need an item
it's probably about the chair I think
it's underneath it right yeah uh nothing
I guess none okay good talk no
[Music]
it's an under like what wait no um
a point on her belly what is it
um
let's see you wait what is it
[Laughter]
yo it's yo it's yum where did you get
the gift from
what about the chair you just said that
let's see
[Applause]
well
ah if you can prove it I mean it'd be
kind of cool
oh shut up
no come open again
well
um
no come on I want to see a miracle
that's not it
now
impress me Nostradamus
stink
what about the sink about it I'm not
sure
why don't you just bring it up
the event what about it yeah uh nothing
I'm so stupid good talk yeah we'll just
die then let's see yeah the lightning
but didn't I already make it go off in
this nah not in this one
I mean I'll prove you
we're about to switch
the light switch in the bedroom
something's really wrong with wiring
don't we already know that no kidding
you really got to fix that thing any
other suggestions let's see oh I didn't
know that I'm waiting
maybe she's hiding it in the closet
the
presents okay I'm waiting
um
[Music]
oh
what do you got your phone well uh your
oh your phone what about it
cool your phone see
that's a loser okay can we just then
wait I don't know
great shut up
just show me again where you got the
present from
the book out of her ass of course you're
gonna pull the present out of your ass
as well
let's talk later [\h__\h] it
I'm going to investigate
in the medicine cabinet
sleeping pills living the same day yeah
that's what I'm saying
what could I use those for why does it
why does it give me the possibility to
pick those up that must be a reason for
it
oh oh behind
[\h__\h] police open up
is that him yeah
don't tell him I'm in here I don't want
to die
you deal with that [\h__\h] if you want it's
your problem
open I guess
do you come on
okay
he'll probably open the closet door
anyway me yes
we'll point out that I'm in here
don't say anything oh hey
hey
ow
that's help me you come help me
well who come help you so
someone is here
okay next time I tell her don't write me
out this promise
[\h__\h] what do I do look I maybe while
he's looking for me I could do something
don't have to handcuff me we can talk
this out we still have the knife yeah
you're making mistakes let's go oh yeah
cause I guess they also anticipate his
reactions
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] hell oh my God
I'll be out in a second
I don't have a second
wife
it's the same day I know this sounds
weird but the day's repeating itself
like I haven't figured out how it all
works yet but for example if I get beat
up I go back to the start of the evening
what do you mean beat up who's beating
you up is he's
he's not important I'm just I'm not
trying to stress you out I'm just trying
to give you an example wow great choice
for example
um I'm not stressed at all now
[Music]
me
no I still don't know what to prove it
with
um
[Music]
I could I could say I know what she's
making for Desert the desert dessert
let's see because I I would shouldn't
know yet right
here I know you're making this for me
what did you close it the dessert I knew
you made my favorite I told you this
morning
I didn't know you told me exactly
Nostradamus to guess I'd make your
favorite right yeah yeah let's see good
try though good try she reacted to it
um
let's see
um well I give up I'll check your phone
on my own what is it
you know what for great listen
just let me know when you're up for it
not not up for it
and better things to do
oh shh
I I like this game so far I wasn't
expecting a storm tonight what
did he take it okay good so what
I like it called uh
hello does this work
emergency services oh oh
I mean
tell them your wife is a murderer
[Music]
um yeah I mean I mean I think but how
then I have to explain them why I know
that the cop is coming to kill me
if I had
um proof there's somebody breaking into
my apartment he's got a gun and he's
gonna kill me and my one in the unit
right now we'll get to a safe place oh
for real how did they get here he's
almost inside they should be there in 15
minutes we can't wait 15 minutes sir
officers will be there as soon as
possible get to a safe place
God save
this service is [\h__\h] can I
um
why are you in the closet
hiding because I'm scared I'll try to
knife again when adapt uh stab the
person
okay let's have the [\h__\h] dessert
no
um
time for dessert just give me
no not one second hurry up hurry up
I mean
I gotta get this fixed babe someone's
someone wants it hurt let me look at
where are you getting you just move it
to yourself sure
I checked in there before
um
the speedo is actually 14 minutes
ironically wait can you really extend it
um no okay okay no it's okay
um
I know now you got it from there
I mean there weren't many other options
so
yeah yeah yeah
hurry hurry hurry hurry with the curry
I don't think we have time for this
you eat that [\h__\h] I don't care
lock the door
no no no no no
wait look
huh see I clicked on the door before I
didn't realize
I think he's coming
I think
honey yeah
you really like that color
I like small places
I'll get it
[\h__\h]
did I not explain to her good enough
what's the place turn around please what
baby look at me
you don't get to talk wait who are you
jump out of there what is this [\h__\h]
warned you
can't sleep
[Music]
no
okay I need to tell her for rolly but
first
um oh God okay so we need to tell her
that I know uh something and we need to
tell her even about this and that you
know another many things to tell oh okay
okay
hi let's talk
days are starting leaving over and over
been there
um I approve it yeah great let's see you
okay
let's see
look look look look
in here
in the drawer
that's why you got the gift from there
it is
didn't think I would I could read your
[\h__\h] mind huh
look look it's clearly an open but I
know there were baby clothes exactly
bought them today
how could you know wow kind of freaking
me out but do you believe me now I
I'm meeting there I thank God all right
let me try and prove something else
something else
do I know something else
I mean the dessert but she told me about
the dessert
the light Maybe
switch the light switch in the bedroom
something's really wrong
you really gotta fix that thing any oh
that the storm is coming let's see
because it's not raining yet oh what is
this Mouse oh uh well how do I tell
seconds we're gonna hear thunder yeah
forecast is clear listen yeah I know
wait and see
oh wow cool stuff I'm drawing
I'm drawing look at that
there you go
uh-huh okay
okay I think I
believe you wonderful we got her there
speed running it you need to sit down
okay
um so next this is crazy
it's not how I thought this okay no time
for that
um
now that you believe me let's tell you
about the club
yeah their cop he's gonna accuse you of
killing your father what
my dad died of a heart attack I
should do that right away crazy talk
he's lying
just don't open the door okay that's not
gonna solve the [\h__\h] problem is that
uh let's talk later
this is not how I thought this night was
gonna go
let's not waste of time
um
are you open to telling me more
babe stop lying to me
where's the watch you want to watch your
tone tone me please where you hit it oh
[\h__\h] off hey we're done here
just trying to help I'm just trying to
help
but yeah I don't think I'm getting any
more out of these questions am I
oh should we dance
this is not grayed out yet at least
the dessert probably don't talk later
I'll take this no uh time Luke oh you
wanna talk
I have no idea how to react to that
well
I don't know either I'm gonna hide in
the closet
so are you like gonna learn piano or
something what the [\h__\h] would I guess
you've got the time
what Oh you mean by time looping I have
time to learn a piano
no it's a very specific time Loop you're
acting really strange today I don't know
Public's at him for Groundhog Day
I told her right I told her
it is is that him yes can I answer this
too do we open the door what did they
say no wait for him to leave yeah
open the door
yeah but you don't show me where it is
can you make him leave
no
I have a warrant open up look
look at this go away
open the door now or I'll kick it down
no wait you know what he wants yeah
yeah but um
should I give him the present
you're watching can you make him leave
what do you mean Megan
[Music]
with my place turn around please
what me yes you don't dance behind your
back still
his own town
stop
[Music]
help me will you come help me
well who come help you oh
someone is here
this is a mistake
babe will you tell him should I this
misunderstood I wonder if I can
Blindside him a little bit
um look I I don't know
don't have to handcuff me we can talk
this out
you're making a mistake this is
do this thinking he's thinking
please listen oh this is more
complicated than you think
well
well there's no
there's not for me please
I barely see it but I think I'm gonna
lose anyway if you struggled really hard
though good job
I think we struggled better than before
now I don't want to tell the cops I want
to find some info on the phone but can
you only
gotta find another way yeah okay another
way sleeping pills how about we throw
[\h__\h] ton of sleeping pills into ah man
ah okay let's lock the door
gives us time right
um
all right uh
and I can prove it every time
the founder two seconds with your
thunder I know the forecast said that it
was going to be clear but just wait and
listen sure
not for real for real
is the final gonna come earlier though
because less than a minute it it doesn't
it doesn't you know while you do that
can I do this too
cake of the sleeping pill can you do
that
under first okay wow why you're so
strategic man
maybe that's how you should do it yeah
okay present first can I redo I should
do I should do present first
because we gotta wait for the Thunder
we could use the rain
wait a second girl
I'm just gonna hide here from the
Thunder because I'm scared of the
Thunder
ah walk out the front door to reset the
time nice okay I'll try to find out
something within this one too
[Music]
there we go
yeah I told you wow
that was spooky
how did you do that you see I'm in a
Time Loop you believe me now I mean
it was definitely something but
I'm gonna need a little more than that
to swallow the whole story to you oh
what if I make her swallow those the
sleeping pills by putting them into the
cake but how does that help us
Maybe
then hide her sleeping in in the in the
closet
oh my God am I a genius
am I a genius
but
um
then I don't think I care about proving
this [\h__\h] to her you know what forget it
great listen I prepared some stuff for
tonight just let me know when you're up
let me ask
okay thanks
try finding the watch is there really
want to look everywhere
uh I mean the vent but like
wait what no no no no no no no we don't
care about that uh wait sleeping pills
are in here
[Music]
take those okay
genius
a genius
wait I came up with that idea by myself
I'm a genius
what did she oh add this she does not
noticing right these pills are huge I
should dissolve them
seems like
seems like a thing that I can actually
do so ah
dissolve
could you just move it to your side no
can't put them like will she see it so
maybe I should hide do it elsewhere
she's making her own glass wait
um
and now
I just give her that to drink
okay
sneaky
um
can I give it to her here you want some
water you should hydrate
who's this there's no thirsty anymore
but thanks
oh
such a genius let's look there must be
there must be it the watch then
somewhere maybe behind a painting well
how tacky
you can't move it
um
but why is the knife not good enough to
open a vent yeah
surely it's an event
[Music]
I'm sure I didn't check the chair I
guess
okay I can only sit in it
funny thing is that dude never checked
this room yeah
um
don't know why
[Music]
I wait ah wait if I do it like this I
didn't realize that
yeah because there's literally nothing
else oh there's someone coming already
check the grade yeah
you sure you don't see anything there
[\h__\h] police open up
and tell her
I'm with the police yeah I know there's
another event me yes you and it's behind
your back let's go
[Music]
what is going on
help me will you come help me
I still don't know like even with my
idea of making her sleep how that would
help but since it's a possibility police
yeah I mean just hiding her and then
saying oh she's not home come back
tomorrow so
look I I don't know
don't handcuff me we can talk this out
hi you're making mistakes
oh
I can talk to him I am innocent just
take my wife I didn't do anything I'll
show you you can't do this shut up and
don't move I'll deal with you in a
minute please
don't move no
all right all right easy peace
yeah whatever it's okay
we'll do
that
the sleeping pill face under arrest for
your father's murder eight years ago
no no no that can't be my [\h__\h] one
okay
babe
[Music]
oh
hey somebody else see what you're doing
to me remembrance
[\h__\h] well no calm down lock the door
lock door save us some time
um I should take both mugs so she
doesn't take the other one or so
[Music]
okay I'm getting the
getting the medicine I'm such a genius
how's she looking at me
stop kissing me I didn't hear you come
in best night ever guests who made
dessert yeah yeah I know
um I'm sorry thanks that sounds great
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm nice don't worry
um right can I put put those this water
in there too
throw it all in here
saving time
oh I'm such a genius
all right let's feed her the pills
ah
oopsie let's talk later
oh here muggle with pills drink it
water
oh yeah thanks let's go we're on a round
get sleepy quick
sleep slip slip
what else could we do
um the other ones no this is this one
just don't
she mind if I do this
what are you doing oh my God
isn't there is it broken yeah now it is
gross in there yeah
I'm tired all of a sudden okay good oh
I'm just gonna lie down for a second
um we'll talk later yeah lie down
and then I'll carry you into the closet
or throw you out the window which would
be probably most ideal surely there's a
dumpster that can
oh
okay baby
those pills are strong she's gonna be
out for a while and I pulled her in my
inventory
what what if I just kill her first then
eh I can't
spell okay
her Adams oh
peace
well but when I use those keys for
and someone stopped
to test for
I already locked the door the first
thing I did uh was locking the door are
you not watching the Stream
phone help me
um here
was anything missing or out of place the
apartment looked the same to me hmm
hey babe I forgot to kiss again I know
I'm can I get a spare and I didn't know
tree just got to work you're feeling
better just saying puking sucks when you
make it look sexy as hell it's not
that's not useful it's not useful
it's not useful
mmm
you've been calling 9-1-1
oh man
I don't want to take it
what if I set everything on fire
once we're set the apartment on fire
um
the light look look look look faster
there's nothing
okay take your phone back
uh
yeah the other one the other one
Whatever even if we die even if we die I
just need to I just need to I just need
to find out uh wait the event wasn't in
here
read the book oh please do not thank you
but this is the one game where I don't
want you guys to back seat me too much
not so easy unless I ask for help you
know
do it what why do you not want to do it
ah because it's still
um
we still have a little bit of time
[Music]
okay nothing there read the book
huh
it is only by forgetting that we ever
really dropped the threat of Time come
on I never approach the experiences of
living in the present moment have you
heard faster
can I read more
oh
it is only by forgetting that we ever
really dropped the threat of time a
warrant and approach the experiences of
living in the present moment that's very
deep and cool but open the door now or
I'll kick it down close door
I surprised him with a knife
be ready West Park
you ready be ready
book only has freedom in front of it
I should hide
it's too late now
would that help ah at least you would ah
yeah
she wouldn't tell him then I wish I was
small enough for the hello
police
um come on out
okay
but then I mean still bad ending
[Music]
let's go
come on
why don't you just stab him in the eyes
so why don't you learn
ah Jesus [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay no problem we
learned something
[\h__\h] we learned something
that's important
[Music]
no no no no I could start by filling in
with water here I guess if I really need
all that time
[Music]
hi no no no no no no no no no no no
not now okay
rude
wow he's really not wasting time I like
it I like it he understands the
situation you know
and I know by now the knife makes no
sense but I still take it I'll still
take it I want at least a chance
oh I
[Music]
oh I'm sure give me the number uh but
besides that
how about you drink this water
oh yeah thanks I was about to grab some
what
okay what was the agent ball that didn't
even like look at that go sleep
what else could I do that would be
useful
maybe the spoon would help
sleepy time
yes I locked the door
oh I'm just gonna lie down for a sec
we'll talk later
yeah okay
let me open the door
it'll be a lot of waiting I think
okay okay
um
I could even open the door make it easy
for him to enter that door
um well I'll take her belongings though
I guess just because
there we go yeah
lights out
where's it no it was just uh
turn off the candles
okay yeah just put them in your pocket
you could have just gone
at them but no
uh the clothes
I don't know why I would call the cops
still but okay
we can try again
I know the number
emergency service
maybe they come faster if she's
unconscious but um
I mean how is that more important than
because they actually believed me about
the cop story
but like how is that more important
that I don't think they would come
faster
um ambulance gets her faster really uh I
drugged my wife and she's not waking up
so
sleeping pillows I gave her way too many
sleeping pills if she regains
consciousness
and ambulance is on
15 minutes that's not what if she
doesn't have 15 minutes
the nearest hospital no no send an
ambulance thank you
hmm
of course everything takes too much time
all right we'll wait and see what
happens
now that he can't
look at wait yeah
it's funny that he knows I just want to
wait I didn't do anything
okay
better than the UK these days I honestly
don't know what's normal
um I feel like in some cases they come
under 10 minutes open the door
hurt cases where they arrive pretty fast
um
I have a warrant faster if you unlock
the door yeah but I don't really wanna
oh but it's not weird open the door now
or I'll kick it down I mean there's
someone who why do they even turn off
the lights like I don't get that either
because she's there
but but but you know if I
what if I put he should put the sofa in
front of the door
and all kinds of furniture that will
save us even more time
and then
maybe we get the 15 minutes
what do you mean what the hi
[\h__\h] light switch
big Kusa
ma'am
interesting it
what
why is he checking the other rooms
what what
does he not recognize us hurdle
[Music]
don't open the closet please
ah looking for the watch
don't do it okay
but
I'm I'm just okay you're under arrest
what don't move
I don't really know what I learned from
this
nothing really what happened to her uh I
need to talk to her she's got an old
watch fancy she doesn't know anything
about it
[Music]
um
I don't know I don't know anything about
a watch sure you don't
where is it
I really don't know I would like to know
too if I knew I would give it to you
I swear I don't know anything about any
watch well
then I guess I don't need you [\h__\h]
don't kill me please
should we do this again just to ask why
for silencer beautiful [\h__\h] you
okay
okay don't worry I got this down
[Music]
[Applause]
came from the cake maybe the watch is in
the cake
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off no no lock it already
I don't think I did rude but I guess we
don't need to lock it huh
right
[Music]
why would why would it be in the cake no
no no no no no no no no that's stupid
he was gonna eat it
okay
um
use Mark to spill water on the light
switch what
well I'll give it a water
oh yeah thanks in for the chocolate cake
true
but that type of chocolate cake I'm
really not impressed by
I don't think it's
[Music]
um
that's nice
ah wait what what now we gotta clean
that closet okay
is it even worth still talking to her
pirate all of a sudden maybe next run oh
I'm just gonna lie down for a sec okay
we'll talk later okay
happy do people
let me in
let me just take your things I wonder if
that
sheesh baby
it's kind of sleeping pills or nose man
really strong I guess I really pulled in
a lot huh
well
um
wife's got cake
okay uh
switches off
[Music]
um
I'll take the knife too
maybe I should do us all a favor and
just
just kill her then nobody can even know
where the watch is because she's dead
oh well
try hide somewhere else there is nowhere
else also so he opens all the doors and
we want to talk to him anyway
um
yeah I can try extracting more info but
it seems kind enough well let's ask him
first he might tell us something about
the watch that we can then ask her about
like prove her that we know more about
the watch then she might be less
reluctant to tell us about it although I
gotta be honest though it really seems
like she doesn't know come on I know
you're home open the door she seems
to me is dead by the way
what the
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] light switch your back chat
welcome back
um I don't need to wait in the closet
okay well done hi hi
don't [\h__\h] Hey listen
uh should I asked us wait wait wait wait
wait wait what is it that we're being
accused of exactly quiet I'll deal with
you in a minute okay you run for a rest
don't move that wasn't the minute
let me ask Phil please
oh
can I ask now what happened to her
I need to talk to her she's got an old
watch fancy know anything about it
why why do you even want the watch
because I do where is it that's not a
good reason how do you know she still
has the one
what makes you think that she still has
the watch that thing is worth an awful
lot if she's so that we know where is it
well that really doesn't help me
ah I don't think I really gained
knowledge
hmm
I don't know anything about a watch we
sure you don't where is it
um I swear
I don't know anything about any watch
well
then I guess we got what we need I'm not
our patience we know it's expensive yeah
okay I mean I would have liked snow a
bit more than that ended already
I strangle strangle strangle
oh
[Music]
leave conversation it's getting easier
okay uh wait wait a second chocolate
chocolate chocolate
don't want to lose time on the chocolate
Okay do I still want to prepare the
concoction
[Music]
um
oh
actually a good idea because she doesn't
hear me coming in
and I have a little bit of time
I could go into the closet but that's
not I don't think we should do that now
um
we first want to know even more
let's see how much we can get out of
here
[Music]
we'll do that next round maybe if we
need to
hey there hi
[Music]
um
well in that case
if we want to know more about the watch
do we also want to prove her again
that we know
we probably have to
do him
um
she talks more right okay
and I can prove it
right
and uh we'll start ah [\h__\h] I'm telling
you the day is restarting let me prove
it again with this yes
let's see let me start with the present
because for the other one we have band
my Paradigm what
every time
the other thing we had to wait endlessly
this present look look it's clearly an
open but I know there were baby clothes
inside I just bought them today
if you know
I mean
okay I'm impressed it's all right I know
you need more give me a sec
few seconds we'll hear thunder I know
you need more okay I really like this
game
he's he's got no time man to [\h__\h] around
come on
three two one it's gonna start now
awkward silence yeah
I better wait for the Thunder first I
never realized I could click on the
radio before I tried to hover over it
and it didn't show okay
okay I think I
I believe you there we go down
I mean if you think about it I think
it's quite nice of her to believe me
about a [\h__\h] time loop with these two
things
I mean
yeah that's pretty impressive but
time Loops like would you believe it
hmm
nah
I mean the Thunder is pretty random the
present is impressive the Thunder
doesn't really you know
this is crazy you trust the person yeah
I thought this night was gonna go
okay uh let's talk
um
in the next few minutes a cop is going
to be at the door what does he want
he wants uh the watch but
um yeah that cop he's gonna accuse you
of killing your father what
my dad died of a heart attack are you
sure it's a crazy talk
he's lying okay that sounded like a lie
that uh
okay
um
no
okay babe stop lying to me there's
nothing new where's the watch you want
to watch your tone Tony please
yeah maybe we can eat things that wasn't
grayed out yet so maybe we should
continue that but I don't think she
wants that now
you've been lying to me all this time
what about your past about your father
what
I don't know what you're talking about
what okay the more I hear what she says
Ah there's something new the more I feel
like she might indeed be lying what
about your father's murder
what is this
my father died of a heart attack [\h__\h]
I don't want to talk about this
um we have to talk about it though I
know the truth the truth about the watch
your father what is this
all these accusations
done talking about this no no no we're
not done
hey
your father died sudden tone switch
that's a fun conversation topic we
already no that doesn't matter what we
already talked about but okay she's calm
again I guess did you kill your father
excuse me I don't have time
fun question though that'd be funny
okay did you murder your father
what the [\h__\h] kind of question is that
is this some kind of mind game
I kill him I can ask again and again and
again
what if I actually try them
I know I keep
it sounds ridiculous but what if I
really try I might tell me did you
murder eventually
of course not
you're scaring me and now all these
questions
by the way [\h__\h] up time Loop stuff oh
I need to get some air
I'll be back
oh
it's something we did something guys
come back to me come on come on
come on what if I unable hyperchat I see
you again
okay nice nice hi
we did something
hmm
poker man you are just all classy shut
up just go it's for your safety and I
guess my safety what do I do go faster
do I have to do that every time though
oh
I hope she's not gonna meet the cop on
the way what do I do
maybe I hide too
then for real you must know
it might be too late
excuse me ma'am sorry no will you follow
me to your apartment I'm with the police
wait
no
make noise and I'll break you off back
inside now what she has the keys
she does have the keys though
foreign
hold still
ow stop I'll come with you how can I
make her leave and take her keys
help me will you come help me
I will come help you my friends
behind your back don't move oh man
this is misunderstanding
oh
you're making hide in the shower hmm
you're under arrest for your father's
murder eight years ago
murderer you had to say that twice
because it's important no that can't be
right shut up
you know what this is now Now where's
your father again Mike Bob please must
be thinking of someone else ah no
playing dumb tell me where the watch is
I'm not lying
who can't help you exactly
do you wear the watch is and we are I'm
not intervening I
okay
no no please don't go for me what what
did I do I'm torturing again to make her
talk
just just kill him what he's in
wow all right it's getting easier
the watch is in the
it sounds like it should be in the
apartment right okay uh I won't go
looking for it just yet what if I hide
in the closet no for real and maybe
maybe she'll actually for some reason
take it out
we want to see how that goes
foreign
I am not here we will observe
maybe she'll take it
so we know where it like is
maybe we'll give us a new exploration
option
I want to watch her
why'd you make me wait
[Music]
no
no just skip holy open up but she still
doesn't know that I'm here
she also will open the door
so she can't read on me right what's the
place turn around please she can me yes
you hands behind your back let's go this
might still be interesting
doesn't have anyone to torture but then
will she talk if there's no one to
torture her because she didn't talk
until I was tortured this
I I don't know you don't think of me we
can talk about this we will
okay
I don't know why
I am not who you're looking for this
anyone else it's a mistake I'm not here
stop looking
please don't hurt me I'm not here anyone
else here
no no husband boyfriend please don't
please don't open my husband
he's at work he's at work he'll be here
any second okay good good good all right
nice
eight years ago your father a Gun Ring
of the Bells why are you asking
only question is how much you make me
hurt you before
I I don't know about anyone
see how creative I can get help
yourself
knew this would happen there's no
Cavalry I am like what the buses watch I
know it's expensive tell me where the
watch is this
anyone
here so then I make her uh sleep you
find it I did and I'll just give the one
to him and we're happy right
are we are we gonna be just happy
[Music]
well
but he still kills her even though he
has the watch
[Music]
wife dead
what what what sorry what no no no
it'll restart it has to restart wait
okay well that's because you're not
hurting this it's not
it's not really like losing you right in
the in the baby oh [\h__\h]
that's gonna restart I know it will it
it has to ah
I guess I have to kill myself
uh
because they won't restart otherwise
I mean I think
now that he leaves us alone this is an
option
this is an option
go outside does it work this time okay
okay
what the [\h__\h]
are you kidding me
um Okay so
I don't know if I have to do that do I
have to do this wait no let's talk first
let's talk first
thank you
we should talk first
no no
because we have more information rude or
should I just get it
um
okay we should just get it
should I make her sleep too oopsie
will that be useful
oh I forgot to call the landlord about
the light switch am I doing that
tomorrow like where is
where is it
don't I also need the phone
ah okay let's make her sleep uh oh God
how do I look below
where are all the glasses
wait I gave you something just here
or should I or should I take the what if
I take the watch and then confront her
with it though
I don't understand how I get below the
Madison cabinet
[Music]
oh she's leaving too too well she's so
nervous
I don't need this right now I'm out
okay yeah fine I mean then I always
don't have to drug you
so
oh she's it
she's not concerned about the watch
really
there it is okay and now so this was her
father's watch
wait can I change time with this yeah
follow me to your apartment
I'm with the police okay oh
[\h__\h]
um she didn't leave the time
well
thank you what's going on I have a
warrant right here this will go easier
if you cooperate hold still you're out
cooperate I'll cooperate hey you're
hurting me listen wait
here's the pocket watch sir
please don't move
okay
listen
yeah I have it uh no I this is
misunderstood I didn't do anything sure
you didn't shut up and yeah
father's murder eight years ago no no
there we go I know where the watch is I
don't know what haha don't handcuff me
we can talk this out
just take it and leave us alone
do this
did I clear the game
why it needs to be this way I understand
for rolly donkey don't
know
please don't stop
oh my God
I got you all right it's getting easier
laughs
um
um I have I think I have some more ideas
[Music]
yeah I wonder if I can just put the
watch on a table
or
um
out there for him to see it
I can't confront her because she runs
out when I
or I can try that the proving thing
again
and then prove it by showing the watch
[Music]
look
at
I mean like are there still some options
hmm
close the door huh
[Music]
goes ah goes to the bathroom door and
getting the watch
yeah okay but then I guess we're still
not giving it to him though wait so I'll
close the door I'll get the watch
then I will
still drug her
uh
I hopefully I can leave no I can put
them watch in her inventory so she has
it on her
and then I'll hide
[Music]
then if he wants no Witnesses he'll just
kill her but he doesn't know I'm there
and then he'll leave right she'll still
die yeah that's okay
I mean
[Music]
um
are you unraveling the mystery yeah wait
did you ever play this game don't get
spoiled if you didn't
it's really good it's really good you
shouldn't get spoiled
didn't work last time
um
[Music]
well okay we close the door
okay it probably won't be the solution
yet she played it okay it probably won't
be the solution yet but we'll get the
the watch behind closed doors and then
confront her again
[Music]
oh
should I knock lock the door to
okay hi
nice to see you my beautiful Sim wife
you not now okay
rude
all right
let's do this
[\h__\h]
guess who has two thumbs and remember to
pay the electric bill today what you did
I didn't expect that no out out with you
and yeah we can still try something with
the switch I know I know
man imagine having two thumbs and you
guys can't relate huh
do it quietly
thank you
thanks oh 31 months of membership thank
you
um
I
um I'm stuck in a timeline I'll prove it
with the right we should
I prove it
by the launch
let's see
okay wait I'll prove it no just the
normal way I want to see a miracle
ah the light
well okay I mean I still have to watch
then I don't know
even if the Thunder already happened
this present
look look it's clearly an open but I
know there were baby clothes inside I
just
okay I'm impressed right and then
magician
okay let's see
um yeah I'll give you
I'll give you the pocket I found your
watch in the vent
what what
get accused of killing your huh what
what are you even saying the Shadows are
tricky to tell me the truth
where is this coming from I told you
I've all
voter I don't even know where to start
my dad oh wasn't always the man he
wanted to be oh
after I was born my mom was really
focused on me and I guess my dad felt
it doesn't matter
uh he started sleeping with my nanny
it was the start of my mom's spiral
Nothing Was the Same after she died
I blamed him
I mean
it was sort of his fault
and I poked at him a lot we fought
nobody can hurt you like the ones you
love right oh anyway
oh hey
I know that this is hard
but please
I need to know yeah
yeah uh
Christmas Eve uh-huh he had caught me
trying to sneak out and I was so mad
I just poked at him and prodded at him
and he
hit me Jesus Christ anyway I saw it red
of course and
he always had guns around
I grabbed one I think he's coming and
died shot
okay and I just ran uh-huh there we have
it New Year's Eve
Polaroid on the fridge was actually
taking an hour after I got I can use
that as proof I was gonna turn myself in
but it was a new year
a few weeks later you showed up and
wow and things were almost good
before it all ended today
I built my father
never thought I'd say that out loud
peace
talk to me yeah so then
[Music]
well now
okay we'll just maybe with the police if
I don't get the watch we'll be able to
prove it faster yeah
let me look at the picture
look up yeah pull over uh yeah so you
can take defense behind your back please
okay okay
[Music]
I mean oh the watches on hair dude will
you tell me this is a misunderstanding
you're under arrest for your father's
murder eight years ago no how did they
like suddenly know about it though it
can't be shut up
you know what this is now where's your
father's watch I don't want to do this
please ah no playing dumb tell me where
watches I don't want to do this babe are
you he can't help you just you and me
tell me where the watch is and we all go
outside
what do you mean
say another word
and we all go our separate ways please
please just let us go okay
okay [\h__\h] warned you
I don't know
so much
[Music]
all right it's getting easier is it I
guess
I'll take the picture
[Music]
hey there
hi let's talk
not now okay
rude
yeah uh locking the door
let's talk
not now
um do we have to prove it again
stuck in a Time Loop and I can prove it
let's tell the story about the Polaroid
please ah okay we have a shortcut now
look I know how your father died
better it was
cooking out he hit you how how could you
I couldn't right
you told me in a previous loop I what
look I'm on your side on my side oh god
look I couldn't
I didn't know how to tell you talk
faster
talk faster please
talk to me I didn't even need the polo
right huh well you just say yeah
something so then
[Music]
here's how you found out about my dad
yes
and now
we ask questions why don't you lied
about her past past week of blue uh the
details
um
and this this I think we don't really
know yet right
how'd you get the watch not [\h__\h]
watch
it was my mom's her grandfather actually
made it it was gonna pass down to me
well I guess it did didn't it hey after
I shot him I wasn't thinking it was
there and I just grabbed it
I hate that thing so much
but it's all I have left I just pawned
it off
um
I don't care it doesn't matter I forgave
everything all of it all that matters is
that we have each other
that's it moral yeah
wouldn't that be nice yeah but you won't
forget this neither of us you gonna kill
me
things like this just don't get oh he's
gonna take the knife kill me is she
[Music]
um
look we already talked about this but
could you tell me again don't tell me
what happened that night I don't want to
do this please not do this please babe I
need to know
you need to know it was Christmas Eve
yeah
I didn't know that I don't know why it's
not grayed out when I already know the
information
I murdered so there you go yep cool
story you needed to know now you know
you're still here
I'm still with you yeah
for now
uh yeah because soon we'll be killed
um well then this will also result in
the same note
did I
but even if we don't open the door he's
just gonna kick it in
and
ah
that's why she lied about it first you
remind me all this time I'm
yeah
what else could I do work together the
damage to coffee
[Music]
we are God I did I could do that
wouldn't it be why it's an upgrade out
uh
okay
too late now
why'd you do it
I didn't plan it
I never meant to hurt anyone
I'm sorry yeah you're leaving a little
bit too late
I don't want to be here
[Music]
even if she leaves right in the
beginning like as early as she could it
still doesn't seem early enough
foreign
[Music]
this is misunderstanding
look I I don't know
don't have to handcuff me we can talk
this out
what could I you're under arrest for
your father don't [\h__\h] move
look oh I can get up oh wow
okay
um
the switch
okay I don't really understand like
physics and all that so well as you guys
know from my Google play through uh but
okay electricity and water I know that
doesn't mix so well
um so
uh
I what would I look
um
[Music]
I don't I don't know
oh
[Music]
now I'm kind of
don't kiss me
not now okay
do I still do I wanna convince her again
in this run
um
yeah
yeah well
oh it does it every time
oh my God
whoa hey are you okay no
what
man the second time the second time it
does that
okay
so so so so so I do it once
um
no I convinced her that I know
then
I turned the thing on once
uh
when he looks for me
he would go in the room and turn on the
light right
then he gets knocked out but then I'll
have to tell her to not tell him
to that I am there too
uh
oh
ah
that's the only go in there when she's
sleeping
okay so we make her sleep
we lay her down but then she can't help
me killing him that's kind of sad
doing it together would feel like a big
bonding experience don't you think
it was strengthen our marriage
um but okay
I think it's stormed tonight
uh all right but that's that that should
work that must be the solution
uh
can I still go in this run I don't think
so
I think it's too late
hey I finally remembered to put the
spare key on
CE no thanks otherwise I wouldn't have
been able to get in
try it
or should I
go on
okay classes
what's that that couple that commits
crimes
[Music]
we need we need everything
Bonnie and Clyde yeah we can't be Bonnie
and Clyde
do I want to lock the door
wait wait what else are we doing
um
water
[Music]
hey there
I'll turn on the light switch one don't
kiss me
grab pull over too not now okay
rude I don't know why but okay
I'll take that because I feel like I'm
so close
yeah
no uh in here
no go in
we don't have time for your shenanigans
that's not the solution
then I don't know but if this solution
is kind of short game huh but yeah it's
supposed to be 12 minutes so it's
actually a long game way longer than you
told me it would be
water
oh yeah thanks I was about to grab some
should I grab the watch too
no why we're for killing him anyway
should I
um no let me just do it this way first
and then because I don't know you know
that's that's probably
another spoiled just do it
grab it after okay wait wait wait uh
this room
uh will she turn it on when she goes to
sleep
[Music]
tired all of a sudden look at the film
oh I'm just gonna lie down first we'll
talk later yeah
follow me
oh I got the phone in case I really want
to get them no no
okay
do it once
and turn it off
and now
just in case I guess I'll take the
candles
is it safe to hide in here
I think it was before pretty pretty long
here oh light should I turn these off
too
and locking the door I think would
really not change ah the other light is
on oh it doesn't matter does that matter
of time I think stop time
is that light really on or is it still
the window oh it's really on
okay
do you watch the photo
I mean
well now I can't see
New Year's Eve ah eight years ago it's
less than a week after she shot her
father I can't imagine what she must
have been going through
okay cool New Year's Eve eight years ago
okay should work this should work
[Music]
one of the psycho by the way
is that a like a hint
the hand come on I know you're home open
the door how do you know
call it pointer in a German
what the what
is
come
[Music]
yeah all right here's the clap
how we got rid of the body I don't know
but um you know do it think about how
many times he killed you
just do it
that's not enough more more you think
he's dead like that I don't think so
dude
that's what I'm saying
that might be enough
Maybe
[Music]
um
maybe one more take the gut oh
where's the gun
ah I can look at this inventory yet
handcuffs got him
oh what if I leave them like someone
alive and you know
oh interesting
and I'm just asking can I I mean he's
dead now okay let's look at the phone
Dad don't forget to call before the
session okay you always forget another
session
sucks oh no
I'm sorry I was too aggressive
interesting I'm glad you still listening
to me
I killed the father
we need some money uh
I didn't call they said they want to
talk to you about the payments ah
because his daughter has cancer
[Music]
um
thank you so much for being there dad
mom would be proud oh
oh
your cat is past you oh
okay well that's sad
um
but I mean
he's not a good person even now what did
I do
should I get the the pocket watch
because she'll wake up and I I'm I'll
need to explain I suppose
why I did what I did
my dog is dead
may I mean maybe I shouldn't have
stabbed him so much I could have just
handcuffed them at that point waited for
him to wake up
um
yeah eh what are you doing
I didn't open it yet oopsie
yes let's use the wait it's already open
what am I there is it no okay no it
looked open huh I'm so confused
prank called a thought no
no what
in or the phone number of his daughter
and call
next
side quite um
quite the back city
um spoilery okay okay I wouldn't have
done that otherwise I think
but calling the daughter
[\h__\h]
not a chance and hey what
another chance in hey hey
wake up
should I handcuff her so she doesn't
freak out
I don't know
that might make her freak out even more
oh no I can tell her
I saved her you know
oh well
then I guess try to sleep
a knife oh I can make it so that she did
it that won't make any difference
anymore I would trust me
um
well then I'm not just wait I guess
Callie's still here hi Caleb we're
getting closer I'm getting closer
how would I remember this four one three
five five
four one three five five five two one uh
uh zero one nine I mean so I guess I
could warn the daughter to warn her dad
but like what
what
yeah
hello
weird
oh oh [\h__\h] that spooked me I thought
that was her standing up already
yeah well
wake up
can I move him
hmm he's dead he's dead oh
that he is good job you did it
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] just close the door
more business
I'll just wait then
Paul is that and trust me it'll be
hilarious how could that be
alone
do it to be cool
eat the you guys and your stupid ideas
man
that is so mean like look
oh
[Music]
what wait but oh God damn it what God
damn it
[Music]
what I didn't
why
but I mean no but before it was on
hi
only when I got hurt
let
me
[\h__\h] hell ah why
ah
that's not the criteria
maybe the park watch I need to turn the
time back in pocket watch and then I it
will never or
um
hmm
sorry I moved the microphone
[Music]
take the battery wait is this the pocket
watch what I'm looking at right now
take the batteries off that's
interesting
but I mean there are other clocks
right
it is huh
wait wait what should I do next
[Music]
killed them and then we took his things
yeah talk instead of killing
see hi girl I oh you saw me this time
ever yes great I'll let you know when
I'm hungry hey why are we why is he not
telling her that we don't go at the time
um
oh God
okay how do we what uh
mug guess who has two thumbs and I'm
going to pay the electric bill today mug
[Music]
this
are you reading something interesting
honey
about time
about the how it is of the essence
sorry I'm getting confused
I'm getting confused just stop it stop
it
I'm freaking out I don't want to lose
time cronies
crony
okay hi you must drink
you don't wanna see what's gonna happen
oh yeah thanks I was about to grab some
good
[Music]
now
let me grab the while you're while
you're thinking about sleeping soon
I guess I have some time I could do this
afterwards too but
tired you're so tired isn't this open
that's what I'm saying that looks
awesome doesn't it it looks the same
after you opened it
bugged
[Music]
down for a second yeah yeah we'll talk
later
wow this is close
because it's dark
hmm
okay
close one yeah
yeah sleep
and one and two all right
and now uh
think just do the same thing
but
uh this time don't kill him completely
but handcuff him right okay
I'm set I guess I'll turn off the light
so it seems
really realistic I guess
all right
Polaroid is necessary oh we can just
grab it once he's down
that's fast
keep your murderous intent in check
okay we're hiding we're hiding
just just
yeah one step didn't say he was dead yet
I think
should I because even when I handcuff
him when he regains Consciousness he
might be dangerous
I don't know
no stabbing
and come on I know you're home open the
door
um I mean like even with handcuffs like
a guy like him I feel like he could do
something
like knock me with his head what
the [\h__\h]
don't understand how this will help me
but I guess I can show it to her once
she wakes up or so I don't know wait we
should close the door
faster
unconscious very good
who's breathing so loudly
quick quick
scary
it's like a like a jelly
all right all right oh he's already
regaining Consciousness what
listen
okay
where do we what do we even
um
one chance let me go right now
um listen
your daughter
is sick don't you [\h__\h] say another
word I'll help you you can have the
watch and pay for it with the watch I
guess
why do you want the watch
I'm here for your wife let me go no what
why are you trying to hide it now
look I know about the pocket watch
congratulations let me go
wait shut up handcuff my wife too
Maybe
because I don't know what she'll do when
she wakes up like she'll panic and
she'll do something stupid
I don't know man like she killed someone
before
you know
okay okay
you'd kill us for it are you even real
police no [\h__\h] you attacked me you
don't have moral High Ground here
I do if only he knew should I prove time
Loop to him
I should prove the time Loop to him
tell him he'll never win this
because it will just keep on repeating
yeah it broke in
hmm
yeah
10 hours until she wakes up your thing
anyway what are we being accused of
exactly let me go right now you won't
talk I'm a [\h__\h] I was gonna leave you
out of this you were not uh
wait wait
um I would like to just knock him with
overall but I feel like he would just
shoot him if I do that
so should I knife him
show his leg can I do that I just don't
want it to escalate I'm like ah
don't oh God
Jesus Christ stop I'm I'm not fighting
you I hear the baby what do you want
um
about the nanny
what do you know about the nanny who the
nanny the old man had the affair with
what do you know oh yeah and what do you
care about the nanny I don't know I
don't really care
uh
I wonder if we call the police
in the beginning
but it will still end at 12 minutes
right
like in theory we could stall this until
after 12 minutes until 15.
but all of this I already told I would
talk about this
should I eat
cold hmm
show him the photo
leave conversation
look at this look at this picture yeah
cute pic what
what do you want yeah that was stupid
you want to look at the pocket watch
is this the watch you're looking for
[\h__\h] off
talk to me
[\h__\h]
are you dying
stop crying listen up oh I said that ah
try to watch again
okay okay
ah I feel bad
aren't they gonna the neighbor's gonna I
have a daughter I know you have a
daughter
all right I think I failed it I can't
improve this can I
it's nothing to do now
okay we'll just shoot the legs faster
and uh
are you sure I know
um
time to reflect on your action time to
eat dessert if it's not great really it
didn't really see my new information oh
well all right
sorry baby and we're back yes we are
we're doing the same thing because it's
it's I think it's
in the right direction
[Music]
taking the polo Road
even though he had no reaction to it
I
um
not no okay rude
uh
alrighty take the medicine
[Music]
get your blood thirsty no not me
by me
I am innocent as [\h__\h]
I'm a good person I wouldn't hurt anyone
all right I don't have the phone yet
it's so stupid that I can't grab it
without the phone
can I I can't okay I did okay all right
oh wait don't go out yet
I left the water
thank you
now
make our Watson concoction
where are all the glasses I got them
I was just washing them in the bathroom
sink for whatever reason what
yeah thanks I was about to grab some
okay uh
uh take my phone I guess it's not even
my phone I think
[Music]
is it mine
things
I'm so tired all of a sudden
oh I'm just gonna lie down yeah you'll
go do your thing later
we'll talk later indeed
turn on the radio why would I do that
but I'm interested too in the radio
isn't she lying differently than before
okay well
why does she lay different lie
differently
why
does it matter
no we wait I have everything right I
think so
Alex open up
maybe so I can stab her
I guess I always could
mmm
[Music]
come on I know you're home open the door
every time
you guys said there's a big twist so I'm
assuming the twist is gonna kill my lips
okay time
come at least close the door behind you
man
locking it too just in case
confused
um okay
got it got it got it got it got it got
it
now put that on him
almost blocked myself up too
should I already show them now or do we
want the effect you know
of of him really realizing I shot his
leg
what
listen
what are we being accused of exactly let
me go right now
oh you little [\h__\h] just made the biggest
mistake just like me let me go right now
[Music]
why you're here
said let me go right now
son of a [\h__\h] I was gonna leave you out
of this and now you've got this coming
yeah
all right you don't want to end up like
water right you want to kick your legs
right you can keep him maybe I'll think
about it now let's talk Jesus Christ
um
why do you want the watch
I need a dog not my cat yeah I'll say
and I'm gonna hurt you again if you make
me yes come on Brandon what a good time
do you have any idea what that thing is
worth yeah I know now that's what this
is about you'd murderers for money you
really don't know no
your wife her father I know I'm just
distinctive family I ever had you knew
him her father
he taught me everything I know like a
Jedi it was good to me
but no one else was that monster
murdered him oh it's not just uh
not just the watch you knew her father
right yeah
he was good to me
taught me a lot
I owe him this
please I don't think the father would
want that though
um what do you know about the nanny he
had the affair with
who cares it was years ago
I care that's what I'm asking
you stuff exactly you really have no
idea
years ago she murdered a father in Cold
Blood
oh why would you possibly doesn't even
know how they know it was her how was
the father murdered I still loved my
wife
and I don't have time for all these
questions I know the answers to half of
them but okay
what money jealousy a million reasons
you you should ask her but we don't need
the real reason
um
what makes you think she did it of
course she did it same gun same room
it's obvious
same gun same room
yeah man I believe you she confessed to
me
why are you still after her it's been so
long I never stopped looking finally got
a tip pointed me here
who gave you the tip the pocket watch
she stole she tried to sell it and let
us know she did
how did her father die her she shot her
nicely there you go didn't kill him
though and then on New Year's Eve she
came back and finished the job two shots
close range
less wait what no no no that's not true
she told me she ran away on Christmas
Eve but by New Year's
on New Year she was here
she was hundreds of miles away when he
was killed
she was prove it she's a murderer
murderers lie you don't have proof wait
it was someone else it had to have been
look by New Year she wasn't there
anymore sure she wasn't prove it yeah I
wanna no one tied me
what about this
look at this picture I mean there's no
time on the picture is there look at the
date oh there is December 30
th that's that's the day she murdered
him
no no that is the day he was murdered
but she was hundreds of miles away I
don't understand
no [\h__\h] it wasn't her she didn't kill
him
oh but then why would you tell me she
did
huh I'm getting confused here Kelly can
we we ah
well you're a rape but you should know
like you did you Reaper father like do
you have any Deeds that you could tell
me spill it spill it or was it like a
colleague that was at the job
she thought she did
or she's covering up but nah like she
really didn't want to tell me in the
first place
who could have killed her father so who
could have killed her father
I don't know everything points to her
I'm bleeding out [\h__\h] listen up uh [\h__\h]
there's no more info
what I do
well I guess I gotta work with this
information now and get back to waifu
handcuff the leg
ah so it doesn't bleed
Wow first aid amazing sugoi
sorry but good idea
um I can't help you I can't help you
unless I don't know maybe I can turn
back time If I Could Turn Back Time
is that what was that mean
it's a shooting thing
okay listen up
what's an order is it a shooting thing
ah
he wants to die
uh
uh okay
yeah
your daughter
don't you [\h__\h] say another word
got me loose now maybe I should because
I'm interested what's gonna happen if I
do that stop crying listen up
oh no
I want untied uh
[Music]
okay wait
um but all right now we confront her
take another way she might try to kill
me
it's still a Thruster especially now
we're not making her sleep this time
close it close it close it closer closer
closer
hey there hi let's talk
um
we're probably gonna prove it first
again right
I'm stuck in a Time Loop and I can prove
it right
I would have oh yeah wait we have a
shortcut don't we look I know how your
father died
how he really died I don't know what you
think
he's really really died he hit you
how how could you I couldn't right
you told me in a previous loop I what
look I'm on your side
oh god look I couldn't
no
how to tell you there's nothing to tell
me I guess you didn't do it maybe I did
it
oh you just say something yeah
so then
um
[Music]
why'd you try to sell the watch we
needed the money for the
pregnant
I know I'm I'm sorry
[Music]
of course you do Jesus yeah I don't know
wait
oh
babe no I have questions ask me about it
why did I tell you
baby baby
baby baby I got questions babe
oh come on
[Music]
and we're back should we only get like
one question now who would he listen to
[Music]
what who would who listen to ah you
think that you you want you mean who
would the guy listen to well probably
his daughter
[Music]
okay I got it I got it do I need to make
the call while she's sleeping Maybe
because otherwise
go away go away
not now she'll be like what the [\h__\h] is
going on
what's going on
foreign
[Music]
about the photo still
I still want to talk about that I need
that information first I'm stuck in a
Time Loop and I can prove it
right I want to know what she says about
that look how he really died I don't
know what you think but you better it
was Christmas Eve he caught you sneaking
out he hit you how how could you I
couldn't right you told me in a previous
Loop all right what look I'm on your
side on my side
oh god look no I'm in front of you
I didn't know how to tell you
please
talk to me haha funny right
just say something yeah okay
you didn't kill him what when you shot
him he survived no that kid that can't
be I I saw positive information babe he
didn't die he was going to recover and
somebody else came in and killed him on
New Year's somebody else but it wasn't
you maybe the daughter Polaroid I don't
want the fridge why are you even alive
all this time I need to sit here
probably but like she would really be
really [\h__\h] young
that said you're investor and me too
this is too much
darling
[Music]
oh
wait I want to hear what she says but
eight years I thought yeah
no nothing okay here look at this look
at this look at this
you have to take the picture
why just trust me
what does he know that I don't know
why does why does
what I don't understand that
trust me
why doesn't she have to take the picture
she will show that but why do I have I
don't I don't know that I should do that
yet
mmm
but I feel like that won't go well still
will she try it do we want her to try to
convince him
but that won't go well will it
I thought he was dead
if I had known
yeah all right
sorry this is just don't leave Jesus I
mean I guess even if you leave you're
probably gonna be held up by the guy
anyway so then
who killed him maybe the daughter or me
I don't know
there's a twist
Ed
um
interesting your dad says that my wife
killed her father whatever it is this
isn't funny
don't hang up
stop what do you know about your
situation
and I'm sorry for you the good news
that's it I can't focus on one sorry
what and now that you know it I mean
have me
start fresh
clean slate
uh
and in the next few minutes the cop is
going to be at the door here's how you
found out about my dad yes
the cop says that he was close that's
good when he died this is personal yeah
I messed the loop up okay well we still
can't get info
let's wait for him to arrive now we wait
uh
is that him
yeah but what do we do
[Music]
we open is
keep a good time for the dessert really
hmm
your Nanny what do you remember about
her my Danny
come on I know your homes
name
your father's Affair we're in a
conversation right now oh [\h__\h] I have a
warrant for you wait wait what's going
on wait on the ground I know why you're
here wait stop I have something you need
to see yes we're probably not gonna work
out but do it
I didn't kill anyone look I can
no excuses you have to listen to me
I said nowhere else no I do not
only people I have to listen to are my
daughter and my mother oh and my
mother's dead
now shut up that's enough hold still
no no she she has the picture I think
she was trying to chill in
[Music]
um
Let's help me
what a live
Jesus
all right all right
thank you well I think
okay
um
um we'll call the daughter again try to
not freak her out
um
[Music]
and before I do that I have to let her
know again that I know I think there
were maybe still some questions that I
could ask her to to Unriddle the riddle
unravel the riddle
let's take the knife
I always see the knife you wanna get
backstabbed you know
did crony ever finish this
I put part one on the funnel because I
thought it might take longer than the
stream but we're doing pretty good
let's talk I'm stuck in a Time loop I
completely still watching right
ah so
listen dad not what you think
what are you it was a heart attack she
beat it in like a few hours well it was
Christmas why are you flexing I mean
like that I'm I'm also only at two and a
half hours
how could you I couldn't
you told me in a previous loop I what
but he didn't die when you shot him
exactly he survived somebody else killed
him after you ran away
from the coffee shop I'm pretty sure you
weren't there at the time I know like he
was a lot of people but I'm pretty sure
now
you ready there's more there's more a
man is about to ring the doorbell and
accuse you of murder oh another shortcut
what's close to your father and when
your dad died it really
messed them up
okay
I'll be ready okay and I need to sit
down yeah sit down I'll take the picture
again
this is too much
and now should we call the daughter
right away
the truth he doesn't understand though
he doesn't want to understand
the listen right
right no he will not I know it from
another time Loop
it is for like oh
the shortcut to that yo every second
counts
hello hey hey
don't ramble like that please he is
gonna hurt her what are you talking
about
why would you say you're gonna break her
out
um
[Music]
I don't know what you're talking he
doesn't have the whole story please
could you just tell him to listen to us
please she's making a big mistake you
can help him I mean
fine okay awesome good daughter who
killed him good daughter and while we
wait
I'll talk a bit more what what's new
father's Affair he
God I hate talking about this
I don't know I don't love my mom
but I guess having me make things tough
on the marriage
okay
he wasn't always as good a man as he
wanted to be
I want to know all these things though
[Music]
um
I have time right a little bit how'd
your mom find out about the affair dad
knocked up the news
tough to keep that secret
there were complications
poor woman died second child's birth
my dad God
he wanted to adopt the kid but he could
not do that to my mom when did your mom
say nothing
she just got sick she hated him so much
by the end what did he do nothing he
didn't do [\h__\h] anything
and I didn't until the day she died
I'm I'm confused hmm
okay we'll do the Polaroid let's talk
later
here you have to take the picture I'm
not going to be able to give it to you
later
okay
[Music]
what do you know about your Nanny's
child your brother I guess I honestly
wasn't even sure he existed I think I
overheard stuff about my dad wanting to
adopt him but
no way my mom would have it she hated
the idea of that kid so much
uh
yeah yeah she has a half brother from
The Nanny who had an affair with her dad
uh
and the dad hated the kid what
okay
you know where your brother is now I
have no idea sometimes I wonder if he
was even real my mom was so out of it
and I mean if this kid did exist I'm
sure my dad would have tried to find him
after my mom died
so it's going too fast for me is the kid
maybe the the same kid as the kid that I
just called well I'm confused
so
who could have killed him I mean with
his work he had a lot of enemies it's
not like he was always the easiest guy
to deal with I mean
okay that's nothing new
oh I guess I'll ask this too because
like what do what else
but you
why'd you lie to me all this time I mean
how was I gonna tell you hi nice to meet
you by the way
but you you were so persistent
I guess
what I just wanted to I'm trying to
listen the phone
yeah I guess that's over now
we're in fretton no we didn't Britain
Church's dance
there but she's probably just gonna say
no thank you
it's okay let's talk later if I'd known
he was alive I could have done something
I could have stopped it I guess should I
hide maybe would that help good news
that's the skeleton I'll take care no no
you know it I mean okay is that even
listen he promised his daughter he's
gonna start first listen clean slate
thank you
what do we do
we must listen
is that him let's open the door it's
locked do we open the door yeah we open
the door we need to tell him come on
okay
let's talk oh [\h__\h]
wait wait
please stop I have something you need to
need what did you say
good I didn't kill my father I have
proof sure you do she really does look
at this picture yes yes look at the date
New Year's Eve the day my dad died this
coffee shop is around the corner I
couldn't have killed him I can't be in
two places at once
congratulations no you faked the
photograph how do you fake a Polaroid
listen
I know my father was important to you
I miss him too
I always thought
you weren't there I wasn't there but
then yeah I don't know
but it wasn't me
I'm sorry
I really am wow
my daughter see
she's all I care about she's dying we
can still give him though
in the insurance one
I can't pay for the treatment I'll watch
though
not nearly died before okay
oh I was doing this
thank you for not if you told her ah
what I was really here for she'd never
talk to me again I'm going now wait is
this happy end wait just a second let me
give you
you get the glory lady
[Music]
yeah you need it more than I do yeah she
does
I'm pretty good at finding people
obviously
I'll find out who killed your father
thank you
actually there's one thing that might
help what when I found him he lost a lot
of blood I tried to stop the bleeding
Boomer anyway he was saying something
just the word monster over and over I
always wondered what it meant it's not
the end oh my God you have a brother
your mom's right
she was right all along when my father
and my nanny were having their affair
there was a baby a boy a
pet I knew about the affair but he never
mentioned a child my mother hated him
for it hated the kid too always yelled
at my dad about the monster that's him I
didn't know I'm sorry oh man
I'm fine don't kill him now and for him
thank you I mean
how the police herself
is it over I guess I think it is yeah
now we can go find your brother and move
forward yeah can we
yeah wow
never thought I'd be able anyone would
happen
I thought I'd have to hold that forever
that you listened
it's really here
not going anywhere
man
I really really love you oh really
really
I really love you what you too
no
I don't know I just don't I don't know
either
that's a bakery zero stuff there
well
now
hey there hi
I'm busy
what I didn't hear you come in Morgan
guess who yeah let me know when you're
in there
should we eat and dance
I thought it was done so yeah that would
have been a good ending more or less
I'm stuck in a Time Loop and I can prove
it
right for real though
look how your father died
I know how you
doing uh it was a heart attack
well it wasn't I'm gonna go artists
caught you sneaking up and he hit could
you know that I couldn't
told me in a previous loop I did what
listen he didn't die when you shot him
what are you doing
he survived your brother the one you
always called monster he killed him a
week later yeah I have a [\h__\h] brother
you don't have brother from your
father's Affair he's the one who did it
that Polaroid from the coffee shop it
proves it wasn't you yeah what is going
on
I know
okay you ready there's more yeah
and accuse you of murder what
when your dad died it really messed him
up
one of the brothers the cop I don't know
can that be
I don't know anymore
uh
this is new tell her the cop wants to
watch uh wants to watch her save his
daughter
treatment that's awful
I can't imagine what that's like
find more about the brother being should
I call first
um
I probably should call fish all right I
should still do that I assume let's talk
later one second let me go
this is too much
and I always have to get stupid phone
and some cop guy is coming okay
so we got a shortcut for bumblebee too
to like talk to her faster your dad says
that my wife murdered her father yeah
please he is gonna hurt her what are you
talking out
[Music]
ah
he was thanking me that I didn't really
tell like why but now the game
seems like it wants me to tell her
but all of this has new info
don't what
no no so no let's say first
my wife is Innocent but your dad won't
listen to us I don't know what it's
insane could you just call him and tell
him to listen please he doesn't have the
whole story
all these years
open
yeah my wife is so chatty
all right more about the brother being
the killer brother he's
he's I don't know nobody ever told me
anything about him I don't even know his
name okay what about the nanny I was two
years old I have no idea
I mean
the cop said he knew my father right
right maybe he was there back then
I'm I'm having a hard time following
this at this point
oh
[Music]
um well
care to dance what you want to dance
right now yeah
no not now
um
[Music]
look at that I've lost my appetite you
could try again later understandable
okay but there's nothing else that's new
so let's talk later this is crazy
well did we really gain enough
information to talk to the dude now
brother
to change something
um I didn't think any other family
we'll get straight to the point I guess
I don't know anything about him
[Music]
sure
all right you're hiding I don't need no
more questions to ask maybe it's on the
radio
I mean
good news
secret doing a good job great job thank
you
picture I'm not gonna be able to give it
to you later okay
now that you know it how do you know you
can't give it to her later have me
start fresh
clean I'd be at the right timing
all right all right
I've never
I've got a pastry around the room well
before
no
thank you you're welcome and I said we
can clear this up hey bumblebee all the
pressure taking off of you now what's up
there's a membership gift
what
do you
honey if this doesn't work the next time
we're gonna rat him out
did they threaten you
no pranking no no
no
listen listen oh okay I'll listen to one
behind me he's got a Sweet Soul at his
core the fact that you know he's so
determined to do this [\h__\h] and a very
very convinced about his own opinion but
his daughter he loves her so much that
just her saying this even though she has
no proof
convinces him to to
to listen to us that's sweet
saying okay
okay killed me but what do we do do we
open yeah we open the door
come on I need to tell him you want to
talk okay okay let's talk oh [\h__\h] wait
wait please please wait stop I have
something you need to see
what did you say
you can't react to the game's doorbell
he had a love try
oh
we're getting straight to the point
you're expecting me to believe that I
don't care what you believe the bastard
destroyed everything I loved to
destroyed my mother
called him
he was
Monster what
oh it's just that was the last thing I
heard him say never occurred to me that
it meant
I know my father was important to you I
miss him too but I
I always thought squid scratch you
weren't there that sounded like a spirit
I don't know
but it wasn't me
look I know why it could have been this
beard
can't make us pay for what your daughter
is going through don't take it out on us
sorry really I am
if my daughter knew what I was doing
wouldn't understand
she'd never forgive me I'm going now
wait wait just a second yeah
hinged
here
take the watch
I was asking for me to tell his daughter
I'll look for your brother Hey listen
well he knows that now
how's your daughter doing
steak
[Music]
Mr angry we're being friendly what the
[\h__\h] is you bro well now I'm mad wow
that makes
it
huh I was just trying to I don't know
what
hmm
I thought maybe not now okay me asking I
was out of character what
okay well I don't see a big change so
the only thing I really could
do something as if I
tell the daughter maybe the daughter
knows more
I'm stuck in a timeline
right missing a few Clues only
um
look how your father I know how you
really died what do you do it wasn't it
was Christmas Eve and he hit you how
could you know that I couldn't
I didn't remind him that his daughter
has cancer he didn't die when you shot
him nah not after we were already so
chill and gave him the one you always
called Monster the pocket watch for the
money the half brother he's the one who
did it that Polaroid from the cop it
proves it what is going on I know all
right there's more listen a man is about
to ring the doorbell he's gonna accuse
him but he's actually just
watch will pay for the treatment yeah he
was close to your [\h__\h] yeah
tldr
okay uh
what
here you have to take the picture I'm
not going to be able to give it to you
later
okay
now we call
I guess
no this is too much
hello hey hey your dad says that my wife
wants your phone can you help please he
is gonna hurt us too what are you
talking about okay why would you say
that
your daddy is gonna hurt us he wants to
steal from us so that he can pay for
your treatment what yes no my dad he
wouldn't do that that's not right
what are you talking about just call him
and ask him I will
[Music]
but would he like kill us because we
told his daughter dad would like it that
he she wouldn't like Daddy but would she
this is crazy
we gotta try all the options yeah is
there anything else you need to tell me
nope nope
nope okay let's talk later
well I didn't want to see it but I saw a
hint in the chat
I can't unsee it now I didn't think I
had any other family
what
I don't even know what questions to ask
I guess
I mean somebody said something about the
flower that's it
that's the secret that's the skeleton
and now that you know it I mean it feels
to have me
start fresh
yeah
ah wait do I have to put water on the
flower
and it suddenly blooms like a miracle
I've never been able to see that
wait I don't have a cup so
thank you you have enough time to do
this for listening
okay
well my dad would be so tacky
wouldn't it
move one of the flower
maybe it's a prank
ah here flower water in the flower why
it's kind of cheap and for fluidity was
it a joke
does it not do anything
oh he's here now he'll be mad probably
we'll talk later
oh
honey I think you've got prank calls no
he won't come in now what did they
didn't you
not at all
it's ridiculous
honey that's impossible
of course it's not true
I wouldn't no no you wouldn't hey
I'll do anything oh man
now my wife I won't hurt anyone my wife
won't believe me even now because she's
not coming in and I said he will gonna
come in
I'll be right there
I gave her the pick yeah yeah
um I have a whole routine now okay well
he left [\h__\h]
radio
we left
that's not it
flower
window
chair
share
interesting
well I can be in the shower
I am just grasping straws now
um can I get another funny achievement
if I take the pills
and
this
[Music]
what's that do nothing I think I'm gonna
achieve band man flash to watch No No
One's Gonna be happy because of that
oh my God though he's gone
now we could dance
because seems like she has a new answer
hey you want to dance you haven't asked
me to dance
man okay I was looking forward to it
let's talk later
foreign
okay seems like this run is over
find any new information here maybe it's
in the spoons maybe the answer is in the
spoon
spoon's no good in its own is it good or
something else
maybe the answers in the painting
[Music]
there's an egg
the egg is the answer did you guys do it
was it you guys
[Music]
I think 12 minutes is probably gonna be
over soon but
unless we broke the
Loop
it was you it was a you
welp
but it's pretty big
damn is it really gonna be it
well I
um
lost our money
I'm hungry
I have a chicken Caesar noodle salad
oh he's enjoying it I have a ride in
front of me just a small one
well um
why is it 12 minutes did I break the
loop let's talk later
why is it not ending
and by now I'll sleep until it ends
eh but was the flower just the jork like
for an achievement then then I'm not mad
if it's not actually anything to do with
the story then
then I'm not mad
enough
yeah I give this to you as if it was a
print from me to you
how to turntables uh talk about talk
about this later
I've lost my patience
uh it was a crony joke
I know I know going outside breaks the
loop uh or like redoes the loop but
all right
it's locked oops
[Music]
wait but uh
but yeah you thought that was a solution
huh well it turns out it wasn't and I
really I don't know we'll call the
daughter again I suppose
call her again oopsie
the clue be in the present
interesting
I didn't hear you come in who's the best
and I never guess let me know when
you're yeah I will
stand
don't tell you why I have to stop it
give your wife everything she will know
what to do
what that seems
call her before wife sees you
um
look this is proof you're innocent
suddenly what are you talking about yeah
I don't know
the man told me you killed your father a
man told you
what the [\h__\h] I don't even know how to
say this but look I'm living the same
few minutes over and over and over it's
kind of a shortcut look how your father
died it's not what you think I know how
you really died what are you doing it
was a heart attack no it wasn't it was
Christmas Eve and he hit you how could
you know that I couldn't
you told me in a previous loop I did
what
he didn't die when you shot him make her
happy first survived you mean by dancing
and eating the one you always called
monster he killed him a week later I
have a [\h__\h] brother a half brother
from your father's affair he's the one
who did it that Polaroid from the coffee
shop it proves it wasn't you
all right there's more listen a man is
about to run
but he's actually just here for your
father's pocket watch what his daughter
has towards her if the treatment
he was close to your [\h__\h] yeah
I like the voice doctor all the
insurance company this is too much
do I have that number
and some cop guy is coming hello hey hey
your dad says that my wife wanted her
father please he is gonna hurt him what
are you talking about why would you say
that okay else again
[Music]
listen
I'm trapped in a Time Loop and I can't
figure out right yeah okay you have to
yeah yeah yeah
I was just gonna try it because it
wasn't grayed out but of course I know I
knew
and and we're back in Deans I'll take
the Polaroid I will not tell her this
time for whatever reason I don't see it
oopsie I don't see how that would help
not telling her
[Music]
Cali's still here what did Kelly say
oh there
what is going for This Woman's head
not okay she must be thanking her
husband
[Music]
maybe he's related to The Charmed Ones
because he knows about time
hello hey hey your dad says that my wife
isn't the wife gonna hear this please he
is gonna hurt her what are you talking
about
why would you say that
um
my wife is Innocent but your dad he
won't listen to us I don't know what you
want hey please could you just call him
and tell him to listen he doesn't have
the whole story okay
fine
[Music]
and now not tell her
mom
that's my cat
um
should I ask these questions but then
she kind of knows that I know what are
you talking about I messed up
could you leave the party meow
um
[Music]
I don't know I know they're not grayed
out
man what's wrong
she wants something she wants my pet
pets yeah she's yeah yeah what what are
you telling you are you trying to back
seat me too do you have a smart opinion
you don't seem very smart you know but
you still talkative are you out of
Kibbles is that what it is
missing what what what what what what
the missing info is somewhere else
anyway somewhere else
never mind
somewhere else
foreign
[Music]
keeps on talking to me I wasn't
expecting a storm tonight
[Music]
she's like uh
rubbing against my leg so cute baby
clothes baby clothes was my mother's
name yeah
baby Club
it doesn't really seem like a hint
oh good
you opened it why did you say that name
boy what the hell that was supposed to
be a surprise dummy
wait what
his
um
finally what
finally
talk to her now
should I I'm stuck in a time I guess
we'll start with that again
but now I don't think I have much time
um
[Music]
asking about the baby's name but I don't
have an option
I know about the pocket watch it's an
event
use whatever I have as an option A man
told me you killed your father a man
told you
look I'm living the same few minutes
over and over and over what look how
your father died
I know how you really died what are you
doing it was a heart attack no it wasn't
it was Christmas Eve he caught you
sneaking up and he hit you how could you
know that I couldn't
you told me in a previous loop I did
what listen listen he didn't die when
you shot him what are you doing
survived your brother the one you always
called monster he killed him a week
later
the half brother from your father's
Affair he's the one who did it that
Polaroid from the coffee shop it proves
it wasn't you
I know all right let's go the cop
guy's watch his daughter has cancer and
the watch will pay for treatment
he was just like picking everything off
his list it really hit him hard yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
um
yeah oh this is all old again
let's talk later I'll give you the polo
Rod maybe take the picture I'm not gonna
maybe something when the cop comes and
talks to us wait I didn't call yet did I
did I I didn't call yet
call again
too much
hey sorry I can't talk right now what
leave a message or just text me okay
it's too late to call her tell him the
truth I did
[Music]
really wasn't this this run but I
freaked her out did I not
[Music]
are you sure it's this one this whole
it's I feel like I didn't destroy
I did
she asked me to lose her number yeah
okay so I didn't freak her out
completely
this is crazy all right okay he's
talking to her
honey
I think Minecraft right
did they threaten you
I didn't think I had
can I like any other family use my phone
on no I can put it back but I want to
see more I don't know anything I'll
listen to him but huh
yeah don't worry bumblebee I'll take
care I don't even know what questions to
ask I guess
she loves talking to herself news
that's it such a rambling secret that's
good evening sir let's have the talk
let's talk now
get on the ground oh [\h__\h] please wait
wait wait stop I have something you need
to see what did you say
I didn't kill my father what he had a
love child bastard
killer
you're expecting me to believe that I
don't care what you believe
the bastard destroyed everything I sled
her explained first
she's the watch no I will not monster
that would make me a monster oh it's
just that was the last thing I heard him
say it never occurred to me that it
meant that
listen
I know my father was important to you I
miss him too but I want to eat sit on
the car I always thought
you weren't there I wasn't there I'm not
like I don't even matter anymore man I'm
a side character now
I mean I know why you're doing this I
get it you couldn't possibly you can't
make us pay for what your daughter is
going through don't take it out on us
I'm sick of it
the solution
I mean he's sick of it
surely is she wouldn't understand
never forgive me I'm going now the sad
piano music
you guys are just
here there is no take away
you need it
more than I did we'll wait for that but
I'm scared to leave right away
okay he got the watch I'll look for your
brother I'll start with the nanny go
from there how much do you remember
about her
I it's been a long time do you remember
her name
ah something flowery
Daphne Daisy something like that
I'll let you know when I know I need to
give him the baby clothes wait listen
sure sure so what happens now
you're over no did he know the last time
we had this play out I have no [\h__\h]
eyes
flower yeah [\h__\h] wait but like uh what
what
who did he say had a flowery name
I was like focused on the cake
The Nanny
and the nanny is his mother
which means
her father had
wait he's the brother you see what wait
her father had an affair with a nanny
that has a
um a flowery name which is obviously his
mother now
uh
uh the child that came out of it is her
half brother and that's the [\h__\h]
twist that yeah incest
did I cook sufficiently
am I getting it don't say it's casually
well I mean I'm just trying to make
sense of this
okay
let me get to here
what was this other story
A Game of Thrones wasn't it
um I won't get into it you know
wait uh should I unpack the thing first
that's why you said flower
it wasn't even the flower on top see
that wasn't such a bad spoiler because
in the end I didn't learn anything from
that
okay I did it
right but I killed her why how do I not
remember that I killed what
how does he not is he look this is proof
you're innocent is it pushing his
memories out of his brain or a man told
me you killed your father I'm
how does he not remember
this but look I'm living the same few
minutes
happened the same way
I know how he really died what if you
cannot realize yeah it was a hard
is he gonna kill him it was Christmas
Eve I think it'll die anyway and he hit
you know that I couldn't
no I'm rambling listen he didn't die
what are you doing survive your brother
he killed him a week later he doesn't
realize yes he's pretty witty and
understands pretty fast what's going on
faster than me sometimes
I got it you should get it tuna actually
just
his daughter has cancer
he's close to here
yeah
okay now we gotta call the daughter
[Music]
this is too much
I know right it's [\h__\h] crazy
cop guy is coming my head hello my tummy
hurts yeah it says that my wife murdered
her father can you help please he is
gonna hurt her what are you talking
about why would you say that
because my wife is innocent my wife is
Innocent but your dad he won't listen
and I am mine please could you just call
him and tell me I am not innocent of
murder and I Am Not Innocent of fine
I'll call him the other thing that is
not good all these years I thought okay
um oh I gave her the pull around I
called the daughter I'm ready right I'm
ready
I think I'm ready this is crazy I got
something
I mean always take the knife right
my brother
I take it
I didn't think I had any other family
I'll just I'll take us
[Music]
getting juicy yeah
questions to ask
yes
I mean
good news that's it
that's the secret
it's the skeleton
and now that you know it I mean
feel still me the question is will you
still have me
Clean Slate after you know
why is this happening eight years after
it anyway
I've never been why am I ruining my own
life Justin oh thank you for listening
um
why am I ratting myself out
[Music]
no no
should we flush something again
there he is
hey Bumblebee
what's up
why would I
plug them
what
[Laughter]
honey
you don't want to give him the pocket
watch
keep the money we don't need it oh okay
I'll listen to him we're going to prison
anyway
go to heaven
flash chat
I love you more
you're gonna there we go all right is
that up
sounds so friendly
wait stop I have something you need to
see
what did you say let it play out
it's gonna happen guys you had a love
child bastard the big conclusion
you're expecting me to believe that I
don't care what you believe
the bastard destroyed everything I loved
devoid my mother
called him the monster and he was
monster what
oh it's just it's just like I heard him
say it never occurred to me that it
meant
that wow listen wow I know my father was
important to you I miss him too but well
maybe not I know Kibbles I always
thought no you weren't there I wasn't
there but then I don't know
um but it wasn't me look I know why
you're doing this she's so talkative you
can't make us pay for what your
daughter's going through don't take it
out on us I'm sorry when we're done with
this I give you cables okay
if my daughter knew what I was doing
she wouldn't understand
never forgive me no problem dude
wait just a second
into the Good Feet
[Music]
here and normally I talk to my catch and
cat language you need it more than I do
not English not German
I'll look for your brother
I'll start with the nanny should I just
give it straight go from there let's ask
a question
tell him her brother no we don't want to
do that right
no no never mind all right
not another word out of you wait wait
wait oh
no
I'm scared don't hurt me
the name look at the name is that the
nanny oh the nanny from the old man's
affair
what oh yes Dahlia that's it her name
was why are you saying this this
surprisingly it's funny to you
oh
she was my mother oh
oh they're gonna kill me together
no no no
sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
well
we're going back all the way
many many years back
[Music]
hey come on snap out of it
look I know this is a lot to drop on you
huh but I gotta know that we're on the
same page concerning these feelings
so consider your answer to this question
very careful what do you want with my
daughter
I can't just stop
feeling forward
I love her right
I love her with everything in me I don't
care about your feelings feel however
you feel feelings don't matter what are
you going to do
you
you have a [\h__\h] radioactive you know
radioactive just you existing what
killed my wife well I'm confused your
mother too uh oh you walked my [\h__\h]
daughter
you want to know my answer can I do this
wrong I do
Maybe
she doesn't need to know maybe we can
just be happy what we just keep this
from her
you expect me to stand here and say
nothing while you just just [\h__\h]
dance around like nothing's wrong
what if she gets pregnant
you want me to just keep this secret
from her from my daughter we just
pretend to be happy so is the thing that
you tend to be happy all the time I'm
trying to convince him why he should let
me be with you you loved her you
wouldn't lie to her she deserves better
than you you [\h__\h] idiot
you are so naive so stupid
oh
it was an accident really Oh I thought
it was on purpose
uh
was I supposed should I do I fix this
too
[Music]
are we rewinding that too
we're here
[Music]
how could I forget honey babe are you no
no oh wait oh hey it's me it's me it's
okay it's okay
don't touch me but we tell her it was an
accident stay away but what will you
think if she knows that her brother her
half brother hey
but I knocked myself out it can't be
true
you know
it can't be true what
what now I should call the police on
myself maybe
about 15 minutes
oh man
I returned my cousin
should I
um
should I tell can I tell the daughter
and then daughter tells him
oh man
tell my wife
wow okay okay
hey there hi
so listen
not now okay
rude uh no I need to talk
tell her
I don't know how to say this I've
forgotten a lot of things that
memory
differently what are you talking about
I've heard this um first because I love
these two pieces of information
this one seems a little bit less
like it would upset her I don't know
your name from your father's Affair what
about her her name is Dahlia she was my
mother that your dad found me after your
mother passed it's me I'm your brother
what the [\h__\h] saying babe there's more
it was me I'm the man that killed your
father oh kind of sick [\h__\h] joke it's
not a look his office is filled with
books all the way up to the ceiling and
never forgot how weird that all is yeah
that was weird no no hey here's having
your baby yeah I don't remember
say it's your faults it wasn't my fault
uh I feel like deflecting the the blame
off of me just makes it worse so all my
oh I should have told you
God you're my only family I couldn't
lose you if I could go back I fix this
go back
you could go [\h__\h] back oh he went
back I'm having your child
oh you're sorry that makes it better
[Music]
I could suddenly change my mind
apparently no I I guess I will confess
but I want to confess to a real cop
ideally
there's a cop coming here I'm gonna try
and arrest you what how do you even we
don't have much time look I cannot do
what I've done but I'll clue your name
I'll confess who are you just let me try
to fix this please I ruined everything
but you deserve to have a life you're
disgusting
we'll wait
oh she's crying
do I still get for the polo Road would
you explain her name with that right
there there you go
it doesn't say why anymore
oh she doesn't want though
oh man
should I get the watch
yeah
should I call the dog I should at least
call the daughter right because
otherwise this will go wrong
shut up already we're flashing the wife
wait
what does Kelsey
have you seen aha
don't you bring something like that up
now
no no no
hello hey
hey your dad says don't say you didn't
say it yet what are you talking about
why would you say that
at least you stopped talking
oh should I tell her
that seems um
not good either
[Music]
um
no
yeah I mean it's new but I don't think
um my wife is Innocent but your dad he
won't listen to us I don't know what you
want please could you just call him and
tell him to listen
he doesn't have the whole story okay
oh fine
[Music]
[\h__\h]
man you [\h__\h] up so bad
oh man
should I take the watch will she still
try to give it to him but if I take it
she'd be like why the [\h__\h] did you take
it why is it not there anymore
[Music]
that seems wrong too
should I take it
um
watch it we can't do it
I don't know if I want to take it like
that seems wrong like what am I trying
to do taking it
I can't run guys
I'll take it though oh
what
and I move it
it's going it's going back
slowly is he okay what's going on
no don't reset
huh
[Music]
hey oh there he is
you're back the book
book
I know this is a terrible shock but we
need to be on the same page what about
the page that she was reading his
feelings for my
your sister
look I
this isn't how I wanted to tell you
you deserve both of you deserve better
I uh yeah
all right all right
we're gonna go with the technically
correct thing right
I guess there is a world where I leave
yeah and where she doesn't get to know
why there is no I know
that's the right thing I think thank you
for understanding why it needs to be
this way
this whole
why can't we just be a brother to this
it's not too late now but for what it's
worth
oh man oh I got achievement alone oh
so there's another ending wait is that
the ending and there's another ending if
I chose the other option there wait that
was so sudden
oh credits
oh Hulk okay that is the happy ending
right
happy as in well she gets to live her
life differently and I mean I'll get
over it too like what the hell you got
over eventually
there are a few endings
Willem Dafoe maybe Willem is the foe
and not me
[Music]
how many times most of you have heard
that
um I love the dad
well that's what the ending there was
kind of sudden just looking at the at
the watch and then just turned back and
I
I change my mind
after telling her directly once
took him up a little bit to realize why
was he
why did he forget about all that man
damn you must be a quiet the psychopath
to
ignore
all of that completely for years
yeah drama I guess
so long
now it comes back
when when
they're getting pregnant
[Music]
foreign
did he also not know that he was her
brother until that point until that
conversation
try another ending
sure where we were starting though what
point from the beginning
do I not get a new game plus or so
Is this different
it's not telling me how to play the game
at least
no tutorial
the other rooms are gone
locked
and the plant is gone
oh this is scary
it's the apartment
is empty
foreign
so sad
nothing here at all
this is like a nightmare
am I moving in here alone
oh
am I at least out of the loop now
there's a
there's some thrilling music creeping up
on us can you hear it
look look
I'm so freaky
it's so freaky
and scaring me
no power
's out I mean no power the light is on
is that from outside
do I have anything besides the keys
I mean I was gonna open it but I have no
knife
no
I'm gonna do it with a key
really damn
oh he's doing it and the watch is still
there
why or why
what's it's broken
it's just pointing downwards
I can move it why is the two
lit up
huh
the watch is watching me spin
backwards Maybe
do you want to go backwards
or forward
keep going
backwards
second and still moving can I move that
one no
oh
why is it tall like this
you wait for this one
oh
look it's getting louder
oh it's so scary
we're in the library again
we're not happy with this is he not
happy with this ending
there he is he turned it back he's like
I'm alone I don't like this you could
accept this ending or you could not
we need to
need to page
these feelings for my daughter yo if
he's not he can't accept that after
eight years I
this isn't how I wanted
you deserve hey it's only by forgetting
that we ever really dropped the thread
of time and approached the experience of
living in the present moment cool story
bro
you read that one I
I know the idea of forgetting things
sounds crazy but what if
you could I can help with that if you
want
all you have is the future you'll forget
everything you went through all the pain
all the stress forgotten
forever well he makes me forget but then
he supports incest there is no turning
back
you can't undo this
we can talk about her still
you can choose an answer
you don't have to forget if you don't
want to
choice is yours
this is your last chance
change my mind to what
I hope you find what you're looking for
all right close your eyes I got ending
number one I think because achievement
now has a one before it had a free
I want you to think of a flower ah Focus
breathe but I even forget aren't we
going back to the same problem
changing
moving backward returning to its bud
think of that bud I'm open and fresh
that makes us even more fitting for a
crony flower joke notice the changes let
go of houses play this game as her first
don't let anything open the perception
of
today
just focus on that bud
silently repeat these phrases
may you be free from suffering
may you be free from fear and anger
may you know peace and joy
credits but isn't this like
the same like what happened then no but
but I guess forgetting without him dying
means that the cop will never be angry
okay
and we'll just yeah
never have a wife know
[Music]
happy end because the father doesn't
mind either
oh
that is so [\h__\h] up
that is messed up
[Music]
but of course that's better than the
original ending
I mean the one that you know we played
the whole time because
that's why we forgot and we're happy
with without knowing anything and unless
the fire staying alive so it is an
improvement
foreign
[Music]
yeah
yeah let's just hope she will never see
a
a family tree a proper one
[Music]
I forget about her completely too
I thought I'm just forgetting about us
being related
[Music]
oh
I forgot about her too then I guess
that's good too
oh
then I'm alone too now I mean
[Music]
did I forget
about the father as well
[Music]
but wait there is more
I forgot everything that game resets ah
yeah
you can play again
in here that's just another time Loop
oh
what they deleted my safe
really
no
[Music]
I shouldn't have done that first oh no
should have done that last
oh well there's a dessert ending for
real what the [\h__\h] is the dessert ending
it's not important okay but so this is
the is this the main ending
I would say so
because the alone one felt kind of like
undone incomplete because we then did
something with the pocket watch
arguably no
seems like it
room closet
[Music]
you could stop at the ending yeah
which is that one he knows
and chose to not
yeah
but isn't the loan ending and an ending
that I just got now
basically the same because the father
stays alive I just I just don't know
but yeah okay
and the me not knowing will make it
easier for me to move on
but then isn't there like a big puzzle
piece missing in my brain too like who's
my father
[Music]
oh
does it start from the very beginning
well
let's not check if this is really reset
oh yeah it looks like it
yeah okay
cool y'all
that was a lot of fun
that was really cool I'm glad we
finished it in one goal way
yeah I'm gonna read some superchatos I'm
just gonna check up on on cattle Kibbles
if they have cables because
this movie seemed very upset
hmm
that was a good story yeah I think so
too it was very interesting I like the
whole mechanism the gameplay
the the fact that it's you know point
and click I like point and click games
and you know very story focused
for even for bad Gamers it's uh easy to
handle this game
hmm
yum I like point-and-click Adventures
was an interesting story to unravel but
[Music]
being related huh
unfortunate poor guy
didn't think it would be him
after all that
cause she was so convinced it was her
but she it could have been her it almost
was her imagine the ending an ending
where
she did actually kill her dad on that
night
we then get together
and then together we just killed a cop
because he seems to be the last
straw oh we don't kill him and we we we
tell him it was the brother and he
doesn't figure out ever that the brother
is me
who knows who knows possibilities
the man creepers unicorn famous
huh which voice actor
would the loop have ended
oh I think the loop wouldn't have even
existed
because we changed the timeline
then if the dad really died by the
wife's
hands hmm
oh
uh-huh
yeah the voice actors are famous actors
hmm yeah I guess I heard the name before
William the foe that seems familiar the
other ones I'm not sure about
um
ah Spiderman Star Wars the lady is from
Star Wars
really which one
hmm
[Music]
which main Star Wars from seven to none
a main character from the one I didn't
watch
oh Naruto
yeah she was fun she was fine she was
she was talking usually very calmly calm
voice
no I think the voice acting was all
right
the Star Wars you don't talk about oh
the bad one
foreign
okay guys thank you very much for
watching I'll move over to the office to
read super chats and just really quickly
give my cat some Kibbles to check if
they still have some e
H yeah
oh ah [\h__\h]
such a [\h__\h] mess again
[Music]
yeah
yeah okay
okay I'll be our Bean enjoy the music
okay
foreign
that rarely happens
I gave them some
happy I think
she was complaining aggressively
[Music]
all right I'm feeling a bit dizzy ever
since I stood up
man dizzy dizzy dizzy dizzy
oh dizzy
me too you too
no that was a good game oh I'm small
that was a good game I'm very satisfied
um
so let's see
super chattels
[Music]
last time I read
how much one two one
I read the Minecraft super chats
I guess I didn't read the karaoke ones
right let's suppose
oh yeah thank you I always got Bad
Endings did you not get the one that I
got
AI the somnium files
detective room all of those I'm gonna
play it right
it means the stream hey you just arrived
at you end it why do people always
arrive when I just ended
then
but the other one didn't she do the
other one
Ahmed never plays based games of course
she does what are you talking about
um
okay feeling a bit weird for real for
real but
it's okay
Yoshi's Island is based
true true
good for you I didn't get that one what
the [\h__\h] is the proof class in handy
oh thumbnails so tomorrow there will be
a rebroadcast of this
foreign
[Music]
let me try oh
feeling hot too
feeling funky
funky
[Music]
un momento
helpful
let me try first I feel like it's not
gonna work let me try this way first
there it is and it's gone
why
did Google
[Music]
obs
YouTube chat
disappears
if you just there could be a few
possible causes but the issue occurred
with the YouTube server or that an issue
has occurred with your internet
connection I mean mine seems fun
um need to update your browser to the
latest version of YouTube what
no this doesn't even have anything to do
with OBS I think
that doesn't seem kind of obvious
or maybe this
Focus for a second and then disappear oh
that seems right
selling the only way to make the chat
appear and make it stays by unchecking
all of the animation properties on the
chat V2 blah blah blah style generator
[Music]
okay
why I don't know
I haven't used that site to change my
my chat box in a long time
yes I have the newest version of obs
I'll just use this basic
because when you open the chat style
generator it gives you like a basic
thing to work with
I'll just go with the circus
[Music]
and I get rid of nothing
I don't know I'll just go with this for
now
hey
hopefully this works I'll just replace
the code
oh I'm such a hacker
oh
you're working
I teach
yay
[Music]
welcome back it's been 84 years
yay now sit down now
it's been so long where have you been
yeah YouTube must have changed YouTube
YouTube must have changed some kind of
code
that was again an app why do I even get
advertisements on YouTube I shouldn't be
getting other choice but
it's weird
well it had been 12 minutes guys
foreign
okay now everything is fine again
I mean I have an ad block but the thing
is I think
there's like
different
takanasikiara whole life Ian accounts
and sometimes it automatically locks me
into that one that doesn't have
this
YouTube red or whatever I guess
that's the one right to get no ads
one of them is no no no that's not what
I mean no no
are you the premium yeah
okay anyway it doesn't matter let's read
Super chatos Chat is back we happy we
can
move on do the thing
all right
and tomorrow the rebroadcast for this is
a bit early for other time zones so feel
free to stop by if you got time yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
I just love singing your rendition from
a year ago you got this book oh thank
you I can skip it really
ah
wait which song was ah
Ariana Grande song
wait
bacon eggs eggs bacon XX bacon XX I'm so
[\h__\h] grateful for my eggs
changed it
oh you changed a few things
fits so well it fits so well I love it
uh
because her name is Kiara and I'm so
good with Dad she taught me love she
taught me patience she handles pain yeah
that's amazing I love them I've lost
well that's not what I see cause look
what I found and only for searching and
for that I say thank you eggs eggs bacon
eggs eggs bacon eggs eggs I'm so [\h__\h]
grateful for my eggs
oh those must be the original lyrics for
When the demo tape was recorded for the
song and first presented to Ariana
Grande like what do you think about this
song and you know then what she did is
she changed the lyrics because she
thought this just wouldn't be good good
enough
but I say it's good enough
this is the truth lyrics for that song
it would have been even more successful
if it had this these lyrics
um
not a breakfast person
yeah
I mean I don't normally eat bacon and
eggs for breakfast either but now I'm
feeling like eating it for tomorrow
breakfast
I don't have bacon or eggs right now
though
man
okay I mean
I'm not I don't need hash browns for
breakfast either but if I have the
option like in the breakfast buffet then
hell yeah
um
you know breakfast buffets in hotel
usually always have the same thing
but the same things but
the one I was in recently
I was like mind blown because it was
just like a relatively normal hotel but
it had
kaiserschmann the emperor's mess for
breakfast as one of the warm options
I was wool yo me and my Austrian friends
we are so hyped about that we were so
excited because you don't normally have
that anyway but it's kind of like a
pancake replacement I guess so I think
it makes sense to put it in a in a
breakfast buffet and
it might be an Austrian thing but this
wasn't in in a
uh what's Bayern in English again
Bavaria yeah this wasn't Bavarian
Bavaria has like pretty
similar many similarities with Austria
in terms of how we speak and what we eat
and what we call things
we have similar dialects and all that
so I think it makes sense to me that a
hotel in Bavaria would do that
but I've never even seen it in a hotel
in Austria before in a buffet
so I was like really happy
yeah buyer number various the same place
yeah yeah
some people don't know
well I see waffles and some hotels
restaurants yeah
once I was in a hotel that had a waffle
maker where you would make your own
waffles they would put the the dough
there and then you could Grill your own
Waffle and I did that and they weren't
even that like convincing to me you
think oh this is awesome awesome
breakfast option you try you wait for
your waffle and then it's not even like
that convincing
um
did I rate the kill suppose I don't know
I'm at the karaoke ones now
um
anyway thank you duck Hood mwah take a
47 Whitford
for the pinky
want some pancakes Prince apparently
did I sing that when I was singing the
when I was singing the the the
Raspberry Beret
song did I
don't remember making up lyrics like
that
Raspberry Beret
second hand store Raspberry Beret
and if it was warm she wouldn't wear
much more hey it's a nice song
I mean the melody into all that
good song
[Music]
couldn't learn at all but good song an
old sketch about Prince beating someone
at base basketball oh oh I thought
beating like giving him a beating and
then making them pancakes like I like
midday what oh it was a sketch
comedy sketch
I misunderstood everything I thought you
meant sketch as a drawing and beating as
a like punch beating
okay okay okay okay okay now now I
understand
I don't watch that
never watched it I think
[Music]
okay but anyway good to know I wonder if
my mom knows that sketch I am
almost [\h__\h] up with my glass of water
because I needed to reach the sensor
button
s
Jackson FB Junction
utano Pandora
[Music]
is always a joy to watch you slay Queen
thank you I I put in a lot of time to
learn some new songs for you guys last
time because I don't always want to sing
the same songs to you I hope they add my
all my requests at hello project song
soon
I need to add some more dough
more and more and more
I hope they aren't the ones I already
suggested soon please
oh
good morning
[Music]
yeah because otherwise the new system is
of no use for me yet
um
what's
what's that for
I don't recognize the melody for those
lyrics you came up with
ah cut my corn into pizza I've got my
plastic fork oven baking heavy breathing
don't give a [\h__\h] give us carbs and I'm
eating
[Laughter]
and then it continues but I don't know
the melody now do you even care ah do we
even care if a great cheese is something
that would it be fair no would it be
fake if I choose my door tonight chances
that I might chicken wings on the side
and I'm contemplating crispy fries
huh
so funny
oh God you can't I think you should go
for the crispy fries yeah why not treat
yourself
[Laughter]
nice one Moon dong
[Music]
so funny
and I'm contemplating crispy fries
cut my corn onto pizza I've got my
plastic fork oven baking heavy breathing
don't give a [\h__\h] if it's carbs that I'm
eating
huh
so good holy [\h__\h]
you guys should become lyricists for
songs
with pinky amazing color really thank
you that was around I suppose the
the that song
thank you I'm glad you enjoyed it
my song Choices were as surprising as my
game choices these days huh eating
[Music]
do you say lyrics says I wasn't sure
they sure are yeah
except for the K-pop yeah okay Bob had
to be
it had to be
yeah
[Music]
thank you
did something happen with your name
was it always like this
are you
are you not top Canon Ganon
and change it to top gallocouple because
it sounds like
pop Canon Uganda
sounds like it doesn't it
it's a different person
has the same uh like first letters
oh wait it wasn't top it was Nam count
again okay
ah Oh I thought somebody like changed
the name to like Bamboozled me okay okay
doesn't it
can again and Gallo Capon to me it
sounds similar
they're cousins
long lost cousins
that sounds similar
sorry sorry sorry
thank you doll
it was in my side losing my mind wish
somebody would tell me I'm fine
nothing's all right
[Music]
mm-hmm
Viper under the Lemon Tree Duncan Bruce
ready I love victories
shadow Cross Zero thanks for the pinky
gray color contains your fangs nah thank
you for listening and staying until the
end I appreciate it glad you enjoyed it
thank you very much it was totally worth
taking off work to watch you sing I love
you singing you took off work for me
[Music]
for that karaoke
I love you thank you
oh so sweet
you did you're the best
thank you Bruce daddy lee Danke Schoen
Ronaldo Jordan
as always best one yet thank you I I had
a lot of fun with it this time
I mean I always do
well I have had a lot of fun
[Music]
I enjoyed all my song Choices
um
chat this stream has been the highlight
of my week easily really amazing karaoke
Nintendo 10 setlist your voice fits
perfectly for songs like this I adore
you singing oh man thank you you're so
nice
glad you enjoyed my song Choices
and yeah I also think voice fit well for
many of the ones I chose
the Carly Rae Jepsen songs for example I
think
fit quite well
I was surprised I didn't sing those
songs before because back when the album
came out I think I was like listening to
it all the time
really good choices thank you
and then I completely forgot about the
existence of them
the choice is always fit you will thank
you
I brought untouched back because I knew
you guys liked it and I thought it
sounded really good on me too and it's
fun to sing because the fast parts are
really fun the rap almost rap parts
really fun
thank you simply
I feel so untouched right now thank you
so much somehow I can't resist you going
crazy the moon I miss you was I really
learned
ah it's a fun song
cause I can't wait wait wait wait wait
don't even care about the consequences
fun next is fifth child part two there's
so many games
all of them at least I finished uh 12
minutes within one stream but I want to
finish uh I want to finish face
simulator but the new one is coming out
soon so it doesn't really make sense and
I want to finish a Hotline Miami
I will finish last epic and members only
Q I'm not gonna finish but passport to
two I also want to finish
oh man
so we'll have all of that running on the
side I guess
while I'm playing uh
tears of the Kingdom
but I don't think I can fit
all of this into next week
I would try to fit a passport to two
stream into the end of next week though
because I requested help for getting my
model into the game
and they said yeah no problem should
take like what two to three days or so
but now it's golden week and they're not
here so
they'll tell them like on Monday and
then from then on it will take two three
days or so so I have to schedule it for
the end of the week I almost had it
though
I almost was able to do it myself
because I had the model in there it was
just something about I guess the
polygons or whatever because we had to
size it down there's like a maximum size
for the model that you can put in to the
game and that's pretty small uh
originally it was like double for my
model's size and we signed it down that
probably messed up with the textures and
then when I put that into the game I was
like all glitching out in terms of
textures
[Music]
and we tried to figure it out and then
and then we fixed the textures but next
my body was just t-posing and not moving
with those funny animations and that
wasn't good either man I almost did it
without the staff's help oh
I also request that I remember to
request that our models are at least my
own will be released for like MMD
uh for the public
ASAP
and you just requested and
yeah they said yeah we'll do it
okay but I think they forgot about the
original plan of doing it but now I
reminded them
and I'm hoping that some people maybe
want to try to make you know like you
know like this one like poses and
expressions like this so it would be
really helpful
kill you know
um
yeah I'm sure MMD is not even that
difficult to handle is it I I need to
like look into it too maybe I could
figure it out too but
I feel like you guys would have fun with
it
some town and fans have made wishes
like animations would be fun too if
people couldn't make it and think like
for example he has access to my model
but I think he's probably not using it
for his private like
hobby videos
because he only has access to my model
because of the music video commissions
that we made and then in his other
videos like he wouldn't really have it
so he doesn't use it and he keeps on
using my my uh chibi model
and I would I would love for him to just
use my normal model normally so that I
can
see more fun videos in in 3d kiwawa full
size you know that would be cool
do I hear baby
why are you meowing so much
I gave you full
[Music]
meow
um
foreign
to do it I mean he could probably ask
for permission but
I would probably not even have turned it
down
if it's for those fun little videos but
uh yeah I think he's just waiting for it
to be publicly released
so needy today yeah and I already gave
her so many cuddles you have no idea
we fell asleep together again for a
little nap while I was like wrapped
around her had my my head on her butt
which is dangerous because sometimes she
she farts sometimes but she didn't she
she usually holds back on farting when I
have my head on her butts
and then I had my head on her butt and
my my hand on her tummy you know
and we fall asleep like that super often
these days man she purrs Persian person
eventually she stops she falls asleep
too
so nice of her right
no it's really cute about you can't hear
the sound of it you just smell it but
she doesn't like all the blue farts
yeah
they audibly sneeze but they don't
audibly fart
you can smell it though
it's not
not as bad as a human fart I would say
though
can we not talk about it though I don't
like this topic anyway I think it's
funny when I when I say you know cat is
that's what a cat lady would say
hey dog farts are audible she looks so
surprised too the cookie I can imagine
yeah doggos
I think I've seen like a video
of something like that before
where dogs surprise themselves with
their body sounds
dogs are funny
many stories of such cases it seems
all right where was I
oh
I didn't even
I didn't even read a single one I think
Jacob tank
what happened recipe I just used the
random German recipe from YouTube
Someone who was making muffins
they weren't even that good The
Chocolate ones I preferred but only when
they were warm oh I didn't tell you guys
I had um like friends and acquaintances
eat the rest of my muffins at the
convention I went to
and
at that point they were it was a second
day I think
they were still good edible but they
didn't have the like good texture
anymore it seems
and you know everybody who's who hated
said the same thing they said they were
kind of dry
I didn't think
tried a little bit and I didn't think
they were that dry
when I run this fluffy anymore and I
didn't have the crunchy top anymore
and I always had to make this like
excuses and say you know it was really
good when it came fresh out of the oven
um
it was my first muffins okay
they said it was good like taste toys
they were good but the texture yeah they
were dry now
I kept them in a small uh closed
container and I felt like when I opened
up the container when I was like at the
hotel
I felt like that it was moist
it was
like I saw like moistness on the
container inside
oh I didn't make it early in school
so I was convinced that they all said it
was actually dry hmm
oh oh well and maybe it's evaporated
[Music]
oh wow
well well I I wanted to impress
everybody with my muffins but I quickly
lost confidence after like the second or
third person said hey these are kind of
dry
but still I was able to feed my muffins
to everybody yeah
let's try again yeah maybe next time
I'll make a smaller batch and eat it
alone
fresh
enjoyed by myself
all by myself
I'm gonna eat all by myself
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
I'm gonna try a different recipe too
though
wanna see how different recipes change
the muffin taste
I need to try making cookies chocolate
chip cookies
ooh I think I've made chocolate chip
cookies before though
sometime in my life
I feel like I did
[Music]
oh did you even know it
oh
but you remember it so I must have like
posted it ah Valentine's Day
I mean I mean I made Christmas cookies
yeah but you guys are talking about
different cookies
oh did I use the Doubletree recipe
oh my God
yeah they became huge but they were
really good I think
was that my conclusion that they were
really good because I think they were
but it didn't finish them alone either I
think
oh yeah cookies I need to make those
again
oh
the shape was um they were huge I think
[Music]
I do want to make those
those are like the best at least the
ones in the hotel
best chocolate chip cookies
best of luck thanks
Aya uh thanks for the pinky a green root
Jerry super chatting please give us the
muffin recipe it's so basic thanks for
the extra streams this week Lala always
takes care of her timkins when she's
away now let's get more wow was awesome
booty uh the loot I mean
[Music]
yay extra streams I did extra streams
this week what do you mean that week
thanks for streams
and I just stream what I said I would
stream
why did I stream extra
that you didn't plan to do at the start
um
did I did I do that
ah the chronicle that was extra
ah true true true
that came in last minute yeah
it was originally free turned into five
well what was the other extra stream
oh
coronation who are you coordinating
are you Royal
[Music]
yeah small week turned into normal like
true true
I guess I I had many days off but then I
filled the days where I was streaming
with so many
uh streams that it was just a normal
week
[Music]
wait is is that the the husband
or is that one of the sons
takes forever
oh next week is Eurovision oh I also
thought that that already happened
somehow
wow
the Sun
oh oh
ah yeah
okay
the official coronation was today what
oh I guess because it's late
um
interesting
[Music]
so you were actually talking about an
actual coronation oh
interesting anyway thank you Taco
yes
Jacob 47 for the pinky did you know
flight simulator has an entire update
themed around Austria
what why
why
is there like every country
what they do Austria
it was almost the same time as the Myra
tournament
why not and because Austria is small and
others don't understand why why they
would choose it over other
countries ah it was in the German update
Australia has its own with New Zealand
imma try to ask for perms but no luck oh
it's amazingly accurate
they want to make the whole world
oh wow
oh
Your Truck Simulator 2 has lost your
cities too if you want to try aha is it
like in geoguesso or that basically
Austria consists only of one city or is
it like in real life where somehow all
tourists go to in Spoke so what they
have is in this book
[Music]
this book Vienna sets book and more
but the cities are also small how is the
truck gonna drive like through the city
or do you have to drive from City to
City
to another city
that brings back memories of when I had
to learn Austrian highways and mountain
passes and [\h__\h] like that for my
um
for my degree
my hotel degree
I had to learn that [\h__\h]
from where to where it would go
and what it's called and then if
somebody says I want to go from here to
here I would have to know during the
test
which
wrote to take thankfully even though
they made us learn it
thankfully they didn't ask about the
mountain passes because that's
ridiculous and because my argument was
if you work in a hotel or if I'm a guest
and I ask someone if I just so happen
that I want to actually rent a car and
then drive over a mountain I do not
expect
and in any way that the receptionist
knows
every single mountain pass by heart
though I don't think anyone would expect
that
so either you ask the receptionist to
look something up in Google Maps or so
and print it out for you or you just
look it up yourself like every other
person would normally do just use your
[\h__\h] GPS right who doesn't use GPS
these days especially if you're going on
a trip like that
right that's so goofy that was what I
was thinking the whole time like it
makes no sense that you're making maybe
okay you can have me learn the the big
um highways okay okay but mountain
passes really
that just makes no sense nobody would
expect me to know that but I had to
learn them anyway and I think I I didn't
though
I was just hoping for them not to come
up in a test and the final one because I
knew I couldn't remember this [\h__\h] I was
already like
over
whelmed with the with the highways and
there was um
other there was something else we had to
learn to besides highways and mountain
passes
I think we also had to know like every
connection
or so I don't know
and maybe other big roads I don't know I
don't know
it may not be entirely accurate but
still like nobody would would want you
or expect you to know that by heart
can look on the map always
so that was uh
unnecessary but I don't think I even
wasted my time with learning it anyway
and then thank God they only asked me a
pretty simple one
at the actual test
[Music]
yeah school will be like I'm gonna make
you learn all these unnecessary things
if you don't learn them I'm gonna make
you failed test but then later in life
you will probably not need most of these
things but we're not gonna tell you
we're gonna act as if you will need all
of these things
[Music]
yeah right
well my PC just um
froze for a second
okay continue
you felt it well we're connected
we're intertwined our Fates are
intertwined
we have the same destiny
yeah quadrat quadratic formula let me
tell you
all right let me spell it out for you
[Music]
rectangle spots
practice good
it always like advertise it with it
being
a
quadratic
and a practical and good
square chocolate is good
I never see my favorite one being sold
anywhere anymore these days so it makes
me so sad
why why why
I passed
look so okay
ah
I had I didn't have okay let's go from
top left to right and down I didn't have
the that one before I didn't have that
one before
that one's actually interesting the
Olympia oh it's like breakfast
I don't have I didn't have that one
before I don't like that one then I did
have this one the cornflakes one before
that one's yummy this one's also pretty
good but I don't normally don't like
chocolate with like huge nuts in it
and this one I don't really like bitter
chocolate but I wonder if I'll get into
it at some point the Alpine milk one is
very like you know basic but good very
good chocolate yeah on this one no no
thank you this one tried before but
again that's too big this one I've never
seen before it's like the same thing
with almonds nice yummy
this one I don't like marzipan so [\h__\h]
it but many people like it here it's
like an even like it or you don't like
it this one is my favorite technospa
cakes with the big butter cookie that
was my favorite and I don't see it
anymore anywhere but that one's the best
that one was my emergency chocolate when
I was in Japan the one that Casper was
nibbling through [\h__\h] Casper
the nougat one I actually
I'm not a huge fan of nougat chocolate
actually the yogurt one is really good I
also like the yogurt milk very much
I'm selling it
peppermint chocolate I'm not a big fan
of those Beaver ah this crispy one is
basically like the cornflakes one I like
that one too they did strawberry yogurt
one really good really good big
recommend Yum Yum Yum the cacao mousse I
never had uh the Eden formation I also
never had never see that one as the the
coffee one nope never had coconuts I
don't like those nuts
and the vanilla mousse I never thought
of one before Oh I'm curious about that
one uh
interesting but no
no Sports potato chips what the [\h__\h] no
no thank you
so there's even more than these though I
have so many good ones
so many good flavors oh man
I'm an awesome assist I've heard but am
I also available as like a character
that you can play or am I just assist
foreign
[Music]
is
is en only a cyst
only eight playable characters
who
which one
I'm the only an assistant oh
ah nice copium
Alex music is in the game
Amazon assistant
oh
yeah
and fubuki IMF
oh
to say put in both accent but it doesn't
seem like they go by generation
they started developing beforehand wow
really
bam
interesting
maybe I'll take a look at it maybe maybe
where was I
think black Christian language
[Music]
I can't [\h__\h] yawn properly [\h__\h] uh
soon
Anthony
oh that was fifth simulator
oh
girl I did it
I did it
yawned properly it triggers me when I
count
ma'am
okay let me read the usual room videos
[Music]
stupid advertisements
uh what was I gonna say oh yeah
I think the next one we're gonna do
I felt like making a froggy Wawa one
next
because
uh
it was one of the questions that iron
Mouse sent me like about froggy Wawa
uh didn't come up in the questions she
did ask me because we didn't get through
many
I thought oh maybe I should make a video
on Prague
yeah
let's do that
okay
seven evil donation
it's a nice trip down memory lane isn't
it yeah
did you recognize all the voices are
made by me in this video of course
but I feel like they all sounded very
like unique
especially with the editing
sounded so much like Gladys but I I
actually like you you know I I I talked
on purpose already before the robot
added like her
so a lot of that you know weird
pronunciations like
welcome to the usual room that was all
me
and then the last one
cow card asked me to like imitate this
video
uh apparently it's a meme and I have no
idea what I was doing
I was like what the [\h__\h] is this this is
weird but you know cow carrot always has
good ideas so I trust in him
I didn't know what I was doing but
apparently it was funny
and with speak I was
speaking like this
or so I don't know
really
weird
[Music]
the G-Man
I don't understand
oh
he talks so
weird
just reach round
[Music]
12 hour turnover there was a tour oh
I mean at this point at that point the
2.5 hours don't make a real difference
anymore even don't they
but welcome to Roma
welcome welcome
pretty late there just like here so
hopefully you'll reach your Airbnb or
hotel or so quickly and can relax
maybe during the ride you could listen
to My Stream could you maybe not do you
have reception like internet
oh one in Rome sleep well at this time
yeah
chill
yes I am pecora
I am
back okay
um
[Music]
foreign
thanks for the pinky how much to get out
of the usual room wait are you still are
you in there for some reason
why you in there
have you decided about MC tomorrow no
what should I have decided
first things first we're doing karaoke
rebroadcast
um
I missed the Enzo Series yeah I should
make one again
[Music]
painting switching it out no so far I
think I'm fine
yeah I haven't talked to Dakota since
[Music]
the incident
oh
when I spelled my spaghetti
yeah
Mario thing yeah yeah I was watching a
little bit
I'm glad I didn't participate because
like some of the matches were extremely
laggy and I would have been affected by
that too
and I don't know
practicing for days and then just having
it ruined by lag doesn't seem like so
much fun
and I don't like the pressure
that much anyway of those kind of like
uh contests well I I the thing is like
they
the staff
like several times
they were like hey we want to do
something like this
who wants to participate and then not
enough people wanted to participate so
they changed plan okay we will do this
instead this kind of tournament they
want to participate and again not enough
people to put one of one who wanted to
participate some of those I was like
yeah I want to do it and some of them I
was like no
but they were asking like I think all of
her life
and they did it like I think four times
eventually they were like okay okay
never mind instead we're doing a pekorda
organized tournament who wants to
participate in this Super Mario
tournament
and at that point it was already like
so many times
they asked us what about this one what
about this one hey we're changing the
game we're doing this tournament now
we're changing the game we're doing this
tournament now
and I was like um
yeah you know what nah
no it wasn't first come first if anyone
could participate
it wasn't the invitation or so either I
just didn't feel like it at that point
yeah
I didn't feel like it in hindsight
I was I'm already busy and yeah
maybe next time when they do another uh
tournament
but like damn that
that lag look
yeah and I'm not good at Mario our new
dad so I would have had to practice a
lot so even being useful
uh
and then
it would be ruined by the leg
[Music]
and just even even without the lag I
would have probably lost
maybe another time I mean even losing is
fine and all that
I don't mind that
well I just didn't really feel like
participating when it came up
um
thank you for confirming that I am not
very good at Mario
it was kind of funny it was funny and
frustrating at least for me to watch
like it was all slow motion it must be
so difficult to control with all that
slow motion
ah yeah but that's the problem I mean
good that they're uh inviting like all
the branches but the problem with that
is
if you have all branches and you have
all servers
and that's why I like because the the
few groups where they were like
Japanese only members weren't lagging
right
or not as bad at least
it was really only for when all of them
were mixed
um
and that made everyone lag not only the
overseas people but by the overseas
people being involved
the Japanese people were also lagging
like crazy
suffering at least that's fair if one
suffers everyone must suffer
and it's like another like addition of
difficulty
just just another gimmick to add to the
level to make it more difficult but a
little bit too difficult don't you think
because I saw like Bales was doing so
well
she came to that one point where she had
to like go down and up again so fast and
then like she kept on like missing her
jumps and all that because of the
slow motion
at that one point she was stuck forever
man
forever
[Music]
the wall jump sometimes she managed to
do it nonetheless
slow motion motion why are you so slow
yeah they adapted to it
yeah
anyway uh deeply thanks for the pinky
since you haven't been to the usual room
before please I need to know I don't
know why don't you not know
you should know
I'm having a hard time keeping track of
you guys usual room schedules
gotta keep track of it yourself
repressed memories
you should know
okay next one I'm gonna read will be the
last one
[Music]
this one
hmm
no Jacob thank you soon the game oh this
is after I came back
thank you twice even
Dominic K thank you thank you
gummy worms
there's gummy wormy molds now
where'd you get those gummy wormy modes
on me I type it in and I can't find them
how did you get
hidden how'd you get them
how'd you get those
worms Oh
they look yummy why do we need those
who needs this
emoji
no one
you're just taking up slots
could give those slots to me for my
members emotes
no we don't need it
but are they only YouTube emotes or are
they also outside of YouTube
that made fun of
who did I watch recently who made fun of
the YouTube emotes
is that they're bad and cringe and I
thought they were actually decent
who was that
I was watching someone a bit too bad
Eva Holo on YouTube everyone nah
it was definitely an En member and they
were like oh this YouTube emotes are so
so stupid also
and I'm like what but
there look at the cute heart
that one's okay
and and I mean there's some okay ones
[Music]
and they're they're useful
because I can't get membership
when I'm like you know lurking
can't get the membership so
what can I use those
they're okay
but right now my chat is broken and most
of the emotes don't show up in my chat
when you guys are posting it it just
says it says face purple white eyes
face purple white eyes taste Rich heart
shape
my own work though
are they broken for you too
oh
YouTube what the [\h__\h]
what's happening
it's not just me
father was just me
so you play fifth simulator too well
probably oh
anyway Jim Tracy done kitchen
zip please
[Music]
Kiana let's say that bay asks you and
Ina if you'd like to go to a world where
you live together however although this
movie is the same cat in this world
chunkers is now a pot bellied Pig
if Ina really wanted to accept base off
or would you say yes nope
nope
because I mean why why
we don't have to go to a different world
to live together either because stay in
the same world and I keep my cats the
way they are
uh Bob thanks soon
oh yeah yeah
I've never been I should go to college
that
I'm glad you had fun
I saw a little talk merch arriving at
people's places it looks so good
function
with all 10 of the Hawaiian girls were
characters in a horror movie who would
be most least likely to survive to the
end please rank them well am I ranking
them on their lower capabilities or on
their real life capabilities
because if it's Lord then I wouldn't do
so bad but if it's just me that I would
do pretty bad
uh
uh if we say real life
capabilities let's say
um
in a horror movie
least likely to survive
I don't know what I'm basing this on but
um
[Music]
that's really difficult
I don't even know who would do well and
who would do bad but I would say we all
would do bad but
[Music]
um
pink crony and bae
might be able to
do decently because they have some
physical skills maybe like they work out
so maybe that could help
and amen you know she doesn't get
freaked out so easily I think
she she's not scared to use the weapons
she knows how to use a gun I guess
since she used it in her stream
not a real gun but
same thing right
so Ahmed would do well probably too
but he gets scared easily but well and
once you've put in a situation like that
when it's about death or life
survival situation
I mean
and then
[Music]
I don't think Inna would be good at like
defending herself
nah
uh
Haley
mid
um
depends on what kind of horror too
me
nah
[Music]
don't know but nah nah bad bad chances
uh fauna is good with horror right but
like if you put in the situation like
that IRL not just in a game you're in
the movie so you think you're part of it
like you this is your life now
um
then
oh no
I don't think she could do [\h__\h]
and then
[Music]
mid
gonna put her mid
follow with surprise yeah I would like
to see that I would like to be surprised
it's just something about Oliver's like
sweet voice and sweet and parents that I
can't
really see her leading
the group in a horror movie
would get lost first somehow oh wait I
forgot Iris
Iris
does Iris work out or so
um
[Music]
no well then
mid I think she would have at least even
if she's like physically not capable of
doing much I think she would have at
least the motivation to stay alive
and and be quite determined to make it
through at least until a certain point
when she's then devoured by zombies and
cannot do much more
[Music]
yeah like willpower yeah yeah yeah
especially if she likes horror then
that's good basis to work with
um okay moving on now a channel thanks
for the pinky I just want to say that I
really admire your dedication towards
your work and fans I live in a rural
area and listening to all these stories
helps expose me to the outside world bit
by bit oh it reaches fire it made it
here way up in the north whoa north of
Canada huh
oh
I'm sure it's very pretty up there
that is sweet thank you very much I'm
glad it can help somehow thank you for
watching my streams and please
don't feel I know don't feel powerless
or anything like that
you should
go out into the world and enjoy it
um
maybe if you feel like it
or maybe if you don't feel like you can
unleash your full potential in the rural
area also you could consider moving
or traveling hmm
I don't know but thank you very much
I'm happy to hear that
ah there you are you want to someday
well I don't know how old you are but if
you're pretty young then you got a lot
of time
to move out and see more of the world
definitely recommend it
but like Countryside also nice sometimes
like sometimes I I feel like would be
nice to live on the countryside
so bad either but that shouldn't be like
what your whole life consists of I think
you should see like different places
different types of environments
um
thank you for the pinky
cat hair
in my mouth
and there you go got it
okay thank you so much for creating our
community Kiara thanks to you I was able
to make and meet friends from all over
Europe oh
it was so much fun like we had Korean
barbecue went sightseeing and more that
was so crazy I drove 1 645 kilometers by
a car in less than 50 hours oh yeah I
read that part of your Super Chat
already
mmm Korean barbecue huh
well I had Korean barbecue like only
once in my life or twice I guess the one
that I had in in Korea was also somewhat
Korean barbecue even though it was
mostly some guilt sauce
is that that's not really Korean
barbecue right if it's just that thing
try again just today I saw a video about
Korean barbecue at home with this nice
plate hot plate with like compartments
for all the side thingies
um
I had it once I had one Korean barbecue
as I remember
at some dokumi
couple years ago
because all we wanted to eat Japanese
but all the Japanese restaurants were
like way too crowded and reserved for
the all all the hours of the day because
you know dookomi
when docomo happens all the Japanese
restaurants are booked out
it's impossible to get in if you don't
like stand in line for hours or Reserve
early
and then Korean barbecue
Korean places are like also somewhat
popular but not as much so it was easier
to get into one of those
the reserve miles before actually a lot
of places also just don't accept
reservations so you really have to stand
in line for hours
which is not good the smart thing to do
would probably be
leave the convention a little bit
earlier than the others
or just go to a different restaurant
maybe come to dulcami a day or two early
or leave a day or two later so you can
enjoy those restaurants on one of the
non-dokamides
and then during the dukumi days just go
to less popular places
just non-japanese places there's a lot
of other good restaurants
just eat if you're traveling from
outside of Germany anyway then you
shouldn't even go for Japanese food you
should go for for German food but the
Japanese food in Dusseldorf is just so
good like if you don't really have a
chance to get good Japanese food
elsewhere normally then then yeah it's a
good chance to get good Japanese food
there
um
[Music]
you don't even have Japanese food and
Dusseldorf last year
anyway
oh damn
you missed out on some good food but I'm
sure you had other good food
anyway thank you natsudu I'm really glad
to hear about your experience glad you
enjoyed it and I'm really happy always
to hear about my community
how they like to meet up and hang out
together and get along together it's
really sweet
I'm happy for you guys
please continue being tainted
wings
are you guys are building for my art
thanks
baked turkeys
foreign
thank you twice
meta Richmond Junction
thank you for a red what double red wow
what the hell
hi Tanto I just want to say thank you
for everything you've done and I wanted
to say I met my girlfriend for you about
a year ago today she was the first
person to talk to me at my new job
because she notices my Kiana kitchen no
way
we love what you just used to come no
and then you start dating no way
[Music]
you must have hit it off
amazingly well thanks to my keychain
is my keychain like love inducing or so
what
that's incredible I am Cupid yeah
passive Cupid
legally you have to name your kid Kiana
now yeah yeah
change together by my keychain and I was
the key keyada
[Music]
what
if it's a boy oh it will be a girl don't
worry
I will I will make it be a girl
I don't know how
wow
eh I'm happy for you guys
that is amazing almost unbelievable but
wow why would you lie to me that is
amazing
that's amazing I'm glad you guys are
happy to cover
hope that will continue forever
hmm
don't forget about me
is it even appropriate for me to give
you a kiss
well you know I always do that okay it's
not like you know you know you know
here just just uh
in the air okay
not not on your face just the air just
the air was kissed
very
um say so all is professional here
foreign
thank you
forgot to spoken
payday people keep on telling me about
payday and you know I'm open to playing
it but like which one
which one do I even play there's free
right
which one should I even play
two
this is a story not collected
guys I'm always so tired even when I
take a nap
don't answer don't even answer
gonna tell me to work out and eat
healthy and I don't want to
[Music]
uh
okay
there's a story but it doesn't matter
okay okay
you know what I will eat ice cream after
this well I might hmm
foreign
Ty though but
well
it's been like this for so long
I'm just always tired always
lacking
energy and motivation
um
but it's okay
I'm making it work with my job
thankfully
hmm
I think yeah maybe a little bit
depressive espresso
that's what I've been
expecting thinking
but it's okay
is okay
I have it on the control
yeah
oh
what's a thyroid
I forgot
could be able with Summer soon thinking
summer no it wasn't even like winter
related I had in the summer too
oh well that's okay I will
um eat something now
and
then I will sleep with my keto cuddles I
actually have some
singing deadlines or deadline
maybe a single that no I have a couple
oh yeah
I still need to record my the two album
songs that I have already but it's okay
I still got time and then another one
and I'm gonna record and I for one of
them I said I'll do it uh end of the
week until the end of the week
so maybe I can do it tomorrow or worst
case Monday or so
I'll probably take Monday off because
like this week has been pretty
exhausting for me I feel like I need to
go back to taking two days off per week
this this week I only took one day off
because I felt bad about not streaming
on the weekends
um
but I don't think I have the energy man
I need two days also to just function in
life because
oh
like I need time more time for like
everyday life things
yeah I don't know I'm sorry guys I'm
just I think I would love to still go at
the pace of before
I'm like I don't know the first year
second year
but don't worry I won't I want like it
won't get much worse
then two days off per week at least not
like
on normal weeks
um
well if there's a phase where I'm
traveling or so you know that's a
different story but in normal weeks
I think I gotta continue to take two
days off
um
it was fun and I was very motivated to
just um give you guys a lot of fun
content because I want you guys to be
like oh
thank you for delivering fun content yo
this is a great schedule this is such a
good schedule you're amazing I wanted to
hear that
so I put a lot of stuff in the schedule
for this week
but I've been feeling very drained
it's okay though now I'm really tired
[Music]
yeah so this is normal yeah but
I don't know
you know I mean we've did it for a while
a couple schedules were just two days
off and it was fine it was plenty right
for like content-wise
um
thank you
yeah
thank you guys oh
[Music]
yeah
I'll see what I can do for you
thank you for being so sweet thank you
Sean I have no energy left for some
reason so I will go now ah it was fun
I'm really glad we could finish the game
within the stream it was really good I
enjoyed it thanks for being here and
watching me play it and for being
respectful about the spoilers I mean I
feel like they were not really spoilers
but a lot of backseating
it's okay I mostly relied on myself
until like some more difficult Parts in
the end
but thank you thank you I think you know
kfp chickens always backseat me so much
and I welcome it so at some point you
don't you just do it subconsciously and
you don't even want to upset me but it
just happens to your fingers they just
go do this do that because you want to
help me and that's really sweet you
can't even stop yourself anymore
okay I also when I have when I want to
stream where I know how the game goes
also you know I can't hold back I'm back
sitting like [\h__\h]
I mean
there's just this feeling that you need
to help right you want to help you just
want to help that's it's a good thought
behind it
it's a positive thing in fear you just
want to help
yeah
that's okay no Fire Emblem totally okay
even back sitting was so encouraged it
usually always is I just felt like the
backseating in this game would also
simultaneously like hint at a lot of
spoilers so easily especially in the
game where it's so contained into this
small space that you can play in and
walk around in
mostly I should be able to do everything
without backstaining right point and
click and whatever you can click mostly
there's a reason why you can click it
whatever you can't click you can't click
because you don't need to click it
so it's pretty easy
um
very interesting to unravel everything
very cool
yeah but yeah backseating that game
can backfire
flower one was the was the flower was it
was kind of a spoiler yes but at that
point even after hearing it I still
didn't really didn't click with me
thank God
thank God it didn't click with me
but also I knew that there was a Twist
so the whole time I was waiting for a
twist
it was okay even then I didn't know what
was going on
thank God
um
[Music]
click with me
thinking the vibe was gonna kill you I
mean
could be you know that the twist was so
shocking that
who wouldn't be surprising if the wife
would do something like that too I mean
yes in this movie I am finished with my
stream thank you for picking me up oh
no she's so why does she love me so much
why do you love me so much that you get
me in trouble with the police huh
you love me too much
loving you too much so much
[Music]
I picked her up and I'm squeezing her
pies
I know you don't like to be picked up
like this I know you don't want to be on
my lap but if you come here to annoy me
then you must be picked up and cuddled a
little bit easier
just escaping she's escaping
she has Escape
So Soft they're shedding so bad right
now I've been trying to
help them but it's a daily battle
be
and it's out
[Music]
something under my table
scratched me screech scratch
all right I'll go now
tomorrow Minecraft
in the evening same time as today
so I see you there in karaoke early in
the day rebroadcast if you missed it
last time or if you want to hear it
again
hey
put up the reservation
hmm
I don't know I didn't see on your
schedules or so yet
[Music]
about other Minecraft Plants but I said
even if not even if no one's playing it
at least not scheduled
no you don't know maybe a lot of ID
members log in even when they're not
streaming right so that could be and
otherwise it's fine because I could work
on Phoenix 10.
and then it's actually better if I'm not
like
being disturbed
okay so and in German we say every
dancing I love you guys good day sir
good evening ladies bye bye
see you tomorrow
[Music]
foreign
and the a42892s they would choose extra
light shoes unknown shoes and then
switches
[Music]
yeah yeah cheers
XK juice
[Music]
pumpkin salad juice
spicy chicken butt juice Simply Juice
Exile juice
[Music]
and juice
parsley cheese and broken mentions
how about juice Anton juice
frozen juice
juice
my push
as a country
but for cheese and rice juice
um
I already said that tomato juice
bonjourn juice chicken juice
[Music]
cabbage juice
um
sea bass juice
Addy juice
[Music]
blood chicken cheese
Chloe beaches
juice
[Music]
the tickets Monkey Juice
gym 22.
swatter cheese
got it for me but juice cut it two steps
motion juice random name juice
Taco matches
[Music]
fry cheese
juice
[Music]
should I stop now
Alexander juice
a running juice
beet juice
King of the gravity juice
what arcade shoes Nike shoes
[Music]
I'll go now
leftover lemon juice
and pickle juice
[Music]
juice
silver wolf juice sticker sticker juice
foreign
[Music]
shoes
um
[Music]
mmm 92.
delicious I probably already write a
couple of these
hit
I'll go now
enough juice
no cheese no juice no no choose
[Music]
I might do this sometimes okay from now
on
[Music]
ooh pumpkin milk cheese
all the greenberry juice Cosmos bunny
juice
[Music]
bye bye
for real for real for real for real
what's these ugly you want to buy okay I
will I was holding it hostage now I will
give it to you
but only if you give me something
in exchange
otherwise I'll continue holding it
hostage what I want is your eternal love
a dedication to me and kfp or else
okay bye