[Music]
oh a so
sleepy and attention pleas I'm rainy
from whole life ID generation 2 and
welcome to the very first program of
rainy's thirdd anniversary called well
rain versary but with the letter with
the number three replacing one of the
e's in rainy let's
go very CH bgm that we have here because
today so happens to be the grand opening
of rainy catron Cafe wow what is rain
catron Cafe well basically rain catron
Cafe is just like a regular Cafe you
know but with a little twist with a
little twist you know so um just like uh
regular made Cafe you can pick cute
drinks and um stuff see like this uh
amariz and waffle and ice cream you know
ice cream very nice yummy ice cream
stick but you can be you can choose
which type of R you want to be served
OMG first is rain antagonist
stepmother yes and two rain kind-hearted
Soul who was oh my gosh I'm forced by
the evil stepmother to help out in this
Cafe can you believe it oh my God so sad
and the third one is rainy biological
daughter that the stepmother treats
kindly as opposed to how she treats the
stepdaughter AKA like I will Che hat you
know like oh my gosh how can we Aid the
stepdaughter right wow raining as a kind
soul what kind of weird auo is this hey
wa hey hey watch it watch it anyways
other than that please enjoy the visit
as if it's a normal made Cafe there will
be cute food and drinks to choose from
and we hope you you guys have fun at
rainy catron Cafe so um this is like the
grand opening thank you guys so much for
um actually coming here so early you
know it's a very special day and I also
have invited my friends to come uh for
the grand opening and they can taste the
drink uh and the food for free and have
an experience with uh rain and catron
you know because oh my gosh um oh my
gosh and uh actually this store hasn't
opened yet but somebody's already at the
door yet oh my gosh because they're so
hyped for rainy catron you know usually
rainy catron is very Indonesian but I
want to bring it to an international
level you know oh my gosh for free for
my friends for free for you pay okay
thank you all right and um without
further Ado let's open the door for our
enthusiastic friend it doesn't open till
like uh 10 more minutes minutes but it's
okay uh she'll be the very first guest
of the day hello and uh I have the
[Music]
uh
hello hi
Raine hello um welcome to the grand
opening of rainy catron Cafe um who am I
speaking to today and what should I call
you uh this is nerva ravencraft you can
just go go ahead and call me uh Arisa
would be fine thank you for letting me
in early since I was so impatient a okay
lady Risa thank you so much for coming
to the grand opening of uh rainy catron
Cafe and as briefed in your invitation
letter there are three options that you
can choose from a is rainy antagonist
stepmother B is rainy kindhearted soul
and C is rainy biological daughter who
wants to help um the I don't know the
the poor child uh ABC see who uh who
would you want to pick let's go with C
that sounds like fun Okay
C okay I see we we'll do see okay and
okay I'm going to serve you today in
three 2
one hello lady Risa are you here today
um so I have a little problem actually
over here I'm supposed to be serving you
these three dishes oh which is the
amariz as you can see here and the
waffles and the ice cream um before I
say anything though please uh can you
choose one please uh could I could I
please try the waffles today Raine oh
waffles okay um the waffles for you I
see here are here are the waffles that
I'm going to uh serve oh oh no I'm so
nervous that I'm here here's for you
it's for you it's for you um okay um but
for this um do you see um that person
over there she's always being scolded by
the by the stepmother you see she's
always yelling at her I wonder if I
wonder if you can do something about I
I'm I'm powerless to do this but will
you help me I really want to help her I
I can try do you have a plan what what
can I do what can I do to help no
because I'm useless can you um please
give me a a plan like I can't just come
up to the stepmother and
and you know she won't stop she won't
stop making the girl suffer what would
you do in my
situation if I if I were you or if I
were me what should should I oh anything
cuz right now I'm the customer so I
could I could just go up and yell at her
actually oh oh no will will will you do
that for me yeah yeah yeah so wait give
give me a little background first so so
what exactly is so that's that's your
step that's your stepmother but are you
I I'm I'm the I'm I'm her I'm her
daughter actually like I I pity my uh
step sibling so much and she's so mean
like she's the my mother is so nice to
me but so mean to her but she won't
listen to me why wouldn't she be nice to
her yeah yeah that's that's so terrible
um well okay well then I guess I guess
I'll have to I'll have to have a word
with her over my delicious waffles will
you do that oh my goodness thank you so
much you are a very kind soul so much
lady Risa yeah if it were you I'd say
the best thing that you could probably
do is uh set up a giant plot where you
and your steps sister actually run away
together to start a new life away from
your your mother because clearly she she
she might not be the worst person in the
world to you but clearly she's she's a
little bit mean you know I know I know
maybe losing both of her daughters yeah
it'll make her realize how awful she was
and maybe make her want to repent you
know and then maybe she'll finally want
to apologize you know oh thank you so
much for the advice that definitely I
will I will I will work on that I will
talk to her after this oh I feel so bad
maybe after the shift I'll I'll just
whisper to her about it and then oh
thank you so much that would be so
helpful and uh how how's the dish taste
by the way oh it's wonderful I love
waffles I was just craving something
sweet so this is actually amazing oh
that's that's that's very good that's
very good especially since you know the
very Ed full advice that you gave me I'm
very glad would you like an extra ice
cream uh just because you're you're so
nice to me all right ice cream for you
okay ice cream for you and this this
this this uh this ice cream is for
you wow very nice um okay so what do you
think about uh Dan catron Cafe actually
it it's very fun obviously there's a
wonderful spread that I presume is all
made Handmade by you thank you so much
thank you throwing off your cooking
skills love that a do you have any um
special words for me in my for my
anniversary yes happy
anniversary 3 years is such a long time
I'm sure it's been a long journey for
you and I'm happy to uh be able to be
your friend and uh join you in it and be
a part of your special day thank you so
much I'm looking forward to um the stuff
we're we're going to do soon
right thank you so much Nissa for coming
oh I mean lady narusa I'm sorry please
spread the word of rainy catron Cafe to
your friends okay of course what a
wonderful exp I'll have to tell
everybody so everyone can come here and
spend all their money cuz how could they
not hell yeah I I mean oh yes that would
be a that would be very good thank you
so much for coming we will be waiting
for your next visit thank you narissa
thank you I'll leave a five star review
yay please
do okay
[Music]
byebye I I don't know what I just I
don't know what I just
said yo that's nice actually that's the
first time I talked to I talked to Risa
I was like yo hey what's
[Music]
up pussing pussing pussing what happened
I don't know yes see so it's kind of
like that right so first we go in we as
the guess so what should I call you see
actually this is this is she was
actually being really nice about it she
was like oh yeah please call me please
call me Rissa you know like some some
people I would expect them to be like oh
call me whatever you know you can't
actually do that by the way and well
that's brief the invitation letter you
have three to choose from and and I will
serve you according to that scenario
thingy and other than that it's just a
normal make Cafe you know you order uh
really good food you order you know food
tastes good everything's nice and yeah
that is the grand opening hopefully
after this you know this also serves as
a promotional stream so hopefully people
will
be maybe
so bad after all yeah so well this
Callin is pretty LAX you know I don't um
usually Callins are like oh my gosh 5
minutes 5 minutes next caller is in next
caller is in well for this is not really
you know because um I invited my special
friends but they can come in anytime
they want some people uh already said to
me oh I'm coming at this time I'm coming
at this time yeah so I can also uh pitch
to you yeah the concept for raining
catron Cafe uh from the beginning
you know maybe the out donation people
are still like what is catron what is
catron so here remember the little skit
in my 3D
showcase uh is it my 3D showcase or is
it the or is it the Holo showcase it's
it's all a blur I think it's the hoto
showcase I think it's the hoto showcase
the little cetron T NOA thingy that is
cetron in Japanese the staff instantly
got it it's Hora you know it's the H
little mini life yeah yeah see I got it
mixed
up catron is Megatron let's go so it's
basically like that it's actually a made
Cafe with this kind of concept so I've
always actually wanted to make a made
Cafe thingy but for the longest time I'm
like what concept you know and well
since recently me as Indonesian the ID
Bros knew me as the antagonist tante you
know and I'm like why not bring this to
everywhere and make it a concept thingy
right oh actually I see somebody at the
door I see somebody at the door all
right uh we can't open the door for her
actually because we're opening soon
anyways we're opening soon
anyways she can come in anytime she
wants um she's supposed to come in in
well 2 minutes I'm looking at the time
right now 2 minutes 2 minutes 2 minutes
but it's okay 2 minutes do we have two 2
minutes yes we do okay we'll just wait
for 2 minutes cuz she seems she seems
like she's uh she seems like she's
sticking to the
schedule unlike the previous customer
the previous customer is so excited but
this one's like waiting right in front
of the door like I'll wait for the
opening
hours
huh he waiting to KN well you can knock
now if you want you
know you can knock now if you want but I
don't think she wants to well we'll
see I had a little um I had a little
picture thing but okay you know what I
I'll
do I'll I'll save this because she
worked so hard because she worked so
hard I
will y like my picture I I do I do like
it I do like it I I was going to problem
no you my
picture okay fine
look
what I I I apologize for my smugness no
it's all right no no cuz like I I did
say like I don't think I need it I'll
just steal it from your Twitter or
whatever but thank you need for stealing
I give this to you all right thank you
so much but anyway you can you can print
it out and then put it in a in a heart
locket necklace neckace oh oh I was
thinking I was going to like print it
life siiz and then you know so there's
like a little bus on my desk or
something oh yeah yeah that's fine too
yeah so like there's a little space here
on my desk so it's going to be like oh
whenever I work like you're going to be
watching over me and
stuff I would love to be there
really oh yeah why am I not there really
yeah well okay thank you so much for
showing up so early welcome to the grand
opening of rainy catron Cafe and who am
I speaking to today and what should I
call
you uh uh please call me um the cutest
uh of them all Miss W
bro well the cute what uh I'm surprised
I was some wanted to say didn't weren't
you tired why are you so
energetic well you know the show must go
on you know let's get into
[Laughter]
that so um what was it the cutest of
them all uh who the cutest of them all
Miss wa wait I'm going to I'm going to
take notes the cutest of them all Miss
dress me properly thank you all right
the cutest of the All Miss Wawa as
briefed in your infation later there are
three options that you can choose from a
is reigning tagonist stepmother B is
kind-hearted Soul who was forced by evil
stepmother to work and C is biological
daughter uh that the stepmother treats
kindly but not the stepdaughter um who
would you like to serve you uh how about
wait which one did you do for narissa uh
I did see the biological daughter that
the St mother just got le as opposed to
how she treats the stepdaughter okay I'm
scared but I'll take a
okay well all right and then that please
enjoy the visit as if it's a normal made
Cafe there will be cute food and drinks
to choose from we hope you have fun at
gr catron Cafe and okay you chose the
rain antagonist stepmother so I will
treat you as if you are my stepdaughter
the cutest of the All Miss waa oh yeah
okay but you're evil right yes I
[Laughter]
know 3 two
1 the cut St them all Miss waa what do
you think you were doing waiting in a
glass window like that you know the cafe
was already open huh uh well I have a
reservation and I thought it would be
appropriate to come at the actual time
excuse me princess yeah but you were
standing right in front of the glass
window and I just wiped it no I didn't
wiped it the worker wiped it and your
presence kind of disturbed the balance
and cleanliness of the glass window cuz
I saw you pressing your face against the
glass window a few times was I
wrong well I was I was just uh laughing
at how little customers you have in here
because it's the grand opening you must
feel special that I am inviting you by
the way what between three of the dishes
which one do you want free
free the aliz the waffle or the ice
cream you have eyes right you see it the
ice
cream the ice cream you do not make fun
of my accent girl you have eyes
right I want I think uh I'll I'll is
there is there mushrooms in
theu no because I know you hate
mushrooms what you actually leaving out
the mushrooms because of me isn't that
kind of nice yes it's actually nice but
it's not me who left it out it's the
cook so I'm not the nice
one ah oh yeah oh oh I know him oh yeah
he's he's he's really sweet yeah yeah so
so so quick quick quick quick quick
quick quick just
pick I please ah okay okay
okay okay if you don't cook it then what
what do you what do you do here I serve
you the cutest of them all is wa you
acute but do you have
brain brain or grain what brain
here is the hold on I will I will zoom
in I will I will I will feed you I will
feed you so open your mouth quickly stop
talking and open your
mouth oh my God she's feating
me you're choking
[Laughter]
me she's trying to kill me she choking
me hey no no slander allow that is a lie
how do you think the Alo rice
taste uh like I kind of
suspicious no the cook cooked it not me
I'm just here to be evil uh and serve
you no it's the cook if you if you say
that you were giving slander to the Cook
no no the food was fine but the service
of inserting it into my mouth was a bit
uh felt a bit dangerous okay yeah just
as plan thank you thank you okay okay
okay so I hope I hope you enjoyed your
visit how was it can I not have a
dessert
[Music]
too I don't know about yeah this this
person I don't know this person already
not fine yeah yeah sure sure sure
because it's the grand opening oh it's
so nice of you thank you so much Evo
[Music]
stepmother yes see I already treat her
nice like this and she's so ungrateful
saying a lot of things talking back to
me oh my
God
wait so uh okay the cutest of them all
Miss Wawa you have any words for my
anniversary uh I'm I'm looking forward
to having you over soon oh yes yes yes
oh yeah yeah I know that I know that
come to me come to me way yeah I know
that okay okay okay yes yes that's all
that's all that's all I to say I I yeah
I I want to spend many many more years
with you way oh do you hear my cat yes I
do they're so cute you can meet them you
can meet them way yes oh my God so
exciting she's she wants to see you yay
I want to see I want to see the flu too
y you'll see all my fls wa wa I I I want
I want to do many many more things with
you I hope you stay in Hollow at least
as long as I stay you have to okay
promise promise course
promise and I wish you lots of uh
success in the upcoming year thank you
and I'm so so proud of you for
everything you've done until now
congratulations on your anniversary way
thank you a I'm so excited to see you me
too
got to I have to clean my apartment for
you I have to make everything
clean okay okay see I broke character
just for you cuz otherwise how was I
going to respond to that yeah I know
character was interesting but I wanted
to hav't talk to you in a while so I
wanted to talk to you
know is it is it uh looking very very
busy today are you having many
reservations for your uh Cafe oh I don't
know it's a pretty much so so not too
crowded not too any
yeah we're going to you're doing twice
right you have like a ID version later
later later at night I so I was so
confused I saw it and I was like wait
wait wait wait in 14 hours did I get it
wrong I thought I was up in an hour it's
the other one yeah oh Nar okay well I
wish you good luck with your with all of
your streams you have so many such a
hard work a about thank you
you I guess I'll go wait how how much
how much does it cost what do I leave in
terms of money um it's for free from for
the cutest of them all what okay 10 out
of 10 I'll review you on Google and Yelp
and everywhere leave a review thank you
yes I will thank you so
much
[Music]
enjoy ah
cute yeah so actually uh the antagonist
um I don't think we are going to be
having uh visitors for quite a bit I
have uh some moments for
talking so for uh the antagonist whole
thing is uh it's my first time to
actually
uh do a bit of that antagonist
stepmother to translate it to indones I
mean not Indonesian to English so I was
kind of like on the Fly thinking of what
kind of personality I should be because
it's kind of different I guess like in
internationally it's a little bit uh I'm
not sure so I was trying to be like I
ended up being like a bit of a mix of a
very strict Asian mother or something I
don't
know
yeah like a like a very strict Asian
mother I don't know step or biological
because yeah it's like the kind of
mother that will that will slap you with
the chanla you
know you are still so nice it's in your
nature it suits me yeah mean Auntie yeah
mean Auntie kind of yeah and then well I
still have to serve the guest so you
know like I know you don't like much
well it's the chef it's not me it's not
me I'm not the I'm not the considerate
one cuz I'm supposed to be the evil
one yeah so well the antagonist is a
little bit different I also figured it
out myself cuz in ID it's normally a
very well-known role but internationally
maybe we got to lean in into something a
little more I'm so
scared consider it evil made you look to
yeah well in the main Cafe you have like
the sun people
right th yeah next time someone ask for
evil throw a drink in their face n okay
okay see like even wa says it's in my
nature so I don't
know yeah like the reality show where
women threw whne in each other so true
so true yes yes yes yeah like latam the
evil Mother exactly doesn't have to be
stepmother I guess like even biological
mother can be
mean very nice um our next guest doesn't
come until like uh 4 minutes I think and
um there's actually a lot of gu so uh
for this uh reservation Cafe I actually
didn't really schedule anyone in so it's
kind of like okay come between the time
this and this this Cafe is supposed to
be open uh because well technically it's
the grand opening but this is like the
special for people the you know the you
know the owner doesn't have to be in the
cafe all the time right but for this
limited time uh from uh
6:45
until like for 2 hours until 8:45 is
until 900 a.m. I will be here just to um
uh greet my friends and let them have
the experience yes so to repeat the of
the first option is antagonist
stepmother which I will kind of edit
to
just no not evil maybe uh what's galak
yeah mother strict mother strict
mother strict mother would be better I
think and B is kindhearted Soul forced
by the evil stepmother this is so long
kindhearted
Soul uh who was yeah forced by the evil
stepmother to help out it's fine maybe
and then biological mother that's the
stepmother treats
kindly a strict Asian mother cuz it's ID
that's where the ID gets uh that's where
the ID is you know is Asian strict Asian
mother strict Asian
mother getting the slipper ready ready
yeah see even like I got the ice cream
you know some people in ID probably
recognize this ice
cream very nice I was uh considering
what kind of ice cream to put in it's
like oh I considered paff or something
but I figured to make it more Indonesian
is like oh maybe the more sea ice cream
you
know yes yes yes yes I see you guys
mentioning the
brand yeah something like that guys the
real CA experience strict Asian
mother yes yes yes you go you go back
from school you you buy it right right
and then you drink
[Music]
it yep and then there's the omarise so
let's have a little counter
actually let's have a little
counter uh oh somebody's already at the
glass door so let's do the counter
later
oh they're going to be here in 1
[Music]
minute oh
hello hello hello
hello okay well they're very punctual
they're like literally waiting by the
glass
window this is so funny because usually
in like the busy tto it's like oh my God
oh my God next oh oh oh hello hello
excuse me is this the careful F yes this
is a cafe and welcome to the grand
opening of rainy catron Cafe and who am
I speaking to today and what should I
call
you hello my name is B acos but you can
call me the greatest of the great king
Bay okay the greatest of the great king
Bay okay let me turn you up for a minute
for a sec all
right and everything should be
[Laughter]
good there we go is that better yes
better all right well the greatest of
the great king Bay as briefed in your
invitation letter there are three
options that you can choose from first
one is antagonist stepmother or strict
Asian mother and she will be strict
towards you and B is kindhearted Soul
who is forced by the evil stepmother to
help out in this Cafe and third is the
biological daughter that the stepmother
treats kindly as opposed to how she
treats the stepdaughter and other than
that please enjoy the visit as if it's a
normal maid Cafe and there will be cute
food and drinks to choose from we hope
you have fun at rainy catron Cafe which
one would you like to
pick Mom is that
you m m you I didn't know you opened up
I didn't know you opened up
restaurant okay you choose a okay the
antagonist St mother
okay
okay hey the greatest of them all a king
be where have you been I saw you in the
glass window why you just not coming you
scared to face me
huh no I was
confused I was going home from school
and then I got hungry because you
wouldn't feed me and then I smelled
something really nice and I walked in
and Bam there you what what are you
doing here Mom I thought you supposed to
be at home and that is slanda I feed you
every day I feed you you think you I
don't Feit you eh then formit everything
you know formit everything you ate this
morning you still dare say I do not Feit
you huh no this is lies oh maybe I I I
didn't I don't remember that I no I
don't get I have I'm hungry mom can I
have some food please okay okay okay
okay ah sh you okay we have three food
here what do you want we have the omu
rice we have the waffle and we have the
ice cream you're so hungry which one do
you
want I want all of them oh why you why
you this child so greedy you always eat
the everything in the house even in the
cupboard you eat everything why you not
get taller why you so
short I'm a growing I'm a growing rat
and besides it's not I I was DNA
my DNA was was was sabotaged by my God
yeah okay maybe you got DNA from your
dead your dead your dead DNA very very
bad okay I understand you want the mall
okay okay I Fe you yeah I want the mall
please okay okay the first one is
Mom can you make sure that but can you
make sure the omu rice is like the the
the omu pot the the egg PT is like
running I also don't want any uh don't
want any broccoli I don't like broccoli
and for the waffles can I get them with
extra cream and extra strawberries
please and also I'll get the ice cream
on my way out because it's going to melt
if I eat it now okay thanks
Mom hey who do you think you are talking
to you are my children just eat L open
that mouth you so that mouth for eating
not for talking you know do you
understand here eat the rice well this
is a C I'm going to go go on Y and give
you a one star R is that what you want
Mom hey you are so ungrateful yeah being
a child you don't know how hard I raise
you yeah from the belly I lay an egg and
then a red comes out how do you think I
feel
man just eat step you're my step mom you
didn't even get bir to me you think you
skipped the hard work you just bam
daughter yeah that's true okay okay okay
I I make the egg right just for you
there okay oh just this time
okay okay this is the
uh and here is the waffle just for you
so so you give good review
okay wait wait wait wait no before Mom
Mom Mom this is this is May Cafe I want
May magic I read on the internet and
that's what you doing at May Cafe so can
you can you give me with the May the May
magic please hey the only magic you will
get is me not whooping your ass after
you asking so much from me you know hey
what do you you give to me I give
everything to you why you not give
everything to me just eat
M no I want
the come on
[Music]
eat M okay and the ice cream the ice
cream ice cream airplane airplane for
[Music]
you enough enough enough you finish the
ice cream no need to eat the stick as
well
okay hey my mouse my mouse
fell my mouth
fell damn she feeding
hard yeah just for you you know see
you're so
ungrateful you're so ungrateful okay
okay God well uh do you have anything to
say about my anniversary cos Bells uh
sorry the Great of the great king B yay
happy anniversary rainy 3 years that's
crazy yay oh my God I'm so happy for you
thank you I want to do something with
you yeah me too I feel like we meet so
many times but we barely do like actual
stream things with each
other oh I think like this is the I
think the only times I I've tolded you
on stream was that one collab and then
there's toes that's it that's it even
though we've hung out I know we H so
many times and we
have we should definitely get something
going I'll I'll I'll talk let yeah let's
talk after this okay yeah I hope you've
enjoyed the three years
here and here's to many more yay thank
you thank you for inviting me yay give
me five out of five review okay okay
yeah I'll give you I'll give
you yeah okay can I borrow your laptop
momam I don't have yeah sure for doing
homework only
[Music]
okay
okay you you send the password to me
okay yeah yeah yeah I text you the
password yeah okay okay the password is
uh our the password is our street name
okay oh I don't know that okay okay
bye-bye bye bye thanks FR love you bye
[Music]
[Laughter]
byebye all right the strict mother the
strict mother stck is working good we we
doing very well the password is not 1111
it's the street where we
live this is working way too well
oh my gosh what if it's what if in the
cafe
I what if in the cafe I I satel any you
know Christmas
songs but it will be copyright so
no just just put on the same Christmas
song over and
[Music]
over you I thought you a street name
like your gang name no no it's like the
actual Street where we live you know cuz
like mothers are just like you know
setting whatever they want as their
password free use Christmas songs
n it's the Christmas
[Applause]
bells it's uh it's like punishment for
yeah punishment from the mother
torturing with music well I'm a music
person so that's that's kind of thing
right you know well next guest uh we
have 5 minutes until the next guest and
then I literally have no idea when the
other guests are coming cuz they did
really save up the time maybe I will um
maybe I will
say
anybody cuz one I know one person is
coming wait why why do I look so sad
I don't want to look sad okay I'm not
sad
anymore anyone want to come in 5
[Music]
and and I
forgot and
950 what's what's that in Japanese
[Music]
I'm asking if anybody can feel the time
slot for 40 and
because because I think this is the
perfect ratio you
know yes maybe you will need GTO my eyes
for N I think this is
fine
yes it's 9:30 a.m. JP right now yep yep
yep normally I just like say everything
in 9:30 because I mean not 9:30 at like
jst time because it's easier for
everyone because I don't know it just
seems to be the time that everyone's
familiar
[Laughter]
with very nice so we already have two
people
choosing antagonist and then C B is the
one who
is who hasn't been chosen yet I'm
curious about the popularity like at the
end you know oh I said I wanted
to I said I wanted to make a food
counter said I wanted to make a food
[Music]
counter food counter can you guys help
me remember who ordered
what no one wants the catron protagonist
yeah I wonder why H could it be a
cultural thing or could it just be that
people want to get yelled at
secretly
including dessert narissa
ice omor
[Music]
Kiara maybe they want to be the syron
protagonist I guess so instead of
instead of instead of having the
protagonist talk to them they want to be
the protagonist and get yelled
at yes yes yes very nice very
nice andisa took the waffle you got the
promote option be more so true so
true okay well let's let's let's let's
let's list
it next guest uh comes in 3 minutes so
we still have
time we still have
time test okay there we
[Music]
go
oh
y there's there's somebody that's going
to fit
the
40 so we're
[Music]
okay all
right so what was it count there for
food um
omiz
waffle uh ice
cream so om ice
[Music]
is Waffle is
one right so is this correct Omar is
Wawa and Bay waffle is narissa and Bay
ice cream is narissa and
[Music]
B ice cream three ah w I wanted the ice
cream as
[Music]
well
okay this looks great and then what else
do we want
[Music]
to okay counter oh yeah and counter of
the
modes mom one
two um Pro tag is zero and
then um biod
daughter
one biod
daughter all right this looks correct
right biohazard
daughter
oh I wonder where I should put
it oh maybe like
this just small would' be good oh what
oh
hello hello wow you surprised me I
didn't see you there I know I was here
ever since you said biohazard
something biohazard will you caught me
hi hey welcome to the grand opening of
rain catron Cafe who am I speaking to
today and what should I call
you uh my name is Oro crony from Hello
Life English but um should I go by a
specific name for this case if you want
to I I would like to go by um
marabel
marabel what it sounds like a royal name
you know all all okay Mar Bill well Lady
Mary Bell as briefed in your invitation
letter there are three options that you
can choose from and also by the tally on
the upper left first one is the
antagonist stepmother or strict Asian
mother it's all in one package she will
be evil towards you and B is the um
stepdaughter who was um forced by the
evil stepmother to help out this Cafe oh
my gosh so and then the three is the
biological daughter like the stepmother
is nice to you but you want to help the
stepdaughter yeah so uh which one do you
want to
choose uh I would like to choose option
A oh my gosh popular choice other than
that please enjoy the visit as if it's a
normal made Cafe there will be cute food
and and drinks to choose from we hope
you have fun at rain is in interon Cafe
okay lady marel your service starts
now okay thank you thank you so
much Mary Bell what do you think you're
doing you don't tell me you don't say
good morning to your mother when you
pass by you just stay there where is
your
respect mother mother I'm already grown
up you don't need to yell at me like
that let's be civil here but see feel
see feel that mouth is for eating not
for talking who are you already talking
back to me and how old are you you just
a little
child I am not a little child uh mother
uh my name is marabel and I am about
60 9 years old yeah if you're 69 years
old I have 69,000 years old you little
child so shush you are here for a reason
right you want to eat the food yeah
that's why you're here huh I mean I'm
not really feeling hungry stepmother but
if you really um want me to eat your
delicious food mayhaps I will you D
talking back to me who thought you that
who thought you that mommy I'm not
really hungry or something did huh
mother did mother did oh no no no that
is just not true why you now lying to
everybody who taught you to lie maybe
your stupid father yeah that's why he
left I don't know he left to swimming in
the water and never came back
uh mother mother I thought you pushed
father off that Cliff before no he's
swimming and never came back okay what I
okay yeah so which one do you want omu
rice waa or ice
cream um those are very delicious
options but are there anything else
anything else anything else you looking
for other food I am looking for your
respect I don't see it anywhere so just
choose off from the tree okay um yeah
I'll just go for
um Omar eyes that looks good okay okay
Omar Omar yeah yeah yeah yeah simple
enough simple enough this the cook
already cooked this for you so if you SL
give slander to the food you are not
slandering me you are slandering the
innocent people at the back of the
kitchen you know yeah so just uh eat
okay okay um you know it looks great and
all but uh it's looking a little cold uh
can you maybe microwave it I'm not
insulting the people it's just that the
food's a little cold yeah it's okay
maybe some people with a cold de cold
demeanor like you maybe you like cold
food
yeah stepmother I think that is a little
uncult for I would like to have a word
with you some other time the M is for
eating no for talking okay n just just I
feed you okay oh
okay oh oh yum oh oh is it delicious is
it
delicious uh I
mean yeah yes very good that's the right
answer right answer yeah yeah use a
little more salt and pepper but it's
okay you know that's good yeah it's okay
the salt is in your blood yeah you will
get used to it okay and anything else
you want my daughter you want a waffle
and uh you know yeah I know in your
report Cat last time you got see but
yeah I'm being very gracious gracious
today so if you want waffle or ice cream
I will give
you well you know I I would like to have
um waffles for dessert okay good good
good okay okay this waffle uh very nice
with berries and stuff like that
yeah oh wait that was
[Music]
so yeah yeah uh yeah I hope it's okaya
for your taste buts I don't know what
you eat in the streets but uh this is
very nice um I my streets are the castle
thank you very much okay your Castle I
don't know I have been isied into uh
being a villainous in the other world
and I live in a castle and I'm rich and
they give me a free massage and all that
you wouldn't understand stepmother Mar
I'll invite you yes marel you hit your
head where I take you to the hospital
um my hospital is the castle actually so
if you would like I can call the Family
Doctor oh okay okay okay yeah yeah yeah
whatever you say okay uh do you uh have
do you have any message uh to me uh for
my anniversary
marel well um you see I would like to
say happy anniversary even though our
father's missing at the
moment for searching milk at the bottom
of the ocean or something but yes
through
through but you know if you'd like I
would like to invite you to my castle
one day and um
my my servants will serve you very
kindly over there unlike I mean like
what you have done with me
here okay okay okay okay yeah acceptable
acceptable so will you give this Cafe
five out of five
refie
um I
mean usually I wouldn't but since it's
you mother and I'm
feeling kind today sure okay yeah that's
the that's the right answer you are so
you are so smart sometimes you Mar Bell
okay thank you so much I uh by the way
I'm looking forward yeah for real to you
you know because uh we met last time
right so let's let's you know maybe
collab together or maybe like spend some
time together okay as rain and not the
evil antagonist okay oh where's Raine
yeah Raine is lost yeah May yeah he she
hit her head and maybe I don't know
she's sleeping right now oh really wow
she hit her head really quickly cuz I
was talking to her just fine about 5
minutes ago yeah I know right I don't
know maybe that girl just it's kind of
dumb sometimes it's okay yeah okay thank
you so much for uh coming yeah Mar B I
hope you have a good day okay and please
spread the word to your uh family and
your uh you know WhatsApp group or uh
your I don't know people in college or
people at your work or people at uh the
streets is so F okay like the castle the
castle the castle Yeah the castle yeah
okay okay okay okay well happy
anniversary don't be too sad about our
father that you happened to push off a
cliff oh no I've been so happy yeah what
sorry happy oh yeah set yeah and then
yeah oh no wonder no wonder you applied
for the insurance about a few years ago
okay I understand now anyway great
anniversary thank you thank you love
love okay love love bye-bye
[Music]
bye-bye
we spent almost 10 minutes talking what
the I don't know what that
[Laughter]
was why the mom so popular I don't
know I guess there is a reason the mom
is
popular Mone well um after this we got
uh oh somebody's already at the
door yeah by the way it's okay to talk
for 10 minutes obviously somebody's at
the door I'm also I'm
drinking I can hear the knocks
already I don't know when she's coming
in
though yeah everybody coming I can start
anytime the guest comes in but yeah I
wonder what the next guest we'll pick oh
hello hello is the store open right now
oh hey welcome to the grand opening of
rain Cafe who am I speaking to today and
what should I call you um you are
speaking to Iris from H live English but
uh since this is a kind of like a
roleplay Cafe I assume um I want to be
called Ojos Sama today
as briefed in your invitation letter
there are three options that can you can
choose from first one is rainy
antagonist stepmother or strict Asian
mother B is the kind-hearted Soul who
was bullied by the stepmother and she's
going to ask for your help and C is the
biological daughter who wants to put an
end to the conflict between the
stepmother and the
stepdaughter um other than that please
enjoy the visit as if it's a normal made
Cafe there will be cute food and drinks
to choose from and we hope you have fun
at the Rainy catron Cafe um who would
you like to choose ooh wait I'm a little
bit confused about the biod daughter
one no it's just no it's because it's
just too long if I say biological
daughter it just means it's not
biohazard it's like a the biological
can't what you mean but like wait so
does that mean I will be talking to the
biological daughter of the evil
stepmother is that is that you if you
choose see um you are like a guest and
then the biological daughter aka me will
talk to you like uh oh like here's by
the way like you know maybe like uh by
some chance like they were like oh my
gosh what should I do you know cuz the
stepmother have been like bullying the
St blah blah blah you know something
like that ah this is hard I'm really
debating on the mom and the biod
daughter right now daughter cuz mom is
like you know like you know she's going
to be so mean to you you know I kind of
want to be be I kind of want to be you
know in that position once in a while
but at the same time at the same time I
already two people already requested or
two or three people three people
actually I haven't edited it right okay
in that case in that case I guess we'll
go with the biod daughter oh my
goodness I know I was just thinking like
the step mother like yelling at you and
calling you Ojos at the same time would
be so freaking funny yeah I know that's
what I was thinking too when I said Ojos
sama okay you're going to go with the
biod daughter uh I don't know if you if
you don't mind doing mom again I don't
mind Mom
either cuz um the customer is king
[Music]
So oh daughter okay antagonist
antagonist okay
okay
this is hard
okay why did you make you why why did
you say you want to be called oama is
your life not oama
enough I always bit you and feed you
every
dayama you watch too much anime okasama
I am your mother mother m a d e r
right you watch a lot of anime too don't
you okasama no you want you want to be
called oama Ojo Ojo you know Ojo in
Indonesia means don't you know means
don't I'm I'm being for real I'm being
for real are you are real oh okay well I
mean don't is a is is just a word of
rejection but I'm sure you know you
always reject my kindness every single
day right mother your kindness your
kindness you go home from school will
lock yourself in your room watching
anime all day only going out to bring
dinner the bring the dinner you bring to
your room and what you make me wash the
dish and everything you don't know
gratitude yeah and you dare step your
foot inside your foot inside this Cafe
huh I'm so sorry mother I didn't think
that you that's what you thought of me
every single day um I was I was just
thought I shouldn't be in you know like
I shouldn't be in front of your face cuz
I I know you don't like seeing me every
single day and so tell me tell me tell
me what you did tell me what's what's
your Twitter I want your face hold on
you want my face now every single day
you always say I don't even want to look
at
you and even cooking for me you always
say it's such a pain in the butt yeah
but I cook you real fot I see see so
don't complain I cook you real food if I
cook you poison then you
complain I'm so hungry okas you're so
hungry you have the dog ball over there
you just go
eat okay okay I I I want some some
motherly food mother I want I want to
feel that warm motherly love through
your food today okay okay you want
motherly food there are three foods here
yeah you have the omo rice the waffle
and the ice cream the ice cream I bought
from the supermarket but yeah just for
you like I give you yeah so which one do
you want is this free mother yeah free
just like you fre loading in my house
what's the
difference that's true oh in that case I
would like Mother's omur soup please
okay I want my Ur you want anything to
have a yes please I'd love a a personal
message okay good to know but I will not
do it yeah you won't do it I was just
asking I was just asking here's your yum
yum yum
yum oh is so good mother oh stop
stuffing it in my face I can't fit all
of
it okay enough that's that looks like
enough food okay uh do you want anything
else full I'm full m oh I don't I'm I
think the race is kind of still like you
know it's still not hasn't really gone
down yet okay maybe CU maybe your your
stomach so slow like your head I don't
know what I did to get to raise a
daughter like this oh my God like your
daughter yeah like like your daughter re
your daughter re E I am the daughter of
you know the a father that you loved so
much right mother who father who I don't
remember such a guy in my
life rather than talking about this
father father I don't know you see you
see your friend to the neighbor the
neighbor child re is she's so smart why
you not like her how did you end up
raising me then mother uh that's why I
also wonder myself how did I raise you
to be a daughter like this come on me
how did you end up having to raise me
like I mean if if father was never a
thing then I don't know I also don't
know did I end up being in your hands
it's the universe mystery I don't know
maybe the gods give me a curse I don't
know well you know no matter what you
tell me I still know that deep down
you're still so kind and for raising me
and even if I didn't have a rich father
you decided to you know take me in your
loving arms um through divine
intervention okay okay yes um mother
like what do you I have a sister right
what's sister oh I don't am I the only
child oh oh your sister the bio the bio
the bio daughter why why the bio
daughter you talk about daugh no like
you know you always treat me like this
but I always see you you know saying
such nice things to bio daughter yeah
cuz biod daughter different bio daughter
so smart un like you what is the
difference though I try so hard to be
like biod daughter cuz CU you you you're
not biod daughter she's biodegradable
you
are Mommy I'll try my best to study I'll
get straight A's if I get straight A
will you stop you know being so mean to
me mother yeah proof first talk later
okay okay mother I'll study hard okay
did I ask you if you had any words for
um for my
anniversary oh for for mother's
anniversary yes um thank you so much for
raising me these past 3 years mother um
you're
welcome and you know it's been such a
great you know you you've been here for
3 years already you've been a stepmom
for 3 years already I don't know how you
handle it I don't know
either okay thank you so much my the OM
was delicious oh thank you thank you
okay my my daughter my daughter how is
your health doing by the way my daughter
oh you're oh you're curious about my
health oh thank you um yeah it's doing
great thanks to Mother's uh cooking and
you know even though sometimes you tend
to you know sneak in some eye drops in
my drinks I know that because sometimes
I get some really upset stomach days um
I still hang on because I know that deep
down you still love me yeah just asking
just asking for a small talk but it's
okay yeah uh hopefully we can we can do
something okay together okay yeah of
course let me know anytime yes yes okay
thank you for coming to the cafe please
rate 55 yeah thank you yeah yeah yel yel
yeah yeah definitely I need your
business needs to Boom for yeah so more
more pocket money for you okay yeah yeah
more money you for you more money for me
thank so true so true okay all righty
then bye mother byebye bye mother
[Music]
[Laughter]
bye-bye oh my God the mother is
popular um let me edit so mother is four
ready what she want
omarise did I count it
correctly is the alarice
updated is my best roll M
[Music]
for very nice bio
daughter very nice nice the calls are
actually long yeah cuz it's like a
pretty relaxed call um I don't really
worry about time slots and it's not
really like a crowded call-in or
something but it would be nice it's nice
for a change it's nice to be this way so
I get to spend more time with the people
biodegradable I don't even know where
that came
[Laughter]
from but yeah I resist is
great I love how we never sort of break
character try guil Tri the next customer
make them feel fresher to pick b h i
don't want I don't want to I mean if
they don't want to pick B
then it's all right narissa picked the
biod
daughter and that and I guess everybody
saw the mom and they wanted the
mom they mama I think I've warmed up to
the evil mother I'm afraid to see how
well you do if someone else picks
it warming
up yeah yeah but I think it's fine
La if there can anyone if there's anyone
who wants to come around 9:55 please or
something but if you know we're still
waiting for people in the shop so I
don't know what we can talk about you
are oh so true I'm a mother figure
remember when I just debuted people are
just like oh oh Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
but then um oh it turns out that rain is
not mommy well it just needed 3 years
for me to cultivate that mummy nature
you know it's probably like a different
mummy than you're probably used to but
you know a mommy is a
mommy I think they were saying that a
little differently I mean see you can't
beat choosers you know a mommy is a
mommy and dad is forever
swimming dad's then the bottom of the
ocean oh no we got we got we got some
lore
here they need a stepmother voice pack
yeah see this is what I'm doing with
this anniversary thing cuz like the
stepmother is mostly ID content before
now but I want to try to bring the
stepmother in the global
scene
in the global scene you
know yeah dad had an accident an
accident is when something bad happens
but it's not anybody's fault yeah
International stepmother and if it
proves that the stepmother is a hit you
know not a hit with the sandals but like
an actual hit amongst the people then
maybe we can pitch in some yo you know
this whole stepmother thing seems pretty
popular maybe we can have that you
know dad died of natural causes but yeah
also the bgm is really chill right I
really like the bgm if you can't hear it
I hope you can hear it if you if I can't
then if you can't then that
sucks is the customer stepdaughter in
accident too well I don't
know yeah that's just swimming no big
deal so the lore of the stepmother now
is so I guess we have to change it
into we have to change it into I'm not
sure
H so I think a guest is supposed to come
in 5 minutes it's just so it's just that
right after crony it was Iris and
Iris and Iris yeah basically back to
back so we have uh a little bit of a
free time and well we wait I'll just get
the I'll just get their profile
picture u i don't get
hi I'm very happy but I'm really nervous
because what if I eventually have to
speak in Japanese I'm not sure I think I
will speak in Japanese have
to I'm not sure I hope not what am I
going to do if they pick if they pick I
will speak in japang English I
[Music]
think but that's for future raining to
worry
[Music]
about hold on hold on give me a
sec
e no stupid and the stupid trying to
kill my Cafe my Cafe is driving it won't
be dead oof we back we back we
back sorry sorry it's not my end
[Music]
we're
back but anyways um I got the picture
for the next
[Music]
person so it should be
good yeah I invited some of my friends
but it's also kind of weird because I
know that I had a lot of collabs in July
back in Japan but aside from that I
don't really have that many collabs
huh H so I talk to them and like and
it's so funny cuz like with ba also I've
hung up with her like quite a bunch but
we never really did any like actual like
yo let's collab and even like the
collabs that we did it's just that we oh
we just like happened in to be in the
same place you know or something like
that yeah some of these have been
dormant for too long dormant that
word yes you have a secret project with
Rissa yeah we
talked we talk for a while and um for a
bit and we decided to do on a project
together probably hard to um do it for
the end of the year but maybe early next
year for sure for
sure yeah mostly in Japan and then Vivid
happened so true so true but
yes let's go excited for it
[Music]
oh there's somebody somebody's at the
glass door I wonder if I can use English
for this maybe I can
English
uh please come
in please come in you can come
[Music]
in oh hello hello
hello
hello welcome to the grand opening of
rain cetron
Cafe Hora Cafe one person one one one
person yes yes um what's your name in
the
reservation yeah uh I'm
Taki okay
takui uh what do you want me to call you
today Lou okay or yes Louie okay wow so
kind Lou so um welcome to the grand
opening of L Hira Cafe and this is like
a ma Cafe but the roles are
different first we have rainy strict
Asian
mother Mar okay yes evil mother fat
mother mhm and then second is I'm very
kind but my mother always bullying me so
I ask your help and C is the biod
daughter I'm daughter but I want my
stepmother to stop bullying my step
sister yes okay other than that please
enjoy the visit as if it's a normal M
Cafe there is food and enjoy who do you
want me to act as uh f is
recommend recommend uh recommend is
stepmother is most
popular uh right now because h a
little they like to
be so eil Mom most
popular I see
okay today is
one one first one you want strict Asian
mother oh my
God hey why are you like other Holo
member you atama okasi you weird weird
yes yes yes oh my God how did I raise
you I you come from my stomach o i I'm n
I'm ninin and I give birth to you while
you become like
this
oh uh ma
yes I want
to uh I
am I'm
hungry oh my God but because she is so
honest she is maybe a little smart yeah
she is very very polite also you are
very uh
SE so I feed you with food
okay which one do you want omu rice
waffle or ice
cream
uh
or everything oh my God all of them why
are you so so greedy people pick one why
you pick all who thought you to do that
so hungry mother please everything my
God please make me make for me you act
like I put you in jail you wake up every
morning I feed you breakfast lunch
dinner I feed you you still ask for more
you are so greedy oh my God okay
okay cannot be helped which one first
which one first uh Omar rice okay Omar
rice do you want me to uh write
something oh yes please right the hot
Mark okay no I just asking I will not
write I just asking just asking
okay please say for me ah okay for my
daughter because uh she is
polite thank you very kind
mother okay okay good and then uh
waffle or ice
cream uh waffle okay waffle yeah
waffle here ah waffle
ah
ah and please say for me uh okay uh
my yes yes
ah oh very first fast to eat okay yes
eat you can eat the plate if you want
eat the plate oh
please say for
[Applause]
me okay oh good good good yes yes see
this daughter is so polite yeah unlike
the other daughter you are polite you
are good okay okay last is ice cream yes
you want ice cream here yes please
stopping the chocolate uh no
okay eat
eat
yes okay okay enough enough enough
enough no greedy no greedy uh I'm still
so hungry you still so hungry
yes uh then uh maybe you go uh you go to
the street and eat street food
okay
okay and free please U make make for me
the Indonesian for
okay it's hard yeah normally I am eil
but because you are so polite what what
Indonesian food do you
want uh in a popular one okaya I make
you instant noodle Okay C instant noodle
instant noodle oh okay okay
okay okay uh pretend I don't have
instant noodles
uh I said I will transfer it directly to
your stomach with my
power
please and okay
[Music]
uh this come mother oh okay oh I'm so
old cooking instant noodle make me die
okay
you H oh make your dye yes yes because
I'm old oh my God oh my God but it's
okay it's okay yeah you you are young
it's okay mother okay okay so I will
feed you in tight your
stomach yes that is the instant
noodle I hope delicious
delicious thank you m are you still
hungry
yes yeah uh okay you can eat uh the leaf
in the back you know there is plants and
leaf you can eat Leaf
yes
T yes uh plants plants plants Kusa you
can eat the Kusa e it's not full and not
make me full okay okay then what do you
want I want I want want to eat beef or
pork okay then you go to the
farm farm yes you go to the uh Farm guys
you go to the farm in japanes you go to
the
nojo nojo yes you go to the nojo and eat
pork it's a
low low pork right yes like sushi like
sushi like no it's make me stomach oh my
god mother why you say like
that like big pork Sushi delicious in
the nojo oh my God natural fresh you
know not natural fresh it make make me
stomach egg oh mother oh if you stomach
egg you can come here and I give you ice
cream ice
cream make make me more stomach cake
right yes yes if you need stomach egg
maybe you need to eat more you know
stomach and N because if you eat more
yes uh mommy love me a lot so
IU want to do I right yes yes uh I love
you so I take you to the nojo to eat a
pork
Sushi enough I I'm already full okay
thank you okay I hope you have fun do
you have any words for me for my
anniversary
uh H congratulations L Senai I love I
love you so much and I want
to uh I want to meet
again yes in Japan or Indonesia so if I
go to the Indonesia please guide for me
thank you yes I will thank you so much
thank you bye bye mother bye-bye bye-bye
have fun Sushi bye-bye no sushi no
okay uh don't you guys just want
to Pork sushi is so
delicious
[Music]
yummy yeah you go to the farm you go to
the nojo and you eat the pork Sushi and
the cow Sushi fresh fresh from the Nate
natural
source new
met I'd eat it if you use the antagonist
voice I don't know maybe that's like
special treatment for for Louie in a way
like I
think in a way I was more
um in a way I was kinder to
her I was kinder to her than the others
but I did not tell anyone to eat pork
sushi so I don't know if at the end of
the day like I'm meaner or more I don't
know wait I'm going to
I'm going to
ask um I'm going to
[Music]
chat okay I'm just going to message A
bunch of
[Music]
people
everyone love is heavy in the belly
short see like I will feed them see no
matter how much mean things I say I can
still feed them you
know very
nice what is the magic to transport food
directly for your stomach asking for a
friend pork Sushi is the real biod
daughter would you guys eat pork Sushi
or is that like
dangerous but you gave Louis extras
while everyone else just got kicked out
well I guess so but I don't
know if it's raw Park you would probably
die okay okay okay okay probably not
that's just asking for parasites okay
okay daring aren't we we are pretty
daring I I think we have some time to
rest for a little bit I'm going to take
a
drink I'm going to make a poll for you
guys which food is your favorite cuz
like if I ask you guys which roll do you
want I know the
answer uh omiz waffle or
[Music]
popsicle yes yes
yes which one if you go to rain and
catron Cafe which one would you get you
can tell like there's no pancakes cuz
waffles are just straight up
better never tried omiz but it looks
really good it's pretty
nice yes yes I'll come in shortly okay
Callie seems to be
coming I'm going
to cuz like a bunch of people like a
bunch of people did say yes yes but I
have a
feeling I have a feeling they fell
asleep like trust me I would fall asleep
if that were
me but yeah we do have the nighttime
slot but that's kind of for like the
Indonesian people it would be in full
Indonesian cuz it's really rare I feel
like I've been getting
requests uh for doing like a full
Indonesian stream from like the ID Bros
so far I've been doing like a lot of
mixed but I feel like you know this
whole rain 3rd anniversary is has quite
a bit of what people have been asking
for you know but um so I thought to
myself aside from the 3D ring fit people
have been asking about that
actually uh
[Music]
but oh Kell's giving me an actual
picture holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
people who are like
instantly but yeah I think uh ID Bros
they are going to be excited for this
one because I've been showing this
character for a long time oh udai is 50%
so strong waffles a close 40%
though yes yes yes so aside from um
aside from Cali kiar send a picture and
the other I can just
steal well I want to spill cuz the
stepdaughter is the stepdaughter we
haven't picked we haven't picked the
stepdaughter at all I want to play a
little bit of the stepdaughter while I
wait for cie I guess hold on oh [\h__\h]
Callie's in the Machi so maybe after
cie I see cie in the glass window just
looking hello cie I can com in anytime
if you
[Music]
want
Hello
hello hello and welcome to the grand
opening of rainy catron Cafe who am I
speaking to today and what should I call
you me and a song it's me Mory kipy from
Hol live English myth I'm the
hardworking Shinigami of Hol live
hi you can call me you can call me cie
because I feel like I feel like you call
me cie more than myy it's always a it's
always a 5050 what are they going to
call me Mory or C so yeah I'm I'm the
I'm the Cali type of person like are you
a Cali person are you a myy person I'm a
Cali person I mean I'm a myy person
personally but I can I can understand
where the Cali comes
from I don't know how I started calling
you Callie cie but yeah it just has a
cute feeling to it anyway
congratulations congrats on on your
anniversary your three has it been 3
years I know it doesn't feel like 3
years oh that's crazy I mean you guys
you guys came around pretty soon after
us so I mean I mean it it feels like
it's been a long time for both of us you
know yeah we like the same year right
did we in the same year yeah you guys
just came like um like a like three or
four months after after you guys right
yeah mhm so we've been we've been around
a similar amount of time I guess yeah
true true
true though oh thank you it's very nice
to see you here thank you so much for
agreeing to be here yeah happy to be
here I'm in a straight jacket right now
I'm I'm forcing myself not to not to
play stardew and take a break so my
hands are a little tied but I'm excited
to push my face into some waffles or
omise or popsicle I'm excited yay okay
well as brief in your invitation letter
there are three options uh that you can
choose from on like who to serve you a
is the reigning antagonist stepmother or
strict Asian mother and you will be the
stepdaughter she will be evil towards
you or be rainy kind-hearted Soul who
was forced by the evil stepmother to
help out in this Cafe and you are a
guest and see Rainy biod daughter AKA
biological daughter that the stepmother
treats kindly as opposed to how she
treats the stepdaughter she might ask
you for help to you know resolve this
conflict oh biod daughter sounds like an
SCP or like aary horror creature um okay
you know I was thinking about this and I
think the mom sounds really cool because
I heard some of how you were talking and
it reminded me of like playdates that
I'd have with my friends who had like
that kind of mom I guess so sounded just
like that but I see that the
stepdaughter hasn't been chosen yet so
I'm kind of tempted to try that instead
oh finally the stepdaughter gets
chosen normally in soap this kind of
soap Opress the stepdaughter would have
been the protagonist so in a way you'll
be the
protagonist of this Cafe so you're the
only protagonist of this Cafe so far oh
cool I'm the main character my dream
other than that well please enjoy the
visit as if it's a normal made Cafe
there will be cute food and drinks to
choose from the drinks not so much the
food maybe we hope you have fun at rainy
catron Cafe and I will be
Callie's um I will be just like a
stepdaughter who's working here to serve
you yay wow okay I'm excited I don't
know what to expect I I'll do my best to
to be cordial and polite and me too it's
my first time doing this today this okay
cool well I'm hungry um hi what would
you like to order we have Omar we have
waffles and we have ice cream M let's
see I'm thinking waffles waffles okay um
anything you want um for your waffles
any modifications anything you don't
want oh man okay I want I want whipped
cream and I want ice cream and I want
strawberries and blueberries and rhubarb
and I want orange and Mandarin and pear
slices and mango and cherries and then
also some caramel as well as some
chocolate syrup and sprinkles on top can
you remember all
that yes I think I can I'll I'll I'll be
okay I I'll go shortly I'll tell can
chicken with those waffles too chicken
and waffles together is really good yeah
yeah sure sure sure I can do that oh I
love that y yeah okay
wow okay okay wow
I feel so bad she's so she looks like
she's trying really hard but she's
really flustered I can kind of relate to
that relatable for I'm sorry I didn't
know you to be a come back right there
the the food Gamba
Gamba durian no
durian sorry sorry sorry please can I
can
I oh no it's stinky
it's it's okay it's good to try new
things don't worry about it I'll take a
bite I'm sure that it's delicious it's
just a little stinky that's
all
okay my my mother just scolded me
because I couldn't get the order right
oh Pats your shoulder it's okay it's
it's okay to make mistakes we all make
them I make them a lot of them also so I
understand here P you I can help you if
you want you want some help in the
kitchen I do but if my mother sees us
she will beat me with the
sandals oh no not the sandals ah
go I mean then then I will shield you
with my body I don't mind getting beaten
by a sandal I've never gotten beaten by
a a sandal before um by a by an evil
stepmother that sounds kind of
interesting like something that everyone
should experience once in their life so
oh really you would take that for me but
what if what if my mother bends you from
visiting this Cafe because of me well
that's okay because I'll have tasted the
most delicious waffles in the world and
helped the prettiest girl ever you're
too sweet how can I ever repay your
kindness oh with
waffles
yeah I will cook waffles for you every
day please save me from my evil
mother okay we can ride away in my in my
Lamborghini I don't have a Lamborghini I
have like an old Jeep we can ride away
in my old Jeep oh damn it oh yes yeah
your Jeep would be so nice yeah there's
enough there's enough room in the back
to store all the waffles and we can run
away together and I'll I'll take you
away from this place are you sure it's
okay what if our mother what if my
mother chases us then then we'll throw
waffles at her okay I I trust you just
trust me thank you that is called
kidnapping it's not kidnapping I'm I'm
helping like she's in a bad situation
it's like it's like saving it's that's
this is like good in that case yeah no
kidnap no kidnap you can't solve all
problems with waffles yes you can well
my mother is distracted let's let's head
to the door and and and let's go get get
on the Jeep oh but what about my sister
though my sister is nice oh I mean uh I
don't know I I feel like though she's
probably in a good situation like your
mom really likes her a lot right so
she's got like a good thing going maybe
we should just leave her here oh I I
think so to I hope she doesn't miss me
should I leave her my contact number
yeah just write letters oh easy letters
would be so good you are so smart I will
I will keep feeding you waffles are you
sure you don't want anything else can I
get the popsicle and Omar rice for the
road of course of course I will I will
steal as many I will steal the whole the
whole freezer for
you let's go okay maybe we should invite
your sister because we have too much
food here and I feel kind of bad that
we're just leaving with all the food
it's no good oh okay you shouldn't hit
people with sandals that's a punishable
crime punishable by all your food being
stolen and you left to be alone with no
children yeah I will I will I will text
her and she can also help bring the
freezer and stuff and the food and my
mother's Cafe will be bankrupt because
she will have no food and she deserves
it yay we'll start our own Cafe that
sounds fun yes thank you so much we can
start our our own family Cafe that's so
good anyways here's your ice
[Music]
cream wow wo Yum Yum
Yum wow here waffles again's go WAFF who
oh man it's delicious but I'm getting so
full okay okay you have to you have to
be full because you're going to be
driving
right yeah that's right leave it to me
I'm I'm a great driver I'm one of the
only licensed members to drive an Ian I
think let's go let's go leave it to me
before we leave for the Jeep is there
anything you would like to say to uh for
my an anniversary I mean you actually
did at the beginning but yeah I I do I
want to say um that you are an inspiring
person Renee and so cool you have you're
doing so many things I really really
respect it like you make you make music
you do like originals and covers and
your voice is really great and you also
stream and you think of new ideas to
like entertain everybody and I think
that's really cool because a lot lot of
times these days I'm just kind of like
oh play game Play game but then I see
like the creative stuff you're doing and
I'm like man I should try to be more
creative so you're literally very
inspiring and um I just wanted to let
you know I'm very very proud of you and
happy to call you a friend aw you
inspire me too in lots of ways we should
do that thing that we've been wanting to
do yeah yeah yeah we wanted to do some
things together and I I think that we
should let's do that okay yes of course
it's a bit of busy time right now with
all of the with some things going on
like this is a little bit busy we can do
some early next year maybe yeah when the
New Year strikes we'll do something cool
together mhm okay thank you so much
Callie for coming to the cafe I hope you
have a great day no that was very fun I
had a great time I'll catch you later
Renee and happy anniversary thank you so
much bye-bye bye-bye peace
peace it's
[Music]
cute a that was wholesome finally
stepdaughter gets a you know gets the
show if she chose uh if she chose the
other one I was going to give you guys
an example of stepdaughter um I kind of
winged it actually but that seems like
it's going in a good direction that's a
wholesome kidnapping so true so true I
don't even know the counters anymore I
think I'm like
missing peace Kelly y p Papa kidnapped
though well it's for a good cause okay
like you know she's getting out of a uh
abusive household she wants the waffles
right and she got the ice
cream I don't even keep track of the
tallies right now it's um it's not
accurate but
whatever the ELO but the mother still oh
well because this is hypothetical
scenario well after Cali gets off the
call they're all back in their initial
position it's called Child Protection
Service so true so true 544 for
[Music]
food 544 I'll I'll Trust you guys I
don't even know
anymore she's like the prince charming
to my Cinderella you know she's like
let's alope with me you know and stuff
was a lot of waffles in a fridge full of
popsicles so
true thanks Kelly and Iris yeah was
great Lou added a few new entries yeah
cuz I didn't even have like the H
me I didn't have the instant noodles I
just teleported it to her stomach and
then well she um she indirectly gave
birth to the new innovation that is pork
and cow beef sushi well beef sushi isn't
really
new
I don't know about pork though I haven't
seen pork
Sushi she ordered like off the menu like
a real customer like a real
regular I've seen beef sushi but not
pork actually so you guys ever seen pork
Sushi H maybe there's a reason for that
I guess so kind of like chicken
chicken's kind of no good when eaten not
when eating raw but I've seen some
rawish chicken being served maybe
they're special not
sure yeah there sounds like there's an
open market yeah straight up from the
noo AKA
[Laughter]
Farm yo I feel like the yo I swear to
God these people are freaking sleeping
they missing the opening of
the but it's okay yo like if I were not
the owner of this CET I would be the one
sleeping but you guys are not sleeping
I'm so happy that you guys showed up to
the open opening of the cafe and I'm
also very very grateful to the people
who showed up even though it's so early
somebody
even stood in front of the cafe even
though it wasn't opening time yet it's
evening for me perfect time also yeah
I'm going to try to message some
people
uh I'm going to try to message some
[Music]
people are you
awake
[Music]
are you awake these messages are just
are you
awake it's 2:30 I should be sleeping
well it's okay though if they missed it
uh they can probably go they can
probably go at the night slot if they're
available at that time or no but I
honestly really just want rain and
catron Cafe as a Kickstart of this whole
rain versary the hashtag is on the title
anyways it's rainers
with number three replacing the first
e uh because it's the third year you
know and this is going to be a new this
is going to be a new uh not new as in
like a full program so let me see if I
can get you guys the schedule here uh
it's already on the YouTube community
and on Instagram and also on uh Twitter
or X but hold on schedule schedule
schedule
schedule schedule schedule
schedule oh my
gosh schedule all
right there we go I can put this
here look at this the schedule is here
this one is uh right now we're at here
the first one rain catron Cafe and we're
actually going to finish in half an hour
and we're we have the past within with
chat at 11: so that's 2 hours
Break um the pr within is a puzzle
game the pr within is a puzzle game in
which uh it's a co-op uh I've played it
with paa before basically one person is
past and one person is future so because
I played the future last time I want to
play past and you guys can play Future
so the game isn't actually connected so
it relies on like
confirmations and so that's why a lot of
people can play together at the same
same time so I'm just going to like pick
comments randomly and see how chaotic
it's it is you know maybe we can uh
think up of a good system as we play but
it's really the aim is not really to
just
um it's not to finish the game I mean it
would be good if we could finish the
game but also I just want to have fun
and be chaotic with you
guys
H yes yes yes yes yes the aim is just to
have fun and be chaotic and then I think
we can finish that in 2 hours and then
have uh some prep time for ringfit
adventure 3D I know a bunch of people
have been asking for that uh I tested
everything and everything should be
running okay so you know it should be
good with ringfit Adventure at 2
p.m. um if it's not a good time for any
of you it's fine the bot's going to be
there if you guys want want to stay up
it's fine too you guys are adults I'm
not going to tell you guys to sleep or
[Music]
whatever no and then uh after ringfit
I'm going to take a break uh a longer
break in which I can eat and I can do
stuff
basically and then afterwards it's going
to be another session of rainy catron
Cafe uh for ID this is supposed to be a
full Indonesian stream but in uh in case
uh the people who missed
this the people who missed don't want to
um you know they want to join here
instead then they can join
here and there's actually going to be uh
for the first time in my life I think
there's going to be a non Holo guest in
this ID
toat there's going to be a non Holo
guest that is not a uh that is not a
mama or something like
[Music]
that yeah are they an idol too mhm sort
of yeah it's just one person honestly
but it's funny we had a talk and it was
just so funny like okay uh you know you
want to go to my
TSU it's not a it's not a it's not a
vtuber actually it's not a
vtuber not a vtuber it's uh somebody
from Indonesia as well because this is
originally Indonesian
stream your
mom your
mom is that the daddy little princess
guy oh I wish oh my God I want the daddy
oh my God I want the daddy little
princess guy oh my God I should have
thought of
that like
hoping the dead little princess
guy and then after the catron cafe we
are going to have mini karaoke I don't
know it says mini but I don't even know
if it's going to be mini and then
closing no please no more what do you
mean no please no
more yes
[Music]
yes some size of car
okay
yes y stop this name your Japan Engish
was so good hey what go to the nojo go
to the nojo for pork
Sushi um so I can uh show off some I can
show off some stuff for you guys too and
by the way here's the hashtag and don't
forget after the six it's a lot of time
I have been bestowed the noble task of
promoting the Holo stream but that's for
later probably because this program just
started is still the
morning hopefully the karaoke is not so
mini well it depends and also it's going
to be archived anyway so it's going to
be
fun promote it
everybody and let's just do while we
wait for people to wake up and if they
don't wake up it's fine too um we're
going to because there's so many moms
I'm going to do another stepdaughter who
can I invite it's hard if I go with with
one person so stepdaughter is basically
just me being scolded by Mom working in
tears I hope
chat here's your armor my mother scolded
me cuz I burnt the eggs but I hope it's
okay and then and then from afar you see
me getting hit by the
sandals mama peile she even
awake I don't know the ID part will have
same setup yes but because it's ID it's
going to be different I want another one
this one's Sprint no please please don't
say it so loud please don't say it so
loud because if my mother my mother
hears me she will she will hit
me can you find a slipper for ID part
yeah I will I will be able to prepare it
no worries no
worries I wonder if I wonder if my
mother can use Discord I don't think she
knows how to use
Discord I don't think my mother knows
how to use Discord so I need to teach
her if she if she wants me to uh if she
if I want her to come to my
Cafe it's probably a good thing does she
know how to use sandals she probably
does but yeah she probably does
[Music]
what she use Skype she use she use
zoom she use zoom and she use zoom and
WhatsApp or something yeah just for like
the older
[Music]
people but yes have her call over the
phone let me see if I can
huh I can ask yo I can invite I can
invite I can invite uh not nurse I can
invite not nurse but I can invite
massage I can invite massage
person maybe I can maybe I
can no actually do you guys have an
illustration for massage
person maybe a placeholder illustration
for her
[Music]
maybe I can make I can do
something I can whip out a little
something actually just use my profile
picture and people will be like what
just use my purple picture and people
would be like who what what is going
on hold on be right back be right
back be right back be be right back be
right
[Music]
back
hello everybody hello everybody oh my
God oh my God
everybody hello welcome welcome to the
cafe
hey hey welcome to the cafe hello hello
hello
hello welcome to the cafe uh inia um who
um welcome to the grand opening of rainy
catron Cafe who am I speaking to today
and what should I call you
uh
what's what's your name what's your name
uh my name is saena oh her name uh your
name is Rena oh my
gosh okay okay Rena and Rene okay
um uh so okay yeah as briefed in your
invitation letter the unang you know
there are three options you can choose
from Welcome to the cafe this is like
you know um Cafe for uh Angry Angry
people you know you eat and then
I uh the first one is uh rainy
antagonist stepmother or strict Asian
mother okay
understand yes uh yes yes yes okay okay
and then two is the protagonist you know
the protagonist Always by the stepmother
you know you know you know yes
yes M yes
uh yes yes yes yes yes and then uh C is
rainy biological daughter the anak you
know and then you see the IBU always
Sika always torture the uh stepdaughter
right and she is so sad because she like
she like the stepdaughter they
[Music]
good
torture
step other than that please enjoy the
VIS normal M Cafe there will be cute
food and drinks to choose from we have
you have fun who which one you want a
stepmother rarted Soul or R biological
[Music]
daughter also
[Laughter]
Bike by your daughter by your daughter
okay okay welcome
welcome uh welcome uh
welcome hello are you
single no
no not
single okay uh welcome uh to the
cafe uh I am the biod daughter uh which
food would you like would you like uh
Tor would you like no would you like uh
omu rice would you like waffle or would
you like ice
[Music]
cream waffle waffle waffle waffle okay
okay okay waffle waffle waffle here I
feed you the
waffle yes
yes not
bullying yes yum yum
yum
yes this is he wow what do you think
about the any the waffle delicious or
not uh delicious okay delicious
[Music]
delicious delicious delicious okay uh
actually you
know you see do you see my uh my step
sister and my stepmother my IU TI and my
uh ad
do you see
it yes yes yes yes uh you see she is so
mean you know I want to resolve this
conflict I will translate
it
[Music]
yes we have received the answer it says
she wants to get out of the cafe because
I'm
[Music]
crazy
yeah guys I think this Cafe is not for
everyone I think this Cafe is not for
everyone as proven by the existence of
uh Raina yeah guys so that just means it
just proves that uh Holo members are
very very strong yeah they're very
suitable for this Cafe uh maybe normal
people like Raina uh because their brain
are normal maybe they don't think this
Cafe is good for them which is honestly
I respect
okay okay okay
okay yeah
guys yeah Raina Raina cannot take it
anymore sorry but somebody asked if
Raina single and Raina answer not single
so yeah maybe next time chat so Hol
member not normal yeah Hol member little
bit at you know I thought like for
example when Lou came in I thought she
was like normal like w we're going to
have a normal one but we had one of the
most one of the more insane
conversations with pork Sushi and
everything it's going to be insane one
way or another you
know tell her when we want to come back
for another time oh
[Music]
go I
miss this is rain show rainy catron Cafe
not Raina catron Cafe
okay
yeah little bit
[Music]
[Laughter]
atami is Raina mom single I don't know I
didn't
ask but yes I think people are sleeping
so it's okaya we will be ending the
stream uh in 10 minutes but there is a
little
bit uh if you see from the
schedule if we see from the schedule
it's all of chat next is the pass within
with chat
[Music]
11:05 and then there's ringfit and then
there's also
there's there's many many
[Music]
people I will I will ask one more
time
[Music]
yes well we will wait and we can talk
for 10 minutes and then we can move on
to the next program yeah
awake
say and they will wake up yes yes yes
yes very nice though we had a normal
stream before this and I I feel very
happy that I can actually wake up this
early who was it that asked me why I was
so energetic even though it's so
early I don't know I guess it's kind of
like the adrenaline for the adrenaline
for this whole thing you know it's just
the first stream and I'm very excited to
show you guys next it's the anniversary
adrenaline so true so
true I will give them a special price as
a sign for thank you for joining rain
catron Cafe like legit like ship them
keychains or
something I can make this rain catron
Cafe like a keychain and then when I
meet them I will give them this keychain
I feel like it's a good plan it's a good
branding I want to make this a thing
actually I I want to make this a thing
raining catron Cafe like I said um the
whole catron thing um kind of started in
the ID fandom and I really wanted to
expand it to the international just like
how I'm uh a little bit like spreading
to the IDS the Indonesian Watchers a
little bit by a little bit I want to be
able to exchange you know the whole
culture thing you know can I get a
keychain please maybe maybe we can make
merch like that in the future too I
don't
know drama the acting so so engaging
yeah this is why I'm also like I wish
more people would wake
up so I can do more but anyways in case
uh this is popular I might be able to do
it uh more as a regular program instead
of just like a anniversary
exclusive we designed a logo too
yeah very nice and um R the planning
what it
this is a fun program yeah it's the
music is Chill yeah catron is a it's a
soap oera or hudora like the drama in
the daytime in
Japan and yes it's usually like
antagonist and like soap opra accurate
archetypes with the evil
stepm yes
stream is back stream's back by the way
everything chill everything chill oh can
I good
morning good
morning
congratulations
R
anniversary yeah did you just wake up
in yeah and from now I I I should
go
walk
is no okay it's okay it's okay oh okay
okay thank
you
shba okay
okay sleepy
sh good
morning hi so short
[Music]
letter
first antagonist
stepmother
[Music]
so so she got
is my
daughter
[Music]
yeah I choose
a think
[Music]
[Laughter]
think
okay okay I know
[Music]
know
sha shba practice dance and sing singing
shba at the morning shba singing singing
you singing But in gako your s got ooh s
down down down back back you know go to
school you dancing dancing
only I love you
mother oh my God you have dancing
dancing no you um
hungry
yes
I okay because it's okay
you I you eat I feed you a thank you
okay thank you I love you mother
yes here is your
[Music]
omiz soba
growing
okay and I want
to I want to go to
P together tonight
no why why why why why because you sayi
bad maybe you sayi good you bet with me
[Music]
okay okay so you study okay thank you B
okay I
study I study uh if I grow up my study
yes so
then can you go to bed together yes but
uh you uh speak less no speaking but
action okay no speak yes but you only
talking action okay than you oh okay
okay please please teach me
St okay okay yes no actually you go Juku
alone Juku
[Laughter]
Al thank you I already feed you you
alone thank
you uh do you have message
for thank
you thank you for
[Music]
always
praying hanging out yeah hanging
out and uh next time uh if you come
Japan yeah L I think L cooking me om
rice
okay home uh weekend cooking cooking
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm happy
and anniversary congratulations thank
you let's cooking
cooking oh my
God okay okay thank you
sa have a nice
day
bye
[Music]
Kawai so cute
Subaru that's that's actually crack
that's actually great subba so cute N I
couldn't have uh I couldn't have the
heart to be angry because she's such a
cutie japang
[Music]
good a lot of
every every time at 900 a.m. uh I have
my alarm ring because that's like the
threshold on like when I absolutely have
to wake up it's like 9 is like the
max I love you mother sh is a gem
actually um I call her Shuba
son for some reason all Hol M choose
strict mom yeah
step mom being kind
[Music]
with it's very important that I can get
my things across my mind if and if Japan
English is the one thing that
you know makes it translate well to both
Shuba and you guys then that's the thing
see the reason that I speak in Japan
English is to find some middle ground in
between the listeners and the person I'm
talking
[Music]
to see
right so
Subaru understand you understand Juku is
cram
school M Juku is cram
school saki is
[Music]
grades yes
yes I'm right now
nice well yeah I think people are
sleeping and I think uh 2 hours did I
say 2 hours I'm going to I'm going to
cry if I accidentally said the wrong
time it's it's now 11 jst
right I think it's now 11
jst it's been 2 hours plus yep I think
okay I'm just checking the time in case
I
[Music]
accidentally so 10 p.m. EST would be
one oh [\h__\h] oh no
[Music]
10 p.m. EST is in another
[Laughter]
hour oh
no I I think no I think like just one
person I think like just one person I
forgot
to oh my God I always [\h__\h] up so much
with the time zones
more
[Music]
Z just blame daylight savings true
everything is Daylight Savings
Time one more hour
[Music]
together
let's do TT five stream no I feel bad
because this person is sort of the
person I invited
[Music]
first right
now
[Music]
um
Bor MOS B MOS everyone got are you awake
or no no no no not everyone just one
person just one person just one person
cuz I think like uh this person uh so uh
basically this uh the opening
Cafe the opening Cafe was uh basically
the opening was supposed to be
later than
usual
but because I accidentally because I had
to move it lower so it fits more time
zones um and I updated it in the
group but so I feel like the info should
be there but
I didn't I should have said it in DMS as
well oopsie whoopsie because that person
is the one of the people I asked from
the
start you know so I was saying the times
and stuff at her
[Music]
too yes yes yes F any time right now so
yes it's okay any chance for Gilla
Collins will wait for her well we can we
can but I don't know I don't know who's
going to call actually I don't know who
we can call this early in the morning
because
normally I wouldn't be awake at this
hour I mean I would kind of but
yeah time zones are never a winning
battle so true every time I say
something I'm just like yo can you
correct me if my time zone is wrong I'm
always very bad with time
zones
[Music]
h I'm asking if mchan wants to be in
call is it allowed or
[Music]
not is it allowed or
not
oh
okay she said maybe not allowed
she said maybe not allowed so let's
stick on the safe
[Music]
side let's on the safe side on the safe
side I wonder if everybody I wonder if
anybody is awake M ch's like I want to
but I bet probably not but it makes
sense you know for
safy for safy aan I asked aan but um aan
couldn't make it because uh of a problem
she cannot
call but I saw her tweeting though I saw
her retweeting me so thank you Anan for
your support if Anan is here at some
somehow thank you you are always welcome
to Raina catron
[Music]
Cafe good
morning oh good
morning
good
[Music]
morning
spee donut
fore
[Music]
for
for just
being
[Music]
for
speech
[Music]
spe
oh
God
[Music]
okay
n
[Music]
[Laughter]
foree
foree spee
fore
fore spee
foree
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
anniversary anniversary need message
[Music]
for
fore have a nice
day
have a nice
[Music]
conrat I don't know what just happened
yo
[Music]
to Yo okay that was stepdaughter I don't
know I just ended up
crying she just woke up and she was like
yo this is so complicated I don't
understand okay
angry or so I guess stepdaughter gets
pick once
again so
[Music]
well well I guess we do have
somebody we have somebody I want I want
to go to the bathroom but let's um you
know the cafe shift NOS no
bouns we can only take breaks in when
our shift ends okay
but I guess this might be our last
person for
[Music]
[Laughter]
today my guest is so understanding she
says I can wait if you want to go to the
bathroom but no I am
fine I can I'm fine I will wait until
the shift ends this is why we wear
diapers what no you you wear diapers we
at the Rainy catron Cafe we do not wear
diapers not that we judge anybody who do
but we do not wear diapers here our
uniform does not consist of diapers but
I guess if somebody needs it then it's
okay
too okay so uh Our Guest is already at
the front door she's already I see her
against the glass
door um hold
on you can come
in I'm so hungry after this I am going
to
eat my shift is going to be over
technically I'm the owner of this Cafe
so there's really no
shifts
hello hi say hello
yes welcome to the grand opening of rain
and catron Cafe who am I speaking to
today and what should I call
you this is FAA you can call me
FAA okay fauna I like how like all these
people like you got you got people who
wants to be called like some the
greatest of the great and you're just
Faun oh I didn't even think about that
oh oh sh maybe I should have I should
have taken this opportunity oh okay well
I'll wait we wait Almighty all powerful
Queen Fawn of the universe Almighty all
powerful Queen fa of the universe all
right all right Almighty all powerful
Queen fa of the universe as briefed in
your invitation letter there are three
options that you can choose from first
is raining antagonist stepmother or
strict Asian mother and you are the
stepdaughter she will be evil towards
you or rainy kindhearted Soul who was
forced by the evil stepmother to help
out in this Cafe oh no or rainy
biological daughter aka the biod
daughter that the stepmother treats
kindly as opposed to how she treats the
stepdaughter AKA she wants this conflict
between stepdaughter and stepmother to
end ASAP other than that please enjoy
the visit as if it's a normal made Cafe
there will be cute food and drinks to
choose from we hope you have fun at the
Rainy cetron Cafe what would you like to
pick I'm curious which option has been
the least chosen today um I kind of um
screwed up the tallies a little
bit yo chat um is stepdaughter or biod
daughter chosen least cuz I know uh the
person before you the guest before you
picked um
stepdaughter ah it's a tie between the
last
[Music]
two um or bio oh sorry biod daughter
yeah biod daughter is leased
now okay let's go with that one okay
biod daughter bio stands for biological
I
guess okay
so hi uh Almighty and all powerful Queen
fa of the universe welcome to the Rainy
catron Cafe uh what would you like to
eat we have waffle we have omiz and we
also have ice cream which one do you
want good evening I the almighty all
powerful Queen F of the universe would
really like some waffles okay that's a
great
selection I will prepare it
[Music]
to oh no what what's wrong what's wrong
the almighty all powerful Queen F of the
universe please avert your eyes from the
view in the background totally there is
no view of U my mother they torturing
the stepdaughter uh near the kitchen uh
please please wait for a second as
I how could this
happen anyways um here's your waffle I
simply cannot avoid such a such a sight
my eyes have witnessed too
much yeah well okay um well the waffle
can wait actually how can I enjoy my
waffles yeah with such an image
okay I've been um I've been having a
little bit of a trouble here like I
really care about my sister of course
but my stepmother I mean not sorry my
actual mother my actual mother my keeps
being not nice to my my my my sister and
I just really wanted to stop do you
understand why I'm feeling you need me
to go back there and and and just put
put her in her place show
show your mom what's up you can do that
I could I could try I could I could slap
her around a little bit and see how she
reacts oh but the thing is this is our
grand opening of the cafe if she gets
beaten up then it would affect our
livelihood I don't know it sounds like
it sounds like she's a problem it sounds
like she's getting in the way of your
sister doing her job you think so you
think we'll be able to be fine without
our mother I think you'll be fine
without her oh okay um by the way um I
have a
question yes what's your
number my
number okay you can you can call me here
let me write it down for you on this
piece of paper oh okay here you go I
don't I don't want anybody to overhear
you know this is sensitive sensitive
information information yeah for your
eyes all right okay I received it thank
you so much um no um I'm just like
simply asking because uh you know cuz
you're giving a good advice and I'm
about to follow your advice and if I
have if I have a problem then I can
consult to you or or something you know
oh oh well just I'm just want to make
sure that I'm not held liable for any
actions that may occur at the cafe today
as a result of my slapping um oh okay um
I cannot be held accountable I cannot be
taken to court for this oh okay okay oh
so no
courting well courting courting might be
all right okay I see well I'll see what
I can do about it well first um okay uh
since we're here anyways uh it's okay
you can go to the kitchen and beat up my
mom it's fine okay okay I'll do that
that'll make the waffles taste even
sweeter yes when you're finished please
tell me oh yes of course um if you're
done uh please tell me okay okay okay I
will I'll be right back I'll be right
back wait you stay here actually I'll be
right back okay I'll stay
here o I heard that you were mistreating
your
stepdaughter that's not okay take this
slap slap
slap yeah have you your lesson yet will
you treat her kindly from now on SL slap
[Music]
slap okay I think she's I'm back I think
she has learned her lesson I don't think
she'll be mistreating anybody after that
ever again ever never again okay oh
that's good what was I going to do oh I
was going to feed you waffles right
right right right I hope that she wasn't
the one who had the waffle recipe no it
was our
cook it's fine it's a different you be
just fine yeah okay
[Music]
um it's so delicious thank you I'm glad
you think so do you want another bite
yes
[Music]
yay I so glad that enjoy you enjoyed the
waffles actually um I was uh I was in
charge
of um pouring the whipped
cream oh you did a great job I would say
the whipped cream is my favorite part oh
okay thank you so much that makes me so
happy do you want anything else like an
ice cream
or
maybe your
number oh oh well in that case Oh you
mean my phone number or my
measurements I
mean if if you're
offering oh okay well I'll just um I'll
just text you cuz I have your number now
right yeah I'll I'll text it to you
right
now yeah cuz it's secret information all
right wow oh
wow oh my goodness yeah yes thank you so
much I hope that information was useful
to
you very okay well we'll have sweet
dreams tonight oh thank you I hope you
have sweet dreams everybody deserves uh
sweet dreams except my
mother I don't think she'll be dreaming
anytime soon so don't don't worry about
her oh okay well
um uh Almighty all powerful Queen fa of
the universe
do you have a message for Raine for her
anniversary Raine thank you for being
here for 3
years I have watched you since before
you debuted and now it is great to be
able to know you and hang out with you
and play fun puzzle games together yay
I'm very very very happy too we should
play lot more of mystery games escape
games and more you're my like designated
as game game partner now yes I'm so
happy to have that
spot all right I hope you have a nice
day we should catch up and do that thing
we were supposed to do yes we should we
should I I sorry I keep forgetting no
it's every everybody's been busy lately
I know yeah thank you thank you happy
anniversary yay thanks thanks byebye
[Music]
bye-bye see it could be anything like
you get ABC you get ABC like you get a
it's never the exact same experience you
get B is never the same experience you
get C is never the exact same
experience that was some good slapping
some nice
impromptu um some nice impromptu um
acting
acting she went to that's great I'm so
glad I'm so glad she called
in but anyways I'm surrounded by great
friends thank you so much
for everybody who came to the cafe today
and of course the cafe will be open to
the public soon and well I'll just going
to think of something but in in case you
guys like this I might be able to turn
this into a regular program and just not
a onetime thing you know so it's going
to be great we're
lucky yeah your friends are lucky to
have an evil Auntie like
you but yes guys um next stream is going
to be at
1105 uh we're going to be playing the
past within with chat
so uh if you guys don't have the game uh
you probably should get it or I mean if
you want to play together if somebody
wants to get the game and you just want
to watch that's fine too and so well you
just mess around a little bit with the
game and then you'll find out um how the
co-op Works basically you don't really
need to be connected there so it's just
relies on communication and Confirmation
and stuff like that it's going to be
chaotic I think but I don't know how
it's going to be it's going to be funny
their way and yeah there is a
anniversary playlist on the pin message
if you want to see so it's easy to catch
up on so right now this is the first
stream and we're going to go second
stream at 11:00 so yeah I'm very hungry
right now thank you so much yeah I'm
fast and all chat future because last
time when I played with fauna I was
future and she was fast so I I've never
seen anything in the past and we're
going to check and we're going to choose
um the B one the butterfly because um I
played with the B you know you'll
understand when you uh boot up the
game eat something yummy and feeling
yeah going to eat some Cafe food all
right thank you so much guys I'll see
you guys very very soon and by the way
before I stop the stream uh remember
that uh rainy birthday CS uh is still
available on
Holo still available on Hol life shop
and yeah it's the sales are going to end
sales are going to end soon and um Holo
shop is mainly for Japan uh it's already
all sold out on geek Jack by the way but
for Hol shop there's
still um some stock uh it's uh it's for
Japan but it can ship uh it can ship kri
outside Japan even though not everything
it can ship to the United States can
ship to Canada it can ship to Korea
Singapore Taiwan Hong Kong Malaysia maau
New Zealand Argentina Chile Brazil as
well as Mexico
yeah yes so if you guys are in the
countries listed and you guys haven't
gotten a chance to get the Rainy
birthday merch it's going to be over
soon uh the order period so get yours
now thank you so
much and also um for tokopedia recently
there has been a restock of the you know
the resale one dakimakura only for uh
tokopedia uh for right now so if you
guys are ID Bros and and you guys still
haven't gotten it and you want to get it
now is your
chance yeah and also I think there's
still a few pairs of the birthday Goods
in uh tokopedia too but for tokopedia
it's there's only very few left there I
think there's only like two full sets
left and there's only like um some
individual towels so uh it's really
running out in tokopedia for the ID Bros
knows your chance um Hol Pro still have
uh more Stocks by the way but yeah
um so yeah that's it for me um I'll see
you guys very soon I'm going to eat and
then I'm going to go to the idle meeting
too um let's have a really fun day today
everybody I'm looking forward to the you
know the other streams we can have fun
at all right thank you so much thank you
very much for the attention hope you
like the morning session of rainy sron
Cafe there's going to be another one at
night Salam everybody
byebye
bye
[Music]