[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
okay
oh well i mean
i know why it's not my greeting but
sometimes it's
you just want to say what
you just can't
you know hold it back that's just how it
is
hello everybody i'm young
hello
welcome to
my 12 hour
marathon
it's gonna be a long long long long long
long stream
and i hope you guys are all ready for it
all up for it
yeah
thank you guys so much already for the
sweet messages
ah so cute thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
everybody's so sweet
thank you
um
well yeah we're just gonna say today is
my anniversary because uh since the myth
members
debuted within the span of less than 24
hours
if we did all our
um
anniversary streams at the right time on
the right day
then first of all i wouldn't be able to
do a 12-hour stream
a second of all it would be really
stressful and also back then i was
living in japan
so
now that i live in a different time zone
streaming at the same time in the same
time slot is not ideal you know
um so yeah
um i i thought it's good to spread it
out um
you know
i personally always thought and i think
you guys agreed with me would have been
better if if we would have debuted one
person per day
um
and then you know a lot of things would
have been
easier especially during the actual
debut
oh
but maybe
maybe at least this way like doing it in
less than 24 hours it kept the hype
rolling and going i do understand that
but it was stressful for us
as of course we want to be awake for all
of our gen mates debut streams as well
we were really excited
and uh ideally
we all wanted to i i wanted to sleep
through two of them because there was a
little bit oh this is we're already
reminiscing
there was a little bit of a break
between
mine and cali's uh debut stream and then
the rest of the girls
uh because yeah they were like i don't
know three four hours or so
maybe
until inna did her debut stream so i
thought you know cause
i did my own stream at like what 11 p.m
or or 10 p.m or so
and then you know stream wasn't gonna be
until like three a.m or four a.m and
then gura name and then collab stream
and then fall guys
so it was gonna be um
a lot of streams in a row so i wanted to
get some sleep but i ended up being so
excited and also nervous and there was
[\h__\h] wreck and
um beating myself up immediately after
my debut about how i did
um yeah so i couldn't sleep
four guys yeah
four guys is a stream that
almost feels like a fata morgana to me
did that really happen
i know
[Laughter]
yeah um so let me go a little bit
through what we're going to do today
where did i put that schedule here
okay second anniversary 12-hour marathon
you know right now here where i am
it's 12 p.m
plus 12 hours i will end at midnight my
time
so actually
in my timeline my time zone it's perfect
because
uh
it will end right when it turns to 12
for me which is when my anniversary
actually is
8 p.m to 8 a.m here
sorry it had to be
um it had to start and end at a decent
time for me because i'm gonna be doing
this for 12 hours
[Laughter]
6 pm to 6 am
um
the good thing is since we're starting
early
s-e-a time zones can have some fun
uh
even if they sleep later
and but you know we have something for
every time zone today
yeah
yeah yeah yeah and a
already already probably some people in
the stream from n a anyway thank you for
that
but uh the latest dreams are
gonna be better for you i hope you don't
fall asleep midway through
[Music]
oh my god thank you guys so much for the
super chat already i hope i hope i don't
have to do super chat reading for 12
hours but i i i i did that
after my last marathon and
i don't think i can do it again
nope
no
no i don't i don't have confidence in
myself like that anymore
so even if there's a super chat's worth
of reading them 12 hours long i will not
be doing it for 12 hours i will spread
it out
thank you guys thank you
i'm i'm really grateful for all the
incredible support thank you
i hope that my voice survives the day
um
my voice is not as kang gang gang genki
uh anymore as it was a year or two years
ago
money
um
so we will be taking breaks
like a sane person usually would do
uh i also have some tea ready and i have
fruit candies but
you know at some point of this day
i will be suffering
um
the only the only straw of hope that i
have is the collaborations that i put
into the schedule
because i'll be
especially during oink games i'll
probably be
a bit more quiet
yeah we will share your suffering you're
cool together we suffer together we
stand
yeah
um oh thank you
kim dong-gun
thank you
[Music]
no kartik phone is with you guys and i'm
counting on you guys that um
you don't [\h__\h] this one up okay
because last time i did it with viewers
pretty much everyone participated with
like
mouse and you know there's some good
people some people who can do well with
mouse
but you guys were not
one of those
so i'm i'm personally hoping that you
guys let the people enter who either
join on a tablet or phone because i
suppose with the finger you can still do
a better job at drawing than with a
mouse um or you let the people enter who
actually have
some skill
[Laughter]
that would be nice um but i know i know
even though we do say that kiwawa is in
control it doesn't seem like i have you
guys in control in those kind of
situations
but it's okay if you guys draw shitty
then i will draw shitty as well
yeah please get the artists again i
can't get them on such short don't
notice but
if they are watching if they are around
please join you know what if there are
artists in the chat during garcic phone
uh
i will give them
uh a pre pre-joined pass i will give
them the code beforehand and let a few
of those in
uh are there any artists
are there are there
i mean
i mean maybe some you know like um
the ones that are good
oh grammy is here go to me do you want
to join guardian phone
we got some artists in here
let's go
manzanita of course also here
yes please please join yes okay i don't
know if you ever played garcic phone
before but um
i need some good artists so that this
doesn't end up being too shitty
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah
if you guys don't remember go guru mia
drew some really
cute and funny
uh kibaba fan arts before
[Music]
yeah anyway let's go through
let's go through the
uh
let's go for the schedule
right now we're doing chit chat that's
done it's starting at
uh 12 p.m cest that's my time zone
6 a.m est
that means it's like what 4 am pst oh
dear
and then uh 7 pm jst was already pretty
late
[Music]
thank you
casually roasting kfp um yeah why the
[\h__\h] not
okay and we have garcic phone in about
40 minutes
there please good artists be by my side
uh and then we have ultimate chicken
horse
with reina ollie and kobu after one and
a half hours of garcic phone
i mean maybe
uh i will need some setup time so i'll
probably be gone for like 15 minutes to
gather the girls
and
uh get a try to get us into a room
and last time i played ultimate chicken
horse i was not the one hosting the room
uh but i hope it's it's just gonna be
easy
two clicks and that's it
i hope it goes easy and well
i don't know
you don't want to wake up so early for
the news well you will [\h__\h] have to
yes you will have to yeah we collapsed
that game before on vata senpai's
channel
so we're gonna play that for
oh
like one and a half hours maximum
probably
because uh then we have uh homocure
i've heard
that kiwawa is really strong now
and i need to see if that's true because
last time i focused on the new members
um
so i don't know yet if that is true
oh [\h__\h] i got i got a leg why was that
lagging
not even playing anything oh well
yeah yeah yeah kiwami strong
got buffed
what
what i can play with controller i know i
don't know if i want to try now that i'm
already used to
playing with the keyboard but maybe
maybe
you beated both new stages of kiwawa
both new stages
there's another stage
both
[Music]
oh you just mean heart mode
hard mode force ah
[Music]
okay okay okay oh dear
ah
i see
i don't think i'll i'll get that far
but i do want to try the office again
with kiwawa i guess um
so we'll be playing that for
two and a half hours
with a little break in between i think i
think for two hours he'll play hollow
cure and then i'll take like half an
hour break to eat
i won't go away completely i'll be on
screen but i'll be a bit more quiet and
i'll i'll eat a sandwich i have some
snacks um
ready
yeah yeah yeah i'll eat a sandwich and i
don't know what else but yeah
uh
[Music]
yeah
so then we'll play rust
i have not yet tried to get into the new
map
hopefully that goes well
and we'll try to start building
something up again
i want to ask
[Music]
already right uh
rest
does anyone know
like the new season
yeah
no
oh she said she might the reason is
she told me
that she thinks she can or she told
everyone that she doesn't think she can
play so much rest in the season and she
asked if anybody wants to be like you
know roommate i guess and i was like i
will be your roommate
let me be your roommate because i also
i'm starting to doubt that i will play
it much this season
due to several reasons um
yeah so we're gonna build something
together
and i already know where we want to
build a house birdhouse yeah
birdhouse
i don't know if she started building i'm
guessing she didn't
but then what did she do
if she played off-screen then what did
she do
but there's a good spot that ame told me
about
um where it's good to build a house so
i'm going to go there
mother mother logo instead
um and you know even even if eating only
takes me 10 minutes we all know that
loading into rust takes me 20 minutes or
everybody takes 20 minutes
because it takes
way too much [\h__\h] time so
yeah we will have to stop hollow here
after two hours
yeah and then we'll play for half an
hour seven eight
i don't know how long
but
right before oink games i'm gonna go
into preparation phase again to get the
girls together hopefully they'll all be
ready hopefully hopefully they all got
the memo that we're playing oink games
uh
i i want to message the all the collab
members quickly one more time
in a second
and then after on games which is by the
way like a board game game
for a nintendo switch and probably also
on other devices but we're playing on
switch mm-hmm
[Music]
karaoke and news which is announcements
but announcement is such a [\h__\h] long
word that always [\h__\h] up my my stupid
thumbnails and all that every time i
want to put the word announcement into a
thumbnail i'm like where the [\h__\h] do i
put this word i want it to be big
because because it's an important word
and normally you make the important
words big but
and not quite possible when announcement
is also such a [\h__\h] long word what
the [\h__\h]
i want us to cancel the words
announcement
cancel
kill it
so anyway in this case i went with news
yeah karaoke going to be archived yes um
so i will only be singing like japanese
songs and my own songs and so on i guess
yeah yeah yeah i didn't really um decide
on what to sing uh we probably won't
sing much anyway that's only a one hour
time slot and
yeah it's just the ending phase and some
special announcements
um i got a couple of those a couple
announcements
some more special than others
yeah yeah
cancel the word announcement
yeah it's too [\h__\h] long
and now i have a sad announcement right
away off the bat uh you're lucky that
you get to hear this announcement early
but i have a sad announcement
today when i started my pc several times
for some reason
data board
wasn't working so right now i'm using
my old
keyboard it shouldn't be broken but i
don't know for some reason it's not
working yesterday was working
so no no beautiful
sounds today
yeah
i don't know why i didn't have time to
like properly
test it out but i i really started to
see several times and i could never
input the
my my password for the
for the pc um to log in
yeah i checked the cord
but it didn't work
the clickety clacks please god no no no
no god no
[Music]
well i'll look into it when i have more
time but for now
let me quickly message the girls
um
[Music]
girls please be ready
and on standby
um
15 minutes
prior
um
i will
i will mute and hide the screen
so we can set up properly
yoshiku
okay
one group has received the memo
and i know
crony inna
i didn't get your okay yet if you got
[Music]
the memo
about the game
make sure to get it in time
so yes that's okay but there's gonna be
12 hours of streaming well actually
until oink games
uh i don't know how many hours
um
enough hours for ina to wake up and
download the game hopefully if she
didn't download it already
what i just ordered 10 pc wicked wings
wicked wings and wasted some of them
because i was full please give me mercy
it's okay don't worry it's just not the
same yeah i know
ah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah my my my keyboard
my keyboard is
it's not working properly
it's okay it's okay we'll get it to work
again properly don't worry
so
let me pour some water
uh half an hour until we start garlic
phone huh
mamma mia i have nothing to say
what can i say um
[Music]
oh yeah in between
in between i'll be answering
marshmallows
uh
i did i did open the marshmallow last
night and you guys can still send
marshmallows if you want to
uh
okay
if i ran out of things to talk about
uh
yeah i might ask helena um if you guys
want if i guys if i guys yes i guys
if i
have
things to talk about i will pick up some
marshmallows and write them maybe let's
check
maybe i can go ahead and pick the first
one now
let's see if we can find a good one
bye guys
hi guys ah what
okay
wow okay wow
oh
motto
there's quite a bunch of them thank you
guys for sending the mushroom bottles
thank you
oh
wow so many
so many
where is the start
most of you guys sent them in 11 hours
ago
good chickens good chickens
or 12 hours ago wow 13 oh 14.
oh there's more than i thought there
would be uh
[Music]
oh
come on where's the ending
where's the start to start to this list
lots of topics yeah hopefully
hopefully i don't i don't think i have
time to actually look at every single
question
uh like properly i'm just gonna like
zoom through them and see if something
catches my eye
um
[Music]
let's see
i've reached the start
[Music]
okay i got one
all right why that's oyo why does it not
it saves them as html what happened
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
huh
[Music]
html it didn't do that back in the day
oh wait guys download that that was uh
there was a little
button for it downloading the
actual image there you go
[Music]
hey wawa hi
did you know before you ever debuted
that you had the ability to keep talking
and streaming for so long that you had
the ability to keep people entertained
for hours on end every day
[Music]
i don't think i was made aware of it so
much
uh until
you know after i started streaming
oh
but um
i do think that i already had the
ability before that but yeah it was just
not you know made into a big deal or
anything
um but
um
i do think that like my friends
they like having me around
because of reasons like that for example
that i
and like like
you know with italy remember italy when
i was like do you guys like that we were
gonna go to italy and i was like i don't
really want to go anymore because i
don't really have time for it but do you
guys want to really
like have me with you do you guys feel
like if i go with you
i will be a
big
an enrichment again
an improvement to the group
yeah i asked that and they were like yes
yes yes yes please come
we need you
they were very very certain about that
and i think um the reason is that
apparently
i am i'm just i'm just a good
entertainer
even though
off screen i'm not
trying as hard to entertain as i am on
stream
um
but it just comes naturally
it just comes naturally but
my
mom
i noticed once again
the other day
um
when my mom came to visit
she was talking so much she's probably
watching now sorry mommy
but she talks
even more than i do much more than i do
often i don't even get to
like
talk
uh because she never catches a break
sometimes she goes on and on and on and
on
[Laughter]
yeah she gets really really
passionate and excited about certain
topics
um
it's a family thing mm-hmm she tangents
really really really a lot now
yeah yeah yeah yeah
are the marshmallows closed no they're
not they should be open um
they're still open but i'm in theory i
have enough marshmallows
to go on for days and days
actually let me is it okay for you guys
if i pour myself some tea now
already
i have the i have the hot water over
here
[Music]
all right
have to protect the fruit it already
feels dangerous
not good
but you know we wanted to do a 12 hour
marathon because i wanted to stream
like this was a special occasion and i
wanted i wanted to
i wanted to give you guys something i
wanted to give back and i wanted to
prove
that i can still do it can i do can i
though
i don't know
so um my my honey
container is gonna make some weird
noises please don't mind
wait
come on honey please
give me some honey
give me some honey oh
why are you so weird microphone
give me some honey
[Laughter]
oh come on
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
come on a little drop okay
you done
without the what about the cat hairs
please
no
that was my honey container
i told you beforehand
this container always this bottle always
makes the weird [\h__\h] noises it's like
a ketchup bottle
how hot is this
stream honey
wait
wait why
it was
wasn't it hard challenger how did we get
to because
because wait maybe during zelda play
through we said heart challenger becomes
heart container and then from there it
went to honey container
oh man
we're getting really creative
[Music]
live conqueror
wait what are you hot heart heart
conqueror
uh heart why is everyone [\h__\h] up hard
challenges so much yeah love challenger
it's hard challenger you guys are
gaslighting me again
[\h__\h] atsui
[\h__\h] assoi
okay i can't drink this now
okay that's fine not like i wanted to
drink any tea no
it's not like i wanted to drink tea
okay so thank you for the question yes i
think i was aware um
although like in in
[Music]
i think
i think like in high school
and junior high school
i used to be more quiet because i was
just like
i don't know shy i was more shy and
um
like i i probably had the ability to
talk a lot but i was too shy so
i remember myself being more quiet in
school but then
outside of school
the older i got the more i would talk
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god thank you
50 memberships
you're crazy
[Music]
well um you're welcome to watch last
member stream uh we've played slate
slater why do i always say like that
slay the spire
uh last time i want to play it again
like next week but okay next week would
be i guess through but we can maybe if i
can squeeze it in i don't know
oh oh new members welcome so many eggs
that i can crack
and make into breakfast
ah slater slicer spa
what
okay let's get rid of this
are there any good artists write me
um tweet to me
now
so i can dm you
anybody who is here at the moment
please please tweet to me
[Music]
obviously with you
you
kartik phone
dakuma
[Music]
okay
oh i'm good at art
are you really
oh yeah we are pretty decent good good
stuff
okay uh
dm okay so i'm just gonna get everyone
ready uh so i can send them the code wow
there's actually quite a quite a bunch
oh
okay
yes i'm gonna have a stroke is the
message that came back
uh
ah
i'll try to get all of you guys in here
um we're probably gonna have more than
one round so don't worry
diem
oh wow wow wow
oh
i'm surprised we have so many artists in
here also a bunch that you know i'm not
so familiar with
wow
oh another artist oh nice art wow
why have you not drawn chihuahua oh no i
guess there's some uh
fan art in your header
you need to draw more
draw more qualifying
all of you i didn't send a code yet just
totally wait
we're not starting yet i'm just
preparing
[Music]
we're gonna mix some okay artists with
some
with some viewers
you guys get a chance to don't worry
oh oh oh oh
good art nice to know so
does it count if i haven't drawn kiwawa
yet well that's kind of illegal but
you may get a chance
dm
wow so many dms
yes howie i know i know elmi i know
elia how to send him no i'm the one
sending dms after you guys sent me a
reply telling me that you are an artist
but you better be an actual artist
you guys like the bgm you're hearing
this right
do cosplayers count um
not in like how i need you right now
right now i need some decent artists so
the guardian phone
session will not be too shitty but i
love my cosplayers
i love my cosplayers
if you have like a drawing tablet or so
then you're already above average
probably so
please go ahead and and reply to me
no musical actors no no oh
korean artist that i didn't know yet oh
nice marine money fan art oh
oh where's kiwa fan art
where i'm going through the twitter i
don't see chihuahua fan art doco
well you got homework
tanuki
yeah you're gonna dm anyway it's your
chance
go to me of course you're an artist
where's your message i'm gonna just
throw you a dm from my side
dm okay this is already a lot of people
let me stop here for now
if i need more then uh
wait a second
uh if i need more i will go for my
replies again
last one dm okay
okay
i haven't played kartik phone in a
million years let's see how this works
gothic phone
thankfully this game is free and you can
play it on your browser
um
[Music]
what is this authenticated
oh oh gowdy phone now has an option
where you can
log in with discord or twitch
but what does that
change like how
only ah if you join with discord or
twitch and also everybody else can also
join if they connect with discord or
twitch which probably prevents like
some hardcore trolling or so i don't
know i suppose
i'm gonna guess
[Music]
okay
uh
not a little but we're just gonna do a
non-mess
[Music]
go away
wrap up the lich king classic let's go
there better not be any more pop-ups
like that
boy
the [\h__\h] is my uh ad block
[Music]
bad are you even on
that's weird
hmm oh well
oh i'll just um don't worry
playing me and telling me to play
volleyball classic you know what i'm in
i'm in let's do it
i want to play [\h__\h] classic
again yeah
[Music]
hell yeah
okay
so
how does this work again invite oh yeah
i got a link
um
then we send it first
to a couple but i'm still early i'm
still so early oh my god how why did i
give myself one hour to chit chat what
was i gonna talk about
i gave myself way too much time
[Music]
oh
being such a well-traveled chicken
i was wondering if you had an opinion on
which country has the best cheese
chocolate and beer
do you
know me
who
the [\h__\h] are you
i don't drink beer you should know that
i don't drink alcohol at all
but anyway
mine is probably
netherlands for ultra all free but japan
has asahi
well
so i absolutely cannot answer the
question of beer
uh but chocolate
[Music]
i don't know if i want to focus on the
country because i think overall in
europe the chocolate tastes very similar
and we share
certain companies chocolates
uh and have them in all of our
supermarkets
um but i will just say european
chocolate is best
especially no
especially central european
chocolate
yes central
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah and then for cheese ooh
i did have
like a cheese
fondue kind of thing in in paris
remember
that was really good but um
i would need to eat more
cheese everywhere to judge it to be
honest
i'm not like a huge
cheese fan like i i like like normal
cheeses no when i say normal i mean like
the ones that don't have mold on them
um so yeah like mozzarella gauda
uh
stuff like that
butter cheese i love butter cheese
i don't know if they also call it butter
cheese uh outside of german language but
yeah um yeah emmentala idama cheddar all
of those i love them
but
like the moldy cheese no thank you
but yeah because of that i just don't
eat that that much cheese like
if i do then i mix it with something
else like in a sandwich i would
eat cheese with something else
oh my god
[Music]
oh
god wow another 50. we're going to get
like a million members today oh
awesome thanks for the super chat thank
you
actually this is a bad question because
i can't answer any of it
[Laughter]
never mind jen
i don't know the answer
i don't know you tell me
wow
holy moly
i drink my tea now why did i put it into
the firma's cup
why
there was an attempt indeed
[Music]
yeah it's been two years it is weird
because in some ways it felt like a long
long time and in other ways it felt like
a short time so weird
anyway let me get another question um
[Music]
or interesting
first of all congratulations on your
second anniversary thank you the
question will you
you will will you expand the variety of
your streams now in this third year i
mean whole talk come back
well you play other types of games you
haven't played before
lara croft resident evil others
metroidvania thanks for your work piece
callie no just kidding
well expanding i don't want to say yes
because then maybe you um expect some
huge changes and huge expanding but it's
not going to be crazy i do always try to
um
bring in new games
new ideas
especially difficult though cause like
the other day
when i pitched an idea to the girls not
much
like feedback or or uh replies came back
but then i pitched another idea and
actually that one got surprisingly more
replies
um
yeah but i think um
there's a lot of ideas that i've had in
my mind that i haven't really worked on
yet um properly
so
i don't wanna
do them and
yeah i i i think i'll just you know
it's not big much of a change because
i've tried the same thing for two years
now um
just you know little little bits of new
content here and there
um
but i won't suddenly turn into a
completely different streamer obviously
uh
because it's even impossible like if i
if i want to do like
so many like completely an overhaul of
my channel it's impossible it it's like
step by step a step-by-step kind of
thing
um
but mostly i wanna instead of like all
kinds of new games i just wanna
make my project ideas
into reality
[Music]
there's something in my throat
not good
yeah yeah yeah recently just like i've
been playing so many new games
overwatch rest
aoe2
and some more
so
if you if you ask me i i would say that
we have variety already and
actually
recently in the past
year
it's been getting more and more and more
and more got a frog yara in my throat
perhaps why what is she doing in my
throat huh
what is she doing in my fruit
maybe you will find out soon
[Music]
oh yeah city skylines as well
that's weird
oh well
yeah that's that thank you very much for
the question um the games that you
mentioned
i'm not sure about them i don't even
know like lava croft if we have any
perms for those games
in theory
um
i like me some
cute
girl in short pants
and triangle boobs
and a nice a nice braided ponytail
so hell yeah hell yeah
a tomb raider oh yeah yeah yeah
i mean i would probably prefer to play a
newer version as as charming as the
triangle boobs are
it's not square enix anymore oh did they
like change
really is that so
[Music]
i have yet to make
um
acquaintance with square enix besides uh
near automata
sadly
i would love to play more
okay
return to triangle
square please
you mean square boobs
or square enix
how about triangle enix triangle boops
maybe maybe they ditched lara croft
because they thought yo triangle boobs
girl is not for us we only like square
boobs
[Music]
it's not not our style no no no no no
okay let me try to set up garcic phone
now
let's see
what how do we do this without
showing something yeah bye cho tomato
let me go into
intermission
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
yay here we are here we are
okay this is our new bgm i collected
some
bgms for this purpose some fresh ones
yeah
i called this one
questionable super chats pgm
[Laughter]
oh no our outfit oh you're right you're
right you're right oh i want to thank
you for reminding me
[Music]
so
let's see we will go with this one
outfit change
it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
what if i'm just here
you're small
small
[Music]
but
small wow too small for people who need
glasses so
i make myself big for you guys
big big small wawa
so now i send url
[Music]
one okay i set uh
uh
we're gonna have 10 10 players for this
round
so
let me send something in some some dms
[Music]
how many are how many decent people do
we want to have versus how many
how many bad artists
all right why they're not joining
come on there we go
okay
legacy
oh oh
nice
[Music]
so cute
okay i sent like uh one two three four
four maybe one more
one more
okay
come in come in come on come on
where's my pen here's my pen i have a
pen
i have a pen tab
ooh
welcome to blend
there we go
i think we're still waiting for
uh
waiting for some people
or christina
oh that link didn't work when i oh oh
i am having this thing again where
twitter says it's spam
it's not it's not it's not
[Music]
about
the rest should have received it
properly there we go
[Music]
come on
get in here oh she's here
okay one two three four five decent
people and now we make some space for
for you
guys how do i
how do i do this do i just throw it into
the chat
did i previously did i send it on the
community board maybe
i think i did it's just that
a streaming kartik phone for members is
not allowed but
giving them the link to join was okay
as far as i remember so let me send it
on the community board although you guys
will have to refresh because you won't
get a notification that fast
[Music]
oh what's this
uh no wait
do you want to play
kartik ball
[Music]
do you want to play garcon
it's up let's see how fast
this
okay
i'm gonna delete it
[Laughter]
okay we're just gonna play normal i
think because i haven't played in a
while and normal is nice uh please
write your prompts
in english
[Music]
can we keep the same room for later no
i make new room
so new new url next time yeah
uh
what do we write
kiwawa burnt tongue
[Music]
okay this is my prompt for you guys
but right now actually the tea has a
good temperature
[Music]
give me something good don't give me
something [\h__\h]
froggy i get out of my fruit
time is ticking
seven eight
nine and
okay how much time do i have much time
hopefully
okay
[Music]
hug
but i use small lava as reference
[Music]
but small vowel has small arms
i think that's a really easy prompt
though
why small while i have no feathers i
always wondered what the [\h__\h] is up with
that
really important thing
and
ena what do you look like again
like
this
[Music]
flap
inna brush your hair
how to how to hung
flat and then small vowel has bubba of
course
and tentacle
nice
[Music]
hug
we still got some time so let's add some
color
character assassinate what do you mean
how can you do this again with the color
change
here
[Music]
this looks pretty accurate to me
but does it look like a hug
[Music]
i think i think this is fine
yes this was drawn by an artist
dance with chicken
i'm so cute they're dancing ah wait it's
the shuba dance wait it's the sugar
dance
shuba dance
see i'm actually good at recognizing
that remember when i was trying to make
subaru and rayna know that i'm doing the
shuba dance
i can see it here with the feet and the
hands i'm pretty sure that's the shuba
dance
[Music]
on your chicken left the stuff on now
uh stove as in the the top part right
are we trying to recall that memory
from previously
[Music]
that happened racism
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
now
[Music]
yeah unfortunately you can't see my face
but uh do you know how shocked i am
i'm i'm a bad artist i shouldn't be
participating in this at all
and
it says
[\h__\h] you i'm just trying it's not that i
agree with it but i know what you guys
mean so i'm just you know
you know i'm just going with the flow
[Music]
yeah
i'm done that's wait i mean
what's up time let me fix some things
um
yeah that's kiwa red okay well orange
no not quite uh yeah that's good that's
good
that's good and let's give me a skirt
we could give me a bath too
who wants to see kiwa but i wish i was
one of the things i could announce today
that my butt
nerf
has been undone
okay where's my taco
you're my top there you go
[Music]
beautiful
shiny butt
sunny butt
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is this
uh
what the [\h__\h] is this what the [\h__\h] is
this
um
who the [\h__\h] is that
on the side
who is that
got it
it has cat ears
and it's
it what the [\h__\h] is that
hulka
and polka looking at that
rats i don't know
can't sleeping up a keyboard okay if
he's not amused
what what
i was sleeping with keyboard oh
why is kp not amused at that
why would you not be amused with it
[Music]
it's probably a laner board
bed hair
[Music]
okay
yeah and then kfp is somewhere there
unamused
how to draw chicken again
[Music]
i don't know how to draw you guys that
doesn't look like a chicken oh wait you
need a beak oh [\h__\h] how do you
how do you make an unamused beak
how how do you make an unamused beak
i guess you just don't
[Music]
what are you guys jealous of the
keyboard
it's weird that i would sleep with it
though
is this what my hair looks like
[Music]
[\h__\h]
and time is over
town is over
looks like me oh
[Music]
go hunt for
chicken
maybe
maybe i'm on the hunt for you guys
[Music]
oh
we are looking for chickens who need to
go to the
kiwami nature
yeah it looks like a scythe
oh well
oh well well
is that a whip i think it's a scythe hmm
good at trying to math
okay
i find it
interesting i could have did like a
a class
a big brain class with others
i don't know how to draw good huh
quick
while she should be
in the classroom
[Music]
yeah
was i not included in the picture person
this probably was originally
the kiwa gouda one to five thingy
probably
let's say five
while here
we have
[Music]
one plus
six minus nine
um
frame
minus
2 3 9
i don't know what i'm doing
plus
um
60. you guys can figure this one out it
continues here
divided by
69.
is what and kona is just like
yes
that
is that's that's five
that's five
easy
i wonder what it is if that's even like
an equation that you can actually like
figure out if that makes any sense
[Music]
i want to be cats
how long are we playing this by the way
i forgot
chihuahua bill's a snowman okay wait a
second oh [\h__\h] i have no time we'll
figure it out after this round is done
oh
chihuahua builds a snowman
um
[Music]
why can't my small
my quinoa was so small
[Music]
you don't even know that that's cute now
now make orange and then you know kiwamo
[Laughter]
because small
make we make a big smile
oh it looks like i'm hiding the snowman
cute
an orange nose
i don't think i've ever in my whole life
successfully made like a proper snowman
like a good one
[Music]
he's not cold
because obviously
they need it
otherwise you're gonna be suffering look
at this beautiful scarf
this makes me look forward to the winter
time excited
wow my body lasts you
okay
body
i had to draw a smokey mama but
what happened what happened
[Music]
can i can i get my ugg boots
i need my ugg boots
yeah
i'm small
how do i make how did i make such a
gigantic
snowman huh
the
sun okay it feels like i i fell back
into how i drew out when i was three
years old
a son with a smiley face
nice
oh oh we're done oh and display mode
manual
voiceover off
exhibition flow beginning to yeah yeah
yeah okay let's take a look oh somebody
european in pain left the room why the
[\h__\h] did you do that
so my first idea was
kiwawa burn tongue on t on yaw
tizzy
drew
cute ah
you know my my feathers look like a blue
christmas tree
but this is cute also it looks like i'm
drinking tea
out of um not a cup but you know those
measuring cups the see-through measuring
cups
ah the car air freshener
uh but you're cute cute i like the i
like the tongue that
bad
he allows his tongue burnt from chicken
tea drinking tea yes that's it
[Music]
cute
oh
that's so cute
ah
hashtag blessed
looks like coffee though
but dubby also knows i don't drink
coffee kiwama drink tea
phantom cat draws
oh very consistent very consistent
that's actually i think that's not one
of the artists that i invited but
actually
actually doing well there
okey breathing fire to put out the pan
fire
oh
that but that's a tea cup yes mia
you saucy baka that's a teacup
it's a teacup
[Music]
i mean that actually happened
yeah yeah yeah yeah i blew out the fire
but wait i did not brave fire no no i
did not break fire to get rid of fire i
just i just went
normally like a normal person
oh and then they yeah
yeah ah
they got the same prompt as ymir uh gave
probably
because when someone drops out um
it just gets ignored i think
holy [\h__\h] that's so aggressive that
happened
nice
next door
it didn't stay the same throughout the
whole thing but it stayed close enough
it didn't go completely off topic
um
[Music]
oh showing the beatles okay yeah now
that you say it it makes sense
see that one
is still
recognizable
[Laughter]
i guess because of the bear ears or so
nana's showing bugs
that's a that's a caterpillar isn't it
another i mean um
a ladybug looks like a ladybug i got
plenty of those in my in my
apartment for some reason
oh gift mirror
huh
um
at least polka and ninety
are in the same generation
so
close enough actually
it was me well i mean look at that
look at that also why am i like crying
or i guess those are supposed to be my
my feathers
i'm not sure
[Music]
i love the eyes beautiful
beautiful
kiwawa and polka watching bee
sleep for me
wait will the next person figure out
that it's bae oh uh this person dipped
out though did they make it for this one
no okay
so
it ends or
ah no okay this one just gets some
skipped oh and then in some faye but
casper
yeah more accurate to kfp lore
[Laughter]
don't know
why polka is there to look at casper
because i don't think
i think i ever mentioned casper to polka
but maybe i should have introduced
casper to polka and she would have taken
care
of casper appropriately
um
nice
next on
very cute
show
himalayan new keyboard
ah this is probably what turns into
sleeping with the keyboard
why am i on the table
it's like i'm playing air guitar with
the keyboard
on the table
really passionately
oh not oh okay i can see why that looks
like i'm i'm on a bed i don't know what
the true intention was there but yeah
yeah
oh my god it's so cute
[Music]
[Applause]
it's so cute
i love it
yeah i'm sleeping with a keyboard and
kfc is not amused well they don't look
completely angry but they also don't
look
very amused indeed
yeah
yeah okay they didn't see that wait so
the next person gets to draw this again
i think
oh we got two versions of that
well i think i didn't do so badly
compared
the chicken
the chicken face
[Music]
nice oh
angry employee watching tangible sleep
at work
i can sleep at work if i want to
oh
yeah you tried
why you so mad and i'm sleeping let me
sleep it's healthy
sleeping is healthy
yeah
all right all right cute
next one
is iceberg
oh
interesting concept oh great i like that
concept
instead of the fire bird that i am
one day
i spurred cuba
has a new outfit
oh that will probably take a long time
for me to
bring to reality
but maybe
2023 or 2024
interesting
i like that
i'm making a snowman of myself
ah
that is so adorable
oh
christina
oh my god
[Music]
it was interpreted as a huge mama tony
ah
then we're having a snowball
i guess it looked a little bit too
realistic
[Music]
that chicken buried in snow i suppose
also very cute
oh [\h__\h]
ah the next person just looks at this
again and reevaluates it which is
probably yeah how we got to kiwawa build
snowman oh that's actually
kind of what was actually going on
cute that's better than my drawing
[Laughter]
wow
cute it's it's kiwawa snowman
yeah
that detail was missing when i was um
drawing it i didn't get that in my
prompt i think
what is wrong with my hair
but i like the nose
it's like a doo doo doo doot nose
chihuahua builds a snowman i mean
that was not just a snowman that was a
particular specific snowman
cute
i'm looking forward to winter time let's
go winter
and the scout art is cute too it's a
good mix i think we have a good
balance the reason
oh
what look at the prompt is that
the reason froggiada was in her throat
oh wait a second that person didn't draw
oh that person oh they attempt to draw
and then delete it
[Music]
what what is manzanita
are supposed to make out of this
[Music]
that is so well put
that is so creative and well put
abstract art let's go
um i do want to know the reason i think
we all want to know the reason why
frogiada is in my fruit
oh he's so angry with the cat probably
because the cat keeps on playing with
the art supplies and jumping on the
tablet or on the canvas and all that
it's like cheeky cat and the artist is
like the [\h__\h] cat the [\h__\h]
orange cat looking at dude and
oh man come on come on
how cute what a cute cat
and i like how you turned the orange cat
into a kiwama cat
dude very confused
and cat meow
[Music]
yes
i love
so cute
i think this
had a happy ending
something that just was not supposed to
happen
because the reason
must be a secret for now
it was it was perfectly censored by this
european
who might just be me in disguise who
just came on a mission
here
to hide the truth
and then we quickly
changed the topic yeah
yes yes that's the only thing they came
here for that's why they deceived and
contributed absolutely nothing
next on
an axon
besides protecting my secret
yeah
it makes so much sense you are my
training chickens
what um
what what what
what
i have a weird weird bulge here
why or is that my butt
is that my butt
i hope so
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] um
okay i understand
that
and that was ignored unfortunately
because this happened so they just drove
the same thing i don't know why they
don't just um let this person answer
what that is instead
hmm
what is the potential well okay
one two five
the famous
i think that's where the gouda came from
where is friend for ptsd
[Music]
the apples save the apples
oh we all understand what that means
even though there is no five here where
is the five where the [\h__\h] did the five
go there's only one left
that's right
ah
and here comes kiwawa to save the day
i think
this is uh quite
quite the effort did anybody figure out
the result
any math geniuses like olly
[Music]
okay there's the five
there's the five
oh
it's oh it's five oh yeah it must be
five
it's just five it's not solvable really
did you try
it's five okay yeah guna says it's five
then it must be five
i'm such a genius too to come up with
that
to
choose a random number and then come up
with a really complicated equation for
that on at the spot i'm i'm such a oh
wait it's actually
like about approximately -119
i got a minus 199 it's 100 minus 118. ah
most people got like a minus 118 119
nice
[Music]
we actually have some real results
with a failing kindergarten kindergarten
math
dear lord if that's kindergarten math
then i would have failed kindergarten
already
that is
that is kindergarten math
probably
yeah or preschool
[Music]
next up
nice
how would you know ah
what do you mean
because there's no x your [\h__\h] x
usual room ah
nice i like the detail that they're in
chains and there's a kiwa on the monitor
you did actually pretty well
not bad i think i would recognize it's
something like the usual room
[Music]
me on the left
chickens in the usual room watch only me
yeah okay
they got it they got the memo
oh no
like it looks like lips not like peaks
cursed chickens with lips instead of
beaks
oh
oh someone saved them
kawaii
it's like they just got brainwashed
chickens being trained nothing
suspicious
[Music]
ah
but that doesn't look like
training give me a
it looks like i'm on the hunt
but okay let's see what we get from that
wow go hunt for chicken
oh
nice
wow that chicken looks so
[Music]
that belly
i just want to hug that chicken
and blow raspberries into its tummy
cute
it's so thick and juicy
and i love the way you drew hunting
chihuahua damn
damn but i'm a bad hunter because the
chicken seems to have noticed
why
[Music]
nice okay hunting and chicken exactly
that's what i'm doing oh one more
[Laughter]
oh
this way i'm going with an axe and a gun
first shoot the chicken and then use the
axe to take it apart
thinking strategically thinking ahead
it's bloodborne oh
oh bloodborne chihuahua
interesting very cute this is one of my
favorites
this is how i get chihuahua feather oh
wait there's even more oh
so many
wait a second let me check them
four
four thirty
okay one more hour we have like one more
hour
saku chicken realizing he'll be cooked
again this like lips instead of a beak
but the chicken is cute
oh no you're not gonna be cooked i'm
gonna cook for you not not with you
no
no no no no today i'm making dinner for
you
and your chicken left the stove on oh no
oh no oh my god let's go
no
no they're gonna they don't they won't
see my eye the next person is just gonna
draw that no
my art
is being ignored
no
manzanita
that looks better that's the meme that
looks better
those round chickens
oh they're like as round as a ball
well yeah you guys at least saw it
[Laughter]
oh
that's amazing
i'm like
man you never disappoint
yeah the famous girl house on fire meme
oh
yes
you know the meme do you know the meme
we all know the meme can i set fire to
publish bad cave no no no
it was an accident i swear it was an
accident
what
jfp haven't heard that in a long time
jeff be pretty good huh oh oh oh it's me
with the lighter and the oil
okay yeah that would be a reason to set
them on fire i'll be honest yeah yeah
yeah
if i hear that
you might not survive today
next off
wait i kind of want to download that oh
well
i got that one
[Music]
wow so nice
yes
even better
it's like
this is this is 480p
and this is
2k
do we get 4k next
no
they're gonna re-evaluate that one then
yes so cute
and okay now we get 4k yes literally
or maybe 1080
and 2k
one more
oh
4k
yes oh with the tacticals
nice nice nice
yeah
so cute
oh
that is so cute
next on i think that's the last one yeah
dancing with chimpkin
yeah
it's not they didn't tell them to do the
shuba dance but i'm pretty sure they
had that in mind
[Music]
very cute nice butt i see the chicken
has a butt
he had an employee making music ah
not quite
but i guess by looking at that art you
could think that we're just singing
or having fun
um
oh we're starting a bed let's go
that guitar is huge
what is that
who's that i don't know
i'm not sure what that is kind of
singing with guitar guy
it's a chicken for god's sake look at
the feet which guy has feet like that
oh a guitar guy is callie
chicken turned into cali nice
no
why
christina what the [\h__\h] did you do and
this is gonna be empty too
oh come on guys
you're slacking
i need your finger close it up
guys
it was so fast
okay i forgive it's okay
ah guys i need to go quickly to an idol
meeting and then we'll start another
round
yeah
brb
[Music]
i'm back
wait a second
[Music]
probably gonna have to use a few
less people so that the round is gonna
be a bit shorter
because
don't have that much time left i think
including preparation time
is this still hot
yeah
okay
i'm gonna make
a bit more tea
[Music]
understandable welcome back thank you
come on honey
honey
honey come on
i don't have time for your [\h__\h]
come on
[Music]
drop somewhere else
come on i need to buy more honey this
bottle is almost empty
[Music]
anyway are you hearing this
come on
yeah
oh
okay i got some
some honey
okay
now wait a second
[Music]
thank you for participating
gonna make a new round
no
oh god that's some
advertisement about some stupid
i don't even know i don't even know what
you would call this shitty game
the lady sound i know it sounded erotic
but it's just like
you know some towers of enemies inside
and the dude is trying to get to the
girl
yeah yeah yeah go away skip skip skip
okay
i know i know it sounded weird
but it was nothing weird about it
did i have 12 players before or 10.
you guys remember
yeah yeah yeah you know that ad thank
god
tell them tell them it wasn't something
weird
i had ten okay let's do eight i guess
[Music]
okay
then
invite link ghost is going out
oh
yeah
we might fill it up with artists only
this time
perhaps
um depending on how many i have
show
[Music]
come on come on come on come on ah
twitter keeps on sabotaging me
doesn't want to send out the link
let it happen
let them in
good
yay
[Music]
and dakuma
come
and
[Music]
you
hello come
one two three
guys check your dms
oh who else hmm
this this person i i don't know if they
are here are you here
do you want to
do you want to join
you can join come on
we have
three more spots let's see
i think some
people uh
are gone by now
all right
oh you didn't get the link
now oh pablo nasty
who joined this papua new guinea
what
who is this
got it
who is
someone i invited but i don't i didn't
invite anyone with the name pablo nasi
got it got it
we're full
did everybody
get in
did
did you get in
if if somebody who was gonna
um join
didn't get in let me know
[Music]
i have a feeling i know who it is but
then i could be wrong
i could be
wrong oh
oh
no problem
uh no then i'm wrong who is this maybe
oh [\h__\h] ah
twitter
wait i added another player because
twitter sabotaged me and didn't let a
specific person join
here one nice space
yay
okay
oh
okay i guess we're gonna do ten after
all but you guys gotta be fast
you have to be fast we have to i'm just
gonna review the art much faster than
before
go go
go go go go go go go
um
how much how much time do i have until
the collab
oh
i know who papanashi is now
someone called tanuki
an artist called tanuki
only only 40 minutes but i need to set
up okay okay
let's go
fast be fast
uh a prompt
um
[Music]
what's the word pillow fight
done
on the screen i forgot
quick get your prompts guys have no time
drinks hot chocolate and dies why the
[\h__\h] would i die i love hot chocolate it
was poisoned
no
no why would i die a lot i haven't
drunken
hot chocolate in a long time though
i should maybe this is a sign
that i should
okay
oh my god so ugly
[Laughter]
your belly button belly button is dead
too
um but of course
booby
important detail
and then we have
um
hot chocolate but it's gonna i know why
because i thought it was hot chocolate
but in reality it was
coffee
[Music]
i thought it was choco
i am [\h__\h] coffee [\h__\h]
ha ha
bamboozle
it's a big bamboozled the biggest
bumblezza of the century
i'm creating history making a story
out of this
[Music]
where were you when kiwa was killed
huh
i was
playing a game of gothic phone
i'm dead
thank you forever
yeah i'm dead
i'm dead
starbucks
cup
oh that's such a beautiful green oh
beautiful done
go next
i was watching you last year during the
legendary shadow bamboozle
oh
you mean that time when i was killed
[Music]
who drew this
so cute
mama
take photo of
cute cute owl
yeah cute
so cute
love you mama instagram girlfriend
oh
i miss nabi mama
nabi mama doko
numbi mama
nami
[Music]
mama can get some beer from chihuahua
yeah
oh i'm like oh no no i don't need that
beer thank you you can have it
hmm
yeah yeah
a german beer
[Music]
i know how to draw a beer
beautiful
what a masterpiece
[Music]
um
cute
here i draw my feathers
they look kind of like that
i am i'm a bartender now
i used to i used to pour beer into
big beer glasses
you have to hold them sideways
so that it doesn't
overflow
and now we draw a chimken
[Music]
cute
chicken chicken needs a beer belly
honestly
but
i'm so cute i love chickens honestly
this whole
life as kiwawa made me love chicken so
much
i found
an appreciation for chickens that
i would have never had otherwise
[Music]
i could
i'm i'm practically done we can move on
to the next one please
go
i'll go go
yes and you found appreciation of
the marvelous
gorgeous fabulous animal that is a
chicken
same actually
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
garfield just looks so
i i never used this word before but i
think a good way to describe it is
uncanny
right what does it actually mean i feel
like it fits in this situation
uncanny
i think that's a good word
oh god it's such a creepy face
straight favorite night oh
the thing that comes to mind
immediately for some reason
is when me and and uh ame were dancing
on the disco floor
in
um rest
yeah
let's see
and how do i do this when i already drew
the floor
like i need like approximately this area
probably
ah
yeah
[Music]
yeah and bounce and bounce and bounce
that's so cute like people made jiff's
gifts out of it
animations like they cut it into a gif
and it looks so cute
it actually looked so good
i had to show it to amit afterwards i
sent her a link because i wanted her to
see how it looked on stream
because she probably had no idea what i
was doing
in that situation
[Music]
yeah now quick we need ahmed uh
i'm
however was just this big dude
[Music]
yeah that's ahmed
that's so scary
i just have no time i need to be fast
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm enjoying this shitty art
sleep paralysis demon
[Music]
oh god um
yeah
that's dad
thank god we have some good artists here
oh
and kiwawa
holding hands nervously
done
i drew a jinx
but when
you just censor this am i gonna get
banned again oh no
oh maybe this was drawn by pablo nashi
tick-tock
time is running out
go go go go
you are falling from heaven to bless
chicken as i always do that's how i was
born obviously
okay
i wish a good artist would get this
prompt but okay i guess it came to me
i will try so this is the chicken
being blessed
[Music]
that's cute can i just end it here
now here comes
chihuahua
i just dropped myself from the back then
are you guys hearing this holy music too
shabbat bang
chabity bang noises
and then we have give give me some
yeah a halo
and
some wings oopsie no no we don't want
them to be so pink
yeah beautiful
this is literally a scene from the bible
yeah yeah yeah
wow wait the chicken is so big
chicken is humongous
compared to
me
here's some orange so you guys actually
know it's supposed to be me
oh no time
holy holy wawa
bliss blessed be the chicken
i think i'm i'm done
besides the fact that apparently i'm
bold
there you go
perfect
yeah
nice
holy jaw
chubby bang oh
[Applause]
[Music]
mound
chica rest
is this understandable everest chica
rest
[Laughter]
hmm
chica rest
mom's chickerest
mount chicorus i want to climb to mount
chicas
it's my everest
that looks like dakuma art
taco that's the chicken lore and eena
watches
[Music]
okay
are you not just watchers where is kiwa
line dead
but they look like they look like
pac-man when i draw them like this oh
because
they don't have their flaps okay i was
wondering why does this look like
pac-man
that's what happens to taco dodges
if they don't have their flaps
will give you the flaps
i don't have enough time for this oh my
god
a war normally has
more than just one
this is a gun
this is also a gun
this is a sword this is a sword
this is the sword wait we're we're going
in with guns this time yeah yeah
always know your enemy
and then uh oh god one more chicken come
on
i don't know what kind of gun is it this
is but it's it's good gun and then
and then inna inna just
you know just observing
oh no no time
does this look like eli doesn't look
like
do something
hmm
okay
that's the best i can do in that short
amount of time
we're already finished nice okay manual
we have to be a bit faster this time how
much more time do i have i have no time
okay let's go
uh-huh
faster faster faster faster oh you need
anything i would play pillow fight
wait
there's one person missing there's kobo
missing where is cobalt club is already
bedtime kobo has to sleep
only nicki we're having a pillow fight
ah
this is lena kind of unrecognizable what
the [\h__\h] happened with me
i look like
i'm like coming out of the shadows
to ground pound them
yes yes yes yes
oh
good me add
cute
to faces
wait why am i losing
why am i losing
i should be winning
absolutely body kiana in a pillow fight
alright
[\h__\h]
the indonesians are all over me
what
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh it's cute
it's so cute
even though they lost kobo and me
why
kiana and kfb jet plane
cause i'm
leaving all the chat play
i don't know when i'll be back again
oh bad
i hate to
i i i didn't do this guys it's guru mia
can i flying plane to the liver
configurations
[Music]
coming
oh cute ah
i see
i understand now
uh
in
five to ten minutes for lisa
from heaven to bless the chicken
yes that's exactly what's happening here
beautiful
angel keep our blessed chicken with your
presents
it's like what happens when um chicken
walks into meet-and-greet room and sees
kiwawa this is what they're the chicken
is seeing literally an angel on the
screen
wow
[Laughter]
you did put some work into the pose
there nice that's what i had in mind
when i was drawing mine but i couldn't
draw it so well
wow
holy chicken
i'm saving this one too i like that
goku
drinks hot chocolate and dies
unrealistic prompt but okay
it's coffee it was coffee no
your dad figuring out whether it's
coffee or chocolate
wow another realistic one damn
[Laughter]
damn
rick couldn't even ride rip
oh did i write that on there with my
finger i wonder i tried and then i died
um
[Music]
clap me see please
okay
get exhausted after
after exercise or something
after the 12 hours
i wonder i wonder how i will feel
afterwards i think mentally i'll still
be really really excited and happy but
um
i will
my voice will be drained probably this
is the future dakuma you can look into
the future i yo
hey
yo
yeah it wakes up after 12 hours
oh
i guess
yeah i think that's probably how i would
feel after
sleeping for 12 hours
because recently compared to like four
years ago i definitely do sleep less
yeah
because it feels
i can't sleep so much at once anymore i
have to like spread it out
into two parts
cute
i like the alarm clock it looks like the
alarm clock has eyes
i see eyes everywhere
wow i didn't wake up early clock is dead
she's drooling that's a very specific um
description
[Music]
sorry i'm writing to oli i am going to
be on this channel soon
cute i don't
okay i wanted to say i don't drool when
i sleep but i guess recently i remember
there was one night where i was
definitely drooling when i was half
asleep
a little bit a little bit just a little
bit
cute
thank you next one odakuma prompt will
be
kiwamo meets garfield
[Music]
oh we're gonna get a lot of uncanny
garfield art now
garfield's shaking hands
yeah
oh yeah that's that's the one
that face look at that face
in garfield
oh god that that doesn't look like
garfield anymore
that's an imposter that's even worse
than an imposter
that is not garfield
but it was recognized as garfield thank
god
good deal yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah good
deal we are making some lasagna deals
yum yum yum yum
that's why recently i can't find lasagna
in the
in the supermarket anymore because it's
being directly delivered to me
close business deal
nice
beautiful [\h__\h] i should have saved that
lots of garfield and kiwawa interactions
here in the mountains alps oh
makes me want to sing sound of music and
the hills are alive
with the sound of music
wow
inspiring
now that picture makes me want to climb
a mountain
oh looking over the alps yes my kingdom
it's my wow
i like that i'm just this little blob
but it's so cute i'm just
some chewing gum that someone spit out
but you put so much work into the
background it looks actually nice this
could be a postcard
noise
amazed by cool mountain view as i
probably would be yeah
wow look wow mountains noise
pushing some good mountains wow much
nature yeah i'm touching grass
and touching grass and snow oh chicken i
knew this was dakuma
chicken mountain
chihuahua found the mount chicorist
wow
[Music]
i love it
sad
nice
i need to find manchu chris now for real
me mama
yeah oh that was dakoma too oh
cute
now we wanna take photos
yay
cute that's exactly the pose that i did
yup yup yup yup
yeah yeah yeah okay how can we
um change this up so that it's
unrecognizable
oh that's perfect
i love that outfit
rocking those boots
wow i love the outfit
this looks like some kind of i don't
know
70 no
i'm thinking of like
um that hair musical
that kind of style
uh
uh what was it hairspray shampoo
what was it
was it called hairspray
what a weird [\h__\h] name i know grease
grease
but why are you gonna sing hairspray
there's no hairspray
i'm thinking of grease
the [\h__\h] way that that was called
great hairspray
[Laughter]
now we've been kiana doing our idol
concert on the street ah
there is also a hairspray musical
what
what a lame name wow
wow
she do be performing
oh it turned into elena understandable
because of that blue hair piece yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
this is realistic too
oh so cute
that's of navi mama
fan art now
um
go have a nice sharing cake
we did do that in the maldives i brought
some cake
didn't i
yeah i brought some cake but not cake
like that it was a
chocolate cake
small chocolate cakes
that one looks yummy too
we already look super chubby in this one
nice
waiting in kiwawa on day ah that's where
the cake gets lost
oh
oh it's like like a story
we eat some cake together we get fat
then we're gonna walk
i like those nervous faces
oh
cute
[Music]
load
sensor
i can't show this on
on
live tv
i thought your spy is a mogus
they got us
oh no you think i don't recognize you of
those flaps
wow
holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
damn
that's very intimidating
cult of the tackle
and i think there's a chicken being
sacrificed there
wow
inspiring [\h__\h] right here inaudible
[Music]
wants to see the world burn
attack
oh
here it is
[Laughter]
i feel like i would be the one to order
that though not inna
dental can serving beers to drunk
chicken ah
diendle i was supposed to wear a dandel
cute i like the green one
wow so many beers
she can get some beer from quinoa
yeah
ah
[Music]
that's more like a waitress more fitting
that's oktoberfest kiwawa
okay why am i handing out a cold one for
the boys
oh
it's coca-cola
you know honestly if i would have gotten
that prompt i may have not understood
what a cold one means either
yeah that's um
i think ili chan
is uh not her first language is not
english either
so yeah we both wouldn't have understood
probably
oh but that i guess that that does say
beer ice cold
but they're they are drinking cola at
the moment
what
that's cute i need to sell that glass
shape as merchandise
that's so cute
whoa
i mean the color is perfect
richness wow
chicken bottle bam
wow wow
we learned
so many new things
merch idea okay last one
yes
nice
that's reality
on my birthday
hype concert yes yes
yeah
those stages on fire
straight people ah that's where dad came
from oh oh oh oh i'm sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah that's the kiwawa paper night
clothes um
[Music]
damn
amazing absolutely amazing guys thank
you so much for participating in a round
of a garlic phone we now have uh past
the second stage of my 12 hour marathon
i will uh go set up the next thing
where we will have elena only and
cover as a guest so i'll see you in
as soon as possible to be honest
[Music]
bye bye
stay
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
pushing me
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
foreign
break away
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
me
away
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
it says poor connection on my side on my
side too we're live
[Music]
yes we're on screen now everybody say hi
to my guests
hi
yo
let's have some introduction starting
from
uh my left side kobo
okay
at your service let baby our son design
your date okay
from hawaii
and your stomach is awesome
[Music]
you can be in you can be my son yes
yeah yeah yeah people say i'm the son
because i'm a phoenix
but i understand why you would be oh
that's son i thought son s-o-n
my daughter my daughter my child
yay okay thank you for joining and good
morning kobo just woke up
yeah i heard a little bit of a kobo
morning voice
i'm good
okay and then we have of course lena
yeah
attention please and favorite reigning
from whole life id generation two thank
you kiwama for inviting me guys
[Music]
have i told you i love you later
[Laughter]
yeah and then we have the uh the one who
takes up the most space on the screen
only
[Laughter]
happy anniversary senpai
yeah
happy anniversary mommy
yeah two years it's been two years now
crazy crazy but not as crazy as kudaiji
only
okay we're gonna play this weird game
ultimate chicken horse uh does
everything sound okay chad is it
relatively balanced and is the game
lagging or not
only a little loud no problem that's her
standard uh stage
only always loud
yeah follow her a little bit but
we need only to be loud these three
girls i'm gonna help you save some
some voice for later
thankfully yeah
i got a lot a lot of loud girls with me
what happens when you get in the well oh
oh my god oh whoa what's that
oh level loader can you come back up
though
oh sorry i think you can shoot oh
i can oh yeah
thank you
i didn't actually i didn't see the
answer from the chat what did you guys
say is everything okay besides only
being loud
stopping nine eight
seven
starting
it's okay four three two one and let's
go
um
before i played it before what about you
i don't know
oh i don't know about this game
i think this game um you choose an item
um first and then you place it somewhere
to make it easy for you to get to the
goal but difficult for the others to get
there
does everybody have like uh different
skills
no well everybody has a different item
but besides that we're all the same
ah
oh i get chad well my obs screen is
really laggy
try turning off the thing
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's all about skills
easy no points yeah
i don't get it
you have to make it more difficult
more difficult
[Music]
interesting yeah that already looks more
difficult
but i think that's really smart from the
game to recognize that it was too easy
[Music]
oh so like the items just like keep
stacking
[Music]
when everyone gets to the ball no one
gets a point yeah
what's that
this red light green light
what the heck is that oh we have two of
those
yeah
i have no idea what this is okay oh
interesting
[Music]
it's not so easy
yeah it's too laggy oh wait wait a
second why is it so lagging i i like
um is it laggy on your side or on the
stream side
i see you lagging on obs but not on
on the game screen
oh is your v-sync uh on oh i turned it
off
yeah maybe you turn it on unless it is
like frame limits
we think on
okay
let's see if that happens
[Music]
oh my god what the heck what the heck i
got crushed by a flower and i do that
you got punched by a windmill
buy a flower
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't even know the flower can punch
you
the hat
well at least it wasn't so easy anymore
we keep on improving this place
apparently also you can rotate
oh this this will hurt i don't even know
what is going on now i can't put it
there why not
oh because i need a platform to put it
on maybe
oh a yeah that's like a platform i think
or like
oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh oh oh oh
i don't know here
okay i guess we're going without that
thing
fine with me
[Music]
if people die from my trap
you'll also get a point
oh dad what the heck is this
is it a bomb
it's fine but what is that like gooey
thing is that like booger
i don't know i died from my own trap i
think i'm sorry
that does happen
sorry guys i'll have to figure it out
but it's it's only our [\h__\h] not again
our only our avatar like this on the
whole
this stupid thing that i put oh
i can't pass through that
um
everyone died
yeah i i don't i don't actually know
what that was
uh no and there's no points
well we all died amazing
yeah we all have backgrounds from the
same thing i forgot i didn't know what
it was what that was wait i want to try
fixing the game but the game keeps on
going
i want to fix it
[Music]
it's a flower
wait how'd it get there
[Music]
thank you
nice
nice drop points
yeah
oh yeah what is this how about how about
now
okay is it already enough what the [\h__\h]
oh my
what what is that
ah the flower is way too much
oh no did you
[Music]
okay
now may not
i will help you all i'll put a i'll put
a platform for you all
oh it's so sweet of you you mean down
there at the bottom i couldn't even
reach that plane hell yeah
engineer
[Music]
that those spikes
oh my god
wait a minute
that's a lot of traps
oh freaking guys
i don't understand
i'm sorry
five times more flame tellers
[Music]
oh my god what even
ah
not today oh no not today well that
gives me time to figure out what's going
on
[Music]
okay
slowly
can we cut there like can we go like
yeah
slowly but sure
oh no i died
[Music]
said oh come back it's real
wow she's a natural at this game
i'm a gamer girl
girl
of course you're a gamer girl because
you take after your game of mommy
yeah give her mommy
i'll make it really difficult oh this
will [\h__\h] everything up
what is it
is that a black hole yes i placed
beverly hills
oh my god
what the hell how do we even huh don't
jump there we go oh there we go what
the
what
the heck
oh my god please
perfect placement
yeah oh no wait if if you could go for
the door it would be fine but somehow
yeah
oh my god it's either death or the door
oh no
oh no no she's gonna wrap points though
no no
all right um how are we gonna get
through that
let's build above it to get like on top
of it for some truth some somehow but i
don't know
block it but
i think i ruined it wasn't there like a
way of destroying items you already
placed i
really yeah possible
i saw it before yeah i played the game
the last time but i think this should
help
what
oh whoa whoa okay i'm stuck
oh no no not suck anymore but okay yeah
we're talking yes oh no
oh no
i was oh no oh
i'm still here
oh no mommy dad touching it okay wow
[Music]
i think it's possible though the way we
just built it
oh damn okay
yeah
i'm a horse though she's the dark horse
nice
[Music]
knife what is that that's a different oh
a different place yeah different place
but still pretty similar
go go stopping
party starting
[Music]
don't make it too crazy girls
yeah
but also not too easy
oh there's a balloon up there with a
gift
are we
nice
can we even get this we don't i don't
think we can even reach
oh
[Music]
i see
it's good that i found it because i'm
the toast let's let's like make a pack
first yeah okay yeah i feel like so like
somebody cannot leave so we can go
okay i'll do this that already works
yeah this one works okay
oh what the hell is
that also kills i think
no because i died it's not going to be
deemed as too easy
yeah yeah
yeah okay died together
yeah okay
that was pretty good
[Music]
thank you what is this clock
good question
oh
no no ollie don't you dare
where [\h__\h] i put this one maybe here
yes you're right
okay oh what is
oh that's what the clock did it made it
so that it's a slow motion
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
game says i'm the underdog okay i'll
prove everyone that i i'll have more
clocks
if you're a chicken
oh my god ollie has some respect
but you are a chicken look at your
avatar's a chicken is that a dog that
that's
somebody
oh
[Music]
go can she make it
can she save herself
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
back let's oh
nice
oh
ooh what is this fancy let's see if kobo
remembers how to think with portals
portal that looked like a portal yeah
i don't know what that is
oh oh
couple put something down there down
there to help the ones who fall down
that's so kind yeah oh
that's so sweet
what does this do
the portal's not opening up
oh
the paper plane is cute yeah
cute wait is there damage for the paper
plane
i don't know or you can ride it
i don't know if it's friendly or if it's
a phone it's so easy bruh anyone who
wants to try it out
try out riding the paper plane with this
box
i'm gonna put a box another paper plane
here so it's like annoying this will
self sabotage
airplane more airplanes
airplanes yeah more airplanes
[Music]
[Applause]
i like that one i want a bomb
oh we got the same ollie
oh
great minds think alike
that is so annoying
[Music]
oh
that was mean
that was mean i agree i want to cover
that i can rotate blocks what's that
even mean
what is this
what happened
if i
oh
oh what the heck oh
oh no i died
oh wait can i pass
oh what the heck
oh
[Music]
that's a problem i don't think so
because the fire um fire thingy blocks
the oh oh oh oh oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
the chicken falls today i'm dead thank
you forever wow
again there we go
maybe
one more thing at the bottom so
not that
yeah
yes yes that one
yeah cobra
all right
decided
oh [\h__\h] oh wait
[Music]
oh i'm safe
oh
oh you're safe right
oh yes thank you yeah
nice good
wait what he died i died nice ride
thank you
oh no i'm almost there
this one this one was more fun because
we kind of understood what does what
yeah
we learned
[Music]
the old mansion
yeah i think i guess i have to climb up
let me see
oh there there yeah
there we go
party at the old mansion let's go
mansion let's go
let's die chad how bad is the lag tell
me please i think it got better than
before at least but i still see some lag
a little bit
maybe it's maybe it's like that i have
all of us in
in one room that's [\h__\h] it up no lag
oh thank god okay now that okay it's so
cute how every time combo looks down you
can only see her little hole again
[Music]
oh
oh they already have some stuff here huh
[Music]
oh oh okay yeah okay that's good oh that
is annoying i'm gonna go for the
presents though i think that's another
new stage let's see if i can oh
[Music]
a checkpoint
is that what that is checkpoint no way
okay i will try to get the present i'll
give you girls a win
you can go without me
i will sacrifice myself
for the prison
you're a present
oh
wow maybe i can be your present
then does that mean i can open you up
uh yeah but fill me with some spices
william oh let's go
[Music]
it's like a snow squirrel yeah lisa can
join us
oh what the [\h__\h] is that
is like a parrot always repeating what
mommy said i just wasted that
yeah
thinking hard about that placement
yeah that's awful what the hell we have
to we have to get to the very top
oh no what
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
the bomb at the bottom it looked like a
bomb oh my god jet pack
i got the fire guinea
wait did we click it at the same time
because i also got it
oh
[Laughter]
wow
nice wow
challenging oh no
i like putting here
don't
wow oh god
you know what i think i might need this
where's the jet pack yo to use yo jet
pack please
what the what
finally first oh spikes
yeah
oh no i just focused on winning for once
okay quick question for you guys usually
when you guys take a shower which part
do you guys watch
okay
nice thank you what what did you say
only i think my boobies you guys take a
shower the uh which part of your body do
you wash first my heart oh first
my body
your what
i mean you have head and then body and
legs right
and hands
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm dead again faster faster
wait you guys are making oh i have a
joke okay if you have the jet pack why
do you take this complicated brute
i'll try
no
[Laughter]
it's too easy
now place the dab back there
you got to get rid of it
[Music]
okay now it's really difficult to
arrange man
man
how do we how do we even get up there
look now there you go but here is it out
there
ah boy i got the backpack
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah what do you say in english i have
no idea
taking a nap
like i'm thinking about except for death
yeah it's like
you're dead but then you suddenly wake
up again it's like zombie but not really
you're still a human oh
direction a coma
a coma
no no it's not a coma you literally it's
like
you literally die i think
[Music]
that's the only one
no wow okay oh what's this looks fun
what's wrong what's that
oh
it makes you die
[Music]
yeah
yeah we were impaled
[Music]
wait i'm not win i'm not winning yet oh
you didn't walk in
yeah i was like
just chilling
oh the black hole oh yes black hole not
the black hole and the bamboo is along
with the black hole
[Music]
oh i hate that so much and the fact that
there's a trampoline
that's a problem
[Music]
i'll come back with the flame chiller i
swear
oh
what the heck
what the heck nice ollie she's got
[Applause]
[Music]
that's gonna turn around right
i thought they were gonna
[Laughter]
i just go simple
i want to create more chaos already
chaos
it's still too easy
what are you doing kobo
wait wait what's crap
[Music]
is
i gotta make that side a lot more
difficult you can't die there okay nice
oh cool
[Music]
more fire nice flame jelly needs more
fire
[Music]
needs more saw how do you flip it oh
yeah like that
we can flip it yeah yeah so cute
pressing
oh
oh cool i hate it oh
[Laughter]
we already have the black hole that's
bad enough
yeah
more flame colors
how do we fix this
there's no way you don't going
through oh maybe
no
i don't know how to fix this
that's what are you trying that's the
thing
what is that i can't fix it
[Music]
i got penetrated and i walked into the
black hole
oh he'd almost had it what the hell is
that stupid thing under the black hole
what the [\h__\h] no cover
ah you got this you got this wait
yeah that's i wanted to jump on top of
the flame for a two but then it still
sucked me in
yeah let's let's see i need to calculate
the
how far can we jump okay oh she's doing
maths
one
like here we go from here
and then we have one job
oh what the heck
okay
okay i got you see watch and learn
what anyway
okay okay
we're watching we'd love to see it
okay oh it's telling you
just give up
how do we pass
you know what we need some actual paths
yeah that's look at that that's what the
game is giving us yeah the game's like
you guys suck here
i'm getting rid of this i'm sorry where
am i
oh oh there okay
it's out this way too knowing we already
have the black one
what did you get rid of
the spikes oh
they're way too annoying oh
okay okay okay
new cap let's see
okay
that was not a good idea
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
congratulations
[Music]
okay
everybody's gonna hate me oh
really don't you
[Applause]
i don't think it's okay just so you know
it's impossible
oh she's doing it she's doing it she's
doing something
no no no it's gonna tell you to give up
again soon
oh
okay um i actually might
consider helping yes
you should
i hate the flower
oh okay
i'm sorry
yeah i hate the flower too
i made it too high i think
oh well it might still work you guys
will figure it out
cool still has zero points
don't worry she's the underdog
[Music]
oh you almost touched that dad
oh how did you laugh kobo
because i'm a pro player wait i i i
don't know how to
jump
cool
so difficult
[Laughter]
now
[Music]
that should help oh oh oh oh
i'm gonna
[Music]
this is troubling
oh no
whose idea was this what the [\h__\h]
come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
returns left
i will destroy something
but okay
what do we want to destroy
um
no
i want to destroy those [\h__\h] glass
spikes but oh well
can you
um no only items that we placed
by my black hole this is how how you get
freedom
oh that would make things a lot easier
welcome
too easy
too easy sadly
[Music]
where next oh god oh no
oh oh oh no there was the eye i see
oh do you see hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
at least someone jumped on my trap
nice oh
i don't think she's [\h__\h] kidding you
she will die from that i'm telling you
[Music]
that's unreachable
oh this is sticky i can't jump realize
oh
[Music]
it try it go go get it you did that
it gave me a boost
i am giving you a boost
you could have died from that um
thing
[Laughter]
mommy not make it uh
she just won because she killed all of
us
exactly are you calling her a murderer
yeah
murderer
well okay hmm
i i don't know if there's any other
levels or if we just keep on using those
free ones we should be able to get more
but where where are they
where are they we just have to play more
until they get more levels maybe there's
one at uh in the underground let me
check underground let's go underground
wow
[Music]
blank level one blank level oh maybe you
can like make levels or something
yeah and i guess maybe if we do one of
those maybe it will give us new levels
probably because there's abc all those
should be filled with levels i think
it's a free play okay a rooftop question
mark
oh no this is like a level maker
okay
huh how do we fill it well our inventory
oh
oh so much choice
chad's saying
oh
chad's saying like there's something on
the rooftop okay something that has like
a question mark do you want to exit and
check this that out
okay
so
um i wonder if quit would make us leave
the group let's see
ah return to treehouse okay
okay let's check the rooftop
[Music]
uh here
a rooftop
yes yes farm wanna check the first level
or a rooftop
ah i guess the question mark shows that
there's still something to find there
okay okay okay okay
all right
i'm gonna go back to the farm
only next to the farm
i'm trying to get back
this is what happens
wow
yeah when i'm a zombie it's hard to
actually get up to like the oh yeah
it's okay it happens sometimes
huh oh huh wait wait wait wait wait no
no no i think it's this one i think it's
because the game mode is free
there is a like a gift there too let me
play something try to reach it
oh i'm sorry maybe it's because i kind
of press buttons
uh
how can i
yeah i don't think it's supposed to be
free play
i think
i wanna
no this is like a
like you test out they're like you put
things and then you test them okay
change mode oh when did i change the
mode
uh no i was only kind of changed it oh
there mode free play
party i think that's what it is party
yes party oh party i see
pop
party there we go party party
okay
another challenge a waste
uh wait a minute
okay
waiting
oh boys yeah gone
koopa
no it's just her i'll just sprout
can you guys start drinking from it
oh
i need to get closer
yeah i'll need you to get good she's
already back
i'm back
see you look i'm the only one who picks
like okay look look look look look see
oh thank you that's so nice whoever
placed that piece of wood there thank
you it was me
genius
thank you
so nice i only care about winning
i got it
is that from like barbie the island
princess one
[Music]
when did you girls watch
your last barbie movie
uh
last time we watched
us
all right we did yeah in reyna's house
like like a sleepover and you want your
barbie movie
wait was it a sleepover um i think like
who somebody stayed over kobo stayed
over i think
yeah i stayed over
oh i i noticed all the time like on
twitter
like when you guys post like voice
messages so often i notice you guys do
so many sleepovers and visit each other
i'm jealous
mom you should visit
i want to be here sleepovers too with
you girls
yeah
yeah sleep with
what the hell is that
i like the flamethrower
really
really good addition
you better all die now
what the
okay i lost
[Laughter]
[Music]
with that thing you can destroy some
items that you don't like
very effective
[Music]
that's what i thought
oh my god
[Music]
i keep on getting fried what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] oh sorry oh my god
i'm gonna destroy something
pisses me off here
what pisses you off everything
[Music]
what the flamethrower
is
oh
thank
you
that is ridiculous
well huh
you destroyed one of the platforms oh
okay and there's still other ones
oh
all right
oh yeah
[Music]
all right there's only a flamethrower in
it but oh
game
oh at least people don't always kills
people which one was it uh the
flamethrower
mummy loves a good flamethrower
what is that what is that
what is that only
oh i see oh
there we go
oh oh it's going to break
let's
i'm go
oh
you're smashed
oh you can go there
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh you got the coin coin is counted okay
what's this
i'm making them very easy down
there because no one wants to go up
seeing no one wants to fly
[Laughter]
man
oh no
damn pixel
um
[Music]
oh look
a flying platform this would be really
useful
wow
uh
i'm
we're are we self sabotaging again
beautiful
how about this
i want to try going
up this time okay
[Music]
i'm sorry mommy
oh no i died
[Music]
yeah
how does she do it
what's her secret also one second let me
check rocky i said rocky
is to have precious gem mates and
precious
friends and precious waifu
for the power of friendship
i know friendship is magic let's try
rooftops again
[Music]
[Laughter]
it is your favorite again a twilight
toyota sparkle my little pony sparkle
what what a sparkle it's a purple pony
purple oh god
wait all three of you like my little
pony
um i never actually watched it
i don't ollie let me let me put this
here i think it would be fun
it's not even like bad
i'll put this here then
you know this is already whack oh i need
to how am i supposed to
whoa
the thing is how do we jump
sticky
oh and the middle part is clear yeah
good luck
oh man
yo
get up
let's add more
you girls watch a lot of like children
stuff huh i need to keep up
barbie and then and milo
what do you know
do you not watch it
no come on i need to get the one
[Music]
it's okay you still can't get the
balloons
there we go
nice
oh you discovered the old mansion
exactly i was down there how did i
discover
random or what i guess so
i guess so yeah
oh someone munching on some chips
kobo i see you're munching come on
come on flame chiller no snacks before
dinner kobold
why
because then you can't eat the dinner
properly
i need my
snack to get focused can i mommy please
mommy
ah
she sent me these scares didn't play
i'm eating you right now
you are a bad child you you deserve some
ass spanking
but i'm eating i'm eating
um excuse me kirsten i am also a bad
child
excuse me i am bad at everything and i
am a child
no no
no near to ollie always just want to get
spanx
what are those moves oh [\h__\h] oh my god
oh no
oh my god
wow we died together
nice
nice still no winners hmm i'm kind of
hungry what are you munching on
everyone starts munching
um chicken burger
wow oh my gosh
that sounds good why do you have a
chicken burger
why you want you want it too mommy no
[Music]
i mean is it like a burger king or
mcdonald's or it's mcdonald's
you disappoint me child
should be keep
[Music]
yeah you have to buy it from kfp
now i want to order some burgers as well
oh cool oh
clutch wow you got this you
[Music]
i saw that coming i knew that was gonna
happen
i'm going to order some dumplings
yes
and then maybe some
um
[Music]
am i gonna put this
[Laughter]
look at that and i thought it's like a
surface but apparently not the screams i
always think that that thing is a
surface
oh
cobalt
can you do it this time well i'm going
to order food
i don't know
oh i don't think it's
oh anything is possible anything is
possible anything is possible
possible
b
b b
how did you do that
oh [\h__\h]
no
give up no what the heck
no give up i'm never gonna give can i
get a gift
there's always be cover just reminding
you
a circle on my end oh controller huh
yes
yeah on your dead body oh my gosh we're
not winning any of this
we will eventually i'm gonna i'm gonna
put like a path because
this is so annoying wait can you help me
build a path um up here to the top
i'm gonna use this for
the bottom sorry because it really
messes with my brain like i thought it's
like a surface but apparently it's not
no please pull it up up up left yes
somewhere there uh bit a bit more to the
right
yeah
why you put the coin there that's so
weird
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
i mean you put it up there for free
finders keepers right
yeah
the coin is not free or required
money is not free
[Music]
oh
no your face is
[Music]
i don't think because there's like the
flamethrower yeah
um
as long as all they still haven't given
up like see
she's not getting
[Applause]
oh you guys you guys are leaving
another black hole
down
[Music]
[Laughter]
good luck getting it
[Music]
that's too high for me
come down
nice
and discover something new
but it was disgusting
okay okay then we have to try to get the
other one too
oh
nice jump oh clutch
oh nice
oh
um where oh no to the right side
[Music]
i'll try oh
i suddenly received like an achievement
called animal cruelty yeah i saw that
too
much i think i have it but everybody can
um i might oh i'll do a platform um
[Laughter]
hey this path is good
why did i do this to myself
oh mommy got that
yeah
old mansion for cover i'm buying a
mansion for yeah
oh
what if the game says it's too easy one
of you guys got to die
oh [\h__\h] no yeah no it's too easy nobody
gets a point nice oh no
it's all about that sabotage baby
sabotage
[Music]
come on
wait for it for the jet pack users make
it difficult
the jet pack is gone
is it a one time thing oh god
that was one time
oh [\h__\h] nope
nope
it was the pig
the [\h__\h] pain me
you can see on my right side here it
says poor connection it's the ping i'm
telling you okay man why the hell is
there a door
so you can go to welcome you in oh it's
actually yeah
oh my god i put this thing by myself
okay nice
nice uh oh
i'm the underdog now i like being under
okay only under dog now
under under what
what
[Music]
but what's up dog if you're under a dog
did i say something no bad no
where should i put this thing
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
whoops oops
[Music]
i wish i was sorry
oh [\h__\h]
i'm sorry mommy i'm sorry cursing in
your stream oh don't worry we always
curse on my streams always always we
always curse nice yeah it would be weird
if we wouldn't oh
i can't
well well well well
just die if it isn't this time
consequences of your actions hmm
consequences of my actions what do you
mean maya of everybody's actions
yeah
i didn't place anything there
except there's anything there either
except the big thing that goes from left
to right yeah that was me that was me
that was me anyway you mean i have not
saw that coming
fine let's go
oh no she's going no no no no no no no
no no good no
why you gotta be like that
i feel like we should have put like
something here though because like
everyone climbs and uses this path so
easily true oh
yeah okay i forgot here but what now
there's too much
outside
i think i know what to
[Music]
how
and when did she go there
when last turn last turn no
i wonder
what
hey you put something here put something
like on this side okay okay
i i i i i i i'm gonna see you later
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was waiting for dad
[Music]
oh
unbelievable
i feel pretty funny like well you guys
were jumping i was waiting for someone
to actually die
so that i could get in and i could get
a point big brain ollie
yeah you got through with it once but
you didn't get through with it twice
yeah throw your your tricks and your
little games
party at the mansion once again oh
there's four balloons that's so many how
about we assign each other to like get
each blue yes yes yes
i can get uh which one do you guys wanna
really i swear
wait what did you know okay i'll just
put this okay i'll put this in like
somewhere that's
okay wait guys okay i'll let y'all let
you choose
you're a little [\h__\h]
but i love you little [\h__\h]
yeah what she said
but you know why you don't love
well [\h__\h] that
oh no
go get it get it for me
yeah take in the elevator oh
nice oh no
oh you got a square roll and we got
what's for nice squirrel again and
you'll get the square room
and you get a square nice curl
but the elevator's not coming back down
well then you go
you need to use your skin you can press
the button
oh there we go oh there we go yeah all
right i'm at this lead wait the one on
the right side you don't even have to
take the elevator but
you can just jump on that platform in
between the spikes or you get that one
yeah
oh yeah
nice let's go ollie let's go
i got a squirrel
another
it
and me and dana died for science
for science oh there's tony oh
nice
hmm
here i can help someone get this i can
help somebody get there get this one oh
yeah yeah yeah the stairs would be
wonderful oh
what's what's with the fist though
oh lena wants to
get
somebody want to try
chihuahua you want to try oh i've
already got tons many times by um
oh no
i'm upstairs pick me up
all right we should do something about
this
is not going to win this time no no what
is this what is that thing i don't know
oh
is it gonna close again please nope
oh it is a platform
nice we gotta do something about that uh
elevator
you're right
who took that flower
here here good stun joke yes don't talk
yes
yeah nice
[Music]
how are we going to reach that
wait wait why
oh there's a trap there
there's a trap oh i didn't see okay okay
okay
all right all right
then how am i gonna jump oh i know you
tell me you put that thunder there
nice mama it wasn't me
oh it wasn't you i don't know
down there the tundra on the goal was me
oh
that's a lot of cannons
[Music]
oh my god
that's fine interesting that's fine
interesting um
yeah i don't know how the tone joke
works
it activates probably when you get close
to it or you have to touch it
i think just getting close to it will
work
[Laughter]
elevator oh
no careful the flower slaps
oh
[Music]
i mean i think i'll try something yeah
okay
still manageable just a jump in the
right timing and a big jump
oh no
jump
[Laughter]
wait i'm curious can we go here
oh no no
sadly
you can go up there overall
right
[Music]
all right can we go here oh yeah okay
you know where the traps are going to be
placed
oh nice
[Music]
just put a bunch of them everywhere
oh this is going to trigger some people
i think
get the elevator
oh oh and yo what did you build there
ow
yeah well good luck with that oh nice
yeah
nice
oh my god that was quick
[Applause]
my little pony my little pony
[Music]
amazing wait everybody
i think we reached the time of the end
let me check my schedule
all right
okay yeah we reached it but
um
can someone uh
of you
no no i'll do it i'll take a screenshot
um we'll go to the um intermission and
then i'll be right back guys we'll play
some hollow cure
see you in okay three minutes guys bye
bye
bye bye
[Music]
thank you girls
foreign
[Music]
me
i
[Music]
drinking so much i need to go brb in
minutes
[Music]
is
that's funny
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
do
all right
i'm back
[Music]
how's it going guys
how's it going
[Music]
let me organize everything here there we
go
i'll go here
i am summer travel kiwawa
now
from cat to traveler
you know i was i was doing my idol
meeting you know and then just minding
my own business and suddenly i hear
i hear uh
[Laughter]
from the distance but still in the same
room i'm like
chunky wonky chunky monkey
turns out she was hiding in the laundry
basket in the bathroom
she just made a little purse sound to
let me know that she's here thank you
guys for the super chats thank you thank
you
yeah
she was there
so cute i was just thinking that you
know the bathroom is actually pretty
cool um it's not
it's like one of the coolest rooms in my
apartment so
i thought this would be a nice place for
cats to hang out and surprise she was in
the laundry basket
yeah it's so cute
yeah
both of my cats enjoy being on top of my
laundry
yeah yeah yeah
it's cozy i suppose understandable
so we're gonna play
hollow cure now for
like two hours
so tell me guys after two hours please
tell me to stop so that we can have some
snack and a little break okay
i would appreciate you guys reminding me
okay hold up cure
[Music]
oh no wait that's it wants to update is
that the old launcher maybe that's the
old launcher
[Music]
i'm confused
oh cure
dot accent
oh maybe that's it
perhaps that's the one
oh she sent this
is this it is this that one
i think so
because i i got like a different version
beforehand
is this the one
i hear no sound
sound
press update well for this one i didn't
have to press update because i already
updated before or is there a new update
the launcher is the new one
or is this the old one
i got an error message abort
okay
then the launcher was the actual one
okay okay did you hear that window sound
[Music]
sound
good question
we'll figure it out eventually
let me start the game first
there we go
play
oh
okay
hold up here oh sh
yes yes yes yes next next oh
[Music]
why does it not show i am because it's
window capture
[Music]
oh
we're back and ready to attack
[Music]
it's pretty loud
around here
oh
this should be
uh
wait is that let me okay you're gonna
say play with the controller i will try
[Music]
then i have to disconnect my
switch from the controller
[Music]
because i got it like beforehand i guess
before you guys
yeah this is my my save file
okay
um i need to figure out how to do this
first
and since i never played with moment
before and with fauna i'm gonna try
these two as well
to get used to
the game well what what buttons do i
have to press i have the left controller
but the right controller doesn't work
right now
is there any what's the okay button is
it x okay
yeah i heard my character is super puffy
i want to try it out
okay
ah
oh so slow
oh yeah it aim
is movement really that slow is the game
lagging
oh oh it lagged oh [\h__\h] oh now it's not
lagging anymore
oh
okay oh the aim
so accurate but now it's lagging again
why does it lag
how do i pause
there you go
why
what is this leg
um
i mean
just yeah it can't be because of the
controller
it was controller i'm using a controller
ah strave
lt'd
cancel special
wait what lt was like locking it right
um straight was locking it right
special is a circle
or
ah
no never mind okay
[Music]
oh okay let me see
oh not lagging now then let's see
okay i think it's fine now
[Music]
yeah yeah no i'm using my right
thumbstick to aim and my left thumbstick
to run
uh
so what do we do with mma civilization
attack increases by one percent for
every target currently on the screen up
to 100 percent
whoa
the more the merrier
so oh there's lag again though
it's a problem with the engine
wow
why is it lagging sometimes
it didn't do that last time i played the
game not like
this hmm
i need to update i already updated the
game
restart the game to fix my lag okay i'll
try it
on
[Music]
your things open the background no
actually not
um i don't know
i think you know the reason i think i
know perhaps the reason why it was
lagging with the girls but i don't think
that's the same reason
i already turned off damage numbers i
turned off everything
um
so far so good
[Music]
how is it on your side guys
yeah seems fine so far
is it wait no now it's lagging now it's
lagging
is it because of the controller no way
[Music]
did anybody else experience it like this
never seen this with anyone else try
again without controller
i am not okay i will try
oh
uh forgot how to play with
uh how do you how do you lock it in
again i forgot
what's straight wasn't it like it was
what [\h__\h] what was it
set
oh god i need to change the keyboard
then
i shall
okay
if the lag stops now then
that would be interesting
[Music]
i actually wanted to try it out with the
controller
that's [\h__\h] scary mate
oh no it's lagging again
wait why
that is so that's a jump scare excuse
me
jesus
still lagging none then why the [\h__\h] is
it lagging maybe i shouldn't use the
demo version anymore maybe i need to use
them
will i keep my characters though i don't
know how it works
[Music]
uh how do i launch a game i don't know
just use the launcher
okay how do you actually get the game
under normal circumstances
oh look here
there
uh
okay download
come on okay
sorry guys i don't know today
um
some lag problems
i wonder why
which case i'm gonna reset my pc but oh
uh a version of this product is already
installed installation
cannot be okay
[Music]
i do kind of have two launchers
i think
i don't know which one is which
yeah i hit update already
it didn't lag last time
so i'm like a bit confused
try again
because i guess we didn't um
which button was it
okay
and i want it to be
oh oh that must be the other launcher
because
huh
oh no that's fine that's fine
let me change
[Music]
okay
i want to change this because that's how
i had it last time
yeah
this must this must be the other
launcher because otherwise wouldn't it
still have a space as my strafe button
yeah
friend
ah
sometimes someone is also one of the
characters who have a friend a buddy
try controlling now
and wait
i don't want to [\h__\h] it up again
are you ready
but this one seems fine huh
okay i will try
okay
no no no
i'm controlling again
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] why did this miss what the [\h__\h]
what's missing
[Music]
birds better
birds of a better flock together oh hi
talking about birds
i think it's fine now
right
i have yet to feel some lag i don't want
to jinx it but it seems fine
jinxed it yeah i don't think i can play
with controller
when i when i played without controller
it didn't lag uh just before i
reconnected it
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
is it because ps5 controller
[Music]
do we have to play something else
should we play something else if this
continues
let me restart the game again
because the controller maybe [\h__\h] it
up again
[Music]
come at me
where yes here you go
i have to say though it's been four
hours and those four hours went by so
fast thanks to the collaboration for
example that time
went by so fast
how much was that one and a half hours
perhaps
yeah did you enjoy it
the ending was kind of abrupt i'm sorry
about that i was like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
the time is over i gotta go
sorry
i should have let them say goodbye
properly i said that to them as well
like oh [\h__\h] guys sorry i let you go so
fast oh was that a lag that i just
experienced
let me go
[Music]
what does friends do again
oh
[Music]
it's not too much though it's just every
once in a while
it's so scary
oh [\h__\h]
maybe i need to play a different game
i almost want to restart my pc but um
i wonder i don't remember last time i
tried something like that if
that ended the stream if i could like
reconnect properly i think i did it
before
in the middle of a stream
someone's gonna use one of your weapons
at random everything oh
so like normal feather weapon but also
the extra items
gotta keep the endurance going yeah
[Music]
is
oh my friend collects my
experience
what a good friend
that's a friend you can rely on
oh oh there
hmm
oh my god that's a long leg oh yeah
because that wave is coming
chill
chill the [\h__\h] out
[Music]
are you gonna die all of them yeah
except for the boss whoa
hi nina nina help
my pc is lagging i don't know why
the game is lagging
i do think that the wait
i thought it wasn't hitting them i do
think oh a triple i think the other lag
was in the collab was because of the
application though to be honest
[Music]
yo
i will never be able to play the end
normally then if it already lags now
oh [\h__\h] i wasn't thinking what i was
choosing sorry guys
brain is empty
i wanna see some whole camera please
[Music]
it's like the cursor is still like
normal speed
but the characters are not you see i
mean i mean this aiming cursor
i can change it as fast as i want to
that would be weird
i still um the coins if i quit like this
[Music]
oh pretty
oh no i mean it's not more than usual
what i have open
it's just normal stuff
[Music]
oh i can close that
okay let's see now
oh
why did that show up so fast so lucky
is that random
rng come on hit him hit him
nature shields
protect nature and nature will protect
you what
what what's happening why is it why did
this show up again
sapling defeated targets have a five
percent chance to drop saplings the
sapling heals three percent and
increases fauna's attack by thirty
percent and speed by pretty personal
[Music]
well only if there's no lag
only then this can be an easy run also
first time using fauna but that never
stopped me before
every 10 seconds gain one whisper each
stack heals two percent hp every two
seconds oh she's a healer
hmm
nice
nice no lag
no lag
did that break the [\h__\h] game what
what
that's the third time like we're in the
beginning
when healing a branch will grow under a
random nearby target
wow dealing 200 damage oh lag sorry i i
jinxed it
[Music]
my special is ready what is my special
let's find out audrey
it's um
what's the name again of that tree
the big big fancy train
in like rpg games
oh that heals me
a dress yeah
okay this lag is incredible
maybe we have to play something else
what do you want to play guys
let's see if another game
wants to put me in trouble as well
i can offer
you have to
do something else we can play
age of empires
we can play well a lot of the games i
have
i already deinstalled because um
yeah alien
anyway too
[Music]
trade offer
you receive
right now
are you here do you know if i restart
my
pc while streaming
what happens
[Music]
why lower resolution from the game it's
already tiny as [\h__\h] on my screen
minecraft
what would we do in minecraft
yeah we can play aoe too
i don't
think i don't think ahmed is available
let me let me tag everyone
here we have an sos channel
at everyone
does someone
know what happens when you restart the
pc while streaming
yes rest is on my list anyway
so i'm not going to replace hulk with
rest
yeah
and everyone
it's important i will delete it after i
get my answer
you guys done it and the stream was
still up i feel like i did it too before
yeah
i think
obs
kind of stays connected
somehow
so pings even if you delete that's fine
it's okay so it will it will not make a
difference we get so many at everyone
pins pings all the time
don't worry
okay let me kill the game for now
um
oh wait
unanswered me
as long as you have the option checked
not to end stream automatically all the
stuff should be off on youtube
why is it setting
cheeto stop ah i got it off okay okay
[Music]
okay never mind then i will delete my
everyone
okay i will try to
restart
and then we can try holocure one last
time
um
and then we'll see okay so
i don't know if this
i don't know if this screen will stay i
don't know
you guys will probably be disconnected
from the stream but please just wait a
moment
i'll be back as soon as possible
inside
[Music]
sorry thank you for waiting
thank you thank you
[Music]
let's see if this fixes anything
we will try
again
with the whole cure launcher
and if that doesn't fix it then we'll
change the game
[Music]
here we go
speed run
ah all those anvils little waist
huh
all those animals ever come back to me
oh leg
that was a leg
guys
it's not looking good for whole cure
tonight
it's not looking good
[Music]
yo the rotation is kind of hard to
figure out oh man why
why why why why why why
okay let's try
to play a different game
capturing in windowed mode yeah that
might be an issue too cause like in obs
you can't capture um holocure in the
normal capturing method that you capture
games with
and window mode might i don't know
give it some problems some issues
yeah it's not worth it
uh let's try aoe
i'm i mean we just played it yesterday
so to be honest i'm in the mood i'm in
the mood for some aoe too
let's go
change of plans
it's opening
wow
is it going to show up
wait
i'm going to go here
you guys are going to go up there
[Music]
i just have to wait for obs to capture
it
i believe in you come on
come on obvious
don't be such a little [\h__\h]
[Music]
hello
you hear the music though right
can you please capture this [\h__\h] i'm
going to kill you
what's your problem
i swear to god
[Music]
90 minutes to lunchbreak i want to play
a game i don't want to eat lunch
[Music]
sometimes it does this and then when i
go when i tap into the game it will
eventually
capture it anyway
but it's not doing it even though i'm
tapped into the game
[Music]
restarting game
and
uh
yeah now is a bad time can you please
not
ian law don't don't do this with me it's
gonna show up now it's gonna show up now
i believe in it
yay
finally
talk you long enough oh my god
i've done this before
uh companies are
where should we try a different campaign
what what does america have to offer
what is this
the forgotten campaign countless tribes
for supreme general steep mountain
valleys on the dense jungles of south
america but which will prevail and earn
the favor of the gods
interesting
but that's two that's two uh swords
already we only want one after centuries
of conquest the aztecs now ruled the
mightiest empire in central america
wanted zuma
ooh
so much
ah where is one you guys want me to play
oh these are locked
these are locked too
these are locked too oh
man
europe has the most why not finish john
should we
continue john
barbarossa
okay i wanna check barbarossa up so you
have come to hear the tale of frederick
barbarossa
better order us another round maybe
three
you see
it is a great tale
but then again
everything about the man was great
barbarossa was a man of great appetites
oh great ambitions hungry man a great
red beard oh red beard question
the question you want to know
was that enough of course not the will
of what wait sorry about that watch an
empire
for there was no holy roman empire at
that time oh
only a gaggle of quarreling city-states
this dubiously loyal princetons were
more interested
in a loose confederation
than a unified empire
he believed that he was the emperor by
the will of god
and he intended to bring the delusional
empire back to its former glory but okay
if that meant crushing all of the german
princes
well
so be it okay let's do it
all right all right i don't know
anything about this guy but we might
learn a lot from it
barbarossa
game isn't fully covered it looks like a
little a little itsy bitsy tiny way to
beat
ah
that's too much
oh wow
okay oh wait that's still
[Music]
how about
now
main objectives capturing gary's son in
your monasteries for up to six relics
from the surrounding german
duchies
okay uh
okay okay
captain garrison okay
oh [\h__\h] i should have read that the
other stuff
barbara ross has access to all imperial
age technologies but his population
and purely age
is capped at 10-25
is that after castle age i never went
past castle age
because barbarossa faces so many enemies
it would be a wise it would be wise to
dispose of one or two early before they
become a real friend um
remember only monks can transport in
garrison relax yeah yeah
take care to have a monk nearby
and to support the relics that you look
at
you can tell if an enemy one monastery
has a rally paris on the side of the
monster and the flag fridge on top of it
okay okay
they know that they do not pose a real
threat that's so mean but are in close
proximity to two stronghold dutchies
they will train longsword men and
battering rams
bavarians well my besties are one of the
stronger factions as they control a
walled town
feeling knights and scorpions they are a
formidable opponent
the duchy of saxony saxon
has a fortified town to the north and
are strong enough to oppose barbarossa
head on they use crossbowmen and
teutonic knights
oh man oh there's so many
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] this is the first mission
why are there so many already
should i take down austria first then
oh my god
they don't pose a threat so it should be
easy to take them down
no no no we'll focus on spider-man but
it will also train nights and got
mangled nails
what is that the bohemians
start off rather weak initially oh but
they left but if left alone will grow
into a stronghold maybe bohemians
hmm
let me get practice
okay burgundians and bohemians cyan and
purple
those maybe
also the rain will also conduct early
raids [\h__\h] them
but okay i think
cyan purple orange
something like that
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
teutonic knights
dear what am i dealing with here oh gosh
uh i already forgot how to play this
game
don't do i not use my keyboard
what what's that
what is that ah
hey yeah
what do we build what do we have oh okay
hey also we have we need a wood camp oh
there's fish
[Music]
lumber camp
yeah yeah yeah
first of all we start
building some [\h__\h]
yeah oh you guys can
work on that
nice berries
[Music]
i'll need materials let's go
we're surrounded by some good stuff
do we have a scout yes you
go
uh all the scouts
don't die please
sir
okay
[Music]
wait it says you are being attacked by
one taki-chan
what the [\h__\h] that's my steam name
what why am i attacking myself
makes no sense
that makes absolutely no sense
okay
[Music]
defensive maybe
oh
so many sheep too
i need houses too
and then we need to build some walls
eventually maybe
we're right in the middle i think i saw
some i see some purple over here
so the purple ones are here i suppose
a yellow archer
hey sir
okay we will build
[Music]
we'll build
a house for nowhere
wait that's already a monastery okay i
didn't recognize it
let's build
and
blacksmith
we don't have a blacksmith right
beware of the hungarians yes yes
i need sheep to attack
hey did they take my sheep
where my sheep
stole my [\h__\h] sheep are you for real
my sheep are gone
i claimed them back
i don't see them
you [\h__\h]
move get out of the way
i need um
hey i told you to be defensive okay well
i guess it's stan brown
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't know where
oh
how do you turn them again
what was the turning button
oh wait was there even no
turning button maybe that wasn't
boov good spot
no rotation oh that's sad
that's a bit sad
yeah
i can see deutsche
sheep behind trees oh yes i see some i
see them
[Music]
wait wait
let me send someone to take care of that
oh both of you oh
i guess
and when should we start what kind of
what kind of army do we want a little
bit of everything
archery range
during range
i put it right right here
[Music]
i don't like that there's so many trees
here what the [\h__\h]
too many trees
platonic knights that's what i want okay
i saw them here just need a lot of meat
[Music]
items are good and infantry and they get
more mealy armor
five
where
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
uh
uh for now
and we need more houses holy [\h__\h]
they're so fast
titans
platonic knights
slow and powerful strong versus
millionaires weak versus archers and
scorpions
[Music]
okay then i need some watchtowers
some watchtowers
i guess would be good right
build a watchtower we'll build one
[Music]
right
this area is kind of
restraining me
to stay inside of this relatively small
area
i don't know what's over here
all right um
shall we build a stonewall or palestine
wall
currently we do have a lot of stone and
there's more down here
[Music]
let's try to build a stone wall i guess
um
i'll start
like this
close the bridges should i completely
block them but what what if i want to
pass
well if i want to pass by
gates okay
all right all right
so i'll just put
um
this
this gate
here
like so
[Music]
another one of those
oh [\h__\h] wait i can't rotate
i must be able to rotate this
[Music]
you know rotate this
um do i have to make the wall first
how do i cancel again
and how do i cancel this again
oh thank you thank you
thanks guys for the super chats delete
key
i hear okay you can start building here
[Music]
hey
actually one of
you is gonna build me
let's get
oh
[Music]
this
should uh this edge will protect me
anyway right
so it doesn't have to be all around here
so far this
edge will protect me
okay okay
nice
look at this gorgeous
gorgeous wall
and now
this will fit
here
okay
[Music]
oh hi you built that very nicely thank
you uh
what am i missing
a market
i don't think i've built a market yet we
can build it like here
yeah way better than my previous wild
attempt what the [\h__\h] is that
[\h__\h] is that
he not built because of the stupid bush
really
[Music]
let me get some some water
oh oh that counts as a as a wall
natural wall okay it looks a bit stupid
but okay i'll take it
natural wall is
[Music]
now we need more food
you guys can get rid of that and once
we're done with that we'll get some um
farms and we get a fishing place
gold would be nice too
[Music]
hey yeah yeah
yeah
uh i guess it can be
anybody um i think we go for an archer
wait did i even build an arching archer
archer place thingy
oh yeah this is this thing
skirmisher
and um oh let's make the
meeting place here in the middle
i can see you better
oh
go get him go get him yeah yeah you
can't escape recording him nice oh he's
gonna escape
shoot him
never mind go back here
be um
stand you set your ground
okay be good
i need to finish the wall over here too
though where the hell did that dude come
from
it's still from the bridge
okay
and we'll build
more
more wall the more the merrier
built all the way over
here
that should
protect us
voice is cute thank you welcome
[Music]
land landfords shallow river
uh here
oh where
oh probably
ah here
okay oh wait are these my people
what are you doing
no here and then stand around
hey
[Music]
so there should be like a gate here i
guess
those are the ones i wanna kill
don't don't don't don't
they are leaving me absolutely no time
i'm being attacked by saxony
um
oh here's also a path where you can
cross oh that that's yellow didn't we
say we're gonna attack purple and yellow
very close
oopsie
another wall
uh
now i can't pass i know we'll figure out
a way
we're doing barbossa
wasn't one of them from um
pirates of the pirates pirates pirates
of the pirates of the caribbean what's
what
[Music]
is that
bar bossa
[Music]
okay
i think we didn't build a
um
a stable yet right
i might have scooped the nikes
[Music]
that one
where did that one come from
[Music]
oh
there's one there
what the [\h__\h]
is chilling because they're in
defensive state it is
defensive stance this bag
then
[Music]
hey
oh [\h__\h] i changed the window size to my
hand
oh nice oh they're very strong
we have to do something about this i
thought the
this will protect me
you guys sad natural wall
i don't
trust it anymore
ace it
[Music]
i don't know how to build it
um
let's do this for now
austria advance to castle h
those damn austrians
chop down the tree
[Music]
okay we need more and more more more and
more and more watchtowers as well
[Music]
not going
so well so far
[Music]
um
i want to build
i want to build a uh
a
[Music]
let's see if that worked fine now i
wonder
it's like low-key german
is that hungarian
does it sound so
oh he's gonna come from the side
oh he's just running away okay you guys
go back in here
no oh she died from the
i thought i thought you have to send the
villagers to kill the pigs you get
actual meat from it but you just died on
it
we will just die no
can we have yeah okay we will have to
have some revenge
the titanic night will kill the pig
successfully surely
oh
we could like pre-kill them
like
a few hits
and then
no one ever just kill them just kill
them
no mercy
you are the enemy
[Music]
more
not enough gold oh oh oh you guys gonna
get more
they keep on coming in
but my my wall is not complete yet once
it's completed it should be finished
wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
[Music]
my people
you
[Music]
uh
my what my small army is chilling what
do you mean
i have another army somewhere
hmm
you see how orange walks in
oh [\h__\h] see they lost
they can't get in anymore wait i will
build a gate for you guys just chillax
for a moment
i will build a game yeah i will be bill
gates
after i built the gate ha ha
happy anniversary thank you
i'm so funny well
i'm starting to get hungry so maybe it's
time to start snacking a little bit
not too much
i have a sandwich too proper sandwich
thank you for the super chat elita thank
you
it is incredible indeed
also incredible how i am
unable to um
open this bag of mikado aka pocky
i
can
maybe maybe with this
no that's a spoon
with this pen
oh there we go i opened it with the the
pen tablet pen
okay a little bit of a snap
[Music]
oh
he was already inside
what am i hearing
it was already inside well oh my god oh
purple
i know at all
[Music]
my army so far consists of twenty-one
that's going to take a while though
oh won't take a while yeah
i'll put one more here
[Music]
now i'll send one more to repair it
while they're shooting it
at least we see that the trees are
blocking them from going in i think
it's castles instead of towers
castles you mean like these
but they stopped why did they stop
[Music]
do we um have that upgrade um that the
towers can shoot
uh everything even if it's like super
close right in front of them
so many sneaky invaders yeah castles
these ones some more they can shoot too
these castles can shoot too
yeah murder holes burner holes
oh great
no green i'm green oh yeah we need monks
too
[Music]
no
they they can just walk through there
you can you
do something here
what am i supposed to do
like like this
[Music]
like this
i can't reach this end but i won't have
to i think
dear lord
pull the wall
this will be my oc thank you for ushing
me
happy anniversary thank you
yeah hello kitty was lagging too much
i'm sorry
oh guys
[Music]
get back inside
no no you know what stay here just
everybody stay don't let them in there
[Music]
no no no no no no no no
the horse is bugging you thank god
thank god for that
i need for more more gold oh dear okay
market time
sell some wood
sell some stone
and research
um the relics i wonder do they have
around like two that i need to capture
or
do i not need to worry about that i just
wonder if i could just go now
what's with them
what is this is this normal
yes i will be still streaming when you
wake up
oh yeah i will
[Music]
gonna make
[\h__\h] one of these
healing so nice of you thank you
actually smartphones have to go back
gotta go for now bye-bye thank you
thank you for coming so far
am i halfway through yet i think
my my obs updated it's back to like 43
minutes but i feel like i'm halfway
through already
[Music]
you know
one
one hour more to halfway through okay
cool cool cool
[Music]
you know this kind of
medieval h
reminds me
i actually found another kind of tutor
related show that i started to watch
another one
what was it called
oh [\h__\h] what was it called
ah i think something like becoming
elizabeth i think
the daughter of
ambulance
and
yeah yeah yeah it's pretty cool
it's not
not the best show but yeah
why did you watch it it's on amazon like
on stars play
oh there's even more gold here what the
[\h__\h]
hey yeah
yeah
it's like um
it uh
talks about the history of lisa
the three remaining children of henry
viii after he dies
there's three different children which
they all have a different mother
there's the one from catherine of aragon
there's one from ambulance and then
there's the one from uh
wait was it from catherine park i'm not
sure there was a little boy but he i
don't think he survives long because we
all know that
afterwards
it was not a male who became a king
yeah married tudor and elizabeth yeah
um
he died at 18. oh that's actually later
than i thought it was
great
um
should i build a university as well
[Music]
or mill
there's no mill right
so i'm watching that show and i'm also
watching rings of power obviously and
game not game of thrones house of the
dragon but also i started
another
weird show
this can't be normal
i'm watching another show
um it's a german netflix show actually
but it's also a non-german netflix i
think
i think it's called cleo
actually pretty fun
flickman pikman
ah there's more and more of them coming
[Music]
oof
i i really need to go kill them now huh
am i ready what do you think they're
late i mean the good thing is they're
bugging out so
oh cleo was okay
okay
35 of them
[Music]
need more houses oh
more houses more houses always more
houses
[Music]
thing on this thing
aggressive
kill those funkers
can you reach them
sure if they can reach
oh there we go oh
come on one more
hit him hit him
oh
it's trying its best
and they're also trying hard
yeah
nice hit oh no no chill chill don't
don't even think about it don't even
think about it
it's just having fun should i get more
of those
i get more of the mango nails where
where did they come from
it's from here
uh conscription tree
oh
oh there's friendly fire because of them
but we will need ramps probably right
i hope i'm not too slow i feel like i'm
so slow also they're getting rid of the
forest more and more
and can they not work on like other
trees
actually
built
now whatever just continue
siege workshop build
[Music]
okay
a few rams
the bush is so strong here on
oh oh nice
my
whatever mangonel is very aggressive and
killing those scorpions beautiful but
i'm i'm i'm feeling stressed out i feel
like it's time it's
it does seem to be time to go
oh oh oh oh
he's gonna die where's he
so oh
incredible
what else do i need
everybody's knocking on my wall
hey yeah hey
clickman repair that [\h__\h] he's never
gonna stop unless i kill him
well eventually the watch star was gonna
kill him hopefully
yeah slowly
very slowly
cases you want
one more watchtower here
okay
[Music]
there's some some units in it to have it
fire more into
the rams or no you mean this thing
okay what a big thing a pikeman
oh no you mean the watch talent yeah
never mind
what was the red button here
does it also count for
the mango now though
systema
[Music]
let's put you in here
what shows are you guys watching
currently
anything interesting anything
interesting that's maybe even new
why do i always go back here
hulsa hulsa
no time for shows
hulsa
liquor is recoil i saw like the
characters look really cute
lorraine advanced consulate ah
hey sir brings your power in your
streams thank you
cuphead oh there's a show
do i do guys can i go am i ready
anyone who played this
um this campaign before
the office the office is always good
classroom of daily dragon blood
how to get that membership
congratulations
treat it well
hey okay you guys are going too far with
this wood
look at him camping
there we go that's what we're building
okay i want to go now
yeah everyone
get together
oh [\h__\h] no yeah
i guess
we'll just take everyone and go this way
i guess and yeah we should save
[Music]
it's a german very common german name
you guys use that in english too barbara
i guess so
i've heard it being used before
um
[Music]
i should leave some people but never
mind i'll just i'll just go and then
this one i'm gonna go this way
and then i'll create some more
[Music]
to protect while i'm gone
yeah yeah yeah
oh i got like barely any cavalry archers
huh
oh i made scout cavalry oh well
all right we're on our way
we are on our way eat the kuluja
[Music]
oh
don't leave anyone behind except for the
rams i guess it looks like we don't need
them
they're later
what are we gonna attack uh
yeah
streeted oh i mean the rams would be
nice um killing the buildings yeah
oh [\h__\h] maybe not fun
all right go back first
if you can
yeah
oh
[Music]
my mom's even healing don't even have
any monks left i feel like i don't
wait
oh boy
uh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay oh there we go
shall focus on the castle i'm gonna take
down the castle right
now the question is
where is my monk do i have a monk
seems like they died because i also
don't hear any healing noises
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what's it they said if there's a flag on
the castle
or on the monastery
which one was it and they have a a
cleric inside there are flags but oh
yeah okay mine doesn't have a flag
okay then uh
yeah
later
everything okay here yeah yeah yeah
monk
monk okay okay you
join us join forces
[Music]
oh you were shooting
ah
[Music]
oh
bye
[Music]
everybody everybody just everybody
everybody who can fight
[Music]
no
ah
[Music]
oh my god wait maybe maybe wait for a
second
maybe wait maybe wait for a second i
don't know
[Music]
ah
uh
yeah barbara please
um
so
i guess focus first on the enemies
um not on the buildings
the actually living people
oh man i'm gonna bring some extra people
though
this is not enough
[Music]
buy a trebuchet
where do i see that
what build trebuchet some gold i need
for that okay
what's the trebuchet what is that
what's up
all this i also need to upgrade all of
that
[\h__\h]
so much to do
very long range catapult
but does that also do friendly damage
friendly fire
oil
um
[Music]
great
shoot more
so
why can't i not buy it now
why can't i not buy it now real
more houses
yeah we are winning here
um
[Music]
level armor
even more houses
[Music]
these weapons have extra melee armor
sure anything that helps
yeah the blacksmith upgrades i'm working
on them there's upgrading currently
i need a few more
blast furnace
needs a lot of gold
resources dough
resources
help with the wood
[Music]
it was also hard kept on yourself you
couldn't bypass with even more horses
yeah yeah yeah
wasn't it like 125 but that's just a
general villager amount i can have
[Music]
and i missed my arena keyboards
i was lighting the keyboard back
i wonder why it wasn't working
everything was
kind of weird today
isn't there like
hmm
i didn't ask yet i'll ask like later
but maybe after i restarted pc the pc or
i mean i did it several times but
maybe suddenly miraculously would work
now who knows
it might
hey yeah
it might suddenly work it's often like
that isn't it
but
the other day i had a friend over rbf
helping again with um
some stuff
putting up a lamp
and
uh
he checked out the keyboard
he got really jealous he really wanted
to find out like
like what what is it
how to buy this
what's it called what are these switches
called i need to get those switches he
was really into it
everybody loves my keyboard
what's rvf um
the boyfriend of my best friend
um rbf stands for rental boyfriend
because he helps me often with like
putting up some furniture and [\h__\h]
because i can't do it alone
i always have to rent my best friend's
boyfriend
yeah to be like that
where's that sound
excuse me with what what what what
where's my where's my thingy
mango no
help they didn't come while i was
fighting the
the purple ones
what the hell what's up with that
oh no
oh my god
you know what this means we're not going
for purple we're going for the yellow
ones faster you little [\h__\h]
wait where do i make uh
oh my god
siege tower
scorpion scorp is scorpion good too
santa cavalry cavalry calorie coloring
belated which one's calorie archer
[Music]
oh no you're gonna die dude oh oh yes
yes
a friendly fireman oh my god
wow
i am terrified
climb onto them
[Music]
uh
it's easy it's not
[Music]
okay question do we go for purple for
yellow yellow is so far away
hill is so far if we have to go up here
should we go for purple first
purple okay
they're later i mean this better this
better be enough
[Music]
uh houses okay yeah
oh wait i can't turn
what's that who's that i can't turn i
can turn
wait oh is it just variations
never mind i think it's just variations
or is it
maybe it's just variations
okay yeah or is it uh only houses you
can turn i'm not sure how i did that
just now
[Music]
burgundy seven
of these
i'm gonna go
i'm going to go again
um
[Music]
this [\h__\h] is destroying my natural wall
i can't believe it
[Music]
[\h__\h] repair this thing immediately
okay
um do we send in the people no maybe ram
for the tower
and
yeah the the ramps
ramps go in for
these
and they can't pass pesa everybody's
just
their later pacer
system can you guys move
yeah
oh no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
hey
flickman
hey sir
[Music]
they're later
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
what did you guys say um
which ones which ones were hey
i
[Music]
they stopped though oh god oh god i
can't do this both at once
[Music]
ah
i'll get used to it
[Music]
he's not even doing it he has to go
outside but then he's gonna get shot now
at least they stopped attacking for now
okay
give me some breathing room
oh my rams no
um
i want to attack the castle
faster
uh oh
[Music]
uh go in for the attack street
not you you're right you're not you're
not you're not you
[Music]
come on
i'm losing again
oh the tower's not even down yet
[Music]
oh
i think we lost our monk again
[Music]
i'm losing
i'm again a gun
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't think this is worth it but we're
gonna
you know
create a couple of those again
[Music]
i don't know whatever
okay
[Music]
i thought they were already dead all of
them i didn't see
not enough
follow closer behind rams of your army
um
mamma mia
um did i spend
after creating a couple more
55 yeah i think i did
try again we brute force this [\h__\h]
salsa
[Music]
it's doing it again
it's triggering me this is [\h__\h]
triggering me
hey ya clickman
okay lady please repair this thank you
soldiers
aggressive well before they there's so
many chances that sent them to defensive
so now i'm just sending them to the
defense because before they were
aggressive it wasn't particularly
helpful
um
build a castle across the bridge
why
how
do you want me to
make use of that
how close
[Music]
foreign
bro that's not gonna work you will have
to walk over the [\h__\h] bridge
no
why is the ai so ridiculously stupid i
say sorry
hey yeah
yeah yeah
that's why open here
nine don't go back
the other one made it across
system
[Music]
okay
hey
no no don't don't don't be so aggressive
[Music]
no no no no no no no no
no later
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna kill all my people
peace
[Music]
well at least i can quickly spawn more
nights
[Music]
stated
quite working
[Music]
reinforcements
uh it's somewhat working
[Music]
okay
what is it even worth it
[Music]
they always change their [\h__\h]
[Applause]
we're so close to winning
[Music]
computers
uh
[Music]
oh they decided we finally decided
i'm losing so much
i don't even know what's happening here
are we good here
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah
we're fine
[Music]
all right now now now you just go back
um bring into the castle now bring it to
the yeah
greater
drop relic drop the relic
[Music]
oh my god what an expensive war and so
many casualties
i think we're pretty much eliminate
madison
[Music]
and [\h__\h] girl
oh wait i guess you dropped it there oh
that's the sun
sorry that was my mistake
the latest
um
okay we don't have much left here
[Music]
yeah
yeah you know what go back retreat i
think do we oh is it okay to retreat
they fix the [\h__\h] castle
i mean we got the relic
they're gonna keep
that's a on
i never completely got them i got what i
came for is that good enough
[Music]
is that good enough hey sir can you like
chill in the castle
[Music]
wait okay here he is
drop it off oh god
at least we did some big ass damage
[Music]
all right
um
holy [\h__\h]
i now have to rebuild everything
oh my whole army
is it time for us well thank [\h__\h] god
no it's time for a break right
break and then rest
oh my god i'm i'm glad i'm glad i don't
think i
i don't think i can do this
anymore
yeah i keep on chopping that wood
unbelievable
well
that says
six hours it's been six hours we're
halfway through
it broke me
i don't know john the arc was a better
oh experience dropped it okay we dropped
it
[Music]
oh wait something was there before
wasn't there yeah is it i don't want it
anymore
[Music]
no
that was that was tough
that was tough
that was very tough that was quite a
challenge at least we got one relic yeah
with um three tries and
that's a big difference to john dark
put up a good fight despite the stress
and frustration really you think so
oh my god
okay guys next will be rest um but
uh i will be on screen but i need to eat
a little bit so that i can survive
uh 12 full hours
yeah
so we'll go to my office
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna go grab like my sandwich
i've got like a mozzarella tomato
sandwich
the salad if i need but i think the
sandwich for now will fill
my tummy
quite well
okay
i am here i am here
sorry that not everything
went according to plan so far
i'm a bit unlucky today but i'm still
having fun i hope you guys have fun too
whoosh
mozzarella
tomato sandwich yummy where are we in
the schedule we're now between holocure
and rust
that's a oh i didn't write the breaks on
the schedule but right now is break time
oh
[Music]
um
oh
yummy mozzarella
[Music]
wait i mean
right
um
break oops
break
time
okay that's really hard to see
you just stay strong
yeah
[Music]
no way that works right
oh yummy oh wait is that olives
i don't really like olives hmm
no
no why don't you put olives into the
sandwich
one
now you guys should get some food too
olives
are so hated
all over the world home
i'll all live the world
thank you
for the memberships
thank you thank you
oh no i never olive
i'm coming to get me they're out for me
no
um
besides the olives
it's a really good sandwich
[Music]
1am in korea so i'm not eating anything
because i'll gain weight
i've never
ever followed that rule before
well i eat
whenever i feel like it
when i need to eat and i need to eat
like i
i can't i can't sleep with an empty
stomach so before i sleep with an empty
stomach i'm gonna eat even if it's like
2 am
uh
yeah
is it really my body does it does it
make such a big difference really
[Music]
i don't know if there's spanish
i'm not an olive racist
no
i don't like any of them
oh yes it will have a ball that's why
i'm stopping at 12 hours
we will probably stop like
i know five minutes before just to be
safe
[Music]
is it me or the stream lags quite hard
if it's not just you then i would like
to know that indeed
what are we at where we're at break time
here marine time
not laggy okay
exact starting time was like one minute
before
um
yeah one minute after 12 i think
but now i don't know
if youtube
calculates
the
the time i had in between where i was
restarting my pc beforehand like now
or afterwards and it's gonna [\h__\h] it up
and bleep blue
but we're just gonna five minutes before
midnight i'm gonna end my stream
hmm
oh yummy
[Music]
thank you
i should have prepared like
a clip to watch together while i'm
eating
[Music]
i did watch a funny clip yesterday
though
cow carrot uploaded a clip of my jump
scares in aoe too
that was funny
i laughed so much at myself
from being so stupid
yeah i did watch to episode 3 um
of rings of power
i think i was alright um although like
you know when the elves were fighting
the orcs spoiler alert but i mean that's
a pretty i think that happens quite
often
in that world
but if you watch the episode you
probably know what i mean
around the end where
those elves were fighting the orcs
um
it was kind of questionable for me a lot
of questionable things happened like for
example
that one main elf dude that they have
there
was it some kind of [\h__\h] magical
stick or how was he able to kill an orc
with a [\h__\h] twig
huh
explain that to me
he just pulled out a twig out of the
tree literally a twig
a twig
and stabbed an orc with it and suddenly
the orc is dead
are you kidding me
i mean
at least like it didn't have to be a
twig he could have like picked up
a big
a big log and then
smash his brains out of that
i felt that would have made more sense
[Music]
maybe
maybe that tree was magical but we were
not told during the episode that that
the tree was magical so i'm like really
confused
really confused
whatever the hell was going on there i
will
not understand eva probably
oh why isn't this piece of mozzarella so
humongous
very oaky
and then the ending
was so lame of that fight the ending of
that fight was troubling because
i don't know who watched it but when the
l was looking at the other elf
but first of all who shocked the elf
once he reached the top
but i was thinking
during that time when the other apples
was watching he should have
climbed up
just climb up
an orc in a distance
when i didn't know
that they apparently are sensitive to
light i didn't even know that
have they involved in lord of the rings
because
i feel like they were walking around
outside just fine
sometimes
but maybe it's because they were covered
in armor
as long as they're covered somehow
they're fine maybe
[Music]
ah
those are the oobleck ah they're fine oh
oh
okay okay okay i was like oh this is
news to me
um
oh
that reminds me of something
someone in the chat
someone just mentioned sour on way to
chicken and starving
[Music]
um
wait did i write that correctly
i feel like you know today i was looking
at smoothie
i was looking at this movie and
i noticed a pattern on her forehead
that reminded me
it looked like to me
the eye of sauron
on on the tower like um
between those two
i don't know how to describe it it was
basically sovereign's eye
on on the tower
i noticed like a
like a pattern on my on smoothie's
forehead
that looked like that
uh
like if you look up sauron tower that's
what i mean that's what i saw on her
forehead
there i even saw like the pupil
in the eye
like also clearly in the pattern
is she sour and reincarnated
[Music]
i'm terrified
help me
save me
no i didn't get the bundle i had the
window open open and i was looking at it
before the time ran out
i was like should i really buy this but
i wasn't that interested into the games
um that they were offering
i didn't miss it i just purposefully did
not buy it sorry
um
[Music]
yeah 90 of the games were lego
lego
didn't feel so
interesting to me
[Music]
hmm
laughs
[Music]
i did play
some lego games when i was younger
in theory they're fine but no
[Music]
of course i played with actual legos who
didn't
upcoming golf game what
what
what no what i didn't see what what what
golem game is he like the main character
no way
[Music]
a lego game or a normal one
i need to wash my hands on you
i did see it before really
i don't wanna play gollum as the main
character
no
give me frodo what the [\h__\h] a brb brb
[Music]
anna i'm gonna restock my water
orange juice who wants orange juice
[Music]
orange juice okay
some sweet
some sweetness i even got coca-cola in
case i get really tired
even though coca-cola won't even help
that much
[Music]
okay
well we'll take like 10 more minutes to
reevaluate the situation
we only have
two more games coming up
and then cut okay
well maybe we can read a
marshmallow but give me a moment to
breathe can i just have one one minute
of silence like trying to talk a little
bit while eating
really like cuts off your breath
hmm
[Music]
done eating
hmm
[Music]
um
someone asked in japanese don't expect
me to announce any merchandise at the
end of the stream
no solo
um
merchandise
for anniversary this year either
who knows maybe next year
who
knows i i feel like i i i said suggested
last year
that we also get like solo merchandise
for anniversaries like um other
uh
like other
whole life members
usually do
but oh well
group birch is nice too
okay so tight indeed
you know what because i i googled
sauron's tower
um and it comes up with
like a lot of pictures but there's like
there's also
some pictures of people trying to
recreate
the tower
in terraria
and a game called valheim
honestly
i could recreate that in minecraft
you don't notice valheim game but they
also seem to have square blocks
idea
a watchtower
scary eye
wow that's so scary
eh no i don't know i've probably heard
of wildham before but i don't really
know it
like rust but even more primitive
can i even get more primitive than that
okay i'm gonna try opening rust now and
see
if i can enter
the game
even
begin with
[Music]
is definitely the most primitive
definitely
i hope this game doesn't lag i hope that
it was just like a holocure thing
look your problem
hey what the [\h__\h]
oh the size of the screen is so [\h__\h]
up
what the hell
this game loads like a million [\h__\h]
years
oh why is it here now
oh okay
um playing
game ah
huh
if a server gets reset
you guys know in russ do you change the
ip
can i join this one join
there's two people online apparently
[Music]
yeah new season
shouldn't change
okay okay okay okay
so far so good
i want to build a base
in k20
that's um the square where i want to go
68 rust
could it possibly be
[Music]
oh my god
i'm so excited for the end
i feel like you know the holocaust
didn't go so well i'm sorry about that
and then aoe 2 i kind of sucked today
and there were some legs and ultimate
chicken horse so yeah and the last two
slots were not going so well i'm a bit a
bit sad but
i hope the rest is gonna be fine and you
guys are hopefully still enjoying it
i want us to go through this together be
strong together and at the end i'm gonna
reward everyone
all of us also rewarding myself by
finally announcing the things i want to
announce
i've been waiting so patiently
it was still fun thank you
thank you
i hope so
[Music]
yeah what's fun with the id girls ah
i think both the game and the choice of
members was really good
i wanna play more of them if we didn't
have time restriction i think we would
have played longer
i've been having a blast thank you
i'm late so i missed the scuff parts
nice
but
the ultimate chicken horse is definitely
worth a re-watch even though there's a
bit of lag in the beginning
it kind of gets fixed later on
uh all right i have to change
clothes
we want to see
all shades of guava
all shades
what comes after casual farmer girl
kiwawa
[Music]
you know it
oh wait oh that's kimono wait a second
that's wrong
ah this one
okay
oopsie
oh so i'm in the game
i'm in the game
from here or not we'll be playing rest
how do you like my my outfit
looking cute huh
thank you for capturing that immediately
after i chose
this game
i am
impressed
[Music]
although
the window size is not quite accurate
a second
i wonder if my character will be male or
female this time last time i was a
female i guess that's random right
oh never mind it's not here
oh wait
oh wait no size oh god
wow wow what
what is this place
[Music]
oh yeah
i'm making my own window size
[Music]
oh
does this cover the no a bit more
this should be fine that's that's about
right yeah that works
here i am where are we
age 19 and i want to go to k20
happy city up
oh it's super close is this the spawning
point for everybody
oh
we are starting out in a desert but i
think one isn't isn't the whole map kind
of a desert like this
oh no there's some snow there's some
snow
lack of water ooh
spawns are usually by the beach usually
nice palm trees we don't get any of
those in austria
like i really
enjoy seeing very different fauna
from what i'm used to
when i was in
uh
where was i
los angeles
in summer
i saw these nice trees and i was like
whoa whoa whoa it's a different world
flora oopsie farmer is animals right
flora is the plants even the fauna kind
of also sounds like it could be that
oh that's someone's house
you guys know who
there seems to be water
don't need a dad originally but might as
well oh
that looks like polka senpai
oh they're living together
peace is number one let's get along cute
so if you guys like peace so much you
surely will let me drink from your water
catcher right how do you do this again
like this
oh yummy
[Music]
thank you
i kind of need some food but
no food here
we'll have to go to the convenience
store
how do i look at my character again
i'm a girl
i'm a girl again
yay
i'm not surprised i knew i always knew i
was a girl
there's food in the horse ah no i won't
steal it no no
oh the character stays the same
oh
yeah
oh scraps let's go scraps
starting again with the scraps but um
i've noticed that you know i got really
unusually far with my tech tree because
like ahmed was asking
the other day
just like two three days ago does anyone
have this uh can anyone anyone build me
this
explosives and i'm like yo girl i
actually know how to build that
surprisingly
thank you for the rest of it
i don't know if she still wants it
though because i i couldn't build yet
because i i didn't ever log in
wait uh yeah i've arrived
oh oh oh
no um
[Music]
i think
yeah wasn't there like a convenience
store or something here and also a pond
because like i'm a oh wait that's it
is it
oh no that's not a convenience store
i think that's what i'mma meant maybe oh
there's a recycling
it thingy close enough
was that
black raspberries those are not
raspberries
that's
is that just blackberries or blueberries
and this is i guess the equivalent
of the convenience store at least in
this area
okay cool
[Music]
and that was that is that a thing
is that just decoration
i feel like if i jump on that it will
hurt me
is there an opening
yeah raspberries are like red pink
i know i need to eat
i need more than that
but
i can get some scraps too
so i guess we're gonna build our base
around here
and mummy is gonna be my roommate in
this season
key card on the table oh what a key card
for that what that fence
yeah
are you holding up so far
totally daijoubu zen zendaya
oh [\h__\h] i hear a helicopter
but it's really far really faint
let me look at the map a little bit
oh
is there any abandoned convenience
stores at all
no i don't see any say junkyard
oh [\h__\h]
ah
green key card
what does that do
well now it's coming
what do i do with that
and i just live in here
open screen doors
let's go exploring more yeah i wouldn't
mind
open screen door in certain locations
the thing is like uh i've heard some
things about this server already like
things that are missing
for some reason oh wait there's a
there's a supermarket that's it
instead of missing
and that also like made me think like
what
what what what
what am i supposed to do
but oh well is that card gonna respawn
if i lose it
repair bench just chilling here
car parts oh wait scraps let's take the
scrubs
okay
well then uh i need wood and i need more
food
shall we go to the abandoned supermarket
fix your neck what do you mean fix my
neck
oh
yes yes yes
a lake
emma really wants to build more cars
here i heard you open up a shop
but i wouldn't even need to buy one i
would be capable of building my own car
because now i have all the car parts
recipes
my shoulder well it's as bad as always
it's at least not as bad as
like two days ago that was like i don't
know
weirdly painful
wow there's so many
should i i guess i should maybe bring
them along anyway
oh
a weapon nice that's gonna cover us for
now if something attacks us
[Music]
nice i never used a bow before in the
previous season
the stone should be like the mascot of
rust
they should make like flashes out of the
stone
the stone and the torch but more more so
the stone
i feel like it has this personality in
this potential this is really important
character in the game you always have
this rock
and it's the only thing
you work with in the beginning
unless someone gives you all kinds of
free items
yes sell actual rooks not a [\h__\h]
but that that will be heavy
i wonder who's online i wish there was a
list that would tell you
who exactly is online
[Music]
and data
who's playing
is anyone streaming rust
right now because that's me
last time i did that when i was playing
off stream i asked and nobody answered
i don't know if they have if kate or
they wanted to stay like
um
if they wanted to stay on the cover
for some reason
emma's here
that makes me happy that makes me so
happy i got a guitar when the [\h__\h] did i
get a guitar
wow
how do i eat this again ah here
mommy
all right i still want to go to the
convenience store
do you have to swim
the map is kind of blurry
i didn't steal it
i didn't steal it no
i only took random
random things
yeah
what do you mean i stole it
let's pick one oh wait [\h__\h] i didn't
mean that one i guess
lives there
[\h__\h] i wanted to go here i made a
mistake
that's that fits her that spot fits her
in the water kind of again surrounded by
water god damn it
god damn it but that's good
we have peculiar close by
um if i live around here
or someone living here as well who is
that
alcatraz island
[Music]
i know that from that um skateboarding
game who is this study
no no signs really small house maybe
it's just like a storage for pickle dog
no no
let me see
oh i've never like fought with npcs
before
[Music]
in any case we should at least be ready
to attack if necessary
how do you reload
oh god ah quiet
scary
and then i can't reload with the arrows
i got
avoid avoid avoid
pumpkin
yummy
and a seed we can use it for
our
little farmland
okay
that is
nicely positioned
i see not not the only reason why
piccolo got that island because just
because it's an island but also because
she got these nice places right here
is that like a like a dungeon if you go
inside
over there
this part is just a typical convenience
store
no
front okay yeah yeah
it's pretty
fine
i will i need to start building but i
need wood
okay
maybe we should focus on that
you guys see any trees though
i feel like i passed
all the trees
okay wait let me let me focus on
focus on
[Music]
oh wow the pumpkin gives you a lot
although it's gonna get dark soon trees
this is a tree is that a tree
no not really
trees
is this a tree is this considered a tree
yes okay
oh
getting wood a small baby palm tree
and drink
is it smart to build literally like five
meters next to the convenience store
where would i make myself a target
although i i think like people wouldn't
even attack me
what do you think i missed a crate yeah
on purpose no space
there's my woods there okay
target i would make myself a target
is this the place well it was roughly
the area
she recommended k20 for some reason i
think
yeah
i guess she said she wished she built it
there
uh but in theory she just
showed the pond and she was like the
pond would be good space to build a base
saturday built didn't build mine here
whoopsie oh god
if you're participating in pfp at the
end
well
[Music]
okay we can just
maybe not five meters but like
10 meters
10 meters away
who is this house
[Music]
become piccolo's minion
yeah i wouldn't mind you know i feel
like that's a good sign to be on
although now that we've all already
faced peculiar once
i feel like some people
may have
you know
like a better idea of what they need in
order to defeat ecuador
whoa
is this is this also her
is this also her is that fabuki sample
again because it has that shiny tower
again
[Music]
oh horsey
hi
oh
it's getting dark i don't like that
let's build something but where
where
[Music]
i'll go i'll go here then because it's
still close to the water but not the
supermarket is like
[Music]
maybe
although i mean that that area also had
some scraps
it's fine we don't need to be back
supermarket
like the torch here
wait
uh how
oh nice guy's nice
ah yeah it has a recycler yeah yeah yeah
yeah
so that's good enough right
and then i'll get a car and i'll be
zooming for the map hopefully
candy junior
[Music]
has been preparing so much for the
anniversary again
big respect
and yet i don't know how she manages to
play
uh rust
and there's so much to do like she'll
she'll figure it out she knows
if she has a plan
what is this funny stone
yeah she doesn't sleep much
i guess
i hope she's
not doing anything stupid
and don't ignore your body what your
body wants what your body needs what
your body tells you
that it needs
always listen to your body
she said she worked 14 hours straight
i hope she slept after that
yeah she's super super hard working
i'm gonna change to bgm now because i'm
i think i'm going crazy
all right let me just go
over there okay
oh it's so peaceful
all right
let's build here maybe on the street
hmm
i see something there who is that
did i ask you guys already is that's not
something that lumay started hopefully
even if she didn't get really
far
what is this
hello
am i here oh did you used to have a
horse
leave you
oh is that water it looks disgusting
[Music]
maybe that's me
by anya's place really
i don't know if i actually built
anything like like
uh
i told her if she plays before me that
she could
just start
build something ahead of time
[Music]
pumpkins free pumpkins
yeah
all the seeds on your
[Music]
oh that was a worm
corn seed corn seed shouldn't it be
pumpkin seeds
horse
could that be my horse because that
looks like it's nobody's horse oh you're
my horse
you don't belong to anyone right
gonna be my horse yeah
circles show me your name
how about that
okay
i will
let's see what's over here
oh
nice view
[Music]
oh the cove
i'll check that out
eventually another horse
yo
i rarely bumped into horses on the old
server
how about no that's right next doors
and i want to build too close to that
house
don't know if that's smart
[Music]
i can't decide can't make up my mind
i'll build it
[Music]
yeah
maybe here
maybe here maybe here
kind of protected by the stone a little
bit
maybe could even like build some stairs
is that possible
to get up on the rock is that is that a
thing you can do
[Music]
you can build on top of the rock well
that will be a pain in the ass to get up
onto
[Music]
it would be cool but also hmm
how high
how high can i get
without um
interesting
without using any tools
this high
render error
all right going down
oh what is this
this little
flower spot
no no flowers
this looks so suspicious
it's nothing special okay
[Music]
build platforms
like hmm
i might want to try it out but first
let's just build on the side to it
[Music]
ah
okay
wood oh wait don't i need a hammer
and the blueprint
uh
hammer
[Music]
oh i got corn where did i get the corn
from
and the blueprint yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
building plan
and i can put down this thing already
a large plant of books
um
[Music]
i'll put you here
and then we'll build the house
here
[Music]
all right
let's get building
ah
i don't know what i want it to look like
now but maybe just for now we can just
build a temporary house
right
[Music]
and then if i have an actual idea of
what i want
it
then i can still
change it up
[Music]
okay
i need some
[Music]
some steps
uh
maybe from here
oh yeah that wasn't something like these
only work if you have like
a i am foundation
oh
[Music]
like
look here
and then stairs there you go
okay and then we need some walls
[Music]
it shark gremlins
under the floorboards underneath
oh
i guess they could crawl underneath and
try to destroy it from underneath oh
terrifying
eh i'm out one already
[\h__\h] kidding me
mo kiga not
[Music]
oh no it does not matter here that's my
rock
um trees
there's not many trees here do i get
wood from cacti for some reason
or do i get water because they save
water right today
oh pretty
oh you get a cloth from it but it also
[\h__\h] hurts not worth it zero out of
ten on yelp
yeah
there's no [\h__\h] trees here oh no some
of the damage so far
it's gonna decay until i'm back now
[Music]
a [\h__\h] desert
who thought of this whose idea was this
i'm it
terrible idea
there's nothing here right on bright
knees
yeah stones yeah
and relatively easy to find like i had
some troubles
um later in the game of season two
to find
oh this place is cool
[Music]
to find uh stones because like it was
just hard to see them to begin with
i guess and here they stand out maybe
[Music]
oh a hatchet
what do i need for that
wait i don't even have to rest before no
i do
i do but i don't have metal fragments
yeah
for now it's gotta be the stone look at
the xo
you know what i need to make
my
come on
my chainsaw
yeah
good for the beginning if you can't
actually make it
i can't get that [\h__\h] axe
[Music]
who's it
oh it's gone
oh no
that is reachable thank you
my stone can break
i still never broke before
are there not like any random wood other
than that that should that i should be
able to pick that up
am i no
no
pieces of wood there's a boat
these plants are interesting too
[Music]
you guys think my my building has
decayed already
and axe i'll go back and i'll try to
recycle some stuff into metal fragments
i want this boat
[Music]
it doesn't not yet okay
okay good
let's go
back we go you don't need my tone
is there a hatchet where i don't need
metal
[Music]
what does i need metal maybe is there
like us like a
[Music]
stones
and that's a pickaxe though
[Music]
stone stone stone
i've got stones
but i can't make it because i don't have
enough
i've got 50 only
the struggle
[Music]
what
that thing
it's only 50 more where there any stones
ah
[Music]
last time the beginning was actually a
bit easier even though i was very
confused but at least oh there's some
tree stamps um alma gave me
some stuff in the beginning
she gave me an axe i never had to build
an axe myself
hallelujah
would
oh stone
[Music]
sulfur or no
nice but
i need stone
oh that was theresa
i guess someone's teresa
i'ma help me too a little bit to explain
me some basics now i know the basics i
don't need anyone to help me yeah
[Music]
by the way guys i will have to
order some food before i end the stream
can you guys try
to remind me of that because
i end my stream at like midnight so
afterwards it's gonna be difficult for
me to get food
and the thing is i yesterday
i
in order to prepare properly for the
stream i bought some frozen food
um hi horsey
i should use you i bought some frozen
food like a macaroni alforno
um to eat afterwards you know but then
apparently yesterday i forgot to put it
into the freezer after i put it
down
um
so
it started like it was still kind of
low-key frozen and cold and all that
when i noticed like six hours later but
then i was like oh man i'll just eat it
now then i guess i don't want to put it
back into the freezer after it already
low-key
start it
um
melting
[Music]
so i ate it and now i don't have
food prepared
[Music]
i already ran out of wood again
unbelievable
[Music]
how
oh wait oh
the floors don't take that much
ah never mind no now it's over
it's over
it's over fam
oh [\h__\h] with windows
oh
maybe it's good to not have windows on
the first floor
you know for safety
for safety
all right
um
i need metal fragments
[Music]
we're in the game
when do you want a reminder
maybe in two hours from now or one
yeah
two two two hours
but no wood yeah
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it do be like that is there is that a
tree over there what i saw
that's decoration huh
i will take the horse
and go
look for the trees
[Music]
when there's there's a tree there
all right i'll take this one
but wait i have no axe oh
what am i gonna hit it with
[Music]
can i craft a stone oh
that's ridiculous
oh wait i can't craft the stone
unless it's not cold stone maybe it's
called rock how about that
it's called rock guys
ah
it's a [\h__\h] rock
yo kobo mimicking my words again today i
was so cute
[Music]
she learns from the greatest
her english skills
getting better and better
so proud super proud mommy
[Music]
like mother like daughter
yeah also like me and my mom
because she has um
quite the hairy party mouth as well
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's so cute just maybe is this the way
you feel about me guys
because when i hear kobo swearing
since since english is not her first
language
when i hear her swear in english i feel
like it's so [\h__\h] cute
is that what you guys think when i swear
or are you too used to it already
whenever you say booking yes yes
sometimes i forget english is in your
native language
that's my problem i'm like too good
my english isn't perfect but this is
just like with japanese
both my japanese and my english
are
not so bad that would that people would
think
that it's cute
anymore
[Music]
oh wait
what about second floor
oh [\h__\h] this is just temporary whatever
it's just temporary
[Music]
door
a door you have to craft right i feel
good
no no now now we have a stone
uh
yeah stone hatchet
[Music]
i don't have enough stones what about
i can make this one
yeah yeah let's see see
tool
ooh what is that nail gun
wire tool
noise
[Music]
i'm on the iris level of building what
do you mean what does that mean
what does that mean
[Music]
oh workbench
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
workbench
yeah okay
oof that they had scraps thank god i had
some
you
yo
[Music]
okay
temporary housing
what else am i waiting for
did i make a hatchet or did that not
work with
without a workbench
i guess not
eh that's not true i upgraded my house
last time for the war and before that it
was just not necessary to waste all my
materials too much it's not that i love
wood that much it's just you know oh oh
people decaying yes yes i'm gonna get
more don't worry
[Music]
now i can't make it
after all
[Music]
hmm
i can demolish it with the hammer
all right all right if i really still
can do it then i will
make um
i'll make a some windows after all
let's throw in this and
[Music]
the bucket
maybe i don't know
i kind of need the things that i have
spawn me something interesting come on
[\h__\h] it
[Music]
i i knew it i knew i heard footsteps how
did i use this [\h__\h] but it ran away
don't worry nice escape nice escape
let's escape
[Laughter]
[Music]
why
good that i had a healing
first aid kit
that's exactly the amount i need noise
or is it
now i don't have what are you kidding me
i
don't have one and then i don't have
this no no no i don't have that
tree
like
i uh kill all the trees that i wanted
we take that beautiful horse up there on
the mountain
how long have i been going over six
hours like seven hours now maybe
hi horsey
and my friend now you and me
friends forever
[Music]
i was hoping you would help me with that
thank you
just put like the copyright descriptions
into my
whoop
description
of the stream
[Music]
what
just a little bit of wood
okay can i make it now finally yay
what an accomplishment
incredible
[Music]
i should actually
i should go get some marshmallows
i don't mean edible marshmallows i mean
the questions of course
[Music]
i'll just have it open on the side
okay
ah [\h__\h] i need to go to my stupid
workman unbelievable unbelievable
[Music]
okay let me see what we got
good
oh wait those are
[Music]
not the red ones
what is this question
happy second anniversary kawawa
wait which way here uh you've been a
huge inspiration for me i started
drawing with you demi and have been
slowly improving since the since then i
haven't made any art for you since your
debut
because i realized
how incredible the other artists in your
community are and who are self-conscious
i hope one day i can either become brave
enough to make art for you again
or gain enough confidence in my heart to
share it i hope you know that a lot of
people
i can drive robot looking a lot of
people look up to you and want to
support you even if they're shy or
subtle about their support thank you for
everything oh that wasn't a question but
thank you
yeah have confidence
you probably also improved a lot since i
debuted i assume
so give it a try
i want to sing
i want to see
draw kiwawa
rocky wawa
don't let your dreams be dreams
i want to make this one too need some
stones
[Music]
yeah but thank you for supporting me
no need to be so self-conscious like
there's
all different
there's people of all different kinds of
skill levels
drawing fan art for me and i'm happy
about all of them
[Music]
the more the merrier
i'm gonna make
let's make a chest
[Music]
or a box as they call it in this game
right oh
metal fragments
and wood of course i don't have okay
never mind never mind never mind never
mind
would have been nice but okay
[Music]
hatchet i made the hatchet headshot is
here
i've got the hatchet
just gonna get a [\h__\h] on the wood now
and come back
[Music]
oh sure
oh wait
ah wait that's not stone that's not
stone
but
is that how bad is that for the ex
am i picking it up
[Music]
it's not saying anything about
me retrieving it
is it buggy
my game is broken
never mind never mind it works
don't hit your toes don't hit you out oh
that would have definitely hit your toe
be careful
survival kiwawa
[Music]
yeah yeah i know it's for one but i
thought maybe maybe
it could work
maybe maybe
do i get stones from this as well when
i'm done with it like at the end maybe
[Music]
we only just need stones right now
okay i'll take what i can get because in
the end i probably will need everything
[Music]
nope no stones
you guys remember the the snacks that
elena sent me
[Music]
me and my mommy we tried some of them
and um one morning i woke up
and my mommy she was like
that white coffee that elena sent you
it's just normal coffee
remember i was so like fascinated by it
i was like why coffee what is that does
that really exist
fascinating
even the coffee beans are white on the
picture
now it was just normal coffee and my mom
told me
basically
it's just a coffee that's not wrote like
on the picture it hasn't been roasted
yet
but
it's actually yeah
it's just normal coffee it's roasted
just on the picture they use the picture
that's not roasted
on the packaging
yeah it's normal coffee but they call it
white coffee because they added some
milk powder
in the packaging inside already so you
don't have to add your own belt that's
it
i thought this was some kind of
really
incredible revelation something i've
never seen before
in austria
[Music]
not funny
they roasted less so it has more
caffeine really
i thought it was just some special
edition you know
big bamboozle don't run into the trees
but besides that
my mommy and me we enjoyed the snacks my
mommy tried that um
i forgot what it was called
with some
some snack where there was like an egg
on the picture of the packaging
i have no idea what it was called
it's some kind of savory snack
really yummy
rocketing
[Music]
does that narrow it down well i mean if
you look back on when i showed the items
on my stream i think in mind you can
probably figure out which one i meant
yeah
but don't worry about it no need for the
effort
both my mom and rbf they both wanted to
to get those key caps
i'm fascinated by it
also my printer works again hello
[\h__\h]
finally
how much what is that
already quite a lot
let me get a few more stacks if possible
[Music]
wanna see [\h__\h] where's the eggs
see
so hard to see
[Music]
it's too dark for wood chopping
metal ore
what about stone
my stones are [\h__\h] rare
[Music]
normal stone
no really
[Music]
and the palm trees make it a bit
difficult cdx i agree
i agree
um
heard some rivet noise
okay now it's getting spooky i'm gonna
go
i feel like i hear some footsteps
where's my horse where's horse
of course
i wonder if it runs away when it's too
dark and it's scared
shouldn't it be like here
[Music]
first
could be that just leaves on its own
it must have been like somewhere in the
beginning of the forest like here
it may despawn ah
i probably despawned
oh man i gotta walk all the way again
before i do that i'm just gonna get some
more wood
oh it's too cold now
circles and that one if it despawn i
can't save it
nothing i can do about it i'm sorry
sun already coming back feels short
more yoga
[Music]
changes to like two minutes wow
i thought five minutes was a minimum
it would be in a bush
[Music]
circles
circles you there
i swear to god this game
killing me
i got a [\h__\h] heart attack i thought
something was attacking me
[Music]
my heart
it hurts
[Applause]
i got scared so easily i swear to god
one day i'm gonna die from a heart
attack
pretty sure about that
[Music]
i can walk for that train what
that's weird
right here
yeah
no helicopter right no no
[Music]
no i don't want them playing horror
games please no every game for me is a
horror game
[Music]
okay here's a marshmallow
about one year and five weeks ago you
said you would consider
playing spyro
uh-huh i know exactly who rose is have
you
considered yet
just i i recommend you to
like
if there's a game
that you guys want me to play
you don't need to
remind me of it continuously for moms
and moms and moms and moms in a row
if i feel like playing it i will play it
but like pushing endlessly is not gonna
do the trick
it's
not gonna suddenly make me wanna play if
anything it will make me want to play it
less
chances of me playing might actually
reduce
because it just gets annoying after a
while
[Music]
which is
sad because i actually like spyro
and i was the one who
brought it up and said
i want to play spyro sometime
but
yeah pushing endlessly no
no
[Music]
that's why i stopped mentioning a
certain game oh i wonder which one but
that's a good choice probably
if i want to have recommendations like
what i should play then
[Music]
there's a chance i will ask you guys
anyway on my own
hmm
[Music]
like hey i know i ran out of ideas what
i should play can you tell me
any recommendations
pedophile
crazy
hmm
hi nacho happy 2 year anniversary those
two years
have gone by so quickly huh i'm happy to
have followed the rising of this
beautiful and cheerful phoenix until now
and i will continue to follow you to the
end of whatever awaits you in the future
thank you
so after the aoe 2 stream yesterday my
question for you we all know you weren't
an avid world rocket player back in the
day have you played any of the warcraft
rts games
[Music]
uh before that warcraft orcs humans vs
humans markup two worker free
no i don't think i did
i don't think i ever played any of those
sorry to disappoint
um
wow
i don't think i did
i know i know of the game's existence
[Music]
oh if you don't need to mind the
permissional cost what kind of stream
you are really in one to make happen i
want to do more you know concert stuff
yeah but
um
it it definitely costs money no matter
what i do like even if i
do it in the japanese studio in japan
then i will still have to buy a plane
ticket but okay that's like a minimum
charge it's just a bit uh
inconvenient because
japanese members they're already there
and i can use it for free
um
yeah so
and and
um yeah but if i could just do whatever
the hell i wanted
without thinking about the cost then i
would wanna
do a really cool sick concert
[Music]
yeah i heard her
indonesia first generation
is in japan now
and they announced
they announced it right
i wouldn't say anything
yeah bye but they announced the thing
right
yeah yeah 3d showcase
pretty debut not really a debut but you
know
let's call it a debut
like some mental stuff
[Music]
which makes me
even more hopeful
that
we will get the same chance
[Music]
hopefully
soon
but that's really exciting and i'm happy
for them
what's about time i'm sure they waited
ages
i mean we from myth know how it feels
very very impatient
i mean
ideally
and this is still my
my ideal idea of how it should be but
ideally i would have wanted it to be um
3d debut first and then
anything
else like doing anything with your with
the 3d avatar
model
yeah
but things don't always go the way you
want them to go and i mean
imagine imagine us having still waited
until now and then
still never ever showcased our 3d
we wouldn't have been part of those
concerts
and
other things
[Music]
that would have been lame too we would
have like continuously looked at the
others and be like oh man i wish we
could do that
so considering how long it's been taking
i guess it was the right choice but it's
not the ideal
choice
reality is often disappointing
oh yes it is
yeah
ame ame has been
very helpful in creating such
opportunities for us indeed instead of
pc
a computer loader software that can
analyze a video and produce rotational
deltas in individual objects contained
in the feed
what
sounds fancy i'll take it
[Music]
i can finally play minecraft in rest
well
yeah yeah
given a chance what advice would you
give to 2020
[Music]
i feel like a year ago we probably also
kind of talked about
this
um
i probably tell
that chihuahua too
[Music]
if possible
already put out an original song at the
time of the debut
also
[Music]
perhaps
get a proper
microphone
and
yeah and invest or like borrow money to
get a proper microphone that works
where's the chest am i blind out here
[Music]
i finally got a box yay
let's put some of the fancy stuff what
is this not a nearby object such as
friends who can't even follow species
maybe for researching
and
some materials
crunchy mic was fun
all right turn off your sink in near
automata yes
that would be helpful too
and besides that i mean a lot of like
mental advice i guess but in the end i
don't think
it would help anyway
because like
it's just i don't know
[Music]
gonna recycle that and that
keep
that i think i'm gonna make like a um a
water catcher rain catcher
all right
set your monitor no i think in japan i
don't know i don't know how i was in
japan i had a different monitor it might
have been already set to 60 maybe but
probably actually maybe not probably not
probably not
oh yeah
you forgot your keys oh yeah there was
was there something
wasn't that cali
when did i forget my keys in in japan
during the whole lifetime
[Music]
that was cali i did in austria yeah that
that's not 20 20 kiara
that's a different quinoa
do you guys want some water
i'll give this to you
what
[Music]
okay
pour it out
[Music]
want it
i'm trying right click left book eat
everything
do i put it no that's fertilizer
it's empty oh
oh
my plants
who have
the closest
[Music]
wait can i fill it with with the
lake water
yes yes yes i hope the pig ignores me
yeah okay
we got a lot of sulfur over here wow wow
yeah it has water in it
ah
how do you use this
that's what i'm saying right here i
could even drink it
[Music]
on
can you [\h__\h] off
[Music]
it doesn't even work like anywhere
it doesn't work
5 000
does does 5 000 even fit
in there
and can it be sea water or
does it have to be
like a different water
[Music]
ah
okay so here this water would be fine
[Music]
okay
what you want in a good cup of salt okay
well that's at least realistic nice
i hope my plants don't or my seeds don't
die until then but as long as nothing
has
um grown
out of the seas hopefully
it won't die so fast
please
i want for once even if it's just in the
game i just want my plants to survive is
that too much to ask for
just this time
how do i know this water is not
contaminated huh
oh heavy
[Music]
where do i live
believe in the water okay
i believe now
[Music]
do you ever feed that
i tap back into the game with right
click that was a mistake you ever feed
your cats a couple pieces of salami or a
salami as a treat
my cats
are a weird
um sometimes i offer them
or i used to offer them sometimes some
like raw meat like uh
raw chicken
or raw anything
because i remember from the cat i had
when i lived with my mom
my cat back then
she loved that
anything really anything
like any scraps from the kitchen like in
terms of
meat she would jump on it
immediately
and be really really excited about it
and eat it within a second consume it
vacuum it
but
like her cats are not interested in it
either in it at all they don't even look
at it
[Music]
how's this
i think that hit everything
water 100
okay nice oh
[Music]
now a rain catcher would be nice too but
i guess it won't catch much rain here
but better than nothing what do i need
for that
[Music]
cooked meat
actually
i don't remember if i really tried that
but what i did try
tarp and metal fragments okay
[Music]
i will
go
get some metal fragments
when i did try for example as well was
like ham
now ham
they're kind of interested in
and they like smell it and they start
licking it
but they quickly get
like
[Music]
and sick of it
trying to trying to eat it because they
they lick it and then it gets like stuck
to the floor or whatever surface it's on
and then i can't properly
like
bite into it you know
and that frustrates them and then they
just give up and leave it there
yeah yeah it's too flat for them to eat
yeah yeah yeah
but
sometimes if i position it correctly
they will eat it
but they they make it really complicated
yeah
it's cute though sometimes i try to
share it with them but often it would
fail so i'm like why am i doing this
we're both not enjoying this are we and
then the more they lick on it on the
ground it's got it gets more and more
disgusting
i heard explosion
[Music]
okay oh another
explosion
[Music]
who's shooting
thank you guys thank you
[Music]
thank you
so sweet
[Music]
now we place this
oh
oh you're picky about where you're on
huh
oh i can't even put it here what
oh that's fun
kokonema
thank you thank you
thank you
all right all right basically the base
is basically done
now
we want to improve it
maybe
[Music]
first of all make the walls into
um the nicer type of
wood
i've got some
wood here
so that oh i was i needed a thing i need
a [\h__\h] sleeping bag too
[Music]
yeah
and the door
okay yeah
we're working on it
i'm working on it
i know how to do this now
[Music]
yeah nice
nice skills
a swimming pool but i need the dlc for
that right i was looking at it i was
like nah
[\h__\h] dad i don't need it
no i'm not interested in
stuff like that for real money you know
what it would make me consider buying
these cute clothes but if it gets
if the characters get wiped and [\h__\h]
and then i'm not gonna put much effort
into how i look like yeah
uh
what about stairs
but it's only temporary for now so maybe
i don't want to think too much about
stairs
and stuff like that one floor only is
okay for now perhaps
oh worst case we can even make stairs
outside but
yeah
okay and then
and then a sleeping bag what i need for
a
sleeping bag or even a real bed
for now
sleeping bag
[Music]
very important
so that if we die we actually spawn here
[Music]
happy second anniversary backyard
a way out to the mountain
some birds perching on the mountain top
[Music]
there on the left side maybe
i want to try
but wait how do i
i will have to build
a house and a tc
at the top to keep the
stairs from decaying but then everything
has to be connected right
or how does it recognize it as part of
the tc
[Music]
ladders just normal ladders
that's a bit like if i'm stressed out
and i need to get back inside quickly
i mean nothing's going to be fast but
you know
[Music]
uh
okay well i'm gonna try
some some wood to
waste
okay
so tonight yeah
yeah but i didn't put down the sleeping
bag yet
[Music]
chihuahua bag
okay
let's see if we can make something fun
here
we need um
we start
start
maybe here
i'm not sure how to build this but okay
let's see
but then
how
to continue
stairs
[Music]
i like that
oh yeah that's gravel
[Music]
i know the tc won't reach it but we'll
have to build something eventually but
for now
[Music]
if i do that
can i
i can't continue from there i need to
buy i need to build another like a floor
maybe as a floor now
[Music]
no
does it need to be walled
but
i gotcha
[Music]
how about this
i feel like amet could be really helpful
here but
[Music]
i wonder if this helps
but no since now they're on different
levels there's no way they will connect
[Music]
can't connect
but if i build a wall
or half a wall
or
[Music]
half a wall
low
half wall
[Music]
and then a floor on top of that
oh
wait how much more time do i have for
this before i have to go to the next
thing
[Music]
because what if i don't finish and it
will all decay
can i just put um
an hour
an hour okay okay
i wanted to just continue straight from
here
[Music]
but it won't ah wait
can continue from from the middle
but do we want that because
[Music]
this is like a like a
puzzle
[Music]
how how would i add this can i even
maybe
add a floor
here
[Music]
oh don't fall down quinoa
i wanna ah that's stupid
that's stupid
no can i turn it
maybe demolish that one
how do i demolish it
[Music]
r2 rotate okay
a buffering
[Music]
wow
you're back welcome back
[Music]
i wanted to go to the left can i um the
use where you stairs
oh wait that works
that works that way that works
and then does it always need a wall or
can i just
a floor
no
always needs a wall i guess
and i can get rid of this again
[Music]
don't pull anything funny susan i've had
enough trouble today
you know wall frame what's a wall frame
wolfram here
interesting
[Music]
i don't now if this does anything nah
nah
[Music]
how do i actually demolish it
tell me why do i do this bunk is this
your only way to do it
works i guess
[Music]
wall frame hold up for the next level
not there
oh i can't without a tc okay
i don't mind
a warm frame
here
over or
ah maybe here
beam
damn
and down
floor
let me try if it also works without the
floor now
nope
floor here
see where we go next
[Music]
i just wanna
can i just keep on spiraling spiraling
it would be cool if it could go all
around and around and around the big
stone but if i could just
ah
[\h__\h]
direction was wrong
yeah okay
triangle or normal spiral
[Music]
i just
do this
[Music]
at least for a part of it
or maybe i can
what's that
[Music]
hey you guys my super chance thank you
i appreciate it
what about what about this frame does
this help
where where does this want me oh it
wants me to
put something
here
[Music]
i want to go up there
we could parkour and go with a jump
i mean it works
[Music]
protected a bit from
from like people shooting me maybe
this sucks yeah
[Music]
ah
it's not quite
maybe maybe the other
spiral would have been better yeah
[Music]
add on to it
oh wait never mind
i don't know how to make stairs yet
oh
[Music]
why
why because of no frame
[Music]
doesn't need a frame
understandable
support
okay okay i'll give you as much support
as you need babe
baby girl
[Music]
which ones did i use this one
god
you can't do this to me just tell me you
can't place it to begin with that's
ridiculous
what about actual walls
my head just scared me
oh come on
why is that so
hard to destroy
[Music]
support it like the father had never had
yet
me the mother of these stairs will
support it double the amount
than the father ever could
[Music]
i'm so strong
yeah but what do you want from me though
is this strong enough [\h__\h] it's so dark
oh god oh god i'm scared
it's not gonna be long though it's not
gonna be long
just chill
let's take a look i don't need this huh
but i'll take it anyway i'll keep it
so far
this works
we're already what halfway there
[Music]
this this side could get rid of and
maybe build an actual
wall there but i'm scared if i get rid
of this frame now everything will fall
apart
[Music]
[\h__\h]
because i can't just replace it right
[Music]
foundation into the wall for support
into the wall
where
[Music]
you mean like i did it here maybe would
that be helpful
and maybe like
here
[Music]
let me see
i'll [\h__\h] you
how many times you're gonna break my
stairs
the stairs are not temporary no no no
this is the way to the to the actual
house i guess
a foundation
oh
what where where exactly
when i built the foundation
huh
[Music]
again we're not done
what am i doing i'm trying to reach the
top
of this
mountain chica rest this is my checkered
now me and me with me
oh no my no it's broken my axe
oh already me and woman can just fly up
there obviously i'm just building this
for visitors
[Music]
yeah
bye can't why can't i build yeah
[Music]
will this help support the whole
structure
[Music]
make sure the stairs start there so
that's kind of stupid
[Music]
do i have to get rid of the other floor
as well
this one
and then try to put the foundation there
if it works
now i don't have an x anymore
[Music]
i'm gonna i'm gonna make an eye
can i make an eye an egg
i need to connect the stairs to the
foundation
looks like a lot of drinks or extracting
excuse me are you are you saying that my
stairs look ugly
is that what you're saying
[Music]
no
ah
a few more
please don't decay how fast is gonna
start the can
yeah it's amazing it's a defense
mechanism exactly thank you
that's what i'm saying
[Music]
and org bills honestly they're not so
bad like what i've seen
it they can't even be that bad because
they let
at least in the episode the last episode
of rings of power they let the elves
build it for them
i'm not so bad and pretty smart actually
look i was actually surprised by how
smart
they seemed in that episode because
oh no from lord of the rings
my image of them was just
they were so [\h__\h] stupid
and
primitive
can i get some food
i grew i'm growing pumpkins
i'm currently growing pumpkins
oh they have been lowered nice
[Music]
thank you you guys are sending too many
super chats
thank you
[Music]
it's too sweet
you don't have to
[Music]
been on the tower with a stack
built
built a normal stupid tower yeah
i might be smarter i know
but i kind of originally i wanted to
build around
the whole structure
you know
the whole um
i wanted to build it around the mountain
spiral around the mountain i guess it
doesn't work that easily
outside there
wait i can repair that right
on the repair bands
oh
you're [\h__\h] nice oh wait i need to
take it back right
[Music]
no
it saves me
some materials
okay
[Music]
oh
what
might be built from the top down but how
do i get to the top
should i abandon this for now make
another one
how much what did i spend not that much
build
[Music]
let's assume
i'm gonna build like something from down
there to go up here can i start building
the tower right here
foundation
as close as possible
i guess
i hope nothing will like obstruct me
maybe
like about this guy and then we can try
uh
[Music]
the lower one here get the stairs and
get more stairs okay okay okay okay
and then from here
uh
go up and spiral over half a block
height
[Music]
wait which one's better
normal spiral
wait does this even work
[Music]
yep but will it not need a foundation in
between
do i just need to like wall it in maybe
yeah i know the museum is like rpg town
i know
[Music]
huh
this will be quite
the impressive home if i be able to
build it at the very top
that's all i wanted to build a really
sick home where people are going to be
like a young woman
and if someone pisses me off i can shove
them down
the mountain
and have them die
[Music]
i would like to build some walls to
cover it up
like here
ah
can i don't
because there's nothing like in between
maybe a half
like if i put a wall frame
and i built
the walden
yeah
there you go
kiwama
genius wawa
now i'm getting it i understand
enlightened i have been
and round we go and round we go and
round and round and round we go
[Music]
i agree too yes yes of course i do this
place is dangerous too a little bit to
be honest
i would like to build
i mean you can get really close to fro
big here i suppose but
it's better to be safe
oh wait oh there we go
oh maybe i should have built a wall
there hello
[Music]
wait can people like
somebody let me test something
[Music]
okay i don't think they can jump up
there
ah anya what's up i'm building a
yay someone saves my efforts
i'm trying to get uh up to the very top
yum yum
yum yum yum
[Music]
my previous try kind of failed
um but this is a i guess the easiest way
of doing it
[Music]
you're welcome to visit but i just
started it's my day one on on
in season three
just started just building a base now
see they may have restricted me to use
to not use um
uh
oh [\h__\h]
ah
why
surprised i didn't die
may have restricted me in terms of
turrets but
i'll just make it difficult in other
ways
that did sound painful yeah
why did that happen though
am i not supporting you enough already
my dear tower of doom
my dear sauron tower
build a wall
on that side
i guess i'm being forced
huh i can't
huh have i already no
i can't
made a mistake
oh wait
i can't this game is so stupid makes you
think you can't do certain things but
yes you can but wait line of sight huh i
mean line of sight blocked let me do it
let's see
now it's red
this game is so stupid
here it says i can't what about this
side
line of sight
oh yeah yeah yeah
stupid game minecraft wouldn't do this
to me minecraft wouldn't make me suffer
like this
are you happy now
i think it's happy now
[Music]
but now you're [\h__\h] with me
this place is being supported 100 by kfb
what's your problem
[Music]
rusk rust
pros tell me what am i doing wrong i
have to use ladders now ladders
oh upgrading the foundation would make
it stronger
[Music]
when we have some stone but
do the walls matter
[Music]
what if i make the stairs stronger as
well
does that matter
or won't won't that take
more support as well
if i make the stairs stronger they also
need the more the stronger the stairs
are the stronger the foundation needs to
be
you would think
none of the upgrades matter
oh 34 percent stable
34.
can i run out of
no
17.
yeah like an in-between floor
[Music]
let's try that
like
like here
and then i guess we have to make this
room a little bit bigger
am i safe
get rid of that and then build like a
foundation over there
can i
lucio
i wouldn't be able to fill the
foundation foundation used to be on the
ground right
scared
coming back
a foundation on the bottom go up with
frames
[Music]
oh so
noisy oh yeah my axe oh yeah true
um
i can build a floor there
you know you almost saw me
oh my food
hmm
that would be fun that'll be fun
so
[Music]
well there's a floor
we made a floor
[Music]
i don't know i need someone who really
knows what they're doing in this game
like pekura they're gonna play
[Music]
fourteen
percent six percent
eight percent oh the higher we go the
less stable it gets
[Music]
mamma mia what if it's out of stone with
that solved problem
[Music]
oh or the food fire at all
yeah fine
remind me a little bit
now what ladders would be like it takes
so much time to get up an elevator
how high
[Music]
can
an elevator go
[Music]
above or below this to connect it
requires power
i would just need power
maybe maybe we can build the elevator
[Music]
on this platform
what do you mean what do you need what
do you think but i mean in order to get
power it's gonna take me a while it's
not gonna be just like fingers snapping
and tadaan
get up there with lettuce first yeah and
then we build a ltc i guess
at the top
ladders rope
need rope
your rope
okay please don't decay
[Music]
europe
is this what it's like to live in the
desert huh
europe
i need a lot of roads
now i really don't have
rope at all
um this is quite the endeavor
how am i pumpkins
pumpkins
they're done are they done
uh
h it disappearing what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what's happening
no wait they're not done
i don't even see the pumpkins but okay
cool
they're growing
[Music]
and they still have enough water
26 mature
i didn't even know that pumpkins could
grow in an environment like this cool
i need um rope
i need a lot of roof
how many how much rope
three three ropes from one ladder and
how many ladders do you think
it will take me
we're not not even quite halfway there
yes
what an answer
i don't have a green card
damn it
[Music]
yeah yeah
turn
turn the clock into rope i get it i get
it but it's not gonna be that much is it
let's see if we can get some free rope
level gloves ooh
my first piece of clothing
should i go
there's
actually nothing new spawning over there
should i go to the convenience store
[Music]
let me leave some stuff at home
and then we go to the convenience store
a horse would be nice but all horses
despawned it seems
what my rascals are
i don't know what my worst goals are now
either
i feel like i had a goal
i've lost it nice gloves thank you
friend alma's car
[Music]
i need a door
but
it's fine
[Music]
thank you clear stage one heart mode
nice congratulations
[Music]
okay i'm going to go to the convenience
store kombini ikimas
hoping for some materials and you know
on the road there's gonna be some
materials too hopefully
do you see at the bottom now
it will it will wait
a little bit right for me a little bit
just a little bit
[Music]
not gonna be gone for so long
i just wonder if it's all worth it
i'm not sure about that ooh jacket nice
let's check it
nice
looking good
anything else in here oh yeah
food
this girl needs some food oh sewing kit
sewing kit
nice trip yeah anna thought it was cool
a baseball cap yo i'm getting all the
drip now oh
wow i just need pants now but who needs
pants let's be honest
what's up
why did i throw up
also why did it just say too hot 41
degrees holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
what's your problem with pickles
or sheets season
overheating
all right naked we go
i guess that was a winter coat
[Music]
what do you want
you're cooling down
[Music]
we find some stone on the way
let's find a question
[Music]
foreign
okay okay
a mailbox nice don't have to make our
own
[Music]
the question was if i
uh like why don't i want to live in
japan and so on and i you guys already
know the reason probably but you know my
cats number one and also second reason
is it's a bit difficult to live in japan
on long term
so those two reasons and you know i've
lived in japan for for three years and
right now
i would i want to live here i mean if i
wouldn't have cats right now
i might
i might have decided to live in japan a
little bit longer if i had the
opportunity
but i didn't so i don't even need to
talk about it
it's not
not
hmm
[Music]
drink
shorts
good for the desert no
i would say
pretty decent japan doesn't like it no
no that's not it but um
[Music]
like i've i've heard of people
bringing their cats overseas on like
long
[Music]
what was that hello
what was that
on the horse
couldn't be on
was i saying
was i saying yeah worried about the long
flight like um i've heard of like
stories that where cats
died from the stress
that was inflicted on them
through
the ride
[Music]
yeah and i don't want to risk that with
my cats because i know my cats are like
especially since they're they're cats
that stay indoors
they're not used to all that stress
outside
and my
chunky monkey every time i do vacuum
cleaning even after how many years four
years or so
she still
gets so freaked out
when i turn on the vacuum cleaner
oh look at that rope it's my rope not
your rope
tomorrow
[Music]
i don't want to have that
burden on me
[Music]
any advice for your loyal lurkers is
there anything you want to say to them
me you're my absolute favorite person an
important part of my day today congrats
on the anniversary attention love you so
much i hope by now you understand
every lurker how would i know until now
i'll continue to watch you loyally and
faithfully from the sidelines loved with
love and earnest congrats to my aussie
thank you
oh you sound so nice you shouldn't be
lurking
why why are you working stop working
that's what i want to say to you guys
stop lurking
yeah i i guess
i'm not taking the pickles again i guess
you're allowed to lurk
um
but i don't know see if you can say hi
every once in a while it would be nice
or like make a twitter and at least
reply there you don't have to always
brag in the chat but after stream ends
i love reading through everybody's
feedback and opinions
from stream
[Music]
because it also helps me
with my motivation and also with
planning future content
but generally i also like always like
having a really active chat
i forgot i could go upstairs
[Music]
to interact with
and honestly there's lurkers who became
non-lurkis
after i picked up
um
solar panels nice for at four four four
four four power maybe can i use that for
power
if you try
interacting with me
once maybe maybe if i read your comment
then you'll be so happy that you'll
cancel you can't stop
and you will continue
writing comments you can't look anymore
i'm going back i think
check out this place one more time
[Music]
oh that's yeah
oh no space can i wear this is it too
hot and now it's nighttime so it
shouldn't
shouldn't be a problem
[Music]
they can't stack why don't they stack
first time order food
no
i'm lazy you order food for me how about
that
[Music]
why are you laughing huh
why are you laughing chet
[Music]
all right
got some a good amount of
of scraps
beautiful
wow
change the music
you should be ordering a food for me not
laughing
i don't even know what i want to eat i
had um red pasta yesterday i had pasta
the day before i failed no
i had crabby boost
wait i still have like curry boys but i
don't want to cook after 12 hours of
streaming you know
i could still grill i have one more like
raw curry wurst and some potatoes that i
could make into fries but i don't think
i'll feel like
cooking it
afterwards you know
[Music]
what's it gonna put in there is that it
highlights good
okay you can take that
okay
to put a car on it
i guess
oh man i got i got binoculars
nice
so what is that
oh yeah flair i don't really need that
but maybe if we get on top of the
of the mountain my mouth checker is then
i can light up the night sky
yes of course i've tried base chicken
salts i talked about it like
oh the day before yesterday or so
i put some
chicken salt on my fries
oh you can't enter here you have to jump
from the top or what
shimani muska who is eight zed ask
example
she's not streaming rest right she's uh
she might be online though
let's see if she answers
because azuki senpai asks
not saying boy but are you in
are you on your island
is she
damn i got even more to recycle
no answer huh
don't think she's
i think she's around
look for other pizzas so it must be like
2 2 a.m 3 a.m
one more recycling sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry coming through coming
through
that means also i'm gonna be done soon
yeah
[Music]
that's this marathon
almost feels too short
yahoo
say hello so she doesn't feel lonely
because she got no answer
i said oh guess she isn't here but hello
i am motivated
i wonder how much azuki senpai knows
about
uh
she's pretty good at it
go away
i want to go that way
oh she's there
maybe we can ask her for some food
i say hello
[Music]
does she have another entrance
oh [\h__\h] how did you build this so fast
i have something
nothing interesting
[Music]
oh sorry i'm trying to knock
hello
how do i
do
sorry
huh
oh she's drowning
drown
maybe she's just um
[Music]
i think my voice is not working oh
oh oh that was a good oh i think she
hears me
[Music]
arigato
foreign
dead eyes
i asked what they're doing jump
conversations yeah yeah tell them oh
she's dancing oh
i'm really wondering if they don't hear
me though
i don't i think since they're not
streaming i guess they just oh
eh
[Music]
summer
is
[Music]
[Applause]
she's going to take a look she said
she's an amateur but she's going to take
a look
at
okay okay
and they look like fortnite players
[Music]
okay
i told her i'm building the house there
because
i can have a good look at piccolo
senpai's face from there which is not
actually the actual reason
but now that i think of it it might be
the actual reason
oh oh corn
corn let's go
yummy
now this is a stone that i was working
on right i think so
i think they're in like off streaming
modes that's why they don't talk
they just chat
it's too late
[Music]
i wonder if they hear me from so far
it's very helpful to say she's an
amateur yeah
um
[Music]
i said what that is i was wondering what
that thing over there was on the screen
huh
[Music]
me
it's half the cake no i don't is it oh
is that
oh it's starting to decay oh no
oh no
ah
[Music]
okay telling me to create
a tool chest first
yeah yeah
yeah i will i will order food
soon
spoon
[Music]
you probably they think like what the
[\h__\h] is this it looks so shitty
[Music]
yay i get oh thomas
oh
[Music]
she wants to try something so i guess
maybe no tissue yet is better
okay
[Music]
so sweet
i heard something fall apart what was
that
what was that was that my house
is decaying
i take up some clothes
how does she survive with this hot
hot outfit
damn i have no idea what's going on i'm
trying to get some advice you know
from
professional rust players
oh
i guess just building a big base around
all of this i wonder if that would be
effective
[Music]
the foundation is
one of them was so proud they had to
make real snurfer
if you think about it yeah
[Music]
it feels like she knows what she's doing
let's check if it got stronger at the
top because it was six percent before
all right that's just the
walls
oh no that one's still six percent
ah
i lost track of the time
uh
yes um can you oh
what's that we just go
where did that go doesn't fall down
oh she's telling me where it is
[Music]
[Laughter]
can you guys
wait like
can you can we
can i get like 15 more
minutes sorry
okay i told them a little bit a little
bit delay
like like uh cutting this off here now
is also a bit difficult oh oh that's
what's falling apart okay good
it's professional resting
eat eat
eat
yum yum yum yum yum
did it get better now maybe
mother mother
[Music]
building inspector
yeah i have first priority
that's eight percent six percent still
oh
let me try it i'm guessing it doesn't
work but
yeah okay
it's all the snare
damn
live structure going on here to support
that
[Music]
oh
wait that's
was that always 100 stable
at the bottom
hmm
oh no yeah yeah yeah
use other stairs
use the walls yeah
[Music]
it's a mystery
oh
can only stack up to six floors
[Music]
is
oh that might be true because it is six
floors right now is it it's really so
can someone google that
no higher spelling 40 free flows
[Music]
which one is it 33 isn't really possible
it's really only six then well
start a new one on top okay we can try
that
rotate rotate but that
even that is only 14 stable
like i can i can
probably put stairs here but
google says 33 floors
pretty free for a whole building a
single set of stairs can't go that high
ah
[Music]
even if this is six percent and i
continue on the side
just because six percent doesn't mean
that
it's gonna fall apart right as long as i
have a tc
yeah i have to go
ah
[Music]
i feel bad for them i just got them to
help me
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
they want to continue building
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
she says she's going for the tub
yeah oh they're so sweet what the
hell i said don't worry about it if you
guys don't feel i can just leave it like
that don't worry about it but oh
[Music]
oh okay
okay uh set up time uh
intermission
oh what the [\h__\h]
please don't shoot me
what
i'm scared i don't even have a door yet
but oh well okay close game
bye bye
i hope i'm safe in that house
i might go get a door tomorrow okay i'm
gonna set up now um i need a little bit
[Music]
me
tell me
[Music]
um
i
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
oh
is oh
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
know
so
[Music]
you
oh
[Music]
me
oh
is
[Music]
i've been trying to find my destiny
um
me
[Music]
okay
switching to this screen because you
guys apparently think it's already over
it's not over
wait we're setting up please wait
so
[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
my
so
[Music]
sorry for the wait it took a little
while also i had to go to the idol
meeting and then
um we lost someone on the way but we're
all complete now
yeah
hey
yeah yeah yeah
uh here we have
some lovely whole life english members
with me
uh yes indeed let's start to introduce
them right next to me ina please
introduce yourself
hi i think everybody except ahmed and me
are really tired cronie and you know i
think very tired doesn't it
uh
by tired you mean just woke up yeah yes
yeah
we woke up
at around the same time
yeah
good morning
morning girl good morning
it will be just sweet dreams it'll be
good because
they're like so green
they can't focus on the game so it'll be
easy to win against them
strategizing already
no you don't know about the sleeping
tiger rising dragon strat
yeah yeah it's like a drunk
dragon yeah
but an insomniac technique
i mean do you want to put yourself a
little bit higher
yeah
yeah yeah a bit more she's right she's
ascending
cute okay oh oh that's too much
yeah that's good that's crying
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna um not show you
my screen anymore i'm gonna oh wait i
wasn't showing it anyway huh huh
hold on all right
okay yeah i've never played this game
before i don't think you girls have
either right wait wait we're not done
with the introductions
i don't know who anyone is who are you
people who is that blue haired girl i'm
new but less cool
oh oh that blue hair girl that beautiful
blue haired girl is oro crony from
hollow
[Music]
yeah there was an effort yeah thank you
nice to meet you thank you for hanging
out today
of course thank you for inviting me
and next to me amelia watson who was
just playing rust with me but not quite
with me but she was definitely on the
server doing something
yes
hello amelie watson number one detective
from my live english myth yeah i was
playing rust i was just gathering cars i
was gonna visit you but uh i didn't have
any time there's still one gavin how
many do you have now uh
how many cars do i have now
uh one two three four five oh whoa
you can have cars and rust yeah yeah i
have an auto dealership oh chronically
you're right
i'm starting too right
yeah um i haven't started like how long
has it been since the new season started
only like five days or something i think
yeah that was pretty cool and i just
started today so everything's like
jointly definitely not cult of peace
definitely not relative nah crony
violence choose violence
or something in between like you know a
movie stance
i'm like in the moody stance sometimes i
choose violence sometimes i choose peace
it's so you know
you go with the flow you go with what
you want what you feel like you could be
a boat seller oh
a boat seller yeah they got boats
yeah oh
boats boats bugs that reminds me of how
i met your mother i know i know i know i
don't but
there's this canadian lady that i think
she did uh was it was that girl when
they did some commercial about boat
sports books i think
both phone calls
i don't know what you're talking about
okay well anyway thank you thank you for
being here we're gonna play this game
called all games which is i think about
board games
uh no idea how to play this game but
let's figure it out how to play
oh deep sea adventure
roll the dice and descent to the bottom
of the sea pick up the treasure back
this is a game where you try to make it
back to your submarine submarine
cool the deeper you go the bigger the
treasure gets however the amount of
treasure
oh wait
you guys here
we had the problem because you know how
i i couldn't capture it properly for a
capture card but since i captured for
obs
i don't hear the sound but
never mind now we hear it
all right turn it on through okay
because obs hears the sound even though
i don't really properly hear it you can
monitor the sound yeah yeah i'm
listening to it through obvious now okay
okay
is this double or
let's see it's currently on monitor and
output so it should be apparently it's
monitor only
okay now now it shouldn't be doubled
okay then if when you're going to make
your turn
you will start to slow down
not only that but as you pick up
treasure your air supply will rapidly
deplete and everyone shares the same air
supply whoa if other players start
picking up treasure the air supply will
decrease even more quickly
a yelp a bit loud okay
there you go
if you don't make it back to the
submarine before the air supply runs out
you will not earn any points watch the
movements of the other player z and
decide when it is the right time to turn
back aim for victory
interesting
i thought this was like
wait there's like more
ah this is one specific table but aren't
there like games in between i'm not sure
we should just
go into it without thinking too much
about it but maybe
maybe that's a bad idea
uh i mean we can just wing it yeah swing
it
yeah
i'm sure the game will
proceed on its own and we'll make it out
a lot yeah
i'm so sorry
i'm still used to ps controller because
i played so many things with ps
controller recently
i got it
i'm still in the same table
yeah yes oh then i should be able to
rejoin
probably
is there like a new leader now is you
know the leader it's me
oh no
ah
but that could just invite you no more
oh can you
[Music]
um
what do you want to enter the code oh
how do i
i'll do it i'm going to take that
oh
my gosh
notification yeah screen
oh i didn't know you could do that on
switch as well i thought it was only a
steam thing oh i'm in
nice are you the leader now
i am okay let's go
um
[Music]
25 air
except for amen
coincidence is it my turn oh it's my
turn yeah you can dive down
into the deep blue blue ocean
oh
[Music]
i'm not sure i guess
but it's like free real estate
[Music]
but then you have to make it back in
time right and then there's i guess
there's different maps okay
is this this is it
rule that's
oh no
oh i can jump over you then okay okay
you all rolled like four oh
i rolled five uh-huh close enough
[Laughter]
oh my god i rolled first
you slow down when you pick up treasure
it's about greed
oh so there's 20 24 more times we can
ah go i guess
oh so you can like go back and drop off
the treasure
[Music]
okay the more the more we pick up the
less air i remember that from the
from the description uh-huh
are you kidding me
i like the colors and the board just
pretty yeah
nice water reflection
no don't don't do anything you don't
want to pick it up
whoa
[Music]
i'm gonna i'm gonna go big or go home
well you'll make it back on time that is
why is it always four
oh
obviously pick up why would i not pick
it up pick it up pick it up
yeah what you said you slowed down what
do you mean by slow down like if you
roll a three you only move two spaces or
something i'm not sure about it yeah so
really so i'm assuming that little
thoughts like the minus like whatever
you have
like from your dice roll so if i wrote
the two but then i had the dice or the
platform too
then i would have
gone nowhere oh
oh there's like math involved and stuff
oh
i can't
handle the math but okay
don't think too much about it but was it
inna and cronie
you guys learned
oh
but i mean the few games that i saw in
the first part they were not not much of
a challenge so
you know you would think that until
like
you actually are at the spot and you're
just like breaking no thing
did they get more difficult
um there were some tricky questions oh
the tricky i mean the the questions
themselves were pretty broad
man the rainbow thing
but i guess what you mean with like
being under pressure then you can't
answer questions like the other day i
recorded some official program i won't
say exactly what it was but
then it was like awesome
oh you know how are you laughing do you
were you by any chance there with me
oh i don't know that's nice oh
or another yeah it was a pretty easy i
would say a math question but i didn't
have much time to answer it and then
like
i had it yeah
that one was i think it was pretty
insane probably but i couldn't answer
but did that take two
oxygens oh
oh
maybe because everybody's picking up too
deep
[Music]
how far do you want to go
how far are we going
[Music]
what what is the famous fault line in
california
oh my god
i'm thinking of going back
you can go back yeah
because it gets dangerous we have to
make it back with the treasure or die
what yeah
oh each brick is minus one air ah
oh you can even drop yeah if it's too
much treasure okay it looks yeah bye it
looks pretty
available already
earlier
something so bad
i could carry the most treasures but
that might bite me in my butt later
wake up wait no cronie has also the same
amount
but she's way further ahead than i am
danger zone
what is this game we're figuring it out
right now
it's a game of chicken it's called oink
games i'm going home sport games a
collection of really real life existing
board games on the switch i guess
ah
oh
goodbye cronie
i don't think you're making it back
oh no
we all planted food stop moving these
guys only have three oh my
[Music]
if i die then everyone died
wow
okay now i see the problem
oh no
pick up one and then go back and keep
going a little bit at a time i guess
so oh no
no we did
we couldn't we're dead we couldn't move
even one spot
we died
oh but that's it we still win they're
still winning
can't believe we all died oh that's
unfortunate
oh wait what the heck
oh my god
i'm not gonna go that far i'm not stupid
no no no no
[Music]
oh it's three rounds this is the second
round mm-hmm
surely we can survive at least one of
the rounds right um yeah
yeah i have a plan i don't know about
you guys okay she has a plan
oh six oh nice that's pretty that's the
highest yeah yeah yeah pretty good
i think i'll
go one more and then i'll go back maybe
[Music]
is there music on this game i can't hear
you yeah it's really quiet though it's
like serene oh
meditation yeah
it really is like what do you imagine to
hear in a spa like when you get a
message yeah like when you're getting
outside
[Music]
i know how that feels so i've gotten
many gotten many massages always listen
to this never
never got one she got him you're amazing
highly recommendable
i'm gonna try
follow ian's body
actually maybe you guys heard of it but
when i went to the
to the maldives with rayne
we also went to a spa there like it had
a spa on on the water
on the top of the water and see yeah and
the floor was see-through glass
so you know how you put your face
through the massage table and you look
at the ground normally i've been to
million massage places but normally it's
just like ugly floor
but in this case you could see the water
and you could hear it turtle no turd
don't know but fish fish many fish yeah
really yeah many beautiful fish very
beautiful like tropical amazing fish and
then you look at the water and you hear
actual natural ocean sounds and not just
something from a cd player or so
yeah
that was nice that was pretty
dope that was the real spa experience
did you get some fresh fish
um
i think i completely stayed away from
seafood throughout the whole trip oh
okay
honestly it's not a bad choice because
you can get sick from eating seafood if
you don't careful oh yeah
oh you keep on diving crony
yeah
they're going big
when you grab them all
are you going for the bailout
didn't learn anything
i'm going back
[Music]
chicken
chicken okay
okay are you kidding me what are the
terrible
terrible diced fruit
you gotta real bank to go home wow
everybody's gonna die
no you're gonna live you're me you're
gonna be fine it's right now i have a
choice
you should go back
okay go back
you guys are too careful now
i want to live
i want to live do nothing okay
mood
slowly getting to the midpoint
i can only go back it only lets me go
back
oh
oh congratulations to you first
okay okay
nice nice okay i'm gonna go back
oh oh okay there you go
oh can't go far though
oh she's she's
making a bath
oh
wait you only have a four right now
cronie did you drop something else
nah i only picked up one oh
i guess that's a good idea too
oh okay
do nothing
well our eye colors are like a gradient
sort of oh
we could we could like arrange them true
from light blue to kind of darkish blue
to purple blue
[Music]
you're not going to make it
let me live
i will 10 air no crony wait for me
yo
[Music]
i think so
you have like two turns probably
okay come on okay okay it should be fine
[Music]
okay just one one air went down nice
nice
oh
one two
oh you you can make it i can make it i'm
coming home martha
america
[Music]
give me give me more
give me two seconds why do you know her
name
[Laughter]
what the hell i'm gonna be last no
[Music]
homies for real for real
oh
oh man why am i last now
oh wait oh you're still here
so close
let me
i listen make it
okay i think the dices are the dye the
dye are somehow rigged because this oh
no it's crazy you can make it you can
make you just gotta roll it
higher than
oh one okay okay you made it you mean
all right
no nice we all made it well yeah
who got the most one more round
one more round i think
14 i think i have the most
oh this is like a random number in the
back oh
oh oh what really i thought was just the
thoughts that are being added up i
thought yeah that's what i thought too
oh this one's a short course but then
yeah because the ones were already
picked up they stack up at the end so
that it gets less and less
[Music]
gotcha by the way since i'm doing this
12 hour
uh endurance stream for my anniversary
what are amanda planning for their own
anniversary stream do you have something
nothing as long as 12 hours
variety of stuff yeah oh
nice when when when
when are you doing it um on the
i think it's on tuesday
[Music]
what can you give us a hint where we can
expect
some oh [\h__\h] laughing at myself
goddammit
laughing at yourself what laughing
didn't do that last year oh i'm laughing
at myself again okay okay you're gonna
watch your debut stream or or watch the
when you watched your debut stream like
the watch along i'm watching myself
watch the debut stuff
yeah i'm gonna do it every year i
decided to not do that because that i
don't wanna see it again one time is
enough
[Music]
what about what are you planning or are
you just you know focused on
our together thing uh
i have a stream oh i'll just be on
watson wednesday so it'll be eight hours
but i think i'll probably just do the
anniversary stuff like in the first few
hours and then after that i'll just play
games like normal so i'm not really sure
actually what i'm going to do yet i
don't know but i have
um an announcement during the stream and
that's it
announcement
do i know what it is
no you want to know tell me
no
yeah slide into your dms after you tell
me
it's not that cool though
[Laughter]
i'm curious
i'll tell you guys after okay okay okay
secret announcement
we gotta keep going we're going deep on
the floor
oh inaudible oh [\h__\h] yeah you're gonna
go for the stack i'm going for the stack
i'm gonna take your stack first i'm
gonna take the stack i want to stack two
but i guess inna needs the stack more
than any of us
what the heck i'm so far behind
it's okay on me
i
[Music]
oh
don't you kind of have an advantage if
you go first in this game i feel like it
oh yeah i think so no
that was a nice row one last stock for
me
good stack
it's okay we saved my here
we got
there's a really small oh aina is
getting the smaller stack i mean there's
a big one for you sir
no
[Music]
no you can do it
going later you get to skip spaces okay
guys come on come on you can do it on me
oh yeah first movement usually has some
advantage in board games sucks
rigged games
which makes going for
[Music]
you guys have a favorite board game
sorry
[Music]
i only remember playing monopoly
i've changed
what was that accounts
chess
checks checks did you like chess
christmas
board game passing support game yeah it
is but i didn't know you liked chess
like so much that you would say it's
your favorite board game wow
yeah
it's fine
oh no can i make it back
crony should play
oh
oh i didn't already oh really
yeah i missed it you win
i won one she won once it was a tie
wow ollie was coached by a professional
chess player before so you're winning
against her was quite the accomplishment
i would say mm-hmm
be proud of yourself
oh yay
oh yay but yeah about you
favorite board game i remember when i
was younger i i loved monopoly but also
menshi agora technique which uh i think
in english is just called
ludong
but
this is switch
51 board games or whatever it was called
that game made me like um that game with
the pebbles with the marbles
i mean what's the one who taught me i
think was it you
uh
i think so yeah yeah and since then i
enjoyed quite a lot
yeah that one's fun yeah
oh god it's only was it oh
[Music]
am i not making it back either
maybe oh dude have you guys ever played
snakes and ladders that one's fun no
what's that oh yeah that one's fun too
snakes and otters
[Music]
first one to the end i think and
if you land on a snake it sends you down
but if you land on a ladder you go up
the boards it's kind of like similar
layout to how this board is like for the
submarine thing what happens when you
land on the otter
you swim around the map and you get to
the end
yeah you get eater out of the board oh
no i guess there was no other choice
ah she set us up for it
well i guess this is i don't know if
this is considered a board game but
probably it probably is but as a child
as a small baby child i also really like
the one where you have like a little
um a fishing rod and you fish like these
these fish
in the on in the board game
they open up their mouths automatically
you have to
try to catch them it's like a
batman yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
so cute
what about hungry hippos i love that one
too
but it was so scary that one was so
scary yeah
i wanted to buy it since i saw the end
like hungry hungry hippos
guys
yeah we're all gonna work
no drop your stuff you guys are too
greedy
any last words oh [\h__\h]
oh
it's already smelling oh we're dead it's
already too late then drop it off
well keeping it
i wouldn't be able to keep it anyway
yeah right because
we all died yeah we were all dead it was
fun
i could have made it out
oh
oh the moral of this story is don't be
too greedy
we finally learned something from our
mistakes but the last round we still
lose that's so sad
because you pick up so many i think on
the way back or something well i was
trying to pick up some on the way back
understand like a different game in this
game there must be a different game
yeah there's more yeah there's more
let's play another one different one how
do we
get to a different one
oh i'm it press
eight
okay hey
what should we try oh there you go
what's happening goes to new york
startups moon adventure let's face that
face that looks funny
this one
girl she's only 15 minutes so
yeah in a girl it's your game yeah sure
not quickly
oh well we probably should have just
jumped in
oh
oh the air oh there's a lot of styles if
you play
uh
oh i got the best mustache
[Music]
oh that's a classy mustache
oh okay
great they're free suspects it's like a
video only check to
guess the criminal
suspects each have a number from two to
eight and the suspect with the highest
value is the criminal i know there's too
much tanks tldr
what within the freestyle space the tile
the highest value is the criminal
aha however
a one of the suspects is a5 what
no we're too new at this game to set
someone up oh the suspect in the
smallest value is the criminal what what
unless that i'm just going to choose i
think if it goes over eight then
that means that they're waiting
cara you have to you have to do
something okay
i'll get it
i'll get out if one suspect is five then
reverse numbers
what
if there are three suspects that you can
only check two guess the criminal
the suspects each have a number from two
to eight and the suspect with the
highest value is the criminal however if
the suspect has a five then the suspect
with the lowest value is a criminal
detectives can be hints but they might
also be trying to set you up oh so one
of you is a suspect right
okay
because it's not me
oh no each player is a detective and
must figure out who the criminal is in a
series of crime scenes
the criminal is uh one of three suspects
the the little little human shaped
plates um the criminal has the largest
number out of the three suspects but if
one of the suspects with the five the
suspect with the smallest number is the
criminal okay
the information that each player will
observe is slightly different than the
other players so the guesses might be
different too
try to guess correctly and pin the blame
on the anchor
blame of incorrect guesses on other
players so that you don't get stuck with
the
inaudible complicated among us
complicated among us
pals with two to eight written on the
movie is the number one yeah
that was five so what happens i don't
know
huh
is the game just like playing on its own
i think it's revealing
oh this
oh
[Music]
did i accidentally win yeah you
accidentally won yeah
how did i do that
if it wasn't five
wait but if one of the suspects has a
five the suspect with the smallest
number is the criminal
yeah but there wasn't a five it's not
one of the three that's on the board
right now
[Music]
okay cool
okay run scene begins five got killed oh
okay
i
think i understand
[Music]
oh okay okay
i need someone to explain this to me in
german
[Music]
i think it's like
if if you imagine a group of people
walked in and they each had these dots
on their body
and if the dots correspond to whether or
not they're a criminal i guess right
so
if in the group of people that walk in
one of them has five dots on them then
the lowest number is the criminal but if
there is no person with five dots then
the highest number is the criminal
huh
okay so now it's showing me two numbers
uh the title the highest value is the
criminal
okay so the one that i don't see it
could be a five and in that case
it would be the
but i don't see the five so for now i'm
going for the highest i guess i didn't
see
oh yes
maybe
i wonder if i chat did i understand it i
think you got it really
i do not unravel the truth unravel who
died the x died okay what was x what
does it matter who died does it change
the values because there's only a number
uh set number of um
thoughts right
oh nice yeah
i think i understand it
i don't understand what that d is or
what is doing over there these the the
person who died
oh
oh oh oh rip oh no crony oh i am coming
don't die no no no i'm not smart no i'm
dying
i'm dying here and you tell me it was
much
not a hunter okay i'm like the opposite
of smart right now i'm like
like dying dumb
okay i think understood roughly at least
the basics
what was that
okay what's that though
what's that that they just showed us
though the alibi ones are the innocent
ones so they will not play a part in the
uh
everyone sees different um clues
you have to figure out
like if that's gonna be the lowest
number that's the
criminal or the highest number oh so
that i could at least make out when they
show me only two out of three
that i know oh it at least can't be
those numbers that i saw from the alive
eyes
yes okay well what did you see inna what
did i see
what did i see though you see mine
i don't think i saw the middle one no no
[Music]
yeah so everyone gets like a different
set of clues and you gotta figure out is
is this gonna be a case where the lowest
number is the criminal or the highest
number that's criminal
[Music]
i'm gonna go for the one that i don't
see
[Music]
please be an
oh yeah because if it's five then it
would be uh the lower oh okay okay
i got it right three times in a row wait
why did i get four out of five though i
don't understand
you don't suck
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
okay
that person did
okay huh
okay
okay okay okay
oh
now the question is what are the chances
of this number
being the right one
[Music]
nice crime game i think this is a so
it's like really it's kind of guessing
yeah it is kind of a
like percentage you know
what's the chances of
yeah and also rng on one of what you are
being shown because there are numbers
that you don't see right you have the
two clues two on the board and the one
dead person so you don't know
i'm joining you ina
could be the one i didn't see but you
probably saw that one and you still went
for seven so okay okay okay oh
okay what also is really helpful is
seeing on the side next everybody's
icons to check which ones they've
checked oh
[Music]
what are the chances
that's true if i wasn't if i was in
europe like a boat i probably would have
also picked that one mm-hmm because you
would assume that wait what did kiara
get to yeah see that's what i don't get
it's the last person who guess
like they get the all of the
man with hands
what the hell i'm fine with that
oh it's cuz it's cause you can also like
call a bluff so a small person like
someone else gets the uh
oh how do you call someone bluff
like like you have to place the icon and
kind of try to convince
oh that's risky others to like put it
down where you put it
so that even if you get it wrong you
don't get the
you don't get ah but it's not like you
were bluffing you were really thinking
you can't trick people though yeah yeah
accidentally you can't really like
piggyback off like someone's
you know guesses i wasn't drunk
this will be hard wait how would the
game assume that i did that if i if i
chose something that was not um like
visible to me okay i get that but i'd
show something that was visible to me
hmm
i'm just thinking for myself
you know i feel like even if we read the
rules though i probably wouldn't have
fully understood yeah
okay anyway that's an interesting game
very interesting
is getting stronger
[Music]
you're not moving anymore by the way are
you thinking so hard you stopped moving
oh probably yeah
[Laughter]
don't make me pick last
[Music]
but you have higher risk of getting like
all the chips
like me in the first round
well the numbers i'm seeing
okay i see that's the dead purse okay
yeah that's good is that good okay yeah
is it six
[Music]
could it be
[Applause]
okay we got it right we got it right
thank you
man i'm too trustworthy
now i just thought it was that one
because the numbers the other ones was
low and you know
both of them are the ones that i saw
were both low but i was like what if
there was a five in the middle but then
like if there was a five then i don't
know currently wouldn't have tried that
one i got five in the crew so i knew it
wasn't i knew it wasn't a lower number
oh
[Music]
i was like where would the five be it's
kind of like what you have to guess for
too yeah five is really important
[Music]
okay
see the cars we're dealt so this means
uh what does this mean again
oh i don't want to go first
[Laughter]
that's risk though even if you get it
wrong
someone else not true because it's with
you
okay she's chosen
okay
what is an x
it's nothing it's dead i think the
person is dead
is it no it's just okay numbers used for
four players two three four five six
seven yes eight can do it as a zero yeah
oh
that's
zero pretty much i think it's just like
a non-existent value
ten says chat
ten roma and roman is ten and like no it
is but it doesn't happen
they both wait you guys are both seeing
you three all saw the same
same clues okay
oh
why do we all see this why did you guys
pick that one what's that yeah
[Music]
yeah why did you guys pick that one huh
don't trust me
i'll backstab you
oh i'm going for the original choice
okay
oh i see
you know oh
[Music]
oh but
it really depends what the middle one is
i haven't seen the middle one oh you're
still thinking about it yeah it depends
on what the middle one is
yeah we'll do it yeah what the middle
one is maybe it's a seven then
[Music]
oh
please please
please
she didn't
[Music]
unless there's a five no okay if there's
a five at the time the only way we would
have lost if it was the middle one was
five oh okay they would have gotten it
yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait nice nice nice thinking good
thinking i thought i had to go to the
i did
oh so you guys didn't see a five yeah
yeah i i saw a five yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh
mistake at the very start though with
crony getting battery by mistake yeah
that was yeah that was amazing that was
like what like did i get like three all
at once
is it because she voted with like
everybody else that was wrong yeah
uh okay okay yeah okay
that was cool i like that one actually
now that i get it
yeah i think it's we could even try it
again but let's try a different one
first oh different okay
this one um this one's ten minutes this
face that face looks funny um let's read
how to play first
oh how to play yes
did one person read it
uh one player uses a variety of
differently shaped parts to create a
face according to the theme card while
the other players try to guess correctly
sounds like fun within the time limit
the player making the face needs to
match the face to the face on the theme
card the other players will try to guess
which theme is being made
both the players that guess correctly
and the player making the face will
receive points a new player will make
the next phase in the game continues
even though the face parts are geometric
giant
there's a pn
yeah
tricky shapes you can put them together
to make some surprising facial
expressions
you can use this part like this oh yeah
you're creative
yeah one player uses a variety of
differently shaped parts to recreate the
facial expression written on the theme
card while the other player try to guess
correctly about the player that um
okay we already wrote this okay so one
person creates the face with the theme
and then everyone guesses and if we if
whoever guesses right plus the person
who makes the face
gets point okay let's do it i think i
get it also chad i'm not sleeping i'm
playing on handheld mode so i keep
looking again that reminds me this
reminds me of my favorite ever board
game actually now i remember i don't
know if it exists outside of like europe
but there's this game where
um you have you play with uh one person
i don't think you can play with more
than two people and you both have a set
of like people's faces that only you can
see
guess who yeah guess who
yeah it's supporting them here too
i love this game
isn't that like where you have like all
the people and you like um
yeah you're like yes with the pieces
yeah yeah yeah and you like flip them
flip the little yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
you put the person down
but okay let's try this all right start
okay
who's gonna be making the first face
all right
here is the face maker over here okay
don't look at my stream that's big
cheating okay oh i chose the theme
oh no ah the theme is being chosen for
me okay
oh make a face according to the theme
okay are you guys
even seeing the pros process of it
i think if you're putting stuff on it
yeah obviously you see it
[Music]
this is cool yeah
[Laughter]
why why is the forehead so big
because he's bald don't worry about it
poor guy
can i change the color no okay so it has
to be like mixed colors all right
well okay i don't know how else to
express this hmm
dude would you guys take a few more
seconds oh do you see them already
[Music]
wait are you done uh
yeah
i mean if they wouldn't think it's that
they wouldn't think it's
that
i wouldn't think it's
[Music]
although
are we supposed to guess yet yeah we're
supposed to guess right now okay okay
okay good luck guessing
i'm done
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh i should have added a tear
maybe okay oh there's a teardrop not
really but you can make one you can make
one yeah
which i didn't think of ran away i don't
get points because nobody guessed it ah
we'll get on the next one
[Music]
okay
your best dummy
oh
look at him
[Music]
i don't see it well there you go
oh
we have i was speechless
i have enough
forgot my wallet that's cute i don't
know any of these people bring it on
okay
and see what amma will be making out of
this
i'll make it cute
are those the eyes wait you shouldn't
tell us i guess oh
wait is it good for the drawer as well
if we guess that does everybody get
watched because yeah points even though
you didn't guess it but uh-huh yeah yeah
only only when someone guesses it right
the uh the face maker that's the point
okay
but you probably you can just
give us yeah vocal cues on what it is
oh that's that looks sad already
i think either
this or that
oh
do i get points if you guys get it right
yeah yeah but don't tell us anything
just
yeah communicating i think is no no
illegal that's illegal
okay
i'm done
[Music]
oh he says
i don't know any of these people kind of
thing
i'll get there
yeah it makes sense
to say
okay yeah
all right how best to convey
a good face
okay who is it
it's me okay okay okay the tools so make
something
all right what's the themes
nice today i'm just going to say it i
love you
i want to go home man i slept great i
did
get out of here let me handle it that's
cute interesting phrases i like this one
i love um
there you go
i said it
i want to go home in such a mood
but aren't we all already home
home is where the computer's at yeah
with faster internet
computers
[Music]
those eyes closed don't say anything
i wonder if this is gonna
work
is that a tooth
are you making a petal a tongue
looks like
[Music]
and smart way to use it um okay i'm
already done we all got the right answer
problem yeah
sure you guys got
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
give us points too for guests garage
come on
wow that was so man i slept great
[Music]
i wish i had that
yeah okay i sleep as pro cronie's nicely
oh boy
okay
no crony go crony cronin
i'm gonna throw this
i believe in you
oh
a new one ouch that was hot and that's
exactly what i thought that was
difficult that's difficult
how would you convey that god what
angry
no
not quite
oh
that must be an eye right yeah
where is where's the other one there's
only i don't think there is yeah
like
sizes and so on other colors
it's fine
what do you call this again when you
have two different eye colors
oh
hi okay i
hit
had a chromium thank you that's it
oh oh unamused very only i think it's
this one
it could even be that one
[Music]
oh i can't i can't change my yeah no
changing
done how do i
get down
we're still going
whatever good enough i feel like it's i
feel like it's the wallet i don't know
it could be that oh yeah
yeah it could be almost all of them
except for that looks yummy
yay
[Music]
okay
nice yay
[Music]
oh wait that was the fourth round
that's a good one kind of really bad
that was pretty good yeah oh
crooney oh close to three
right
at the end you get points for voting i
guess correct
i think the first person who to guess
right gets like another point yeah yeah
around this game
i'm gonna press okay i like this one i
wouldn't mind playing again yeah
check out the other games we have like
uh 40 minutes adventure yeah the moon
adventure is 40 minutes oh
um startups
fake artists five minutes this one is
five minutes
[Music]
what how do you play this one everyone
draws on pictures together according to
the topic you'll take turns drawing one
stroke at a time oh one player is fake
oh
i want to try
okay oh that seems fine i think i just
figured out what the topic is
it reminds me there's like a jack box
game that's kind of like among us but
you have to do that yeah
yeah trivia murder party
that's a cute game
like in trivia murder party they have
like oh yeah yeah yeah that's true yeah
yeah i was thinking of the other one
that's uh it's like a sp and you're on a
spaceship and you have to try to guess
who the oh
push the button yeah yeah
[Music]
oh that one yeah yeah
they're both yeah though that's right
what's wrong it's pretty fun though the
fake artist yeah
okay quickie
[Music]
there is one fake artist
if it's something difficult then we will
easily figure out
which
yeah i feel like this is more of a
table top not not the handheld one oh
yeah true ah i have a pro controller
okay vegetables
that's right i have a touch screen oh
ten seconds reveal hey guys don't look
at the
screen
okay
don't look at the stream
and choose the color
work together
everyone has um
yeah
also everyone's drawing
oh everybody same time
yeah
the same
oh we're continuing it damn that was
fast
it's okay i don't either
i like when i let go it takes er i
follow oh it's one stroke without
lifting the pen yeah oh [\h__\h] i don't
know
i'm sorry
i'm trying to draw what the the what's
it the joycon it's hard
uh-huh
likely story
so much for being an artist
wait what the heck oh what
okay okay okay
that looks really cute yeah i think this
is already perfect
yeah
oh [\h__\h] yeah okay
[Laughter]
it's the shine it's the shine on them
okay
[Music]
i just wanted to do something wait it
wasn't me i just wanted to do something
fun
[Music]
is there only one round in this then
yeah i guess we can do it again
really
what that was what the [\h__\h] is this
what the [\h__\h] is this
oh where are they drawing
jordan
what what am i supposed to you will no
longer be able to see the finish okay
i'm supposed to guess what this is now
oh i already said what it was i didn't
hear it i didn't hear she didn't hear it
okay i first thought it was like a
pineapple but
then i didn't
think so anymore
but i guess it's something shiny because
you guys were talking about shiny
and there's a star
something shiny a vegetable fruit that's
shiny
it looks so weird like you guys are bad
artists
hey you're reading the show
no i'm not
no no no they don't they don't know
either they don't know either because we
didn't see what it was
but it looks like
something shiny or maybe an eggplant
the bottom look kind of round and big
and i guess the eggplant could be shiny
out of these choices i'll go for the egg
one
that's my answer
[Music]
oh let's go
no i swear i didn't hear it when nina
said it
nice and i carry beautiful artwork i
carried with this dress
yeah wait the top what the [\h__\h] is the
the the purple top
i was trying to draw the eggplant like i
thought cronie drew like the bottom half
so i was like i'll drop the top half of
the oh yeah there are eggplants that are
longer and then ones that are shorter
that's true i just thought you were
drawing like some sonic hedgehog looking
my sonic oc on screen
like forgivable because it was the first
time
that wait can
[Music]
oh i don't know how to do this it
doesn't work anymore
all right say no more
yay okay go go
okay handheld mode now no more no more
no more excuses
okay
um
oh
the more difficult the word is the
better for us i think because the fake
artist won't know
what yeah
okay
announcement okay
[Music]
oh
okay okay
[Music]
i see one of you guys this is the fake
artist
um
don't make it too easy though for the
fake artist this could be easy for too
good then it's too easy
[Music]
okay okay
yes yes
okay i think cronie is the fake artist
why
i haven't even done anything yet add
anything to this let's see what cronie
adds to this
well what am i supposed to add
like it's so like it's already done
i mean we can improve it okay we could
have
[Laughter]
even easier it's too easy stop it guys
we understand
[Music]
i think it's
kiara i'll really get anything yes you
didn't really add anything to be fair
that's a good point and they're going to
be added but two in a row
i think if i had too much it would be
too easy
believe me trust me
i have a reason
[Applause]
it looks
yeah like
knew what kind of hockey i mean i'm
sorry
you would know what what it looks like
you know
which house that looks like a hockey
with the net
ice hockey doesn't have a bar at the
bottom
yeah
oh really no
cause the puck has to go in you know i
didn't know that okay see that's that's
my defense i didn't know that
[Music]
wait who wins because she guessed it
right oh yeah because she has to get
something sorry i i gave you a little
bit yeah
but like i already
knew wow wow wow okay i want to play
around you guys weren't too good
oh sorry it was hard like it was such an
easy
easy yeah
go
this is actually such an easy game to
recreate in real life just with like a
pen and paper if you have something else
and like uh you just make little cards
or something and yeah everybody picks
one
[Music]
okey-dokey
um
this will be a little tricky
okay
[Laughter]
uh
i think it's almond
what
we didn't even start trying
[Music]
like there's just
okay
i don't even
[Music]
for sure
i can't do that i can't be one again
just
one line
i wanted to try to add two lines but i
couldn't you know
oh
okay
okay okay
okay i think it's crony now never mind
it's chiara sorry ahmed it's it's
kiara it's crazy
they're both playing it too safe
wait oh crony
judging by how fake i don't want it i
don't want it to be
[Music]
last time i was right remember that
last time i was right
hey
so that means that kiara can go twice
all right all right i mean
it's not quite
[Applause]
oh she's happy
just happy
no eyes though
yeah yeah
yeah yes
yeah i'm sorry kiara
what
crazy
oh you can't vote for yourself i guess
that's understandable
oh
what you could
i don't know come on that's a tie
[Music]
[Applause]
i should have known it's too easy to see
through it if you think strategically
and smartly
what do you think this is from yeah what
do you think it is krillin
yeah oh god
[Music]
yeah because of the crown yes there's a
lot of you know princesses and so on
yeah and it's like shiny stuff
but if it would have been for example
the beauty and the beast then we would
have drawn the beast as well i guess
but you yeah how i knew it was crony
because first i was guessing was amic
was the lack of her reaction towards the
topic but then she drew a snowflake-ish
kind of yeah so obviously yeah the
snowflake i was i was like did kara drop
the snowflake because i made you one
because you drew the star first i was
like hmm
the thing that i drew was like that
little green thing what did you think it
was a fairy
oh
something else oh
it could have been like peter pan or
something honestly i don't even know who
the snow queen is so i wouldn't know
what else to add that's why i added
another snowflake-ish attempt
like tina drew crap i was like okay
i'm gonna draw a face
[Music]
[Laughter]
i want to see if i can guess that it's
her if i can read her well enough like
if we get the same one can we just quit
the same one i don't think we'll get the
same one it looks different everyone no
no like
if if like one of us oh the same artist
again two times in a row yeah
okay you know i'm the fake artist
yeah
i i don't wanna be like three times in a
row man
can we cancel that's understandable
i don't know
i don't
oh if you press how do we how do we just
quit
look i think you have to go through
because there's like a leave but i think
it leaves like a huge frog
if crony can at least guess what it is
it's probably a butterfly
what the [\h__\h] do you know
wait is it actually yeah
it looked like wings so i was like oh
it's probably a butterfly
what wow
what what what does that mean
as one of us
would have been convincing you knew the
topic
exactly
what is this becoming though it doesn't
yeah what is this great is that that's
true that's the antenna yeah some of
them have really long ones but it looks
like another i don't know
how many how many ways this is
a pattern it's a pattern
okay okay
i think we're done what well i mean
this is turning into a monster
it's a monster what is that a little
butterfly oh okay
well i think i think it's uh it's still
me right
i think it's amazing
[Music]
sauce
yeah you were why did you vote for ina
uh
i just pressed a i wasn't paying
attention yeah
i'm sorry
it's okay confused but she got the
spirit
okay butterfly mosquito
this is definitely a mystery definitely
a bee
yeah
the wings i see
nothing real fast you know yeah one more
really beautiful
bee
[Music]
okay let's do this again once more okay
please please please please please
please not me please
please please please
oh
[Music]
okay this one's uh yep
okay
let's get this started
[Music]
what
what's obvious
did you see it
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh and now we know for sure okay
okay
what the [\h__\h] is this don't tell me
it's hard because i had to start out i
couldn't even go by yeah i was like wait
what
oh man
[Laughter]
when you were like oh it's definitely
ena i was like
so funny i'm like thank god you [\h__\h]
up right away
you were too eager to blame it on here
now what was it chiara what was it what
could it be it depends on what i am
going to be offered let's see we have
something that looks like a watermelon
well the [\h__\h] the [\h__\h] that i drew
should be ignored anyway
yeah it looks like a person with big
ears
what is that
eight
seven six
five
four
three
two
one
what could it be i already forgot what i
was looking at uh like a watermelon
no
what has that shape
wait
it had handles you added like something
like a handle physics
[Music]
yeah like person with big ears oh see
then the circle that i drew was probably
the face of a person
yeah and we were building on it because
yeah yeah yeah
what is that watermelon
one yeah it was a mouth right on me
oh it was a mask you know like the mask
shape yeah yeah i need your mouth your
teeth in it oh i think you're trying to
hide that it's a mask shape
i want to go again
sorry i'm really liking this game now
i want to expose you guys
being fakers
[Music]
make it till you make it
i still got 20 minutes
[Music]
i'm on so
okay if kiara or
no
we might just go with the flow it's
funny
just go with it
don't look at my stream
all right i'm just gonna we're not yeah
we're gonna minimize
sea animals
okay we're gonna draw gouda
yara
yara what
we're gonna draw
[Laughter]
now i know what to draw thanks
[Music]
i think yeah did you give away her salad
for not actually knowing
i can't tell
i think so
i was just making a joke as good as a
sea animal
oh okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
no i wanted to end that it went out of
the frame no no
no i'm not gonna
what are you guys drawing
what are you drawing
[Laughter]
it's good
[Music]
i don't even know what's happening
i don't know
it's already so beautiful
[Laughter]
i'm gonna die
what the [\h__\h] is that
what did you draw there the hat is that
supposed to be a hat
honestly try a bit harder
what do you mean what are you guys doing
curly understood my my uh my intention
for this
yeah yeah
what
i understood too whatever
you were destroying whatever weren't you
you weren't even trying to make it look
like something
because you all know the answer
i don't even get a chance on winning the
guests
[Laughter]
it's not even not even close to
resembling what it's supposed to be huh
no it looks exactly oh okay oh really
yeah i know it's on my in my eyes and
you're lying with me so blatantly what
do you see chiara you got
it's so accurate but since i added like
an eye i
i felt like it looked like um like a i
don't know i can't even explain it
because you guys probably don't know
what i don't know what it is but okay
you guys were [\h__\h] with me weren't
you
it isn't anything you little [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
it looks so
on point
[Laughter]
oh because when i was saying oh let's
draw gouda that would have been so
cute
if i was not the fake artist i wouldn't
say that because i would give it away
right
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
what do you mean this is kuda oh
yeah like
what part of that was supposed to be
gouda none of you none of you even tried
no
it's a different shark
you know from the front you see the
front of the mouth
and he has a little fin at the top yeah
okay i had no idea yeah i'm glad that
what i was doing worked with whatever
you guys are doing just because there's
no idea what you were drawing
what
what is
crony what is the
dark blue line on the left side explain
yourself oh i was trying to draw the the
no i was trying to draw the thing and
then it cut me off
once i went out of the frame what a
coincidence same thing happened to me
i thought it was the water
it was the oh it could have been the
water yeah
i honestly thought i was a fake artist
or something without knowing because i
thought you guys were drawing like a
landscape i had no idea
like for like
[Laughter]
that's true yeah okay okay i want to
play one more i want the element to be
the one
man i
uh that was incredible yeah i i thought
omni drew the cloud
it's a fish you know it's a fish the
shark's chasing a fish you know
oh really i thought it was like a cloud
like you know it was a cloud but now
we'll just say the fish
i thought it was the water and i was
like man landscape
it's going to do random what not okay
not that category that's too easy
oh what
oh
okay
[Music]
interesting
i think
i think i know how to draw this
[Music]
go crony
do you know what that is
yeah i do
what kind of sound does it make
okay
okay you know what you're doing
i'm not gonna question you
yeah yeah it looks good
oh it's amit
that hurts me
okay i mean
i think it's on there but then still
then
we're making it too easy
what do you mean i'm drawing it just
like you guys
yeah because you don't know what else to
draw so you come you call it no i know
what it is because i'm not the fake
artist
[Music]
yeah we all know what it is
but there's only one fake artist the
mughals
kiara's blaming everyone again it's
probably her
[\h__\h]
could be oh go ahead and don't trust me
whatever
[Music]
you said last time
you have to pay attention to my
reactions my reactions were very genuine
this time
they're not so genuine when i'm the fake
artist
it's easy to pretend
oh
[Laughter]
oh no but i think she knows what it is
[Music]
as soon as uh crony or somebody drew the
second line started drawing the second
line i knew what it was yeah instruments
is so easy i told ya
oh i was trying to make it like
less easy by just drawing a line does
she know the name of it though
yeah
i used to have one okay oh no
[Music]
no she knows
okay
you know what
um there's 10 minutes until my next
section
but so we're gonna do one more round of
this
okay last round last round i have a
problem
oh man it's my favorite game now
choose something difficult okay
uh okay okay what would be difficult
occupation's just kind of like yeah okay
let's do that
let's see all right
[Music]
interesting
okay let's ragu
[Music]
yes okay okay yeah yeah okay okay
this music reminds me of a wind waker um
when
[Music]
not looking at it i'm looking at kind of
from the bird's perspective maybe bird's
perspective
she sounds like a faker now this is a
little too abstract
i need another turn just you draw
somewhere else i'll i'll i'll i'll need
another turret maybe it looks like a
slanted bird's view um
like first view is like top down right
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
this looks more 3d
we can work with that i don't know what
you're going for here i don't know
either anymore okay okay okay at least
like we're finding a direction
okay are we done
yeah
[Music]
what the heck is what is
it is difficult very difficult
i know i know i know something that
would give it away immediately though
but that would make it so much easier
okay give me a chance come on don't
don't cut off this is
no
what the heck
[Music]
oh
is this still a bird's-eye view
i don't i don't think it's a bird's-eye
view
[Music]
yeah it looks like an arm yeah what
happened to the green thing though what
was that supposed to be i don't know
what that is so i just i don't know
what
i have to contribute
really
what
a smile you think this person is happy
[Music]
or maybe they like maybe they like their
occupation
oh wait i wanna
i want to i'll tell you later what i
wanted to add
you know
what you know why not no not me
i mean curly actually also didn't
contribute much if you think about it i
don't know
yo i
like what am i supposed to activate i
need to do a bird's-eye view of this i
don't know who to vote for originally
i gave up on the bird's eye i wanted the
light
blue thank you i wanted it to be a table
originally
okay you guys are wrong
and the green part that i drew was
supposed to be an arm holding a suitcase
through a person knewing that he would
be a person but that don't say yes she
doesn't know what it is she doesn't know
at all
okay good thing we made it abstract yeah
okay this person is not happy what's not
happening okay i missed it with a
suitcase
but no
there's a smiley face
are
people ever happy
are we wait wasn't that a smiling face
or yeah it was a smiley face okay who is
not happy here um i'm not happy
nobody is and nobody
[Music]
if you work you lose
let's all become neato forever
just kidding i'm happy i love you guys
can you be maybe doctor
[Music]
yeah and they're raising their hand to
say objection
yes i don't know why they're raising
their head
objection sign on the right side
that would have given a lie
oh
i was trying to make it hold the
suitcase with the green part nice i love
you like somebody going to work
yeah yeah yeah good job good job but
attempt yeah needed a few more strokes
though and we would have maybe had
more chances at making it look like what
it actually is
amazing oh good round good round that
only took five minutes
all right we can't understand
thank you
what are you trying to imply yeah
[Music]
thank you for entertaining me this is
really fun
[Music]
i think occupations again is actually
too difficult
it was hard like it's like there were
enough artists people usually say like
lawyers you know okay i was surprised
that was a lawyer
[Music]
do you see everybody
i see you see
i mean do you see yeah
what yeah
well how do you draw this dough well
well i mean okay
i think
i have an idea
[Music]
what is that
i just i started drawing with my
controller instead of on the screen by
accident
you'll see on the next turn i'm so
confused
oh it's my turn oh [\h__\h] uh what is that
supposed to be where am i supposed to
continue
just try to make it into something
that'll work you know
oh god um
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know what it is
i i see it don't see it i don't see it
open your [\h__\h]
i'm really
i'm trying really hard
[Music]
just can you you know
you know
come on
out and
add the head
just a different i already see one yeah
yeah yeah
ah
so at least now it's a person
now we can all um try to go from there
yeah okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is that
[Music]
careful
don't go out of the frame don't go out
of the frame no [\h__\h] oh went out of the
frame what
if you if you know then you who said
what just now who said what
no i'm just trying to it's ina
no i think it's crony yeah i i think oh
oh okay okay what's up
i feel like
defend yourself defend yourself you know
yeah morning barely added anything what
was that last line you pulled it was one
yeah
a hat why why would they wear a hat
what do you mean they don't wear a hat i
mean anyone can wear a hat i'm just
wearing them why would why would this
[\h__\h] i really don't notice
it could be crony too but she's acting
pretty well if it's her then she's a
good actor right now
who is a good
so actor
pretty honest
don't tell her
all right time to guess what is it what
can you see you know
yeah
holding like
i don't know like a
plant or something
damn did we make it too easy
yeah
there's only one person here that holds
plan
it holds a what planned
yeah
interesting interpretation
like isn't that a quill that they're
holding or something anything anything's
fine anything why are they kneeling on
the floor and drinking
on the floor
i thought they were like doing the dog
and i was really confused for a second
like are we thinking about the same
topic
and then i started seeing it
yeah
i drew tears because um well those were
tears
happy
that's true they're really [\h__\h]
excited it's like ears because they're
like facing downwards
oh can i ask what um amma and cronie
intended with the first line each
i was trying to do the tip of a pencil
with the first line but i was doing
a half yeah
oh
they're kneeling
yes not well i just was trying to
interpret whatever
and i could have put a chair in there
like sitting in a chair so i decided to
make them kneeling instead i thought it
was like a gardener or something like
they're like planting the
the plant in the middle
yeah when you said it i was like yeah
that looks like it and that makes sense
why they would wear hats because they're
outside in the sun and so on yeah
you guys got me that was so much fun oh
thank you i had so many laughs out of
that
amazing sounds great i was trying to
draw a table
[Music]
oh yeah next time next time
yeah okay i have like um one more hour
of streaming so i will say goodbye to
you guys but i wanna take a picture so
we'll go into intermission for one
minute and then we'll go into the last
hour of my 12 hour marathon thank you
girls for being part of me
and also happy annivers two year
anniversary also to inna and ahmed of
course yeah
happy anniversary
let's see i'll see i'm in inna in our
collaboration which will by the way be
on amis channel so you guys keep an eye
out it's gonna be very special again
yeah yeah yeah yes
and cronie i'll see you maybe i know
somewhere in rest hopefully
yeah
yes yes if you need help
i wouldn't mind teaching i already
taught like dana because
but if you have someone already don't
worry about but if we're just online at
the same time don't you can you can
always ask me for help if we're online
at the same time just saying
just me too me too
[Music]
amy got cars if you need a car you need
a ride yeah you want to rent one
oh it's called scraps the price of your
life
oh that's a little hard
dang
i all have to consider she probably also
will take some preps yeah yeah anyway
thank you girls hope you had as much fun
as i did elise
yeah
it was fine
i'll have some breakfast and uh go go
back to sleep uh or whatever you want to
do i mean you should sleep i feel like
you haven't slept in a while yeah
i'm gonna stream i gotta stream like oh
okay oh no we'll have fun
but still stay in the room for a moment
i'll i'll be going to intermission see
you guys see you chat in a minute okay
bye
[Music]
me
away
[Music]
me
my
[Music]
oh
let's change clothes don't look
[Music]
sloth left so i guess i'm gonna go for
the camera
yeah i know i know you're supposed to
hear me i'm talking to you guys
[Music]
i actually have three more outfits
because you count the 3d
then i would have one more oh well don't
worry about it how did you get food i
decided to just um
i
decided um
[Music]
here on stage because i'm gonna sing a
little bit and
you guys are lucky my throat is still
doing okay but
i'll take a little fruit candy break
i won't talk much but i maybe i'll i'll
look for some songs okay
give me like um how about like five
minutes of science i you know i can
never like stay silent because
i feel like if i stay silent for five
minutes like as a as a viewer they will
be like oh this [\h__\h] is boring i'm out
of here
oh god
huh
why was he not talking to what do you
mean i didn't hear her huh
laughing so it was so [\h__\h] funny what
the [\h__\h]
that the first game was kind of like
a lame starter to start out with
the first one is like yeah nothing going
on you know just
but after that it was getting better and
better
not good at drawing i legit how i was i
just i really just said it because of c
uh sea animals what was the word see
see
see things
yeah that was such a coincidence
and
like in theory that would mean that i
knew what i was drawing but the fact
that i would give it away like that
was would be reckless if i was the
actual artist
[Laughter]
oh man that's so funny
it's so funny
oh man
so good i'm like fascinated
oh god okay let me do one thing here
quickly
give me give me
one minute
i don't even know what you're saying
i'll probably sing for like half an hour
because i have a lot of things to talk
about in the end and
that will probably take
another time honestly it doesn't feel
like 12 hours to me at all
starter son
oh we can sing that have i ever sang it
outside of dukel me
no i didn't make a setlist i didn't have
time i'm so sorry
um
never outside of google me really
but it felt so quick it's because like
pla
doing like different games in different
sections
goes by way faster than playing the same
game for 12 hours
song is a banger so it would be great oh
we can sing that yeah but maybe like a
warm-up song first like an easier one
um
i'm gonna look into my list
it would probably be a repeater
that's how twitch students go okay that
makes sense yeah because i do change
like the game they play a lot yeah yeah
yeah that makes a lot of sense
um
you can i borderline
uh i don't want to sing that right now
it's tough on my voice
i love it
oops
[Music]
um
ideally i wouldn't want to sing
something i haven't sang before but i
sang
ah
sometimes i don't even know what i
haven't said it's been two years like
hmm
it's hard to judge
how do i know what i didn't sing before
i know
my originals too perhaps
but at least one one non-origin like
from like my
not none whole life
oh this is gonna be our craft so it has
to be like a japanese song
should i just
throw a random hello project song at you
you're not gonna know it though
have i signed a bus guide song before
the bus guide song i wonder
let me try to find kiara
it's probably not stationed
unless the clip was deleted
then i probably didn't okay
okay i'll start with this one
i just don't know what to sing so i'm
just gonna go with this one
we do have a list of every song you said
really
it's a badass kobo song
station
bus guide
is
[Laughter]
wait a second
i got some some last-minute stuff for
some an announcement
oh yeah
last
okay
yes
okay okay okay i will sing now
even i still have a fruit candy in my
mouth
thank you
let's write
here oh no surprise in two songs i mean
there will be
some announcements but we start with uh
one
station bus guide
from betty's global daddy mushroom
yeah i can i can sing
even if the candy i will like put it on
the side of my cheek and then
uh
oh hi smoothie i'm almost done
a little bit longer hold on hold on
i'm almost done kitty cat
singing time
[Music]
i
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
um
i
[Music]
is
i swear i haven't heard or sang that
song in like 10 years or so
i don't even remember if i sang that
last high tone correctly if that was
really intended but i just felt like
singing it that way
hell yeah
i'm glad you like that song i told you
before that this is my favorite idol
group and it has like a lot of dorky
songs
like this was actually
um another
uh ending ending song for inazuma 11
that they did
so maybe some of you guys heard it there
before
hmm
it's it but
does inazuma 11 have bus guides why do
they sing about bus guides
i always thought they looked so cute in
their bus guide outfits though so cute
yes based baby scuba enjoyer if you want
to then you're based as well
sing more songs from them in the future
there's not that many
instrumentals and like permissions in
the list for them but
i think i definitely sang
the wonder bento song before
[Music]
and a lot of you guys knew that song
thankfully from uh
yeah yeah
oh i want to sing this one the classic
that's a classic
i'll sing
a singapono song bono is also from hello
project and consists of two members from
brady's global and one member from a
cute
an idol group called cute and bono was
really popular and really famous and
because they were just a perfect the
perfect combination of members that just
harmonized so perfectly well
that they were like partially even more
popular than their original groups i
would almost almost say
considering that it was only like
three members two from one group and one
from the other one it's it's absolutely
amazing bono bono the group they brought
in
so many new fans because they actually
became relatively mainstream in in japan
at the time
here comes the the hello project lore
they brought in a lot of mainstream fans
um
so that's that was really cool
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah cause like
babies this is cold and cute as much as
you i would as a fan also wanted them to
become more and more famous and bigger
especially bayless cobait wasn't quite
able to do that because they had just
these dorky songs
that's why i
even though i find them funny i feel
like i should have gone for a little bit
more
mainstream acceptable songs
but oh well that was idols back then
a lot of them a lot of them went for
doki themes man
i love talking about items
um so we're gonna sing how do i still
have energy what the [\h__\h] hatsukoi cider
which is a [\h__\h] classic that
everybody knows because bono made it
famous because they're absolute
divas genius divas
all right let's go
[Music]
my
is
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
me
i really mess we want to chant
[Music]
is
money
[Music]
oh man i love it so much
oh that
feels so good
i just love this one so much
lots of memories
of that one such a banger
such a freaking banger
thank you guys actually we're already so
close to the
half an hour mark
i don't want to sing at least one more
song
maybe
[Music]
oh so many choices maybe maybe kiwa song
should i sing a kiwa song because it's
my anniversary you know
okay
let's sing favorite night yeah fifa
nights
people that need to be more appreciated
please listen to vivina
and stream fever night
uh where is my
here
night there we go
lyrics
so let's sing
[Music]
hey
i'm tired of the same
[Music]
do you feel the music
new i don't need no drinks tonight give
me that please
[Music]
oh
hey
i'm dancing alone
so robotic so emotionless
but then i see you
across the
dance floor so now honey
follow me
[Music]
don't look away now it's just the two of
us
[Music]
give me that
don't care who's watching us so baby
[Music]
i don't need no drinks tonight
until the day
[Music]
a lot
hell yeah
that was
very nice
i think i can fit in one more song
[Music]
one more
one more should be fine
[Music]
what do you want to hear
you know what we haven't sung heart
challenge in a while i feel like
we should sing heart challenge sorry i
asked you i decided already
spark is like my two ghost song but yeah
and then and then and then maybe some
announcements oh
[Music]
let's see there
heart container or love conqueror or
whatever it is
[Music]
oh wait that wasn't a blue
blue
[Music]
how could you forget guys the title of
the song is
hijab
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
wow
[Music]
oh
me
[Music]
m
is
[Music]
me
[Applause]
i need to tell you that i love you
through and through
[Music]
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
love you can't be follow me until the
verdict
[Music]
foreign
wow yeah
[Applause]
i have more energy now than i had like a
few hours ago perhaps
um i'll be honest i was a little bit
sad that so many things went wrong
actually like
behind the scenes like
i i was able to overcome it by playing
for the obs screen but my game capture
card didn't show um the game in the
program
even though it showed it before the
stream
but honestly that program
i'm not the only one like who has
problems with it every now and then it's
just like [\h__\h] you i don't wanna i don't
wanna cooperate with you today
no uh no i don't wanna
yeah that program just sucks
but crony recommended me like a
different program actually i'm gonna try
that one out hmm
yeah
oh thank you so much guys for a sweet
applause i can almost hear it
coconuts
we're going to move to my
office
or should we go to my ballroom
no no actually ah
now we're going to stay here
because i put one thing that i want to
show you on on this
on this um
like scene already it's already here
so i guess we're staying here
but i could change my clothes
at
since we're entering some kind of like
different
well
oh god all the all the water
different different kind of
whatever
yeah i'm gonna uh i guess wear the chemo
because i haven't worn the kimono yet
today
last outfit
[Music]
yeah why not
ideally i should have won this one first
i guess oh well
is the news yeah
no
good news only
[Music]
nadimas
i have many things to talk about
um
yeah
but first of all
you know anniversary so
i like to get a little bit um what's the
word sappy
but i don't have much time left so oh
sheesh
okay
i wanted to say
i don't have much time left so this is
gonna be a little bit
fast but yeah um
in these
two years wait
i have a music for this
i'll prepare the music for this
here there it is
sounds so sad
um
yeah it is these two years
i've made
many many many memories maybe because i
have a brain a lot of them are really
hard to remember
or too much to remember
as i told you guys my memory card
there's not enough space i need to
upgrade it but it's impossible somehow
it doesn't work
but um
i think the reason why
they are hard to remember is because
every
stream even if it's a normal supposedly
normal stream
every collab every day
every day i interact with you guys
it's just so vibrant and vivid
for me
i don't know how it is for you guys but
for me every
stream
i try my best
and every stream is special for me even
if it may not feel like that on the
outside
it's special for me and i hope it's
special for you guys too
and i wish i could
remember everything clearly
and i really suffered from memory loss
i wish i could remember everything
clearly because
i feel like many many years later i'll
feel really sad about not remembering
properly
something so precious something that
changed my life so much for the better
but
at least i can watch the votes
that's the good thing at least i haven't
recorded other things that you forget
you can't recall that easily that's why
forgetting is so scary
and i hope you guys
will not forget me and will
look back on those memories
for many years to come even though i may
only be in a small existence in your
life
all of you guys are a big existence in
my life
and then we're
definitely in these two years
so many
challenges and problems and
i almost
like recently i i bumped against one
it might have been like the most
[Music]
the most terrible and lost i have felt
in
those two years
[Music]
oh wow the music is not helping
um
[Music]
very recently i felt um
like this it can't get any worse than
this probably
okay stop bgm yeah go go be happy again
um but i endure and i do it because
i have a dream
and this stubborn very stubborn mindset
and i have goals and desires
and i've told you guys many times and
some are accomplished and some are
definitely not
yeah
you guys probably know i've been
unsuccessful
for a long time in my life
um i tried so hard to be successful i
didn't want to be a failure
and thanks to whole life
i
got a little bit of that taste
that sweet taste of what it feels like
to be successful
thank you so much for making that
possible
but because i was like
so unsex unsuccessful for so long in my
life even though i was trying so hard i
did start asking myself why am i doing
this
why why do i keep on doing this for
years and years there's
no way to go
it doesn't seem to get any better
but now i have the answer
now i have an
why am i doing this
it's for you
yeah
so for the coming year
i want to of course this is just a
standard thing
as i do it every year i want to continue
improving myself and finally grasp those
big dreams
like a concert and an album even though
it's going to take a lot of work and
it's going to keep on getting delayed so
have patience
i hope more people will give me a chance
and watch me
join kfp
give me a chance even if before you [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] sucks
cause i'm trying really hard you know
i'm i'm really trying and i
i believe in whole life
and i
i want this
to be
my biggest accomplishment in life
so i'll continue working hard
and i want us to grow together make
memories together achieve more and i
want you guys to be proud of me
and speaking of proud thanks to you i
can finally feel
that i'm proud of what i'm doing and
live comfortably and help my family
members out so i'm really blessed and
grateful
i thank you guys for that
i want to give back to you guys
as much as you've been giving to me
so here's a few announcements
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's what that was my speech i like my
speech
i almost cried
okay where do we start where do i start
number one
uh
the long-awaited uh hotel comeback
oopsie
um
it's supposed to be next week sunday uh
but it might have to be late again
because they're
the current member i have
lined up
we're still like discussing some things
unsure about so it might need another
delay i'm sorry about that but also the
studio um
still needs a little bit of finishing
polish polish but it's coming back and
hopefully within this month definitely i
promise
okay that's one thing
um
oh okay uh this is uh
one thing i think i'm gonna say now
how much time do i have like
maybe 10 minutes at most
whiplash
sorry
[Music]
so this is for all the members
i want to let you guys know i have
decided
on
on a
third year and fourth year icon that we
are hopefully going to reach
so we're reviewing
third year
it's going to be
you know how your buckets now i will
give you feedings down and you'll become
a chicken once again you would think but
now you're going to be a hybrid
of kotoni and
chicken
fire chicken
yes
this is for a year and then
by the way this is by dakoma thank you
so much for helping me out on short
notice
[Music]
after that if we ever reach fourth year
hopefully i want to reach this because
you will reach your ultimate form
supposedly
you'll become
rgb chicken
super special rgb chicken
these two
no membership icon tonight
[Music]
yeah
they will look
gorgeous on you guys on the novel
day one members
you're gonna get them the soonest
okay
next announcement
um
i don't have like a graphic or anything
for this because it's still
way
before being able to make a graphic out
of it um but
um
i requested
a long time ago uh
for the two year anniversary to receive
a new hairstyle with some accessories
and it's it works more or less
but it takes ages so you probably won't
see it until i don't know probably 20 23
spring
anonymity
[Music]
yeah it will be not for the main outfit
for the default outfit
i i'm not allowed to add anything it
will be for a different one you will see
yeah
and then
another thing
another thing that has been
awaited for a long time
tomorrow
and
let me go um time zone converter
really quickly
tomorrow
okay tomorrow 8 00 pm
uh cest so my time but uh 2 p.m est
or 3 am jst
finally
german demon on my german channel
[Music]
that's finally coming i was waiting for
um some things and it's happening
tomorrow i know a lot of you guys don't
speak german but you're welcome to come
anyway yay
see more chihuahua the moyumeria if
anyone can speak german
or you know someone who speaks german
who is not into youtubers yet or for
reason to be jewish let them know let me
know
okay tomorrow wait i should you know
what i'll leave but i'll leave it on the
screen
that's tomorrow
tomorrow
[Music]
morgan morgan um
of my channel
um
this is
kind of still in the works um
i was pla i had this in the works for a
long time and i didn't know like when to
reveal it
i was like unsure i couldn't make up my
mind but i think like very soon probably
within this month we are going to
do something with this
[Laughter]
yeah i was thinking of doing a frog week
so actually a long time ago i requested
a [\h__\h] ton of rock games rock related
games only like two or three of them
came back to me with a permission so
i know
maybe it will only be half of rock week
but anyway it will happen um
it's modeled by prachu um after the
mabaloni
uh frog yara that's why i said so
suspiciously in the beginning of the
stream when someone joked to me oh you
may have a frog in your front and i'm
like yeah maybe why why do i have a
frogiada in my throat remember
okay
so now we barely have time so let me go
to it quick quickly
the biggest announcement of them
[Music]
finally [\h__\h] finally i swear to god
uh
i hope this won't be double double audio
let's just hope it won't and otherwise
we'll play it again
last announcement
three
two
one
let's go
oh god
[Music]
hey let me do that again i had some [\h__\h]
on the screen one more
let's go
[Music]
and on the 18th it's a sunday in one
week a new song with my first ever
3d music video
song title is do you
producer is
did you hear it did you have notice
again producer from spock
[Music]
subscribers
you see members
last night the poll and i was like do
you
want to be golden or rainbow
do you was capitalized for some reason
[Music]
yeah a little hint um but yeah um
a new song i've been working on this one
for ages it was supposed to come out
i already had the song it was supposed
to come out like around my birthday but
it took a lot longer due to
circumstances you know delays happen so
here it is finally i'm so excited i
really love this song um remember the
first time i listened to it and let let
reid listen to it was in the maldives
that's that was like march or something
yeah
so i look forward to it i'm gonna upload
the teaser on my channel and tomorrow
i'll see you on my german channel and
then a few hours after my debut on the
german channel i will be on amma's
channel for a special stream uh
anniversary collab
and with that i say
uh i love you and in germany we say
[Music]
thank you guys so much obviously for 12
amazing hours we did it
good night love you
please be nice to me youtube please
don't cut the haircut it should be fun
should be fine
and theory should be fine
[Music]
i'm just scared just you know
we want to be safe
bye-bye
[Music]