[Music]
every
move
[Music]
feel
to keep up all
[Music]
Al my
my
[Music]
C
just
do you feel
[Music]
but I see you acoss
k
k oh this is so weird I don't like the
Acoustics here K
Ki ah ah hello hello hello hello can you
hear me yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah but I want to be
equalized why is there no equalizer on
this wait is this is
this no that's not it either I don't
really know how to use this
thing really but it's okay K Kitty I'm
just going to stay as close as possible
to the microphone podcast mode it's my
birthday I'm H I'm a bit quiet um I'm
going to probably stay around this uh
volume though because I tried I mean
I'll probably have to readjust
everything again but I tried adjusting
myself to all the Kad videos that I've
been sent um is this really like too
quiet like if you put your phone or your
PC or whatever on Max DVR is on oh oops
[\h__\h] did I did
I ah the latency is okay ah DVR can
still turn off okay never mind then
latency uh no DVR is off H so uh if you
uh guys put your volumes to the max am I
still too quiet for you or are you
good it's muffled as [\h__\h] muffled well
that's just
how the Acoustics here are yeah I don't
like it's that much either but it is
what it
is sounds fine
okay oh okay it's fine not muffled okay
thank you for saying that I I do think
it's a little bit muffled or not not
muffled but like it's because there's no
like um I think you call it equalizer
like there's no the mixer here I don't
know if there's a way to maybe there is
but I don't know if there's a way to
like balance
the the quieter sounds and the louder
sounds to be all the same I would prefer
that just not the same as your home mic
exactly it's actually um also it's also
a Shore but a different Shore smaller
Shore not the one that old all the
famous people have a compressor that's
the one yeah is there a comp there's a
there's a button that says comp EQ but I
press it and I don't what if I press
both of
them what I'm speaking quietly am I um
no I don't I don't think I don't think
that I don't I don't think that did
anything I don't oh did it or maybe it
did did it did it do something did it do
something did it do something wa maybe
that did a little bit did that do a
little
bit what what is this by the waybe this
wait I think
this am I like wait compare this whisper
whispery voice to uh this whisper I
think I think yeah that might have that
might have done that might that might
have done something I think maybe that
do something I don't know I'll keep this
on I don't know what that you can't tell
I can't tell
either why is the chat slightly angled
because I can't really like when it's
just straight it also doesn't look right
it doesn't look right when it's just
straight and it doesn't look right when
it's like slightly angled because like
the angle of the screen is like not just
angled in One Direction you know it has
like uh what do you call it you know
dimensional angles I don't know but at
least I finally figured out how to mask
it so that you won't like that that so
that you stay like within there yeah um
yeah oh yeah I think I think I think I
think uh n to maybe to a small extent I
fixed that
thing but yeah uh sorry for
um being kind of all over the place uh
so
far if you can tilt the chat so it has I
tilted it it's
tilted you it's tilted but it needs to
be like like the the top part needs to
be tilted up like up and the bottom part
needs to be tilted down for it to be
realistic yeah and it's my birthday it's
my birthday we're going to party like
it's my birthday what is the song we're
going to party like it's my
birthday uh
uhhuh don't get tilted about not being
tilted enough yeah don't get don't get
tilted is that 50 c
[Music]
oh so I'm still in Japan I'm still in
the studio I can't get out I'm stuck
here for uh 72 hours now I haven't
gotten anything to eat or drink I
haven't seen a person or light there's
no windows haven't seen light or sun or
Darkness anything in the past 72 hours I
think I'm
dying I might evaporate soon uh this is
my own personal usual
room I'm in the Mr Beast video is he
[\h__\h] serious about wanting to go for
president
mamaia celebrities are okay what no no
politics no Politics on my birthday
stream still any ice cream left yeah I
still have ice cream left that that's
like way too much it's way too much ice
cream to just be eaten by one person
Jemma if you're listening to this feel
free to she's not in the same room this
time she's in a different room Jemma if
you're hearing this feel free to eat
some of the ice
cream yeah
ra oh and Elizabeth Rose blood flame uh
Channel whole lifean moderator also here
yay my co eyes it's so nice to have co
co eyes like new Co High because they
are they're so so attentive to
me
hey popular sampai I wouldn't say I'm
popular it's just my birthday like let's
see how how popular I am once my
birthday is
over H yeah so today as you can tell by
the stream title is a Kad with guests uh
pre-recorded guests they sent me like uh
them their recordings of them
singing um songs I gave them like a list
of songs uh that they could sing that I
could probably also sing and then they
chose a song and Elizabeth Rose blood
flame herb knows a song that got me so
hyped the the fact that she knows the
song just saying that right now cuz
she's in the chat doesn't mean she's
coming up right away but maybe maybe she
will I don't know I'm going random order
probably I don't know what order I don't
really have an order I think I'm going
to go by feeling but yeah they chose a
song and then they recorded it and oh
first I did like lyric splits for
everybody which was a lot it was a lot
what do you mean you're I'm talking too
much shut up this is my birthday stream
I'm I'm I'm this is my day I can talk
however much I want people know this is
Thea yeah I gotta Yap I haven't had much
like opportunities to Yap to you guys
towards you guys recently
so let me Yap let yap yap yap yap yap
what was I saying yeah then I did lyric
splits which took quite a
while and then everybody not everybody I
think some there are maybe like two or
three people who ran out of time uh but
that's okay I still have a lot a lot let
me see let me count one two three 1 two
three four five six 7 8 nine 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 17 18
participants
oh plus me that's
19 thank you thank you to all of my
beloved kohai and uh I guess I would
also say sam there's there's a few senis
in there from
ID yeah and and gen mates I guess a few
genm mates maybe yeah so we're GNA we're
going to sing sing sing sing that means
that's going to be 18 songs can you do
the math guys 18 participants means 18
songs yeah awesome no no JP no I I I
figured I I'll just keep it and the ID
to keep it less complicated and all that
cuz I don't think have Japanese members
even done this kind of style of K stream
before like it might be hard to explain
and all
[Music]
that I got warm green tea with me my oi
is so smart what what why what makes you
say that thank you yeah I think they may
have contributed before but they haven't
done it themselves before
[Music]
maybe COI and you were ah yes yeah she
hosted her
own that's true okay and this stream is
archived we have only archived songs but
I think there's actually a few songs
that I haven't sung before in
koku uh and one or two that I may still
be struggling with so have mercy on me
and I was like setting up all the videos
like putting color filters and
everything like the green screen stuff
on every single videos uh one by one and
trying to adjust the audio and that then
then for like I was I was doing that for
over an hour I think and then and then
10 minutes before the stream starts I
realized
something and changed things up again
now I have to probably readjust every
time I play the video so that's okay
that's okay happy birthday thank you so
this year actually my birthday was
yesterday I
I I was confused when I was planning my
birthday streams I was confused I
admitted and I planned both of my
birthday streams for
Sunday uh this one I couldn't move
anymore because this one is is the merch
one um but the other one I was able to
move to be yesterday at
least my actual
birthday
yeah I was wondering why it was today
well at least the countdown was
yesterday at least that was
yesterday uh one note uh in 45 minutes
like 1 hour into the stream as per usual
I'll be showing you guys the the
birthday
merchandise but I want
everybody to be aware number one there
is time limited time limited uh no not
time limited you know there's limited uh
uh you know the the the signed ones the
real sign versus the not real sign that
exists again um there is an insanely low
quantity for it on geek
Jack so if you were looking forward to
using geek Jack I should warn
you the digits are not even three digits
it's two digits so if I if you want to
yeah if you're UB bro for real you're
going to get it cheaper even and higher
chances to get one if you just use
tensel or something like that uh so get
it ready now if you haven't done that
before go to tensel T NS
o and set up an account it's basically
how that works let me really quickly
explain for people who don't know this
kind of stuff um basically you well I
should I should play some bgm while
we're
talking you hear this right or or Zen
Market yeah Zen Market is also one of
them denmarket apparently is easier I
don't know I haven't used it before but
people are saying yeah uh
denmarket uh is easier apparently but
tenso is also easy to use tenso needs
IRL verification okay maybe maybe
Denmark it
doesn't I'm sorry guys it's not my fault
I told last last year last year uh I
told staff son a geek Jack geek jacket
geek Jack with so little uh quantity
let's do more next time and it has
actually become less I don't know why um
but if you want a limited thing and
you're in Europe
uh you might want to look into that if
you already have an account definitely
recommend using that you have to wait
for them to order for you though oh my
God H by by works too for the official
shop if you already have an accounter oh
is all of that like w hi
Ollie o I didn't announce the merch yet
no not yet I'm just warning everybody
who's from Europe who wants limited
sets that on gek ja there's an insanely
low quantity I am
sorry tenso is great once you have it
set up yeah I think some some of my
European fans have
uh uh set it up before right some of you
guys have have used it before please use
it again come
San it's my fourth
birthday h
sorry yeah uh if you are able to buy
from the official shop instead of geek
Jack do it do it do it do it do it so
that the geek Jack people who have to
use gjack have at least more more
chances yeah bu has to purchase for you
10 so you can buy yourself and use their
address that they give you yeah but
apparently you have to be uh uh your
your account has to be verified so it
can't be done immediately I guess
[Music]
sorry
yeah I know I know it sucks I said that
to Jemma like what are European fans
supposed to
do you gave me a [\h__\h] heart attack
happy
[Music]
birthday
surprise
hello Vis is uh behind
me hi
I'm
yeah I could I couldn't send you a song
cuz of my voice but I decided to give
you a special iners thank you did you
get the did you get my gift I did thank
you I haven't opened it oh oh you don't
know what it
is I think I know I think you know okay
I know but yeah she got you got to you
got to come closer oh hello that's B
it's B oh BG BG I'm loud okay hi
everyone she surprised me surprise happy
birthday yeah I wanted to I wanted to
appear in person you know to make up for
the couldn't s thing so hi but bio I was
so surprised just now but I actually
gave uh bibo's manager
permission to tell you that you may
enter my room anytime today if you want
yeah I mean I I didn't barge in like you
know un invited I was invited to barge
she has the barge perms I have perms
yeah small
small can you can you sing happy
birthday oh okay get cl to the
happy
birthday to you I guess
whatever happy
birthday do you it's not like I care
it's your birthday or anything or you
can come in here especially for you a
happy
birthday dear
Ki I suppose happy
birthday to
you yay happy birthday
that that sounded sensual but also it's
supposed to be sun it's supposed to be
like edgy emot oh thank you thank you
thank you yeah sorry this microphone is
not made to be uh far away yeah the
microphone is that you have to get in
your face really close yeah yeah get
real close ASMR style yeah people
channeling her inner Marilyn
Monroe yeah
yeah thank you how's your stream
going I just started I've just been the
oh you just started I've just been
warning people about geek
ja it's okay I haven't even started
singing oh you haven't started singing
yeah okay I came in a perfect time y y
bble it's bble thank you for coming yeah
enjoy your
birthday bye everyone bye bye
this was okay B's voice is slowly fading
away into the background make sure to
open your present okay open thank
you there she
goes that scared the [\h__\h] out of me that
scared the [\h__\h] out of
me I was like kind of uh expecting her
to show up at some point between the
songs today but uh not like like
now I was like I heard something and I
didn't see something yet just like from
behind from the left side of my ear and
I was like
ah
bro so scary I should lock the door but
no I gave her permission to come
in yeah I think she has like um has to
be a little bit careful with her voice
that's why she's not
participating uh singing Le vocally but
that's okay
I think uh we should though like maybe
get started with a song right uh it's
been how the how has it been 20 minutes
of me yapping already again I'm sorry to
the European BRS but it is what it is
okay it is what it is not my not my
fault not my choice I'm just warning you
out of courtesy because I want things to
be better for you so if you want the
limited version then you
know yeah if you want it that bad then
you shouldn't be relying on geek Jack I
guess okay I wonder what song we should
start
with who's in the chat maybe someone
who's in the chat so that they can be if
they're just waiting for their turn then
they can be
released who's who's still in the chat I
mean and you guys are in the chat of
course ah
w i kind of didn't want to like start
with uh justice right away I thought I
should keep Justice a little bit but you
seem you seem to be okay don't okay you
seem to be okay with like waiting a
little
bit okay how about how about how about
we start with um oh this one okay okay
yep yep yep the first participant is
quason
and the song she chose is perfect
because there's a new season of
[Music]
Bim and you know how much I love bat I
was surprised she chose the song because
uh I I I just I don't know didn't
imagine her singing it before yeah okay
let me try chat feel free to tell me if
the bgm is too loud or I'm too loud I'll
try my best to
adjust
Quon okay
[Music]
okay and happy birthday kiar on your
special special day and I hope you're
having a blast cuz you deserve it and I
wanted to use this opportunity to tell
you that you're really great with
dancing and singing and I think kfp is
very lucky to have such a talented hear
that you hear that M and with that I
can't wait to sing this song with think
she's quiet when she sings let's begin
shall we shall
[Music]
we
know go
[Music]
wooo here we
go
[Music]
for
for I never I know where this goes I
never know where it
is hi
[Music]
hi
foree this
[Music]
hi
no
[Music]
this
now I don't
[Music]
know there we go that's
right guys it's ketchup time Kat up
[Music]
[Applause]
s with
[Music]
me come on and slam and welcome to the
Gil
that was so much fun and thank you so
much for having me and once again happy
birthday Kora yay thank you for
participating beautiful blue lady she's
so beautiful she's so gorgeous and such
a great choice of song was the audio
volume okay I feel like um you know all
of these videos are like the the
instrumentals are baked in their voice
and their um the instrumental the the
balance I cannot change that anymore so
uh if you feel like the their voice is
not loud enough that's just how it is in
that case uh but yeah it was good right
I was checking the chat the whole time
you guys seemed fine with
it uh but I think yeah was good was good
was good I
love and this song you guys know right
this song is special because it's sung
by the character who is just like me
spoiler
alert
Phoenix yay SK ski did you guys you know
that you're not allowed to watch the new
season yet right because we're supposed
to watch it together cuz we didn't
finish watching the previous Seasons
together yet I mean I watched it before
obviously but we're doing a watch along
right now and you guys are not allowed
to watch a new season yet wait for it
[Music]
it came out yesterday right but still
just one episode I suppose so you can't
get that far anyway
yet I don't know when I'm even going to
when are we going to get to this anyway
I don't really have
time ah wait one thing why why do I have
nine DMS Mama Mia oh ah
mush mush mush mush she going to pick
up pick up the phone pick up the phone
pick up the phone yo pick up the pH oh
I'm picking up I'm
picking why do you why do you hate me so
much that you didn't call yesterday
happy birthday it's okay it's still your
birthday not really but we just pretend
no no it's your birthday today no it's
your birthday today my merch is my merch
is going on sale today so I guess we can
pretend it's my birthday today
still yeah yeah yeah yeah right my arch
nemesis on
you yeah I'm not missing I'm not missing
this moment this is not a to moment
you're the only one that I allow to call
call me today the only
one
[Music]
yay we still hate each other by the way
yeah we do I hate you so
much yeah that's why I didn't come
yesterday mhm you're trying to mess my
plans up you're trying to like mess
everything up so that I'll be
embarrassed and all that huh yeah you
know chat told me that um you had me in
your thumbnail and I was like wait no
that actually crazy that's actually
crazy and then I went to J and I was
like yeah you're not even there you're
not even freaking there
man no wor you're just sabotaging
me yeah um how long did you wait for me
yesterday I'm uh I stalled like an hour
for you but it's okay because eventually
Zetta came to my
rescue yeah you know you know what they
call that just according to Kake Kaku
all according to the plan according to
your yeah that was the whole plan cuz
like if Zeta didn't come didn't come
like imagine there will be zero ID
coming right uh wait wasn't there there
must have been someone else was it I
thought it was only J
though what id hates me now what's going
on I thought we were good I thought me
and me and ID were like besties like
really
besties well about
then I think everyone's just busy I
think everyone's busy cuz we're cooking
a lot we're cooking a lot I was touching
grass yesterday you want some grass no
you want some grass no okay so that's
how it is so that's how it is so that's
how you hate me you you hate me that
much coobo in the chat that little SOI
also didn't call me yesterday
okay it's okay where were you Cobo where
were you not calling your mommy
on apologize it's okay okay because both
of you are participating in the K so yay
see all according to plan yeah yeah yeah
no worries thank you Ana I'm going to
I'm going to actually sing with you now
yeah oh yeah um thank you so much for
having me you got to tell me like the
whole schedule like at least a few weeks
before next year okay a few weeks before
okay yeah a few weeks before you got to
tell me all right yeah it was it was a
little bit last minute I'll agree that
I'll I'll admit it yeah well I mean
you're in Japan now so I don't blame you
can get really hectic yeah okay well
thank you Ana I'm gonna sing with you
now so sing thank you for having me Ana
thank you so
much happy
birthday goodbye
bye I hate you I hate you too oh so
sweet yeah she dm' me like uh when can I
call because yeah she she was uh busy
yesterday now then in that case since
she just called how about we sing with
her now she chose a really difficult
song so that'll be fun um
uh okay I like this song though and I
was the one who offered it in the first
place so I can't
complain it's anyaa from H second
generation I stole your
intro anyway happy birthday
Kiana it is finally Ana's annual time of
talking to each other though this time
we're not actually going to be talking
and instead we will be singing together
that's right this is one of my favorite
vocalo songs too tell me I am very
excited if I'm too loud or if she's too
loud then let's go let's
go start the song Anna there we go it's
not aoll
we would never collab with each other
never at least not one in
[Music]
[Applause]
one how's the
volume never ever
ever hey
[Music]
hey
for I I I I
[Music]
I
for
[Music]
fore
fore fore
[Music]
I was to quiet this whole time
really wait wait ketchup
time oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
let's go Ona hi cry hi cry cry hi hi
good song Choice Ana good
job GNA say something Ana or you just
going to be quiet yay happy birthday K
thank you
an sorry I was I was kissing
[Music]
myself I love her and I love this song
yeah I was like going through songs that
are in the Kadoka app and this was one
of them that I found I was like oh I
think I can sing this it's been like a
long time but I think I can sing it Ana
is gone finally finally that that
smaller smaller Japanese member kusogaki
is
gone oh she said that this is one of her
favorite vocal art songs
and I was happy to hear that cuz she
gave me an opportunity to to sing it yay
y yeah yeah thank you Ana woohoo
she did a she did a good job too I
missed like one or two lines cuz I was
checking the audio
volume yeah because you didn't talk on
your birthday you're obligated to collab
one-onone this year I don't make the
rules but you don't make the rules which
means this is not even what you're
saying is not necessary for me to do and
also like I mean Ana said this is my
birthday so and we talked so merch
dropping in 15 minutes wow I'm excited
to show you I'm so excited to show you
my merch my merch is really good I think
uh like it now let's sing another song
then if we have 15 minutes we can sing a
little bit here and
there okay choose uh an Ian generation
choose wait should we do a Paul let's go
just use up some time but myth uh let's
do uh wait
promise ad
Advent and Justice choose which one you
want someone from
now oh myth is winning myth power myth
power myth don't lose to the newbies
don't lose to the newbies yeah 46%
stable hey 49 oh 50% oh nice I'll take
that as a win I'll take that as a win
and I'll stay with
[Music]
with what's the song what are we singing
oh oh that one I might not be so good in
that one we'll see wow hello good
morning afternoon
evening my an from English SMI same one
same same generation as K
here the birthday
girl birthday
W oh my goodness I'm totally at living
this right now I should have wrote down
some some script or something
anyways happy
birthday yay oh my God I hope you're
having a good birthday celebration with
kfp and you know I hope you have a
wonderful wonderful uh year and filled
with lots of fun things lots of happy
things lots of lots of exciting things
lot you guys see of Ena en she's
uploading uh a new song cover today and
I I didn't even know uh but I saw it
today and it's an old also an old vocal
song that I really really
love sweet magic right is it the sweet
magic that I'm thinking of sweetie swe
swee swee swee swee I love that song I
know the dance
Too should I unpause
her okay I laughing at what I'm saying
and me stopping always such a big big
ball of energy who you know puts in
their 120% and everything you guys watch
her you have cover very productive and
wonderful upcoming year it's not up yet
it's not up yet thank you Ena Thank You
song I wanted to sing with you today is
a song that I know very well I hope you
know very well I know chat knows very
well so try yeah let have fun singing it
you by you want me be
fine she she she okay it might take a
while for it to start yeah it loads a
lot doesn't it it's loading yeah I know
it always does that too long it's
loading I'm sorry slow I know I should
have loed it's okay I can get mentally
prepared doesn't it start like right
away though anytime
now any anytime
now so yeah I'm
ready yeah wow it's loading longa what's
with your
[Music]
interet nice scuff we love
it I I I
[Music]
I
fore
[Music]
spee foree
let we together forever
[Music]
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
fore for
hi hi hi hi hi hi L oo e La a happy
birthday w byebye
thank you that's actually not too bad he
thank you in that was fun I feel like
our voices maybe it's just a song I
don't know but our voices work together
quite well
[Music]
huh style I feel like that's like I have
a lot of song covers right
collaborations but that was that's like
an all-time favorite from everybody such
a good
[Music]
one five minute warning yeah should I
can I squeeze in one more song I mean
they're usually just like three or four
minutes
long I could squeeze in another
one honestly not sure how long all of
these
are or should we just should we not
stress I don't
know I still have so many
Benny is Ollie still here maybe we'll do
the only one which one is the only one
is that the only one okay ah that one I
think it's not too long unless she has
an intro ah she does I think she does
have an intro like she's yapping a
little bit okay let's just let's just
not stress let's just not stress I have
9 DM what's
happening okay okay okay okay okay
oh ah oh J is also telling me to
announce my merch okay okay okay okay
I'll show you I'll show you it's been a
while since I've done this so I kind of
don't have a feeling anymore for when is
a good time to do
this okay well then
um where's my bgm let's play
some it's merch
[Music]
time what the [\h__\h] is that art right oh
n n
is that from the one and only hook Papa
my illustrator my my Creator oh yeah
you're so right it's the one and only
Stein gate and black rck shooter and
takanashi Ki
Creator hooka has uh participated in the
merch creation yay okay what do we have
what do we have what do we have
okay let's put
this I'm going to go here let me
introduce to you uh birthday celebration
2024 Taki
merchandise first off we have this is
going to be the you
know wait how does this how does this
work again wait let me turn off the
automatic manual here there we go uh uh
This Is The Limited it's a polar W again
I'll be signing the limited ones and
otherwise they're like stamped with a
non non like a fake
signature yay and then now let's look at
it one by one one by one so the hookie
Papa illustration one is this amazing
happy you guys wanted I you guys made
fanmade happies before so I was like are
you sure you guys want your like a a
Kiana official happy and you guys were
like yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h] yeah and I'm
like really you have to promise that
even if you already have one you're
still going to get the official one then
and you guys were like yeah so you
better go get it
and for this special occasion of you
know an official happy I thought I
should go all out and ask hook Papa to
draw it and I asked hook Papa to draw me
and like uh actually the inspiration was
like you know K-pop style stage outfit
like a cool one yeah and hey
and and it has like in the front it says
and in German we sayin and it has a KP
logo and has a Tak logo it has flames
and everything and I have wings I have
wings this is not the first time I think
that hook Papa Drew me with wings so
this should be like you know a cannon
now
please go get this super cool howy happy
and then wear it everywhere yeah will
you guys be proud to represent me in
this cool happy it'll you know it will
take a while like 6 months until it
arrives but um and I really love the
fan-made ones too so like it almost
breaks my heart uh cuz you guys are
planning it but I I mean I still wanted
to do my own happy so you know yeah
please wear you can switch you know but
we should mostly wear this
one are you you have six more months to
wear the old ones and then you got to
wear this one yeah it's so cool it's so
hype and I really like the hairstyle
that uh he came up with with the my my
feathers are like implemented in the
Twin Tails if you look closely later
you'll notice maybe and next we have a
super cool fan with like I chose an
artist hamu uh who like does kind of
abstract looking art uh cuz I wanted the
art to look kind of abstract and cool
and artistic and creative and beautiful
um I don't didn't want it to look like a
too clean uh perfect illustration I
wanted it to be more
like you
know
[Music]
yeah it's so beautiful it's so beautiful
please fan yourself I mean this will
arrive in the winter from most countries
but
uh yeah
well wouldn't it be nice to have it now
in the summer I I know I know
anyway next
is do you guys know the bath top robber
duckies well well well I made like a
chicken Cy chicken rubber ducky I can't
believe I didn't have this idea earlier
but I think it's an absolute genius
[Music]
idea it also has a hole at the at the
bottom you know whatever that hole is
for I'm not sure but that's why air goes
in and out so it says it makes a sound
when you press it Telly I made sure that
it makes the sound like the usual yellow
bath rubber duckies so so when you
squeeze it it will
go that's exactly how it will go almost
like a horse but yeah it's going to be
so adorable please uh even if you don't
have a bathtub you should still get
this yeah and then we have this super
cute uh like card holder it can even be
e either be for the polar orange that
comes with the set or you can like put
any kind of card in if you live in Japan
or so and you use like sua ikoka pasmo
any of those cards uh they fit in there
as well uh you can use it like for
transport uh public transportation like
put it on attach this to your bag and
then you always have easily access to
your public transportation card if you
need to go like beep beep beep oh you
The Limited it's happening now guys it's
happening it's happening it's happening
go go go go go go go get the Lim you got
the Limit Oh you guys are so fast what
the [\h__\h] I'm still just yapping and you
guys already got it thank you you got
the limited on geek check oh good job
I'm happy for you I'm glad I'm glad go
go go guys I I'll let you focus on
getting ordering the merch uh for now uh
gek is a really small amount but uh the
usual whole life shop should have a good
amount
so I think uh yeah and there's a
situational voice pack which I wrote the
script for I normally don't uh have time
to write the scripts um but this one I
wrote the script for and it's a a
personal conversation between me and you
kfp annual employee performance
review you got one you got one y
y finally time for a raise raises may be
discussed during this voice pack yeah
I'm sorry for my mistakes no no mistakes
right I got the limited merch let's go
yeah even if it's if you can't get it I
I would still be happy for your support
please um get your hands onto the merch
sold out you mean on geek Jack right
yeah not on the uh big shop the official
shop I think you can still get it there
yeah an EXT you got an extra fan too wow
nice the fan is really beautiful I think
it's going to turn out really beautiful
yeah I'm 100% getting one of those
duckies right you need one of those
duckies Mama Mia look at look at look at
this this is the full lineup we have the
beautiful hoppy I hope you like it I
hope you like it I think the the orange
and like blue dark blue com color
combination will look really really cool
and stand out from the other unofficial
happies that exist so
far yeah and the the fan the what it's
named wa was number one
fan If You Think You Are W was number
one fan you have to have this
fan
yeah number one
fun you bought to by accident wink oh
well good fun you you don't seem unhappy
about it thank you so much I hope you're
not unhappy about
it yeah H limited limited version still
available I think un official um but go
go hurry go hurry now if you want to get
it go get your hands on it geek Jack is
over it's so over but official still
selling
[Music]
sorry about geek Jack being gone right
away I'm
sorry maybe other kfps can help you get
a limited one go go go kfp Discord help
each other help the
Europeans I don't know if this can be
done so suddenly
[Music]
but what do you guys think of the merge
this time it doesn't have like one the
proper theme but I think the happy goes
well with the fan cuz usually when you
wear the happy you're going to like a
concert or something and you probably
are going to feel heated up like hot hot
hot hot from from even in the winter I
think even in the winter when you get
cheering in a venue or so you're going
to feel hot so having a fan for it for
yourself and go
like it's going to be very very
convenient and then actually okay maybe
it has a theme right after right after
uh the concert where you use the happy
and the number one fan you're going to
use the kfb card holder where you put in
your public transportation card in to
get home and then once you arrive home
you're going to go take a bath with the
rubber ducky which is a rubber chicken
and yeah you're taking bath together and
then after you're done with all that we
have a meeting it's the voice
pack ah I didn't even know I had this
whole Synergy going on ah yeah yeah all
according to
Kaku yeah I'm really happy with this
because hook Papa's art is really
awesome and you know I was thinking like
uh you know what kind of
merchandise is good for like big full
illustrations that I haven't done yet
you know I've done like a big desk mat
and stuff like that before or like um
tapestries and stuff but I don't I don't
want to repeat too
much so uh yeah I thought of the fan and
the happy would be good
canvases
for uh yeah for
that the fan so beautiful so
beautiful let me show you the the big
banel one more time cuz the art is like
bigger on there look at that look at
those Rings wow the Rings and the wings
and the feathers and I'm doing a p kind
of and you can tell like this is the way
the eyes are drawn is very hook papa is
kind of you
know kfp knows hook Papa has different
art styles uh this is the the Stein
skate style or um blackw shooter style
Taki k
yeah I love it I looks so
cool and the the wings look so metallic
this time they're different from last
time so metal so
metal
at much cly it's going to look I think
it's going to look so sick on the happy
if if that is on your back yo imagine
running around with that you're going to
look so cool the illustration looks so
sick
yeah let's let's switch it to
automatic biker
gang no I'm not supposed to look like a
biker that's not an
intention plus 100 drip
[Music]
yeah now let let's
continue where where am I I'm going to
go
back yay y yay real bikers would wear it
the happy or the or the um the lever
jacket the happppy right the lever
jacket underneath happy above I love the
rubber ducky I know right it's so cute
I'm so glad that worked out I was like
hey can I make you know like a rubber
ducky but as a cfy chicken as that
possible it's basically like a
figurine but it's making squeaky sounds
it's so good yay more kfp chicken
merchandise
[Music]
basically it's so cute you can buy like
several of them you can buy like five or
10 and have them all swim in your
bathtub or be like on the on the side as
a
decoration if I C them wey yeah I think
there's a lot of people who just have at
least one rubber ducky in their home in
their bathroom and now you can get them
a
[Music]
friend get him a friend or several
friends yeah make a chicken Army a
squeaky
one yeah
I'm so excited about the marriage W the
planning is like it feels like
everything was so last minute and it
wasn't done all done until very very
recently so it feels so surreal to be
putting this out
[Music]
now I also used to have rubber duckies
like when I was still living with my mom
my mom needs one of these
need to get my mom one of them hon R hon
rber du collection oh my God that would
be such a genius merch
idea
oh we can get like a different version
of mine for
that going to release a different
version of
mine that's a good one can you make it
happen I don't know I got to ask hot toi
producer
son H who get supposed oh really oh I
want to retweet I want to
retweet
who
[Music]
so let's see let's
see you guys can look at it and it's
full
Glory let's go o oh yeah he has like a
huge copyright
being on top of it did it have to be
that
big Jun cover
Corp didn't it have to be so big it's
actually is it the same cut as the no
you can see a bit more in his version it
goes down to the belly
button
H the compared to what the whole life
production English thing tweeted the
Twitter Hey Hey so good so good I love
seeing myself in that
style Ollie loves the merch well then
shall we sing Ollie song I was going to
I was already getting ready to sing with
her
anyway Ollie Ollie I don't know if
you're watching right now but let's sing
past
o okay
I'm so
excited happy birthday
K thank you so much for inviting me to
your birthday tooke party I am honored
to be able to sing with my Senpai SL oi
slri SL future
lover I respect you a lot I look up to
you a lot you're obviously my Oshi and
you do so much for me for everyone you
bring so many Smiles you inspire people
you do so much for the community and I
wish I could say more but I have to sh
because we have to sing thank
[Music]
you I came
out for
[Music]
I
I I I I
[Music]
you're so I really
embarrassed I'm just having fun why y oh
gosh you're so
[Music]
sexy fore
for
[Applause]
I love you that was unexpected oh thank
you
ollie so cute so fun I love her so much
she's the best she is the best
man you I love you let's collab soon
I've been like so busy but I hope we can
find some time to collab all so real for
real for real man she's so cute is so
fun best hype girl y makes me feel
loved get yourself someone that loves
you like o loves
me best girl best girl I love the song
dude so hype it's like so nostalgic to
me too like but I haven't heard it or
sang it in a long time so now it felt
pretty fresh and fun especially singing
it gab with Ollie felt really new to
me yeah yeah yeah was
all from allive
Indonesia who says I am her
oy ol you're going to look so good in
that
happy okay okay okay how about we bring
out one Justice member eh eh haven't
brought out a single Justice member so
far thankfully happily uh all of them
agreed to participate
see no justice Des no uh I don't know
who should we Let's do let's
do okay let's do this one since we're in
Nostalgia nostalgic songs I mean most of
these are nostalgic
but nextg judgment no I don't think so
okay uh next one is just um the audio
and the standing no video but that's
okay whoa whoa whoa whoa so herb chose a
song that I was so surprised I didn't
think anybody would choose it to be
honest so I'm so [\h__\h] happy to sing
this
now
[Music]
um yeah okay here we go uh I could
a CO a let's do a collab let's sing in a
collab shall we you guys uh don't don't
forget if you feel like I should turn it
down or up let me know in the chat and
I'll adjust as fast as I
can let's [\h__\h]
[Music]
go
oh I say
[Music]
happy birthday
K let's go
[Music]
with
[Applause]
[Music]
I
forever go let's go
[Music]
hated
herb my duy
duy Stay With Me
[Music]
for
fora
Senai have an amazing bir
all your birthday wishes come true your
FY passion is bright and beautiful in it
you freaking Legend onwards and upwards
let's
[Music]
go stay with me
foray with me
[Music]
forever you're so good Best
Taste thank you so much P Senpai for
having me sing with you I hope you have
a great rest of your birthday thank you
thank you so so
much after she like she SS so strongly
and then she talks so gently charmingly
so she's also in the chat thank you for
so waiting for this thank you I didn't
want to bring out Justice too early you
know I want to do them Justice
obviously like well when she chose that
song I was like oh my God oh my God oh
my God and then I also brought up like
uh what was it first
[Music]
G like all of the um de Nota songs are
just so hype oh my
God and I felt like nobody else knows
these songs yeah that was epic y'all
when we meet in Japan we got to go to
Kar and sing all of these songs together
and maybe some other we don't know yet
maybe we have some more old nostalgic
anime songs that we both know because
maybe maybe you're the same as Me Maybe
I also don't like what I say also but
I'm just assuming cuz you chose an old
anime song like I don't even watch like
newer anime but I know a lot of these
older ones maybe you're the
same oh yo actually you know isn't there
like there's this character in zuka um
who's like really tall and big
Boba and I think she's like also
redhaired wasn't
she was it was it k k like she literally
has a German name yeah
K like they're like uh they could like
Elizabeth could cosplay her someone do a
fan art where she's dressed up as her
and then I mean I don't really feel like
I fit uh Louise to be honest honest with
you I feel like out of the characters
like in terms of
physical
traits
[Music]
um maybe the maybe the princess or the m
I don't
know but both Louise and the and the
other like calm K uh blue-haired girl I
think they're both not really I don't
fit
them yeah
Henrietta or or Siesta yeah either one
of them get me into those
clothes I like
them that was the most awesome
pronunciation I've heard from K yeah cuz
German name I'm pretty sure they that
was supposed to be a German
name so that was fun we should rewatch
that at some
point that anime I don't know how I how
I would feel watching it now CU there's
there's so much fan service and I
nowadays I don't like it so much anymore
like fan service
she remember it yeah all right all right
all right let's keep the hype up these
songs are so hype aren't they keep shall
we keep the hype up or should we go to
calmer song I don't
know how about how about how about uh
going with what did sh saying what did
she choose ah that okay that was fun too
I was surprised about this one too I I I
wonder why she knows the song
probably because like this song is from
Hell project but a lot of people who
don't know hell project still know this
upcoming song Just because it kind of
went outside of that fandom I guess for
because it was featured in an anime
ending and became kind of like
Mish so thank you
panco and here we
go happy
birthday by the way I can't sing this
song
[Music]
h e
birthday oh yeah I [\h__\h] like
[Music]
it for
don't confuse
[Music]
me you sing so well by the way you're
amazing you're great I love you
[Music]
Shy oh
for s o s o s
[Music]
happy
birthday shooting out
oh my
God she added like special effects and
stuff she's so crazy she's so
crazy thank you shy I kind of like mixed
in the vibes from the meme version of
this song in case you haven't
noticed it's so original buta but then
there's
also I wonder I wonder if she knows it
from that
version I feel like so
that was
intense
intense you went
off yeah I think the SOS part I think
only in the version it goes like s o s o
s I think only in the meme version it's
like
that not in the original there's no way
because she's a pure pure
idoru okay which one should we do next
next next how about we calm down a
little bit although wait that that song
didn't end up being
submitted um
what other calm song do I have I
think this is relatively calm fauna's
submission is relatively
calm here we
go Sona
[Music]
he fora chose a cute song He hi hi hi hi
very but also
[Music]
k foree
come on and SL and welcome to the
jail the instrumental is baked in I
can't make her
louder voice and music is on the same
track
yeah can't make her
louder just listen this one
[Music]
harder for
is
[Music]
come on and SL and welcome to the jail
come on and slam and welcome to the gy
let me say come on Slam and welcome to
the
[Music]
thany you father so cute so cute so
cute
bars yeah sorry if F was a little bit
too quiet because I cannot adjust their
audio they sent me the audio of of the
instrumental and themselves baked into
each other they are married they cannot
be separated anymore but she she has a
gentle soft voice you know you have to
listen
like hard
harder so we had like two B songs
already I don't think there's any more
though
sorry
oh the last sip of the tea was kind of
weird now I have no more water I got to
take something out of the fridge in a
moment and Callie is here I have seen so
maybe next we do c
i Callie
chose uh o okay okay okay that
song G I feel like it's difficult this
song I don't think I ever sang it
properly even though I love it so
much we're going to do our best
okay oh Callie please help me with this
one lead me lead me
cie I love those glasses
[Music]
man I don't want the hbags the money or
the diamond rings cuz guys like you they
all don't care about the little things
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm moving on and I'm never ever back
around around around again now I'll go
higher
higher take me down if
[Music]
you now I can finally open my
eyes
me ins get you out my I'll get
[Music]
oops delete a g number all of my friends
used to warn me about you baby I thought
that I couldn't without you I got myself
now I don't even know a other
I don't want
the so
everying and never ever turning back
around around around again now I'll go
higher and now go higher and you
couldn't take me down if you
[Music]
tried mistake all the goodbyes and the
Heart Break
[Music]
no
break it's K and
Ki you ready he hey so
[Music]
ready let's go
I can finally open my eyes
[Music]
I'll get get
get
all out of my life
[Music]
Bo happy birthday thank you Kell that
was so fun to sing together oh whoa whoa
whoa
whoa those bangs are so dorky
too but I love those glasses the color
is so m p p so good so fun I love how
you sang like like the chorus in a lower
tone uh because then we we harmonized yo
and I can just sing the higher one which
I'm like better at anyway than the lower
one let's go can't wild P you knew I
would
saying she knows
she knows it all thank you Kelly for
participating even though you're you
know busy busy lady but you always take
your time for stuff like this for me I
really appreciate it if you ever doing C
like this yourself Count Me In Count Me
In birthday hey Kelly what do you think
about my merch is this isn't this so
sick like oh my God oh my God did you
see the back of the happy let me let me
put it up again here
woo as a reminder everybody I don't know
if there's still there probably is still
is there still limited on the official
shop go go go go go get the limited on
the fishal up did you see the robber
ducky
though the robber
ducky it
goes kind of like
that yay limited S St go go go they
should have really split a bit more over
to geek Jack
man man
I
wish drown it don't drown the kfb
chicken no it's like you literally you
can't drown yourself come
on you should stay afloat chickens can
swim can chickens
swim if chickens are put onto water will
they swim like a duck and like use
because they they don't have like the
things in between their fies their toes
like a ducky but they might still try to
get forward like that just not as
efficiently as a duck chicken floats I
heard can't drown myself bit no don't
even try you're too fluffy to float I
think H to drown yourself I don't think
you can unless you eat like stones or
you're filled with stones then maybe I
don't think they can swim but won't
their fluffiness just keep them afloat
anyway even if they can't like actually
swim well we got to try it out yeah time
for science with the r duct
iies what if we eat too much corn
H science science
time okay okay let's move on to the next
song let's bring a ID in again shall we
we had Ana we had
Ollie I have um I'm must say some of the
ID submissions are pretty funny
um let's bring in Zetta what song did
Zetta choose again ah that one I love
that song okay it's Zetta time
um she's funny made me I I saw the video
a little bit and I was like laughing at
[Laughter]
[Music]
it one more one more
happy birthday I love you I
hope birthday ever that's just so funny
[Music]
spee
fore for
[Music]
hey what is it what is
it what are you
[Music]
doing
for get over
[Music]
here behave you're real Phoenix right
can you cry no no I don't know all your
wishes come throughly one day just like
how my wishes came I can fly look look
Focus stay still
[Music]
she looks so
cool what don't show me your inside it's
vanilla I so much can't hear her thank
you she is a weirdo I love it are you
surea could be that you're like an
uncolored neroid too because I feel like
once you're colored you should be orange
cuz that was real orange cat
behavior not gray cat behavior I'm sorry
but that was
crazy and like I can't even like she
would make herself so big that she cuts
off at the side so I have to make her
fill the whole screen right but then
like she covers me so much but I love it
I like to be covered by her she was
funny made me laugh orange cat behavior
so true hi there is a high CO K's video
is also really funny by the way but I'm
I'm not going to do it right away I got
to keep got got to keep that one for
later okay okay that was so good that
was so funny man I could barely focus on
singing with that
one let's go
to how
about
E I love the song she chose too
obviously I love all the songs these
people have been choosing because I
suggested them a list in the first place
let's go e so cute I love this
[Music]
outfit go lady go
lady deep emotion deep
[Music]
emotion
for spee
[Music]
Bea Choo cho
cho
[Music]
for so
good happy
[Music]
ch
i i i i emotion
[Music]
[Applause]
sexy Beauty
[Music]
[Applause]
I love you k I love you too thank
you I feel like I don't have many um
opportunity so far to like sing together
with
eie so that was really nice yeah she
sounds so cute and actually that song
fits her voice quite well I was
surprised I like YY singing
voice ah for some reason I'm feeling
kind of weirdly sick right now a little
bit a little bit just a little bit who
picked it I gave like a big list of
suggestions that I can sing and they
chose uh something they wanted from that
list so we both picked it I love the
song kind of know the corer a little bit
too yeah ah actually so one thing that I
forgot to show you guys uh I didn't even
know this existed apparently I requested
it I guess a while ago and then I I
don't think I was notified when it was
implemented
but I noticed it today when I was
putting on this outfit I was like oh
wait what's this it's a
huh this
hairstyle was implemented into this
outfit but it makes sense I feel like I
must have suggested it like can you
implement this for so and so many points
because the braids will work well with
this outfit
too
surprise it's my beloved braids on this
outfit
huh what a
thought thank you thank you cute right
you just downlo yeah I didn't know I
don't know when they implemented it
must have been a while ago cuz I haven't
used this outfit in a while so just
today I noticed can you take off the
headband yeah but I feel it looks a bit
empty without the headband I can put the
kfb on my head but these ones are kind
of like behind my head so I don't know
and I do feel like it looks only go with
the Blazer I don't know like this looks
does it look weird without the
Blazer I don't know you tell me what do
you think of
this onion my beloved
looks good both ways not weird really do
I look cute now I have threee uh free
hairsty of
this like we have this this was the
first and this was the this was a extra
new one
that did this one not have hair Flor
Decor oh it didn't did it not I guess it
didn't and then there's this now
whoa choose your
fighter now I guess I'll sing a little
bit with this my orange onion
head don't don't question which side the
apron is tied on that was like a mistake
um it doesn't mean
anything this drink anything since you
started yeah but let me get water cuz my
throat is
fum is choking
me yes I'm married to you guys if
anything I'm married to my job to my
[Music]
work okay okay okay I want this oh oh
jenma brought me new tea thank
you okay I'm not I'm not going to eat
now but thank
[Music]
you I hear myself what
from I think how many more do I have I'm
not sure a few a few
[Music]
well it's it has the perfect temperature
I love how warm drinks in Japan when you
buy them from the bending machine the
warmth of it the heat is exactly perfect
it's not like lukewarm or so and it's
not too hot it's like the perfect
temperature yeah B she brought me
Bal Japanese people like somehow in
Japan there's a lot of Bal being sold
everywhere but um I'm
cooking not my favorite
thing cuz it's like just like the the
cake base like there's no coating like
if there was a sugar or chocolate
coating or so I that would been
better we don't even eat B cook in
Austria I mean I don't think we do not
normally it's a rare thing but in Japan
everybody loves B
cooking but I'm still gonna snack it I'm
gonna snack it because Gemma got it for
me not now though let's sing a next
song um let me delete the ones that I
sang so I can get a better
overview
um this one this one this one this one
this one I think it's time to sing
another Justice one
okay it's
time where is the
what ah
here let's do gigy how about gigy gigy
chose a hype one and the old
one
and I love her so much my orange
child I will one day when I
die for the short moments what that are
between me being dead and
Reviving I shall uh give her all my
everything she shall be the successor of
kfp and she shall inherit everything I
own but only for the short amount of
time while I'm
respawning
yeah which in the end means nothing not
Cobalt of course not Cobalt Cobalt that
little SOI man she needs to be nicer to
me her mom otherwise she will not get
inheritance good luck out there kid the
Fister who you want running your
business only it's like really a short
amount of time like I I respawn really
fast Kobo behave exactly not
Kobo but I feel like she she's she's
kind of redeeming herself with the video
she submitted you'll see you'll see
later let's go
geky hi geky
[Music]
Lucky
Star
[Music]
my cute
let's
get look
sensation fore
[Music]
let's go
up
[Music]
so where are you going after this you
want to like hang out together or all we
should play some what's your favorite
one by the way oh yeah I played ring
Master G before I so much fun yeah oh my
God you're such an AO Fister can you
like fist me some what don't know what I
meant I'm just talking some random sh
don't even listen to me y y y y y y y y
y y y y
y Chop Chop look
up
educ
ABC fore
[Music]
new that's it you're not going to say
bye H that little Auto
Fister I love her thank you for seeing
that with me that was so much fun she
has this Gremlin energy that is perfect
for the song I want to sing more like
these cute energetic songs with her
Lucky Star was one of my favorite animes
back in the day such a classic so good
can't even say which one's my favorite
though from the
characters I don't think I would be able
to say I think back then I had no
favorite but what what what what my me
what that was just like it I didn't Yap
anything it was just a background
yapping or that was uh part of the
instrumental I didn't say
anything kagami yeah she's freaking cute
she's the the the twin tail one right
the T
one yeah she might be my favorite too it
was the wind it was the wind well
narissa has been waiting for so long
should we do
narissa should we do
[Music]
narissa by the way I just realized this
stream I um does this mean I'm the first
one to sing with all of
Justice I think that's what that means
you'll be here until the end of I love
you so cute so sweet yeah it does I'm
the first one to sing with all of
Justice
wow okay there's Lucky Star and then
there's what narissa
chose which these song Choices back to
back actually have a lot of
[Music]
synergy that's right how he it's h he
time we
[Music]
we
okay happy birthday to the one and only
[Music]
impeccable let's go let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
I have her Max
wait let me give
her let's start from the beginning I
have her maxed out in OBS let me give
her a filter to make her
louder
uh
[Music]
gain maybe like
this oh that was
loud but that may have been good I don't
know oh okay we
start happy birthday to the one and only
impeccable
[Music]
let's
go
[Music]
n
for Fore
[Music]
catch me catch
me messed up a little bit sorry no you
didn't love you Queen I love you too
happy birthday happy birthday to you too
[Music]
spe
I'm going to run I'm going to
[Music]
run are you having a good
day I love you stop moving I'll come
there go
[Music]
[Applause]
catch me catch me
[Music]
she smells
good I keep on running away when just
sing cuz it means catch me run after me
and she just won't run after me what's
wrong with her why won't she chase me
she not much of a
chaser chase me
Nissa it's just the problem of not
understanding Japanese you would totally
chase me right if you knew what that
meant
beforehand I I figured I
figured o means Chase it's like
toy toy no wa not quite though kind of
same
though chasing time catch me catch me
catch
[Music]
me cute that was fun like I'm surprised
like I'm singing all these Classics that
I've heard a million times but they have
a completely new fun vibe today that I
didn't expect at all
thanks to these lovely cute
participants
weisa weisa she's a participant but she
doesn't wear
pants isn't that
weird it's a do
Badu okay next door next St before this
gets too embarrassing thank you M for
the red thank you guys I think next week
I could do a super chat ah speaking of
um so turns out I think we will switch
Wednesday with
Friday uh not because the studio isn't
available but because they can't set up
the camera for us on
Wednesday sadly so we're just going to
do it on Friday cuz seems like seems
like shot is also free on Friday for me
to do that stream same time yeah and
just we're switching the days but the
times like for example on Friday was
going to be 7:00 p.m. J
um I'm going to uh still do 700 p.m.
jst on uh Wednesday sorry if you can't
do Friday
sorry sorry but it's going to be a
relatively short stream I think so you
can just watch the
[Music]
archive something in my
throat okay I don't know if La is still
here but it's time for daa I've decided
it's time for daa
this is also classic but not as not as
old as the other ones I would
say God she's streaming right now oh oh
is she like drawing something nice again
or is she what is she doing she drew me
a birthday illustration and it's so
sweet I love it so much it actually
looks so [\h__\h] good she's such a
blessing already Minecraft okay well
well well Nowa will be in two places at
the same
time let's go she's so cute oh my God
look at her
[Music]
I I I I I
I
[Music]
fore
for hi hi hi hi yeah this is still real
Lou her Minecraft stream is
[Music]
pre-recorded she's the real one
for
[Music]
fore all
a r r
r l
o she is so cute she is pink panda I
love her so much she drew me yesterday
she is an angel I'll hold her today and
tomorrow I will eat pizza I love
[Music]
you fore
to thow as
[Music]
m i i i i
hey oh she's so cute look at her look at
her
[Music]
cuteness she did such a good
job
right who's a cute Panter
[Music]
what that's
a that's a tune I just thought of
spontaneously uh just came up in my mind
for some reason um I'm just so creative
thanks by the way Callie for still
hanging
out listening to this C even
now we have how many more let's um sort
things out
[Music]
here oh okay okay I have one two three
four four
more okay let's do
way but this song I'm really bad about
actually C is literally the only reason
why I know the song and why I ever sang
this song before um I love the song it's
fun but I it's so difficult at least I
had like a little bit of an advantage
um not not not towards D it because
she's already so perfect at the song but
at least I knew it a little bit thanks
to cie teaching
me no not
narut imagine rain is singing the German
Naruto op
okay the thing is like I know the
English version more of this song thanks
to Cali so now maybe you know what I
[Applause]
mean everybody say
winner is going to carry this
[Music]
one like a man
St
[Music]
[Applause]
take a
selfie want to take selfie
selfie oh thank you
selfie
[Music]
she we are
fi
[Applause]
[Music]
MVP
h Huh
[Music]
baby baby baby baby baby
baby
baby baby
[Music]
rock rock rock
rock and rock and
roll rock and roll thank you R she's so
cute see now what I meant with I only
know the song thanks to
Cali I tried though I tried I have the
English version more in my brain than
the Japanese
one I did my best was a good opportunity
to finally sing it like in
Japanese but the English version is so
good Calli is lyrical genius sasuka and
waya is mapmap genius and her RS her ARS
are so strong
sheesh okay we're getting closer to the
end guys woohoo my voice can soon rest I
tried to make my voice strong in this
song just now and I I noticed uh oh AB
don't overdo it with the can R don't
overdo it this next song Maybe is a bit
more on the calmer
side why do I feel like throwing up man
what's going
on I will power through I can power
through even more if you guys buy my
merchandise link is pinned in the chat
and maybe also in the description please
buy my merchandise so that I can pay my
doctor visit just kidding
mommy after a toy another toy and I love
her song choice
[Music]
[Applause]
knock
[Music]
out do you hear me call
for want to
[Music]
do
for ask me
[Music]
out
heart
[Music]
for all right
no excuses
[Music]
I
baby you want to take me out te my te
your
[Music]
eyes W all right
[Applause]
my
[Music]
heart wo all right love
love love stop stop stop and roll st
stop stop stop
stop and
[Applause]
Roll and
[Music]
Roll
and that was beautiful wasn't it she oh
my God this song holy [\h__\h] she sings it
so well holy [\h__\h] M just listening to me
there she
[Music]
goes I've known this song for so long
but I think this is the first time I
sing it on stream it's pretty
old superst is a blessing but this was
um I think from a
movie uh like the an anime movie this
was like a theme track for it where
right I remember watching it back then
yeah s sensor roll I watched that I
did my Fai so far really did you know
the song though or did you just like get
to know it now m i sang it so freaking
well holy
[\h__\h] she sing it so well I tried to keep
up with her she's just too good but I I
think in the chorus and all that when we
sang together we harmonized quite nicely
didn't
we thank you Mum so much for
participating
yeah it's it's um I think within
supercell songs people know it but I
don't think it's as known as as the
other ones that they have but this is a
underestimated underappreciated song hey
love and Roll by Supercell I have two
more
left they're both kind of
special one of them is obviously uh the
last Justice member that hasn't appeared
yet I'm going to go with that one cuz
the Vibes they're both kind of hype they
both kind of hype
[Music]
actually and then coobo last yeah cuz
what she did is um the highest effort
out of all of the participants I
think okay
where is she don't worry she will
come she she's she's
[Music]
somewhere she's out there there she
again sing with us
[Music]
[Applause]
do
so
[Music]
true
for oh yeah
[Music]
Dragon
Ball he
it's drag on
these
balls
sparing oh German
song yeah I actually I think I sang this
in German before in my German anime song
K from quite a while ago but now I have
someone to sing German songs
[Music]
with dragon D that was funny when I was
like uh doing a quick practice of this
before the stream was just funny to me
probably but jenma also laughed I was
like fully in the German accent and I
sang like full German pronunciation
dragon with the
r Dragon
Balls yeah this time I didn't do it
properly English
pronunciation are you ever going to do
German hory again I even completely
forgot about its existence thanks for
reminding
me okay thank you for singing German
with me
yay I think I had like I had the song in
the in the list
of songs and maybe somewhere in the back
of my head I thought oh like if she
chooses this then we could sing it in
German and she suggested suggested also
that we could sing it in German so that
worked out nicely hey okay we have one
last one oh
B it's going to bless us with a full
body 3D performance of this uh Idol song
that is the Rival company
of the idols that I actually like I hope
I I don't know if I actually know how to
sing it anymore I haven't sung it in too
long Co please help me out
here she
so thank you happy
birthday I wish you all the best you
become rich rich out the way give her
space to dance and then many many money
many money spend more money buy merch
buy merch and then uh a good health wow
she's so nice today and good wealth oh
thank you to you too because this is
your special day so uh I am using my
swimsuit now should I wait no I cannot
use this swimsuit on my own ah true wait
kble let me change for you I was
thinking of doing this anyway
um I won't be able to move like her but
at least we'll be matching oh oh I
started out in this POS what the hell
why am I touching my
boobies coobo looking awkwardly to the
side wait
um why stand normally thank you
hey swimsuit daughter and Mommy uh
together in in the
swimsuits
wait so I won't be moving but I'm I'm
here in swimsuit in
spirit I'll just I just I stay on the
sign she needs she needs space her hair
takes up so much space
obviously let's
go continue please child uh there you go
so yeah yeah let's go together yeah
let's go let's
go 1 2 3
[Music]
4 I want you I want you I need you I
need you I love you I love you
[Music]
dance so
cute go
[Music]
let's go come I want you I want you I
need you I need you I love you I love
you give me
[Music]
[\h__\h]
sorry I want you I want you I need you I
need you I love you I love
you know
[Music]
go TR for me
I feel you I feel you I touch you I
touch you I hold you
[Music]
I feel you I feel you I touch you I
touch you I hold you like a
[Music]
baby don't forget to subscribe go on
channel my my
subscribe
[Music]
it's subscribe to
me of course here we go one I want you I
need you I need you I love you I love
you keep
[Music]
me one more I want you I want you I need
you I need you I love you I love you
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God this is so fun next time let's
dance together again okay mommy yeah I
totally danc with herk you
once again good
luck thank you everyone subscribe my
channel no okay byee no oh my god that
hurt my ears
somehow the way she left somehow the
silence hurt my ears ironically was coob
K yeah subscribe to her mine and
Callie's Channel then
maybe you know those family YouTubers
who just expose way too much of their
children's lives but if me and cie will
make a one of those cursed Family
YouTube channels and we just film cob
all the time and use her for exposure oh
cursed cursed but she would enjoy it she
would enjoy
that nope it's okay we don't even have
to do it like she's already doing it on
her own
it would be a April foood bit
H think about it think about it we're
cooking ah okay that was all uh that was
everybody and um I want to thank
everybody for participating that was so
much fun I I don't know why this is the
first time I doing this one thank you so
much for um you know sending in your
videos everybody even during busiest
times when we're merch reminder looking
[\h__\h] dope hook Papa thank you so much
for drawing this sick ass
art yeah I'm feeling like really sick
right now it's um kind of
concerning and tomorrow little little
reminder here uh let me show you my
schedule for the upcoming week I put it
up on Twitter surprising I'm still in
Japan and I'm offering to you a schedule
who would have fought there's a new
members wallpaper also it's kind of late
but uh uploaded it today on the members
um oh [\h__\h] it saved as a [\h__\h] J J Jif
how dare
you cheg please
cheg yes who the [\h__\h] wants je there you
go this is a schedule but as I already
said a cute art by the way woo splits uh
I I had to zoom in a little bit there's
a zoomed out Vision in the members only
where you know you can see everything
that's going on there um uh so the
collab tomorrow is uh sophisticated
English class with ladin I offered her
to teach her German or English or she
could teach me about like art or
whatever I don't freaking know she chose
that i' teach her English even though
it's not my first language but she wants
to learn uh sophisticated art terms uh
which I will uh tomorrow before um
meeting up with her I will make a
PowerPoint presentation I might do a
Twitter space where you guys have to
help me find things that uh like words
that I could teach her um cuz she sent
me a feel that she would need cuz I was
like what what are you looking for she
sent me a few but I'm I might do a
Twitter space while I'm making the
PowerPoint presentation to get your help
but it's going to be on ladin
sen on ladin's channel lad CH
Senai and have you noticed it's kind of
Oreo week because uh two black and white
haired girls uh I will be collabing with
um the other one is shiy but it's now
already changed uh right after I made my
schedule I've been made aware that's not
going to work out I'm still going to do
the Wawa stream on Wednesday possibly
Super Chat catchup uh and then uh we're
switching it around it should work out
on Friday we both have time I hope I
hope the studio can accommodate us cuz
we need to do a hand cam stream
there's I I already I already ordered um
special tools for our cursed witchcraft
room what could it be what could it
be so Wednesday Friday Switcheroo uh on
Sunday by the way it's not on the
schedule here and I'm not sure if I'm
allowed to say it but I'm just going to
say it now uh uh before the football
finally watch along a few hours before
that I have a uh Japan Expo
panel um you know how the Anime Expo had
like this booth
yeah yeah yeah uh I'll have such a
thing with Amy and GAA yeah I asked I
asked them if they want to do something
with me uh uh and we're going to do
something and the the the idea for what
we're doing comes from
GAA yeah we're going to do
something for Japan Expo in
Fr will it be streamed I don't think
so but I don't know maybe uh people will
take a video of it I don't think that's
uh illegal I think it's relatively
allowed it's not like it's not in like a
panel room like you know it's just a
booth in the middle of the venue so that
stuff doesn't get
streamed yeah don't forget to like And
subscribe that's why thanks for bringing
that
up relatively loud yeah what a nice way
to phrase it
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's on
Sunday like uh during the day you know
like normal like daytime of Europe um
like sub by merge exactly so true great
sat lless fun guas thank you should it
be happy birthday now a happy happy
birthday yeah I'm so excited for the
happy all all of that merch will take
half a year but hopefully we can see
some samples I haven't seen any samples
yet like IRL samples but with
the one month where it's going to be on
sale I think there should be um sample
photos at the end happy birthday he
tweeted it like
that oh yeah um birthday merch link up
there at the top of the screen uh chat
and the description I'll tweet it's also
retweeted uh thank you thank you thank
you for the support so far thank you for
the fun birthday while birthday is
hereby pronounced to be dead and over
until next year it's kind of crazy I
didn't even feel like you know my
birthday is coming up the year is going
back so fast and here we are once again
it's July July 6th SL 7th we have
celebrated another birthday together
thank you for spending so much time with
me yeah I'm honored to be your oi or
maybe maybe I'm not Yoshi but you're
just like relatively interested in me
I'm I also appreciate that thank you so
much for being mildly interested in
me or or or extremely interested in me
whichever it is I appreciate any support
had so much fun singing with the girls
hopefully we can do this again I'm going
to throw up now I I think this really
feels so weird holy [\h__\h] I want to throw
up I'm going to go I'm going to go
before I throw up on stream although it
would be fun and entertaining I think um
May maybe not fun but
entertaining I'm going
to
[Music]
oh yeah I should I should end the stream
I would love to puke on stream on my
birthday stream um that would be
content but we have to think about the
fact that this is the internet and I may
think that would be funny now but things
on the internet never disappear so once
I get clipped I'm I'm never going to get
rid of
it in German we
say and if you want to give me a
birthday present by my
[Music]
merch tomorrow collab onad chel it will
be off collab hey I'm excited I'm I'm
I'm oh my God I'm nervous
yay
[Music]
goodbye k k v
super
[Music]
he