[Music]
a
welcome back
everyone uh oh shoot the chat is not
showing up
fix that real
[Music]
quick
huh why is it not getting fixed oh there
we go so welcome guys to
[Music]
the I believe this oh it's the sixth the
sixth stream of the Alon
stream guys
[Music]
it's been six hours so uh just a few
more hours just another eight more hours
am I
[Music]
right
yeah after this I'll have a collab with
alter and axel I kind of want to wind it
down with some uh
Minecraft I want to take it easy I don't
want to
talk too loud I just want to chill with
you guys which can only mean one thing
we're going back to Nostalgia Road and
I'll be cutting some Birchwood but
before that I kind of do got to go to
the toilet all had
a
look
[Music]
hi yeah hoping that the BDM helps you
guys if you guys are tuning in just
because you guys have insomnia I hope
that the stream will uh help you even
though it's just a little
[Music]
bit but I don't want to sleep momy go to
sleep thank you for caring for for a Al
and remember it's been 6 hours if you
guys uh can't hold
on then that's okay okay uh let's just
chill have
fun and see where it takes
[Music]
us much
better
[Music]
yeah oh shoot
SC let
[Music]
me I haven't gotten the stream after the
Apex one ready
[Music]
yet so anyways
um Birch CIA let's cut down some Birch
and just chill
honestly it's
cool I feel like I know I said that
we'll be doing some YIFY and whatnot but
I feel like I don't want to just sit
back relax and do what I do best which
is some deep talk while we cut Birch
been a while
[Music]
huh block of emerald
torch
hey where where is it here it
[Music]
is been a while since last time we went
here
[Music]
iron ah don't worry we still have some
iron axes over here so let's just put
our stues in
here and do some
chopping uh baked potato just in case
get some of
these
okay
and again I would like to remind you
guys it's been 3 years
[Music]
huh time flies like I don't know when
you guys started watching and actually
keeping up with
me but for those of you guys who did
kept up ever since the Beed were at
least ever since the early days we've
actually come a long
way
and it was pretty tough not going to lie
if I said that we went through
everything smoothly I'd be completely
lying but it it was a wild roller
coaster
[Music]
ride
I've been here for a bit over two years
now and that's a long
time might not be from the start but
that's still pretty long like actually
dedicating yourself to something for 2
years especially if this turn something
with someone I don't know I feel like
that takes like a lot of dedication
[Music]
my bias changes a lot it used to be
Taylor
Swift and then it went to uh
BTS I had the love life phase I could
stick to one for too long so the fact
that you guys stayed with
me for years now I guess you can say
years because you know three years and
two years they are
plural it's
fascinating I got
[Music]
every phase you're in you're still the
ol we
love so sweet of you say you the Calli
oi still Baff tell me how people call me
their ooshi though that's still
something that I can't really process
even to this day I know it's
been [\h__\h] 3 years but the word
Oshi Ali my Oshi is Ali that's something
that I still have a hard time believing
[Music]
in
like the only difference in me is that
I'm a zombie and you guys are humans
we're other than that we're all
basically the
same
[Music]
basically
fan how many more rainbows must I send
you for you to understand that you're my
Oshi no it's it's not that I don't
understand that I'm your Oshi what I
can't comprehend is I just just can't
believe how some people would see me as
an
ooshi it's not that I don't believe
that it's just that I I can't really
comprehend it you
know been a true member for almost 2
years but uh was a background member
over my hubby's shoulder for longer as
you are here so I will be here
a you may not be my ooshi but you're the
one who introduced me to Hol and I am
forever thankful hey I may not be the
reason why you smile
today but I'm glad that I at least made
you smile
[Music]
once they choose their oi by the amount
of birch trees chopped down God
[Music]
dang okay
I don't know or some [\h__\h] like
[Music]
that guiney this is what we do when we
do bridge
[Music]
talk I wanted to hit the Nostalgia train
train I
mean
[Music]
yeah yep it's a
tradition once for some three whole
years for some others a thank
[Music]
you I don't want to talk about self
depreciating topics because I feel like
that's something that we always and
constantly talk about in zombies
so the only thing that I can say is
thank you for staying with me now for
only choosing me for staying and for
actually committing to
me the fact that you guys are still here
not because of the games not because of
the people who I interact with not
because I'm affiliated with Hol Life as
a company but because I'm
me means a lot you
know
people come and go I feel like that's a
quote that we've heard millions of
time and you know I've come to
accept uh that um you know people will
leave
me one day I'll die out of popularity
and I might just disappear without
anyone knowing but the fact that you
guys are still here for
[Music]
me makes me super happy
know hell hey I love you for you it's
awesome to know there are more people as
crazy as me in the world yeah and I'm
I'm glad I actually got to meet a lot of
you guys because a lot of you guys are
super
[Music]
cool
again I was a fan
before I was a
talent
[Music]
event you guys have my utmost respect
because again was a fan
before and the fact
that you guys go over the moon
for me or even for other girlies it
still amazes
[Music]
me I hope you guys didn't hear my burp
you guys didn't hear it
right I'm crying right
now you were one of us who got
[Music]
in
yeah
it was
subtle oh but I
wish I guess some actually
heard thanks for telling us oh my God
just a fan that is no information to me
didn't realize that
[Music]
LOL but I mean it is
true
I mean basically okay I'm still a fan
it's just that I
stream I happen to be in the same agency
as the people who I
love and I
[Music]
stream because of the fan history that's
why we love it when you do
collabs thank
you like you guys are all so dedicated
to me it's also again
uh my attention span is very short I get
bored a lot
easily we've been streaming for like 7
hours now and you guys are still
[Music]
here
I'll be very Frank with you guys I've
run out of ways to actually thank you
[Music]
guys
let's say that uh I don't
um I end up have uh uh I end up
not
um getting accepted in hollow
life but I do I don't I don't know if
I'll keep trying because again uh I'm
sure you've heard the story
before it took me seven different
auditions to become a vtu Hol life was
my last one if I actually failed Hol
life I think I would have just stopped
and accepted my
fate as a dead
[Music]
person
like sure uh I guess I have management
to thank for that but
still if it weren't for you guys I don't
think I would have stayed
[Music]
anyways
get bored
easily however much longer you are here
whether it's 1 year 5 years 10 years
what will'll never change is that we are
zombas for the rest of our lives
a and without you we probably wouldn't
have
stayed thank you again is an iversary so
no self depreciating thoughts we're
going to mature our way out of it and
not talk about
[Music]
it thank you for keeping struggling for
us this far too and thank you for
accepting me even during my own
[Music]
struggles
very
thankful they're all just dying together
I mean not wrong thanks for the years of
fun moments with Yi you really help me
my energy support whole life I do
wherever I go my
[Music]
pleasure it's if anything it's an honor
for me
to actually help
you uh get into Hall life ID the fact
that I became someone's reason to
support the
girlies makes me happy you
[Music]
know
yeah
SC
[Music]
um can you please not make me cry right
now woman I'm not trying to make anyone
cry I'm just chilling I'm just
[Music]
talking
yeah you in a VIP place to Heaven be
sure of that I don't know hell looks
pretty
promising you're you guys are dismissing
the fact that I am a
[Music]
pervert too late I'm
balling isn't balling like that one
sport with lots of
pins
[Music]
can you die twice honestly I'm not sure
and I kind of don't want to test it
out I still have so many of you guys
that I haven't
[Music]
tked
foran so any projects in Minecraft I do
uh I kind of want to make uh I just want
to terraform the whole entire server
make it a bit prettier you know but
maybe not today I decided I just want to
chill because you know building those
kinds of stuffs on stream it
takes a lot of brain power and I don't
think that I can do
that at 3:00
a.m. honestly this is more fitting I
feel so too because I don't know it
feels like
we're coming back to Our
[Music]
Roots going to need a lot of resources
like britwood regardless uh best to get
stocked up now yeah might as well
right last one who used the Birch forest
was B on Senpai if I remember
correctly but to be hon but I don't know
will will people actually use the bridge
forest if wen't for a whole IDE in your
streams I don't think I'd have watched
Hall life or even thought about trying
to learn Indonesian
[Music]
really thank you for making me your
reason to learning Indonesian the return
of my tund wood goddess yo
shuya welcome back welcome back or were
you always there I'm
sorry and there's a lot of trees yeah
everyone has Farms now so that doesn't
really make uh the birch wood that
special
anymore it's not special to them but I
do know that it's a special place for
us did I hear
[Music]
something
I knew it I knew I heard
[Music]
something
girl can you please recp that time you
met OK in real life it made me laugh out
loud in the gym that time I met okai in
real life it was very unexpected like I
did hear that kiar Senpai and okai
Senpai might be visiting
but underscore bold it's like the word
might might is a word that's kind of
like maybe they'd
come they most probably will but there's
no guarantee right so to be honest I
wasn't expecting much because you know
um Hollow memb busy
I wouldn't want to get my hopes up but
then there she was
standing right in front of me with Kiara
Senpai right next to her Kar Senpai
introduced and she was like yeah so this
is aaya Senpai I got on my knees I think
I
[Music]
screamed and Oka Senpai had this VI do
do you know how people would just have
like this most huggable Aura ever
[Music]
that was me with Oka Senpai I saw her
and
my my very instincts told me
yo I need to hug this
woman yeah yeah yeah yeah but I kind of
held on until like the very last minute
we talked a little bit and I don't even
remember what we talked about I just
remembered her like laughing giggling
and it was the cutest [\h__\h] I've ever
seen and I think I've fallen in love it
was that lesbian ins side of me I was
like God [\h__\h] dang it if dating in
the company was actually allowed I might
literally just ask her
[Music]
out
yeah she said The L
[Music]
Word
pervert just that she was so pretty and
so kind and so charming and so beautiful
and magnificent and I wanted to hug her
maybe kiss her a little bit that turned
out dark so
fast I thought he told us before it was
allowed did I no no no it's not
um the company does not forbid dating
per se but the company does uh prohibit
dating uh staff or like fellow
co-workers you can't date anyone within
the company basically but if you're
dating someone then uh you know we don't
really care
basically
[Music]
any any any
any
because you know if you date uh a staff
or a fellow
liver it kind of disrupts your
professionality I I would
say yeah yeah
yeah so so
so not allow to fish off the company
Pier right yeah I gu guess that's that
that's a way to say
[Music]
it let think about it this way you guys
you guys have heard how some members
have the same manager
right what if a manager is actually
dating like one of the
uh what if the manager was dating like
one of the talents and then they kind of
not pay attention to the other talent
that they're responsible
for like that'd be pretty bad
[Music]
right
D professional wait is Risa
here wait really
[Music]
wait where is she but Ollie we're
married you see
narissa you're getting mixed signals
here we're not allowed to date
[Music]
co-workers they never said anything
about
marriage
she's backpedaling I don't backpedal I'm
telling the
truth loophole
found
like it um there was a reason to
I I asked narissa out to get married
right away and not dating you know
she's always five parel Universe
ahead you got a five head your way out
you know at least that's what Anna
taught me when we were playing
[Music]
chess because you're a speedrunner I
thought Nissa liked Kaya n likes
everyone I don't mind I I don't mind at
all as long as I am her
wife because happy wife happy life and
maybe more wife for me I don't know how
does the world H how does the how does
the rule work
[Music]
here yes o me and Oli build the ultimate
hero exactly I marry people Nissa marry
people we marry lots of people then we
share
yeah yeah
yeah wa hi what time is it at your place
right now it's it's 3:00 a.m. at my
place going
strong with the
uh what's it
called a
marathon sounds like a
[Music]
cult you're just
confused what Isa sha
o I'm still Shook at how there's
[Music]
no bisa like most of the fan art I see
of like raissa and B together it's like
mother and daughter kind of a you know
fan art I don't
know you guys hang out a lot yet you
know
we are je bird she is my baby oh it's
because bibo is a child
ol Ollie Marathon wi Marathon sounds so
good imagine the divorce papers I have
to sign right
[Music]
afterwards you call me pretty and you
tell every single girl that they're also
pretty you're not faithful well God dang
I'm sorry that everyone's
[Music]
hot I hate it so
much whenever I ask someone out then
they're like oh but you say that to
everyone olly you say that everyone's
pretty you're just you're
just
no I
mean have you took a look at Our member
poster have you took a look at this
super Expo
poster point to
me point to me at least one
person that does not look
[Music]
attractive God freaking
dang
[Music]
you're asking an impossible task I know
you can't find a not hot I mean I guess
you can find like a cute girl that's not
like hot hot but like everyone's so
attractive in their own way no one's
ugly I can't just come up to people and
say Hey Oh my my God you're so ugly
let's actually hang
[Music]
out we need was
that we need 43 wives only one got
dedicated wedding stream we need a
marathon so that the others don't
divorce you you're right this shows that
everyone needs to stop being pretty
obviously Ali is also really pretty
though but I don't know if she's able to
stop
that
[Music]
so Ollie can't love self well gosh
dangel I feel like if I could do that
there would be less zombies streams you
guys are basically my
therapist
[Music]
oh it's honey I thought there was slime
nearby tell us how you feel olly I
feel
liberated if you don't love yourself you
have to do it for you exactly I do not
need to
worry self
depreciation don't worry get yourself a
loving life and you won't have time to
actually think about it you still have
it you just won't think of it that
much the perfect
solution if you're too poor to get meds
or go to a therapist yeah get yourself a
wife hi Ali I heard n wed here so I hope
the
zoms uh enjoy our o magical spell oh
no not my zooming the cute
[Music]
crony let's
try XD
[Music]
meow
should I be sorry I mean uh no uh you
gave me Super Chat so
um yeah thank you so
[Music]
much thank
you wait Ollie does it so much cuter
than I do what the [\h__\h] my wife is
perf but you you know I still have your
your voice back by the way it was
fate it was
love it was Mutual simping I still have
it on my
soundboard I can't bring myself to
delete
[Music]
it
l
yeah you keep uh running that line by
accident in streams yeah I do that
sometimes it's really close to the
uh to the
Dono what what's it called the Dono
soundboards
[Music]
yeah
F the
[Music]
donos oops let me put my gat back stop
it I hear it
[Music]
everywhere I remember the time you got
it swapped with Z the one
yeah that
[Music]
happened
wait when's my Apex clap 4 a.m.
right
yes oh gosh I don't know if I have the
capacity to actually come up with
the with the G topic with the
[Music]
guys a
Al we'll be playing Apex
[Music]
together oh please uh the meme with Axel
was
enough
[Music]
oh yeah The Joint
Turney it'll be announced soon
[Music]
guys just wait for it I mean you guys
will see soon
enough I can't see anything because I am
not the
coordinator I am just a
participant
[Music]
not going to spoil
anything IO that Hol star is still full
on monkey SE monkey do what do you mean
monkey see monkey do what they do what
they
[Music]
do
so next alter is going to do a botu like
Axel I don't even know what Bots did to
give alter and I don't think I'm
obligated to give him one since he'll be
the one accompanying me and not the
other way
around no yawning wake
up
[Music]
was face while I was in the
toilet make him say the oo
Tex have myumi super chat again during
that
time Ollie stay awake don't follow the
light
grandma is that
[Music]
you Apex J clab will be a moment in
history this is just a warm up to
that no Wally don't cross the
[Music]
river I mean this is pretty hypnotizing
doing the same thing over and over again
want to burn some trees
no yes pollution and it causes global
warming we're going to cut them down one
by one and then replant them
[Music]
accordingly by the way are you going to
eat another burger after this I don't
know I'm still kind of full from the
last one I just
finished uh the last half maybe I'll eat
during the garic phone collab oh
shoot [\h__\h] I need to where the pan
tablet I think I think I'll have to end
the
uh what's it called
[Music]
again
stream 51
Club
ptic phone got my pen tablet so that we
can actually do gartic phone
[Music]
well
can tell Ollie's been really chilling
the stream since
she's sworn like three times already
sorry and I get super comfy I just end
up swearing a
[Music]
lot like that one stream I had with Hana
our Apex X
collab I was so comfy with Hana that I
just boo everything
out like if I sound
stupid that's
just I I would like to say that that's
just me but that's not true
because when I have like my guard
up I will be very 100 IQ you but if I'm
like super chill and relaxed I feel like
I get stupider by the
[Music]
second sorry I just got here can I know
why she have so much stream today uh
it's my anniversary my third
anniversary yeah and I wanted to
celebrate by doing my first ever
Marathon
stream because um I feel like I've done
a lot of to matis and I kind of want to
you
know take a break from
theatis and do something new I know it's
just a bunch of streams all at one time
but it's still
[Music]
something how are you liking Marathon
streaming definitely not my fourth day
there's a reason why I've been streaming
for 1 and a half half hour or two hours
max every single
[Music]
day because I would run out of things to
talk
about like during the sushi stream the
sushi party stream I don't
think I don't think he
had a very big vocabulary that one
[Music]
time it's good to push yourself
sometimes yeah just sometimes not all
the time sorry I fell asleep on the
sushi party that's okay because I kind
of got bored
also I'm going to game play with that's
quite challenging too you're focus on
gaming
[Music]
hard it's starting to survive the sushi
party
yeah your English is still really good
though Ollie you think I feel like my
vocabul my
vocabulary went downhill super uh like
big
time
[Music]
I'm really worried that I won't have
like any topics for the
next this is the seventh stream right in
the next three streams I'm I'm so scared
that I'll run out of topics I won't have
like anything to talk about especially
since
two of the streams are like collab
streams that's going to be
something oh wait or was it
four wait never mind four oh this is the
sixth stream right I received your
request and we will be there next stream
for yi thank you
myumi much
appreciated any new goals after 3
[Music]
years wow uh
the question took me a back actually
um not
really the projects that I'm doing right
now they're going to be my
biggest project that I'll do in a
while because
[Music]
honestly I feel like I've done it you
know I've done all of the things that I
can already
do I'll be real with you guys I'm not a
singer I'm not a dancer I'm not the
actual definition of
idol that you see on TV what
not so so like
[Music]
um I don't think there would I don't
think there will oh God sh surpris
me what even is an idol though at least
by definition in like
um Urban Dictionary it's someone who
sings Right someone who sings Dance
produces music I don't do any of those
sure I I I I make songs sometimes sure I
do covers sometimes but that's not my
main focus
actually
making an album is impossible for
[Music]
me
I don't think I can do a concert as well
I can't make a an album letting alone
singing live in a concert right like
sure I'll join like Hol Fest that's
without a doubt because you know that's
a valuable experience with like everyone
singing together
whatnot
but if I were to make my own concert I
don't I don't know if I'd do
that
[Music]
I don't
know you take any singing or dancing
classes do you have any Inspirations for
future activities I was about
to but there were they were three
attempts to do singing and dancing
lessons all three were cancelled due to
scheduling I'm already as busy as I am
so I literally don't know what else I
want to
[Music]
do you're not great but your voice is
good I like all your songs thank
you
how about H idid concert feels strange
not seeing you up there with Vivid ID I
mean surely I will join them
because it'll be our big moment but if
you're asking me what my next goals like
personal goals would it be solo concerts
would it be an album would it be more
collabs I don't think so I'm not that
type of
person I'm a lot of dissatisfied as is
you know for someone to be great I
believe that someone needs to be average
at something because if everyone is
great then no one is super get it like
[Music]
only
I will wholeheartedly accept the RO of
being
the the average one I guess you would
[Music]
say cuz face it there there's so many
talents in Hol life and I feel like
it'll only continue to
grow H
[Music]
life I will definitely be overlooked I
will only be a part of it but I will not
be the highlight of all
[Music]
life that is the fact that I've come to
uh accept I hope you guys can accept as
well because it's not about being
pessimistic it's about being
[Music]
realistic hard to disagree with that
you're so special to us Ali I do believe
that everyone is special in their own
way that goes the same uh the same goes
to you guys
too but there are a lot more special
people than
[Music]
me
no self-depreciating thoughts it's not
self-depreciating
it's realistic thoughts I've really come
to terms because the
more because you know it hurts I I I
make a lot
of
effort in a lot of my previous
projects
collabs
um covers
whatnot and expecting to have
recognition over the things that I do
expecting the rewards that would come
out of the things that I put so much
effort time sweat blood tears
into only to get nothing hurts you know
so right
now I'm kind of just expecting
nothing and except the fact that I won't
be getting as much you know know that
there will always be you guys who will
be cheering for me no matter
[Music]
what I'm so tired of feeling
disappointed Ed feeling that um most of
my
work goes in vain I don't get the
recognition if anything people look at
me side eyed and try to blame me for the
things that I didn't really
do it's a bitter feeling isn't it it's
bitter but
honestly after accepting This Bitter
fact it makes it a lot easier for me to
actually do my everyday um
my everyday schedules you know my
everyday
[Music]
routine
whatever happens we're always here for
you thank
[Music]
you the snow goose need not to bathe
itself in white neither you do but
yeah so so so so
so what are my plans in the
future I want to be the normal part of
Hall life I'll just be somewhere in the
middle if not I don't even mind if I
have to like be at the very
bottom if one way or another I can
contribute to Hol life who saved me and
talents who actually made my days also
this as bright as I make your days as
bright this then that's okay with
me as long as I'm contributing you
know normal said the crazy one that's
the thing I feel like the crazy name
serves no purpose anymore
because you know the reason why I kind
of stopped the crazy gimmick was
that a lot of the I don't want to blame
anyone
but a lot of the talents start Ed
adopting their own version of crazy and
a lot of people started like
comparing it to mine and it got a little
bit tiring I didn't like it being
compared to is the worst thing ever
which is
why I really did come to terms to being
the average
[Music]
one yeah only
for
like no matter how much you guys tell me
Ollie just need to ignore these These
are trolls these are
haters they don't know what they're
talking about and we think you're great
like I know but sometimes there are just
a few of them that manage to
slip as disappointing as it is and
um to avoid getting h a lot more I just
tried to stay away from
[Music]
it so how do you handle them most of the
time I do ignore
them so there will be days where I just
can't ignore
[Music]
them
yeah
[Music]
okay get the positive mentality maybe
the hardest part to be a streamer it is
[Music]
hard a lot of stuff to
consider what to
bring how to improve
what to say how to
[Music]
react
ignoring giving feedback
whatnot it might seem simple but those
things are pretty uh
difficult I would
[Music]
say
all you don't say thaty just lack
sleep I mean we are doing a marathon so
I guess that would make
[Music]
sense the haters aren't worth listening
they just drain our energy
true very
true reduce pain now on it realism maybe
it's okay to have a bit of Hope once in
a while
I'd rather not again
um would rather not have hope at all
then have that hope
[Music]
shattered if we can somehow prevent the
problem
then let's just prevent it all together
you
[Music]
know on 3 years uh my sweet beautiful
zombie princess Alli just focus on being
the best Ali can be yeah that's what I'm
going to
do I'll just keep doing my
best if my best isn't
enough for everyone then it should
probably be enough for some people
[Music]
right
yeah
Reda just a
moment uh it is my belief that you're me
meant to be a late bloomer they will
actually come to you while you're you'll
rise to Super and even if you'll never
be perfect no one is you if you're in
the bottom then so am I and everyone
here and I'm proud to be standing here
with you in the Rock Bottom
h d you're making me tear up like
actually trying not to cry it's very
[Music]
hard thank you for believing
that
[Music]
I feel like I'm upgrading but like
backwards
downgrading
yeah yeah
yeah my Japanese got
worse I can't stream as long as I used
to I can't scream as much as I used
[Music]
to times like this I'd like to give
advice to you to practice [\h__\h] it we
ball
thank
[Music]
you your Japanese got worse B English
got
worse
yo she got us you can't yo my daughter
got a straight bullet out of that you
can't do
that
[Music]
ba is hollow JP now 100%
damn no she admitted herself oh
no 20 minutes by the way
okay I might have to dip within the 10
[Music]
minutes yeah yeah yeah like 10 minutes
before for the next stream I might have
to
[Music]
dip Rex's whole ID gen zero I
know I
know I made sure that he turned into
[Music]
one
there was an exchange uh B became D and
Miko became
Ian Ali
Ian no I'm I'm Hollow
[Music]
DP stands for
disappointment oh no the self
depreciating is coming
[Music]
again
sorry I'll
stop Bad Zombie do it in zomie
sorry and that people was a a free trial
to the zombly
experience m
[Music]
H
right still have 15 more minutes should
we chop more
trees is that even a question
OE oh is this a still here
Hol D standing for a hollow deserving of
the world oh
shush bet you're in it
[Music]
too it's in the
rler that's out El so
[Music]
holiday not stop i' say you're part of
Holan
[Music]
personally sticking out your God for oh
gosh it's
[Music]
everywhere thanks for working hard I I
don't have the words to express my
thoughts but I wish nothing would the
best for you I'm sure I'll disom feel
the same way thank you
CS SEO
[Music]
Crocs thank
you the Gat will be over soon
[Music]
tit
B Bo attack is coming
stop and then the bow
[Music]
bow let me be your
Shori sticking out your account for
AR all Isler that sounds so it doesn't C
off the tongue as well as
nisler all
is no that title is meant for you
[Music]
baby you're so bow
B
gosh oh no it's developing into ID
please we no
no thankfully deci is not that long
enough to actually contain all nine
[Music]
members taking out your God for all is
you're so re you're so Mo this want to
be your Yi oh yo it fit it fits the uh
1.5
[Music]
damn
1.5 no
Isa now we just need bio to dub
it it's the way bio sings it I swear I
tried listening to the original and I
despised it
so I was like no this is not it
[Music]
what
Kiara in the
[Applause]
ks yo welcome to the
stream thank goodness you guys you guys
came in at the right time if you guys
came in earlier it would have been an
existential crisis welcome carison pie
thank you so much for coming to the
stream narissa your wife's here I think
she's here to pick you
up welcome welcome welcome to the
Alon it is a stream marathon where I
crazy your Oli hold in cation of my
third anniversary we're about to uh end
the stream soon uh I have a collab an
apex collab within 10 minutes so I think
I'll be dipping in five and see you guys
then
yeah
yeah yeah yeah we we
just we were just cleaning up the uh the
Birch Forest I don't know if you guys
have ever seen it before it's from the
resource
server Apex no another raid yeah I'll be
I hope you guys don't
[Music]
mind nor said huh n said has
successfully supplanted Moria ki's wife
eh
[Music]
n have you guys ever heard Steve Harvey
said n before I don't I don't I don't
know if it's like
a I'm not sure if that's an
AI but hearing Steve Harvey going
n is like the best thing in the
[Music]
world that's a famous sound bite I've
seen that clip yeah
wait is real oh I haven't it's so it's
really nice
n the way he says it is just so chef's
kiss let's go back to the to the shared
server check the
[Music]
M look here
oh
sorry wasn't
[Music]
bring by oh
ohc since you're ending and I can't be
in the rest of your Marathon I just
wanted to say congratulations on your
anniversary and you're so great you work
so hard and I think you're a great assd
whole life don't be sad or don't be like
unmotivated or whatever like don't don't
don't let anything break your heart or
whatever cuz you're great and you
deserve lots of love and support you're
the best and I really really enjoy your
energy and everything you bring to whole
life without you it would be so dark and
so sad sometimes so keep your head up
and fight though Ollie my
angel you can't say
that
I have to say it I have four more
streams I'm going to be a crying mess
I'm trying to hold them
together well I don't know I heard you
were pretty like emotional before I
raided you so you're not really holding
it together are you but that's okay you
can you can show your emotions it's fine
I think you know we're in the end we're
all just you know something like humans
and we all have feelings and you know
especially when we work so hard
entertaining people people and trying to
do our best and be original and be be
you know something something interesting
oh and always be streaming ourselves and
pouring our hearts out it's like it's
normal to be vulnerable so it's
understandable and you just keep on
being you and I think that's the best
way to
go I need to take you out when visit in
you want to kill me don't take me out no
no not
not
it's okay I know what you
mean yeah I would love to meet you again
always sometime
soon yeah maybe maybe this time I'll be
the one paying a visit oh yeah anytime
yo please come on a trip to Europe or
just come to Austria doesn't matter I'm
always welcoming you with open arms
here let's go but I also I I I want to
go to Indonesia and 2024 again so maybe
you can be part of that because I me and
uh Cy we kind of wanted to say like to
all ID members hey who wants to go to
Bali with us Bali I I know like the
perfect um activity that we can all do
together pillow fight no uh
rafting rafting yeah wa rafting is like
pretty
like
chaotic no
um uh not not so much in the rivers of
Bali yeah but that sounds amazing
actually oh my God is that something you
do in Bali like normally Well normally
you would go to the beach but you know
beaches are so overrated so you would
want to go to the rivers and
[Music]
mountains well generally I would see it
as a Beach vacation but we can certainly
go rafting on one day yeah
yeah I never did that before you you did
it before yeah yeah yeah yeah it's super
fun oh my god oh wait actually I
shouldn't keep you too long you have an
apex collab right yeah no but that's
okay it means a lot that I actually came
into call I was like Oh shoot what you
want to call I I was so surprised I was
like huh N I just wanted to talk to you
and you seemed like you know available
so I'll I'll uh visit you in valy or you
visit me in Austria and um I I hope
you'll stay in whole life for much much
longer because someone like you can not
be replaced
only I'll have to mute myself super
quick after
this it's all good all you're the best
and have fun with the rest of your
Marathon
G thank
you bless you and um bless you rest well
okay you too you too don't overwork
yourself okay I
won't okay bye-bye I'll take my leave
bye-bye see oh okay there she goes I
love her I I didn't I I didn't get to
say that I love her but hopefully she
hears it she knows she knows no I I
promised K senpi that one time that I
wanted to make like an essay I keep
having to revamp it because she's just
so amazing I hear now I love you so much
uh kison bye oh all right and with that
I'll have to end the stream I have to
get ready for the collab no actually I
have to cry first then get ready for the
collab I'm holding it together you guys
can't see it but the tears I can't see
anything in front of me it's all
wobbly the the the water's covering my
eyes so I'mma ball real quick thank you
kison
by for calling means a lot needed to
hear that and also a big shout out to
Nissa too
for hearing me ramble the whole
time hopefully that that wasn't too much
of a emotional roll coaster for you guys
all right so anyway see you guys on the
next stream we'll be redirecting so
[Music]
bye-bye I mean see you
guys
[Applause]
a