[Music]
every day
a great Wanderer
[Music]
retrospective
sleep talking
breath
[Music]
hinatory
heart Challenger
[Music]
Sparks
favorite night
[Music]
let me know
do you
love hate all the same if you don't play
that again
[Music]
first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
the great Wanderer
the ground
at times retrospective
[Music]
my baby
[Laughter]
[Music]
why are you making weird noises
sorry I'm like um
I'm confused
um um I'm still in a bed at the moment
in my head oh you know honestly same
um so I get it I get it second collab
already so awkward no no no no no no
no well it's because I I heard kiwawa's
feelings because I didn't marry her
first yeah that's honestly quite
insulting what went down there but
sorry it's okay it's nice to see Ollie
happy you know every once in a while
so what are we doing today now we stop
you Wawa some fires being so so kind
just to show me around the en server yes
I'm very excited I've woken up in this
spirited away-esque Minecraft area and
I'm scared yeah uh I I I I I am I would
say one of the best tour guides when it
comes to showing around the en server I
was a bit oh sorry I need to turn on
something because I was a bit shocked to
hear that you girls didn't end up doing
anything yes
because this was planned to be you know
after you already saw maybe the Japan
area
um but you know what it is it's okay it
just means I'll be a pro to show the
Advent girls
oh yeah you could show them around if
you remember so take notes okay okay
well well well we have two povs by the
way we have narissa streaming and kiwawa
streaming so I don't know I think we're
still stay together all the time but you
know yes
[Music]
who do I spy with my little eye where is
she
gonna come through the tunnel
I only see your name tag and it's
already so beautiful I can see yours too
wow wow wow
this is like a blind date
hi nice to meet you
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
no don't look at this one directly no
I'm shy
it's time it's time to throw off your
shyness
stood away Kiwa Senpai oh no oh no oh
wow oh you're so beautiful just as
beautiful as the day I lost you
oh so cute so pretty yeah
oh my God so many boxes wow you're wow
thank you here's the fox say too I like
your little cave no my my what my cave
your cave oh wait am I wearing the
sports day outfit right now no I'm not
oh no I am the the ideas sports day
outfit
they're so cute wow your hair is so long
yeah you're you're black outfit it's
just oh it's so fashionable so cool
black is slimming you know
um wait do I
[Music]
wearing you know I don't know did
anybody make a Minecraft skin of my of
your new skin yes they did
wait let me let me see if I can find it
if you have it I can quickly change it
then we'll look better together
um yeah yeah give me give me give me one
second it shouldn't take me too too long
to find it okay here here here here here
music I'm linking it to you
oh my God yeah he made he made all of
Advent too so we all except for she
already used them yesterday oh what did
she would use she already used a
different fan-made one oh okay I thought
maybe she just used a standard Minecraft
it's just a PNG right yep you download
the PNG and then you go to the
minecraft.com there's a place to edit
your skins there
I do it in the just in the game like you
can do it in the game like I mean you
have to go to the starting screen but
yeah one moment I'll I'll get I'll leave
you okay I will stay I will stay locked
up wait can you do it here too no that's
not it okay guys one moment
this is should be easy Minecraft
launcher yeah
you can do it in the game what
now in the laundry you guys mean the
launcher too right yeah because there's
a skin thingy here now I'm gonna be
walking in a different skin
uh OPG outfit did you get the joke
hey watch out I'm gonna be walking in a
different skin I'm a skin walker
wow wow it looks so wow I know I'm
excited to see it oh okay all right I'm
logging back into the game
and then we're gonna be more matching
you know what I'm I'm actually yeah I I
said if I collab with noisa I want to
wear my RPG outfit and I'm such a coward
for not doing it no no you didn't even
know it existed until just now
true I only saw actually when I was
scrolling endlessly through Twitter I
think I saw a like a Minecraft
screenshot of you and me together in
those outfits and I was like it where
where did they get that from Nani
look at my Senpai look at her her cool
outfit
let's take a look to the with them
resizing Minecraft window I love that
you can size the Minecraft window
however you like oh
[Music]
you know uh Minecraft uh server whole
live server etiquette when somebody logs
in you try to greet them ideally with
their own greeting if you know it it's
often just like something fun with
something of their name oh my god oh wow
oh
we are so cute we are
cool game screen too big is it are you
sure I don't think so I think this is
ideal ah wait never mind yeah it's it's
that it doesn't matter oh it doesn't
matter
no I guess like it's so weird because
this layout kind of uh
um
okay I will I will use this instead
we're holding hands
holding hands oh no that's that's that
legal right I can't yes
foreign
guys you will
you will have to ah
okay I am
resizing everything sorry you can you
can look at my beautiful
beautiful I'm checking you out
[Music]
did you
did you so freaking cute
my cute Amelia Watson I love you sorry
you have to hear that I love someone
else but I I'm I understand I know you
have other women you also love
very much so okay well we are here at
the beginning I'm gonna give you a tour
it's gonna be a long one probably let's
go through here
left or right
um uh left wrong answer this side okay
you could if you want right afterwards
here a little opinion about the server
but the reason why I chose this side is
because we're gonna go over here
okay
to my shrine trying to build before
yeah
didn't I I built it with mumaya and mine
was quite impressed um
it's a typical
Shrine where uh I'm gonna take this
it's typical Japanese Shrine
we are gonna you know do our visitation
come up here
okay I took a stick oh give it to me
you took it from the wall right yeah
yeah okay I threw it I threw it I threw
a ding dong
all right
good job make a wish
[Music]
I know exactly what you're wishing
something about marrying me how did you
know but you gotta wait because you're
currently still legally bound to uh
someone else right
okay no no unless unless you ask you
know do you know what this is no no
okay so you push the button right click
it what number does it say one ah
yeah that means you don't have to put it
up there because you only put your bad
fortunes up there
okay yeah I see other ones up here that
are one what are people thinking uh they
don't understand well yeah they don't
understand
because they're not being Guided by
Yours Truly they didn't oh they just
didn't read the sign because they can't
read
I'm gonna clean up here because I'm the
shrine Maiden hey
pretty Shrine mating
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
because of everyone at least know that
song but did you want no I don't know
but did you want it I've seen some
scenes but at the time it was when anime
it wasn't it wasn't available for me to
watch it at the time but you know the
song I need to watch it though I know I
saw a picture of Carnegie recently and I
was like [\h__\h] man I still need to know
what this show is about it's so cute
unfortunately it never got continued but
it's still worth watching it in my
opinion so this area
um was built quite late in the
um second
Century of and and uh
so far girl stay back okay okay
it was built in the year 2000 at this
year this this area was built in the
year I believe um 2022.
um as a project for
um connecting our world with the
Japanese world I think and to impress
them in uh you know a way that would
make them feel very comfortable and
welcomed and this big tower that you see
on your right hand side that goes all
the way up to the sky you know what that
is
even see the planets that you captured
inside her balls yeah it goes up really
high it's really beautiful in the
nighttime especially over here we have a
little Bakery if you're hungry this
Bakery was built by um
maybe maybe
I don't know actually
why is it sparkling here
so would you would you would you like
something out of the bakery we have
cookies we have pumpkin awesome
because she loves bread
[Music]
um well now I feel like I shouldn't take
it of course you should oh I took I
think I read from here oh good job oh
from the sign girl you gotta stop taking
things from signs
okay okay yeah good good okay I'll take
I'll take the cookie then enjoy did you
take it
[Laughter]
oh my God this whole area basically was
built um you know during a certain time
here's a little picnic that is really
cute oh my God yeah the en members tried
their best to get up to
um Japanese server level we got pretty
close this area is the most beautiful
thing we ever built on the server
um over here is what is this this is new
this this I never went inside here what
the hell is this new it's a farm
yeah I guess so oh this is this is
Summer's house what I never went inside
eh
Nani is actually really beautiful in
here oh my God I know is it for sale I
guess not I would buy it totally but
yeah lots of beautiful plants and I'm
behind it of course is
yeah the tower well that makes sense not
Tower should we go up yeah okay I I want
to it's gonna be a little a little walk
oh actually quite a bit we should fly
but you don't have a oh [\h__\h] no I can't
fly
you don't have you can't fly that is
difficult well then let's just admire it
from below for now okay I don't know
walking up there I tried it once what
the [\h__\h] are you doing
alone
okay oh sorry I think that hit you too
it's okay I I like it so okay
um Let me let me go back into the middle
we should go and cry in a circle all we
got right that was a zombie it only got
jealous
run away fast because that's a creeper
and he's gonna blow up everything oh if
he touches you
let's get running to safety very good
very good okay how good are you actually
at playing Minecraft
um
I've never played survival mode really
so I'm excited to start playing it oh
wow okay yeah I usually like to build
like Hobbit houses watching YouTube
guides that's so nice I know it's so
lame I'm so late no this is lame what
the [\h__\h] I love I wanted to build a
hobbit house before but never really was
I was always too lazy well up here is
the Onsen
Dad I think mainly Cali was building but
she may have had help yeah you know
beautiful onset she did a great job here
you know it's steaming piping hot wow
just like a real Onsen I love that a
decent view to Amish tits
too do you see Amish tits I I do I do
actually good view right yeah I thought
they were arms
um oh if you fought those but then
what's that that's that she's holding
the sign with her ears
I thought it was on her head I thought
it was balancing
oh it's okay it's okay over here we have
another little bath open open bath yeah
yeah open air I guess because this looks
very open
wow all of a sudden the snow narissa
have you been to an Onsen in the snow no
[\h__\h] that creeper
no no no admittance for creepers
can he enter uh he's waiting okay no he
can't enter very good very very
uh good protection here and the nice
rest area too we could sleep actually
shall we
yes okay Minecraft
um
etiquette number two when you want to
sleep and there's someone else in the
server but they don't know that you're
trying to sleep right dead in the chat
and you're in a position where you
currently can't sleep just leave the
server for a moment however if you're in
the en server but somebody like in this
area but somebody on the other side like
on the Japanese side is writing that it
doesn't affect you so you can stay you
don't have to go to sleep
okay so over here there's a bit more and
I think there was a like a hot hot room
over here uh there's no this is just oh
wait there's just a we meet on the
that's a that's a choice how can you do
this I didn't know you can put them in
the ground like that didn't neither
where's the where's that hot room down
down
hot room hot room wasn't there this hot
room
it's a what it's an unlit campfire
[Music]
you can put food on the cat is that a
new thing
or has that been a thing all along
because I didn't know about it what the
hell wow okay we should have slept over
here so we could have stopped side by
side yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
yeah I can't even though I've been
inside before I can't find the entrance
anymore whatever we have so much to look
at let's go let's go
[Music]
are you are you are you yeah keep up
with me good good let's walk under this
beautiful arch of plants
and then over here we have some
playground that's really cute
what was your favorite thing as a child
to play with as a playground
it's a really good question
um
I like to treat the whole thing as one
big obstacle course yeah uh so but I
would I would pretend that I was a ninja
running away from
um
[Music]
I was pretending to be a witch always
because my my Charmed influence was too
strong so I was like oh yeah it used to
be on Rollerblades a lot uh with my
friends and then yeah like all around
the area and like act as if we have
magic powers and we would decide who has
which like I would have like for example
Pipers the other one would have proves I
loved Charmed growing up man
oh that explains the Naruto craze right
yeah ninjas
yeah well Naruto may have been the
reason why I was doing that but um my
favorite thing so I couldn't use you
know the like the little bars that you
just slid down I could not do that the
little box
yeah yeah yeah I couldn't do them but I
really I really liked when there were
like platforms you could jump to and
from or like the rope climbing wall type
things you know what I mean yeah yeah so
I climbing walls yeah but those are kind
of I feel like they're kind of rare oh
look at
about oh my God
killed cheese come a bit closer to me
it's so cute oh wow oh
oh
good let's go Let's Go
Daddy Raiders oh hello okay follow me we
start we're getting out of the
playgrounds because we're adults okay
oh are you
are you I just reminded myself you know
when I started playing Minecraft
um it was the first time I ever played
Minecraft when I played it on stream in
2020 oh my God 2020 and I was like so
set on playing it in third person
you're crazy
but it just felt right to me and people
kept on bugging me about please play it
in the first person please play it in
the first person yeah eventually I
changed but are you in first person
right now
boring boring
good old times okay just can't move
around well on that perspective yeah I
guess
um over here is a museum
yeah please enter free entry
um the watch 2020 until I don't know I
don't know what watch that is
specifically maybe I'm his watch kfb's
first employee oh oh my God
from 2021 flower do you know that Meme
blue no explain it oh it was when like
Council was playing uh Minecraft and
they were building something and then um
somebody just you know put a flower
somewhere I guess in the building and
and then crony was like a flower but she
just said it normally but everybody was
like oh my God you say it like a robot
and so beautiful and then everybody kept
repeating it and then yeah it became a
meme flower can you say it like that
flower whoa yeah that's pretty good A
bit more robotic maybe like TTS
flower oh you sounded romantic to me
thanks to Minecraft beautiful
thanks to Discord I mean can you say it
again again
flower oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah
you should you need to collab with crony
at some point I know I need to bug her I
need to be like coronini
call it she loves it
okay here we have Shion and gura Baku
membrane uh-huh they they got a membrane
together against beautiful rip Pizza
okay I don't know about that
sana's first big big bad big
[Music]
more fish this fish is unnamed
interesting we don't know exactly where
it came from this is a deadbeat
um in a fortune cookie
[Music]
I don't know if it's really a fortune
cookie but somehow yeah you know yeah
yeah I see it yeah tiniest deadbeats
scaled up about 100 times for your
Delight please enjoy
amazing outside I don't know that
there's not really it's pretty though
it's pretty but nothing yeah nothing
showcased here besides water maybe this
is water that was captured from the hole
that we built in our first Minecraft
stream I don't know who knows it's gross
bath water
ah oh it's very welcome
[Music]
you know how to sprint right yep good
wonderful that's how I've been keeping
up with you this is watermelon house I
think if you ever need a food like this
is an easy one to think of although
watermelons are not very good to fill in
your stomach but there's like always an
overflow of watermelon so feel free to
take some you know I will take a lot do
it do it
is it automatically like refill itself
yeah what's happening yes you hear the
the
underneath how uh it's like a mechanism
under there yeah if you want to get
deeper into the Minecraft
mechanisms this is probably one you
might learn it's a farm Redstone magic
yeah I never really
melons
nothing really
you can you can collect anything make a
farm out of anything really no no don't
look at don't look at his eyes okay
never never look at enderman's eyes why
because did you just look at
oh my God
oh my God oh my God
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God so when did they kill you when
you look at them
why does she do that Roofing her tell
her not to stop
trying to not pick up all my items there
I'm I'm coming right away oh wait I'll
wait for you oh my God I didn't have I
didn't have my armor on and I died even
though I even used the totem I was
wearing a totem and the totem is
supposed to protect you from death once
and then it goes away oh but yeah he
killed me right afterwards anyway okay
so what did you have in your inventory
besides watermelons all this stuff right
here okay good here's uh more
watermelons you took a lot of
watermelons
I'm really hungry I'm Gonna Keep On
Coming back to me
pick a mom you need to you need to move
I can't take it okay one more uh okay
okay okay okay now it went back to me
that's okay wait wait wait wait it's
fine okay
[Music]
okay
so yeah roughly we've seen this area now
actually oh I still remember this this
area
um is actually where we would first
spawn when we first entered the the
server when it was empty and it was like
you know
let me put on some armor because I'm in
trouble when you're around
it was uh yeah nothing was here only
trees and such and then from here
um I think the first ones were maybe me
and Cali I think we started separately
and we would just um walk around through
these trees trying to find a good spot
to set Camp yeah
um I had oh yeah this just doesn't look
like this
land tunnel but uh I think it we we will
check out good as house elsewhere come
out
okay
I feel like I'm running down that
endless call in uh Mario 64. you know
what I'm talking about stay on the
staircase I love that yeah okay are
there currently any cards here
no cart
no car
um fine we'll walk because I want to
stop in the middle anyway
okay oh Burger House oh yeah right who
made the Burger House again the
watermelon thing was made by Iris the
Burger House I think I remember that but
made the Burger House oh my God
oh you gotta you gotta like the the best
thing is to Sprint and jump at the same
time here yeah don't worry I'm keeping
up with you but there do be the trees
the trees Sal this is the the train that
will bring you to the main area where
myth built all their homes and in
between we are passing through several
crotches of ladies I've noticed yeah I
like that I love that it's called the
pantsu express yes it was a
collaboration of efforts of many people
I see but here I built for some reason I
decided to build it here is my frog a
house
again what did I call them oh my God
what were their names
oh my God they're so aflop are there and
then it's there flip and flop
the flip it fluff
y I thank you
they are I didn't know there were frogs
on Minecraft yeah they're a relatively
new feature I went out to get them in
the wilderness and it was quite a quest
they're pretty rare but I actually ended
up finding them quite easily and then
you look at you you have to breed them
so I breeded with them I brought them
yeah I love them and then these these
beautiful
um leaves and everything all of these
are also pretty like new uh oh yeah
they're pretty I know can I put this
somewhere
um
no okay okay now carefully we go outside
by pushing the button
[Music]
double door system for extra safety for
the frogs yeah don't want to lose them
yes I love my frogs I love frogs I love
friends that we said before and love
frogs don't you love frogs
um I actually do like frogs but I'm a
little scared to touch them like in in
person well I even kissed a frog in real
life no
I kissed a frog and I liked it you are
froggy Wawa
whether or not froggy Wawa is me or if
they're separate entities is something
that you know is very vaguely except for
debate yeah
yeah well let's not
foggy maybe my spirit animal uh here if
you're ever in need for a bed you can
steal one from it's not stealing it's
like you know prepared for newcomers
through server
[Music]
do you have a bag light blue no
is light blue your favorite color
I like blue the best blue blue is my
favorite color okay why is it not Orange
foreign
for some reason to make our area
prettier and she very much did she made
this this whole like rainbow bridge and
then this entrance over here with the
with the flowers and the water the
little ponds The Path all the paffing is
made by her
you made this ring uh to fight and oh
circles oh circles is yeah in cave
history quite important but uh not not
important in in general uh history so
okay can't people be mad but yeah
um not worth explaining I mean he was a
horse that I once left behind and people
have told me for two years straight to
bring him back and I was like there's no
way that Circle still exists and then
two years later I went on a search for
him in the in the desert like millions
of miles away
so I brought him back isn't that
incredible that is incredible yeah I
don't know
but like for Minecraft when you when you
lose something as long as you don't go
like as long as you're not close to the
area it will not like really load it so
you can even find what you lost like two
years later yeah sniffer
this is a really new animal
what is this thing it sniffs in the
ground and finds you stuff oh like like
oh he's kind of ugly I love him
this is his title form they also have a
child form which is a bit smaller he's
sniffing me yeah his name is Gooba
yeah I still need to make him like a a
house a proper house how long did it
take you to find this thing
oh quite a while yeah because I had to
go diving I think to like find an egg
and then I had to bring this bag here
but the egg finding the egg is like wow
difficult
but he's worth it he's cute he looks so
funny
he's a funny looking guy here Marissa
this is the legendary first home of
takanasi Kiara ignore that ignore that
okay Okay Legendary first home of
takanasikara and originally Calliope
Mori our oh our beautiful
um first house that we built when we
first settled in our first Minecraft
stream we said this is the area this is
where we're gonna build all the miffings
and we said we're gonna live together
and we're gonna do regular Minecraft
streams after that we never did regular
Minecraft streams and she moved out so
that's dance
my bed yeah so I'm just my pressure
using this as my house even though I
built a proper house later on but yeah I
still stay in here meow this is a cat
this is a bed if you want nobody Larissa
[Music]
yes
please you don't have to tell me twice
wait I need to remember how to play
Minecraft
you can do it put it in your yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yay I'm Ruby with my simple
I see a future where I log into
Minecraft each time I see the bed coming
closer to mine for some reason I'm
wondering why
what a weird thing to happen yeah it was
so strange so
um I can I can make some drawers free
for you maybe I can I can set up your
own drawers maybe in the future I can
I'll make you some space
it's okay so oh this um oh this place
isn't very pretty right but you know
it's very functional but I ended up I
built it I built a an actual house
um chicken house yeah but I don't use it
but let's take a look
you have to press the button here I'll
press it for you come in come in
welcome welcome
[Music]
I have a couch that is out of marble
very comfortable
I'm sure looking at the other creeper uh
explosion about to happen a kitchen
makeshift kitchen tried my best here and
then there's a second floor press button
go out
good job I did it
oh oh wait thank you for letting me use
Elijah is this one I think so
oh I don't remember that there were
emeralds in there no it's all cool
emeralds
and some slime yeah and I I never have
slime when I need it second floor is
bedroom and and armor room
um
I'm coming oh he's coming
okay good job this bed is non-functional
we can only role play on it
what kind of role play would you like to
do Key Well the world Planet you're
doing like World of Warcraft
um yeah I have some storage stuff that I
always forget about here
what the hell are these what oh there's
a shocker boxes
[Laughter]
I'm gonna steal your stuff I'm gonna
steal your diamond sword and uh yeah
sure I guess fine I probably really I
probably won't know what's missing so
which one are you taking
oh cover her in diamonds
my reputation I just wow
that looks on you like
um like uh what do you call the American
Football
um
because of the shoulder pads being huge
on you
oh my God look at the B
yeah
oh no it's not their own purpose it's
been stuck forever
I didn't even do it that's so mean of
you
you know what this is
the ender dragon head yeah I'm just
storing it here
yeah yeah this is a nice view from my
balcony
yeah on the you know on the right side
we see a whole life sign with a ice path
you see the big bridge no I don't know
if you can see that far I can see it not
we're not where it leads but I can see
the ice bridge that bridge leads to
Phoenix Sun where we'll be going later
and yeah well I'll show you everything
that you can see here because I'm very
knowledgeable especially about all the
myth houses and all that so let's yeah
oh it looks dangerous yeah it hurts a
bit
but you know you should know how it
feels as an angel falling from the sky
yes thank you
down here is my neighbor Wilson
you know my Wilson she has this like
really dark bridge but then her house is
so so pretty and natural yeah she needs
to clean up the front of all these
Amazon deliveries her front porch is
like
yeah too much going on here or Ina
Senpai attacks this seems like it's from
a long time ago
it could be
come in she has very many animals so if
you have allergies then oh this is not
the place
oh my God I don't know what her problem
is it's like a what do you call people
who keep things
too many things yeah she's an animal
hoarder basically
clearly crazy but she built her house
like a like a tree
um house basically
so at the very top you know depending on
the seasons you will have different uh
Tree Top but oh my God she some you know
out of the myth people she together with
Anna she's like the one who has like
cool stuff like she will she will focus
on like potions and other cool things
while Anna will focus on like red uh
Stone things and all that so yeah she
has she's she has the cool stuff when
when you're thinking of something that
you need chances are Ina who has it
maybe but that's more like back in the
day I guess you girls could probably
very much rely on Japanese server all
the time if you want up here is her
Observatory or so I guess
oh there was an incident when her tree
burnt before
and since then she put uh this glass
over it to protect it
smart yeah man it really has history
doesn't it and the axolotls too yeah I
just got Excellence here I don't know
why they want to go into the corner
I feel bad for them
they're they're looking for something
the brown ones look like they're dying
is that a normal color for them yeah
axolotls have a wide range of colors
yeah I know but the brown not not blue
Brown is not all damn they look like
they're like dehydrated
oh well they look like for dirty it is
[Music]
okay that part I don't understand did
she help with this tree
maybe you probably know there's some
people who keep track of every Minecraft
stream specifically Minecraft yeah
really
visited ah okay okay so she didn't help
where are you
I'm behind you okay let's go down let's
go it's like they they merged into one
animal okay we're leaving in a house
uh on her
um left side here we have her farm for
all kinds of animals I don't think it's
really being used much but what she
really like one thing that she made that
really helped us on the server for a
long time was the wolf Farm it's pretty
naked right now in fact what though yeah
looking for a specific color just come
back here and then check out the sheeps
and the chests underneath
and you'll surely find the right color
this is not all the possible colors as
far as I know unless she extended it
recently
just a lot of them yeah a lot of them
there's still some more possibilities I
think there's here some grapes
yeah all these grave is here too so is
suppose now that you're married you're
supposed to put your grave next to her
eventually oh no I'm fine by the time
you won't be married anymore right uh
yeah I don't I don't plan to die so if
you look behind you now and you look up
to the sky you see sandwiches
that was actually
um as history says
or actually might be within hollow life
English unless it recently changed uh
the longest recorded
one-on-one or even
not even one-on-one collab stream to
date in Ian it was a way too long
collapse stream to build this [\h__\h] how
long it's now the second longest six
hours oh my God yeah we were going a bit
crazy towards the end building this but
is it it is a monument because of our
um song cover that we did I kotoba on my
channel beautiful
[Music]
[Laughter]
and wait I'm should we go
this is I think is it our first
anniversary cake
it does look like a cake now I'm hungry
I just I'm pretty sure it's the first
year because it feels like it was oh no
wait wait it's not first anniversary
it's a Christmas tree Christmas
Christmas tree Christmas cake Christmas
20 20. oh my God
that's even long ago that's that's
barely enough that we debuted
yeah I'm nom nom nom nom nom nom we
built that and and the tree I guess we
decorated this tree beautiful it's still
standing still Christmas you know no
problem to keep up your Christmas tree
forever right yeah are you one of those
people kiwawa
sometimes in some years yes in other
words can you not climb up the Christmas
tree like a cat
come down here
[Laughter]
no I'm a star I'm a star Senpai never so
ravencraft you are coming down here at
once now okay I'm counting five okay
wait wait wait
yeah okay okay you better not be doing
that again okay okay give me a heart
attack you're giving away a heart attack
um okay in the middle by the way this is
our uh never portal our Mania portal
um we we could uh end up checking
something out in there too a little bit
later
[Music]
just chose a really really cool extra
special location in the water and built
herself a nice little Cozy home here
it's a bit chaotic looking and and you
know she sleeps on the grass basically
but you know it's her thing she likes
nature number one
Omega Gosling
I am
the way did you take like one at least
did I get her free why is this like mama
she probably just wants to make her own
frogs or so fun
I can't believe it
that is heartbreaking
oh I put moss and and the frogs in there
and she only took the Moss just Moss
Enthusiast yeah she also has like trees
here
which is cool yeah very nature muchos
nature the frogs are still waiting and
yeah she has like farms and stuff here
hidden uh this and that it's confusing
like I miss houses confusing me
pretty cute though yeah and it leads
straight into our top this is the famous
title
I'm getting PTSD wait don't go
away come on
okay I need to put you on a leash
um this tunnel
and out in whole life English and whole
life myth equal in that case
um first ever Minecraft don't
we're not going
and our first ever Minecraft collab
gouda took the lead I think the thing is
like we were doing weekly group collabs
and
um at some point uh it was good as turn
because I think we had it always on
somewhere somebody's Channel
um and then it was good as turn and we
decided to do Minecraft in this collab
and that would be our first Minecraft
club and she decided we need to make a
tunnel to reach Atlantis
Okay and like I guess she wanted to make
it reach the location where she would
build Atlantis
uh and and yeah without really knowing
which direction is correct this is why
the tunnel has
um curves and [\h__\h]
um we built endlessly for hours for
gouda an endless towel on the tunnel I
died a few times
um me and Cali were probably falling
asleep a few times and and and Atlantis
is I don't know where it is though I
don't know can we go look no no not yet
oh we're gonna take the train in a
moment here's Cali's uh old house
ah
you can come in yeah uh Callie moved out
and then fought this hole in the ground
was a better place to live than my um
unbelievable unbelievable
and it like even it has like she has
enemies coming through here sometimes
because like why it's just like it's not
even safe it's not even
it leads me to the tunnel like kind of
like a a ruin of the tunnel no come
on come back I was just looking I'm just
looking it's not safe come back here
all right I just saw her logging out of
Minecraft oh funny
thank you
but the thing is you know she was she
was uh she kind of gave up on Minecraft
um yeah a long time I think I remember
her saying she would never play it again
and then she played it again though
um so I don't know what the current
state is
I I think she's just not very fond of it
but she is like she accepts to play it
again if need be
[Laughter]
okay oh yeah and then we were just in
Emma's house but of course you you
probably noticed the big tennis racket
on top of it I thought that was the I
thought that was a no it's a magnifying
glass it's a tennis racket please come
on
is it really of course it is oh that's
the only thing that makes sense
only thing
guba house with a not so simple Bridge
she destroyed this is so sad she had a
glass tunnel here
this where we're going now that was that
was once a glass tunnel and she got rid
of it I see so sad hi and she put a lot
of work into that man girl girl
yeah uh
I don't even know if she uses this
please still actively is this no it's
not for me anymore
yes this is uh her her Hood I guess
a shark coat oh yeah
very very special as well
mm-hmm okay
did you read
yeah it's a kiss from Barna yeah but
she's telling everybody who's here
what if what if we kissed in the garage
house tunnel in her basically in her ear
I think
thank you Father for that beautiful prom
um let's see we could go back up first
she has
kind of spread her
Estates across the server and it's
confusing because nothing is finished
I see him but oh yeah by the way I
forgot next to the wolf Farm is the iron
farm if you ever need iron
as always
yes it's nice always iron here
nice
it say you know for our Farms there's
always like a better version on the
Japan side but if you want to be you
know like me then you call you go here
and get it here
this is um yeah
I remember I can't explain no she can't
it looks funny with my Shader though
what the [\h__\h]
it's like freaky
um this was supposed to be something
um that's good I made as far as I know
yeah
that was like a Revenge project on he
could assembly I see you but yeah who
knows what it was supposed to be really
from here
do you see this like
guess who made that
I'm I don't know that thing in the sky
which en member would be capable of
building something so crazy
no one because it was made by hajama
really yeah
yeah no she kind of died there
um but yeah she she left something
incredible behind and she's welcome for
real thank you
yeah I guess she's you know I was making
a joke then guess who made it in the end
um no one the engine zero yeah she's gen
zero you know
um oh and from here we don't need to go
there but do you I don't know how far
you can see do you see
um
something bright orange
I do it has like an old Oz on the head
yeah that's a stage I build with an
energy
[Laughter]
I already don't have fireworks uh or
like a um you don't have a Lightroom
okay
um uh I'm going down not the best path
to choose but you know is there a boat
here oh there's a oh
oh
Kiana's trying to kill me
oh they're skeleton what there is
where did the skeleton go
it's killing me
I'm trying to protect you I'm out of the
water
meeting some food I think I saw a boat
oh did I
is there one here
no okay
um
uh yeah where are we going I guess uh
over there there's another cool farm I
guess and there's good as attempt at
something let's just swim
just try to follow me
we're just gonna go to gura's glass
thing at the the farm thing we don't
have to look at at the moment um
just swim swimsuit do we have any
shaders on
uh no not on my side you're pure say so
minecraft
pure and say so
fresh out of the
out of out of the Minecraft Pocket okay
oh
so
good I was building something like uh
Atlanta where are you oh where are you
are we swimming there's a door there's a
door with a chicken ah don't go in go
back up to the land to above the water
oh
see there's fireworks
no I don't see him oh my God why I lost
her were you supposed to stay behind me
at all times
slowly look behind
look behind I saw you I see you okay
this way okay I'm coming
[Music]
this is actually quite pretty if only
gouda would finish things this is not
finished right right guys
it was actually quite pretty
cool
why is there an eye on my screen and I
oh yeah it's uh it has to do with what
she what could have built in here oh
okay
Sal look at this what
the [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
you little [\h__\h] how dare you
yeah not very insecure in terms of
enemies you need to put down more lights
um but this is this is uh yeah
um pretty Atlantis actually is it
finished it kind of looks like it's like
I get to be finished oh it's a yeah
Atlantis placeholder more or less
in here
okay I think it looks better at daytime
it's not finished okay well it probably
will never be because she abandoned it
no but she got some you know she had
like uh issues with getting like enough
materials for it so she got some
donations too and she got so far and
then she leaves it and then
[Music]
bye
oh wow I guess we could go this
direction I don't normally take this
path but it should lead us to something
follow me I think we'll go we'll get to
the side of Phoenix then if we go here
maybe oh yeah shrimp
shrimp the shrimp
[Music]
he's a big shrimp he's a big ass shrimp
yeah it looks nice
looks edible looks tasty yeah she
finished the shrimp and tea
shrimp shrimp is finished oh and let's
see where are we coming out here ah yeah
it is
it is at the side of Phoenix Sun yeah so
here yay
look at him I'm not looking I'm not
looking I'm only looking into your eyes
when I want to repeat history
um he um uh Cali at some point decided
we should do oh like a like a carnival
thing here
so some of the things we built you know
together with Ian
um here uh let's find the entrance
yeah yeah
yeah it's it's not you know ID or Japan
quality but is he and quality built with
love you know
um there's um a shark tank where if you
go inside on the other side I can shoot
and then you fall into the water which
is actually you know yeah quite cool
yeah yeah
somebody would have to enter from the
from the back
and then I could try it do I have an
arrow oh I do
let me let me yeah you sit on there's
some yeah okay okay
get you into the water and you need a
little bath Madame oh yes I'm so dirty
oh no she's no she's out
yeah that's pretty cool though I think
yeah that's cute in here was yeah
fortune telling oh that's got a fortune
another Fortune but this one actually
has text on it
so uh I think yeah you just push the
button push that button poke has
suspended and you are not alone no don't
take it off you have to take it from the
button eh I have to share with one and
again Sheriff blesses you what did you
get okay wait I'm trying to remember how
to get in my
you are illiterate oh yeah wow
um that's nice that's not very that's
that's not
that well you know you win some you lose
some yeah yeah yeah yeah
I don't know I read it no I don't think
it was maybe correct you know I think it
might have been wrong
funny ironic behind that is the
unfinished ferris wheel
oh my God I love Ferris wheels
chihuahuas yeah I love them too but not
if they're overpriced like in London
yeah this was supposed to be a project I
think from gouda and Cali I think oh man
there's so many yeah
[Music]
what these pork Goins
they're chilling they're entrapped what
happened here and that's supposed to be
here why did they all
how
what I'm I'm
flabbergasted it's turning into an iron
farm
they wandered in and can't leave and
they keep on I guess creating more I
hope that one doesn't fall in that's so
weird I mean we could build them a way
out if we had blocks but I don't
yeah but uh very difficult to get them
they're supposed to be in Phoenix then
you know but it's okay then
hang out maybe we'll help them out later
this is a little Animal Farm wow oh my
God a petting zoo yeah
zombie
the skeleton horse yeah very nice
skeletons
very comfortable oh the pole on there
polar bear
[Music]
yeah yeah if you know you know you know
and if you don't know you don't know
it's a slim pull out there
ah cute
and what else there's a kfp uh
uh over there a little little kfp
and another like shooting range where
you can get like gold pieces I guess do
you want to try it yes uh houses work
together
do you gotta bring your own
uh let me give you a well let me test it
if it works
[Music]
it's a good shot does it work though
like I didn't get anything
I'm not sure if this is working
that's okay
didn't I built this you're supposed to
toss eggs no I didn't build this but
it's like my style you're supposed to
toss eggs or snowballs not arrows
try it that's okay boxes for okay well
I've got three
uh yeah don't shoot the fox
shred shoot the the one of the targets
how do I throw them uh right click I
think
[Music]
I think um try the left side Maybe
foreign
nothing's happening is it broken it's
not finished really
yeah it's not something like this before
and then Japanese server oh wow but in
theory you you did it so you know what
you're winning what your prices
my heart oh my God my favorite thing
[Music]
yeah I think you know we have enough of
the song Carnival thing
um let me show you the most important
thing on This Server especially as you
are a kfp
this is important to you specifically
yes
um
famous famous Phoenix 10 come in okay
let me explain this to you properly
because some people don't have this
explanation luxury so they're always
confused but okay there's a sign uh
straight you get back to en headquarters
or just take the ice Road basically and
that's better left is the town square
with lots of Traders right is he even
still here I think by now I I put him in
this place this area is basically unused
it's being renovated I see him but the
real Phoenix then
starts over this big wall I'm trying to
really separate it because I was like
renovating and I need the traders to be
in the right places
but Phoenix then basically oh let me
tell you tell you oh my God so basically
this was once a normal village and then
we went through it and it kind of got
destroyed like people
um you know automatically the algorithm
of Minecraft is like sad it kills people
when you go yeah and and then and then
and then and then I was like well you
know I wanna I wanna make you know like
a trading thingy but I want to make a
natural one you know so I rebuilt this
Village from like you know I I
re-rehabitated it I revived it when it
was already dead
um and yeah I kept a very natural
trading uh economy here without putting
them into prisons and it went for
several renovation stages uh that was
this is this is like built together with
my real life mother yeah because she's a
Minecraft freak and she we decided to
you know um right away to make it
prettier so now please jump over here
now you're officially in the real
feeling soon so there's beautiful
beautiful flooring here please look at
the detail on the ground wow it's
gorgeous tonight the lights are really
pretty too
over here is like everything that you
need in terms of like armor and weapons
and so on like if you talk to them they
have names tetsuo is a big recommend you
can also trade um Iron to them to get
emeralds pretty nicely
and yeah I named them so that you kind
of know maybe for some of them like
armor and feather falling decent mining
tools guy
Etc
yeah try to make it as easy as possible
in with the setting Bob the building
tools guy decent mining tools number two
yeah good man good man good man yeah so
they're supposed to stay in here it's
actually a challenge to to take him out
of this area it should always be safe
then over here is anything you need in
terms of books like enchanting
they are currently pretty much enclosed
in in this part oopsie they they are
supposed to stay inside if possible
um try coming in with the button yeah so
we have we have Shawn Mendes who has
something for mending uh we have the
random [\h__\h] guy we have
re-reeptide for uh
uh for Riptide that was a Riptide all
kinds of enchantments you just gotta
look at their names and then yeah
Poseidon
speeder man
Aqua crew what are you zom raid yeah
they all have like things related to
their names
um
some some are important like there's a
silk touch guy somewhere I think
Buzz Lightyear
what's what's your name I can't see
Shawn Mendes Aya silky boy silky boy is
the silk touch guy milky boy you might
need silk touch in the future so
remember remember
what is self-touch uh it's um when you
mind something normally if you mind
something without silk touch on your ax
my mining tool
um then it will
um become sometimes it when you mine it
it turns into something it wasn't but
with silk touch it stays the same exact
way you saw it when you were trying to
mine it you know what I mean
I understand I like to explain well yeah
yeah so this is that area the the people
who are not illiterate are here
farming District
if you need food for example
um always there's um I mean there's
really this this area even I don't use
it much but you could come over here
with a lot of watermelons
and exchange the Watermelons for more
emeralds but they're all somewhere else
right now these guys they're not asleep
we should sleep
yes
[Music]
one important thing is like glass for
example if you're trying to mine glass
it will just break you don't get it back
but the silk touch you get it back oh
that's really really nice yes so where's
my Lord did I is he in his melon house I
recently I recently actually did fix
this area a bit
um and extended it to over here this
cute little melon house this is where he
should be feel free to try it in these
melons I I even put some melons here for
people to create and then I revived this
farming area this was even you know in
the OG Village this is where the farming
area was
yeah
look at his prices
he sells you
he's like he's got discounts right now
do you see them
yes
isn't that amazing
you can trade for them some emeralds if
you want suspicious stew I don't eat
dance
of course but I think he wants full
melons right yeah yeah so you could
combine your little melons into one big
melon you do that oh you don't have the
discounts oh he only has oh my God
they even exchanged bread what's going
on can you not make love over the fence
keep it up
no keep it up
oh my God
can you not like I'm trying to keep this
in control right now he's having a good
time let him live sometime
damn okay wow well yeah so I don't
really use this to get food I mostly
only use this to get emeralds you know
yeah your Emerald Farm yeah more or less
it's not the most effective one but it's
the one that I built so therefore I love
it you know
um these chocolate boxes they just have
some old tools that I was using when I
when I built this place so uh don't
necessarily I mean you can take stuff
but
um I might still need it some some of
these things here no
um that's being stand for you and now
we're gonna go perhaps through here
just walk in and you'll be teleported up
upwards how do you do that
uh it's um it's physics girl physics
get into them get into the boat can we
both be in the boat yes it's so fast on
the eyes this is so romantic Ryan it's
my favorite way of transportation in
this game look at this beautiful view oh
my God it was very quick but this is
basically the shortcut between mid
Village and um get out yeah and Phoenix
then and then if you want to go down you
got to press shift
when you're on the water
shift yeah and then just walk onto the
front can she do it yeah it's just
sinking
oh
yeah sorry there's a little bit of pain
infliction at the end there It's gotta
be like that yeah here's some Farms that
I actually own there's a famous
this is this is
cave piece first ever usual room I
suppose
oh my God
I love the usual room it's so nostalgic
people never get killed here don't worry
oh of course no chickens are harmed here
ever
cute good luck in life
bye bye James come back when you want ah
I'm gonna show you the actual kfb it's
not a nice building because this is one
of the first things I built but
um
oh my god oh it is recent somewhat
recent
um yeah I I built a kfp here there's so
many chicken workers and chicken
customers everything's chicken here the
food is chicken the customers and the
workers everything's chicken
but I thought you were a phoenix
Chihuahua yeah but we eat chickens of
course why would we eat phoenixes like I
don't have many that's just me so we got
to sell we are fried Phoenix why do you
call it Kiara fried Phoenix well just
because otherwise I would get some I
would probably get sued so I see I see
yeah
and because I'm the boss but it doesn't
mean that we're frying phoenixes we're
actually frying chicken okay okay
about it it would actually be pretty you
know useful because you know Phoenix's
can just you know you just reform
Ron this is where you're right
okay correct me Phoenix says depending
on the game or the anime or the movie
that they're in have different you know
lower settings right okay what's your
lore setting
so it's not a lower setting it's the
reality but yeah let's go with lower
settings
um in my case
I am oh it's raining let's take shelter
I am the only Phoenix in this
Dimension left yeah
um I was traveling for Dimensions so
this when I every time I died I switched
to a different damage currently I'm
chilling here
um I'm the only one in this world and
um I I can revive yes uh I can try to
stay in the same Dimension when they
revive but often I would just switch
Dimensions the thing is if you kill me
by eating me
that is making me incapable of Reviving
no yes
[Music]
but if you eat me it doesn't work so
don't attempt
it you wouldn't want me to try eating
you either right no I mean but I would
let you if you ask that is wrong on so
many levels
you can fry one of my wings up it'll
grow back oh you no no I don't like that
no
no Raven Wing no no Raven wings for you
no no I don't wanna eat a part of you
that's just something I'll be inside
your body kiwawa
we'll go into the tunnel now on the
famous tunnel
so this tunnel has been extended
recently
um there's there's uh Anna created a
loop normally it just starts here goes
that way and then ends somewhere but
I'ma graded I don't think I ever did I
ever go to the full loop I don't know
um but yeah you take uh this card
oh God damn it well no go out we have to
remove it first
and then is there another one in there
no no
there's a silky pickaxe though oh
wait
um maybe one over here yes okay you sit
in the cart now go go
okay and don't do anything I sit in
front of you cute
and now we go
oh my God it's like a roller coaster it
will take a little while but that's okay
you know we have to imagine Mick was
building this tunnel together history is
in these Halls
um I died a few times in the process
uh some doors here will lead to little
ruins where the girls were maybe mining
a little bit
and one exit also leads to Phoenix then
it's another way to get into Phoenix
then
where are you I'm still there I'm just a
little ways behind I got stuck oh no
don't worry I'm coming okay
um yeah so there's some smaller mines
some bigger mines here and there
uh but they've been pretty much mined
all over
upcoming is the place where I died I
think we already passed it oh no is this
where I died
it would be a sign that that could be
I'm not sure ah this isn't
it
keep an eye out for a sign I guess
it's too fast read it though
yeah I died here
oh my God
yeah
this is the long ride I wonder if yeah
it is faster with more Redstone thingies
probably or we should replace it with
Ice Baby should be replaced with ice in
my opinion
ah but you know I'mma made this rail
after we made the tunnel and it's like a
little trip down memory lane yeah it's
history so it should stay this way
I feel very emotionally attached to the
en server in general
um so I've been kind of like refusing to
use any of the better
um devices as in farms on the Japanese
side I just use what I have here and I
keep my house here and so on like you
know
oh and we can still go to the whole yeah
yeah we'll get there
um but yeah you you you have a home now
in my house so yeah
but I would be pleased if you wouldn't
ignore the existence of the end server
completely well now I feel like I need
to show the rest of Advent when we
actually get to play together yeah
yeah I think I'll be as good of a guide
as you but oh yeah there's still some
things that I haven't shown you I mean I
don't know if I can show you everything
you know I also like for Council things
I don't know where exactly everything is
but you know we can try so here this way
it would continue but I think it just
Loops back down here
um yeah oh another and a man don't look
at him and yeah
legs but not his eyes so
here is hmm
PPP
previously pecoran's property I see him
because she uh built TTT and that's nice
I'll make a version for that in our en
server I see him and it's it was for a
long time our way of getting uh exp
we can go for the water here
there is a level in between here for
fishing
people have spent many hours fishing
here
just like a whole cure now yeah
um and then wait uh you can go I guess
there wait I haven't been here in a
while
oh yeah yeah I think we gotta go through
here this water it's kind of scary uh
press space when you're in it just space
not going forward or anything why is my
thing so laggy
can you do it yeah okay I struggle with
it sometimes and then up the stairs
that's very unsafe yes it is scary
go yeah go up and then jump
yeah you don't have to go up here but
this is you know the top like she builds
it even higher
oh
but you don't have to go up here
just so you know
um and then yeah this was like I think
we just went up there to make it spawn
more enemies but you don't really have
to do it now I guess you jump down to
the Axolotl you got to get back down
um and how do we get out again
we're stuck are we [\h__\h] ah there
okay let's go actually down
um back to the stair at the ladder
but you know Emma doesn't like this
place she's not happy with it so she
kind of also abandoned the thing
but there's the you can even hear some
cool music here
oh
I'm good
over here
uh how's this look again
was there a button oh
wasn't there an automatic one though
I don't know
[Music]
no [\h__\h] we changed it yeah yeah yeah
I knew we're not supposed to press on it
[Music]
uh
uh yeah yeah how are we supposed to
activate this [\h__\h] hmm
oh I was already broke it two years ago
okay for at least it was messed up
anyway
yeah it made a tune I think was it that
Zelda team
four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve but how do you know that
when it goes low ah well smart girl
sheesh
[Music]
one two three
one two three four five six seven eight
nine okay
twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen Sixteen
at least we fix our messes the demon of
sound is in the end the demon of sound
surprise you thought she was a demon of
soup no no demon of sound
the last one
three four five six seven eight nine ten
okay so uh did you fix these last two or
just the last only the last one okay
foreign
eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
fourteen okay ah with f free you can see
the note oh really oh well uh so
apparently the zombie is supposed to
activate it but like I guess he decides
when to activate it on the zone and what
if I want to hear it now
move zombie
[Music]
he's like on the button right now I
think so he would have to move back and
on top of it again
okay he moved away
hey maybe we can coerce him I don't
think so but it's good he'll get there
and then we will hear if we fixed it
correctly
tap the glass we can don't break
go
on the button
go go
go on the bus I mean dude do you have
any of the stuff to lead the chicken
that the chicken finds is tasty
[Music]
the chest opening sound
we destroyed and fixed it
wow amazing I was scared but you fixed
it you started fixing it amazing so here
the way this works it's still usable
dammit just doesn't like it because she
says it's not so efficient but I still
like to use it sometimes you know okay
so when you push the button these mobs
will drop down and then ah and then you
can yeah kill them and collect the EXP
oh
and if you have an amending weapon this
is what you like to use to mend the
weapon back up because you need the EXP
yeah you can walk around and some of
them just collect what they're dropping
so maybe there's even something
interesting in there you know the the
bottom one has like golden armor that
you need for the nether for example
also there's an enchanting area for the
for the books
but
this is at least on This Server so I
like to use it because it's on this
server but father made an improved
version of this she this is PPP pick
what I made TTT and finally made FFF
father's funny or fancy fish farm
funnels whatever uh that's isn't that
four five four FS F's almost fancy fish
farm is like four finals oh it's not
there's no fauna in there just spawn a
fish or funny fish farm funny fish farm
all right we can just jump into the
water here
spinach Farm is a little bit more
difficult uh to access
um but it's more efficient so
um if I I normally just fly there but
through the wine here if you go
that Direction behind the PPP you will
eventually see some tall thing
that's where FFF is
I see it's spooky dough and you gotta
use a specific sword and all that but
it's nice once you need it then you'll
appreciate it
and there's a there's a fishing house
and then over here let me show you my
biggest rival in this industry let's see
this also used to be a normal village
that was then destroyed by
the natural algorithm of my craft
uh and then oh oh good job
made this recently into a prison
oh four villagers to serve her needs
it's very efficient though oh are you
okay
yeah I was stuck for some reason for a
second
so let me show you this just in case but
you are actually obligated to use
Phoenix then just saying oh of course of
course so I think it's this way yeah
uh press shift when you're on the that
weird thing
[Music]
final lives for efficiency yeah
efficiency but what cost so she keeps
them here like you know in like one
space prison cells so that they don't
run around
yeah I mean you see you see what they're
selling very very easy to understand
very easy to use
but you must please me so you will be
obligated to use Phoenix
okay
[Music]
yeah but she did a good job I suppose
that imprisoning people yeah
yeah well you know fun is fun is my
ocean consoles so I might have to use
both the please both of you
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I guess the myth area because I gotta
show you something there that I forgot
and then we could look out for some more
Council things
um I know where the sauna is
um I know
ah no I know I know of a few more things
I just have to run around and be lucky
to find them
yeah
I didn't look at him I didn't look at
him I accidentally look what is the
battle with him all right he must die
the good thing is he can't go past that
point
uh because yeah a certain amount of um
yeah oh nice the the blocks like he's
too tall for them oh um oh oh that was a
that was a specific Enderman you know
sometimes specific enemies are in
specific location this will be a lesson
for you basically for the future this
was just an experiment to show her for
the future so she won't make these
mistakes
um so sometimes specific enemies are in
specific locations for a reason somebody
may have captured them there
um to to be their pet or so
um did you kill someone's pet apparently
oh no it's fine let's let's run let's
run bro he was
I think we should try to go the other
way actually might be shorter
I think that's what the look is for
right I would think so
yeah so if you see like a zombie
somewhere where he shouldn't be chances
are
hard well
well you know how do you even on it
there's no button here
I guess I'm going
slowly and then fast
how do you move uh golf like with the w
[Laughter]
ow I got it I got it okay yeah
um oh yeah okay chat is just attached to
that one because uh he's been in the
tunnel for a long time and everybody
keeps on seeing him in the streams he's
just been stuck I freed him from his
suffering
oh there's more cars she did it to
protect me which means it was worth it
oh
probably I guess I did that
maybe I did it yeah yeah maybe
why does why does this tunnel make me
lag now
we are lagging
are you lagging too no oh my OBS is
lacking
stop lagging you
look [\h__\h]
maybe my render distance yeah there's
things so basically he's gen zero ND
like the Sora of ND world
what I don't know
uh okay
that's nice oh I stopped oh I stopped it
early I wasn't supposed to stop here oh
that's okay
that's okay my cart just stopped we will
run the rest of the path some nice fresh
air
going on a nice jog with Chihuahuas and
bye I hate jogging me too yeah
yeah I like going for walks though
Michelle walks walks are okay I guess if
they're not too long
I have another mine cart for some reason
so if you found and picked mine up you
can yeah I uh I I may have taken it um
but in the end we're just gonna put all
the cards that we have in in the box
when it belongs
oh this was so long I will keep it
I didn't know we still had so much to go
things just go back and forth here um is
this supposed to be
I'm just gonna assume that the fox is
supposed to be in here because somebody
put it in there who knows let's not free
him maybe it wasn't supposed to be
frayed
there he goes there he goes with his
little snoot oh he goes back and forth
cute oh a lot of things are stuck here
um wait nope oops let's
um unjam this
wait this is also is this the end yeah
this is the end because this card is
like sunken this is the sheep that will
tell you this is the end
thank you sheep for telling us but thank
you continues though ah this is
entrance entrance macaroni
eh what
where are we how do you enter it guys I
don't know
oh here oh I feel so illegal I don't
have a passage allowance don't look at
him
oh welcome to bunkeroni a famous place
um because crony win Council man yeah
this wasn't holy [\h__\h] this this this was
like daily [\h__\h] man yeah Chrome
[Music]
she went crazy she likes to have things
organized so she created bunkeroni and
she didn't want people to know where it
is and she didn't want people to come in
but people went in anyway
but she had everything so organized and
she had really all these things here
yeah
it was quite a special thing
crony's Minecraft streams yeah
yeah and who respected her wishes I
I looked out for where her Farm where
her whole bunker is and I even now feel
bad for being in here well let's let's
get out of here then she has a guest
room oh
oh is it nice it's it's quiet it's just
a single bed so tiny
[Music]
um
and it goes deeper oh yes of course it
does oh okay let's go let's see oh what
is here on this level there's like books
enchanting stuff oh some weird
mushrooms mushrooms
cacti storage residence kante oh yeah
only residents can take ooh so organized
imagine imagine if I could be so over
this is organized now
[Music]
um
burner
wow
look at her do you think if you were to
build your own home would you be like
disorganized beautiful type or actually
this is not really beautiful it's just
functional but what yeah
I don't know we're gonna have to wait
and see
oh there's some stairs I'm not sure is
this where does this lady stairs
we're about to find out
it's scary oh it's scary like it's kind
of nothing
maybe she opens this and then closes it
off again maybe this is the the Yeah the
secret one that people always try to dig
into
now that's another entrance
all right let's leave I feel like I'm
somewhere I shouldn't be you too
up okay
Grafton get past the Enderman how do we
do it eh walk by him well there's two
even oh that's free
[Music]
um oh okay oh
that's closer
everyone's doors behind you in general
yes oh yeah okay this exit actually good
very good very good up here I think
there's a tree farm up there
um oh I know you you might think you
know why Tree Farm there's so many trees
in this game anyway but sometimes
sometimes you need it yeah and
and uh this what was that again
um I haven't seen it in a while
this was chat will tell me in a moment
a creeper Farm oh
this is so
oh
it's not the one that I was always
camping up right oh
yeah
it's basically the same thing yeah gun
powder does she have two of these no
wait does this wear oh wait now I I was
able to
um where the hell I am yeah we circled
back and this is the creeper Farm I
thought it was the second one
yeah okay
um
interesting
ah then we shall kind of walk back to
the direction of myth Village oh [\h__\h] I
forgot to put back all the minecartes in
well it's okay we'll do it later we'll
put it into the tunnel where
you know you know the start of the
tunnel
it'll be fine
it's okay
so what do you think of our area it's
very pretty thank you it's better than
anything I've ever built in Minecraft I
also like to take over Villages I didn't
realize you could do that with them
because admittedly I just try to protect
them uh that's sweet but I've I don't I
didn't I never I've never traded with
them oh well if you would trade with
them they end up like leveling up and
give you some cool stuff actually
and if they don't give you cool stuff
then what you normally do is you get rid
of them and then you get a new Trader
yeah
I see hey
so once again actually this place needs
cards right because it never has cards
so let me put two in here and then wait
wait wait I'll put two down
and and oh actually I have one more
uh oh you put some in two okay I don't
know how I got two but no okay I have
two left so with these two we can go
back
um oh
oh wait did they Loop this thing too
where did that go oh
it's part of the hyperloop now oh my God
okay then better to place it here I
guess and then press forward get in
there and then press forward uh when you
look in the right direction no not that
way yeah that way
or I guess oh button button push me
oh yay
goodbye I I try I don't know where to
get off
um I think it stops you
no don't worry I'm me and her beautiful
boobies make sure to look up
okay
oh
una boob time
[Music]
uh where are you right now
on the right side you may see uh
something with the heart that's green
and pink
it's uh it's the sauna of fauna and Sana
combined fauna and salmon you have a
sauna so they built
oh yeah right iris's house is down there
too
wait
um
the place
The Flower Place I'll show you the floor
okay follow me
follow me anywhere here
on the gay Bridge
and then we will you know we'll walk
around okay have peel
and then
ah this this whole stream is a little
bit biased um
more yeah that I've made this is a paper
form that I made with my mother
um she helped me create this basically
it's farming sugar cane but with
sugarcane you can make make paper and
white paper is so important is basically
once you get an elytra you want to make
fireworks and fireworks are made out of
paper and gunpowder so you will need a
lot of that yeah if you need it I don't
know of any other paper Farm there might
be but I don't know of any so just get
it from here
I only know of this one
eh so
here is the place that created the
flower meme
there you know building their first
flower house here with all
[Music]
and then they put a flower here and then
they said flower Council flowers
oh very luxurious
but you know memories
not mermaids Kiara's things why do I
have things here why is there just a
lava pit ah it's a disposal pen a pin oh
it gets rid of it oh no don't waste my
fireworks
I thought it was for me to jump in no
no no no no no okay one more thing I can
show you because I know where it is it's
the sauna here to the left
yes yes
this is the sun now
oh I love to go to sauna
[Music]
I only recently started to get like to
have a liking for it
um because I always feel embarrassed
about getting naked you know that yeah
yeah
oh you don't need to be with me I don't
need to be naked with you for thank God
no no no no you do need to be naked with
me you don't need to be nervous about it
okay
I love this those Iris people even play
I mean I could ask this question about
anyone really does anybody really play
Minecraft anymore besides fauna and
I played recently actually this is
iris's house I never see her around here
though
but that's what I could say about
everybody really there's a lot of dogs
yeah she collects them too
this one looks different what's wrong
with this one which one this guy is that
a fox
well there's several foxes and several
dogs actually wolves I guess officially
what is this one that's an arctic fox
the front one is an arctic fox the one
on the background yeah
Jefferson
[Music]
the arctic foxes
are flipping
is that like a carpet is that a piece of
carpet yeah I think he's holding a piece
of carpet in his mouth
probably I like that
oh cute oh okay leaving
[Music]
yes do you carry anything like important
with you
food well I have one important thing
uh it's Subaru's uh takoyaki oh give it
to me
okay ugh
why that's supposed to be takoyaki
that's what it says
it's actually potatoes okay
um
I guess we can go this way yeah why are
you still my takoyaki
um
[Music]
I don't want to go this way again no so
much
so much
around around
[Music]
follow me although I don't think
I don't know I
just
sleep talking
yeah
I I I I will show you something oh
follow me this way
where are you come here come here come
here run
okay now
[Music]
here come here
hey come here come here what are you
doing to me wait should I give you
should I give you my important items
I'm not looking anywhere no take free
this is the first time first time first
time wherever I give you my diamond
sword I'm scared don't give me all your
things wait let me let me let yeah let
me give you my armor too so you can give
it back to me because I think you're
trying to kill me no it's okay it's the
experience okay okay okay
um try try to accidentally fall into
this thing where there's some light
there's a hole there trying to fall into
this history about it okay
and then go go back go back oh no
foreign
nice yeah I think I put that there for
safety because I didn't want to close
the hole
um
here that's the question yeah
um I didn't think about that did I
was down bye is there something that
could kill you
I hear some zombies get them to kill you
maybe but I have so many watermelons oh
oh and cookies and a cake from sana's
Bakery
um
[Music]
you've abandoned me
ah trouble okay wait uh I but the water
doesn't it just float well yeah okay we
can do that yeah I think I think I can
do that I will make you make you
I just need to go get some water really
quickly just stay put don't die I'm
holding still but have you never heard
of the Minecraft hole the no serious
hole you know I think I have but I
didn't know what it was so now you've
experienced it firsthand it's a special
hole you shouldn't be crying you should
be happy that you fell freeway I'm just
I'm not crying I'm just so pleased I'm
so happy that I you should I got to
experience you should be it's it's a
special very special
F the bat
I'm scared it's a privilege to
experience the whole of the en server so
basically this hole sparked a lot of
Minecraft enthusiasts
um who are watching our streams to you
know document look back on everything
even look at the the empty server data
of us before we moved in everybody like
had to investigate about this whole
because who was the first one to fall in
me
who built it nobody built it it was just
naturally there oh
yeah and I just fell into it I think
several times and I got I got so mad and
then later other people fell into it and
everybody is just just so mad at it and
but it's so weird that it's like there
it just seems like somebody built it but
oh people said I mean what oh are you
sure but I don't know oh yeah right it
isn't and then people were like who
built it and people were looking back
and at all our streams and we're trying
to figure out who built it but it was
just never documented in the Stream so
we don't know who built it but we we
were like pointing fingers at each other
like you you must have built it yeah
people are saying probably gura no but
nobody I asked everybody from myth and
nobody remembers building this so hmm
makes you question
really I don't think so so you say died
here Iris died here I died here
uh maybe people I lived
well who knows so I will pour down some
water now okay you should how do I pour
it the best should I pour it here
oh yeah that's that might be good water
is coming soon you just stand in it and
then
uh space push okay
I'm ready
if you want to prank Advent make them
run randomly over this path and hope
that somebody Falls in
I don't know seeing how I didn't fall in
I'm kind of I'm gonna drown but I I
managed to fall in there so many times
man
oh you can make it I can even hear you
dying so you're there yeah
hey hey saved by myself I think if you
woke up for saving my life now give me
back my stuff that I stole from you
rightfully please
okay okay only if you promise me to try
to get somebody to fall in in the future
okay if I if I pass by it I'll try yeah
good stuff okay here's a taco what else
yay my armor ah
there you go and there's diamond sword
and you have to take in your butt
I think that's it probably yeah
yeah okay
um there's you know obviously there's
still things but uh this is the stuff
that I mostly remember and that's easy
to access there's also actually let me
show you something
um yes just quickly there are some
roboco Senpai stuff here as you can see
and and although I don't think she uses
it another thing that's not being used
as many things on the server is pecora's
house that I built for her
nice there was a time where you know
Ian's over in Japan server was connected
for the first time and then it was kind
of like a hype thing for Japanese
Japanese members to come over to the en
server and some would get yeah yeah and
I gave her a tour and presented this
house to her
um just for her to have a little little
place to put her things in the en server
that's so sweet I even give the turn a
lighter no mm-hmm where do you get these
elytra what the [\h__\h] uh you have to get
them from the end oh
yeah it's difficult you have to be very
concentrated though yes yes I've never
been there before so I'm scared okay we
can do that let's go
um and then oh yeah there's a Lamy house
ah you didn't see the Lamy house I can
show you that one quickly too yeah
um
have a thing going on you know oh yeah
no it's all day uh live together this
was also during the time when when the
service got connected so everybody was
like you know lovey-dubby oopsie oh [\h__\h]
that was not not comfortable
we can go up here
whammy the whammy
so it's actually I don't know how we
even missed it
I guess because it's like in this like
uh hole more or less but it's close to
the one I built of manichi
why did she build a shooting range here
I don't even know
practice yeah this is Mommy house
she doesn't look cute that is cute it's
the like the the mascot thing of Whammy
yeah it's cute it has an actually nice
decorations yeah I was never inside but
yeah the Yuki mean
yukimi
oh god oh it's so big dude oh cute wow I
like it actually this isn't wool right
what is this
um let me tell you it's concrete blue
concrete concrete is so annoying to me
can you get up to the second floor
that's a nice house
it's empty yeah not being used either
much I think oh the bed looks nice oh
wait that looks like pale oh God
eh
this owl quartz stairs are made into
like a another standing up pillow that's
genius I've never saw that before
it really looks like pillows
wow okay so you would
ah guys we have one last chance to
suggest something that I forgot to show
her that I should be showing her
one last chance because I feel like you
know I've done my job here hey my job
it's for the never okay let me show you
something really important than ever
just roughly roughly
um also because you know this is a
biased stream and I did
[Music]
go jump so high uh
um yeah I I used to never
um to build an ice path
um that brings you really quickly to
some
um biomies that are really far
okay basically you know sometimes during
our free years here uh don't go in yet
you need some gold
uh sometimes during the three years
Minecraft will get updates
um where new biomies would be created is
there anything gold in here look for
something gold
and the problem is that for the biomes
you need to find a new spawned region to
load in for the first time otherwise
like here you couldn't get like a new
baumi in this area over now you didn't
find any gold follow me
wait okay where'd you go here okay Wawa
house
so what I do is like I go into the never
because if you go if you walk five
meters in the never then you walk like
10 15 meters in in the real uh Overworld
yeah
find some gold armor is there any gold
anymore
um there's gold here but it's not armor
I have a gold ingot can I take one of
those the uh take a take uh two four
take four
okay I'll take the whole thing and then
put the rest in there I guess
and then go to this thing
and then write boots or or helmets
whatever you want and then make it
four for boots do you have the recipe
for golden boots yeah okay I don't know
how but I got it okay nice nice so I got
some boots you know why we need that
no oh wow he's such a noob
I didn't know you needed gold in the
nether yeah and uh at least in survival
yeah because if you if you don't wear
gold some some enemies will um aggro you
[Music]
oh my God buddy so okay I'll show you
like some
um famous spots and and my my uh have I
guess we don't have to use don't touch
him don't touch him
oh my God don't touch that either don't
touch anything
uh this here in here
just in case if you ever need
um fancy blocks that come from the Mesa
you don't have to go up now
um uh this leads you to the Mesa biome
that I discovered this also leads you to
a Cow Island if you need to go to our
Island for some reason now Island oh
what the [\h__\h] why so aggro a little [\h__\h]
uh but yeah and then I extended it
recently right ow [\h__\h] you
um
uh
[Music]
I like that you say biomi thank you I
like it too
uh can I kill this one like I don't want
to kill anything that somebody's pet you
know
I don't know if it's someone's pet if
it's trying to kill us if you would love
some new Sakura
that's past the Mesa by all mean that I
uh discovered oh all through here
basically there's an eyes path you go
into a boat and then you go quickly
quickly quickly
um but yeah it might be a little bit
difficult uh at your first visit to
um Find Your Way properly come back
can I kill this one
it scares me
okay I'm trying let's kill it good job
and there's more but wait there's more
fun ways
killing a spider and a thousand more
spiders coming out of it yeah that's
terrifying
okay oh one card
more cards no cards
um
so through here although I don't like
walking here it's kind of dangerous
um this is like our first
path that we built in the in our
neighbor um
it leads basically what does it even
lead to
uh I haven't used this path in a long
time
um what did we yo I'm scared well yeah
there's a kfp and why
for so many things yeah I'm running no
one's scary
Atlantis supposed Atlantis slime farm
yeah some things but not some anything
not really important I guess
um but you know it's got history you
know yeah this is the place this is the
place
[Music]
there's a famous
um prisoner gotcha prisoner but didn't I
kill him
was it yeah well he's not in here
anymore they used to be a famous pig
linen here
uh where we were teasing him to give us
things it wasn't me but he's dead okay
good good good good good I made a never
kfp that's also a long time ago no no
well good luck with that chickens good
luck yeah
it was never really a safe uh exiting
system or entering system
oh wow it's like making this cooking
sounds
yeah it goes even further like there's
another uh it's really hard to see with
my Shader but there's another path over
there that leads through some place I
don't even remember anymore but yeah
this is another
place that has been seen in many
Minecraft streams of ours
for many hours
um
how to get back up
not here not here
not here don't step on the Fire
fire that's almost on fire
again I [\h__\h] hate them no
[\h__\h] them
well we must fight then uh the the never
the most in my opinion nice annoying
enemy in the nether is the [\h__\h] pigs
mm-hmm there's no way to not aggro them
they're so aggressive
kiwoba I lost you it's okay I'm I'm
coming back I just had to save myself
and and kill this I climbed up high
there's a pig no
oh oh and in the air there's a uh oh no
oh no don't oh am I just coming down so
low what the [\h__\h]
go back up go back up not you nerissa
I'm telling the I'm going down don't
worry good
and the gas to go away
bless you
that that little [\h__\h] did you see the
thing that makes those sounds
I think so yes it's very shitty oh wow
I'm back by the KFC building I'm tempted
you're crazy I'm so tempted
you came too close to my territory buddy
I'm so tempted yeah
dude that's just one hit
let's go look at you miss kiwawa
takanashi wow that went down easily okay
let's go back to the is there carts here
actually oh there are a few let's take
them you take one too
here
and I got it and uh is there a button oh
yeah does it work no
I'm on fire
oh no
are you trying to become a phoenix
yes I guess we just gotta go on our own
let's go
[Applause]
it's not working it is it's slow at
first until it gets on one of the red
glowing tiles
it's not working at all then just place
it right in front of a red glowing tile
okay and then press W forward forward
liar liar pants on fire
oh okay now we can put them here so
people can actually use card here
full
foreign
music right I do yesterday I was on the
hills of Sound of Music wait really yeah
like one of them so many Hills that they
filmed at least uh for like some footage
I think don't make me jealous like that
that's my dream man I didn't even
realize it because it was so normal like
such a normal environment for me I
didn't even realize that that was okay
yeah hi I'm I'm Austrian and I just live
in a beautiful place by default I do yes
I do don't mind me
there's another couple of like important
paths like this leads to something that
I forgot but it was important at some
point that leads to something that I
forgot but it was also it doesn't even
say oh it says copper Express this is
the copper Express
mods but as you remember here first
station also leads to Army copper
yes actually I need to edit this
um because
um let me just put one down here
fourth station New
um
sakuna byome
uh feel free to
Loot and Farm
yeah yeah
oh come on
let's go back to the normal World close
behind yes
and they put
no
yes wonderful
well thank you thank you yeah my job is
done let's go
let's go let's go to our home yes time
to go back home with my Senpai I have a
roommate who gladly will live with me
let's go
[Music]
it's not the prettiest place but um
you're welcome yeah I mean it looks like
the places I would build in Minecraft
[Laughter]
so simplistic
uh oh yeah uh I will show you the uh
last but not least I will show you the
portals
um yes new server basically
oh yes we'll go back it's a little bit
um to the side of where you entered from
so I guess we should go for the Rainbow
Bridge again one second yes
so how did you like it I like it it's
very pretty it's nice to see all my
senpai's Minecraft efforts yeah yeah
you know with our our little efforts and
our big soul and our big hearts we try
to make something
it's no you know
you know and we we made lots of pretty
things yeah let's walk let's walk
Walking is healthy
we saw hatima Hogwarts from a distance
it's hard to get up there I don't know
any way of getting up there without an
elytra
and this lady can't fly yet even though
she claims to be a raven or something I
don't claim to I am come on show me show
me make me sound
oh
stop you sound like I don't know
um what the [\h__\h] is that
sounds so so good
that song reminds me of something
I'm so
I'm sorry oh my God please listen to
takanasi Kiana's M Crow because their
sounds so I love that I love that uh
Kermit yeah it has potential to be
kermits yeah you sound like
oh my God how can you attempt to sound
like a bird and you end up sounding like
spits
it's not it's not the video
oh my god oh my god well look you speak
German so you have I yeah I'm I'm a girl
failure so I don't know what you were
expecting for me
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no don't close
your throat so much
not listen
[Applause]
I can't roll my R's how are you doing
that and believe in yourself how are you
doing that I'm not even calling it the
Japanese way I'm just rolling in I can't
do it anyway I can't do the German R
either
say Kiara
Kiara oh hey you kind of rolled a
Japanese Japanese thank you thank you I
can pretend it when I say Kiara Senpai
says
[Music]
oh yeah wait say it again
yeah you can do it
you're putting a little bit too much HHH
in there but
very switzer-ish at the moment
switch switch switch
I guess
you need a cough drop
yes you're ruining my throat I'm sorry
I'm sorry I thought you had a like a
talent for this kind of stuff hey
I'm really bad at accents actually well
okay when I was born as a raven my um my
tongue was fused to the bottom of my
mouth what yeah they had they had to cut
it like the you know the little line at
the bottom they had to cut it uh wait so
how few
how would you describe that ah it's just
like that little you know that little
lion yeah that like connected that was
just like fused nothing like I mean it
was still moving right but like could
you perhaps no barely they had to they
had to get scissors and cut it so I
could use my tongue oh
but you were able to eat right no that's
why that's why I was a really angry baby
because I couldn't eat
that's so interesting because it's a
little bit relatable to me
[Music]
no way
it's not so bad for me but
um I could probably use some cutting
there
really why
I never talked about this before but um
I I it just it just doesn't go out very
far
um like I'm always fascinated when
people pull out their tongue and they're
like and then I I I I'm so embarrassed
about this actually
don't be embarrassed uh like I have
troubles even eating ice cream like
normal people do that's why I just bite
ice cream
[Music]
I see you've got a very I mean you can
get it cut I've heard it I'll take that
that's a possibility but I was just too
embarrassed to go to the dentist and be
like can you you know don't be
embarrassed see mine actually because my
tongue was just so weird uh I also had a
speech impediment growing up so I
actually had a permanent lift so when I
said f is I said them like this and when
I I couldn't say ours either I would say
AWA
so that's why I can't I can't um I can't
learn like it's really hard for me to
master ours and any other type of
language because I'm like I already I'm
already faking it till I'm making it you
know okay uh oh you know it's being a
raven is why a dentist but I was told
that the dentist does it
uh I'm pretty sure anyone who deals with
your mouth will do it so do you want to
deal with my mouth
sure I'll help you out
with another big relationships
random rare thing yeah we've got a weird
weird little talk except it seems like
yours is less connected because it might
have to be cut pretty soon after I was
born or else I would have died
oh my God we have to talk more after the
stream linked
tongues together I'm kidding I'm kidding
I'm kidding
over yeah too compatible for our own
good for real oh my God that's weird I I
don't yeah
yeah
let's compare tongues oh my God
okay
I'm bad like um whenever there's a like
a like a for example like a doctor
situation like at the dentist for
example and he's like go I'll put put
out your tongue and go ah and I'm like
and I'm like I can't go any forever but
he's like more and more and I'm like
oh no yeah no just bring it up next time
just say hey I because I mean some
people some people do it solely for the
ability to stick their tongue out
further like you know those people can
stick their tongue out like really
really grossly far like Orochimaru from
Naruto find that kind of disgusting no
no me too Sarah you don't you don't have
to do it that much but you could be like
hey I literally can't
I'm my tongue is very fused could you
please help me could you please just
trim it a little bit keep in mind though
because it is in your mouth it will it
will take some time to heal and it will
be really uncomfortable no I'm too
scared to do it no give it a try give it
a try
give it a try so you can eat ice cream
like
you know
[Music]
trim my tongue
trimming the thing underneath but you
ever you ever think about getting your
tongue split have you seen people who do
that so disgusting I think so
it's all like in the video I saw someone
showing that off like a snake right I'm
like yeah yeah
I don't think I could ever do that just
because like yeah I like having one
tongue I can't imagine having two
that's some kinky [\h__\h] man like you you
go do your kinky stuff but why else
would you do it if not for some kinky
stuff man or the aesthetic I know I
think if someone has a split tongue and
they just do it for fun
it just makes him happy it freaks me out
like seeing it like there's certain
things that I I when I look at them they
will make me feel sick to the stomach
I'm so sorry but that's one of the
things
um that's okay it's okay
it's okay my tongue's not split okay so
I will you can look at my tongue and
you'll be you'll see one big beautiful
pink pink tongue it's great
[Laughter]
I I am wow I didn't expect that anyways
we need to we need to go through wait we
need to go through ones
um but oh like basically this leads to
the new world
oh
the the news connected one that you uh
yeah I think that should be where you
want to go
where is this
eh
Eh this is this is the combined server
as far as okay I'm just now I'm pretty
sure the other one leads to the same to
the same one no that's just like that
leads to the Japan World I think but
I know that's the old Japan World down
there but you can basically wait wait if
you go through here
um and then you look up here there's the
en world and then there's Japan World
and then there's ID world you would
think you're already in Japan well but
this is I think the old Japan World
yeah yeah oh yeah wow this is another
huge thing to look at lots of History
here too
um yeah yeah so these are the all the
old ones and we're now in the combined
one but if you want I mean I need to go
back to the other one oh yeah the other
one just just because the the one
through the through here
because that's where that's where the
rest of Advent will spawn I'm gonna have
to lead them here okay are you sure
because this brings us back yeah look
see is this where we went in but then
you were in the
this is where we spawned in when we
opened up the game this is the old one
right this is the old one
oh you were hanging out on the old one
were we okay well I now that I know next
time I can lead them I can lead them
yeah I mean there's a lot of history
here but I don't think anybody uses it
anymore do they
um
so yeah now you know how to get to the
to all to everything basically yeah
um
congratulations is it up here oh
nice
well yeah I will stay there because I am
like maybe maybe I am a contrarian I
don't know but I like to stay where I am
no no that's valid I'll stay here just
so I can lead Advent into the Ian and
and other servers
you know I'm not
to be happy about it I think fauna would
be mildly happy about it you know I'm
excited to see fauna's world tree I need
to ask her to show it to me oh yeah wait
well
and the one she's building I know but
isn't that that's not a new server right
I think so yeah
she needs she needs me to help her
because I asked if I could build a nest
there too
um because I'm you know I'm a bird oh
you would be nice in in both of your or
she's home
I well just so you know you know just
little extra extra places that I can
sleep as I'm traversing about you know
yes so I think I guess that's fine
perhaps oh yeah do you not have multiple
houses senpai
uh do do I I mean I have one in the
Japan in the old Japan server because it
was gifted to me but I don't use it and
you know I am I am loyal loyal to my
roots baby
I see
you're so cute
everybody to leave these memories behind
you know I know what to mean so try to
be in both okay okay I will try to make
time and both yeah it sounds good oh
yeah
I did thank you for giving me a turkey
Senpai never forget about Phoenix and
also wait can you um you didn't leave a
sign but I can write for you what you
would say I'll do I can do it next time
no tell me I'm writing right now
what was your impression I write it down
pretty but pretty but it needs work
needs unfinished
okay
wow
three like naughty Teddy
I ran out of letters but let me delete
this
uh
wait what eh I missed how can you not go
back ah pretty but
unfinished needs work
and then
[Music]
wait you're such an underwhelming
feedback
so sad it's so nice but there's also
there's just a lot of things that you
know you're like this isn't finished
well this one isn't finished well
impression on you huh yeah I guess she
did there's a lot of stuff like that
like that watch unfinished stuff what's
that
yeah
we're gonna build a hobby house together
Kiara okay okay
but for now let's let's say goodbye and
stop stop our students yeah that's fine
I'll go okay I'll be cooking out yeah
just one notice I'm moving Baldur's Gate
to tomorrow instead because my
my stuff didn't arrive my camping stuff
didn't arrive so I can't film tomorrow
guys so I'll be streaming tomorrow
good luck and Goldie's gate
no no no no tomorrow we're streaming all
together with Advent again we're going
to be doing a Japanese Crescent stream
what no why not
because uh we had to reschedule to next
week because all of us were already
booked up
on so they're going to be teaching
Advent most proficient ones well I found
out shiori is actually pretty good at
Japanese too and I'm really confused you
never mentioned it what
yeah she just was sitting there and she
just like on stream randomly just
perfectly read something just started
talking Japanese and I was like what the
[\h__\h] I was like what I need to just
don't mention this I need to investigate
oh sudden sudden hidden Japanese she's
hiding her full power she's not
unleashing it yet yum she's scary I love
her wow then maybe she will have all the
answers tomorrow I know she's gonna like
meanwhile everyone thinks I'm good at
Japanese when I suck and then like
coyote is gonna come up and be like
um actually
[Laughter]
what has she
okay I want I'm interested in how how
you will do and how she already will do
don't don't look forward to it I'm bad
I'm bad
speaking of I need to go do my Japanese
lesson oh is it happening now
you have a Japanese it's just Anki it's
just I just need to do my Japanese flash
cards oh okay so I can get lunch yes yes
thank you guys for watching our
Minecraft corner
yes thank you for coming and yeah a
little little trip down memory line is
that how you say it Memory Lane yeah
Memory Lane yes memory lane
and yeah and so more Minecraft maybe
soon maybe yes maybe
yep we can get the we can get the wings
yes yes and hopefully next time you and
Advent can check out uh everything oh
yes successfully next time this would be
good I think people's internet is
already fixed so okay
wonderful and thank you guys for
watching
myself
[Laughter]
[Music]
pineapple stream album POV
police
yes stream stream pineapple stream POV
extreme Kyoto's music or else please do
this is a threat this is a threat indeed
no this doesn't mean I just did just a
just a polite polite pushing you to
listen to good music yeah thank you
it's decryption chat okay yes
bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]