[Music]
n
you want to know what I just said well
first first I said oh high then do you
know what I said I said gosh I can't
even tell you how many times I was
checking that everything was set up for
this I'm not even kidding that is that's
what I said and then I I was muted I was
I was muted as I said that to be fair
that's not what what is happening to me
[Music]
what what okay stop this stop Universe
stop trolling me
what um the universe knows that I'm
super nervous right now and it's just
just really rubbing it in my face
okay making it worse
um hi I was double not even double I was
checking things I've checked a lot of
times more times and then doing some
last minute final adjustments that I
don't even know if they're improvements
or not they might have made things worse
but I didn't check if I was muted that I
didn't check um anyways oh
hi
B sorry I got excited animal is
influencing me I hear bow bow or not
even here I see bow bow I must bow bow
bow bow good bow bow to
you chat come
here there you
go are you for chat are you what is
happening chat okay there we go chat was
frozen what
is
why okay there we go okay there we go
there we
go I think I think that foko already
mentioned I'm not sure because I wasn't
able to watch foko morning but they did
ask if they could mention if they were
in this stream which they are if they
didn't mention it then I spoiled it but
I told them that they could mention it
but I was thinking I wanted to wait for
for um a certain time like not time on
the clock for something to
happen and I'm going to see if it
happens I'm not going to tell you what
though oh okay y yes I have guess if you
oh yeah by the way this is the
continuation of my birthday karaoke
because if you cannot remember I
was blessed with a Japanese
[Music]
cold in the weeks or not we the yeah
within the days
weeks fall or if I can't I think right
now leading up to my
birthday which would have been the time
I would have proberly recorded all of
the karaoke by the way this is I am live
right now hello
I am here there might be some latency
but I am I am live you are hearing me
within a minute of me speaking YouTube
are you for YouTube I just said I was
live YouTube I just said I was live
who's listening to me who is out there
who has this control and why why why do
you
care why do you care so much about me
like why are you messing
with me what
why anyways am am I
live am
[Music]
I
that was a good
one okay that was not YouTube I do not
know I do not know what just happened oh
hi oh hi I have no idea what that was
that wasn't YouTube that was my entire
computer being silly however chat did
not stop so it wasn't internet
disconnection because chat kept going
but everything else just gave gave up so
I have absolutely no idea what what just
[Music]
happened
anyways what was I talking about oh yes
oh my gosh sorry what what why
why is this a side a side of what should
I should I just cancel no no I'm kidding
I'm that was a bad joke it was a bad
joke because as I was saying
this is the part two of my of of
my birthday karaoke where had guests
join me but I got a really bad cold
right before so I wasn't able to record
everybody and I'm not going to jinx it
I'm not going to jinx it I'm live right
now but the karaoke is all pre-recorded
I do that for reasons especially for
Japanese songs so the singing you'll
hear is pre-recorded but I am live in
this moment I'm literally just sitting
in singing to it um
yes anyways everyone was supposed to be
within one stream but I got the cold and
I wasn't able to sing all the
songs and I feel very bad for those
guests who submitted things on time and
had to wait two months but it's here I'm
here now and I recorded everything I I
really appreciate them all waiting I
ended up kind of choosing who to do in
the first one based on if I already knew
the song really well and if the song was
not too difficult so the songs today are
songs I either did not really know
before or they're songs that are really
really hard to sing for me at
least so that's how this uh
split the split uh was decided oh yeah
ad been submitted theirs um before debut
yeah yeah yeah mhm I couldn't
I
anyways yeah I was super happy cuz I was
like can even before I met Advent I was
like Hey can can the new girls join this
it's going to be after they debut and
it's not a live
collaboration and I was told yeah yeah
this is fine so
yay and then I ended up not being able
to have any of Advent on the first
karaoke because bi Boo's got scuffed by
me because I forgot to export the
instrumental track with it so it was
just
Acappella but I have it it's all ready
today this is going to go swimmingly
also I have a premiere of an original
song in MV after this
and the song had a bit of a awkward
scheduling it was supposed to come out
at 12: at
midnight in every time zone but it ended
up just becoming available after
midnight after when when it was midnight
in J jst interesting I highly recommend
you wait to watch with the with the
music video
though I highly recommend you wait that
was not anticipated yes um I I think it
happened to a few other members
though so maybe it's something that is
new like something something's
changed anyways I have to I have to I
have the pleasure of singing with all of
my guests today who were able to submit
and I just want to again say big thank
you to them to everyone who submitted
and now of course especially those who
had to be put on hold I am so grateful
for everyone that submitted their their
karaoke cuz it's so fun it's so fun
singing with everyone and hearing
everyone it makes me so so happy so I'm
so happy I can finally do this and have
everybody U be heard and I get to sing
with everybody now yes yes yes yes yes
yes okay shall we get started because I
have like a little over an hour to do
YouTube I Swear YouTube was that just
my was that was that just me
me
okay oh my gosh YouTube please I will
cry I'm just kidding I won't cry I might
I might do things you don't want me to
do though
anyways
anyways the first guest shall be bi booo
because she was
almost she was so close to being one of
my guests on the first
one but I have
her and I have her I'm ready she's been
ready and this time I have the
instrumental but I don't have the f I
closed the folder somehow of course I
did all right bioo get over here I have
to scoot over to make room everyone's uh
pretty big this
timeo beep beep I was prepared yes I
have her I have
her you've been wondering where she is
she's right
here okay okay let's get this party
started I have to keep track of the
audio mixers
okay are you ready bi boo of course
she's ready she's been ready for month
she's she's good to go
okay
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
say
foree
to take and
I look go I st
[Music]
my
sorry I noticed that we're having some
latency bioo and I we can't seem to sink
our our head banging
together something something's a bit off
I think it might be me I I think I it
might be me that's off it's totally not
me controlling both and the
[Music]
latency the Ping we're having some ping
issues be
boo that's
okay that was fine anyways thank you bi
Boo for singing with
me she going to she go now thank thank
you
[Music]
finally yes we sing what's the song
called connect I think connect on people
oh now she
appeared so that's that's where you went
I
[Music]
see thank you for singing with me and
for being so patient I'm so sorry and
for even being teased
thinking from the first
Dream oh thank you super
cute cute cute cute cute cute such a
good good choice especially
now especially now
after I'd say well it's been out over
two months now of knowing Advent like oh
that really does fit
her and she's even aren't you watching M
Maga the members or something
anyways thank you B boo I'm really bad
at transitioning
this she is I she
[Music]
am nice thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
very much I don't have a set list also
the background is the thumbnail that's
the current thumbnail of my MV it's
going to change once it's released by
the way you guys know do you know what
they are I saw some interesting guesses
I didn't think there'd be questions as
to what what it is but I I did see
people being like Oh my gosh is that a
certain cartoon Mouse's like
pants or
belly
nostrils yeah fingerprints fingerprints
eyes eggs
portal they're clearly
eggs I think it's pretty clear what they
[Music]
are yeah they're just two two they're
not even server they're just two
ovals anyways now it is the difficult
part I don't know who who who should go
next who is next I just knew that bi Boo
the bioo is going to be
first oh gosh who who
who
who but you guys you guys are you no I
said that I want to wait until a special
thing happens for fuok but if it doesn't
happen then then it then I I will still
sing
with it's happened nearly every stream
in recent memory so it ought to
happen
who gosh oh goodness don't worry about
that the cough is gone what's happening
now is I don't know what that is um
anyways let's do um um um let's
do yes I know I know who we shall do or
do what no who who will I bring
forth who's going to do the sing with
me
she's she
oh there we
[Music]
go Kyla
h Hello nice microph oh my gosh what a
nice microphone you have there
oo my gosh it's like her arms around me
oh that's so cute wait that's
[Music]
adorable that's adorable oh my gosh I
love
this I'm so comfy right now oh my gosh
we even have a fire to keep us warm with
that microp oh my
gosh Kyla let's sing together
oh she's just she's just shy once the
music starts you you'll start making
noise right
right I'm sure let's
[Music]
see take take oh she's today M Senpai
hope that all your wishes come true and
let's sing bye
[Music]
together
fore
[Music]
speee
fore
[Music]
foree
fore do
know
so do
[Music]
knowe kind of
foree
[Music]
fore
foree but
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
for thank you so much for inviting me
with Senai and enjoy your day happy the
bless see you see you see you soon
[Music]
bye-bye oh
hi
what was that Interruption don't kill my
mood with
KY Windows please wasn't even
Windows my goodness what is
happening Kyla I'm Kyla
help Kyla help my PC or some I don't
know what what it is something's being
silly
Kyla
Kyla I love you she's she's so cute I'm
I'm sorry I'm not supposed to say it I'm
not supposed to call her cute but I'm
I'm sorry how how do you not how do you
not call her cute after that how do you
not oh my
goodness Kyla thank you for singing with
me and for holding me
close what's that thing you have
wait oh is it it's a pipe I thought it
was a recorder for a second it's not
it's not lit is it you're not setting my
hair on fire are you no no only your mic
only the microphone's lit the hammer oh
it's going to oh it looks like a pipe oh
my gosh it's sorry I'm sorry for showing
that oh my gosh it is a hammer I was
going to say I can't I don't see it's a
flute it's a it is a FL wait wait wait I
was it's not a recorder it's a
FL I I've only made wrong guesses
here let's see it's a hammer flute oh my
gosh oh I oh my gosh cuz she's a black
oh my
gosh I'm sorry Kyla I'm sorry
Kyla it's just you're so
cool
[Music]
Kyla
she wouldn't do that she'd be
like thank you Kyla thank you Kyla for
for singing with me you chose a super
cute song to sing but it was a song that
I've heard that I was like I knew I knew
that but I didn't know know it I didn't
know how to sing it or the verses or
anything so thank thank you for teaching
me or indirectly teaching me I taught it
I for thank you for
motivating me to learn it there we go
thank you it's a cute
[Music]
bye-bye
bye-bye thank you
Kyla I didn't set up a guest a guest
list sheet a guest list sheet of guests
a sheet of
guests I think that's okay I didn't do
that last time
either anyways what was that song called
tabon probably
[Music]
tabon was it called
tabon
[Music]
[Laughter]
tabon okay so we' had
bioo
Kyla who's
next who
[Music]
oopsie
pardon oh you you pretty thing would you
like to sing with
me you
there you there with the Luscious Hair
full of
life it doesn't look like it's wilting
today oh yes oh here please please
please oh wait oh my
goodness oh oh there we
[Music]
go
OHA oh fa fa and I we say yesterday
together yes you guys watch the counil
council plus Iris now called promise
when we're together did you guys watch
the
collaboration I we sang together in
different three different songs we sang
Together We Sing baby metal I'm really
happy we could sing baby
metal I was um trying to think of ideas
of songs for us cuz I knew that we'd be
a unit for the the 3D collab and I was
like oh what can we do we could do
something like serious or we could do
something that's serious but
also really funny
I was like I was trying I was between
presenting uh headbang and uh and uh doy
doie morning we went with doy doie
morning I think it was great I think it
was
awesome we had pretty great song Choices
for our 3D CL if I don't say so myself
oh for mocha
agree baby midal m
M
FAA you want to sing more baby
[Music]
metal she's smiling that says it
all that says it all all right let's get
this set up and let's
rock okay
ready ready ready ready
[Music]
ready
[Applause]
[Music]
say
fore oh oh
[Music]
say say
say
[Music]
foree
w w
[Music]
w wo w
w wow w
[Music]
w w
w my
[Music]
[Applause]
St
[Music]
fore
w w
[Music]
w w w
w wow w
wow
[Music]
oh
hi thank you FAA for choosing this song
for singing with me by the way if you
guys didn't know I basically made this
giant Master list of songs songs I knew
we could get instrumentals for it
included songs that I didn't really know
I was just like I'd like to give them
options you know I don't want to have
you know too few songs so that people
look at and go I don't know any of these
so but I'm so happy she chose this song
in particular I didn't know I didn't
think anyone would would choose one and
I already knew it it's easy however the
reason she was not in the first one was
because I lost certain files
when I went to Japan and I uh I was I
this was not going to work with a
call it was not going to
work so I'm happy we could do it now
that song is so very hard to sing
whether you have a cold or
not thank you
fun thank you for seeing Oh my gosh I
have to go faster what am I doing okay
thank you thank
you
I could just delay the premier am I
allowed to do that what's the point now
ready oh sure we'll see we'll see where
we're where we're
at
okay who's
[Music]
next who's
next
how
about you
there you you at the
[Music]
nuts wait no not you no the not not you
the person there there she
is yes you
hello oh hi why do I think that they are
going to respond to me this is so sad
I'm basically I'm just singing with
cardboard
cutouts that's
okay
hello we're going to sing a song
together we both have look at us with
our hoods o we both have brown hair and
we have hoods ooh wait she don't need be
smug right now wait I can be like wait
we can I can be like
you what
the can I look down I can't look down as
as well as her
wait what is she looking
at what's on the
floor I don't know but we're going to
sing a
song let us do
it
[Music]
hello Mommy happy birthday I hope you
have a great time and I hope you have a
happy happy happy
birthday yes and let's sing together now
to celebrate mom's
birthday y
[Music]
foree
speee
[Music]
L day you made not a fall asleep in bed
of course got a
[Music]
morningday I'll protect you from night
baby
[Music]
could she
for let slow flowing
day go
[Music]
lonely lonely day I fall asleep in bed
got a
morning I protect you from
[Music]
baby
fore
[Music]
like aely lonely day you not a fall
asleep in bed a kind of morning
for I'll protect you from night
baby
[Music]
hi hi
again oh you didn't hear that no oh you
didn't hear that never mind nothing it
totally didn't Loop and I didn't hear
Rea say oh hi
[Music]
M oh my
goodness again that was not an easy
so not for me at least this this so
smooth her voice is so smooth oh my
gosh
soprano
beautiful but I heard TOA Senpai or I'm
sorry Senpai to Su Pardon Me cover that
song and i' had been meaning to listen
to it more like to learn it cuz I was I
liked it but I I don't always learn
songs I tell myself that I'm going to
learn but now because of
this I learned it thank you thank you
for singing it with me super pretty song
it sounded really pretty me sound
pretty
[Music]
goodbye thank
you
okay okay okay okay
okay what you who have we strung with so
far recap
time uh beu
Kyla FAA
and D now we are almost halfway through
I'm taking forever oh goodness gracious
to be fair though we had some obstacles
with YouTu I should stop talking who's
next Who's Next oh
you you fair fair lady
oh Fair
late
ooh
kiaba I don't know why they're appearing
at the bottom of the screen this works
this works perfectly oh how beautiful
you look oh my
goodness she Rises From the Ashes
exactly we're going to sing a song
aren't we
Kara this was probably the hardest song
for me to learn for this entire thing
it was really
hard but it was again a song I kind of
was wanting to learn anyway so thank you
for being that extra
shove shove push but same thing thank
you thank you for shoving me for pushing
me shoving why does push like thank you
for pushing me it sounds good but why
does thank you for shoving me it sound
[Music]
bad anyways let's sing together
kiaha
[Music]
am oh my
God
[Music]
do got this to
you do do
[Music]
do do you know
China CH China it's China CH
China
[Music]
[Applause]
got
[Music]
po
yay happy birthday M thanks for singing
with me this very difficult song Yes
bye-bye have fun
byebye that was indeed
difficult
moly but again a song I've been wanting
to learn I would love to know if I could
actually hit those notes like and be
stable I don't I I was just like
screaming I can't even I don't think I
could do it in this very moment I
couldn't I know I totally just did it
totally just just did that but um I
don't think I could do it again just
just at this very moment yes that that's
that that's yes what's that song
[Music]
called
godish
godish yeah come e
po that's what it means no I thought
that's how I learned what PO is po po po
yeah po po boy boy
boy anyways k waah Ki waah wa thank you
I took a long time to
learn I was trying to S it when I had a
cold too it was so I I wanted to I was I
was close to tears at some point I was
really
frustrated it's frustrating having a
cold and trying to
sing thank you kiaha for singing with me
and choosing a challenging song I think
we we conquered together thank
bye-bye thank you thank you all
righty recap time we've had beu Kaa fa
Ru and now kiaha I'm testing your memory
here we're also testing my
memory the the brain
game
H who's next
uh who's next Who's Next who's next
um um let me check something real quick
I don't think the thing I wanted to set
up is going to happen not even I I can't
set it
up something I wanted to occur naturally
I don't think is going to
happen
so we'll give we'll give a few more
minutes for the opportunity to preent
prevent present itself
if it doesn't that's
fine but for now let's sing
with
this where where are
you wait where are
you where what wait where is
she what where where did you go where a
that's
me wait what the
heck oh there oh there you
are
you yeah as far as you
go
okayo okay
okay wish you all the best thank you uh
I will
see no what together okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah
okay okay you will go first by the way
okay okay Ready Set
[Music]
Go
for
[Music]
why did you choose the short
song so
many
air
[Music]
for
for let's
[Music]
go
got
it I forgot this part I forgot the next
[Music]
part
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday thank
you
[Music]
birth day to you baby
oh I just realized some something
coo I don't have to wait for opportunity
to you you are the opportunity that has
presented itself to me thank you thank
you
for I was waiting for animal to do that
so then I would bring
Ina
wait thank you for Sing for Singing With
Me
Goo thank you I appreciate that because
um
because I also don't really know that
song and
forgot didn't know how Parts go so you
you thank you thank you for sparing
me lots of
[Music]
fun thank you
coo you're a silly one aren't
you she's a
silly there she
[Music]
goes there she goes
thank you oh my gosh thank you
Kobo
okay I will now bring twin twin twins
that go they don't go they don't quite
go like that they go bow
bow oh there they're there wait no come
here come here come here come here don't
be shy come here come here oh don't
don't be sh they're not shy
I I got I got to scoot over a little
[Music]
more oh
hello I'm wait what I'm what button to
my
hello this is
good no there there's too much space
between us
come bow
bows okay let's sing together this is so
exciting
I cannot tell you how exciting it is to
sing with them oh my gosh when I got the
tracks I got I was so this is the best
thing ever oh my
gosh cuz they s they sing together it's
amaz it's
great okay okay
okay background music be gone all right
all right oh my gosh this is totally
live and they're just so good at
multitasking they're not talking right
now because they're focused on the
chat hello hi I'm so excited to sing
with you I'm going to sing with them
right now okay
[Music]
okay
you
[Music]
for for
you
oh
me I will give you all my
[Music]
love I will give you all my
[Applause]
love
good s be in love with
you to do
it Ling
[Music]
you
I will give you all my life
[Music]
Now give me
so I will give you all my
[Music]
[Applause]
love
who be in love with you
[Music]
you I will give you all my
love now the guy
of
my
I
[Music]
not I will give you all
[Applause]
[Music]
my be in love with
you
[Music]
to
loving
you me
ohing
youing you la
Laing
Laing you
[Music]
M happy
birthday we hope you have a hoot and how
of the birthday have fun thank
[Music]
youall I did I did have a Hooten
birthday thank
you
[Music]
oh my gosh they're so cute I'm
sorry I'm
sorry I want to pet pet pet I want to
pet I don't I can't use my hands right
now though I'm I'm too busy
[Music]
streaming I want you pet I know I'm not
supposed to touch their ears and I won't
but I just want it to be known that I
want to touch their ears but I will not
not do not worry I will not they just
they're just really
cute even no scratches behind the ear
the tail I won't yes the tail is very
it's very tempting to pet the Tails but
wait I won't pet the tail I won't pet
the Tails I just want you to know I I
that I want to because they're really
cute but I
won't I won't oh my goodness animal did
you hear me talking about petting other
animals I'm
sorry don't be jealous don't be jealous
anyways thank
you thank youo for singing with me
excellent song choice this was again a
song I knew but didn't you know know how
to sing cuz I didn't know the words or
anything I just you know knew it I knew
of it had heard it but thank you for
choosing this song now now I I I know it
know
it thank you I even went to the original
I was like oh my gosh what is this
because the voice was not what I was
expecting I probably heard like whole
Live members cover it to be honest I'm
not cultured I'm sorry from what I'm not
entirely sure what it's from I know it's
from an older anime but I was like oh so
cut see so I tried to to rep to
replicate thank you thank you
for thank you thank you I hope you have
a good rest of rest of your don't why am
I talking to them like they
chat I don't know what they're going to
go do now but I wish them luck with
whatever they're doing right
now but also thank you M for watching
thank you thank you thank
you they're so sweet they're so
supportive oh my goodness they're
precious precious I will protect I will
protect them so that they can protect
you okay
okay who's next we only have like 10
minutes thankfully or sadly there's only
two people
left I saw that I think narissa dropped
by Z why are you saying Zeta was in the
last one you sillies I already sing with
Zeta but yeah I believe oh hello yes hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi niss where are
you where are
you this you this isn't you where there
you
are I don't understand why they're all
down here oh are you big or am I small I
can hold on I'll
make I'll make myself bigger hold on
hold
on one
second here we go my are are we about
the same
now we both we both I think had this
discussion like we care about this are
our heads the
[Music]
same got good good enough I think I
think this is this is good enough okay
this will do keep in mind I have a hood
like
yeah keep in
[Music]
mind okay we're going to sing together
let's get this show on the road I don't
have much oh wait that was the wrong
thing
okay all
[Music]
right to
you yes my love to you
[Music]
you yes my love to
you
[Music]
fore stay with
me my
[Music]
foray with
me now what should I do that
[Music]
fore
spee need know
[Music]
you stay with
me my
[Music]
own
I my on my Stay With
[Music]
Me
[Applause]
[Music]
stay with
me my
own
night
I
[Music]
don't stay with
me stay with
me
world
[Music]
night and K together in the middle
a
[Music]
oh my
goodness wherea
crazy Miss
Nessie I forgot that's the nickname I I
gave you
forever she's crazy so
smooth like Smooth smooth P smooth
smooth power like powerful smooth
oh my goodness thank you for singing
with
me es especially cuz niss and I we're
going to do a different song first but
then really last minute we found out we
were not allowed to do that song so poor
Nissa had recorded already and then she
took the time during her busy schedule
to record a different song and I'm glad
I I'm glad we were able to sing this
song together so thank you thank you
narissa thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
bye bye okay we have very little time
very little time very quickly last guest
Show Yourself where are you where are
you no where is she where is she where
are you that's it it's time to do this
where are you oh there she okay there
you are there you
are
hello
quickly Now quickly we got to get get it
together get it
together this is a great uh Carver cut
out isn't
it all right let's sing okay okay what
what are we doing wait hold
on yeah let's go hey happy birthday M
thank you tonight we are
hero yeah yeah get down hum yeah do it
get down get down get the guitars out
and go crazy where's my this
[Music]
is of Flavor Flavor Flavor just want to
hold your
hands want to hold your
hands just want to hold your
hands hey people let's go back to
[Music]
zero
are you ready high respect the
[Music]
hero hi hello put your hands up okay
come on on the
[Music]
way who is the master who calls my
favorite name is that forever ever
[Applause]
ever
okay instrumental break
[Music]
okay you know what to do you know what
to do what are they supposed to do what
do they do what are you guys doingit
what do you do
what go on let's
[Music]
go am I in time I don't think I
am
[Music]
[Applause]
just want to hold your
hands
ooh okay they're kind of sweaty though
okay I'm Going's sing it together come
on
okay okay just want to hold your
head just want to hold your head
just want to hold your
hands just want to hold your
hands
like it's really
low just want to hold
your I swear I respect the
[Music]
hero hey hey come on hold your
hand happy birthday bye thank you
we sing the song and I managed to extend
the premiere by 5 minutes I delete the
premiere by 5 minutes right that's okay
because I'm going to redirect thank you
everybody for watching again big big big
big big big
big thank you to all the members who
sing with me this stream and my last
stream too everybody sent in their
submission to at the same time s thank
you thank you thank you so much um um um
we're going to go watch the premiere if
you didn't know I'm premiering original
song with an MV uh the MV is premiering
now I guess because of the little stuff
that
happened so you if you want to watch the
premier we go do that it started i t it
to stop that's okay okay I'm going to go
now bye thank
[Music]
you