[Music]
byebye we're here again is this this is
J sword right huh
[Music]
wait this was I have my stuff in here
yeah my stuff is in here okay my stuff
is still in
here uh I heard that I could make stuff
out of
these is that true I remember I can't
remember what are these though potato
salad full
inventory full inventory should have put
stuff away down
[Music]
maybe oh recipe
book oh wait did I always have a recipe
book right click to use oh those
mine right
[Music]
click with a cooking
butt okay I don't need
doors sure
m i can I have another
backpack
huh can
I baked potato wait wait wait how good
is a baked
potato oh oh did I eat it no I
didn't
H there's a quest for that how do I tell
how much stuff heals
me CU you know the king said we has to
we have to get
ready oh so I want to get
[Music]
ready I'm so confused everything
changed where is is up where is
W this looks
[Music]
big then what is this here what is
that
it's what is
this
oh I don't know uh it's the library
[Music]
can't open
it does seem very
[Music]
accessible is the princess
okay what does that
say what is
this I can't get in nobody wants me to
go in anywhere
[Music]
H I can't
in what is this this looks
frightening Scarlet one Library my phone
number oh hello oh
BBY hello my sweet client how have you
been um I'm you won your case yes
outside of
yeah that's good I guess that's why I
didn't have to pay you anything
yeah you well you did pay me though not
much um is this the library want to talk
to you about actually oh what what do
you have to talk to me about I thought
about it for a while right and don't
don't you think you should support your
local business owners in times of War
have I have very much supported F of my
and look where I have came oh yeah but
I'm not part of
fart I'm part of cilia Law Firm Cecilia
CeCe it's the official name Cecilia from
Cece Cecilia from cilia oh that's pretty
long should I short it do you have a a
an
office yeah I do
[Music]
actually yeah
this is your office that's my off did
you just laugh in my office it it looks
like a a big
chair well it's I'm a startup I'm a
startup company I'm just starting out
you were my first client this is your
start out yeah would you like to invest
in my startup I have invested a lot in
fart and I think I'm okay but I'm not
part of
fart this is a law firm it's completely
different no risk
so far all of our clients have been
happy and all of our cases have been
100% successful uh can you give me some
references yeah so there was one case of
a a a a a wonderful wonderful pink one
that was falsely accused of having
stolen money from pamart and I defended
her and through my dedication uh to my
job and my client she was successful
with a 99.8%
increase margin in her profit maybe the
success was a
[Music]
coincidence but but I thought I was a
good
lawyer I'm happy you think that
yeah what what are you
doing pulling
out oh nothing I'm just thinking about
my options right now don't worry about
it
okay farewell
client again I feel
threatened don't forget to not me
[Music]
what oh it's
gone fight
[Music]
me what is this
here oh women's only no King
allow oh
[Music]
what is this
here I can open it there's stuff for me
to
take
[Music]
M
water it's
it's comfy look at the
[Music]
Ron I'm getting
sleepy I should
get up from the B
my where can I find the so it feel like
You' be more fun with with more people
though
[Music]
comy what is this it's
shiny
oh this is a a cage
can't open
it can't open
it can't jump
[Music]
in What is
this do not just grave here rip
[Music]
wait uh it looks a bit threatening in
here what's this stuff glass
bottle
oh I should have want
this oh it's a ofe his stuff
a melon slice
the water
maybe
oh
[Music]
sugar that looks
frightening is this the
grave how do I get out of here just jump
out I can okay
good not a very good grave
[Music]
huh oh I should eat
something wait how much does potato
salad
[Music]
help oh not that much oh but does it
make me Speedy a jump boost am is it
helping I don't
[Music]
know well I left the door
open should I make other
food oh there's more stuff
[Music]
here
stuff ah stain BS
[Music]
fish there always been stairs up
here
oh secret
area's
[Music]
go three beds
well uh is there anything I should
put maybe I'll put this
away I don't need
[Music]
that maybe this is okay for
now okay oh no no mine ah
[Music]
there
okay there we go
okay I go oh there's a
hole what is this threatening looking
place
though e was the
oh the fling place is the light
oh work in progress do not
enter I can't go up oh
okay what is
[Music]
happening it doesn't really have any
books
though
no can no I can't go that way h what's
at this Library
hi what is this this looks like a
bank no just a hang
out libr
plot I should eat some food what food
what food will help
heal 2,000 coins huh what's with that oh
only sold
29 29 tickets what with that
[Music]
huhuh
no are you
asleep are you as
sleep you keep on doing this you look
sleepy huh have a good
sleep huh what is this
though berries
I don't
know eat
[Music]
another oh Mason were you here
before feel anything you like is this
his
house
oh is this queen
already Mario's Castle
oh can't go in
[Music]
wow I could live up
here I can go in
oh is this for princess
be supposed
to K me
[Music]
because and
upstairs oh is this there
Crown
here what's down
here what's this
what's
this can I get out of
here that's frighten I need to get out
of
[Music]
here not
good not
good no okay let's leave must be the
dungeon I don't know but I know I don't
like it almost up again too I need to
eat again
[Music]
to leave the king and get a real queen
with
her she loves
you she should should iose to her sorry
am I I propose to her yeah yeah you
should you should you know what I
support you Queen you know what I shall
prepare I you can make it maybe you
should get her a present maybe you
should ask her what she want like as a
present and then you should give it to
her and then you is the queen planning
to propose to something right away thank
you not Cecilia artist critic for your
support you finally got my memory back
yeah I'm also wait I'm also a love
advisor ask ask me for advice oh love
ADV what isn't
she today I shall propose and so I
should prepare something maybe here's
what I'm going to do too mhm I'm going
to build
something oh and write her
letter and IDE and then I'm going to
send my pigon to the sky because the
queen right now is not here the
criminal I have you should also give her
some flowers in the color of her and
you some flowers blue and pink yeah you
have some flowers that's my
advice okay I think it'll work well
thank you then do you maybe want
to want
to
what what do you me want
to give me a tip for my Serv advisor tip
what um
well you expensive
night just like just a small
just a small tip of uh 100
coins
okay nobody
nobody thank you very much my queen I
wish you the best of love and best of
luck can you gather some flowers for me
oh yeah I have some I'll give you some
thank you
[Music]
nobody what are you guys do in
our looking at the art was doing anour
looking at the
art I see over here this one is called
allow in uh yeah we open the door this
one is called enies
to what do you think how did can I get
in I can't get in
[Music]
Jonathan don't you remember that I'm of
honorary member of the blue Cerulean
Guild and I literally own every land
so
youg why are you so against me being
here towards the queen who is our
Queen gamber what who is a queen not
even her
name me I I
do excuse me can can you explain now
what happened I want my money back
Jonathan what's her name again I want
your I want my money back D Gander you
feel you are the queen of Evergreen
we've talked about this no the best is
ever
green
yes I want my money back and I uh you're
not my KN anymore you really got
to call excuse
me excuse they didn't
notice they didn't
[Music]
notice can't believe everyone is
betraying me why she playing to Mary
though I would have like loved to build
something if I was like
[Music]
hello
hello it's me I'm stuck in this
place oh yeah oh oh my God okay I don't
think they know this it's
okay it's
okay
OU
okay it's okay it's okay but who is she
planning to
marry this is important information
[Music]
who am I supposed to
tell
[Music]
huh Queen is planning to propose to
someone how should I tell someone who
should I tell
[Music]
wait
no
[Music]
no get you does Princess know I don't
know where he is
though maybe I'll just have to keep the
information to my myself please go
please go
[Music]
please I'm going to sell wait if I sell
my potato
salad then what can I buy to make more
money with it
[Music]
huh
huh why don't you tiet
well fite still owes me my
money my winnings I got my damages paid
by norissa but V Mar still owes my
winnings go to the
pit where is the
pit I don't think I've been
[Music]
there is it over
here huh
[Music]
J Master
oh
[Music]
really you here
where is the pit is this the pit this is
the Coliseum
no
huh Amber
coin
coin H
coin have I ever been in this
building maybe not
[Music]
I
can't never been here
either a big
wall got
W
oh there we are I didn't see that
[Music]
Queen Eternal
Tander I've never seen such a
person who is this
Jonathan it is my Queen T gander is that
different from your
Pearl yes it is very different from my
Pearl well maybe I have to go my Pearl
they yes they are two different
people shouldn't you make one of your
Pearl
um mayhaps mayhaps I should I just it
may take some time do you like the
statue of the queen though I don't know
if it looks like her it looks just like
her I've never seen her are you sure
she's really never seen her yes she is a
queen she has treated me with such Grace
and kindness
oh well I'm glad for you thank you thank
you Moco I appreciate
it you're welcome about you well how has
things been since um everything has
happened to you I'm trying to learn how
to cook yeah you're trying to I see you
have potato salad in your hands we need
to prepare for
it what are you preparing
for final battle final you have word of
a final final thing happening The King
The King The King it is quite
terrifying well I I have words that do
you remember the person who was chasing
you down and calling you a criminal
there was many people including yourself
well do you remember who started it
all
NOA it seems that she's dead what the
dead the witch she she's a witch she's a
witch it seems she has died do you feel
any anything towards that she kissed me
I feel my goodness she kissed you and
you feel sad that she kissed you or that
she was dead that she's dead someone who
kissed me is now
dead my
goodness my why why did she die
she died
yesterday because of a misunderstanding
I do not know she was the way yes there
is yes T
Shakira oh sorry am I intruding I I I
can no you are not
intruding you come Feast your eyes on
the queen Tam Gander H she looks
marvelous today as every day as always
she her beautiful Gand is good but what
happened she died from a
misunderstanding that's it yes that's it
well does do you is Tam Gander alive
still Tam G she's on an
expedition she will return once the
Expedition is over and she will come
back to this Kingdom and Rule and take
her rightful place as Queen what about
yes no this is our Queen she's Our Queen
all of our Queen she's the queen of this
entire Kingdom she's married to the king
then what about Queen
nari what Melody l n
l the
one L yeah she is a queen of another
land she is not a queen of Le
bestl Tam gander is the queen of leest
of these this is true this is true yes
yes this is
confusing
like have you seen any statues of this
other queen that you were talking about
I have seen the the crown Crown throne
throne the throne the throne yes but if
she were a queen wouldn't there be
statues of
her this is the only statue I can see
yes this is the only statue in the lands
and is of our Queen T
gander therefore she is the queen but
I'm the Royal
puppy you are the Royal puppy of
Evergreen I assume
Evergreen yeah that is where Queen Mario
rules yes I should go check with her yes
go go with
haste
misconception misunderstandings are
dangerous huh not all queens have
statues there a big Castle though but
there's no
sign no statue there could be two
[Music]
statues so many queens only one the
kingdom Queen
n Queen H hello hello
good job oh my goodness so many
customers so many customers are going to
be
rich I much money so you're not getting
anything what is this that is okay you
have free
will what is this this is this this is
Nana 11 Nana 11 yes the sister store
Toom Mar but they are not related
oh not related H they offer the finest
highest quality meat as well as the
juiciest of berries we also have six
berries please you can have six
berries six berries six
berries oh what has happened this is
very inappropriate I'm so sorry oh I
don't know if a horse should be close to
food like that did not mean to pull the
horse do not worry the food is all
protected inside of these barrels where
nothing can contaminate them you have
freies H freebies yes we do offer
freebies I never go to free from fart in
fact nothing here cost any money
everything is
free what are you sure yes that is very
I like this yes it is here let me let me
give you your
berries and then I can assist you with
your
berries
two I don't know it's free M it's free I
like it's free for
free I got some
B oh she's invisible did you want a
freebie
Berry I would love a free Berry oh you
would like a free
Berry there is a queue there is a
queue I want the bero the bow bows do
you want a freebies she's a ghost what
happened to her I love freebies
for you
ni One thank you for your
business can I get more berries you can
get more berries oh there it is
here I like you can
[Music]
have
berries is this a good business so far
for
you I'm so sorry there was a ghost
whispering in my ear what is it that you
said is this a good business for you so
far it has been you are my second
customer it's going so well that's
good you have meat too I do are you
hungry for meat yes the highest quality
of
[Music]
meat do I need it no it's already cooked
just don't ask where it came from okay I
will eat mystery meat all right oh chice
not again pardon me I'm so sorry you had
to see
that there is ample supply all the
barrels all the barrels are full H
they're
overflowing yes with meat and
Berry that looks good thank you you
go 11 I like you're welcome spread the
word we are now open yes byebye thank
you for your patronage goodby bye
goodbye what is
this Haunter you must pay my hey do not
hurt her back ghost back gathan she has
killed me and my child what oh is that
you lady narissa Raven coft yes you look
so much her voice does sound familiar
yes it is very familiar the one who kiss
meent
yeah well I have an idea yes isn't there
what is your
idea in lady Shakira's memories in her
dungeon is there not a way for you to be
revived I am un sure I is there a way I
am a phoenix indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feathers to revive you and give you
another another turn didn't you kill her
no misunderstandings are dangerous
H let me I'm going to eat this oh open
all this stuff
open
open open okay I'm going to eat them
they heal a
[Music]
bit oh that was pretty
good wait I want to look at my
recipes a potato salad yes yes potato
salad nourishing
soup sugar
[Music]
I have
a how do I get this stuff
though slime
jump B in Fri
[Music]
St how do I get
sugar how do I get this stuff
[Music]
potato
salad potato
[Music]
salad I should make some more
hot
okay
[Music]
what make more stuff I get off okay
wait wait wait
wait I go like
[Music]
thisuh here like this I have more eggs
right
yeah I have a bunch of
stuff egg egg egg
egg W that's all my
eggs okay
[Music]
make it carrot egg
potato okay here we
[Music]
go there
okay I need more potatoes and carrots
then potatoes and carrots oh
[Music]
potatoes what is that enough potatoes
are
they
potatoes
potatoes I should probably make a lot of
potato salad huh
[Music]
oh I have lots of potatoes
now should try to get an equal amount
more okay lots of potatoes
[Music]
I need to make sure to have L
on I can't get berries from this though
no oh I can ah I can't
[Music]
get I have lots of carrots just a b more
carrots huh
[Music]
there
okay
and do I have enough be
r no okay maybe it's the other
one over
here I want to get melons
this good
enough
I'm oh I a lot of potatoes a right I
need to replant
right
[Music]
oops
just they don't need be
[Music]
fck I'm
replanting
I'm
[Music]
see that
is there wasn't many beat roots over
here it's okay
[Music]
Oh see it's all good it's okay
yeah see I planted them
[Music]
all there we go all
good all
good I don't need the of the SE though
oh there's more stuff
here this wasn't me
though oh my gosh there's
nothing a little it's not
[Music]
me see I'm good
enough
potato
[Music]
okay see this is
good can't build that
[Music]
okay this is
good I need more eggs though got the
eggs
from from
the the the person you over ouch over
here this person shopkeeper
right
yeah the egg okay egg oh they s ah they
sell other
stuff they sell
[Music]
bread
turn surprise box why did you tell a
fishing
rod
[Music]
okay I need a lot of egg
okay I'll stop
there okay
and
[Music]
cing two coins two coins two
coins that's all you're going to say not
hello just can I have
Oney I don't know I feel like I could
depend on you for two coins he I can
give you some pork
chops I would like pork
[Music]
chops just two coins two coins you want
that not 76 coins coins 76 I'll 76 too
76 I don't have much money I want them
cooked I don't know how to cook them oh
oh I could cook them for you and bring
them back okay I'll give you if you can
bring me back more pork chops I'll give
you that much
to are you sure you want this one moment
please one moment
please why is it like
this one I'm just sending you money why
do you need space
[Music]
oh my inventory is full oh I'm the
problem
really okay I'm not a problem
[Music]
anymore with me
please what it says I can only have one
active train at a
[Music]
time that's
disappointing do you have a trade
request
[Music]
okay
okay okay give me cooked pork chops okay
I will I will okay
byebye okay I'm going to
make stuff
[Music]
want okay there potato oh I can't put
potato in oh that's
strange oh no not
potato beetro oh I don't have enough
beetroot oh that's a problem
[Music]
I'm getting ready for the king like this
okay this is
good oh stop cuz I don't have enough
beat R now
[Music]
okay this is
good make a
[Music]
business this is a
business yeah for
battle I need
[Music]
be this is all the beat I planted
right okay let's see if that's
enough oh that's not
much I thought it would be
[Music]
more
okay maybe that was the problem I
thought I would have
more oh I have too much now okay
not
doing
be and
potato oops oops oops oops oops oops
oops
[Music]
there egg
all I can make is potato salad but
hopefully it'll be good enough for
[Music]
battle I feel like I would like
something that has a bit more of a a
blo but I don't
know is that all my
eggs okay it's all my eggs
[Music]
lots of
potatoes okay I can make baked
potatoes
okay not
that
[Music]
okay is it good
okay I don't want to get more of the
bead seeds I just want to get rid of
these
[Music]
ones I should I plant the potatoes
back maybe a bit
[Music]
yeah I
should I want to keep my potatoes though
cuz then I can make the the baked potato
right how I the here big
potato oh and
fold oh that's
good a plant of carrots
[Music]
this is good okay
and I don't need the beetroots
anymore I don't need
them okay I'm going to toss toss the
seeds
garbage garbage
garbage you okay
yeah what else heals
[Music]
well what else heals well
H potato beetro what's
that well maybe I should make more
potato salad
nourishing soup nourishing soup let me
look at my recipe book
over nishing
souping soup carrot
potato water
bucket how do I get a water
[Music]
bucket me me is good
how do I get meat
though get a bucket and pick up water
how do I get a bucket
though how do I make a
[Music]
bucket craft a bucket with iron always
looking craft a bucket with ir oh really
is it free
should I sell
mine some the
exra potato salad okay I'll give him my
extra potato
salad I want it from
there no I didn't mean to eat my potato
salad
[Music]
salid no
Sal and then and the juice is I can buy
stuff I I'll accept the
juice
okay I like very juice
oh what's this side quest I have oh that
is
a huh accept
it
huh
accepted okay I'm not too
sure oh I accepted the wrong
Quest
a I don't have enough room really really
really
[Music]
abandon C yes okay that makes sense I
guess 1
there
[Music]
okay confusing
H okay turn more yes one okay
[Music]
oh more
I need to get a good sword though too
[Music]
huh I have iron now should I make iron
items two more
huh I should probably get a shield too
huh
[Music]
than no thank are you okay that's what I
heard from you why do you say it like
that that's yeah wait what that's what I
heard from you I was copying you oh I'm
talking can you hear me normally now
yeah I can oh that's
weird suspicious very suspicious H very
suspicious no I'm suspicious of you no
I'm normal I was just making fun of
you huh the war is back every step I
take you disrespect me I'm not are you
really a
lawyer am I really a lawyer oh what did
you say are you really a
lawyer yeah I am really a lawyer one
second let me adjust your uh
amplification please speak again are you
sure you're not a
knight no I am a knight but I was uh I
did the I took the bar exam yes two days
ago and then I became a lawyer the
bikes the bar it's like a lawyer exam a
sounds like something a night would take
huh yeah that's why I did it
oopsie I really am a lawyer
don't I feel like I feel like we had
such a a good client lawyer relationship
I don't not understand where this
mistrust comes
from maybe I heard stuff from host you
know
around what was said about my
lawyer
uh
nothing oh nothing sometimes my ears are
strong that's all oh oh yeah like when
you H me okay bye
the ears your things
[Music]
huh what I feel like I can't run that
fast what else should I make I don't
know what to do with
theet sugar cane sugar
cane how do I make
sugar Mel see pumpkin seeds
[Music]
oh
them it's over
[Music]
here here this
thing huh it only makes
one oh each one makes one okay sugar
sugar sugar here
[Music]
yeah
okay what else what was in my rest of
[Music]
people okay potato salad have sweet
berries water
bucket find
you sweet
berries I
want where do I get sweet berries a
well I guess it's good
enough
50ish
okay I feel like I'm so
slow oh wait I don't need to make them
anything okay sweet B
good stain slime ball and sugar make
slime jump and then we can make
breakfast toast I don't know if
breakfast toast is any good
[Music]
though I had the slime in my what's it
the
[Music]
chest wait oops that's
frightening
I what
them okay and I wanted to go to okay
sweet ber okay slime Jam slime jam and
then I can make breakfast
toast do I have bread is there bread
anywhere I feel like someone in here has
bread
bread bread bread bread bread bread no
wait slime
J know what I'm just going to borrow
[Music]
that okay
yeah bread bread
buckets bucket
what can I use the bucket
I
[Music]
noodles butter how do I make butter
milk milk bucket
[Music]
I'll make breakfast toast then oh this
mine no no no where' they
go oh no where did my other one
go oh
no I left to
here
okay take
this b b a
St I'm just trying to make
[Music]
food St me St
B St
or I'm sure they won't know
this
[Music]
or huh
Papa huh that's right I have I have
something for where'd you go nobody know
okay and Ste I have Ste
[Music]
here
okay I can get
[Music]
out just
now
[Music]
yeah
maybe what's
here h
okay I wanted to make okay I have sugar
sugar so then I can make a sweet berries
okay sweetberries slme ball and
sugar
okay sweet
berries slime
ball
[Music]
and I don't know what are you talking
about I would like to give you your okay
give me a moment I'm making slime
jump give me a
moment do you know how to make
bread never made bread but we can make
bread
together I guess you need wheat do you
have wheat I have I think I have some
[Music]
wheat I don't have it with
me okay
oh I
see we are
three do you have more I have
six do you want six I'll do whatever you
have a lot of I can give you more
money you can give me more money yeah
what do you have for food
H you want I only have a little bit of
it right now you make bread I don't know
to make
bread um okay give me some
money I have much
money
[Music]
there9
byebye money I good wow
now I have some more food I Sal before
huh Can you show me how to make potato
salad uh you need all the ingredient
ingredients and a
[Music]
pot
okay I now have to finish off
this bread is not that expensive I'll
just buy the
bread
[Music]
okay bread slime
down haste yeah this is good I want
that how much does it heal though I like
being a
fast good
[Music]
I want to make sure I'm
ready
okay
and I see how how it
is I guess I'll go like
this okay let's see it
heal ah it heals a lot and it makes me
fast is is it do again maybe do it
that's good that's good maybe it's
better than potato
salad
[Music]
maybe mining
speed it's like running with to in my
mouth
[Music]
yeah I'm like
that didn't keep me full for
[Music]
long maybe it's better to H out make the
potato let's see how the pork chop
[Music]
does keep me full
still not very
fast
okay
um
um I have the iron right oh
okay I want to make a iron pickaxe
[Music]
no how do I get this
one oh I don't
[Music]
have I need to do the
quest where's the
[Music]
quest there's a quest for iron
oh in my
[Music]
book
what
B I'm going to get a strong strong
pickax this one is it this one
okay and then bring
[Music]
them to the blacksmith
maybe or the
friend okay yeah I got
money is that done
can I make it
now I
can ah but I have to pay money for
[Music]
it this is how every can't use that
yet
[Music]
okay go
it now get the diamond one
[Music]
huh did you want to get a strong weapon
I have a sword do you I do how I got
diamonds you
look I
too you can't give me a
one can you
I I can give you some
diamond
yeah maybe we can figure out how to make
a shield a shield and then I can go with
you and help you find some
diamonds how do we make a shield
[Music]
is Quest
wrestling don't pickaxe
[Music]
oh I got rid of my stone
pickaxe I
yeah I put it away shovel I put it away
oh I don't have a with
[Music]
shovel thought
I yeah okay
things I do does anyone want me to make
a shield I make a
sh how do I make a shield though I don't
know how to make a sh I don't see how to
sh
ba
oh
hello we have a hello fluffy it's good
to see you no longer a ghost pleasure to
see you I'm sorry I'm not I'm not in the
party can you just revived Miss Nissa
ravencraft how do we make a
shield a shield seems you may need some
iron and and some uh I will make one for
you guys it's no problem let me see if I
have any I have iron I have iron too you
have some iron yeah
my cat yeah welcome my cat Jonathan you
are quite the kind Knight Jonathan
Jonathan I felt up sad that you died
because you kissed me I will go get it I
will go get it I felt up sad that you
had died CU you kissed me
[Music]
I
reted and her I'm no longer
dead J go
[Music]
yes there Jonathan there you go I will
trade
you take this Shield yes thank you it is
no problem fluffy one oh than thank you
what about thank you for your kindness
no it is everything oh your inventory is
full you have too many I have yes I will
I will trade you of a shield okay thank
you yes yes for
you thank
you is there any way to make it extra
strong Shield this is the only Shield
okay I feel like I might break it I will
do my best as it's
APR there we go waiting our next
[Music]
actions it is looking for the
princess gathan we are in a party call
still the gard it's in my
book
oh you're right it is in my book
[Music]
this have you done one of the party Bo
no you want to do it together you you
want me to spend my money huh no I have
some money now I want to try it oh
okay let's go
[Music]
see Party Box oh I don't have space for
it to the
[Music]
berries okay I don't know if
I okay I bought
one okay you bought one yeah let's open
it together then okay okay three two one
oh I didn't open
oh three oh okay one you
going the same one middle middle
[Music]
middle can I choose from
here Construction suppli
[Music]
this is one
you I picked wrong I want this hot too
but I really like this to this looks
very Beau toit isn't this good I can
choose whatever I want
no oh I got the supply box should I can
I take them all oh no it it shows you
what what you
have so I got a construction box did
I did I
it
disappeared
[Music]
all I'm
confused I didn't get a h I like the
blue
too wait what is what
is what is IM green has achieved a new
Global high score of 100 mins
ey what does that
[Music]
mean I'll do my other one I'll buy
one three two one I nothing
[Music]
fun I don't know what this is
no that
[Music]
wasun I'm got lots of construction
supplies didn't get any no I'm going to
do one more
should
[Music]
IO why is pink dye and yellow Dy look so
different let is this
one I was
[Music]
close uh I don't know about that I just
use a lot of money and no did I not
receive it this
time I should put the
[Music]
okay more
stuff I the blue but SW I know
oh I need
diamonds I'm going to go get
them
okay let's use the warp ah wait wait
wait wait wa
[Music]
warp the co
okay Coast
Co the the the coast wait where is that
[Music]
okay
oh but I have I have something going to
make mining faster oh really
yeah a slime bread
oh I shouldn't have follow
[Music]
you yeah
find I need
[Music]
some what
I don't think this is a good
[Music]
area
there oh
[Music]
where let's go to the
coast okay W Crystal
[Music]
Coast over
here huh
[Music]
underwater
underwat but there's the cave
[Music]
was over here di the D entrance
yeah is over
here
no
here oh there's boats
here here here here yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I'm going down into the dungeon area I
don't
okay there's lots of stuff
here where are you I'm at the dungeon
entrance where was that again
how' you get there so fast H
[Music]
swim
huh is this what it
was oh it I get it I got
it BL
diamonds this
[Music]
one huh there you are
get
it
here yeah I got
one hey what are you
[Music]
doing are you allergic to diamond mining
is
Dusty there's a in the wall over here
here
[Music]
too there we
go oh my goodness too much
[Music]
dust blue
one is this
[Music]
do we need
that
want oh it made a good sound I don't
know why probably you up oh
maybe I was surprised
to I won up the diamond's good
[Music]
but yeah okay torch
diamond oh L's
here this is a good place for I'm going
to
[Music]
find pretty good
though back
[Music]
come on there we
go I need
room
oh
oh doesn't go into my
home where are you
[Music]
why
garbage I'll eat the pork
[Music]
chop one
how much Diamond do I
[Music]
need tool I don't have an axe though thr
this out
[Music]
this how do I get up
there yeah I'm living up
[Music]
how much do I
need wait how do I get hands and
[Music]
shoes
Diamond should I get lapis lauli
tool or maybe you can just bring it back
for me cuz I don't have enough space Oh
wait I do have space you still have a
backpack I have my backpack you have you
have a backpack my
backpack yeah up I
[Music]
don't so much of it even
more are you talking to
someone know sometimes you know I just
kind get a little bit of
[Music]
wait I don't have a
backpack where are you I'm in the same
spot I'll show you my
[Music]
back I'm going to get 64 of
them
standing look my backpack
oh I can't take it off my back like that
you don't have a backpack
[Music]
thing maybe we can make one together
what do I need for
it it wasn't that hard what did I need
for it I can't remember
anymore I'm almost done everything's
[Music]
easier okay
get a little bit more Diamond
here is there an area with a lot of
lauli what was that did you hear
that that was like
a this is the area that has the most off
right
here oh there's another
[Music]
right yeah oh I have
32 why get quite a bit of diamond I have
64 is that enough you have more than
enough okay so we I'll get a bit more
[Music]
lapis I should be good now I think so
no I don't have space for
it don't
[Music]
no can I make my slime yum no I
can't okay so we get going
done
okay let's use our all right
[Music]
to
the the best the castle best cast
yes do I need a
quest
Quest there's a bunch of
quest I guess I could do
[Music]
the diamonds looking for five diamonds
yeah
[Music]
okay is that it I'm want to go back I
didn't I
[Music]
except did take all of it from me what
are these other three
things have a
lot guess I should get this
done and then I could get
more I don't want to get rid of all my
[Music]
laes I use that
wear got to do more quests
[Music]
enchanted with
efficiency Ste I don't know how to do
that the enchanting tabl
[Music]
by I don't have a I guess I can make
a let's try it out
[Music]
right here right do you have five stain
hides with
[Music]
you where are you I'm
the I do this can we have
them we have
them am I supposed to do the best
[Music]
NOS why not this
one keep R
[Music]
first I not do it with this one
yet this
one the potato
[Music]
one second are we doing what were you
asking I want the the steam HIDs the
steam
okay that works what do you need Quest
what
quest he wants the stain Heights I
haven't done that before okay can I have
five
[Music]
have maybe I do that
there you
[Music]
are yeah thank
you I did I did gather them be back
stain H wait wait did you not give me St
St Heights I gave you stain
Heights it's probably in the box and you
didn't open it
[Music]
huh
you yeah I need to sell the
potato I can craft the backpack
now what you want me to yeah oh can I
have another five St
Heights
please I'm thinking
[Music]
oh why did I
need do we need a shovel for
[Music]
anything can I have five stain Heights
please I need a
backpack give you no no I
need they took them
[Music]
can I get more
money are you sure it's only
five no 100 is good want
buy
what is that you problem or me
[Music]
problem one second
what is again level requir My Level
drop okay okay was level what can I have
the stain hides now too stain hides
please
one I use l
is this what did he want
[Music]
level I'm
waiting I'm
[Music]
waiting one one one
you wanted the right
yeah can I have more money
please yeah
yeah I get a more it's okay for
now openev
I can
go I put these things in there why can't
I put wait can you not put the stormgate
key and stuff like that in the
bathpack maybe
[Music]
not
what
okay away good put these I
guess what else should I
[Music]
do I get more of that will it use it for
my backpack if it needs
[Music]
it no I just don't
know if I go and get some more the diam
Lev up
[Music]
fast no it
doesn't I need St
[Music]
bones wait do I not how St bones I do
have stained BS it's
just go go go what's going on
yeah
sword
sword maybe this is
a need to a backpack in my
hands that was
scary
here don't get stuck down that that's
probably a good
idea okay
[Music]
maybe n soup isn't good to carry around
huh
yeah I want to go test the SW I am going
I'm leaving the
[Music]
party
okay wait
laest I forgot
oops
[Music]
okay okay
and which one is the lapis only one
huh no I thought I did it no I did
[Music]
it
research I guess I should go get gold
then I do this
then go do that I'm just curious I
didn't mean to break anything I'll do
this
again I don't know
[Music]
I
and get this sinking I'm sinking I'm
sinking okay
[Music]
to level two
right it's this way
right all of
[Music]
these down this way
right under the
board okay
[Music]
yeah
okay I'm going to
fall
yes okay gold
now how much gold do I need wait do I
have space I have space
okay gold gold gold gold
[Music]
oh oh wait no that's not
cool can I ride a horse in
here
[Music]
gold
okay where is more gold oh there's lots
of r on the ceiling but I can't get
[Music]
there I can't wait
to I can't get
[Music]
there I just one I just want each time
hot is there an area with the gold
[Music]
oh here you know where there
gold I can't get to the ceiling
[Music]
though yeah
gold oh there's lots of diamond here too
[Music]
M it's just so dusty in here I can't
help
[Music]
it oh
wait wait
[Music]
wait okay
what oh I
got oh
where horse okay I need lottery tickets
yeah
wait
[Music]
what wait I'm here for lottery tickets
and nobody is here
[Music]
or it
online I'm here in person for lottery
ticket
[Music]
huh okay I need to call someone
okay I will give you four more tickets I
am here for tickets in person and you
are not
here one
second
one
two
three
four oh ring ring hello are you wanting
tickets for the lottery yes I am here
and you're not here I cany oh I'm at the
chicken game you see I'm on the road
chicken game on the road salesman it's
okay we can exchange it this way would
you like a lottery ticket it is
completely free and the first 20 people
to enter win you win 100 coins can I buy
20 tickets you cannot you can buy five
I'll buy five okie dokie I will be
sending them over to you now okay how
much are they they're free oh okay five
tickets free can I have other people's
free tickets you cannot
why because it is not
possible okay well five I'll take much
better than fart I bought so many
tickets but never got anything for free
H yeah I bet you didn't we are in
competition with bomart we hope to we
hope to um to to drive them out of the
neighborhood they have made this economy
not so great they don't allow me to buy
tickets anymore so they don't how
horrible Guild if you like a free that's
awful they should you you are a free
willed person you should be able to buy
as many as you please why they owe me
money unfortunately it's not my choice
that you only get five it's just the way
of physics way of physics how
aerodynamics work
can you send me a request for tickets or
do I have you no I sent you five in the
Discord that is your M okay thank
you okay you're welcome okay bye-bye
bye-bye I came here for
nothing
[Music]
okay to co
did I get enough stuff is 18
[Music]
enough
well might as well swim
again need more wait enough enough
okay let's go
[Music]
back okay
okay and then oh I need
coal I think I have it in my box
[Music]
no doesn't make you much faster huh
course just stop oh go was there always
that sign
there huh
the oh
okay I was
worried
cool I don't need
that noing sou can
[Music]
go okay
so it bring stain Heights maybe
not close the door oh no
there
okay need this the yeah that's why I
need the coal
right this way this way okay
here anyone
okay
[Music]
and are my
potato yeah
[Music]
I need F
right I need more
coal are you sure
[Music]
yeah wait I need the shovel why do I
want the shovel I don't need to
dig
okay oh wait yeah he wants me to get the
shovel
right
ouch does that make sense
[Music]
I
don't gold shovel in with efficiency
feet or
[Music]
higher stor the
library
okay oh no
my
gold
[Music]
yeah
shovel the pig is useless shovel got the
shovel and it was
with
again oh
three
three I'm not high enough level
efficiency three is this
[Music]
three how do I get three
two
[Music]
four okay okay
I'll go dig more
then I can level up fast by digging
right
digging en chanting a
sword
really yeah
[Music]
okay it's not it's not it's not the me
level
three wait can I enchant it multiple
[Music]
times my tree wait can I enchant my
shield you the my tree okay no
no just
[Music]
once wait wait wait I can do this
then efficient
too should I do
this huh just a
try no go fight
no
no why get the diamond
[Music]
one okay
do it with the diamond one
okay maybe we're almost ready to go back
efficiency
[Music]
too
okay
wait my levels just go
[Music]
down wait what is chicken r
SK now I have to go do more
stuff okay let's go back to the
[Music]
coost
okay where can I find the chicken
[Music]
stuff a it's really you
I'm stuck
okay at the
casino where's the
casino I haven't heard of the
casino
[Music]
no why did nobody tell me
this chicken
G oh
falling
[Music]
yig
okay oh if I go over here there's a
[Music]
lot W is will be now in 3 minutes that's
faster than fom
[Music]
Mar
wait I have to be
there my
[Music]
just go
here level up level up
[Music]
okay need to
dock
Castle okay I'll go back then
again I'm here oh hello hello here for
the
lottery thank
you of the co hello the lottery will be
announced in the next
minute I'm so
excited my number is
all
lottery love Lottery very nice oh wait I
saw a ghost I swear I just saw somebody
come by St a ghost a ghost oh you know
what it may have been may have been my
memories of what flew off the was
sounded like a little
confused is this all the pl so
excited
I'm oh the time is here but we are
missing some people it appears the of
the
deal where is Jonathan G jonath wait did
Jonathan G get one yes Jonathan G got
one perhaps we could call Jonathan of
the G with I should call Jonathan of the
G it wasn't important enough for them to
be here then huh no well you see even if
they are absent well actually never mind
I want you all to keep me company I'm
not going to tell you the truth
what the truth the truth being that you
really don't have to be here right now
get your prize money but but I just
wanted everybody together because I'm
lonely hello oh I am here for the
lottery oh exell too is everybody here
except the single person who refused to
ticket yeah a ticket a free
ticket ref a free ticket she was very
supicious what happened to her
sister sister sister wait a minute I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry I you two just
look very similar I got I I assumed I
shouldn't have assumed
they look very different they look
nothing alike yeah one is pink one is
blue they look so much they look as
alike as you look pregnant what
what what time are you in wait are you
are you perhaps not
pregnant that would assume male
pregnancy might even a oh I do apologize
I I to get pregnant I shouldn't
is your business partner you have to
stop stop insulting your
guest to pregnant backwards
backwards I'll oh maybe you are and I
and I am just revealing it to you I have
a hunch you have a hunch Jonathan
G am I I said
nothing am
I is anyone doctor do we have a doctor
Cecilia are you sure you're another
doctor too huh is there a doctor no but
I do I did take I did take a a first a
Course once oh you should I feel like
yeah we should be like a hospital here
the
[Music]
lottery good at all I guess but Lottery
let me me see is more important and if
you are in fact pregnant you would
really need the prize money wouldn't you
that given that your wife seems to be
out of the picture now yeah you would be
raising it alone the child huh I suppose
I would be what happed what happened to
her oh how sad oh she is not of this
world any longer what are you sure about
that yes she is no longer with us huh
she
died is no
longer with us but she's not dead is she
she dead the the version I knew is no
longer here with us what are you talking
about maybe she can come back still the
Pearl you believe so did she become a
ghost put all my eggs in one basket do
not give up
immediately I do not know you as
somebody who gives up so easily on their
love I see well don't give up you know
we got Nissa back from the anient mo of
the co
thank you difficulty I deserve to right
I think you deserve it too
honestly deserve a second
[Music]
chance money money money money alert
money alert money alert the's arrived
the M's arrived oopsie wait oh shoot
hold
on oh oh she snuck in wait let fine this
one you can hang out
paent because you're so patient all
righty all righty everybody I will now
be announcing the winners but please be
please have even more patience as I have
to go through en
count okie
dokie the first winner of the lottery
is you whose name I did not get H the
green you who is
Green Oh
Cecilia Oh cilia I you go by the green
one oh it is I go I can go by the green
one I like the green one but there's
another green one so it gets kind of
confusing well heard the other well just
whoever is present is the green one and
whoever is not present is the other
green one I win but yes you win I win
you you win 100 coin
congratulations congratulations on your
100 coin what is going why is
huzzah oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought it was trying to
make me call somebody I will the TR
request you get 100
coins huz winnings are to be had 100
points for you a lucky
winner the next
winner the next winner is the Lady of
the oranges yipp huzzah yipp huzzah you
win 100 coins what a
surprise I had a
feeling for you I think today we are all
winners next the next winner is not this
N1 March next winner is
[Music]
Mario
yeah it's Mario congratulations so many
you get 100 coins thank not sure why you
need it since you were the queen but I'm
just happy you Andy at all uh sometimes
you must donate to the Royal team extra
all the time sometimes it is required
that you donate a portion of your ear
they need it the most they powerful they
need all the money more than we we
starving people
[Music]
huzzah is Jonathan G thank
goodness crazy oh great
day just got to keep your chin up
Jonathan yes I will keep yourin me A New
Perspective
n you're welcome glorious
[Music]
huz the next
winner is or I believe would have been
Lissa the ravening
C already departed for today she is not
here right now we did confirm that she
can pick up her earnings tomorrow which
she will
do on the mar she may be sleeping on the
mar the ghost one on the mar but that's
okay we have now the final winner of
today moo of the
co and CU you bought five tickets you
get there was the option to do
that I did not know of this you can
could I have bought 20 tickets and get
everything no you could not have five
was the
maximum how wonderful you have
congratulations everybody you have all
won the
lottery it's okay she's addicted as long
as this is the only Lottery she's going
to because then she will not lose any
money here I am baned from today
we point by the way
[Music]
everyone everybody has won it was not a
scam everybody won this is
true family run by a family of one that
is we should destroy
[Music]
destroy F
destroy wait no no please destroy not
destroy the win BR me more perhaps M
would like to share I have been
sharing for you thank my
Wis destyy
I think you should destroy the market uh
I don't think that's a 2,900 coins for
jackpot is not very much of a
jackpot I feel like you have very high
standards for jackpot a lottery is a
lottery down with f
Mar do not do not down with funa Mark we
need f mark for healthy competition on
the market I don't know
I need my money from fart first before
it goes
down haven't you already gotten a lot of
money from
fart
no down
with after I get my money
yeah getting quite suspicious yes since
we also support the same
Queen I yes of course I need to help you
when you need me of child if I am
I
will but keep your chin up because I
have a good feeling about your wife the
feeling good luck with your pregnancy
byebye they're going to need money
huh
swim I'm not very fast now h
oh I'm very
hungry I guess waiting for all the food
the the my wedings took a lot out of me
H eat the baked
[Music]
potato oh it heals a lot oh that's good
ah much faster
now all the excitement yeah
[Music]
see always ask questions it never hurts
to ask questions cuz then you can buy
five lottery tickets for free instead of
just
[Music]
one you
know maybe I should get more
potatoes okay
[Music]
learn how to
enchant should I get to level 35 or
something if it's going to take my
levels away from
[Music]
me
my over here
[Music]
is okay oh
40 get the
[Music]
okay my gold doesn't really do much why
diamonds and Lapis
zo should I pick up coal I need coal too
huh do they have coal down
[Music]
here don't want my
what are
hiding I don't see any coal
though 28
I just like
[Music]
to it CLS up a lot
huh does it go does it go for diamonds
or
[Music]
la oh my kindness okay cool by the
entrance of the town I'm just okay I'm
making
a maybe over here better
[Music]
done some's
destroy princess
[Music]
okay yeah
level not the gold I'll get the
gold just in
[Music]
case level 40 right that's pretty far
are you sure level 40 is good I don't
want to
[Music]
be
to is there a better way to level up
like attacking the stains
[Music]
fighting STS is good now I have a good
sword right so it should be fast
[Music]
I'm too far
away stand to good then I can make stuff
with their their body parts we go
[Music]
maybe it's a lot of Hing h
I can fight okay I am
strong now we just need of
eggs too far away
[Music]
yeah wait till
3 3 three is good okay
huh come on come
[Music]
on I go over
here you hear that
[Music]
huh oh I
couldn't I feel like something's going
to come up behind
[Music]
me yeah okay
PL ruins I don't know where that
[Music]
is
oh I'm lost
again there's not really any stings
H where does this
go oh the ghost oops I'm oh wait where
did I
[Music]
go
okay ah there's a lot of monsters out
here no
[Music]
I feel like there was
no they
disappear where are the
[Music]
things
huh
where there
one they still not that strong down a
cow
[Music]
Pig are strong H
there am I getting stronger very fast I
don't think so
[Music]
the I don't think I'm getting that much
faster
ouch
no oh
[Music]
done and then all this stuff came on to
my magical
to me
eggs oh there's lots of
[Music]
them oh there's lots of
them
[Music]
ouch I use the shield
oh yes how do I use the shield
like that did I use it right what else
should I
put like
[Music]
that not like that
back go back
to
food oh no not
here no not
[Music]
there huh
yeah
and cool
[Music]
here I don't think I need that muche do
I I can the magic too
[Music]
okay I leveled up
right is said that she wanted the the
hide so then it should be valuable
right
ouch
hey is it taking damage The Shield is it
going to
break
hey
[Music]
the eventually
know I don't know how to build it
though should I bring a new one with
[Music]
me
ouch maybe I have
[Music]
enough I'm a bit happy h
okay I'll
eat what should I eat
[Music]
though
potato
yeah okay and
[Music]
I can do that now
right Wanted the old
shovel um this this one right huh
right
okay I talk to you magic feather
huh yeah what's the magic
feather
whyly
oh I see I don't need that
probably I don't know how use that I
can't move it out of
here I don't want that
[Music]
oh
okay that worth
it
okay did I do everything
[Music]
iron axe gold
sword I guess I could do a gold sword
[Music]
no gold
sword how do I get this though
oh it takes a
[Music]
lot so you can like
okay where's
[Music]
the oh
oh where is
time
[Music]
to wait what am I doing am I throwing
these
out
huh
what am I throwing these
out I
[Music]
guys I like this
H okay I'm making
[Music]
space it
oh
man
yeah this is better but I don't have any
coal in here I don't have any coal in
[Music]
here what is this
beef I want it cool I was getting cool
[Music]
CH how can I cook it
then wait I
didn't I don't know how to make that
okay let's put that there
thank
[Music]
you Store stuff at the base I don't need
another backpack I can't access it right
away I don't need the
I don't
know I oh I guess I can just go like
this there huh
H I can probably make more stuff
right do I need more
food do I need more food
[Music]
never I need storage
space I'm going to get cool then I can
cook
stuff
okay this time for sure
cool
okay LU on your
[Music]
stay away stay
away am I doing well
[Music]
ouch oh he flew
away okay okay I'm
[Music]
going
there I have coal right yes I have coal
[Music]
okay and over
here over
[Music]
here okay and then after this I will
cook H the meat the meat yeah
[Music]
okay but I don't want the meat to take
up
[Music]
space I guess raw beef is pretty
good cook it next to the furnace
[Music]
I still
have oh no stop it
okay
[Music]
and like
this does it make it into the
cook steak okay steak steak is good cuz
I had I had steak
[Music]
s i
wonder the oh the
staming does that
help
[Music]
the
okay
[Music]
gra what else do I have in here
not
much
oh I have an
[Music]
idea
whoops whoops
okay I'm going to use all the it turns
into steak regular
[Music]
steak there so many of them now
I just want to make sure that I'm
[Music]
ready last
one I I made
[Music]
it there oh I guess I'll take my co back
is feet
okay and put that
there not there this
here should I bring some more potatoes
or maybe I'm good on
[Music]
potatoes did I need wait I needed St
meat for something
[Music]
I need to stay wait for
something what was the
recipe
[Music]
oops ah this the Bor in fried Stein ah
and the bores do I have that many bores
black pack
uh let's go try to make it for
[Music]
now wrong book this
book it was
uh egg bread meat and Bone
okay I need both egg and bread what was
I doing
okay let's try
[Music]
that
red meat oh I don't have
[Music]
it I don't have enough bread right
okay egg bread me and
Bone ah strength goes up
[Music]
too okay I'll buy some more bread and
eggs
[Music]
okay good this is good
okay then I can cook the
other okay other
[Music]
meat okay yeah this is
good I'll put the other stuff
[Music]
away I'm not wet
okay put in
[Music]
here I don't need the
bread don't need that I don't need a
diamond
[Music]
maybe and
then there I should be ready right
yeah and then I need to go and enchant
stuff
right
[Music]
Le
int a
sword yeah wait is
that is this good or
not I'm breaking fre
[Music]
I'm
in
[Music]
no uh I can give you some raw meat if
you want it if I can have
steak I have much I I have a lot of
steak I could give you some but I don't
want your small little what
[Music]
don't take my
steak the steak for everybody wait
[Music]
what you make a
mistake oh I have extra steak
[Music]
almost
done m
[Music]
m okay
cool
[Music]
okay did I leave my
wait why can't I
move
okay I'm breaking three then
is it
good no no
no no what should I do
then
huh no if you go you can buy them you
there no I don't have eggs I
thought in chance something else
do I have something else what should I
do we
pickax like
this
[Music]
yeah it's purplish
now and then
not back
too is that
good
yeah no I thought I had a
torch
[Music]
no should I try
again sharpness
H maybe I should buy this okay one
second an
[Music]
aive sweeping Edge is that good is that
good yes I need to level up again
okay one
second can I level up getting
[Music]
potatoes can I do that
pot
[Music]
huh where are the
potatoes why is it empty
oh I
[Music]
should why is it
empty why is it
empty where are the potatoes
make a lot of the potato sa
potatoes beets potatoes carrots a
potatoes
[Music]
okay not be
potatoes
okay oh my gosh why am I stuck
[Music]
there okay oh I got a poisonous
one I'll plant that I
guess
okay oh I can't find okay
oh I
[Music]
missed there we
go okay I'll play on 12 of
them where did I take them
from what oh I'm
drowning here
what four
more here we
go there we go oh I have lots of
potatoes there's more potatoes than I
[Music]
expected maybe I'll go over here then
maybe
[Music]
I don't know why it's
empty why can't I
move what happened
here this is garbage let's try this I'm
not cooking po no I'm not cooking a
poisonous potato
[Music]
carpet
garbage and
the carrot
garbage okay wait I'm still not leveled
up
[Music]
yet it didn't give any
exp
ow I
see okay I'll make
the why can't I move
I'll make these
[Music]
here I like let's go back then to the
just thinking about why makes
mey
[Music]
H
okay
get
byebye okay and again
should I get just more of the
[Music]
diamond down down
down
[Music]
yeah I do miss my torch though
huh it's so dark
I like the
light
[Music]
okay oh
h no this is my
spot look at your arm
this is mine did
you hello sorry I was muted this is
mine hello are you
mining this is my
m is it yours I need to level
up yeah good luck I can give you this
stuff if you
want no you don't want it's fine why is
the queen why is the queen in the
mines because it needs to become
stronger
a is this your queen training then
yeah
wor I I'll let you be then I'll go over
there I guess no
worries I can I can take this
Square H there should be stuff over
there too
[Music]
byebye overl it's too dark
though what's this stuff over here yeah
yeah
yeah okay bye-bye a do I need more
levels
[Music]
still do
I just in case
maybe Army
right two
[Music]
more please
33 is
[Music]
good red
stone oh I made it brighter for a moment
I like
[Music]
that Redstone Dust what does that do
though
[Music]
what yeah
why am I
stuck see I'm stuck it won't let me
run h
[Music]
I don't need the diamonds why can't I
move drops are
good
how
byebye
how maybe this is how I can make
yeah
okay I'll bit more
about okay let's go back
[Music]
then
okay okay
[Music]
and it's time for sure I don't grab m
ah I always end up drowning there it's
still not done SL
H more
[Music]
potatoes if I take out the
oh oh I'm going to need all that Co
heart
[Music]
okay this time for sure
right oh wrong
thing okay sleeping Edge
three
yeah
[Music]
okay
okay now ah it's shiny now
[Music]
huh is it any better I go test it I'll
get some more cool then
[Music]
too
what
[Music]
huh I don't want those is there a cow
cow
[Music]
cow I don't know if it's any
better ouch
[Music]
okay I'm not going to cry is no
better I was excited but
now
disappointed
[Music]
huh thank you for
helping cow oh I killed a
cow he was stubborn a cow why do you
want a
cow why can't I hit you
[Music]
huh oh I can get the little one's
fast just
smash
[Music]
smash that's a
cool
yeah okay okay okay okay
[Music]
do I have enough coal
yet oh I leveled up
[Music]
yeah I got coal I got coal
okay there we
go
and I have my
potatoes there we go and I can put
more just up it up just up it just up it
there I want this here
oh doesn't do
[Music]
anything what do I do with this
one Redstone you can use as is
[Music]
wait how do I use
them put
[Music]
this I wanted to do this there we go
oh
[Music]
no no it's in here it's confusing cuz my
to is like a
[Music]
backpack
oh one second one
second okay here usess
I have too many diamonds I don't know I
don't know
that's
garbage
[Music]
okay and I don't need
that
okay I don't want to make the I saive
item okay now I
[Music]
want
yeah oh wa oh wait oh wait wait I have
[Music]
the it's in here
yeah I use this and I use this
is this only
one
FEA I can I can fly how do I
fly I don't need jump ah okay
byby I'm flying where did the chicken go
oh what happened the chicken chick where
they chickens in herei
[Music]
huh did you have a lot of
chickens it overflowed
[Music]
H maybe should put a missing sign
up I didn't know there was chickens in
here
is it a missing a missing sign
up I'm going to make it
[Music]
pretty I need this this I
need
[Music]
one ouch wait wait wait wait wait
oh oh
[Music]
oh I can't fly
here
[Music]
okay oh no
what yeah
[Music]
is it just me or is it sort of
dizzy strange
[Music]
h
no can I get them
back
[Music]
no oh ouch
oh were you raising my
chickens now they're gone put out a
missing sign for them then
[Music]
H you can
call
huh
[Music]
ticke I
tickets another
one tell the
night Jonathan huh
I know they they
are I know where they are you know where
they are
[Music]
where definitely took your
chickens yeah
I'm here where are
you oh
[Music]
there I think one I took
them they have a big chest here it looks
like you can hold
chickens you don't know how to make the
tickets
[Music]
but I will look the for Mar they have to
make the tickets out of
something how do you turn tickets into
the watering
tickets
feathers I have one feather
you need chickens to make feathers and
Feathers to
make slander
tickets this isn't slander I'm just
saying that maybe I got find
okay good luck with your
[Music]
chickens why can't I run
I think it could be you
me what
else I was going to make the no I didn't
make the I made the chck disappear bone
and fried
stain and I have steak
[Music]
oh do you hear me I don't hear
you my stuff
here my stuff
here okay my
[Music]
stuff Jonathan
Jonathan can you hear
Jonathan that's so
[Music]
strange I heathan
now still I hear
[Music]
Jonathan dad
Jonathan my chickens come here come here
come here no
[Music]
no
here put here for
[Music]
ticket I love them there so of
them potato forck every
last of course I have a lot of baked
potatoes
what I
don't no they were very happy they were
so they loved me what all right the
Redstone Dust I should see what I can do
with the Redstone Dust wait wait wait
wait wait I don't think they said there
is a casino I love this and
chickens I don't think chickens can
fly H coin did you say you didn't eat
them did you that
can't you just eat wait
what are you mared me I love them how
could you do
[Music]
that Amber
Queen where is the Amber
Queen C you know the Amber quein
okay here here here here
across the
bridge is it in
[Music]
here color
Canon color Cannon color
Cannon color
Cannon color Canon all your eggs you
sure color
Cannon color
Cannon how I would like to play color
Cannon yes yes
[Music]
yes I need to bet
first
Canon color Cannon yes color Cannon
maybe
in huh I don't think they fall away
huh oh this this up here I can't jump
[Music]
over some fire
H I thought I was doing something
wrong the color you want to bet on
decide how many coins to
bet can I will start firing four colored
squares with each shot after six shots
only one square will remain players who
bet on that color
win winning players will receive a
payout based on their multiplayer for
the color they bet one
oh well I don't know how to play yet
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait how do I make a bed Okay girl okay
I'm going to do
yellow yellow let's see I don't think
they're 31
I
red 100 I TR you why not I don't little
away though 50 really
really and 50 I don't think so why not
let's see I don't know how to play this
yet oh do I go upstairs
[Music]
now maybe this fence is kind of small
go
[Music]
here oh I can stay downstairs
oh I'm here now okay two one starting
fireing red red red ohed is wait is that
good for a long thank you for the eggs
[Music]
okay oh green and
blue green and blue
[Music]
green 150 coins I
won okay go
[Music]
down let's play
again
okay
um oh it was blue last time
right okay 150
[Music]
50 yeah
okay okay stop can't end
[Music]
soon only bet on one color why bet only
one kind color when I can do all of
them you lose money know I'll win huh
I'll
win okay 10
seconds 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2
one here we
[Music]
go red is gone that was quick
guess oh red is
Big that's right I wanted to make this
this
[Music]
blue a princess
be uhoh yellow is right here
H
[Music]
easy blue
blue is the worst one but I bet on
it yellow I still W
yeah
okay okay it's
fine red oh I would like to
play
okay
um I'm going to go 300 on red then
[Music]
and uh
200 let's go with that
[Music]
then green blue and green are the best
ones
oh
100 and
100 I thought red was the best no
[Music]
why can't I get up
there
okay eight seven six 5 4 3 2
1 water I don't know how to make the red
is still
[Music]
there red is still
there
[Music]
Red Run
oh close
[Music]
one green on 300
coins okay let's try
[Music]
again
what that ah I see
okay 300 on red I have a
feeling
100 50
50 and
[Music]
50 TR this is a
one okay
[Music]
this is
good what I did that before I'm waiting
okay why I could go faster would I wait
more if everyone joined
in
[Music]
huh okay three two
one okay
let's hope for
red okay
red
uhoh okay Red Red
[Music]
Run
uhoh
uhoh red red red
red
[Music]
uhoh yeah run okay we can do it we can
do it do it
uh I
just yeah red
[Music]
red red survive red survive
red it's
green
close
[Music]
CL okay last time
red I can't move
okay
oh 500 if I win I get 5,000
right
and
[Music]
100 and
50 okay
[Music]
yeah okay this time for
sure it's so close for
red
[Music]
yeah what the is getting lots of
stuff okay 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2
one okay
[Music]
red this good this is good this is good
this good okay ready save
yeah okay oh red R red r r r red
red
R yellow
yellow okay red red red let's hope for
red red is still safe yes yes yes yes
okay
red uh-oh uh-oh oh
no red red okay this could be it red R
safe close though it's close
though okay one last
time
on
red I think this is it I think this is
it
and
100 maybe 200 cuz I feel like blue has
been
winning okay
let
[Music]
see
okay yeah it will be good it will be
good okay 10
seconds 9 8 7 6
5 4 3 2 1 okay red for sure this
time sa save sa sa
[Music]
sa red and yellow red
red red red still safe still safe
yeah take out the blue take oh
[Music]
no red yeah okay
okay not the red not the red yes yes yes
yes
yes run no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
yeah
run yeah
a okay we're
good yeah we're good see see it's
good see it was the last
time see I told you the casino is good
byebye yeah see it was the last time and
it was perfect
yeah there no problems
yeah princess be
you hello
oh
H where did she
[Music]
go
what princess princess
disappeared what did I do to her I do do
anything I don't
[Music]
know chicken back
oh what is this L
see excellent eats a
we visit the queen think that
you
[Music]
ouch I'm going to die I'm going to die
what the heck what the heck you're going
to make me mad huh what the
[Music]
heck I have the steak I can eat the
steak
[Music]
ouch ouch ouch ouch
ouch OU ouch ouch
ouch
eat what are you doing in the corrupted
land it's said to go in no do not you'll
be
corrupted what you'll be corrupted if
you stand in here for too long I thought
I thought it was yours no it is not my
sign it seems that they have corrupted
my sign
too oh goodness oh terrifying here come
take a bath in the Queen's Fountain and
it doesn't have to do with the
queen what no it has nothing to do with
the queen here take a dip it will
cleanse you cleanse yourself with the
water the holy water I
drowning no you're not drowning we just
taking a little dip I'm stuck do you
feel
better it's supp Poise I I sort of
drawing and stuck but now I'm okay yes
you're okay because the queen is here to
protect us feet water no it is her holy
water it is holy water not foot water
the holy water yes it is her holy water
yes I'm princess
[Music]
beel just be here I have oh
careful princess be
careful very careful oh narissa
ravencraft what are you doing
[Music]
here oh that was frightening a tra
Quest she's
[Music]
not
oh
Fashion
St no no back back off I
wantable no no fuzzy one no fuzzy one
fuzzy one no fuzzy one back I never play
taken in
[Music]
fashion oh
Fashion I can't you
[Music]
might I
feel of
funny I can't see
[Music]
though I can't see
the I thought if I looked up I could see
my hat
butan I can't I can't speak to you
[Music]
not even a
goodbye
no I can't see the top of my
head are you dancing I guess I need to
find H I have I'm G that's probably
enough a Traer
[Music]
Quest oh Construction Supplies
why does this
huh
why what's going onu
[Music]
supplies she's saying to make it more
beautiful
[Music]
again oh
what I'm so high
up
oh no
[Music]
what I should take it
off take it off I feel a bit funny
[Music]
but hi can't they throw it
off Throw It To The
[Music]
Ground take it off before it's too late
huh how do I take it off how do I take
it
off
hi
hi hi
[Music]
be the chickens are tasty
okay chicken
chicken the chicken the
chicken the
chicken
chicken chicken chickeni
[Music]
chick
chicken
chicken chicken's
[Music]
the
chickens
[Music]
yesi okay
huh why am I swimming here is there
always a plan
[Music]
here what's up
here oh
oh
H
we I thought it had something on my
head but I guess
[Music]
not I thought I was trying to plant
flowers I don't know what
happened that was weird wait I want
flowers
flowers more
what what
Jan I don't know I just want to plant
flowers okay
fly fly uhuh oh I use it
fly yeah
flowers what
flowers flowers
[Music]
yeah this is the flower
house
OU I'm going to die like this planting
flowers egg wasn't more
[Music]
eggs okay that there I'll eat the
what wait why can't I
run
[Music]
what I'm making
flowers my chick did you see far away I
never saw your chickens it's always been
empty
it's been
empty I don't know why you keep on
saying that you have tickets cuz I've
never seen tickets are you sure you're
actually growing ticket
here why are you giving me of
those
what I don't want
that I'll make
[Music]
flowers flowers
flow good luck with your
[Music]
chickens I have two
extra I want to go down though how do I
go
down how do I go down how do I go down
how do I go down how do I go
down oh sneak thank
you should I build it so there's a
[Music]
roof make a flower
roof oops
[Music]
okay is this the same height
no Jonathan can you hear
me youan flowers
youing oh no not that not that
[Music]
are I can't hear
you oh
not this is
[Music]
good h
I don't
hear hear Jonathan near
[Music]
me it'll be a pretty Place
huh please
help oh no oops
this is how you make it
right g spot I just thought it'd be
pretty wait what if the queen gets made
here huh that would be
[Music]
nice
yeah okay I'll build it up more
[Music]
wait wait I can hear you I can't I
can't why did it get wobbly
huh is it
[Music]
smoking I don't
think they all good they always so
happy they have many eggs in front of
them build up the tree I was only given
a half but you very
far my big tree
[Music]
maybe I'll make this a tree
wall there's nothing here I
I This I Swear H I'll get my hats on my
[Music]
own
this oh oops no
how it's supposed to look like they're
swinging in the wind it makes me feel
sick oh I'm not flying
anymore I'm not the kind of person I
don't know how to make
TR there we
go
yeah
FL oh is a fly again
can't I
can't
there ouch I don't want to
[Music]
fly
there now it should be nice ah it looks
shiny
[Music]
oh where's the entrance though where's
the entrance I
believe where's the
entrance oh is this the
entrance well is
now it's the entrance
[Music]
now what
I will ask oh there's stuff in here
pumpkin okay I
[Music]
I breakfast
toast my breakfast
toast H is there anything I can leave in
here
potato only potato take I take
steak I
take okay what's this one
[Music]
them I want to make
trees I want to make
trees wait I can't get out of here
[Music]
I can fly right I can
fly
there I can fly
[Music]
okay that a close
oneou ouch ouch ouou
I almost died I'll use
[Music]
this I want to build
more okay
here build up a
[Music]
tree
there down a
bit put it in the oh I don't have
anymore oh but I have lots of
them
[Music]
yeah I don't need the shov oh I get the
stuff I want terer look then I can make
[Music]
trees okay
and this is
good oh oops okay well that works
[Music]
I want more out
here this a
[Music]
huh oh I want
here oh no no not
[Music]
that like this
oh
[Music]
no I want trees
though I never made a tree oh I don't
think that's a
tree oh I guess that's are you sure oh I
guess I should fly huh
[Music]
ouch fell
away should I make it taller maybe
taller
oops
[Music]
no
oops oh activate yeah
I'm
okay this is how you make a tree
[Music]
right make it
if I
pr it's really
complicated tree
[Music]
tree be down
not
[Music]
theree P not your
tree I don't know
[Music]
yeah oh I need
more
up don't
[Music]
a lot of raw chicken I don't think I
have much raw chicken
no no I don't have
any
what
[Music]
no I don't know what you're talking
about
[Music]
tree
tree I like the fire inside there wait
wait how do I make
torches how do I make
[Music]
torches Co and sticks I can't
move I have
sticks and I have
coal
[Music]
this where did the sticks oh there they
are and
cool okay and stick and
Co
[Music]
no like
this oh I made 50 of them okay
I'll be right back
okay I should be able to make them in
[Music]
here okay
and what it'll be nice like this can't
put them on there though
right yeah yeah
oh maybe they shouldn't be there maybe
[Music]
here uh I guess I can't put them there
but I want them here
[Music]
though yeah yeah put put them on the
ceiling no
[Music]
okay I don't like that I have to fly in
and out
but deactivated okay
in I would like to put them on the top
cuz I think that'll look
[Music]
nice oh I can
why wait if I
put put this
here yeah yeah then I
can oh gosh I don't want to
fall
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah is it
normal wait I want it to be like
a wait does it have a three of the
top okay well I'll like this
[Music]
then yeah
it look like
only I want this
one I
[Music]
think
oh
[Music]
oh it keep
Flo that looks
menacing
huh potato
[Music]
it looks beautiful at night
no is
[Music]
there I
want yeah no one here
[Music]
maybe I don't like this one at the front
though uh I'll get rid of
[Music]
it
wild
huh why does it take so
long it's a cute birthday cake
[Music]
a oh
gosh okay I
want cover that up
[Music]
there oh can I not put it there is that
in the
[Music]
way ah I know what I'll do one
second I want it to be shiny
[Music]
let me up let me
up destroy that one and then I'll
[Music]
put that there and then this here oh
wait no I don't want
that
um um oh well I guess that work this
is
huh yeah not there not
there and then is it shiny
huh
yeah oh
no I dig into
it and I can put this here
not
there not there not
[Music]
there
oh not there and see then it looks nice
oh I'll
[Music]
fly yeah like that I'll hide it a bit
more see
[Music]
then you don't see it as
much thought
[Music]
is she look cool at night yeah right but
I I
just put that there I can't really hide
it like that okay
[Music]
one okay destroy
it oh
no no
[Music]
not
there
[Music]
here like that let the P yeah like
that where are
you
oh your
spot h no no no no no there's an
entrance on the other side I don't know
I didn't build the
walls oh oops no no no no you don't need
to break it over this way this way oh
this
way one it again one it again we have to
go
around no don't break it there's already
a broken
part see over this way here no what are
you doing
[Music]
he
here
am here that's can't do this fly
out do that
that's
[Music]
see
no can we build a
door I don't know why we don't have a
door here
Please block
this a of
[Music]
these there you go there's a staircase
oh
be princess
[Music]
be I don't have a horse in our
house
huh huh
[Music]
why are you hitting
her what why is there black stuff
falling off of
you huh
[Music]
no wait
wait fla come back fla come back come
back come back it'll be safe under the
flowers somehow
[Music]
maybe I'll be
safe I'll make it
[Music]
sa okay
come back it's see it's even in the
flowers is it yeah it's
[Music]
te come back to the
flowers come back to the
flow save here
come back to the
flowers come
back come back come back come back here
here here here come back in here in here
quickly
[Music]
quickly okay okay going to the
flowers here here here here here
where
[Music]
here
there it's small but it's
see Smalls
good
yeah
and I can do
the no it's
nice it's bright
don't trusted
[Music]
you Jade SW see J your heart doesn't
really fit but it's blue so it's okay no
it your neck looks like it
hurts oh now it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
better just fig I almost have my soup
all done here soup I'm making a great
soup what
soup special soup greatest soup greatest
soup a little never believe someone
wearing a
hat the things in here can go here and I
haven't needed any of this
we should be safe
now I don't need okay move out of the
way I'll put my lights
down out of the
way no I'm just putting out more lights
[Music]
okay this goes away that goes away this
goes
away what else what else this goes away
okay I'm going to open an entrance and
exit no I'm opening an entrance and
exit there you go I'm putting everything
away properly right no problem it looks
[Music]
nice what
else that's everything I need right
[Music]
have I just need
bones
[Music]
for maybe
go away I don't have to carry that with
my
[Music]
eye lots of
petals it's safe here
[Music]
why do I have this in
my I'm going to open an
exit really I'm not ready to go yet okay
then you get ready here yeah cuz I need
to
leave here
[Music]
here her hat is in the magical
Tob try to get really nice
keep on telling me
[Music]
organiz
build it
was okay I still have it on this is all
the
stuff
better bit more bright
yeah oh I don't need this anymore
[Music]
I I have a lot of
buckets this should be good oh maybe I
don't need
[Music]
this I'll make one one
second actually maybe I can just make my
special
[Music]
here one last time I need do you
have I might
[Music]
one I have one I more than I let me let
me okay
[Music]
I
okay is that
it take the
right
okay here I go oh I need to open the
tree oh I don't have
anymore I like to put that back in there
[Music]
okay we
have we haveen
[Music]
carrot I
forgot oh I have steam meat I think I
think I have too just
one let's
[Music]
oh I
should what you can make the ultimate
soup is this huh butter butter do you
have butter it
huh
okay H okay
you now I'm missing the
B what else am I missing I like to make
at least three more it is soup good I
don't know it seems pretty powerful it
has AB 2 minutes and strength 2
minutes can you can you make one for me
maybe
I need to get back down oh here it
is what do you
need I'm going to
[Music]
put
cook all special
[Music]
oh okay I'll I'll leave
this I'll put it in there a
bit all the special
[Music]
okay it'll smell good in here
H it's me
[Music]
I don't
have
yeah I'm cooking stuff I wanted to cook
one
thing can I cook one thing you can after
this this box
here more
Ste is this from
that no I don't know
[Music]
then H it's okay I'm just cooking them
for the sake of cing them okay you can
that
[Music]
then I'll put in here that I don't
need I think I took your chicken that's
okay you can keep the chicken oh okay
I'll eat
[Music]
it why do you have cooked chicken but no
chickens
you sure about that very
sure okay let's go let's go I'm just
confused
there there I'm going
out okay
[Music]
oh there's still no chickens are you
sure that you're supposed to have
chickens
I am well there's a reason for now
[Music]
huh what oh okay
you I felt like I have one thing I
wanted to
do
I Princess P are you feeling better
no yeah yes no sort of maybe
huh the saf
[Music]
place did you want
meat I have extra
meat ah she has lots of potato
salad I don't know how to get
it oh potato salad
[Music]
potato
salad
oh I am
forgetting
H potato salad oh too many potato
salads
okay did you want a potato salad
[Music]
where are
you oh
okay can I should I potato salad for the
the
soup no potato salad
easy looking a recipe
Pok you can cook for yourself too potato
salad the first
[Music]
and then there's the special things
to that's what I special stained SE wait
I don't see
it that's because it's really how do you
get
[Music]
in I to try
make I made that oh you made that I want
to make more of that
H you have to do arm wrestling I did the
arm
wrest you need milk for that you have a
bucket no you have the iron yes I can
make the bucket done ah okay where go
was the crafting
table and then make a bucket shap with
the iron
[Music]
look together you
want make a bucket
[Music]
sheap how do I get just
one one one one one one is that a
bucket I don't know I don't
[Music]
know bucket mine cart
want to make the noodles fish and chips
made
ym bucket I got the
bucket got it so we go and cows oh okay
wild
cows do you want a potato salad I don't
need one I don't need this one though
okay well sounds like nobody take it
take
it I have too much potato salad I don't
want it you can go sell it
H I'm going to go to the the
planes
[Music]
okay oh what am
I do I just click on the cow with the
bucket how how much how much milk can I
get at one
go go go Stu just beware oh then I only
have one milk you only have one
milk
[Music]
ohk
okay give me milk no no no milk milk not
not damage milk milk milk milk milk milk
milk not milk
milk ouch
milk
up I want the
milk I don't want them I don't want the
water
anymore milk
ouch milk you
[Music]
wait
no get here
fight where's a
cow maybe that's
[Music]
okay okay
wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait what's happening going where's the
cow can't
move I stole milk here I go I need to
empty my bucket on my oh no oh no I
can't move ouch
[Music]
I have
sugar is the arm
wrestling The Tavern okay
[Music]
good goodby
huh I am looking for who
bartender no who am I looking for Marcus
[Music]
Brutus oh
secret ah okay okay okay while holding a
bucket of milk oh that's good I'm here
with
milk now
what huh
[Music]
no I did that do I talk to the quest
Master now
[Music]
okay now what can I make the recipe
now do I have to talk to the quest
[Music]
Master
way I can make
it there's too many
[Music]
Works special St Ste okay golden
carrot
huh where do I get a golden carrot
[Music]
craft it a carrot plus gold ah okay
that's easy
enough have what
[Music]
a okay off off
course no carrot here carrot
there go
[Music]
be do I have
space okay she'll be
good eight gold nuggets plus carrot
[Music]
it it's
me huh so
scary okay where am I am I
lost
okay and then here I can make
[Music]
the can make it I have a gold
gold uh instead of butter
I don't eat
[Music]
potatoes I don't know what this is but
I'll put that in my
backpack uh potato salad for
now oh
nugget how do I get gold
nuggets like that
like
that and then with the
carrot
uh okay that should be good
enough
car i s on the carrot with the Nugget
[Music]
really
Evol come on come
on
[Music]
there
okay this is
tricky car
H how do I make it
[Music]
go like that like that no yeah
D
okay is this
[Music]
waking I don't have enough
no take the carrots
away
oh oops
well
[Music]
okay
okay this is so
[Music]
tricky okay okay right here carrot
carrot
carrot oh oh
okay there carrot carrot carrot carrot
[Music]
okay I don't know how much of everything
else I can make so I feel like 20 is
enough
[Music]
maybe okay
how many of these is
I I don't want to have too many
[Music]
left
may I don't need so many but
happened now I have
what that's okay okay that's good
enough and what else do I need for the
[Music]
recipe uh I need
beetroots how do I make that
[Music]
e
so how do I make
that ohz I'm not H you three beat in a
bow do I have any bowls how do I make a
bowl can I buy a
[Music]
bowl I got an
why can't I
move oh I can M go
[Music]
too
oh can I sell stuff
no should I go get wood done
[Music]
okay it's really slow
huh how much wood do I need
[Music]
wait am I okay I am picking it up okay
good good
[Music]
good
a
sweet oh wait I can just use it to the
crafting supplies
crafting
supplies yeah
[Music]
okay okay then I'll just buy that
then oh
I don't have
[Music]
enough
okay change of
plans they're in here
[Music]
right
no where did they
[Music]
go where they go
I had all the building stuff the
building
[Music]
stuff now I only have
one
yeah I
[Music]
okay okay
okay wait I need them as
[Music]
planks is that good
enough okay and then PLS
oh
h a smallen
[Music]
again
yeah I need lots of balls right
[Music]
oh okay that's
enough I may just want make more
no okay good enough
yeah okay and then wait I need water and
the bows bow and a three beetro okay
oh I don't have that much
be
[Music]
hi doesn't have to be in a super in like
a super shape or something like that
more
beads more
beads oh but not too many
beads that doesn't make
sense oh
I made
[Music]
one I don't have space I will show you
that I can do this all on my
[Music]
own not
it wait
a they don't
[Music]
stack why it's pot Sal can
stock let s done that's better okay okay
and
[Music]
then I don't think this really
helps I don't know if I'm going to be
able to make this
it's very
[Music]
complicated I can't think you this
rabbit
still I did it I did it do I still have
it I still have
it who
I I have stuff for this
St the special yeah but I don't think
huh yeah
I don't have enough stuff though can I
just give you what stuff um I have parts
of it but I don't think it's going to
work what do you mean I have like the
beetroot stuff one second let me let me
give you
ingredients yeah that's a lot of golden
carrots once
again
um I don't need
that I don't need one second use use it
to make
it I have I know but make me
something I can't get everything else
why let me let me check what I don't
have
[Music]
still make
more I
[Music]
okay I have the golden carrots I think I
have more beetroot soup I need more
rabbits too I don't know how to make
that I need more stain
BB you need RIT and a whole bunch of
extra things it wasn't easy to
make I'm going to put my stuff away I
don't think I'm going to be able to make
it okay I'm just going to
theultimate let see what's
next okay here we go holded appon I'm
going to put my stuff
[Music]
away can I get through here
please
is look how nice it looks like it looks
like a little
Crown
[Music]
yeah you think that would be the
entrance
oh that's what was
sing very special very very speci oh oh
oh why is there water
here what is going
on you have any
problems no there's
water what
[Music]
there's
water
[Music]
what why is there water
outside
[Music]
okay I might have spil it you spiled it
where you
closy what
why
stuck to go away you know like the
ground oh it did not
fall oops I don't know how to fix it
well it's not hurting anyone so I guess
it's
okay okay I'm going to put my other
stuff away ah I put my Construction
Supplies in here
that makes
[Music]
sense that that make
sense to make sure I spill it outside I
SP it in the same spot
[Music]
more water now I
hope huh
[Music]
here no no not there here
hot
water this is good I don't have any more
ultimate recipes to
[Music]
make okay yeah okay I want to make some
more good
[Music]
look get a little bit oh my gosh the
pond is getting
bigger I wased to a hole dig a hole then
dig a
hole dig a tiny
[Music]
hole
what pick it up with the bucket
[Music]
I don't want it to flood into our
house don't have it flood into our
house this is the Jade sword
base it didn't
work uhoh the water in
the I don't have
any it's getting
bigger it's getting bigger
[Music]
can't put the water back in
the are
youing it looks like it's getting bigger
no the I got one water
bucket was that the
source try to put it in
here working it's an natural
[Music]
on well it stops back here
but oh no is their house okay okay their
house is okay for now I don't
[Music]
want okay
I've never looked at the back of the
statue it's very
golden can't get
any I don't know where the is
[Music]
either well let's hope it doesn't get
hor I'm trying my best
here see SW is in
danger I only put a little bit of water
and now there's a lot of water
hi well it's a it's a self watering
Garden
right let's
hope you
[Music]
help
how it's not Mak any difference is it
no how many sources three buckets were
wait
what up with blocks
[Music]
did it get better I don't think
so looks like I took some water but it's
still just as much
water do I have a bucket
[Music]
no more bugs
here I only have four blocks hopefully
that does
it
oh kind of kind
of still water over oh I think it's on
the other side
[Music]
I think it's
returned well it's not that big of an
issue maybe we can just leave it like
that it's just a natural onand that's
fine
yeah nobody saw
[Music]
anything
right nobody saw anything right
[Music]
wait wait help no
oops
[Music]
okay just it's just a water nothing
nothing was done there just a little a
little pool right there
yeah it's
beautiful what's the point of here
Beauty
to get
married married yeah I was thinking the
queen could get married
here I guess the ceiling is a bit
[Music]
L maybe this is where our journey ends
for
tonight I'm going to
go it's smells good
here and we'll see
where we get with this thing some more H
[Music]
okay byebye