ah wait one second
my pto
i cleaned up my
my files like i put them in a different
folder
oops
audio stock
stock
audio stuck
audio stock
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
da
oh
[Music]
mom
da
[Music]
oh
hello brb was it
[Music]
okay
just because i got up for one second
before the stream i was always around 70
to
85. what what's why am i so doki doki
right now
hello
calm down chill yeah now i'm calming
down
i walked over to my
uh
to another room for one second and
immediately my heart rate goes like
yeah
welcome
yokoso
happy halloween
almost
er
it is the spooky week the start of the
spooky week it is
trick or treat
wait i think that is a little bit loud
wait a second i need to adjust the audio
every time i tap out it will uh mute the
audio
one second
[Music]
i mean we'll have to see how loud this
is uh during the
actual play for like sound effects and
stuff but i think it should probably be
a little bit lower
because it's probably going to be louder
than in in the game
[Music]
oh oh now i'm calm again you know it's
under 80. so
i'm using a heart rate monitor stream
heart monitor
[Music]
yeah i got a new battery and with the
new battery it suddenly started working
thankfully i was for a moment i was
worried it wouldn't work even with the
new battery because i i put it in and
and for a while it just wouldn't do
anything
but thankfully it's working
yay
so for the whole rest of the week i will
be having my heart rate monitor on
uh extreme cholesterol
yeah but at least um if i am close to
getting a heart attack you you probably
see it coming
maybe you can call the the ambulance
then but this says this game
so
first of all i was super excited to see
so many of you guys so excited about uh
this game
um
i know this game for a long time since
my childhood i never actually played it
myself i just watched my mom play it i'm
not sure if it was this one or american
mech
gg i think the actual creator is
watching this right now so i'm actually
um i don't want to [\h__\h] up the name
but i'm actually not sure is it mac g or
mechy
the other one wait wait number one
backgey or number two mac g which
sorry english not my first language
the heart hard key soft pee
number one meg ghee mcgee
maggie
maggie magic
you don't say mac
is it mick mickey
mickey mckee
let's say let's say uh american
and
macaulay wasn't that a virus program
[Laughter]
monkey
well well anyway it doesn't matter so my
mom was playing either this one or the
older one and i remember her playing it
i kind of had an interest in it already
when i was younger but
i never got to playing it and then i was
thinking about what games to play for um
uh how the halloween week and
one of my or my number one best friend
who's probably you might actually be
watching this as well right now
um she
really loves this game it's one of her
favorite games ever and she said to me
kiana why don't you play this game on
stream
and i'm like you know what
that's a good idea because first of all
ea games we got permission second of all
it's a cute creepy game
and
uh
yeah i i know it from before i know this
would be cute but i didn't expect so
many of you guys to know it and like it
even goodall wrote to me
just before the stream that she's
excited seeing me play the game
because she likes it too oh my god i'm
getting doki-doki when i talk about
gouda
um
uh we're gonna play this today and i
think it's like a 14-hour game if you
play it well i guess
so we might play this in like two to
three streams if you guys want to see a
series made out of it oh
gouda
i'm using the heart rate monitor that i
got for outlast
i think today we will not be too
doki-doki during the game though because
apparently rather than it being a
scary game it's more of a creepy game
right like the story is apparently
very disturbing
uh that's all i really know and i know
it's about like alice and like her
family and and her like story and all
that
i don't know much because i really just
remember barely my mom playing it and it
looking creepy and cute at the same time
which is i think a great
um
combination but yeah i think it's great
that we're playing this rather than a
million jump scare games cause that's
not really my thing but i'm glad we
found this and now let's get started
uh
obviously nightmare just kidding nah
i'm gonna go with normal i hope normal
is actually normal and not hard because
in some games normal is hard
for the sake of the
[Music]
now stream do it around here is this
okay you guys see the the left one you
guys see it
you guys see that one
yeah
yeah okay okay
okay
it's a very dark game so you're gonna
have to
yeah look at dark screen all the time
invert vertical look what does that mean
what does that mean
what do you mean
ah what does this mean what do i want
yes off on off off off off okay i don't
know what it means but okay oh
we're getting started
ding dong collect and treasure every
memory okay okay
[Music]
make it louder
i think a bit louder it would be good
oh man so many keys
wait i have to make a little louder
there's better now aren't we my head's
exploded and there's a steam hammer in
my chest
yes well the cost of forgetting is high
my memories make me vomit what can i
remember other things
i want to forget who would choose to be
alone imprisoned by their broken
memories i'll set you free alice
memory is a curse more often than a
blessing so you've said many times it
wasn't essence
the past
[Music]
no i didn't skip on purpose is it
because i clicked into the game pills
from our high street chemist now can we
redo can we redo i want to redo
i wanna
yes
how much did i skip
continue game no i want to
no give me give me
give me a new game
[Music]
[Laughter]
go
normal
[Music]
confirm
off confirm go okay no no i'm not gonna
click anything just gonna enjoy it
impatient week
welcome thank you for the membership
by the way i'm just going to mention it
now slightly but at the end i'll give
more details there will be
come now alice it's only a dream
it's not a dream something like a
giveaway a memory
and it makes me sick
now
in the second episode of the stream
floating not today but soon
a cipher
relax
i'm in hell forget it
it's unproductive
go
to wonderland definitely a better idea
yeah
[Music]
did she get burnt by her family or what
the house
discover that delusion forget it
go
to wonderland yes that's what i want to
do
my wonderland's shattered it's dead to
me your preference doesn't signify girl
now alice where are you
i'm sailing
pickle bingo
wait i really want something i'm
something in my brothings have changed
change is good it's the first link in
the chain of forgetting what's happening
are you mad i'm not mad rabbit that's
not right
there's something wrong
[Music]
corruption it's killing me
wonderland is destroyed
my mind is in rome no way get it
block that dream
wake up the sound
holy moly
and that's when i skipped
my head's exploded and there's a steam
hammer in my chest
well the cost of forgetting is high mind
men
what can i remember other things
i want to forget who would choose to be
alone imprisoned by their broken
memories i'll set you free alice
memory this is mumei talking to crony
and i will say again the past must be
paid for
now
before our next session
collect those pills from our high street
chemist
very well doctor
interesting i don't really understand
but she forgot oh she's trying to forget
her past
oh my god his face charlie
your power was hung for killing your ma
who beat you oh my god forget that shall
we
the past is dead charlie
okay he just really wants everyone to
forget
everything but
that's not good you gotta you gotta work
for a real past you know boys room
so i'm alice
i'm playing little keyboard by the way i
hope that's
i already done
[Music]
oh is that the dude that's like uh
our our therapist oh nice drawing oh
you also got a weird face
where blue is am i the only one with a
cute face here
i need to figure out the controls but
for now wasd is the way to go can't find
the door
eh me
yeah i can't find the door which door am
i looking for oh my god oh my god
am i looking for this door no
i can't do anything with those doors
no controller i don't know i felt like
playing with uh
do something any keyboard is there even
an option to play with
the controller and that's fun can i do
that too
i want to jump how do i jump
what tears you want to give them tears
what
that's weird alice you're weirdo
here now
okay must be here controller is better
well we'll see we'll see
and the first person camera mode
oh i can look at their weird faces even
closer
number nine and number two
okay
[Music]
earn your keep
mr payne had no idea how humble a home
could be if not for my drawings and the
photographs this could pass for my room
at the asylum
asylum
wait it's all her
all those all those wonderland friends
oh the mad hatter
and those what are those called again
what are they called again the
these two i don't remember
but i remember their existence
this photograph of my family was
delivered here by post no message ah
tweedledee will damn ah
lumas is no return address i'm grateful
for this memento but i wish i could
thank the sander
oh oh okay okay okay
umbrella
all right
a chest can i look inside no
oh oh
sunlight how nice a pet
is a hatter without the charm
what me you you talking about me
why
all right don't talk about me behind my
back like that i mean i'm right in front
of you even then i don't want you to
talk about me at all
[Music]
rude
okay i have found the way out a
different dream perhaps
okay we gotta get our pills
maybe i should
join them
what did you just say
sideways especially oh disgusting oh my
god
oh my god how do i dash i need to dash i
need to cat is that the chest shy cat oh
my god where did it go
where did it go
[Music]
oh my god [\h__\h] the pills i'm gonna go
with the cats it's always the cats
[Music]
no
where am i going
this way oh oh dear
i've got a bad feeling is the cat gonna
lead me to wonderland hopefully
wait where did it go
[Music]
i need to give it some food
seems following furry creatures into
dark holes has become a habit
i hope it's not a vice
indeed
it do be a habit let me turn the music
down a little bit for you guys only a
little bit
oh sure
wow
i can adopt you i'm a really good cat
mom trust me
where'd you go
you jump up high oh
going down the rabbit hole literally
but this time it's a cat hole
disgusting
[Music]
one eye is an alien
eww another one
[Music]
i need to take my pills
oh my god
alice little
[Music]
you have the most disturbing nose i've
ever seen what luck
twice in as many months straight out of
the horror movie lainey you look
frazzled early not doing well dazzled
not really come along home then and look
at my pigeons your [\h__\h]
like you thank you i wouldn't say a
pigeon is as pretty as a phoenix expert
and got me nowhere i might recall where
your mindy rabbit got to i'm looking for
a cat now not a rabbit woman
women still a mess no surprise they know
i'm a burn yeah chestnuts right before
her eyes 10 years in rutledge asylum
wasted everyone's time
dr bombay won't do better
the fire her memory i deserve
consideration
well who are you into her new clothes
who got her place that bombays yeah it
should be without me on the street
selling her backside look like smith
but what i know is worth more than that
kept her secret haven't i what's my
secret
[Music]
that's my nanny holy wow but don't go
stupid rabbit need money wound her i
tell the corpus if she didn't make her
donation to my upkeep she yells and goes
off her head this she cannot remember
her name what i heard
you need to write it on your hand alice
how could you forget your own name it's
famous this is such a beautiful name
such a beautiful name
good pickiana thank you let's hope we're
gonna have a good time today hey jeans
yeah honestly
phoenix and chicken is cuter you guys
are cuter than those pigeons
i mean those are cute too but still what
was i just about to look at but
the thing the thing
the the i could ah see
a coop is really just a cage but the
birds don't see that's not true a coop
is a proper home okay
nothing wrong with a coop
oh
yeah really cool scenery
this kind of gives me those do you mean
it reminds me of um
i won't say no you know in the ttrpg you
could photograph the bird lady where the
birds
oh
[Music]
oh yeah
oh yeah baby
nice now the real game starts yeah
exactly
yeah we're in wonderland
he told me to go to wonderland
it looks beautiful
but my hair is longer my hair is so
luscious now
she finally brushed her hair
oh we're
descending
alice has to send it
very upsetting journey
but i'm rid of priss or whatever she's
becoming what about the cat's doll
at least the place i've landed is
somewhat familiar yeah it looks familiar
to me too from watching my mother play
what the hell is that
lasted cat don't try to bully me i'm
very much on edge got that big smile
actually no age you're taking up too
much bay has those triangle lights
but you know i can be beautiful smile
when necessary thanks very much i was
hoping to escape from all that oh wait
now this subtitle is hard to read a new
law one second this wonderland
i'll change it just as all round when
they stop here talking be on your guard
okay
yes okay so let me move the chat
um
maybe maybe here
yes okay
i thought there would be an invisible
wall hey
hey
also i mean it's just a dream right this
is all not real can't be real i mean oh
now i can jump
oh
yeah
wait where did you go the cow the cow
bird
can i get that
who's that
no okay
cannot get that but ah do i need to get
the the butterflies
oh god it's very close to the ground
wait
no i don't think so
okay maybe i just need to follow them
yeah it looks like i need to follow them
[Music]
um
oh
is that a memory
recover memory oh look at this i swear
i know
i'm wrong
uh i didn't warm up my frogness yet so
it didn't sound perfect but
press space but i already know thank you
i'm aware of jumping
[Music]
and quite honey look at those moves i
got
badass huh praise spacebar again while
jumping to try now
i know
my uh
my guts told me my no way that's not the
right word is it my yo
i had a feeling that's how it would work
yeah
all right we got another memory
um maybe this time i'm not a frog but
a crowd
from that table again alice i'll explain
i'll expire two times
i love that phrase
i have to use that like when someone's
testing my patience i'll say
if you do that again
gouda i'll expire for [\h__\h] sake
[Laughter]
okay
i'll expire i love that
[Music]
a spongy consistency good at is merely a
stinky toad still just kidding
that's such a funny words to insult
someone stinky toadstool that sounds
like something that good i would say
honestly
keyhole
can i can i become small
how do i get small i want to go through
here
maybe i can't become small yet but soon
yo the graphics are actually
damn nice for when was this release 2011
that's like 10 years ago
i mean maybe
maybe my standards are low but i think
it's very pretty
drink me yes give me give me jimmy i
wanna be small
before good things in small packages
though lacking a bathing costume this is
smooth in that pool is in order oh
[Music]
oh yes nice shower free shower good
i'm shrinking in this potion
shall i disappear
but the upside is that while smaller you
can see things that are nearly enough
oh i get it right forests for the trees
just the other way around short sighted
is more than a matter of perspective
wow she's very articular for her age
okay wait hold left control
while strong ellis will gain shrink
sense
is there a difference in what i'm seeing
not yet wait did she just take
[Music]
so wait i have to keep it i keep holding
it okay okay okay memory
look how small she's become all curled
up
oh i've done this before is that what
you're saying i just don't remember
okay
oh
again
all right amelia watson
ah is this
[Music]
haven't we passed through here before
no
i think we have do i need to go up here
ah wait oh no no this is the hole that i
need to go through ah
cute snail oh my god that looks like
that uh spongebob snail okay
okay
what's that what's it called the
gary or
what was it
oh
oh oh
uh
wait a second why is it so big
oh there's another one a tooth
am i the tooth fairy
gary yeah gary right gary
there's another one
another hidey hole
is this just a way to go back
oh
no there's more to it
apparently
why is it so quiet it's kind of creeping
me out that is so quiet i feel like
there's a flight coming
[Music]
sus oh small gary again
oh
look at the walls one shrunk oh okay
[Music]
oh i love this i love slides don't don't
bunk into the snail shells i think crap
i got a ball
right try girls
mm-hmm is this blood that's kind of
concerning oh what is that is that a
dinosaur
easy cut purple blade is sweet and keen
and always ready i smile
it's for me
oh
beautiful beautiful i've not come back
here looking for a fight
that's a pity
once certainly looking for you oh
someone's looking for me
you have just obtained
the vorpal blade
go snicker snack it leaves them dead as
seen in previous poem oh
all right
the warper blade inflicts the swift as
damage to a single target at close range
that looks funny
press left mouse button to attack with
the wobble blip
sweeping these flaps
can we like destroy the shells
oh we can't oh sh
why is the earth rumbling wobble voice
is shaking
why is there an earthquake
and what is that is that
me
beautiful face why are you crying
flight or fight implies a permanent
chance but flight often just means
putting off the fight to another day
choose your battles wisely alice that
sounds like a german accent for me
choose your battles wisely alice he says
uh i think alice is extremely wise for
her age but
we'll see how smart she really is
oh i like smashing those shells sure
oh
wait was i supposed to notice that the
skeleton is gone
i see that yeah
okay
where did it go
[Music]
insidious ruin it's cute
i have to focus on an enemy okay ah
okay left mouse repeatedly for a series
of swift vocal layers
all right easy can we get another one
hey
wait what was focus again f okay left
shift dodge it any time even when when i
left shift
at any time
fun fun fun works nice okay
[Music]
very simple
i like it
i already took a little look at the
controls i saw with right click you get
like a
ranged attack
a flower's purpose is simple and
immutable human purpose is fickle
because it is a slave to memory memories
must be strictly managed alice
unproductive ones must be eliminated
oh i can do a double
oh wait how much is three times the
maximum of jumps i can do oh while
jumping press and hold spacebar to
initiate alice's float okay
okay to further extend float press and
hold spacebar again while jumping cool
okay
hi
oh floating
what's gonna be used multiple times
multiple times when i was jumping okay
jump and oh give me give me
yeah
hey this is a platformer and i'm
actually not too bad at it at the moment
what's this a bottle
oh
what does it do to me i wonder
oh where do i go
over there no yes yes actually yes
left shift to dodge yeah okay okay why
are you telling me now
is there a fight coming up again or uh
[Music]
another bottle
alice
there's a there's a letter inside
can i open it
what
who
could that be
is that also a character from the
original
who is that
i don't remember a character like that
wait is that the queen you may approach
why would i do that you want to eat me
yes well you taught me manners and i've
lost my taste for my favorite one
porcine diet for me
everything's better with bacon don't you
agree
yes now there are big snouts scattered
about i heard a few behind the house go
fetch them for me peak snaps
pests that block your way pepper them up
if they do
they need spice and you're just the dick
a girl
[Laughter]
skin needs protection from the
disgusting alabaster skin commits the
environs but one gets peckish
look all you have to do is listen for
the ointment i'm going to shoot the
snout okay you may like the results
shoot them certainly will
all right uh i don't know who the hell
is this but
what this is this is kiana when i talk
to you
interesting pick up pepper grinder oh my
god you've just obtained the duchess oh
that's the duchess
so it is uh
the the one with the rose garden right
the is that the queen of hearts or is
that a different character
pepper grinder spice up your foes
prepare savory snouts snoots
no that's not her uh huh okay
cute
oops wait uh
wait how do i get smaller again
can i not open the door here open up
maybe for later
all right let's get her some snoots so
she doesn't eat me
uh
butterfly okay okay
that doesn't look like snoots
interesting interesting what first tab
what what what what what
there's so many
there's so many buttons to push
okay okay uh
i'm trying to figure it out okay wait
this one i can just attack normally no
no no
wait i can only attack with the
machine gun right now
did i just see someone sneaking up on me
oh there's more
don't get too close to me
i'm trying to get used to controls
this is my introduction into fps games
well throughout every domain keep an ear
out for snoot snouts
snooty's not skilled enter aiming mode
and shoot the snoot with the pepper
grinder
left yeah if i'm trying to left click
but i think right now only right click
ah tp is all right i guess it's not
first person okay
once the snook is full of peppa it will
reveal puffs and collectibles oh
oh so is it an enemy
we have still asked them to kill
i think now now we're good
now we're good
now we're good okay so
see the toggle aiming mode then locate
this luch
whoa
need
oh more
and at the same time really really weird
it's like an angel i got angel wings
i want to see what's up there though i
haven't been up here right it went the
other direction but
okay wait no there's not really
anything here wait how do i
how do i use my
knife again
right left click doesn't switch to the
knife
scroll
no
try pressing one ah
oh
ah i see i see okay thank you
okay sure
let's see where the little nose is
leading us
isn't that where we came from
yeah are you happy with that the snout
now go away can i have a piece please i
killed it for you i want a pistol i'm
hungry
break the duchess basket to receive a
road oh okay okay now we're talking
oh golden teeth
and now that little door that sassy door
is open
i knew it would open sooner or later
i actually made my myself darker for
today because i thought the game would
be so dark but so far
it's pretty bright
why is the
screen
on the edges
what is that effect trying to tell me
you know what i mean
yeah i mean those lines
i'm not that low health
oh i'm scared
ugh
[Music]
wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait i wanna change like
camera okay
better to keep some safe distance
these are like parasites get out of here
okay i think no one
oh there's one up here
i can't shoot come on
are we calm now
i think i think we're good but there's
still battle music going on ah
um i guess wait i'm coming down no no no
i want to go down
i cleaned up
i'm a good girl mommy you see alice is a
good girl she cleans up all this mess
i'm good girl
oh
can't go for here okay
noise
uh
i guess i gotta go
back up
oh is there is that like a bouncy thing
where there's rainbow shells
what
whoa
wow did they give me more
teeth than others
probably shouldn't jump down there
yeah
i passed it okay okay ah i see it i see
it
i wonder what the dash button is here
i'm sure there's a dash button
i don't wanna know
special
visual usual usually
should i not wait i need to go over
there too right
but where does this lead
the snoot wants me to go here
[Music]
then i kinda wanna go to the other one
first a dodger is just dashing ah
point point crate there we go a memory
finish your suit girls bovine juveniles
gave their all for it was that
i'm gonna fight this later
i can't break it
i think
and now actually the weapon changes
properly whenever i click left click
i don't know why but now now it's easier
okay uh going back
[Music]
shoot the snoot i already did now it's
there so now i gotta shoot it again
tea
and sneeze
i'm surprised it doesn't sneeze
with all that pepper in your nose ew
uh
ah wait did you just build a bridge over
here
oh
oh okay okay
see i could have gone here later on
after all oh well
rpg freak in myself doesn't want to miss
anything
all right all right all right okay
hello enough is that the same girl from
before
or just another one oh god
don't cry
whatever you crying is kind of dangerous
and disgusting
you
think you have some weird illness
that makes you cry
weird ass stuff
can someone like i don't know help her
she's so sad
ew
something attacked me
i thought they were all gone
they creep up on me
leeches those are leeches huh
well the music is getting creepier and
creepier
oh now
uh
okay suddenly the whole mood
changed
oh okay i thought that was an enemy
i know here huh don't touch the black
stuff i suppose
[Music]
i i might want to take one of those
heads as a souvenir um
too bad i can't
pick them up
oh
there's a memory over there
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was so close
wait where was it
oh that one over there i start from here
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah good job good job
i like this whole floating and jumping
mechanism it's a lot of fun
wait how many lives do i have do i lose
hearts when i
uh fall down
i didn't see a live
counter
i could just kind of glide perhaps but
but the the the volcano [\h__\h] sprouting
out of there is
no penalty oh okay it is pretty high i
just i can't just glide over it i think
wait wait one more
one more
hi hi and
yeah
we landed safely ladies and gentlemen
you may now unbuckle your seat belts
the railway running through wonderland
sounds charming but there's a plane
noise and smoke like snips and snails
perhaps best to forget that train
a mock turtle's conductor oh no i don't
think that would do it at all
turtle
why why can't the turtle be the
conductor also which way do i go back
this way
oh didn't get hit nice
this is ah this is my way to redeem
myself at uh platformer games
so far i think i'm doing an okay job
okay now we go left
[Music]
another earthquake
ellis is this whole thing not freaking
you out you're way too used to this it
scares me
or is that the railway that we just
talked about
oh gosh
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
[Music]
unfocused
this
this uh
pepper thingy
is a lot of fun to use
very efficient
where is the salt though can someone
pass me the salt
i'm in
i need some salt here
the balance is off
hello ives read this as your life
depended on it because it does oh [\h__\h]
gabbard these pearly whites to prevent
your premature arrival before the pearly
gates
what do you mean death my friends can
use the choppers and you'll improve your
weapons capacity oh you mean you mean
the teeth i should just keep on uh
uh collecting the teeth no problem
oh you want me to buy stuff now
well i can upgrade
these two
whopper blade give me 150 teeth to
upgrade your rubber band yeah yeah yeah
yeah let's do it
nice this one i don't have enough tea
for that one okay
there was still i was still an enemy
alive though
could have could have let me kill that
one
i'd always hated mechanical maybe there
wasn't this disaster is either his doing
or his epitaph
i want to go up there
nobody died can i
wait
from further away
yeah no
i wanna go up there
veil of tears looking glass railway
[Music]
when how do i get out here
it's small to find clues i am but right
now it wasn't even necessary
one more teeth
oh god oh god the earth is shaking
got another bottle i still don't know
what those bottles are about but okay
maybe it's just like collectibles
for the people who want a hundred
percent the game
uh
how to become small again i forgot
ah there we go
are there any clues
it's so nice being small oh yeah ah
wait
i did not see that before yeah
[Music]
well that's very nice of the game
oh over there
maybe
yeah it is indeed a timeless game
it's it's so old and yet
it doesn't feel so old
what are other games from 2011
compared to this one i wonder how they
hold up
okay this is the way where we have to go
oh i almost died
dark souls skyrim really what
oh my god
what's going on
who's laughing at me this is not funny
[Music]
don't even think about touching me
i am an idol i don't need any leeches
thank you bye bye thank you for your
understanding
[Music]
oh no there's no return
we cannot go back we can only move
forward
that's a nice way of living life though
i'm gonna get crushed here no oh never
slide yeah
what is this
teapot
even in the teapots they got
teeth
what is this like a
village
there's a big big one over there
[\h__\h]
shoot shoot [\h__\h]
doesn't work
oh hello
bad cap
ah you wanna fight
no problem
come at me
a spoon and a fork you think you can
hurt me with that i got the knife yo
i keep on spamming uh dodge
stabbed him right through his heart
oh
alex can dodge enemy attacks sure
okay he's got a shield
well whenever you don't move it might
hurt me but you also get stuck in the
ground so i don't know how smart that
really is
here
did hurt me a little bit there huh
is there anything in here
no
why am i trying to be small i don't want
to be small gotta be big
can small
fight though i guess not
[Music]
those bodies are kind of tough you
fierce alice
[Music]
no no no this is not the polite way
young man
you grounded
did one of them get tortured
i i like um
the way they're guarding their private
areas with a clock
[Laughter]
does it help
does it work
well anything you can take i guess
anything that helps
[Music]
uh which way to go
should i try going up
can i even go up
probably not okay
it tells the top yeah but it's kind of
hard to look at it don't you think when
it's down there
lost and don't know where to go try
using shrink where
ah
oh specifically where those flowers are
okay well strong shrink sense will
reveal hidden paths and close oh
aha
oh
oh that was also not there before
oh wait it's about
i want to go here first
what do we have ah a mama no a bottle
got like a bottle what are they about
what do the bottles mean mason
go inside the flower what
what
what is it doing oh it's healing me
what a nice flower
it kills them as well though
oh
do i have to be small in order to walk
over it or oh no i don't have to
what where does a child
you ran away
it could have been done that way alice
you remember poor mr cru poor mr guy
didn't he i guess so did wilson reject
spontaneous combustion but i trust mr
dickens lady i don't know what you're
talking about what is that in front of
me oh
wow
beautiful
and i see a snook
stupid leeches everywhere they're
everywhere god damn it
oh they're so cute
they're
so i listen to the matte top header man
header
mad hatter
yeah let's see
it's beautiful can we go there are we
going there
do we go left or right
gotta shoot
shoot the snoot
uh tea
eat eat come on a little bit more
that's only one spice we're gonna add
more spices the 12
12 secret spices or 11 secret spices how
many is it
is there something to get here
call cable car
[Music]
damn elephant oh that is a cute cable
car
13 14 x
wait i don't want to go in yet there was
something on the left side
no no no no no no no no no no
i didn't think i would go in there right
away can i go back
[Music]
did i miss something important alice
much has changed since your last visit
dr bumby says change is constructive
that different is good different denotes
neither bad nor good but it certainly
means not the same fine basket
he knows more about different than you
but does he know more about the
difference between bad and good
making friends alex you're as randomly
lethal and entirely confused oh nice
bpm69
we're still calm
to you i'll call if i need you
predictably rash it's not a question
oh my god
um
we're getting wrecked here and as they
say can we go faster
can we go faster why are we so calm
it hit 69 a few times now oh
new dress i like how there's so many
like different dresses in this game i
already like know that there's like a
lot of them
some vents oh and molgus need to be
activated by turning veils
oh
while on the vent you can rotate alice
to exit the event press spacebar or
simply move away from it
uh-huh
okay
we'll try to figure that out look at
that steampunk alice
whoa
damn
how are you
steampunk
okay
memory
remember when a burst of steam blew your
dress up around your neck eh just
outside hands
fortunately your undergarments had been
laundered
uh that sounds really creepy um
kind of uh
perverted why are you even talking about
that
that's embarrassing
can i go over there
wow fascinating fascinating
that's that's the thing that i have to
turn around the valve
with my noodle arms
and
what you're coming to welcome me oh how
nice of you
can i fall down in the middle of a
battle can i fall down here i hope that
it's mighty close kind of dangerous
should i go there first
no it's only a flower
no need i'm full health
i crying
him this time
it spreads
those are flamingos no kind of thick
flamingos though oh what is that a light
bulb
cute
can we stop this thing
i suppose
oh it disappears
ah
didn't they play with those like uh golf
didn't they play both of those or some
similar sports
oh no i don't need it sorry thank you
crockett
what the hell's crockett
the sport that they played i don't
remember
crockett like
what kind of game is that
welcome to kfb guys just kidding no we
only have vegan vegan chicken vegan meat
trust me
[Music]
whoa nice dodge
you hurt me ah wait what i'm not dodging
i'm uh
pressing the wrong button i'm gonna die
oh my god
okay okay okay give me that give me
those roses sometimes i press uh
shrinking instead of dodging
i get confused
what is this
is this uh
it's supposed to tell me something
what if i shoot the birds
i need some food come on i'm hungry
mmm
crispy dodo instead of crispy chicken
might be worth looking into that huh kfb
what do you mean kfd
i don't know do they taste good those
birds
oh i did it again
i missed the
you mean they're extinct
when since when
they aren't extinct anymore
oh you guys need to update the
information you got guys
doodles died a long time ago what
since the 60s what happened who killed
the dodos do i need to go over there
for the keyhole
oh wait what the hell how did i not see
that
the dutch
totals were hunted down
people ate them
but
why why would why would anyone eat dodos
i i i totally didn't
think of that
i i didn't think about that at all that
was that was not my idea i would never
think of such a cruel act
were they tasty what did they taste like
does anyone know
do they taste like chicken
not that i would know what that tastes
like
i thought i was falling down oh my god
is it true that your heart stops for a
moment when you sneeze
because i sneezed before the stream and
my heart rate was normal
maybe it's just uh it doesn't update
that uh
it was really just for like a
millisecond wait what the hell what the
hell what the hell wait for me
but you no but you can't keep your eyes
open that i've heard many times and i've
tried
to see if i can hold my eyes open before
i tried but i don't remember was i able
to do it is it really impossible
is that really impossible
don't keep don't keep your eyes it will
pop you'll just pop your eye what do you
mean pop
what what
you can pop your eye what do you mean
popping does it like pop out of your
skull
what
it's getting a little bit creepy here
this is dangerous they will pop out what
are you talking about no way
no way
you can still see after they pop out
what the [\h__\h] does that mean
[Music]
well now i feel challenged i want to try
it i want to try squeezing with my eyes
open
no way
never felt such a pressure
in in my eyes when i sneezed when when i
closed my eyes as if i was holding them
back from falling out that is that that
can't be true
don't you guys really don't want me to
do that wait wait wait what's with the
battle music
okay
okay okay
the battle is
[Music]
he got me again
oh my god is there more oh my god
the leech
oh we did it
mythbusters proved this
wrong oh really
okay so i can open my eyes when i sneeze
i can i mean i can try nothing bad will
happen
it's a myth oh is it a holo man
oh
this is not the time to
mistake the buttons
[Music]
wow
oh man
of course i would like to continue how
do i press yes
ah
okay
my heart rate went up how fun
i wanna change it to a different buttons
oh my god my wait my my my finger
my finger
my little finger
can we change it
configuration
it's the controls use the controller now
i'm getting used to this i can't change
it now
uh dodge what would be good can i do um
can you do this no
is something on the out
nothing is on alt right
uh
alt
should work
okay
but i'm gonna die anyway i think
ah
out
okay
okay no i'm not using a controller no
uh
i i mean
it is a lot of buttons yeah
difficult to remember for my little
phoenix brain
oh i think i think i can get used to
this oh my god
[Music]
should i use my peppa gun
v or right click for dodge but right
click is ah
kill him kill him kill him come on
okay okay okay okay we're doing it we're
doing it we're doing it we're doing it
we're doing it
okay he's stuck
into little choppy pieces
bite-sized pieces
served directly onto your plate you're
welcome
okay
okay okay
we did it
we did it we did it we did it
i think
i think the placement is better because
now i push dodge with
my thumb
instead of my little tiny
pinky
that's a bit better is that is there
anything to see here though
i don't want to miss out on anything no
she fights the same ass in skyward so
you mean um
oh you mean
like smashing buttons and panicking
constantly
my heart is really doki-doki i feel it
[Laughter]
that is a legit fighting style okay guys
don't doubt it
is there something here oh wait look at
that
look at that it's the mad hatter
[Music]
no way that there's not a keyhole
somewhere here
okay
time to be calm
[Music]
okay
take a deep breath in oh wait what did i
hear a
snook don't see it but i feel like i
hear it
where does the sound come from
no
is it below
i hear it everywhere everywhere i go
it's like super close
okay whatever
ah maybe eyes in there perhaps
oh [\h__\h]
did i even
[Laughter]
oopsie
all right i see the secret path though
can i land
thankfully the game is so forgiving
otherwise
i would be uh
devastated
okay
oh there you are
would definitely not turn that down
would she
a golden teeth that's what i missed in
the other place huh my heart is open
alice never closed
never locked
it needs no key is that my mom talking
doesn't have someone though that uh
pig snoot is a special delicacy
does she know that
because aren't her fans uh the hattons
aren't they considered to be pigs
do they know that
their snoots could be used
for hot summer cooking
wait wait go here
you make bacon out of the hotels
um bacon
i can't i can't judge you for that
i would do the same bacon out of the
hotdogs
before i go to that side i want to check
out this side
no missing secrets
[Music]
or is this the way they want me to go
all along
now
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
i can't believe these weaklings got the
upper hand on me
bricks are rocks alice bricks a bricks
like gibraltar is impervious to fire
weather
and the indecencies of barbary mcax for
the need arise but what what
i say that a lot don't i
your little [\h__\h] is like one of my
two goal
phrases
when i'm upset
why would you do that
it's my catchphrase yeah
goddamn it
oh wait i guess i can wait here
and then okay
[Music]
that was
close but a good try
[Music]
mmm teeny
what was it like for over 400
teeth for an upgrade on my pepper gun
i think it was something like that
it's pretty expensive but okay
475 okay
we will get there
i hear another snoot
where is it
whoa there's a lot of broken plates down
there
it wasn't me i just want to say
oh
on show me the way
oh is this what you did thank you
where would that bring me to oh was it a
little secret
yata
there are no secrets
with alice
i find out everything you can't hide
alice was often
an interior
her sister though loving and much loved
oh
my sister was too old alice had a sister
wait what did she have a sister in the
original too
did she play
she played no role right but maybe you
did see her like in the beginning
when i say original i mean like the
disney original
the old alice
movie
the youngest of three really
[Music]
yeah the movie or the book
i see those as originals i know it's
originally a book but
i mean the first disney movie is a
classic
i would say all right let's see
what is this big room
did someone just close the doors on me
oh
it's like i i called
from apple
oh my god well that [\h__\h] stabbed me
to death
[Music]
oh there's another one
how fun
i gotta hit it from front huh
whoa whoa what's that
oh my god
[Music]
oh
that's a tough one
finally
this what's what's shooting that
oh you're in the back
oh thank you
oh thank you i guess you're just trying
to help right
sorry i'll be right there
honey
i'm on my way
i'm on my way wait for me
you sound so excited to meet me
no no no don't shoot don't shoot don't
you don't don't
[Music]
what do you think guys
i would say
an improvement
has been made
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
oh wait um
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
my heart rate went up there
115 is that the highest i got today
let's make a record
oh hell no please no record lost and
found oh
oh
honey
he's obsessed with time
find him
crash yourself off girl the hatter
should see you at your best after all
you think what's wrong with my looks
right now what's your issue are you
saying i'm i look ugly
i'm beautiful
outlast will hit you you will hit 200 on
no
am i supposed to fly through that what
no you can just go here never mind
oh yeah i need that big flower please
can i open that no
okay
outlast is the real heart challenge
it is
i actually thought of something um
like a stream that i want to do
with my heart monitor um but
it doesn't i feel like it would fit the
best if i were to do it like around
valentine's day
so it's gonna be a while until i
uh i'm gonna make that stream happen
where am i supposed to go
it's it's like i want to use the heart
monitor but not in a
like scary way but in like a
and oh ah here in a doki doki in a good
doki-doki kind of way you know what i
mean
yeah
so i might do that like around the
anniversary of
uh
heart challenger
the one year anniversary
that'll be a first yeah yeah so i felt
like you know why why only use the heart
rate monitor for like spooky games and
scary games
there must be other ways to use it as
well
gotta think
kiara think innovative
i've been actually just generally trying
to think of some original ideas like
um
like funny stream ideas that are not
games just like oh no not never one of
those
um rather than games i wanna
no okay
i wanna do more like i don't know how to
call it like
wait which way should i go first
oh maybe maybe i'm supposed to go the
other way first
ah no no i feel like
one
two
oh my god
straight
sounds promising yeah um like
like you know we're ah [\h__\h]
where for example i would be the host
and like you know how how um
was it mikko senpai who did like a
who's who's the best mommy stream
so i was thinking of stuff like that
and i got a couple of ideas
why
why did i do that
and up we go
okay
i got the bottle
nice
and smooth landing
let's get pretty for the mad hatter huh
shall we are we changing outfits again
because he kind of said
yo you need to
look pretty for him
this is where
i'm supposed to go next
[Music]
i guess so
okay
pull it
what what's changing
okay
yeah getting her drip
did i check this place out before i
i don't always want to go into the most
obvious direction uh i think i did
because i'm scared of missing secrets
but that's the door that just opened
right
yeah are we doing a slide
again that one's fast oh my god
thankfully it was only shorts
oh same clothes
we're supposed to look pretty for him oh
what
he's gonna explode
but wait
am i supposed to run away from him
ah oh maybe ah bring him up here
pick up clockwork bump some walls and
floors are weak and can be destroyed
all right
place the clockwork bomb near the weak
surface
detonate the clockwork bomb to destroy
the weak surface easy
[Music]
heal to throw the clockwork bump okay
wait
i'm trying to platform here
nice way of throwing that oh will that
hurt me too
no okay
i was on a safe distance
throwing another one now
oh
we've got a new tool without working
new tool
at our disposal
i'm not ready to go there just yet wait
have i been there
have i been down there before like on a
different level
yeah okay okay
lost and found i thought we were already
lost and found
there's another last and found
is that
no
can't make that go boom
here's my idea attention during eating
with hard bodies
i wonder if my heart would react to that
um
i've
my dorian tweet oh my god
i uh if you follow me on twitter you
might have seen my dorian tweet um
a lot of people were kind of salty for
me tweeting that but hey i mean come on
do i need to like every fruit
we'll all roast in our beds alice for
the sake of your father's unnatural
devotion to printed paper or this horde
of flammables
it's only a malignant spark and
poof
our flesh and blood is smoking
uh you speaking riddles lady
i mean i'm sure it tastes good
but
why why
cr nature why do you create
a fruit that is so stinky
that smells like fights
huh
are we done with like a chapter now but
our lovely library was a fire trap
a conflagration waiting to happen
[Music]
oh
where am i
hello how's it going here
[Applause]
when alice helped his little hat
he hi he heist
his st
hi he's stereo
becomes available
hysteria
okay
by pressing enter
enter oh
while in
hysteria
alice cannot be hurt and will inflict
more damage okay
be careful hysteria only lasts for a
limited time
you're right
[Music]
wait wait wait wait oh you're telling me
now oh my god
whoa
oh yeah i like this i like it
[Music]
a new kind now that's hysterical
rage mode berserk mode
she is motivated
get those thieves
very important to get all of them
gotta be careful here
what do i see here
nothing
okay
says
enter aiming mode by pressing t
uh-huh i know already shoot the switch
when it's red and inactive uh-huh when
it turns green is activated oh
easy you see where is it
which switch
i'm down there
oh
okay one way around all right
could have been so easy
[Music]
you didn't see that that was a time loop
that i was in it didn't actually happen
twice
trust me
as what happened
you should know that better than i it's
your face after all i know my place when
did you ever know your place or how to
keep it now what's going on
that's going on round it up and down
into my ears and through my eyes not my
nostrils got my gallatin writing in my
guts who did this to you fond of trains
i don't like them much do i like this
one at all i think trains are too
expensive just in charge of the looking
last line this railroads are bloody
the stinky ferocious light blinding the
noise
he's rambling and rambling like an old
dude i don't know is that your hand the
inmates run the asylum no
and worst of all
i've left
tears what tragic it's unbelievable will
you help me in return cross my heart
inconceivable find my limbs and toss
them into the suit machines will do the
rest
away now that's a good girl okay
best way out is through the clock face
clock face
okay i'll go grab your body
uh i'm glad you trust me so much that i
i should handle your body
let me take care of it trust me
i will find a way
to collect all pieces
not the tea
you i have bombs all the time now
nice
i could use them in battle even
huh
i want what what
hey
what is this special door
is it for later
there's another one here
that i can blow up
ow wait doesn't hurt me anyway
do i not get damaged from that
there is a hint here something with an
umbrella
wow kelly you are playing my childhood
if this is your childhood then i am so
sorry for you
that is a creepy childhood and you must
be absolutely traumatized
just kidding if you only played it then
that's fine
i'm implying that the game is your
childhood and that that i would feel
very sorry for pressure pads function
only when weight is applied uh-huh
the clockwork bump can be used to
maintain weight on a pressure pad
oh
smart
peanut butter trauma time
oh i have to leave the clockwork there
okay
how cute
oh there's time limit limited dough okay
okay
i'm coming
let's beat me up scotty
want to play this game again i hope
you're enjoying it yeah go play it
i'm glad i can uh remind people of this
nostalgic game i'm i was really
surprised to see
absolutely no one in her life has played
this before like why
such a cute game
[Music]
and i think as a stream game it also
works well
and who doesn't know alice
[Music]
a new weapon press e while focused to
block
oh
no dodging but blocking if timed
correctly alice's block can deflect
certain enemy attacks oh no i feel like
i'm going to suck at this
substantial report wait what what button
was it again
what's the f whatever what
[Music]
you're telling me that didn't work am i
supposed to kill you or deflect you
come on
[Music]
what
i can keep it i don't know
oh
is that working
oh there we go okay
interesting do you have do i have to do
that again
oh oh only the projectiles
[Music]
oh baby you have drink or something in
me
now more fun and games buddy
i love my babies
no i'm not um i just someone's wanted in
the chat and i thought that was funny
[Laughter]
period time baby
i need some help yo
i could use some health
[Music]
what happened
i need all of them
[Music]
i'm ready to go okay but there's another
one over there
assemble
assemblage or destruction as required
let's shoot this from there
[Music]
huh
what
do i need to get closer
oh god the screen is breaking
shoot the snoot snoop
it's not i heard one yeah where is it
though
is it inside
no
it's again very close
is that something i can shoot as well no
no
i thought that would like go up or
something
look over the edges
oh there you are
are you gonna help me now find my way
oh that's a memory that doesn't
necessarily help me with this thing
though but okay
i'll go grab it real quick
recover years now alice time to put away
childishness no i don't wanna
and that's all you're going to tell me
that's it
okay anyway how do i move on though
cranking up and pressing down
upgrade your weapons
i can do the peppercorn now
well how much how much better is it
gonna be
oh
wow
all my teeth are gone
i know it feels stronger
ah can i shoot it down
no i couldn't it couldn't be like that
yeah everyone's down i'm stuck oh wait
what about here
never mind i'm not stuck
[Music]
foreign
a good worker is a life worker that is
very true yes i gotta keep kfb alive
but you know sometimes sometimes they
make sacrifices but it's for for kfb's
best
payday for good workers has been
postponed indefinitely indefinitely
[Music]
i can't listen to what you're saying
what did the cat say it didn't enter my
brain bad workers are
has slaves postponed indefinitely
[Music]
a bad worker is a dead worker and that
one is a network are you here cathy
[Music]
snap up here
it doesn't do anything
all right
all right then
tiana will make her come back no matter
what
what is going on here oh
turn that cluck around
we pay you and payday has been post
wherever we don't have to pay anymore
no
[Music]
decadence excess waste the hatter's
madness ends today
no it will not
no no does someone here have beef with
the hatter
okay we're finally back to full health
your new leaders they look a little bit
[\h__\h] up i don't know what it is about
their faces but something
makes me feel like i can't really trust
them
and your new leader is not them guys
it's me me
only there is new leader
oh can't break it okay
i am your only leader kfp
we're all mad here at camp we know
you're not we're all healthy and we're
doing fine
why are you complaining
[Music]
hello
get out of here
[Music]
oh my god
i missed my period
[Music]
okay
it didn't have much
no no you dropped my health
why
give me my items
that
came out of nowhere
could you not
okay wait a moment
go down be patient
that's
from
i remember that vaguely
don't fall into the lava that's the
least the last thing we want to do
it's just kind of cute if you would
change out the magma for tea
then this would be such a cute tea
session
yeah bye
can we make it can we make it yes we can
yes later on alice
what
also what am i missing
what am i missing did i come from here i
did
nanka
there's supposed to be a lever here oh
it's down there
is it
no
oh
a secret secret
ah
i see gotta become small
in order to see the big picture
that was such a smart thing to say
no i don't hold
up thank god for the hints
okay uh
phoenix wisdom yeah
phoenix
uh what
oh
wait wait wait yes
[Music]
where do you want me to go huh over
there oh
and
and here
is that where you want me to go i don't
see anything here oh except for you
ah mikko senpai should not play this
game oh but hey they bring me over to
the other side
this would be a traumatizing game for
mikko sampler
uh so wait what
we
did something here but oh wait now that
goes up
i just saw something go up there nice we
activated a new mechanism
why would it be for her in particular
because she has a
ptsd when it comes to magma
lava
i wonder if any
other whole live members see me play
this and they're like oh it looks like a
fun game i want to try it too
i wonder
okay
wait
oh there you oh my god you freaked me
out kitty cat
why are you standing there
there is no lever there
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
no no they're trying to manipulate my
wait i forgot how to dodge
himself
[Music]
okay i figured this out really well how
to fight these guys
what the hell what is this angle
what what
you want me to come over there
wait for me wait for me wait for me wait
for me
we have a customer
oh the lever is over there
by the way today um
today is ttrpg guys are you aware
what the hell
okay what's the timing here what's the
timing here
uh uh gunas channel wait it's not coming
now
oh no there it is okay
gouda's channel i don't know if she
already has the reservation up but it
will be on her channel and then
then i think after good at would be me
again or callie actually who knows
i'm here i'm here sorry sorry for
keeping you waiting
[Music]
all right
i got dodging down yeah
i'm glad
hydration
can i jump over there
from here no
holy [\h__\h] the music is so exciting in
this game
oh that's why that music is playing on
yeah
[Music]
oh
wait
[Music]
uh i don't know what the hell i'm doing
right now
oh my god oh my god i don't know what
i'm doing i don't know what i'm doing
i was i was i didn't expect him this uh
okay
i will continue
i know i have to deflect his attacks but
i was too
too panicked
to do anything properly where the hell
am i
ah here okay okay
the f and then umbrella
i wanna
[Music]
i kind of wanted to like kill the ones
around me first but
uh
they kept on
getting in the way
and then i i didn't know what to do
what's up scott thyme
there was something spawning them yeah i
guess so those those uh flying things
were always sent out by a specific enemy
i don't remember which one
all right
it's like this
and then huh
but but which attack
only one attack the one where he like
attacks me with that fire lava whatever
but i never know when that's coming
we can do it we can do it we can do it
we can do it hopefully
i should maybe from up here i should
shoot those things first
can i i can
will they respawn or will it actually
help me in this fight
okay
that's that's all of them
uh was that it yeah
um
[Music]
oh oh i wanted to dodge with an umbrella
okay whatever i don't care i don't care
[Music]
oh he did he died i wasn't that hard
it wasn't that difficult guys
[Music]
can i jump on here
memory
how do i get there
brain is it telling me to use my brain
is it telling me to think
what
pink
does this blow me up no
isn't that too far to reach
does that lead to that place i don't
think so but but it leads me to
something else that's interesting golden
teeth
thank you thank you yeah i could use
some more
uh flowers though
more flowers no
it's another one oh boy is there another
keyhole down there i can now jump on the
ground right yeah it's safe to go now
oh you got that
hello
and another one
what a sad life
only to live for a few seconds
oh i can't destroy that
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm just relieving them from their
suffering
right
that's all i'm doing
so is there any hole here no
there isn't
hm
oh wait oh that does let you fly
oh yeah
oh i didn't think it would be
reachable from that point
all right curse the darkness or the cold
when you're in the library at night
what's in the library
is there anything else to find here
no
i mean there's some boxes to destroy
books
the snoot the snoop yeah i also hear it
you're right
where is the doll
why is this not
it's not
i'm a bottle collector i'm just trying
to get some
some pennies back
i'm gonna bring those bottles to the
supermarket
[Music]
yoho this
the right way yeah
probably
oh yeah
i need to go all the way to the top is
that what you're saying
wait the cat
oh hello gather your nerve uh
all right i mean i could have followed
that without you but sure
[Music]
activated but wait what about the other
path
oh is there nothing here
oh yeah not really okay
[Laughter]
is
okay an explosion
who's your favorite uh
disney character guys who's your
favorite disney princess guys
let's do girls talk come on
and why is it alice wait alice isn't
really a princess though is she
i would consider
a princess somehow kiana i'm not a
disney princess dog
mulan
a lot of mulan
that doesn't do anything tiara
bell oh rapunzel oh it's not
didn't there uh didn't
a new um
disney movie just
come out
what's it called the new one i saw it on
disney plus
what's it called
not no
you guys don't know what i'm talking
about
the one with that little boy or so i
don't know
raya
is that it
plural
cruella is not a
princess
how dare you
how dare you put her in the same
category
wait a second wait a second where am i
going
i'm going the wrong way
but wait where do i go from here if not
there ah here
hercules i like him too but he's also
not a princess
wait there's something down there dude
what if i
oh
i i would have found a secret if i let
myself fall down there
and like let myself glide into that
tower
at a good time
anyway i think ah
i need to shoot that over there
[Music]
uh
can i make that jump
yes
fearless alice
you're right carella is a queen
she has style i will give you that
but
i don't know i mean actually no never
mind
[Music]
didn't she make
uh
out of didn't she steal dogs and out of
the dogs she made those coats wasn't
that her thing
oh my god that is
that is so disturbing if you think about
it cause like you watch that as a child
and i feel like as a child i didn't
quite
even understand or like grasp
how how evil that really is
uh i feel like i missed one
i was like how am i supposed to make it
over there
hey murray the show
how do i get there
okay
oh wait wait there i can stop over there
go go
when in doubt just aimlessly fly around
and hope to find something that rescues
you
advice for life
okay
we made it out so we made it to the top
[Applause]
hello
has nine lives oh
i hope you have as many i'm actually
eternal i can fall down there as many
times as i want
i'm better than you
[Music]
tiana
mulan and merida are the only
hard-working princesses wait prince
tiana
why does it sound familiar but
it might have just might just be because
of tiana
what is that over there i wanna go there
okay
i'm not a child anymore you can't [\h__\h]
me up this time
um
[Music]
never mind
never mind never mind
i
i am i'm going to be more polite next
time i meet those gentlemen
[Music]
oh i'm gonna die
you stopped me how dare you
right in my back i didn't even look
go ahead
go ahead and show you
i don't need your cat has not died
right how do we
how do we improve this
don't die don't get hit
oh my god
[Music]
um
you have angered me
you will regret that only took me one
hit that was not even worth it
i need help
that's a flower it's exactly what i
needed the purple flower
oh you got that
i'm just gonna
chill a little while in here
just gonna relax and sit back and
enjoy
being hugged by a flower
that's pulsating
it's kind of weird but
it feels nice
it's a nice spot yeah it's a special spa
massage
you don't get that at any spa out there
okay i'm ready to go i think i'm gonna
evolve into a beautiful butterfly
ah i feel
like a whole new person i'm telling you
guys
oh yes i remember
i have to go up there
let me go up there
i want to take what's mine oh wait no it
was over there
it was
here hello
[Music]
all is good
okay
ready to continue
yeah where do we go
this one
ah
i'll have to land on that bouncy pad i
give it a try
[Music]
upgrades
i only have 280 teeth
i don't think it's upgrade time just yet
what's this door
what does that mean
death is waiting for me
kelly how nice of you your presence here
is
we have a mission to complete and you
are an intolerable annoyance
what's the mission
but no one likes it
oh don't you underestimate me bae
don't disrespect your senpai
senpai is always welcome
[Music]
i love it when it's hot
drop it like it's hot
no why didn't i jump at that moment i
thought the wolf was just like staying
there
it took so much time
eh come on come on
yes okay okay okay you're welcome to
move up
what is that what is that above me what
the hell
don't you there
where do i go over there
but now i'm too scared to jump
ah
okay
yes
where
[Music]
i exactly want to go up there's a tooth
felt there
no it's not worth it it's not worth it
it's not working
[Music]
me
that felt like minecraft
[Music]
we might want to go up for that one too
come on
okay
change my mind now we're ready to go
yes
is this a bad idea is this a bad idea no
and go
go
oh it's already green nice
and
i okay it
she's gaming hell yeah i am what are you
doing
i'm always gaming
[Music]
first time totally
anyone who says differently will be put
into the usual room
how you like that well strictly speaking
the hatter needs them
give me the arms they don't belong to
you why do you have them
forward industry
i like that
i like that icon
oops
exploding
all right all right this area is now
safe to walk around
what you gonna do huh
[Music]
oh
wait no i want to shoot the other one
wait
i want to shoot
[Music]
oh
that was close
you're challenging me buddy
oh there's another one
there's another one
i could uh
jump up here
[Music]
uh
oh
oh oh oh oh there's so much stuff here
to heal myself i don't even really need
it but i'll take a little bit
i wasn't finished yummy
oh well
oh
you can't reach me
i couldn't even snap you from here you
don't even have windows
this is unrealistic
i shall be able to hit him from there
okay well well well
plot armor
where i don't see it
i guess that's that's the thing about
plot armor
okay
oh
dangerous
uh what do you say about that bales huh
you didn't think i would be able to
manage to do that uh what about those
they're camping for me
that ain't fair
oh my god okay i'm coming i'm coming i'm
coming
okay
and when you focus uh it seems like you
can't change the camera
it changes it for you
most of the time i think it's fine
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
i could use one of those flowers right
about now
where the arms are
is that the arms now no yes it is
she put the bails put the arms
on this weird
lava teapot
why would you do that
what is this
okay
hey
are you guys uh happy with the games
this week by the way
there's a lot of or only new games
except for minecraft
everything's
refreshing and special
what's the game that you guys are
looking forward most to this week is it
and why is it alice madness returns
outlast
can't look at the chat
oh no
that's the one that i'm looking forward
to the least
this is so fast what i can't i can
barely uh make progress here
or am i supposed to
oh oh
i made it
golden teeth for that one single golden
tooth
okay
i have pumpkin carving i'm excited about
that yeah i'm doing a pumpkin carving
stream
[Music]
i hope that goes well like i never did
something like that before
uh
yeah i guess i'll buy a couple
of like smaller type pumpkins not the
insanely big ones because i didn't even
see a very big one
in the supermarket
i only saw like smaller ones
i'll just move along i'll deal with you
later mama might be better again and we
can do more
maybe i can buy five small ones and on
each one i draw i like carve
and
like the the holo myth icons you know
what i mean
like for me
i wonder if i can do that or if that's
too difficult
what
well what's there what's there
money
is it telling me about the keyhole
that would be cute yeah
and then with whatever is inside of the
pumpkin we're making soup by the way
[Music]
pumpkin soup yummy so okay are we ready
to climb up to bales now
how would we go about that just directly
in here
oh bailey's did you did you uh
run away
oh
what the
chicken
what does this do
what about baking pumpkin seeds yeah
i i don't know is that easy
oh
what now can i drop myself in there as
well
oh
ooh looks like that's what we're doing
yeah
okay
are we sure that it's worth it helping
him out
here take your arms for god's sake take
them
i
tell you you should better be thankful
be grateful
get on your knees and say thank you oh
too bad you don't have knees do you
all right then i'll bring you i bring
you the knees so that you can knee on
them and then pray to me and say
bless takanashikiana
glory to kfb that's what i want to hear
[Music]
glory to kp thank you my chickens are
already
listening very well
good chickens
my bpm is so low right now
oh no it's going up thinking about my
chickens my heart
rate goes faster what what just happened
oh yeah right i have to leave a bump
there
okay okay wait are we going the same way
really no
will it lead me to somewhere else this
time
same way
okay
i guess so
nice nice heart rate thank you thank you
how
how nice of you
to compliment my heart rate my heartbeat
is very excited to hear
that you guys
appreciate it
that was worth preparing i'm glad
uh where are we going this time
oh
wait last time
we went that way i guess
do i go there again or this time i try
to go here
i think so
okay
last time left this time right
isn't the other way around
that's some sexy heart you got there
birdie
thank you
can i marry your heart rate why
my heart rate only comes with me
so
you're gonna have to ask me
pass through me first in order to get to
my heart though
is the bpm peterson
you guys are being weird
i showed you my heartbeat answer me
is
[Music]
that does not fit his whole body come on
the balance is way off
i'm already in australia
[Music]
australia has been mentioned
alice's personal lawyer she has a lawyer
isn't she like 13
wow
am i missing something up here no
[Music]
it's your dad it's a doctor what what
she's 19 in this in this game she's 20.
oh really
she's 20.
oh
i didn't realize that
i thought she was supposed to be like a
child not a teenager ah
oh is she younger in
the american
mcgee uh mcgee alice
is that his hand no i already brought
him his hand
oh that's i made it i made the stomping
stop here ah
[Music]
wait can i
that was risky
the first game was two years before and
she had been in an insane asylum for
five years at that point ah
[Music]
interesting
interesting she's going through some
[\h__\h]
poor girl
thank you for renewing your membership
thank you soon
and now
[Music]
no reaching zero bpm should not be a
goal here thank you for renewing your
membership guys
what what what what what what am i
supposed to do can i go there from here
right there
am i am i
thank you for the uh orange
[Music]
this is where i started
is this where i started
okay well let's put this here
blind choke
oh i guess go here
i've already blown something up over
there wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
for me
[Music]
come on
only by touching it
didn't i pass through here before once
[Laughter]
see i did it and i was here before i
blew this thing up
and then
that doesn't even do anything anymore
does it um and now i'm here but wasn't i
here before
okay
wait no no no no no no
no no no no
oh
my
okay thank god and i was a little bit
too slow
maybe i cannot
dodge through that is what i was gonna
say
um
and by the way guys so
uh
we're gonna have a second stream
on this
game maybe
next week or the week after that
and
make me
what am i doing
has kindly offered
to um
do a little giveaway with us
uh
so if you it was so easy what was i
doing if you are interested in one of
the
plushies from
his merchandise store american
mexi
then you gotta wait oh
for next
the next stream
and it will be easy you just have to uh
follow
me and hit mine in his account
and that's all you need to do
and maybe some other things
yeah yesterday like uh he retweeted my
stream reservation tweet i think someone
tweeted it at him and that's how he
found it
oh my god
pancake
i love pancakes
and uh
yeah uh and then he like tweeted at me
offering to like do like a giveaway
which i think is so cool because like i
don't get the chance to do stuff like
that very often right
i'm so confused right now
what does that do
this is where i need to go right
oh is this going to go down now
we're fine we're fine we're fine
no
no no
i seen
i was just surviving i was distracted
okay okay now i have i got the gist i
understand
you um to see it yeah
the timing here is of the essence
i even made it without dodging before
though
there we go okay okay
[Music]
i didn't find this before
so it was trying to be like kiana
you missed something
thank you
i thank
the game for
having me fail
uh anyway back to the topic so it's
gonna be like um ten plushies ten ten
they look so cute and like creepy at the
same time i want one too
yeah
don't let me start all up in the
beginning nah
mr mckee
why
mr mckee are you watching this why
and normally you're so kind with
response let me respawn like close by
what happened
now focus tangent later wait wait wait
wait wait abort mission abort machine
[Music]
this is fun
okay bob planted go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go
i made it no worries
what do we have here this one
okay easy
place the bump here see how smooth it is
now
why is it going down
wasn't supposed to go up
oh i misplaced it
[Music]
okay okay
i was wondering something was off there
now wait for me
[Music]
that's all right with me
it seems like during the battle you
can't fall down um but when you're out
of the battle you can't pull them from
these kind of areas what the hell is
this
oh no
i'm getting smashed in this stream so
often
okay no problem
okay okay okay
calm down calm down luck show
easy
[Music]
means you're drunk
right
i learned it from the right person
[Music]
don't get too no what no
should i have just ignored it yeah
i'm so young
you're so young
it can't mean more well i mean i mean
the drunk okay
oh is the monster not coming back
please
i will not be stopped
by any doors
getting into my way no no battle arena
oh no no no no no i don't want to fight
[Music]
oh my god
oh [\h__\h] yeah
oh
aggressive stomping
it ended oh my god
that's [\h__\h] stressful
okay
no secrets here
funny well duh
i don't need that drawing on the ground
it was pretty obvious that i shouldn't
go there
the door
what
yes you did it anyway well i mean for
like one time okay one time i need i
needed to get to know
how would i know that it would come down
on the map
okay if whatever whatever whatever
i swear i didn't push any buttons i was
drinking water
if anything i was pushing s to go
backwards
all right so
what
what's with this buddy is that a dodo
he looks like
so messed up like where is his hair
where are the feathers
[Music]
oh my god no
that's torture
oh no
see now we know why dodos don't exist
anymore
now we know why they're all dead
they don't
[Music]
is this the usual no the usual room is a
nicer place than this i swear i promise
this is
scary
well good no don't look at them no
queen
come on
i'm sure yeah
i i i treat you guys better than this
don't i eh
come on
doodle mister
he said an actual word or did you just
combine miserable with
museum
because they are definitely doing
miserable and it's definitely like a
museum are you [\h__\h] kidding me
[Music]
i need to save the doodles
you don't even pay us and make us pay
for our board what
this looks kind of comfy you can look up
skirts from the cage no he can not
no
are you a hentai chicken
is that what you are
a little hentai chicken
oh my god
this makes me really sad to look at
these
greats
how can i help them there's something
over there will i get there later i
wonder oh
but or or this is just a
side half
maybe a little secret
ah oh
oh okay i suppose i'm gonna go there now
this game is so disturbing where's the
fun ride well so far
uh i guess because i haven't learned
much about alice just yet
it hasn't been though
i'm feeling all wrong i don't feel much
disturbed yet i mean it's very very
creepy but i think we need to dig deeper
it gets much worse oh god
yeah i thought so
best alice dress this one is your
favorite really
i thought i'll take a look at the other
ones
its cage and the canary goes to sleep
alice act like a snuffed candle sleeps
the sleep of the just like mamar and
babar
after ten they're unconscious
okay
can i go in there
i could i don't know
no i can't
welcome thank you for renewing your
membership thank
i think it was a
legit guess
ah here i am okay
looks like you could go inside
by the way yesterday guys super random
but i was driving in an uber
and i've been on a lot of ubers okay but
that was the first uber
ever
that i was in that a woman was driving
and that made me think like that was the
first time i even realized that i was
never in an uber before
that was a woman before
there's like
no
no female uber drivers have you guys
noticed
think about it have you ever been in an
uber
or even a normal taxi i told you to
cease and desist but my warning was
unfolded nice legs without we we've not
with a with a woman inside
a boiling pot
never thought about it but yeah think
about it
can you recall
but she was so nice she was sweet
she was very polite and she looked
fashionable she was like
mama age but
not not so young she was like she looked
like 40 or something but
very sweet
very sweet woman i'm scared
easy
that almost got me i didn't see that
coming
[Music]
look at that can you imagine
a chicken running like this force on the
treadmill i would never do that to you
guys i would never
have
me
oh my god look at the butt though
no
what they stuck in its butt nah
oh my [\h__\h] god
this is the real horror about this game
looking at those birds
fade worse than death yeah actually kind
of because you're like a machine you
literally turned into a machine
i never thought that would be possible
turning
an alive being into
a [\h__\h] machine
that is so [\h__\h] up
game giving potential ideas
i'm not going to adopt that idea no way
that's it i can feel it
oh my god his legs are going to be so
buff after this
he's going to thank me
finally getting that workout never skip
leg day guys never skip it
i have to say
i have been
uh
where am i going
i have been very good
in doing my exercises my normal
exercises but my daily stretches hmm
do i just jump down again
what am i doing
proud of you thank you i'm proud to
[Applause]
i go all the way back oh it's done
uh
is this
being really alive though
or are they actually just using it as a
vessel
oh my god
what
it stopped
it's not even breathing
my poor baby no
[Music]
no
my baby
ah
i got 564 can i upgrade something
no i'm very close to this one though but
i might want to um save up for the blade
um
what now what now
down here
so yeah i've been i've been uh doing my
stretches either after
even after uh
i don't like this angle can we have the
normal angle back
oh my god
even either after waking up or like
before stream or um yesterday i did it
before sleeping but i've been doing it
like every day my stretches and i have
to say it does feel pretty good ah
no
no side scrollers for you
i feel like generally
um
it's not it's not the side scrolling
that's a problem to me
like i've had
good
experiences before website scroll games
important to keep at it yeah like i've
i've seen some people write to me
that
after doing daily stretches their back
problems really have improved and that
really inspired me oh no
i wasn't ready i wasn't [\h__\h] ready
[Music]
okay
i'm not ready
okay okay
oh my god okay
[Music]
okay
and
okay okay
[Music]
sometimes she's stuck with the pepper
thingy
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
oh my god oh my oh my god oh my god oh
my god oh my god
[Applause]
give me that give me that
oh
you made
[Music]
what do you want what do you what
free the door or else
i will explode
though not free yet
you're challenging your fate
[Music]
what
oh
secret
are we making good progress
because uh
we've been playing for three hours i
think i'm gonna play
uh half an hour more because then i have
two hours until ttrpg
i can eat uh some dinner
i know i never i never got this far or
really why not were you scared when you
were cheeky
like a plan all right
what am i streaming tomorrow is it
minecraft
i'm am i streaming minecraft tomorrow
huh
huh wait what
hey what
what
sorry i didn't pay attention
no need
this is not gonna beat me up
kakamori time tomorrow
oh there it is
dodging at its finest
hard flow i haven't seen one in a while
all right if if minecraft is tomorrow
hmm i wonder well yesterday
i read a bunch of super chats so i i'm
caught up a little bit
i think today i won't be reading them
because i want to take some like a
little break before the ttrpg
if you guys are okay with that i hope
we're not too too far
and away
thank you
maybe after minecraft maybe i can read
some
questions
why is there shaking again
what is happening
only fast moving today oh okay okay okay
that sounds good
that shouldn't be too much
i'll stop you running your blizzard
wait let me drink some water wait
i have to try i have to finish the game
buddy not today but
let's see how far we will get uh
huh
is this the way to go
everything stops
oh
thank you
[Music]
carrying me on its
hands so elegantly nice all right
wait so we got the feet
is that what you're telling me
narrator she will catch him
so now you can kneel in front of me
sucka
you know what to do once you got those
feeds huh you know what to do wait we
didn't we don't have his hat though
it doesn't matter you don't need it
there you go here's your
under on
lower half of your body oh wait where
did we get the hat from
[Music]
like an unsprung spring like an
uncorroded gear
that that has something
fabulous
answer me hatta i'm suffering and
changes here are a cause or they're a
reflection
or the effect
what's going on oh what do you get that
from the law is just just have whispered
away away home to wonder wonder who
who knows how to measure rules
cruel
idiot i should have left you in bits
come the least you can do is help me
discover what's going on
manhattan has never really been that
helpful has he
oh
alex snapping
he's a good jumper though i gotta give
him that pickle pickle pickle
uh
actually you know what i think
might be good to end it here and then
read a couple of super chats for half
half an hour to one hour
that still gives me enough time
what do you think about that guys
this is a good spot i think we just
finished and fixed up the mad hatter
and i think this clock is telling me
it's about time
and there's also safe so i suppose it
just saved and i can leave now without
wearing
tick tock tick
wow i like how it makes a very slight
sound of ticking
like it echoes you probably don't even
hear that because it's so quiet
uh okay
this this kind of text always scares me
but it's i think it's saved yeah it said
that the game auto saves so
well let me see
does it say where i left off
okay all good okay i'll go get it
that's open
okay so i hope you enjoyed that today
i think it's a really really nice game
to play
and especially because no one else has
played it before in her life um i i'm
glad that i can bring some refreshing
new game
onto
this channel yeah thank you and with my
heart rate monitor i was doing fine
today except for that one moment when i
reached 115
115 that was a little bit of a clutch
moment but besides that i think my heart
has been doing fine
and let's see if the super chats can
make me doki doki though
try to make me doki doki mission
heart heart challenge me guys try try
give it a try
so let's go to our office do you still
want to see my my doki doki in my office
as well i'll try to bring it over
[Music]
bottom left corner it fits well over
there
and let me fix the chat
hey
[Music]
where are you chad
thanks for setting up among us with
hilarious oh you're welcome
thanks aye
um i am very proud of it so
yes yes yes
it's
okay so super chat's from phasmophobia
that's what we're gonna read now
[Music]
one second good work today thank you
what kind of music do you guys want to
listen to today
what are you into
[Music]
and thank you guys for coming today by
the way thank you for watching this
stream if you're not staying for the
super chat reading thank you nonetheless
and see you maybe tomorrow
german metal
audio stuff spooky trip what
spooky music
do i have some spoopy music
what about this uh it says calm
halloween that music that i saved before
ah
oh well this is nice
[Music]
who played before
i think that's perfect
i wonder i wonder if my mommy was
watching
mommy were you watching
or bff where are you watching
if not maybe they're watching the
archive whose channel is ctu rpg
streaming on other reservations still
not up it's gonna be on gura channel
hey
[Music]
all right
right
crikey very crinky mate
oh it's already up okay well there you
go then i'll see you guys later if
you're not staying for super chat then i
hope you're coming for ttypg
wait i forgot to put up the thumbnail
for
me oh wait i don't have it here
i need to download it
oh
what's this
i'm gonna look at that later
[Music]
okay i got it
thank you for your patience
[Music]
look at that look at those
eyes
could you say no to those eyes
don't they make you want to hug me
[Music]
cannot
impossible it's literally impossible
oh okay i'm ready to read the pageants
now
why does it keep on scrolling me back up
here we are patrick and donkey
[Music]
oh
do you miss jeffy jesus oh i mean not
necessarily not at the moment um i also
didn't have any time to play
the rest of tales of her eyes yet by the
way
um but i will have to
finish it sometime soon
because of reasons yeah
i have to finish it i want to but my my
i've been so busy with my with other
things and my mind is just
filled with other
topics
i just can't
uh get to it or even think about it but
um
and this week
now there's no
no day off
until the next monday
[Music]
um
maybe next week i can find some time
still haven't finished it either oh
why why busy
gotta find some free time next week yeah
hope you got the chat soon i hope so too
i don't want there to be too much time
in between from last time because i i
want to be immersed in the story you
know
nick and stunkishan
um
regarding the time on sunday apparently
i
i really tried to have everything
correct and i thought it would have been
correct but apparently something is
wrong here
or uh
the yomacon panel in my calendar
was on a different time than what you're
claiming it is on so
maybe
after it was officially announced maybe
the time changed a tiny bit so
uh i will adjust
my
schedule and my cover release according
to yomakon
so i'm planning to just have the release
be immediately after yumacon
and but i will look closer into when
exactly that is it should be roughly the
time that is written here
there shouldn't be
too much of a difference
okay
um
uh yeah i i had my
time zone
uh converter thingy open and i put it on
the exact date so that it would consider
uh the the the daylight saving time and
all that and it did i saw it i saw it
changing from seven hours difference to
japan to eight hours difference to japan
so i thought it was all correct yeah i'm
confused
green wilder
thank you for the rainbow
oh
the other day you were talking about
making a daily habit of stretching and i
think that's awesome oh yeah
thank you i've actually been trying to
do that myself with mixed results for
most of this year
so i know very well how hard it is to
build such habits yeah yeah yeah
for that reason i want to share some
words of wisdom anything worth doing is
worth doing badly
oh
when you have those days when you know
you should stretch but you can't talk
yourself into doing the full 15 minute
routine do one minute instead oh
well honestly
there is no excuse
to not do a 15 [\h__\h] minute routine
it's so short
so so far it's been fine like i i've
been doing those routines and by the end
of it i'm always like is it already over
and i actually stay seated and do some
more stretchings that were not in the
video with my arms and my shoulders i i
rotate them and stuff as well
and to add a little bit to it because
it's always like oh really is that it
but i always feel very accomplished
after doing it i'm always very happy
that i did it and
basically mentally pet myself on the
back
yeah
uh it's not much but it's still
infinitely better than zero yeah small
steps like that can make building good
habits a lot more manageable since i
still have plenty of characters left
here's a little bonus
this just occurred to me you can use an
angle in minecraft to rename cooked
chicken to vegan chicken if it only cost
one level for a full stack of 64. ah
i don't have to do it one by one huh
yeah yeah yeah
never again will anyone question whether
or not it's vegan glory to careful viva
la chiana we are not a cult i said
volcanic yolk thank you i love you too
thank you so much
so you've also been trying to make a
daily habit of stretching
have you been following through with it
recently i hope you have
let's do it together
[Music]
thank you chad thank you
would you share the video with us boss
oh it's just one of those uh when you
when you go on youtube and type in
a
daily stretching routine
uh
wait if you want i can give to you
daily stretch
routine
why did i type it in in caps lock
okay
[Music]
sorry
i might switch to a different one at
some point though if i find the better
one this is just a
full body daily stretch it's very
focused on stretching the legs i might
want to look for one that's a bit more
focused on the upper body
um but my
my legs definitely need stretching too
because when i've been doing that
routine
i can barely keep my legs straight in
the positions that she shows
there is this one specific pose that is
absolutely impossible for me
wait i want to tell you which one
[Music]
no don't talk shush
and
let me show you
ah at 11
11 minutes and like nine seconds
that looks so easy
but
it's so difficult
really
and she stays in that position for quite
some time
but yeah i i used to be able to do stuff
like that more easily but i haven't been
stretching my body for years
but if you actually continue stretching
your body for
like every day for a while then
you should be able to do stuff like that
really looks not that bad it is pretty
bad yeah it's pretty hard
are you doing stretches or yoga
stretches stretches
but it's been it's been fun it's been
relaxing and every time i do it my cats
are like swarming around me
when she starts she's like standing on
the mat straight
and uh there's like neck rolls and all
that
and when i when i start and stand on
that smoothie always just
rubs herself on my legs and says hello
like meow meow
she's so cute
she's like why are you standing in the
middle of the room mama what are you
doing what are you up to
and then yesterday when i was laying on
the ground doing my leg stretches
uh chunkis
threw herself down right next to me and
was like pet my belly and i multitasked
i was stretching my legs while patting
her belly
[Music]
very wholesome
it's been relaxing so i actually like it
i i'm currently pretty mo surprisingly
motivated to do these stretches daily
yeah
um
[Music]
stretch
and if i continue this for a long time
i might
end up like
this actually i kind of want it the
other way around i want to stretch to
from top to bottom
now i look so slim
i don't want to be oh no no what no no
no
long long you know how long cat looks
like i want to be like that when someone
picks me up i want my body to go like
[Laughter]
[Music]
long
i've seen fan art like that though uh
didn't mamaloni also draw something like
that
[Music]
i've seen it before
someone picked me up and i was like
really small
small cat kiana
in my cat form
in my half cat for him
yeah yeah yeah with cali carrying me it
looked so cute
that's what i aspire to be long cat
potato oh wait i actually didn't give
you a kiss green wilbon
thank you thank you so much and good
luck to you
you can do it fine
we'll do it together we'll be super
stretchy like like chewing them
by the end of the year
yeah there's not much left to the year
but we can do it
yeah
goliath ties duncan
and del star duncan for the pinky
you playing scary games is a better
reward to employees than what other
bosses do like pizza parties thanks
tantjo p.s may i leave the usual room
christmas is right around the corner
uh
no christmas is so far away
what are you talking about
you can't fool me i mean i was in the
supermarket yesterday and i already saw
there being a
christmas decoration sold
a lot of it
apparently it's already time for it
i mean
i'm still i'm in i'm in halloween mood
can they not wait until halloween is
over
it's like no one is in christmas mood
right now who's gonna buy christmas
decoration now
them
get them while they're cheap eh
are they gonna be more expensive i doubt
it kind of
uh
delsa ducation rick spa duncan
[Music]
by the way yesterday regarding the
phasmophobia because we were doing so
bad oh my god um
my bff the one who recommended alice
is actually also very experienced in
phasmophobia she has like
over 140 hours
i mean that's i guess average but
compared to hour hours i guess it's uh
wait was it 140 hours or 140 levels
wait a second
in any case she's very very experienced
in it
it says 134 hours i don't know what her
level is but
is that
and but yeah yeah so she was like
piana i gotta teach you how to play this
game
tell me when you want to do it
[Music]
that is very sweet but
i don't really plan on playing it again
anytime soon
that's like two art damp i guess so i
guess it is a lot wait
i've been so
decent sensitized
senses and
is that a word
yeah fubuki also has a lot of experience
i know i know but i'm not really even
interested in fastball anymore
it was it was fun in the beginning but
now uh
it is a word okay
okay okay
and
thank you now this one i will read this
one i will read no kenji dankeshan spc
kenneth
emberstone thank you i love how tonight
basically devolved into kelly taunting
the ghost in english and you taunting
the ghosts in german
how could anything go wrong yeah
i tried but like i even tested um the
voice recognition before
uh we started streaming and it worked
like at least in the options
but i don't think the ghost ever reacted
to me i don't know if it really worked
oh well
extreme gun the game of dankeshan reena
lucian hailstone
thank you
yeah you're awesome funny and adorable
your hard work is inspiring and your
kindness is contagious i look forward to
more awesome adventures thank you so
much very sweet of you
moon dog
cow slip poetry duncan
the among us collab with stella you
deserve a special super job for
organizing the event thank you for all
your hard work even the stuff we don't
see on screen smart move doing the
practice round before big chicken brain
move
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah that was definitely
necessary
i'm glad
everything worked out fine yeah
were you actually talking in the game i
didn't hear the echo with you that i did
before
really
were you watching from a different point
of view well the real question is why
you were watching from a different point
of view huh
anyway thank you counselor poetry
nominee and mr smithington duncan
sorry if it's inappropriate it was
[Music]
what was what's inappropriate
and black friction thank you for the red
super chat always kiara worship the
champion brothers
you didn't even have to add that that
was exact exactly what i was thinking of
when i read that ooga booga
caveman chimp king
i like how you guys embrace your chicken
selves it's beautiful you gotta love
yourself otherwise you can't love anyone
else that is the first step to loving
takanashikiana
loving me
[Music]
[Laughter]
why
influx is a difficult question
um
it's just the way we do things
sorry to disappoint you
we are who we are i am this this what
you're looking at that's what i am this
is me irl i don't know why you're even
doubting it
what the hell
i know are you
your eyes are not
misleading you this is me this is real
i'm just a freaking supermodel
it is what it is
black rich and woman
lawyer cosmics duncanshire
anthony webb oh wait robin hood was a
pinky you're my first and only aussie
love you thank you thank you
i love you too that is so sweet
i will i will see that
as a eternal promise to follow me
forever and ever
all right
thank you for your support and your love
anthony webb thank you for the red super
chat
hello kiara you always make my day
better i will always be one of your
chickens thank you so wholesome
so see my bpm while reading that was
very nice
oh oh nice now it's high oh look stop so
i'll stop hey hey stop shh
you make my heart go doki dokie
go down chill
shush calm down
calm down
thank you anthony
i love you too
looking for a lawyer
all the brits
ah no problem don't worry about it it's
okay it's okay to ask questions no
problem
easy feel dangerous and they call me owl
mr clear thank you and the arbiter free
o2
i'm hungry
easy fail thank you
more proof of my british fans
thank you
check it out
[Music]
uh super tony duncan
sorry for disturbing super chat last
time i didn't think it would turn out
that way i was in serious pain and high
on pain strong killer pain strong
painkiller misunderstood that you would
remember me because i'm mostly in jrpg
and super chat reading
in early days and you often read my
normal comment
and the community getting larger i can't
even reach out properly it's hard to
communicate properly i still remember
that i am sick and barely move and i
watch your fire emblem
uh
three houses stream for seven hours
i'm not native english speaking so i
have a hard time making speech so
something comes out wrong sometimes
don't worry about it i understood
i understood i understood perfectly
thank you
well yeah uh
yeah no problem about the other super
chat um
thank you for still watching my streams
after all this long time thank you soon
opportunity doctrine the magic
extinction oh wait wait it continues
sang thank you it was actually a rainbow
thank you
a beautiful rainbow
yeah i'm not a native english speaker
either
non-native english speakers very welcome
in my chat
[Music]
as long as you don't bombard me with
comments that are not in my language
that i understand
as long as it's
as long as you try to communicate in
english
brain trash tankishan
thank you i'm i'm glad i could help you
karaoke
slowpoke is back oh wait that's actually
already alice super chats
that's already alice super chattos
all right then i'm reading the those now
let's try to finish them
i'm really hungry though
maybe i shouldn't
now it's two hours until until ttrpg
maybe i'll end it here members only
did i not read those
what
somebody said phasmophobia and from
today so i believed it
[Music]
ah
oh what the hell why did i mix together
that's so weird
[Laughter]
okay
well i'll leave it at that then
if i can't finish them today anyway
then i'll go
grab some food yeah
okay okay
[Music]
good stretch good yawn
so i hope you enjoyed today's stream
everyone i'll see you either at the
ttrpg or tomorrow at the minecraft
stream with cali hope you hope you're
gonna have a nice evening you sure you
guys should uh grab some food as well
and then
[Music]
and look forward to the next time we
play this game because then we're gonna
have the giveaway
yeah oh wait wait oh wait oh wait wait
puzzle piece puzzle piece puzzle please
puzzle piece wait wait wait wait for
everyone who was a good good
chicken
and stayed until the end i have a puzzle
piece
and because we saw
a dirty dirty rat
today in the game i'll give you this one
should it be like on the black
background or what do we do
can you cut this out
i guess not
i'll give you
i'll give you like a wait i i can give
you like a um
[Music]
i can make this probably a little bit
easier
[Music]
snip
okay
[Music]
there we go
okay i'll go okay here
take it
this is a puzzle piece from the usual
room no just kidding the usual will
always be missing
always be missing one puzzle piece i
will never give you that one
[Laughter]
is that fauna
could that be fauna actually i think
that that looks like a corner piece
doesn't it guys did i give you a really
really important
corner piece
you always got to start a puzzle of a
corner piece right
oh my god perfect
perfect
[Laughter]
puzzle
so
if we would start the puzzle yeah we
would put bae here
right in the corner exactly where casper
is
coincidence i think not
oh wait actually that makes you think
wasn't now bae is in my other office
right i placed bae in the in the not
halloween office before
actually
doesn't tell the style looks super cute
because last year um me and
gouda
drew the art together for the puzzle
but this year
can you guess who drew it this year just
by looking at that and maybe the other
puzzle piece you might already have
[Music]
could it be could it be the big big beak
girl
uh
her eye is so cute the whole picture
looks so cute
you guys gotta collect all the puzzle
pieces to look at the big picture
big picture
so
[Music]
it will become a really really adorable
piece of art
at the end of halloween
yeah so please enjoy collecting them and
with that i say auf wiedersehen see you
later
good our channel
bye bye
trick or treat
bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
wow
me
oh
[Music]
no
baby
okay so quiet
bye bye
bye bye bye
bye
[Music]