[Music]
A
Yo
[
Music] [Music]
[Applause]
Hey
[Music]
T
A
[Music]
[Applause]
[  [Music]
What's wrong with me if you love me
? I can't hear you say it hurts. I
love your replies. I love
clothes. I'm an ordinary affair twin. It's
still too early to open up and go out.
I'm sorry I was born so cute I'm
sorry I messed up I'm sorry you're so cute
I'm sorry I'm so cute I'm sorry I
tried so hard I'm sorry I'm a little big I
'm sorry I'm so feminine I'm pissed off
[Music]
Please just take care of yourself,
please don't interfere with me. I say I'll call you,
but I can't hear you.  I'm going to
comb my bangs and
go out with my favorite rucksack.I'm a light woman.I'm kidding, my hair is
too heavy.I'm
sorry for being so cute.I'm sorry for getting so angry.I'm sorry for letting it out.I'm so
conscious of it.I'm sorry
for being cute.I'm sorry for trying to improve myself.  I'm
sorry for turning you into Toriko in Purico.I'm sorry for making you look like Toriko.I'm sorry for making you look like Toriko.I'm sorry for making you look like Toriko.  I do
n't want to lose, I'm not afraid of you. I
want to be my ally. I want to cherish you the most.
I don't want to put up with you unnecessarily. That's
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm so cute. I'm sorry I was born. I'm
sorry I missed you in the morning.  I'm sorry for enjoying life, you're so
cute. I'm sorry for being too cute. I'm sorry for being
too expensive for girls. It's annoying.
[Music]
Za
[Applause]
Ah
[Music]
Present
[Music] I
wonder if there are good or sad things that you want to forget. Even though I don't know the movie, the reason I lose my tears is
because it's not dramatic enough. Do
n't hold on to such things.
Thoughts.  If you're too greedy, your love will
become someone else's property,
right? You can't do it all, but
why, why, why, why?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  I
can't even go so far as to dig up feelings without a human body,
but I won't see any tricks.Why,
oh, it's so hard.My cut is so boring, and
since I left, I feel like I'm giving it a reprieve.Feel
Cal's eyes are tearing up.  Maybe
because of the music in my head, all you say is
that the stars I can't hear are nonsense. Please
help me forget, but why are you
trying to hide everything? You just won't disappear.
Tokyo is here, but it's all vague.
All
I
have to do is countdown to Hololive 2023. It's finally here.
Just a few more things like that happened
. In 2023, I'm going to do my best and have fun until the end. It's
not a joke, Tokyo.  Champion love, I ca
n't help it even if the time has come, I can't do it,
just confirm it with me, Yello, seriously,
Tokyo Cinela I can't help it, even if the time has come
[Music]
Chico
[Music] I'm so
weak that I can't wake up from love, I'm so weak that I can't
wake up from love.
I sit down with my other hand and the back of my throat is throbbing.
Show me how to get rid of
that throbbing feeling. Bring back my love and possess me. Keep consuming me until I'm addicted.
[Music]  Do
n't shut up about the feeling of being late for the coming time
[Music]
Keokekekekekekero Kero Oni guys,
always tell me the punching match You won't be able to
do anything in the end It won't end, I
won't forget you, don't change it, it won't change
My
heart is prickling deep inside, so please drag me out.It
feels good, but it smells so good, but I'm dying.  The
town where you lost your unforgettable death is
full of zombies You're in love with me
Pull the rope and
let's go Pepe Pepe Pero Pepe Pe Pero Pepe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pero Pepe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe Pe basis basis.
[Music]
Mota
[Music] The
flower with an unknown name that you gave me
Traveling alone to Unaka was supposed to be enough, but
if I held your hand, I'd
never
come back to this city where I've never known loneliness.  You can't do it, can you
?
Let me hear you sing a song where shadows are created by the light that you extended your hand to.Continue this story.I
took you
to the stars (music), towering above the sky where no one's hands or voices can reach.
I want you to laugh  The
invisible hole I've been trying to fill up
until now has been filled, but if I were to
dig that hole and fill this hole with you,
it would be a wonderful thing.I'd say it
louder than I've ever heard it before, and I'd finally be
able to convey it to you.  It's just the right time to
connect the shame and shame of this world.
[Music] I'll
travel alone through the air, waving the lights on the windows.
But I want to choose a sky full of lofty hearts.
safety
Now, if I were to hold someone else's hand, I'd never be able to return to this town where I don't even know the ghost.I'm going to
wear light and shadow as much as I want, and I'll sing to you.Continuation
of this story.  I'll take you to a star I've never tried before
[Music] I'll
unite the world's 8 and the bees
[Music]
[Applause]
Ah
[Music]
The clock will soon be 6 o'clock and it's already there  shadow  I want to
step on it and disappear into the night On the way
home,
no matter how hard I try to find it, I can't help but shine at you from a billion years away.You're
loved by everyone,
no, I've always
been alone.Once I get used to being together with you.  As the stars fall, it's
like a momentary wish, and I'm trembling with my signal.If we
get together, we'll fly up to the sky and sting my finger.No matter
how dazzling I am, there's nothing left to do.
[Music]  The
clock is almost 8 o'clock.The night sky is full of stars.There
may not be any more in the distance.The
moon is so beautiful that it makes me want to cry.Someday we'll have to say
goodbye, so
if I can sit down with you, it'll be water.  Let's
get together with Rhythm-kun, talking
to myself as I get cold. If my wish reaches someone, I wonder if I'll be able to
change. I'm like this in the summer when I'm like this [
Music] [Applause
]
[Music]
[Applause]
too
We're
fragile, so we'll meet again and again
through the clouds.If we
can gather together and trust each other, we'll spread out the night and go to painting.Even
if the moon isn't there to illuminate the darkness, there's still a lot of
constellations.  I want to be like that. I'm so
dazzled by you,
[Music] too. [Music]
[Music] I've
added a dream to the pack, and I feel like it's the last one.
Naoto felt like it was the last time
[Music] It was
just a dream, but on the promised night, he
made a wish in the breeze, and in the morning
[Music] A
boy from a distant star made a promise in his arms.  The decorations are
still on, and like a curtain,
my future fades into haze and
disappears.I felt like it would be my last.If I
reweave my dreams, I feel like they'll be my last.Saborian
face  Before the Nosa Promise
[Music]
On the night of Sakasu, still in
the middle of the earth, it accelerates to that place,
further up the Sharia field
[Music] [
Music]
To
[Music]
Fuki
Fume
Masumina
w
[Music]
It's okay
[  Music]
[Music]
S
E
[Music]
[
Music] [Music]
Ku
[Music]
Effort Mirai Al Poster Effort Mirai Al Poster
Effort Mirai Al Poster Power Mirai A Poster
Landry
From  I
want to be happy, I want to live happily, I
want to hold it in my hands, I'm happy in your heart
[Music]
Someday, I want to be happy I want to live happily  It's so nice and
melty, I
don't remember,
Potter is coming off, I'm
hugging a life that makes me feel like I'm going to vomit, I want that umbrella when the rain is falling, I
want that, I want this, I want everything, I want to
be as happy as ever.  I was having
so much fun living, I
want to mess everything up, I want to get rid of everything. Come on out of your heart. It's
heaven that only welcomes good people.
[Music]
Hello,
Sleigh. [Music] Happira, Hello, Lyra-Rai is amazing.
Poster
[Applause]
[Music]
me
[Music] I
knew it was something I shouldn't have known, but everything that slipped through my hands...  The
words I was sure of seemed to be taking shape and I could
say them.I
wrote "yes" and I'm sure that's all it took.
[Music] I'm sure that's
all I had to do.  It's too big and I'm
going to be naked without any explanation. I
just have
to decide.
Once it's all over, I'll break down just like the room and forget about it.
Look at the way I put it on.  I
want to understand you and 2, but there are no strange lies. I want to
understand
you and 2.  It's so sweet, I
don't know how you and I are together, but it's strange that things are so bad right now.
Even if it's a lie, you and I are
here. [Music] Bumi [Music] The sun is in my frozen heart, and I'm with you.
50,000 yen for that position. I'm sorry for
making your assumptions so hard. I
tried to laugh,
but I realized how cruel the coldness of positivity was to the point of
desperation. I'm sure I want to give it to you.
Things are even colder and hotter.  It's
not a pretty thing, but it's not a pretty thing.It's
more than anything.It's something that warms you deep inside.I
have an ideal, but no matter where I look in my heart, I just
can't find it.I want to convey it to you.I can't convey it.That
inadequacy
is binding me now.
Even though I wanted to turn this cowardly one-on-one sword
into the snowy one of my childhood, the more I became absorbed in it, the more I
lost my sense of form, but the
words I chose were the feelings entrusted to them  I
can't let go of your heart.Until you receive more love than I love you.
[Music]
Wait just a little longer.
Even if I just stand next to you in thin clothes, I'm sweating unnecessarily.  Because  I'm
lukewarm and it hurts you, right? The
hotter my palms are, the colder my heart is. Do
n't say such cruel things, even if you're joking. I do
n't have to say anything else, but even if I put my whole humanity on the line, I
want to be saved. I want to be saved.
This equal is
now being gently peeled away. I
want kindness rather than pride.And the only way
to receive it is not to stand tall like a numination,
but just to meet you in person.
[Music]
[Applause]
With the words I wanted, I took them out of my heart,
added too much, and got pulled back. I want to talk about those failed plans over and over again. I
want to
find the best meat someday.  Even if I give you a present,
as time passes, it will just
spill out of my memory, melt away, and disappear.I
think of it as if it were subtitles added to our story.When I look at you in
timeless moments,  looking for something to cheer up  I
want to keep going
Even if the snow melts, I'll still be
there
[Music] Even if the snow melts, I'll still be thinking about things I don't want words or anything I'm feeling sad  [
Applause]
[Music] I
want to be separated from you, right? I
want you to be sweet and young, right? I want you to look sweet and young, right? My
eyes are entwined with yours as I walk alone,
waiting for you.  It
's not like I'm in love with an adult now, but only my fragile heart is still in its blue state. [Music] You know the trouble. You want me to stimulate you. Someday, I'll charm you too.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I want to
connect with you, not just with kind words, but with my heart. I
longed for you to put on makeup, but in front of you, where I can see my dreams, there's
another sound.
[Music] It's
better not to be like that.  In love with an adult
Instead of looking at me, I'm left with only a feeling of worthlessness.
Find me. I want to connect with you, not just with words, but with my heart. I
can't hide it with ordinary make-up. I
've admired you, but I'm dreaming. I'm almost
chasing after Mako.
[Music]
Le
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah,
if the moment ended outside, the sky would be fine,
but I couldn't move on. The wind was too strong, and I wanted to dive into the target. I wanted to sit there forever, even though it would be warm if
only my selfishness were gone.  That's what I
thought.When I went out reluctantly, Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh
[Music] The moment it started, it was over. Even though the weather was nice, I couldn't proceed. It was so complete that it felt like it was disappearing. The middle was over. The enemy was good, but I couldn't proceed. The wind was so strong. It was so bad that I couldn't proceed.
Ah, the invincible smile of Molasmeria. I found out the
secret. She's mysterious and even out of place.
She's a perfect liar. You're a genius,
idol. What did you eat
today? If you like going out,
where are you going? I haven't eaten anything. Keep that a secret.  When
someone asks me what it is, I feel like I'm just relaxing, but with Sansa, the secrets I can't see are the secrets, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't understand anything. Lies, books,
words that I don't understand make me fall once again. No
one makes me fall in love again. You're robbed of money. You're the
ultimate
person. You're the one who never shows up.
With that smile, you've changed.  I love you so much that everyone treats him as a child.
Even if those eyes and words are lies, it's a complete love. Yes, that child is special. We are flowers. We are a bonus. We
are a complement to the stars. Everything is
because of that child.  There is no Kuine  I
can't forgive you because you're not perfect. I can't forgive myself. You're
better than anyone else. I can't accept that you're better than anyone. No one
can believe in you. I can't find a weak point that makes you truly the strongest and invincible.
Even the boss is dying.
Show me that you're weak, don't show what you don't want to know,
that's what true love is for you.Even
if you smile, you'll win.The only secret you can hide is a
career built on lies that say you love me.  The
sweat that flows in my own way is beautiful.The evil that
hides the ruby ​​takes away this dazzling dance.I am Maria.That's
right, I can't lie.I've never been
loved by anyone or loved anyone in my life.
Someday, this lie will become true.Someday, I'm sure I'll
get it all.I
want to love everyone properly, even though I'm
making a tight love.Even today, I'm making a lie.I
hope someday these words won't become true.Even so, I
'm still only with you.  I went without saying anything, but finally
I see, this is definitely not okay, love
[Music]
Oh, can you hear me? I'm
leaving the stage and coming to the restaurant. Oh, wait
a minute. How are you feeling right now? So, senpai, I'll change my clothes, so please wait a moment.
I don't know how I feel right now.I can't
speak Japanese.He's a bad kid.He's the bad kid.He's the one who's going to punish him.Please
do it.I'm half
devil and half angel.And this
is the manager.
[Music]
Let's go, let's change and look at the next dressing room.
Hello, I'm the wind. Why is this dressing room the only one? It's my
turn to smell the air flying in the wind in such a storm.
It's not me who hasn't done it.  Until then,
my seniors have apparently been caught.
My dressing room is full of alcoholic drinks. I
'm a seagull who couldn't drink Ranney's alcohol. Even though it's sloppy, it
's finished.  The
soup stock from the ramen salt bag is effective for
Nehime.Don't make it Nehime.It's not enough to hide it.There's not enough stimulation.Yeah
, there's not enough clouds.Let's
go.The customers are still there.It smells like alcohol and it's boring
.  Let's go to the next room. It
smells delicious. It's
delicious. It's delicious. Why are you so
delicious? I'm cooking more and more. I
'm eating more and more of my friends, but the feeling of the dream is still good.
If it's cute, that's fine.This one
has Indonesia in it.This one has Indonesia in it.It might be a
business opportunity.Enjoy the various flavors.You'll
feel like you're in a good mood.Okay, let's
go to the next room and let's do an
assault interview.  Is this
the interview? Is it the
interview? Well, I don't have to force myself to blurt it out
. They
listened to Emel and the others' songs. I'm
really looking forward to having fun after this.
What do you think? What do you think? What do you think? I don't like it.
What do you think? It's close to the microphone, so why do you do it?
What do you think? Let them talk. So Baton, what's
next?  We're going to be interviewing you. It
's a good evening Rakuyat interview. It
's almost the end of 2023. It's
true. It's almost the end of the year.
How much time difference is there between Indonesia and Indonesia?  The
new year will be celebrated in two hours or two.
That's how I feel about a good year.
How much time is left until the countdown? It's too
late. I have to go to the next one. Well then, the next
interviewer is Wolf Mio. I'll do my best.
Next time, here's the dressing room.  Look, from here on out,
we Holo Graffiti will take over, and
we'll take it back and say what we did. Do
n't wobble, it's New Year's Eve. If you don't want to spend New Year's Eve in a space like this, then stop.
Look, I'm going to use the browser Mac, and the grass won't grow. Wow, it's only my turn. It seems like there was
some trouble, like a big miss. Good evening, Sui-chan, the pinch hitter, Sui-chan. The mouse boy's jaw has come off. I'm sure he'll do whatever he wants.
Just go for it.
If you're Sui-chan looking at me there, why don't you
do it with the power of your heart instead of inside? Come on, I
can't help but leave you in the river of nemi. Then I'll
go to the next dressing room.  Good
evening Nyo Nyo Nyo, that guy's body is completely
empty due to overdosing on magic. You're
also gloomy.
Nebo Momo is too fast for this kid. It
's better to call him a kid who is a kid. Oh, that's
dangerous.
[Music]
Uh, the
next dressing room is boring. I'm sure my
uncle and daddy are sleeping, but I
woke up even though I was a baby.
Shall we go to bed too?Dad, who is my father?There's
nothing we
can do about sleeping in a blanket.Dad, I'll put you to sleep.Can I come with you?
Mom, who is that man?I'm not right.I'm
tired of the baby's acting.  Okay,
mom is going to change the microphone. The next dressing room
is here. Good evening.
Now, my senior is bending too far and I can't
stop. I can't stop. I'm going
to do an interview with the microphone for now.  I
can't interview you in this situation, chocolate.
Please help the teacher, help Ejari-chan. I'm sorry for
not being cute. I'm sorry for not being cute because it's always dark. I'm sorry for not being cute because I'm a
shark. I'm an
alien and my head is still like this. The
stage is yet to come.  Please stop it,
even though it's a stranger, Pecola-senpai, don't be impressed. I'm sorry, you're so cute, you self-conscious person.
Everyone here is cute.
Well, it's over in just a few tens of seconds. Well, it's been a
long time, but it was short. Next year too,
more and
more, together with everyone, come on, everyone, on the rooftop [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Gather together
10987654321
[Applause]
[Music]
Be
feeling
[Music]
Open your heart now
Now
[Music]
Reverberate in front of you
[Music]  When I
hear a voice or hear a sound, I hear the sound of gold,
and my thoughts are always haunting me. Because you're next to me, I don't get lost.  The
rottenness that melts in the sweetness of the sky,
and the open eyes of the sky, lend me your eyes, and the wound
hurts, ding-dong ding-dong. I
don't mind the darkness biting, I don't care.
I'm tired of mine
[Music]
Tari
Papapapapapapapapapa Nenenenenenepa
[Music] Nene [
Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
Te
areehave
[Music]
Mo
[  [Music]
know
[Music]
[Applause]
if
[Music]
Bi
Hey,
shut up! I can't say those strong words
. I want you to be quiet just a little. We should have seen the world right now.
Until the day I can see it, I'll
make clothes all over your town.
[Music] Until
that day, I'll
make my own clothes.  The
stars and sun disappear, my fingertips
sway and stop, and the
clouds that step into the hands of the clock begin to melt. I
know that smile.
[Music]
Yo, I want to show you the fun. I do
n't want to go back. I want to go back. I want to go back. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I want you to
reset your life.
[Music] [
Music]
Because it's medicine
[Music]
Kindness
[Applause]
[Music]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,\hthere is no\hway [Music] it's wonderful like this, once I grab it, I won't let it go,
with a chance I'll shine and my absolute enemy will be regular Takatake
Oh, I've become your god, but Aneki-
chan, you're perfect. I've leaked a lot today.
It's amazing how confident you are. I
'm the closest to you in the world. I
love you so much. In other words, you can love me. Of course things will work out. Smile and
warm.  The cat is so cute, you're here too.
It's great, it's great, it's great. It's great, it's
great, it's so,
so stay by my side. The weather is fine.  It
's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I'll be your cat.
[Music] We'll
save up, we'll shine. We'll
call each other out, and we'll find out without meeting each other. We'll
find out. The
start is degrees
[Music]  It's
you, I'm the one who fills the darkness, and I'm
shining brightly. Take my regrets with you, and
Kazemu is about to fly away.  It's the
end of the light. It's a
wonderful start to jump in with you.
From here on, we're going to power fly
Parepare Le
[Music]
[Applause]
Ah
[Music]
Happy New Year. We need to think about it soon. Everyone's a
little noisy, so first we'll have a strategy meeting.  Okay, it's
not like a love story that starts now, it's a no-holds-barred day, and today
is the real deal.What's important is that it's only a month from now, and I'm so
excited that I've become an adult.  I
want to do both thoughts, sweet
sweet sweet sweet sweet sweet, sweet, sweet sweet,
lovers, and I chose you who loved you.  I
want to reward my love with chocolate.
[Music]
[Applause] I've
already decided that it's today.
But how did I know?
It's true that everyone is tempted, but
if you show me that, it won't work. I
want to enjoy today's meltdown,
but I don't think it's the cute one I wanted. It's so
sweet and sweet.  I love sweet, sweet, sweet, I
love it, I love it, I love it. That's what you gave me. A
surprise surprise, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I
didn't do that.
I'm
sorry, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.  Sweet,
sweet, sweet, sweet, like, like, like, I choose you.
You're the cutest sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.
Let's have the biggest show of the year.
Chochohahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha  I
want to reward my love with chocolate. I want to
reward me from today.  The
fire is lit by the chandelier, the neo-
light spotlight bathes me
in the theater [
music], the
steps
I take to dance, my heart is
worried about the action, and for
a moment,
aaah, my
aaaaaaa, I completely challenge myself.
[Music] I
want to make you the best of all.
[Music]
Please let me hear your voice more than ever.
[Music] The
Narucho Rebellion will
swallow you up too. I'll let it swallow me up, too.  I
can't be lonely again, you
're my ass, you're my ass, and I
'm the leader, and in this
sick world, I'm the leader, and now I'm so heavy that I'm about to cry.
In my thoughts
[Music]
Me
Like Umu
[Music]
Ship
Have you all made it? Hey,
just a little bit. Yes, I think everyone is tired.
Yes, there's one more song left. Yes, this is the last one.  The
song is ``Ma Light'' by everyone at Matic Project
Dance, dance, people should have been born to get hot
[Music] If the
still small homes that are burning small now
become one, a miracle will be born This world
will always have a heart that never gives up  Don't
give me any answers, I'll give you clues to find the way, so let's
keep going till the end, let's dance, dance, we were born to get hot. Dance, dance, I'm sure that's
the case, so dream,
dance,
bye, my best
today.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  ] The
sun will spread out someday The
power to persevere The power to
persevere In this world that is calling for miracles When the hearts that want to shine come together I come up with
something new and start running Even
though I can't see where my feet are, I stretch out my hands like gold and dance.
Dance, the thing I've always dreamed of is twinkling
[Music]
Dance the light, dance, I'm sure it'll come true someday.
Dance, I'll [ __ ] on my unfulfilled legs
[Music]
No
[Applause]
[Music] I'll be
guided by the voice in my heart.  The path has opened again for me Be strong until the end, go
back, dance, people were born to become passionate,
dance, dance, I'm sure it will
[Music]
Let's be
happy
[Applause]
[Music]
Niya
[Applause]
[Music] A
[Music] [
Applause
] A [Music] I
[Music]
H
T
[Music]
Ah
[Applause]
[Music]
T
Oni Oni Koko [
Music]
Mao
[Applause]
You stabbed me in the chest, but I couldn't stand still. I was
scared in the darkness. I was scared, but you gave me a shelter.  teeth
Everyone's Hikari
Su This is my
[Music]
Hikari Holo Plus
Live was the best Post your impressions on Holo Plus Happy New Year
Holo
Plus Advertising Team Leader No Sakino Official app Holo
Plus is holding a campaign linked to the countdown live
Just give it a try
Chance to win a present
Check out Holo Plus for more details Thank you for your continued support of Holo Plus in 2024
Otsu Holo
[Music]
Plus I
listen to it and it's not pretty.I don't like it even if it's not pretty.
No, I don't hate you. I don't
care. I don't care if you're skillful, I don't care, I don't care. I don't care if you step on any rain or puddles. I don't care if you laugh at me. I don't care if it's overflowing. That's why I felt like facing forward without fear.
[Music]
Te
H
[Music] I
'm Shirabuki, the number one boss in your heart with a fluffy tail. Hello, friends. I'll
bring you some breaking news on January 5, 2024.  It
has been decided that we will be broadcasting a 3D collaboration with Patra-chan.
Yay, it will be held on Shiraga Channel on January 5th,
so please look forward to it! A final
word from Patra-chan Good evening, this
is Patra. I went to Hololive Studio on January 5th.
Thank you everyone for your support.