[Music]
sorry
ah
okay
uh made myself louder only on OBS
because I already am distorted over here
I bought a cloud lifter though so so
hoping that it will sound better not not
so
distorted also let me adjust the shirt a
little bit
uh call LIF arrives I think
[Music]
tomorrow oh it's too
low aha okay the bad
I have them separate now but somehow
because it's so long like you know when
I when I move it to adjust it
somewhere uh it it finds the Middle
Point whatever I try to adjust it tries
to find the middle point and that's like
somewhere in the middle of the but bat
so if I want to adjust it to
something I I can't adjust here attach
attach
wait you can't even see
me uh yeah I I would have to like attach
the hand to my BBA or like no then it
would then the middle point of the bat
would be attached to my shoulder and
it's so wobbly but I guess that works
cuz I'm not even showing you the whole
thing but in reality this is what's
happening uh okay uh that's where we
fine you don't see that much of me I'll
make myself a bit bigger oh but oh so
much of the bat wait
[Laughter]
small it's a science it's a whole
science H by the way Kik ke Kik
[Music]
Keo chat so we have last latency today
that should be great or or more more
latency no less latency right that's
called less latency
probably and I made some
tea hoping that today my throat will not
be so
H but the f is I just filled it
in I'm filling it in telling it that
you're supposed to be a te
filling the fmac you're you're a tea
you're a
tea yes hope that migraine's better I
don't know I already had some pain today
I already felt some pain in my temple
and like behind my ear like above kind
of diagonally above my ear but all on
the left
side I think the massage generally maybe
made it better but then I had pretty
strong pain the day after again I didn't
take a pain killer yet but if I need to
I have some
still
uh you are a tea you are a tea what kind
of tea uh just fro tea so some herbal
[Music]
tea
yeah maybe you should still see a doctor
yeah I made an appointment not really
necessarily for the migraine
but uh just for starting all over
again but
because I'm sick of
doctors especially older male doctors
I'm sorry but like so many of these
doctors are older males and they don't
take me seriously they're like oh this
girl looks young she should be
healthy uh so she is healthy I declare
she is healthy she doesn't have any
serious issues so I'm kind of sick of
that cuz that's especially with doctors
which are
free so even though I love our free
healthcare in Austria I'm going to go to
a private doctor thank you so hoping
that finally I'll be taking taken
seriously and yeah I'll I'll I'll try to
get something going again I'll also ask
for um cuz I was always was thinking uh
that part that they and
xray of my back was like a tiny part of
like the
middle of the part where I don't know
your neck and your shoulders connect
that part of the spine so like a tiny
part small small small small X-ray and I
thought maybe we should x-ray my
shoulder whatever but yeah I'm going to
go to the doctor on on
Tuesday yeah and I I'll say I don't know
I want what I don't care I'm paying the
money I want
whatever uh where I want something maybe
where you can see the muscles and the
like San I don't know uh uh what's San
uh strings the strings or
whatever uh of my shoulder and I want
every everything everything I want
everything
visible and yeah and nerves nerves I
want nerves to be visible so I don't
know if that's visible on normal x-rays
probably not but I want to scan that
[\h__\h] and then uh um I want to see if
there's something wrong and if there's
not okay then whatever but I feel like
you know I should trust my guts and
we've already tried so many other things
please please don't send me to another
Physical Therapy I've done so many and
they're all [\h__\h] that that don't help me
is phys yeah it's it's covered physic
phys Physical Therapy uh you can do it
like several times a year for
free but I've done it several times over
the many many years I need an MRI let's
go let's go let's go let's go MRI sounds
exciting do I go for like this kind of
machine like lying down is that what the
MRI
is I want the [\h__\h]
MRI I wonder how much that costs with
our Healthcare the two yeah but when I
think of that I just think of Scrubs uh
that one patient that thinks something's
wrong with his body and he just wants to
find something not necessarily that he
really feels that bad like he's
suffering or something it's not
particularly suffering but he just
really wants something to be wrong with
his body I don't know so he can pity
himself or
something and so he comes back back to
the hospital and they're always like
okay what do you want done
today we we'll check you out cuz
otherwise you're not leaving I guess and
then one time they finally find
something wrong with him and he's like
so
satisfied yeah you know he likes being
in the hospital I don't like being in
the hospital though because of first of
all the
smell I probably told you before
but one time I fainted in a hospital
because of the smell that was
crazy it's not it's not stinky but it's
just something about the scent of
hospitals makes me feel probably also
because it connects with the thought of
everything that happens in
hospitals and I I swear whenever like TV
shows or like whatever if wherever they
show
like for example
surgeries oh my God I hate why do do you
guys mind looking at like clips of
surgeries like when when a body is being
opened up or whatever it makes me want
to throw up I don't know why they show
it like it's like
whatever you don't mind not really you
don't mind I can't watch thank you me
neither I always close my eyes like why
are you showing me
this
why and then some
like like drama not not IRL scenes but
like drama shows where obviously like
it's not really what's happening
like there's not really I don't know a
[\h__\h]
alien coming through somebody's skin out
of their body but stuff like that I also
I can't watch even though I know it's
not really
real makes me shiver and feel
sick no Splatter for you then
no I dislike Gore I don't know if that's
if all of that is called Gore but just
Hospital scenes I can't handle
it a rip alien watch along is that what
happens
there oh my God
e okay I do have a
[Music]
headache do I have a
migraine is this what you call a
migraine
guys I've had it for days now in a very
specific spot and it really feels
like it feels so
shitty
oh Tension Headache yeah maybe it's I
don't know what I would a
[\h__\h] it just hurts and it doesn't go
away so let me let me take the Japanese
pink
[Music]
color no it's even what I just wake up
so I don't think it has anything to do
with uh light and
sound chunky
wonky did you hear that probably not she
said like a
pigeon what is
it come here come here come here come
here
come
here I'm not streaming I'm not streaming
you can
come you can come chunky
wonie no
don't she's so she's such a Pik me
girl no okay that's not really what she
is she's like she's she will sit right
like next to me on on the ground and
she'll meow at me and then I I I make a
move towards her to like pet her or pick
her up and she immediately like the the
moment I start making the move she
senses it h even if I don't look towards
her and and then she walks
in into a distance where I can't pick
her
up and then she comes back again and
then she sits there and then she meows
at me
again I'm like hm okay I try again I
move I try I move very slowly as to not
startle her and then she runs away again
she wants to be chased Cy raid okay then
maybe we should get started on the
game yesterday we finished chapter
one uh spoiler alert chapter one of
Yakuza like a dragon infinite
wealth hello dead beats I will beat you
up even more with this bat are you
excited I'mma beat you up I'mma beat you
up I will beat you up oh I did not turn
off my PS5 as you can tell it turned
into sleep mode this is what it is
right
please be gentle please do oh okay I'm
weak to blunt damage weak as in you take
more damage or weak as in you're weak to
it you like it a chuny wonky is here
again under my table now and then a and
then she runs
away oh spankenheimer
and clubs don't MI what why how do what
is the screen I don't understand
uh uh what do I click I don't understand
PS5 oh
oh this no huh huh what H back to
game there we
go controller needs battery hey
Bley no uh okay uh
cable I
[Music]
have oh okay shut the let me grab a
cable I've got the cable and thus I got
the
power the power to
charge and how low was it we don't hear
be yeah yeah me
neither me
neither okay is it charging now how do I
know it's
charging ah wait I think the sound is
currently going to my dual sense
controller
orange blinking oh it's not orange
blinking it's just white press
PS uh ah oh but that it's charging it's
charging [\h__\h] [\h__\h] dual
sense never told you I never told you
speaker dual sense wireless controller I
never told you I want you to do that
no head headphone no no not the Dual
sense
no
nope at least it didn't change it in OBS
right
chat stereo I
think I still don't have
uh game audio because my oopsie
no I clicked Steam on accident nice
profile picture thank you it's uh one of
you
guys it's one of
[Music]
you Kiana versus
technology we love it we love it because
game capture uh says it's already open
please ENT the application before you
start it again it's not
open we love these kind of issues
because it reminds of the good old
times the good old
[Music]
times ah it still won't let me open what
did I do before when I had this
issue what
this here task
ending task starting again by the way I
did kind of look ah it's open now I did
a dance three
times I did kind of no life I fin I live
tweeted I tweeted but I tweeted on my
phone so it probably didn't work uh I
watched a little bit of a
recap on on high speed where your ah
okay of course it didn't go through okay
now now I forced it
it won't show though it won't show on my
game capture my OBS shows it but my game
capture screen doesn't show it
why
can steam shut the [\h__\h]
up okay sorry guys I have these
problems let
me
something
itach attach this cable
okay you're good thank you you're so
nice guys
so no signal I know because now it's not
connected but now it's connected the
again so please give me a single single
s Give Me A
[Music]
Sign
hello every time I press the PS5 button
my steam window shows up what's up with
that is that some kind of weird
connection
when I press the PS5
button I'm charging it with your PC with
my PC
yeah that's how steam works okay for
[\h__\h] sake steam I hate
you go away okay oh wait why don't I
charge it on the PlayStation it's right
there charging a PlayStation controller
on the PlayStation
probably should be the first thing to
think
about okay but now it's like it's not
turning at
[Music]
all now you know now you know I'm back
for real because of because the scuff is
back we haven't seen scuff in a while
while the scuff is back everything's
back this is how things should
be I
guess we're so
back no [\h__\h] capture card isn't KN me
it's normally it's the internet now it's
the capture
[Music]
card I have angered it and it is
angering
me okay I'm starting it
again please work now it's working for
[\h__\h]
sake
mhm now
OBS you you can also capture it
OBS is it
this oh yeah
okay so okay now we may we probably have
sound once I start are you ready
for the cut scene that we were cutting
off yesterday it comes right in the
beginning
of chapter
twoim I think we're going to go to
Hawaii
today yes
okay oh wait that was no
sound ah ah okay we can get it from
here but why don't I have the sound is
it on the Dual sense again or
what wait one more hurdle one more
hurdle one more hurdle
dle I know how to make you hear it at
least oh I can't hear it okay well I'll
I'll give me some feedback maybe from
OBS it's one way to do
it uh
monitor monitor and
[Music]
output it's
crazy oh that doesn't
work
haai damn
it okay why is this
happening why no
sound uh ah maybe I can do sound sound
capture yeah yeah yeah I know you can
hear it but I can't you selfish
chicken I want to hear it
[Music]
too how do you say saying
something I don't want to miss
it no sound mine no give me share
sharing is
caring I
don't a switch noise every time I un
pause okay okay I don't hear
that let me try
here wait how do I go to the PS5
menu okay let's just make these sounds
then I'm not wasting
sounds
um what the [\h__\h] ah heard it no idea
why I keep pressing the same things now
suddenly it
worked okay thank God thank God that was
loud it's kind of loud I
think we're so back yay volume too low
oh yeah for you probably okay here I
raise it let's
go don't be such a kiss ass ichan [\h__\h]
him so I did watch a recap on him and I
I I remembered for example he is the
father of that child which is the other
Dead one right the other one that's dead
uh who we didn't really like kind of
loud okay and
um uh uh he when he was young he had
this baby with a lady and then I think
did they put it in the locker or was
ichan in the locker I think I think the
baby was in the locker the the Mas was
in the locker right and then there was a
gun in the locker I they both were okay
okay they were switched out uh yeah yeah
I didn't have time to watch the whole
[Music]
thing oh man
and yeah and so the young Master is also
I don't know considered the our brother
I guess I don't
know who who whoa
whoa still too loud
uh yeah yeah yeah cuz he got life
sentence
oh ah flashback let's
go yeah
mhm still kind of loud
okay he's just
[Music]
chilling
unlike
me so we're really mad at him but we
still offered him the the the lighter in
the beginning what the hell trying to
kiss
[Music]
his
for
okay looking
young
she already dead at that
point
oh shirt is so
shiny leather
shirt plastic shirt what the [\h__\h] is
that shirt
made
what what what what
what
fore
[Music]
fore it was set up
oh my God from the
[Music]
beginning don't don't touch it why would
you touch it she's just going to accept
it and play the play the
role have his fingerprints on it
this so
creepy imagine your son telling you that
yeah [\h__\h] and then we we come
in we're like what did you do you
bard
[Music]
well could kind of respect that you were
going to do it anyway
fore kind
of
for what no what Captain s didn't kill
even though he was in oh that's my fault
Oh I thought it was a side note even way
I couldn't have sworn he was s for life
just how did he get
out
because he has all the dirt
maybe oh God don't look down on us from
there
how
[Music]
nice
fore
foree
I guess yeah I'm I'm also straight from
my break I do have time but actually no
that's not true I don't have that much
time next week I'm kind of
[Music]
busy oh how the [\h__\h] do I open
this yes sir yes sir sir
wow
fore
yes of
course you have to join me picking duck
never did wait did we never we never got
to eat piging
duck in the end
in the last game it's pretty fast I
might as well take a taxi no you know
how much I love to walk in this
game same thing in GTA eventually I
started taking more taxis but I love
walking nope never we never did man
that's like the most painful thing I
just want that [\h__\h] baking
duck I just want that fing duck
man is the audio balance okay
now game AIO okay still a little too
loud okay no
[Music]
problem P dog interally
denied damn it what about picking
chicken I have plenty of chickens
here should we really where where are we
going uh you can automatically get to
ride there o
uh to Mother how do I Doom out
there oh okay yeah we we're going pretty
far can
we move
here I guess we'll do
it would that taste better I'm sure I'm
sure it could taste good
[Music]
toilets how much yen let's
go 10 Yen let's
go
we're going to be so rich baby it starts
from 10 Yen it becomes 100 yen and then
a thousand and then a [\h__\h] million
baby we're going to be so rich we are
already rich yeah Rich should love
totally oh what are you gangsters
sitting there on the ground let me beat
you
up going to beat you up I'm going to up
why am why is n so far
[Music]
away I'm
coming we're off to a good start classic
number but at least we had them in the
line M has to be far
yeah Mages are [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] sorry I I I often was a mage so
I'm roasting myself
too how dare you
punk you
[Music]
punk he's streaming Sparks right now
Sparks are all over
him
wa
oh destroyed
him get
ConEd get
menu what the [\h__\h] is that weapon don't
don't let's not talk about it what are
the stores
here
Nan I can get meat buns
what's
here
also big big n fresh
M and
close another one of these do they
have oh no they have
the pretty expensive thank God we found
them on our
own I love nikan but actually you know
for nikan okay let me show you let me
show you let me show you let me show you
let me show you here this picture down
here right this is a nikan but they also
come with different feelings here look
at look at the look at the
display yeah this is nikan nikan is me
so there's a basic one that's with just
basic meat but I like the pizza man has
pizza feelings inside cheese and tomato
uh cream
whatever sometimes maybe some
peon I don't
know and and then there's the Kon Kon is
curry Japanese Curry filling which is
different from other curries so yummy is
it like a stew no no no no it's like
it's like a burger you hold it in your
hand it's like street
food this is not being put in a soup or
something what are you thinking look at
this this is exactly how you eat it in
there that glass display this is this is
what you get like a Hot Pocket yeah but
it's really soft the dough is really
soft oh look at
that a please don't run around like that
like I mean oh those Co why there's
surely flattering more flattering
choices if your belly button sticks out
like that I don't know if that's a good
choice of
those what's that what's a huge bottle
go hope you're going to recycle that
make sure to recycle
it and especially in Japan you have to
take got the the plastic label too and
the the bottle the bottle cap
everything W I did the I did the
Japanese I think
I think I did
it think I did
it did I successfully do it you know I
always aspire to do Japanese R
rolls in like a p way for
example I don't think I could recreated
now I think so I'm Japanese
now oh totally did oh my God I need a
replay of
[Music]
that how romantic is your picking
duck got to be picking
[Music]
duck I don't hate
you cuz I barely remember
you so
[Music]
fore why did we never try to find her
until now
[Music]
you saw
this why were you
watching nice
recap put the baby in the yes this is
how you do it put the baby in the locker
and take a baby maybe uh this is
how yes coin Locker
is has
baby then I would have been a very
different
[Music]
person
so his son was raised as my dad's
son was just raised as
[Music]
nobody not stor no no Co creates
Bab
mama okay so that's why we didn't try
[Music]
to gotcha
babies
[Music]
fore
uhhuh I heard a lot of this from alakan
himself he said that hia pedri was a
total nutcase he also said aanan didn't
make it that he couldn't protect her in
the
[Music]
end
for
foreign
Fore why was sh
why why why were they out for her that
[Music]
bad wa how did she
cross how did she cross them she CA them
to be Dishonored
how
by association right
yeah so much for Honor killing people
because they're
Associated hey oh let's
go oh my God he's going on a
massacre
SC oh
emoi
oh
oh po him off
oh paint the hallway red it's the Red
Wedding no the red
deading I'll get you
all I'll get you and dead
[Music]
you vient hotline
Yakuza Red Dead
mension Red Dead
Redemption he's
scared he's so scared
h w
w
that didn't go how he wanted it to go
huh oh oh my God
terrifying
foree
fore
oh that's suddenly
polite oh I did it
again I think maybe did
[Music]
i ph
really
of
[Music]
speee
is he is he
safe [\h__\h]
[Music]
you do
it
[\h__\h] yeah yeah next
[Music]
one want to rip his
out no I'm going to rip rip something
else out going to rip his
balls CU he pisses me off where you
[\h__\h] you out [\h__\h]
you why would you laugh oh my
[Music]
God
[\h__\h] own family as in his
own
now you think she's alive in
Hawaii a
Pik ah a old one okay but it will help
us
too me
[Music]
Hawai is in your body
baby it was meant to
be actually is that maybe where he gets
his hair from I don't know that ter May
more common in Hawaii than in
[Music]
Japan got that Beach hair that was an
accident on
him
[Music]
[\h__\h]
fore
spee
[Music]
for speech
fore foreign fore
[Music]
speech
for
Fore
fore
[Music]
and he would to
well but still worth to clear it up I
mean just have two sons then you have
two sons then isn't
[Music]
that
n oh but yeah he wanted his son to be
treated
[Music]
well
for
oh cuz she would be in
danger
three half siblings
then course you got to move
on halfings let's
go
nice story
time that sucks that he never knew the
truth
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
it's not going to be that easy right
we're not going to immediately meet her
mom
right
[Music]
foree
for of
course of course this place sucks
everybody hates
me even the V are taking
over making shitty clips about
me
[Music]
really please tell me you're joking but
that's a weird humor
anyway oh
hey GL to see you're sing One Piece One
Piece what were you guys waiting for me
n was worried about you and I somehow
missed my chance to SK
SK look I was talking that's what I was
about to
say so did you find out what sa's
special request
was yeah about that I don't think he was
joking yeah he may not have been
joking
H but who knows he may says it but then
he always chickens out
anyway or or it's too
late things got a little complicated you
don't say then how about we head over to
survive yeah let's do that kinda
okay
maybe
oh
cute oh oh no it's a close-up don't
worry don't worry oh you look good oh
nice close for me
n oh yeah what a cute
smile oh yeah give it to me give it yeah
the St oh nice pie sorry that was
someone in the picture can you like can
you move why you staring into the phone
camera you [\h__\h]
creep can I punch
him [\h__\h] creep you ruined my number
picture why would you do that you suck
you [\h__\h] creepy
ass
mobile NAA so cute by R again what stons
the stons are amazing call me macaroni
I see some sparkling things Co
Superior natural
herb
cat oh my
God
hello hello are you
okay she's
uh why why is she looking at me like
that looks like
she's I don't know something's wrong
like she's about to
sneeze a picture how do I take a picture
again I forgot how I did
it a there we
go I think its eyes are
closed
in oh no wait that
was what's the face why are you eyes
closed get out of
there
[Music]
aab looking a bit weird but I mean a cat
is a cat that's
satisfying
enough oh no not
more
[Music]
sorry you want to wish each one a good
trip that's so sweet of
you imagine if the place I was going
to the the secret trip imagine if that
was
Hawaii
imagine it's not
but I don't know one day
maybe I don't even know if it's worth it
there's surely similar places I could go
to that are closer to
me so where are we
going I
survive
no
a myth Hawaii trip would be
amazing any myth trip would be
amazing could just be um I myth
[Music]
my all right survive bar I'm here wait
actually let me look at your back lot
it's so
addicting damn
it you got a lot of grass in your
backyard rainbow
[Music]
fragments
I see never found out son's life and
well maybe not but kind of sounds like
it was meant to be especially since Aon
un wanted to keep ARA in the dark and
what Happ you yeah this changed after
things changed after the boss passed who
knows if she'd want to meet me otherwise
so what are you going to do going to
ship off to Hawai sure but it's not so
much that I want to see my mom really
it's more about paying my respects to
the women the boss loved kind of my
sworn Duty you
know well I'm sure she'd like to see her
son after so many years especially given
her
age wait a minute you have never been
out of the country before have you this
will be the first time yeah nice thing
is I've already got the tickets Captain
sao's taking care of it I'm guessing all
I got to do is get to taxi and go from
there ah
sure most T spots out there will have a
Japanese speaker or two
um
no no no no no no I'm sorry Hawaii yeah
but uh yeah in Hawaii yeah yeah but no
no not no you can't just go to burlin
and expect to randomly find Japanese
speakers to help you out maybe other
Japanese tourists but um
no he won't survive much on Japanese
also not even on English speaking in a
Japanese accent which is the problem
many Japanese people face uh overseas
also the the third gen of whole life
Japan saying sometimes the correct words
but just in a very Japanese accent and
then you know from a not trained ear
it's it's really hard to hear like I
would understand what they're saying
yeah I know that she means Earl Gray
because I know how the Japanese syllable
system works but people who are not
familiar with Japanese language or so or
even let's say Korean language for
example they would probably they could
pronounce it similarly
probably you'll just not hear it I'm
sure a lot of you guys would probably
not understand what what they're trying
to tell
you so
yeah yeah it's very confusing yeah they
needed you there
I I I actually knew about it ahead of
time and I I I told them yeah take take
me with you guys I'll help you but they
probably had staff that uh helped them
out probably and somehow survived yeah
at least least for that moment with the
ear gray they were they were on their
own of course they had some stuff yeah I
wonder I wonder
who like Anan is really good in
English but then I don't know any other
staff besides Ian staff that are good
with English Yago is pretty decent in
English but I doubt he tanked
along
you just want to be with them aren't you
well I would love to have been part of
that yeah but it was their thing so it's
you know
understandable aan almost fluent yeah
yeah she's really
great maybe NOA nooka I don't know about
her English
skills but
yeah yeah
goat L Lou English is pretty good yeah
yeah but I mean
she didn't tag along it was a staff
member anyway Namba you're
wrong but in Hawai yeah I I I only know
this like from okay
this it's it's my only knowledge of
Hawaii many years ago when I was a very
active no it's not a show not really a
show when I was a really really active
fan of hello project the idol groups
that are in the agency hello project
especially very kovo um you know Idols
Japanese Idols what they would often do
besides making music is they they do
photos shoots and sell the photos in in
form of a photo book and often they
would
go may like on on beaches and whatever
and sometimes you know a popular
destination to take these photos would
be like Guam or
Hawaii and then with the photo shoots
often there was like a making
off and a DVD
and I I watched those and sometimes I
think once at least I think Betty's coo
went to Hawaii as a group as well and
anyway so from that I there were like
videos of my favorite Idols so from
gravier yeah kind
of they were like videos of them like
going to like touristy shops and buying
clothes and accessories and whatever in
Hawaii and then yeah that's the only
place where I would get
information about Hawaii and where I
would find out that there's a lot of
Japanese people in
Hawaii H although no that not the only
place later on I I I watched some kind
of documentary or something like that
where
um uh I think it
was like a dating service that connects
Japanese people with rich men I think in
Hawaii Japanese ladies rich men or the
other way around I don't
[Music]
know cuz that's some kind of service
going on there I don't know man I don't
know it's like a dating service for
ladies that want to go to Hawaii
mhm
male or the bride
similar no it's like it's a dating
service like any other it's a legit
dating
service yeah it's just you know no it's
legal it's totally
legal they they meet each other and all
that before deciding if they want to be
a
couple
H
anyway enough about
that uh legal it's
legal I didn't order Japanese
Bri fans of spam because fishing was to
not allow during the
conflict I did watch a cooking video
about spam the other day but I think it
was an Australian one I don't know
making some great things with
Spam maybe I should do a cooking stream
with Spam but I've never had spam ever
in my life
before spam the the the meat thing
anyway huh really there's been lots of
Japanese immigrants over the years
honest you me you mentioned traveling
abroad to people about my age the first
place they'll think of is Hawaii yeah
you know all those quiz shows from way
back the grand prize was usually
Hawaiian vacation for two yeah yeah yeah
yeah H Hawaiian vacation for
[Music]
two imagine if you went with Satan
that'd be
something like she never said yes to
that after all the things I said all the
things I said all the things I said
every so you guys haven't made up yet
the message I sent last year still
marked as
unre [\h__\h]
really this is not
[Music]
enough that song and I think another
song that kasuga ichan is streaming
actively right now is I can't read
[Music]
do the past and
present calls me the truth
[Music]
and he can't redo what he said he can't
redo the date
unfortunately [\h__\h]
really what the heck did I do wrong yeah
let's forget about that yeah and oh yeah
H don't you need to pack oh yeah [\h__\h] oh
yeah right thanks for reminding me and
there's some stuff to know in advance
like watch out for white tax white taxes
oh a lot of Japanese folks get scammed
cuz Crooks think we all look like
mild-mannered
idiots scam
scam white taxes huh hey what so what
white taxes are there other taxes too
what there's white taxes and and other
taxes and the white white taxes are
bad
oh
so like not necessarily praying on
Japanese people but just praying on
tourists but are they actually colored
white and then there's other taxes which
are not colored
white it's not
literal that's what I was wondering if
it's
literal thank taxi I guess and they up
charge the heck out of you are
everywhere yeah that's why I like to use
Uber yeah one more thing before you
shove off it might be a good idea to
stop by old ARA's grave huh you're right
I should right
right all right we'll all visit him
first tomorrow morning and then we'll
have a cool cut scene for everybody to
watch and some deep conversation let's
go hey but I wanted to sing K why are
they kicking me out of the bar
[Music]
again no well shall we where's my
suitcase now that I think about it this
is my first time visiting ala's grave
yeah same I haven't been in a while
myself hang on I'll get us a cab or a
crab
Cony no a cab a cab is what I'm
getting should I get a
crab I don't know maybe a crab maybe a
crab is what I should be
getting any
crabs pocket to tisue let's
go
hello this is a yellow taxi
so probably not not going to scam
us
[Music]
uh oh
yeah what those flowers in the pots you
know what they remind me of oh I watched
the video today I didn't know you could
do this you can when you cut off a
spring
onion uh like if you cut cut cut cut C
cut chop ch ch ch chop then keep I'm
never going to throw the the back of the
the root part of a spring onion again
you can regrow them even in a water
glass or even better probably better
result in like just like a little pot
with uh with yeah infinite onion glitch
oh my God but like in the comments
nobody said how long it takes do you
guys know how long it
takes so many people wrote in the
comments like oh yeah I'm doing this
infinitely I've I've I've been doing
this with one rout since like three
years ago holy
[\h__\h] that's crazy that's how plants work
I know but like I don't know like
normally you can't like I don't know
it's I didn't think it would be that
easy and was like uh I don't know you
know I don't know maybe the roots need
to be longer or so you
know it takes time it takes some time
just do a bunch one to free months
probably uh haven't patched it out yet
it's
crazy infinite wealth infinite spring
onions I've been doing this for five
years I have a dozen bulbs and I keep
swapping the ones I
cut
oh m I want to try that too next time I
have a spring onion from
hellofresh
who works with potatoes
too I can have
potatoes you can also cut a potato and
have and whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa I need I need I need all these
videos that are gardening life hacks
please send them my way onion update
turn wait um
who whoa
whoa but how easy is that cuz like for
example I tried growing berries and all
that and it didn't go so well but the
spring onions seem pretty
easy oh I have a
DM oh it reminds me of something
[\h__\h] I want to do something but oh well
[Music]
okay my head hurts I took a painkill and
it still hurts
[\h__\h]
[Music]
for he doesn't believe it
[Applause]
[Music]
fully
I mean by now you should
[Music]
know oh I bring them to
Hawai
he doesn't
[Music]
care head H it's more like it's pretty
strong over my ey my left eyebrow right
now
and at my
temple
man
yo I don't want to keep you on a number
waiting I should head out to the station
and snag a taxi for the airport o are we
going to see the
airport like Nar or
honey Hy oh my God it's almost a
CUNY almost a crab
Nancy
why you had that thing
still
F you can't bring her to
Hawaii unless you you tell her to swim
there from Japan you can't take her on
the
plane
[Music]
okay just put her in the ocean she'll
take care of
[Music]
herself
yeah want to see Hawai huh yeah but you
are swimming I am flying I can't take
you you're a no fly
list
[Music]
don't make those noises do
they oh my
God oh my [\h__\h] God we have a [\h__\h]
pet on our shoulder oh now it's gone
where did it
go where did we put it into our
backpack you're going to see it they're
going to scan it they're going to smell
it
too
no no Kimo why does he have a lowkey
six-pack don't make those disgusting
[Music]
movements yeah just kill
him oh my God
that's no lowkey s
[Music]
what Ian I remain on the
[Applause]
face you disgust
me get out of here go back home pull on
some
clothes have some
decency May D paralyzed that's his
name
okay oh he oh he's got quite a bit of
[Music]
HP still paralyzed
nice still paralyzed he probably likes
it he's enjoying it I can see
it hey I pressed it you
[Music]
[\h__\h]
got no I'm not going to give him
Nancy I don't want to know what he's
going to do with
Nancy he's going to make Nancy
private
Turn The Collector or so
right oh my God
are we still doing this
collecting in these trying
[Music]
times
his scar is deep
man what
[Music]
Su it's making some Japanese puns that I
don't
[Music]
understand I unless you have Simon in
Hawai
[Music]
yeah be
true
yes
no to be the very best
no yeah cuz I think I think the Pokemon
company is a little bit sensitive right
now so you should not put this kind of
stuff in your game right
now I don't know if they can still joke
around like
this
no no [\h__\h] virus on my
phone I'm pouring some more
tea and some more honey honey honey come
out of the
bot come out
yeah oh
yeah
who is that
suim I don't want to
know game's already creepy
enough okay but I guess they're all Su
jimon all the enemies I'm finding is
every one of them is a sujon I guess
it's just a like a
[Music]
record none of your business why I'm
going
there suim Paradise in Hawaii
[Applause]
what yeah different regions different
Pokemon
different
uhhuh
Mo I really like that one I remember
playing that oh
my I played sand well everybody else
played
me but look look where maybe that was
Destiny look where I am now look who I
am
now I feel like I always choose the the
less
popular um game from the Pokmon
games you also played Sun Sun here too
let's go yay I just tend to always
choose the one that has a so to say
Brighter
Image if you know what I mean like sun
as opposed to
Moon
for
example where am I going am I going to
run oh oh
[Music]
okay anyone like the lion didn't people
prefer I mean in the end it feels like
everybody goes from moon but then if you
look at the statistics I guess it kind
of like balances out
but everybody I knew was playing Moon
pretty
much oh and then for even for Pokemon go
I went for the unpopular I think the
yellow team cuz there were like three
teams
right the easiest one the the one of the
eest access to Arcanine ah worth it to
get your favorite Pokmon yeah
get
it I don't really care but yeah yeah was
the yellow team same here oh my God same
in I think it's yeah I guess maybe it's
kind of
a no I wouldn't say it's a hipster thing
like where I I I purposefully want to
choose the less popular one no it's
really just like I like the the things
that are like brighter
looking and cuter
looking I don't
know where are we going
oh wait I have to go over the bridge
oh
you just speaks more to
me usually I mean I don't even care that
much because yeah there's some different
Pokmon but not that many different
Pokmon and in the end the story is the
same if the story was different then
okay then I would put more thought into
it
and maybe go against my usual
Choice it doesn't really
matter all my friends buy both
versions damn just just uh why for
collect are they like collectors cuz
like otherwise if it's about the Pokmon
that you're missing out on you can just
um
Exchange
[Music]
Ty what are we
going W every two seconds where are we
going trading requires
friends Supreme
herb
OMG how do I I look at the map guys but
it's like hard for me to understand is
there something
there I'm supposed to take this taxi
this specific
one
y
we got to
buy r
[Music]
r
are they're never going to join or just
not for
now cuz kind of sad to leave them behind
but I guess at least we could fight with
them for a while in the beginning and
now we're going to make new friends new
teams
airplane airplanes in the night SK are
beautiful I really use a wish right now
right now right
now he's got a window seat he's Window
Gang woohoo me too just like me for real
for
real how long is the flight that he's
like so
[Music]
sleepy pretty long oh hi guys we were
gone oh I didn't even realize was
short
I was just
singing International of all of our crew
thank you for choosing to fly with us
today we hope to see you again
soon get up an extra
invitation 7
hours
you B the hero with the hero Savor
complex what you even
making knows better than these employees
I thought they would have some training
or like experience with
[Music]
it
yeah oh wait okay wait we're generally
not doing so bad
oh oh
[\h__\h] oh okay it's green
again I say I you say Bean
[Music]
oh
okay I think we're
good who says that in English little R
and
R just asked here for
tourism
what a fancy Japanese dude saying Bonas
another Japanese dude to flex his
sophisticated with his polo
shirt you say aloha over
here
Aloha those are my Phoenix
Colors oh my God that's oh that's
amazing is this really how the airport
looks they always recreate the cities so
I guess this is really how it
looks oh my God now I want to go oh
[\h__\h] sure would be nice if the taxi
driver spoke Japanese what remember what
they said to you the ones that want to
scam you maybe speak a little bit just
to be able to scam you
oh oh they made an easy conversion 100
yen to
$1 oh my God this is this looks like GTA
now with the different like plants and
all
that honestly like if you ignore the
character that we're playing this could
be
GTA where's [\h__\h] coconuts up
there
trees yeah guys maybe refresh cuz I
don't think everybody's on the same uh
latency right now on the same delay
maybe we try refreshing why is there so
many points to go at the taxis I'm going
to try and see if they speak
nongo yeah do two times
speed
uh
[Music]
sorry
oh you're from Japan
right
aha can you speak
Japanese something I know enough to hold
a conversation oh
sorry my my hungo not Joseph
Dam [\h__\h] too difficult maybe
try
Okay Kasa just just show them the
address you want to go to on your
phone and say go go go
go go here okay
okay
easy
oh oh
oh yeah he looks not like a random side
character especially if that cut scene
is
happening Al
Al he's a main
character say that he's going to say I'm
Japanese
he speaks like a Japanese
dude is he going to join our
team seems
nice have a
[Music]
reaction he's a Japanese
guy
seat Bel seat Bel s Bel
please both of
you yeah the music was sus but he seemed
so
nice I we getting
scammed he's
so
he's
nice like
the
great customers because they're easy
toat I
wouldn't
upat there we
go
no he's
[Music]
fine for real for
real both half have half America half
Japan wait huh are they related is that
one of his brothers are you guys
spoiling me right
now
he would have had a stronger
reaction cuz it's his mom's name
then
what English is strong in this game time
than they're really I know in the in the
beginning too in the beginning of the
game
you
maybe more English
oh okay
[Music]
now yeah that's not just a scammer
that's um dangerous
person who probably did
recognize the
name yeah
did oh my
God America be
like
no no I'll teach you who I
am damn he's so
badass
huh oh [\h__\h] you guys getting
roasted oh my
God
hello
[Music]
okay now now now it's green now it's
green what the [\h__\h] I I was immersed in
the
scene and it was like not it was
dying okay uh uh I don't know what
exactly you guys missed
but uh he was just roasting you guys
ichan was roasting you guys was saying
that the Cowboys in America don't know
what it means to pull the
trigger and I was like ha
roasted
okay yeah you didn't miss too much
okay
Cowboys who don't know what it means to
a pullet
trigger tell
meub seen some
[\h__\h]
transform too no he got a nice weapon
now rough neck damn I even F he could
maybe become part of our Hawaii team I
was considering you nice to dude but now
you have disappointed
me
strongly you could have
been my hey hey I could have taught you
so many things I could have taught you
how to pull the
[Music]
trigger maybe they bom later interesting
I mean I don't know if there's really
still a chance for
that oh o oh hey New
[Music]
Tricks
come [\h__\h] I keep on missing
now car battery laser
oh a car
[Music]
battery come on home around time [\h__\h] at
least he
[Music]
ah he's part of the sui di crooked
cabby well well well I wouldn't say that
this cuz somebody in the chat said this
is why I'm worried about you getting
scammed I wouldn't necessarily say that
this is like comparable
to me and to real life okay don't worry
I'm I mean
yeah
I I don't get scammed because people are
so so amazingly nice to me no I just get
scammed even from people where I realize
that they're not not nice and they're
trying to rip me off a little bit
because oh we're lagging
again
no
m
what's going on should I move the router
around or
what back again but for how
long maybe it's just
generally it's generally weird right
[Music]
now
okay yeah anyway I feel I I was going to
say I think I'm being if I get scammed I
get scammed like in different ways not
necessarily by people who are super nice
to me no they're not even nice they're
just I just can't
really recently I I kind of
was thinking I was getting scammed and I
tried to stand up for myself and I was
like trying to be intense and all that
but then I don't know it didn't work out
it didn't work out I'll tell you that
story
sometime sometime I'll tell
you huh don't say you losted you little
[\h__\h] he going
to no he's going to say I did
that okay yeah he he do be an important
character because we're going to get
back and get that [\h__\h] back and then we
become
friends
why the [\h__\h] would you do that oh maybe
he did that because he is our half
brother and he's like I don't want you
to go see my
mommy she's my mommy you can't I won't
share my mommy with
you help I'm
beloved this H wanted money and she
pointed a gun light at
me wow you should maybe check who the
gun is registered under because
certainly not me my Del just came from
Japan how could it be me how it's
probably registered under some American
dude someone
there all right all right SM guy put
your hands in the air and turn
around so
lonly no understand
I'm pissing myself over here I'm pissing
myself this
English probably also not easy to
understand no
safe who should be arresting is the
driver okay guys if you hear this as
like if you're not familiar with uh with
Japanese pronunciation would you
understand this conversation they're
they're okay it could be worse
but where did he come from
anyway and if proof I recorded the
horing without subtitles I don't know if
I you guys would understand wow you
recorded it
what hey freeze they're trying their
best of the
Engish they're trying
C Us in
4k damn what a bro what a
Chad slightly muzy at wor nothing in
here
yeah could
be
you noticed
it seem so
nice and then and he held onto the back
of the car his wheelchair and he tagged
along without
aing well I don't know
anymore have to wait until
that Japanese half Hawaii guys
out
mhm I wouldn't know can sound address
without it did I seriously come all this
way
no it's not coming out of his stomach
maybe for the sake of the story it will
but yes especially with the help of
a I saw someone make a really blurry
picture really readable with a
[Music]
for who do you think you
are ch to an almost stranger it's a bit
too
early wow I'm
car wa M M strong
guy the
contrast apparent
we're we're
[Music]
rolling if he has the parrot out can I
take
my my my crab
out why is that lady in
the
is the ocean that
close I mean I know we're in Hawaii
but
cute cute uh
cars is there really that much
fire
City
chicken the tail is so
[Music]
big do they really do so much fire stuff
oh that's a fancy ass
Hotel
they have chickens in
Hawaii who Beach the boats look like
[Music]
watermelons oh
nice oh that's
[Music]
nice po
ball and yeah Lo
[Music]
Mah
mahm yeah I know I know I
know
chicken no way chicken in wow we can go
there and feel
[Music]
comfortable
damn what a deep
[Music]
story yeah that's so
petty he's so
[Music]
positive can I catch
him
[Music]
a
tom
[Music]
tom man that was good be great to come
back here once things settle down I'm
I'm glad you enjoyed
it golden hour baby there's so much
golden hour in this game check out the
view all I usually get is some nasty
sech canals and this is really
something yo that mountain in the back
not the guy the mountain the actual
Mountain yeah you can't just stuff
everybody you like into tiny
capsules yeah that's the song I did with
subu yeah that's right definitely
appreciate appreciate it more after
going away back then I took it for
granted all right you said you were born
over here you visiting your family yeah
you might say that always good to keep
in touch got to be tough on the wallet
to come back to Hawaii every time though
huh now he's a rich boy don't you see
his polo
shirt yes it's it's pretty harsh I'll
have to knuckle down at work next
month oh is your job pretty
flexible freelance here we go again with
the
larpers might actually be a volcano I
was going to say but I didn't want to
assume
ly no why do they all turn around and
run
away that's a pretty normal shirt well
but a lot of a lot I'm not saying
everybody who wears a polar shirt is a
rich person but a lot of rich people
wear polar shirts
so e are the volcanoes in Hawaii they're
not active are
they they sure do
[Music]
mhm some of them are oh oh
[\h__\h] but they probably haven't broken
out in years
right I used to work full-time corporate
but it was a little awkward to stick
around once I got in the chair okay so
that's kind of recent so
if you're a freelance you can get it all
done from home so it's a bit more
liberating a freelance engineer huh well
hope you're paid
accordingly you know the trade I've
worked at a hell work in yokahama got
fired after a bit though you
what probably hard to respond to that
don't worry it's all good oh no it's not
that you said you were in Yuka no oh
yeah I was and Hell work fired you so
wait oh
he knows me does he watch
vtubers
oh what's up don't tell me are you the
same customer they talked about on the T
Chanel
No I will never forgive that [\h__\h] that
voice changing
[\h__\h] never never never of course he's a
vtuber fan it's always the vtuber
fans and always the drama
tubers the fans who believe everything
and the drama tubers who make it
burn oh yeah that's
mean I knew it man channel must be
pretty famous huh I mean yeah she said
you've done some pretty heinous things
but frankly I just can't believe it and
yeah he even he even himself he he a I
mean he found me being like in the
middle of being like you know like in a
situation exactly like that where things
look like something that it's
not so believe me
please imagine being a vtu fan can't
relate
ew five million Subs
though probably they probably bought the
subs probably just took over a channel
that already had 5 million uh Subs cuz
honestly I can't even I don't even think
that's realistic getting with a channel
like that getting 5 million Subs I don't
really think that's
realistic n need more than just drama
but what do I
know seriously the whole thing was whack
it had to be and that means you have to
get her to take
back Oh you mean DM her or whatever I
tried sending one but I never got a
reply and I'm not myed about getting
fired I did do some ambiguous stuff here
and there you you really think so yeah
honestly I don't really care about me
and all this what really gets me is all
the people are dragged down you rep for
this whole unreasonable ordeal and
you're worried about other people oh my
God what a selfless
[Music]
guy
he couldn't he couldn't slide into their
DMS yeah unreasonable is what happened
to
them oh what the hell no point getting
all depressed with a view like this we
ought to keep
moving oh
no what was
that what's wrong ma'am I have a savior
complex so let me save you I can fix
[Music]
you is she saying that in English the
wind blew my scarf into the ocean it's
really special to
me I don't know why it would be
British
sorry is he going to be our designated
translator oh my
God her scarf was blown into the ocean
she says it's really
special oh my God it's literally
me
English yeah I just wanted to emphasize
that it's
English like for real
English oh it's going to show off his
sick tattoo let's go
wait how's this it's John can you ask
where she side it lands I'll swim out
and get
it right
uh where did you get what where did you
say it
fall oh analo I'll tell him then
I mean the lightning currently makes the
water uh look very
contrasting I want to see it during the
daytime D hey we're playing da the diver
faded pink book garbage jump into the
ocean no that's not
it oh I got it the second dve
nice the fish no not in my
case
really so
emotionless there was a gift from her
late husband glad we got it back to her
jumping into the ocean just like that
what were you even
thinking he sorry for the scare I
appreciate you playing Navigator aan
goodness I haven't yelled like
that well sorry for that too anyway
let's get going ich
diver not even fence
no I'm surprised he isn't freezing you
think it's cold dress like that all
right nearly I forgot hand
tight or sit
tight so cute with his suck sorry for
the wait now we can go okay lead the way
here we go
wow what of
[Music]
you waa there are some huge Palm Tre is
exactly what I picture when I think of
Hawaii palm trees swaying over a blue
sea that about sums it
up H is he saying that
ironically something wrong back in Japan
I'll up and snag a person off one of
these trees in the park is that a noo
out here m not true I've never even
thought to do that I doubt they'd put
you in jail for it oh seriously good to
know
sick oh he's going for it he's grabbing
some grub
paron I saw it on this one anime when I
was a kid it just looked so good I
always wanted to try it a Cho mate they
sell it right over there sure but isn't
it bad better if you get it yourself and
it's free what a
deal oh he wants to tackle it you're not
going to climb
lame whoa okay I'm doing this if I'm
ever in
Hawaii as if I would get anything out of
it I I I'd probably hurt
[Music]
myself imagine if people actually did
that in the middle of hon Lulu on the
beach
everybody everybody after playing this
game is bonking the trees trying to get
free
[Music]
coconut and then it lands on their heads
and they die let's
go all right it even split open and it's
a full one too all right here goes it's
not even that good I don't really like
coconut juice like
that he's sipping he's
sipping damn this stuff's amazing oh
whoops I'm just here
gorgeous
yeah no thank you come on you got to try
it's really good man your froats all
dried out from yelling earlier yeah my
my
froat oh how did you know that but he
said so I heard that cough a mile away e
blah blah blah just drink
it
this really good really I don't
[Music]
know coconut
coconut so tell me what you want to
do there's so many coconut songs in this
world and I made a pineapple song I'm
such a
contrarian everybody makes coconut
songs I make songs about
pineapples really makes you
think I never thought I'd get one
straight from the tree like this I can't
remember the last time I did something
so childish and stupid and sussy and H
OAB
bonga it's a good time right no harm if
we goof off now and then that don't
actually work can you really just tackle
a tree and they fall down so
easily isn't that easy
[Music]
it would be a 10 out of 10 if it was
just like this the whole time I don't
agree no no no no no no that's not what
makes this game great
solely need a bit more to
that most of the time no not at all
doubt it rarely okay got to try to find
it out oh you want me to suffer you want
me to to Hort my
shoulder you want me to learn through
[Music]
pain I'm sure they monitor the trees in
public areas to make sure nothing falls
on it redar oh yeah yeah yeah I can see
that yeah they probably just also out of
pettiness because they don't want people
to get a free coconut they want them to
buy them over press so whenever there's
something growing they probably just
take it off
don't forget to film it okay I'll go to
Hawaii
tomorrow imagine if the place I'm going
to was actually
Hawaii second time I'm saying this well
Mo R is key I suppose anyhow we should
get going get
that
he hey pretty happening spot it's like
this old all day here there's lots of
stores around
too I'll say good place to pick up some
souvenirs what's
wrong oh
Chad hey CH what's up over
there I don't know what's happening
there the they look H the
guy the blonde guy looks
um interesting confusing he's giving me
confusing Vibes they're probably just
trying to pick her up they tend to go
after the tourists around
here well it's not unheard of she looks
kind of upset though huh yeah I
certainly say
so okay save your complex let's save
her we have to save
her it's literally my job title I'm a
hero I said no
come on baby if you don't got to get
scared come with us I'll be
fine uh
pardon the [\h__\h] do you
want is
that
person n s
h
that that lady ready
there oh there's no way his English is
that good kasuga cannot say troubled I
don't believe
it lady not okay what the [\h__\h] is he
going on
about
ah
problem no good good
English He b s for what you want to get
your face
smashed I I
[Music]
understand
to to to yes yes uh uh what are you
doing
kasas I don't know like this is
difficult because he's like now he's
actually supposed to be speaking
Japanese so I'm trying to mix in some
Japanese so you guys get the
point anything that's not in the
brackets is supposed to be Japanese I
guess in his case yeah hey maybe take a
LP I think I'm about to throw down
now you're just being Reckless thing
things might get a little Rowdy so don't
get too close normally I wouldn't but
I'm not about to leave you hanging are
you actually going to fight with us now
she is he going to show us some sick
wheel
skills some
tricks this guy thinks he's hot [\h__\h] h
let's splatter
him oh here we go he's got a
surfboard
[Music]
nice cheers for now for
real he's he has a support
back maybe one day it'll show us some
real
skills a little come on come on they're
probably not so strong not worth it got
them
ah [\h__\h] I'm so bad at blocking
today
[Music]
nice okay I'll do it
anyway
all right that was good that was good I
got both of
[Music]
them don't ask me to explain it's not my
fault
man no that that thing doesn't even fit
into his backpack trust me guys I don't
know how he brought it
over what's wrong wrong with my
input what's wrong with my input for
real for
real lag
lag ah they probably were like whatever
this guy this guy doesn't even have a a
check bag only one backpack let's let's
let him take the
massager separately in his hand okay
my bad oh my bad he says sorry man we
learned your lesson
Hest they said they've learned their
lesson I bet so didn't I master English
yet or what you're asking
me yeah I'm asking you sorry about all
that you're safe
now oh no need to thank us or anything
thank you for saving me H you're so
handsome maybe let me say thanks my
hotel's just down the street
what what
what she's a sighting
woman
what what the [\h__\h] come on I promise it
will be fun
uh hey I helped that too you know hey
you want to get late
C he probably doesn't even get
understand what he what she's
offering
what well she clearly just doesn't
appreciate a more rugged older man like
myself you don't even look old and
especially not from the POV of you
know white people you know I think it's
hard to judge
the age I it's hard to judge for me
too the age of of anybody with Asian
blood yeah he does not they made him
look so young
though they made him look real
young 40 is in
demand anyway it was good to enjoy the
island a bit about we had about time we
had over to your place actually why
don't we grab a quick didn't we just
eat
okay Cafe easy salad sandwich
nice I do like tuna salad
sandwiches very much
oh free magazine reading this could
impart drop exp for your current job
what I get exp from reading
it I'm not wondering I'm going to grab
these three
magazines
okay okay your coffee machine is not
working but you got the sandwiches o
yummy yummy yummy they're like really
thick
too I I wait I need two I
guess thank you or I don't know if one
would have been enough if we would have
shared it but I got plenty for the both
of
us and we can top it with some natural
herbs sandwich machine is working yes
thank God we're
saved we will not
suffer from lack of
sing
yeah
tell us your
story oh that's pretty recent
[Music]
yeah
for we used to like kind of serve him
like yeah that wasn't a very
beginning kiss
his
[Music]
sound crackling
is
for was just
from
f
[Music]
for
foree
sh
[Music]
yeah no don't feel
like
is such a
baby I thought he would really be
rich H guess I was
wrong but I guess doesn't he have two
homes oh wait that does look nice he has
a pool I mean wa is this it's not a
permanent home is this like an
Airbnb
it I do still think he's
Rich maybe he's rich in
Japan
what do you think that
wristwatch
nice lots of xes on
that don't know if that will help
us
who
hey oh
[\h__\h] ah that bastard oh my
[Music]
[Applause]
whoa what a
guy
and his movement is so that his he still
stays cool in his um he's such an edge
Lord he's trying hard to not have his
coat that's over his shoulders fall down
because I don't know it's cool to not
have your arms in in the coat sleeves I
guess he trying so
hard
[Music]
uhuh behind the scams
partially where did he get the
shers
so probably can see it with the shitty
quality Who whoo whoo not with the
crowbar
[Music]
e no
I hope by now we remembered the address
in our
head Hawai wearing Hawaii
shirts say it a little bit louder so
that they can totally hear
you
black
[Music]
yeah for real can we talk about your
M like you're
[Music]
onion yeah supposed to be hot
right Beach
go
oh yeah he's only wearing it for that
stylish scene of them taking it off to
assert dominance too
all right okay interesting new
Yak little
iPad all right okay let's have some
[Music]
fun wait
um
okay stop
moving
nice turn
around turn
[Music]
around okay finally one of
them oh no is he
stupid my
God maybe we can afford one more Grand
liner if we find a good line No actually
they're weirdly scar
of actually never mind let me not use a
skill cuz a lot of them have low
HP
y oh not this again
[Music]
nice
ah
yes CH
thank I think the boss will probably
fight him afterwards or after I kill all
his underlings he'll be like man I have
time for this fine cuz we're not worthy
yet
something like that we'll
see I feel like he doesn't want me to
give his time of to
day be ready to take y might too oh
okay no I'm ready I'm
ready
no can we get
him feel like we can
[Music]
nice nice
nice uh now I'm finally resisting uh
blocking but I still pretty low on HP
can you heal me oh thank you full
heal
[Music]
T nice okay
I'm in the groove guys I'm
grooving and I get another turn
yeah and why I swear I pressed it at a
good
timing my input is
[Music]
[\h__\h] let's go
yay oh no oh
no something
[Music]
break who oh oh I like their logo it's
kind of
cute not
very intimidating kind of
cute oh the furniture is
back oh my mp my mp is so
low the BS come up h
let's take some
[Music]
furniture while it's still
there
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] yeah
oh he's back okay he is helping me
again I'm going to go for skill and then
soon we might have to charge our
[Music]
MP BR don't worry it's just a
motel
thank
you oh damn it I can't help it I need an
[Music]
item maybe in
sck I like this music right
now think I hear some
shami tast Ste you get want two turns
and me too
please okay thank you without you I I
would not have been able to do this
totally I need your
help I swear to
[Music]
God
sucks oh my God I need a heal again soon
AG okay
okay still take so much damage even when
I block
it oh I was
drunk one
more
so since yamay hit his guy with a
scrollbar I kind of getting this feeling
that you know he'll realized
okay oh God W that's dangerous heal
me thank you kind of getting this
feeling that he'll join us he'll he'll
leave the dark side and come to our
[Music]
side
I need some
more yeah maybe I shouldn't have a boss
that hits me with a crowbar says every
takachi the realization hits
finally I do have a boss that instead
puts me into the usual
room and puts me into the
fryer not a crow guard no
[Music]
just kidding yeah the taco doches are
perfectly happy
[Music]
oh I need to press
something no protect him
no oh there we go the wheel skills he's
going to show them to us Flex Flex the
wheel
[Music]
skills no there were no wheel skills
when is he showing showing me his
tricks oh wow that did do a lot of
damage
okay okay nice 60 bucks from that thank
you I think I learned a new skill just
now did I feel like I did
he's gonna I mean with that purple shirt
he's
gonna finally about
time upload it to an online Drive
pleas
a new Dream
Team he's colorcoded he's joining us for
sure yeah he just kind of feel it with
the character design and all that and
the voice and you know he's already
being treated shitty by him he's waking
up like a [\h__\h] zombie this guy is
interesting
very
[Music]
interesting definitely on everybody's
bucket
list
will he be fine alone I'm sure he will
be he's been in the wheelchair for 5
years oh
wow wow wow wow Are We There is this it
nice
place nice
um nice plants and all that nice Garden
but that looks abandoned
huh looks
abandoned but damn
nice
recently
[Music]
abandoned don't worry she's not in
there would have been too easy anyway
the whole game will be about finding her
mom well she's probably running away
from someone
else but not from me
you
speee
foreign
[Music]
he's so
cute what maybe it's the daughter one of
the one the kids are maybe still
there or's
imagination it's not
real thought he heard a voice but it's
just in his
[Music]
head oh
chapter done that was a short
one or maybe it wasn't so short and the
problem is we only the first chapter was
only so long because
I paused 100 times and today I only
paused like 50 times no I think it was
actually
shorter nice we can do a second one
maybe today
too the fool I am the
fool dating advice it wasn't
important
oh oh did I get arrested for breaking
in
[Music]
why didn't we see
that
for oh the person inside the
house or
what the lady inside stripped him naked
ichan I don't think you understand what
happened you weren't
robbed no that voice is so sweet
[Music]
though it can only be our new team
member
no no no no I'm not making fun of
that don't misunderstand
all he just doesn't understand he
doesn't understand dating he doesn't
understand
anything is he really hearing that is it
a real
[Music]
voice hey and now she's going to beat us
up or
what
hi pretty though I like her hair and her
piercings
be he's going well so
far they're
bonding Hawai so nice to
me
[Music]
foree
he's going off on a
tent don't give strangers too much
information like the taxi driver man
yeah he tells everyone's life
story
really is she
not I would believe her but we I also
believe the taxi driver
so I should believe
anyone I'm just as bad as ichan I I'm so
innocently
naively
[Music]
for I do tell you a lot of information
are you guys just gathering information
to like in the end Rob me and leave me
naked on the
beach
she's getting me
drunk don't drink too much
youne want to steal my heart okay not my
belongings just my heart
[Music]
she's failing me alcohol
crazy nice s
oh see she's so
intimate starting
to just he's
[Music]
sh
oh she's so good at
this I got remember those
lines I'll say it to you guys guys your
wings look so
strong your little chicken beat also
look like they could step on me and I
would squash
[Music]
you're so
small must fly from Europe to America
every day with such swoll
[Music]
wings
her voice is so nice I like
[Music]
[Laughter]
it if all this I'm so
sad this this game is
ruining my
[Music]
my trust and love for
Humanity more
alol she just want my
money this is kicking your ass going to
kick your
ass yeah everybody's taking advantage to
him
did she drink like non-alcoholic stuff
or she was just like dumping it on the
side I can't
believe she acted so
well what
[Music]
theu
okay but I think her motive is
interesting it's not just like to [\h__\h]
me over I I think we'll find out an
interesting motive later
on something like I needed to keep him
safe
the trailer scene oh wait did I ever
watch the trailer I don't remember such
an ass
crack I I I didn't watch
that no wait maybe now I kind of
remember
it oh the hermit crab go faster go
faster
crap yo why is nobody looking at him ah
there we go some reaction
[Music]
imagine imagine the scene taking away
even the sun lotion it gets smaller and
smaller the object gets smaller and
smaller just to roast
[Music]
each
AER look don't you feel
it up dude
[Music]
don't he's so
dumb why is it taking him so
long
[Music]
oh
oh my
[Laughter]
God
I mean it doesn't sound too crazy
does youed to crazy stories
now but like a lot of crazy things
happen the
world like a police guy probably already
heard a lot of crazy
stories ah he lost his
passport [\h__\h] then he can't go back he
could get an emergency
passport the
words
[Music]
really
[\h__\h]
[Music]
fore foreign
speech
[Music]
foree
doesn't know that he should ask for a
lawyer
[Music]
man
at the beginning of the conversation not
just
[Music]
now sound like I feel like he wouldn't
even give you a lawyer cuz he's already
[Music]
see in the
beginning I know they have to but I
don't think he
would I'll have you
know that's right you don't know who
you're dealing
with
dude are we going to sit for 20 years
and be 60 afterwards to continue the
game
imagine
wasting so much time in their
[Music]
life I guess
so
them stop right there hey we got a
runner run yeah run run run
ich ichan On The Run let's
go what the flipflops
stop oh [\h__\h] I think I have to control
him oh yeah
are we running I don't have to
run you're a Deep Pal
this why are we running that
way stop right there no stay where you
are I can't even I can't aim to go there
interesting
oh ah [\h__\h] I I I I couldn't find the
button oh my God that was so last second
or I think I didn't evened cuz I got hit
didn't I you're not getting away I
didn't know where wasay where you are
here he is I had to look at the
controller g g I'd stop if I were you
don't do anything stupid I'd stop if I
were you
really they probably would have already
taking out the guns and start shooting
by
now or bring the
Kines the
Kines is who is
hold
Dar guess
who the
man
what are you doing in
[Music]
Hawaii you your
hair yeah you look
[Music]
different
stop being
[Music]
so what's this charm man it makes me
angry sh
[Music]
the way he
stares yeah I bet he really [\h__\h] to see
his face in
Hawai guess we're going to see a lot
more in this
game
[Music]
he's so
[Laughter]
calm
fore
[Music]
wait was that in guidance or am I
supposed to know
that
did I know
a it was mention in seven
okay I knew yeah it sounds
familiar
[Music]
much is
it it is it
is
[Music]
oh so [\h__\h] up we probably won't know
that she's after aanan for a long time
and they'll like kind of both be chasing
her but for different reasons and then
we'll find her both at the same time or
so and'll be like this K you know and
then he's like oh
okay if she's your mom then
okay yeah I mean if he has to go to ha
wife for
that calling the whole
plot oh my
God we'll have this like big
unspoken miscommunication this whole
time
clearly never going to
mention
I got a big
spoiler yeah maybe it doesn't go that
far but we surely are looking for the
same
person
go to Japanese
Embassy I
guess even if the American police is
looking for him as a Japanese citizen if
he goes through a Japanese Embassy the
moment he steps into it he's
safe right that's how it works right I
was going to say go to Japanese Embassy
oh never mind they're going to like you
know capture you there no
they uh they would hand him
over but if if he makes a good case and
maybe maybe even gets a lawyer the
moment he enters the embassy and tells
like they they understand that he's not
you
know at fault maybe they would side with
him and protect
[Music]
him
yeah yeah he can't really prove in the
moment that he's Japanese citizen
but he did still hit a police officer
yeah but I mean I don't know
[Music]
yeah they would honor a legit
warrant ah oopsy
noop yeah
said the name I only have K know
name he just saw a picture so different
name
yeah finally K you actually looks older
I so you think he didn't die natural
gray
hair
yeah his beard has a few gray hairs I
don't know the hair the top hair looks
kind of dyed but I guess it isn't if his
beard is also
grayish do be 55
huh handsome old man imagine having a
grandpa like this holy
[\h__\h] appreciate the new digs we got the
Hawai sh
in red uh-huh okay red is your color
Choice
okay raan ready to use the
massager he does have a massager but he
did offer massage I wonder if he wanted
to use that thing on
him this store is
real just need a straw hat
yeah anyway sorry to be such a bird
the things that they
sell is this like does it look like
stuff that's actually being sold in
Hawaii like convenience
stores I
wonder real chain of stores
uhhuh like
7-Eleven ABC
Store like a gas station ah where's the
spam
nice when's the last time you
ate forever
ago better not draw attention to
ourselves I know somewhere where we can
lay
L the music he turn the party oh uh they
didn't let me close it until the music
ended that's cute they really wanted me
to hear that
oo oh my God what an
honor same level but he's got a lot more
HP but also less MP
now what about all the equipment I had
are wait is all the equipment that I had
in Yokohama just left on those
characters no I do have this
stuff
oh
six oh that's
mine
Nice N this is
[Music]
good
okay I add was there an auto optimize
button game is very good with not
screwing like that say I wouldn't have
been so mad I would have kind of
understood would have been low accurate
to lose all my [\h__\h] cuz I just lost
everything for
real um how did we get there oh
okay the flipflop
sound his feet sound lighter than before
his his steps sound different I wonder
if it's for real a different
sfx from when he has normal shoes
[Music]
on oh oh there's a weapon shop over
there revolve
bar oh is that our survive bar of
Hawaii after keer R so many people on
the street he gets a taste of
it yeah I guess the drinking lady just
press GP uh on
the nice name
hey the hell you want all I want is a
drink my stepping aside please thirsty I
guess you're going to need to pay to
cover
touch who I I thought these [\h__\h]
were only in Japan shows how much I've
traveled the thing about scum is they
grow in the ugliest parts of just about
everywh huh
you to can talk [\h__\h] all you want but if
you ain't paying you better St
praying ready for
this w wow the living legend kiro's job
Dragon of dojima allows him to switch
between freestyles of fighting
additionally Kio deals increase damage
when attacking nearby enemies oh yeah
brawler Rush P yeah mhm
Nar
ah brawler balanced Rush
speed we had that in Yakuza zero that we
played right the braw style is a well
balanced fighting style with the unique
ability to carry out powerful heat
actions trigger heat actions by
performing basic attacks When
approaching enemies or objects or
meeting certain situational
conditions
Beast is fighting yep probably
did I have to get used to it because
he's going to be around the whole
game I don't really
know
here wait what am I now what does he
now he you
attacks oh wait now he was the I okay
they're forcing me into the style cuz
they're showing me each one the rush sty
may not Exile in raw Power Defense but
it compensates with overwhelming speed
which allows you to turn to come by much
faster and make two basic attacks in
succession capitalize on The Wider range
of movement to close the distance and re
a deadly flurry of attacks on your
enemies however K won't stop to pick up
the nearby objects or perform followup
attacks okay I I might need some time to
really like understand this again
let's see you
try ah change
[Music]
your damn it see you try I didn't expect
Square going to hurt you think I'm a
fool let's see you try damn he's strong
though Beast style the Beast style
sacrifices against
agility a agility and range for attack
and defense with the Beast style your
basic attack becomes a grapple which
deals heavy damage to guard yeah I kind
of remember this despite lacking
Mobility you can dish out the the pain
once and enemy once an enemy gets in
range and make nearby enemy suffer too
let's
go this
one
kah and that's a wrap for this tutorial
switch back to brawler and have cute the
all fs and style okay just try me just
try
[Music]
me dead what
all
Fu going to go for
you congratulations
[\h__\h] you are the chosen
one but I miss the button I need to
learn them
again
OU
I pressed it but too
early well these are Hawaii names
[Music]
H
for oh one another one
[Music]
oh wellow 150 let's go the cover charge
we're taking that
now okay goodbye let us drink
let you have to be careful though some
of them know what they're doing better
safe than sorry especially when it comes
to protecting yourself best carry a
weapon on you don't worry I got a weapon
I guess there are some nasty dudes out
there but a
weapon Yama people over there might be
just a
place they're going to make me buy [\h__\h]
again I don't know if I should you can't
as underestimate s new shops these days
they sell a pretty wide variety and even
the cheaper stuffs good quality should
help us should help give us an
edge a
gun you could probably get some pretty
nice M something pretty nice with the
toll you got from
those okay let's
[Music]
seea all plus
four shoes we kind of need because I
don't have uh any right now plus seven
is pretty good 20 bucks is expensive of
20 bucks is expensive do I really have
to buy something get at least get the
sandals okay okay let's get the shoes
only um for him as well all I need I
already have a
weapon don't you see it kid
you did I not give you the massage yet
after
all you who's going to be our bartender
you
he also can speak Japanese
okay
by the way I have sandwiches as a snack
today but I'm feeling my chocolate snack
right now I only have one left
[Music]
anyway can okay please wouldn't it be
cool if they had like um Hawaii style
remixes for all the songs that are
available us
like a Hawaii remix of
D of like UL
UK that would be so
cute yeah tropical
remix what do we
got what is our
choices
I got to choose right
or it looks exactly like Jo sound it's
Jo
sound it's a legit
K company in
Japan was it joy sound already last
game let me tell you Japan advice for
all future Travelers tourists to
Japan go to Koke go to Japan go to Koke
they have many different Koke companies
there's a few that are very well known
and in any case um within the karoke
let's say for example you go to Kar
can that's a a pretty widespread one and
then often well if you're a tourist and
you you look like you don't know what
you're doing then they probably maybe
they won't even ask you but often they
give you a choice between joy sound or
dumb and then between between those
there's like different database of songs
but I mean really well-known popular
songs are on both usually yeah yeah yeah
but on these uh they also have H life
songs but I think one of them has I
think probably joy sound has more whole
life songs available than Dum d m is the
other
one mhm write it down write it down they
also have a lot of English songs and C
pop they
have
everything but no German
songs which one has Yakuza songs
probably
both there is one of them that has like
more anime songs but I forgot which one
it
is I want the honey toast the honey
toast is m
actually a
specialty of a
k um of a Special
K uh
chain they don't have it in every Koka
place
okay is this one
new oh
no I remember it now
[Music]
and
199 they might have that one
yeah not on this one though cuz this joy
sound is um very biased towards
Yakuza
this one
sounds
[Music]
new I get new ones
later okay let uh judgement
first ah it looks exactly like a kok
screen casual backup passionate backup
uh is that like also like uh influencing
the easiness of the
game that's difficulty okay then I guess
uh wait which one's more difficult
then casual normal pass okay casual
casual oh it's been a while I'm really
bad at this
stuff just
singing
[Music]
together oh that's
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm just
like ult ging at him while he's singing
I'm such a
[Music]
St
I'm so focused this so difficult for me
this is like baby mode
[Music]
for wait I one to watch for the k
I can't watch the
video I hope you guys are enjoying
it it it's out of the corner of my eye
it seems like they're being very
tacher and looking very
cool this is ity bun need your
[Music]
dream judment
Jud it's a
bartender
W
he that's fun
[Music]
though no 86 or 60 what 86 I guess
baleful Tom Jason and mahona Malon
Malone how can I get up to their level
but I guess I didn't do so
bad yeah for first try in a while
another one another one another one
another
one more
more more
[Music]
more oh I'm just sitting on the side now
cuz I
mean shut up
[Music]
you I love
you
[Music]
[Applause]
he really loves the
dog
[Music]
die you suffering he needs a hug a hug
from
[Music]
me
H was that his
dog didn't know he had a
dog
19 let's go even I was
singing I could do even better if I
wanted
to he did get a dog did his dog
die in a game
[Music]
is at his orphanage oh
okay where's
uh this one I think I still know
too oh
yeah is always him singing I guess the
wear one that said my name uh
ichan sometimes I self insert say me and
I talk
[Music]
about
W what's going
on
oh it's so
cool he's rocking in I can barely see it
but he's rocking
[Applause]
in W wo
wo
[Music]
oh nice
pose
sick I had a 133
combo wow 93 I'm getting better and
[Music]
better let's
go one more we want to sing ichon
sing iching M cuz these I guess yeah
they were all cute oh there's only two
ich let's do H
Ste 6686 for hell
[Music]
steel oh the square is coming
in
we want the P Ste rock and
roll ah
[\h__\h] Focus
[Music]
bones death sco
voice
[\h__\h] this is
[Music]
soic the main dish is house
toew
[Music]
get I'm getting it I'm learning the
buttons he looks like the kiss people
right kiss no
[\h__\h] what that
[Music]
GP oh my God they look crazy but I
cannot look at them hey they're in
Hawaii
I thought they stayed in Japan I saw n
didn't
I woo that was difficult that was so
much oh my God
73 yeah it was really
difficult only for the songs oh man
that's so sad I wish you was here right
now all of them one more one more one
more I'm going to waste all my
money you like
hands hand hand okay one more oh it's a
baby hand cheating
[Music]
[Applause]
ever leine song right
[Music]
now never heard
before
[Music]
or like a k
song you're confusing me I need to
[Music]
focus
okay my eyesight is getting blurry now
can't do
more he's cute he the way he Vibes is so
cute oh there
[Music]
[Applause]
more
you can you
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
I love you can you please oh this is
long this is
[Music]
long are those special scenes only
coming when I did something good oh
there we go
[Applause]
[Music]
look prop watch
AR he said a DI is that his child he has
a
child what's going
on
if it was a girl I would say it's K
[Music]
but hey hey this is for K's
Baby he has a
son is adopted daughter's son what oh
that's his grandson wait he has a
daughter what this is his Grand
child
93 that wasn't bad
huh what oh his his daughter is adopted
by him and this is the daughter's real
son is that what she's
saying oh my God so much information
braful time my AR Nemesis one day I'll
get you one day I'll show
you I'll be a bful It Bun that you fear
so
much
nice
CA A lot happened between zero and now
yeah please play more Yak against dude
I'm trying my best this is my third one
and and you know these games take a long
time
and within my whole lifetime I already
played a lot of Yakuza if you think
about
it yes I'm getting deeper and deeper
into it
okay you ready to drink [\h__\h] yeah I'm
done singing my throat hurts let's
drink that was fun it's been a while
since we did Koke in
Yakuza
yeah what this game is as long as yaku
was at one two4
together oh my God you literally played
the verye longest
one oh
no what did I get myself
into the longer the better we say
on
fore ball
Icee
for is guid the
released this like a month or so ago
wasn't there something is that the guid
[Music]
one okay
okay we're not playing that one
busy oh our bond has leveled up doie
doie doie doie as you spend time with
your friends your bond with them will
deepen there lot BL blah BL yeah we know
we
know yeah we don't need guid right yeah
we'll figure it
out
ichan did not learn his lesson of
alcohol this is such a
romance look at this wow look at
[Music]
this I saying you're weak kid
you
can't hold me
easily no other real
back
okay
yeah maybe he should stop drinking for a
little
bit
so
you ready
CH you can now hang out at
revolve yeah cool same as
usual okay
probably won't come so often but maybe
one more time in the
playr at least for cut scenes I'll come
more often but for singing I don't know
if I have time for that if I'm not
mistaken you've got a cro dad on you H
you mean my my my
crab it
is I um seriously considered getting one
of these before and I mean I feel like
maybe in the future I still I I'll
actually get one like I actually wanted
to get a fish tank
remember it's going to get like a blue
one of these
ones
NY guys don't
think don't take an example from ichon
and when you travel overseas think you
can take some kind of [\h__\h] shellfish
alive or dead doesn't even
matter uh through an airplane you can't
okay
Nancy my beloved Nancy blue lobster
again yeah blue blue blue blue I wanted
it to be blue cuz it's nice color
special color
yeah but K Nancy best
pet maybe I don't know if like you can
declare and bring like other pets but
yeah don't try to smuggle it maybe if
you declare it properly you should be
able to bring it but don't try to
smuggle
it in case any of you were ever thinking
about it what if it's a very polite one
don't smuggle
it emotional support
[Laughter]
crawfish ichon doesn't need a crawfishes
emotional support this is
[\h__\h] sorry it actually slips my mind
sometimes wait does this place not allow
animals I don't know if I would put it
in the same category like a dog but
okay
I've had some shellfish recipes in mind
lately in
fact run Nancy
run this one's looking nice
and who wa wow n is part of the team
just not for cooking that's so little
pretty well all leave for a beef you say
so consider a revolve open to her as
well I appreciate it be sure just be
sure keep an eye on her if she want to
do a hot but frying pan while I'm
cooking I can't be held a cannibal canb
I want to speak like tax
person uh yeah she be
careful be
[Music]
like okay that's what you guys are
aha one shot one kill for both ah yeah
she works there man people sure friendly
out here really brightens up your day
welcome to Hawaii
MF
aloh what a pretty lady CH was an an
within a given amount of time remaining
silent either by not selecting an answer
or failing to choose in time is also an
option note that the content of your
answer won't change based on how long
you
take Aloha I'm totally I know what I'm
saying I'm part
from I belong
here I
guess yeah nice to meet you first time
me
[Music]
I told you
serious
she really seems to like K I didn't
think girls went for guys like him of
course they
[Music]
do nice
to very interesting
[Music]
friend the train is [\h__\h]
community
wow
technology is she curious St
did she move over here because of
him we have to protect K you from
[Music]
her
[\h__\h] oh my God I can't believe it
I wonder if that was part of the
pro GE Georgia GG
Georgia
Aloha links has been installed on kazuka
smartphone o Aloha link users are marked
with a special icon over their heads USA
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I I know what
you mean yeah I mean yeah that was I
connected the dots
there is she from
Georgia s and twang yeah wait if you
turn the game
English is she still her own voice
actress and speaks English does she
speak herline
English
ah damn I want to hear that
cool
uh
nice paid twice
baby oh gets paid
twice nice nice
stonks get that bag
yeah uh by using emotes to engage with
these characters you can become friends
with them the friend glass serves as an
indicator of your bond once it's maxed
you and your pal become best bodies as
kasuga gains more of these his
personality will improve so try to make
a lot of friends uh okay I read that and
I I am sorry sorry none of that entered
my brain right now it just went in one
year and left on the other but whatever
it's probably not that
important
you know what he kind of reminds me
of this dude especially in this light
with his cheekbones in that hair he
reminds me
of what's his name
from that
[Music]
anime no h Japanese anime uh what was it
called the hero my hero Academia he
reminds me of the the the guy that uh
the boy looks up to I think that's what
I think I think I'm going thinking of
yeah all
my wouldn't you agree now that I said it
it's like all Mighty to me but like in
casual
undercover undercover all the
might
press wow so
bubbly but you don't like him as much as
you like do
[Music]
you oh nice that looks good Kasa bronze
member what's new you're now friends
with
bartender I
for
[Music]
okay did she say the same line in
English
she says it like that friends coming out
you
[\h__\h] it's almost as if she came up
with the script
herself
Maybe
she's out there living her best life in
Hawaii
man see
[Music]
you nice yeah she probably add lips that
whole tangent about
K welcome to Hawaii [\h__\h]
it's very
personalized the dog I can be friends
with the dog now and the and the CLE cat
[Music]
too there's Clips what there's clips
of some Aloha links users are friended
through actions rather than simple
greetings you can raise your friendship
with them in various ways such as giving
them gifts or patronizing the business
the world can be a dangerous place
sometimes you'll come across friends
from aloh links and distress if you're
ready for a fight you can try dispersing
there would be a silence your Mutual is
sure to be highly
appreciative check the profiles and
friendship meters of your friends and
best buddies for the elings app on your
smartphone is this some like overall an
important system in the game or is it
just like a side
thing okay K you sorry for the wait uh
done talking to my stalker all right yes
sir all right the car I'm using over at
my hotel uh the car I'm using over at my
hotel we'll go straight there just some
side thing but it's cute okay just FL it
does bump your stats oh
okay okay sounds good let's get
going
so good oh look so
nice Hawai I feel like
GTA like one of future GTA's maybe might
play in Hawaii too I can see
it GTA 9 in
Hawaii it's actually I feel like it
could be a good
place to have a yeah a good set next one
is Miami
and let's take a ride or should we walk
but the taxi right there I think the
game is asking be there in a hot minute
we'll be there in a hot
minute yeah I know I said one that's far
in the future on purpose oh I look at
the beans I look at the beans
oh let's get
started W he came all of the s
oh yeah that happens every now and then
on the beach there a common occurrence
be careful in the sand
guys happens
happens happens to the best of
us
careful blind
no wait why is people
de oh what
well you guys can't see it but he's dead
why is he why is he
dead it was an instant kill
what thank God I oh
my thank God
[Music]
I I'm scared can I maybe
run if I don't block well yeah why why
is it not working with I press it on the
moment uhoh there we
go [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I swear I pressed it but I
feel like I'm pressing it too on point I
need to press it
earlier how can we run can I run oh
yeah
yeah the sand
people you know there's a way to summon
them but never use it because you know
you saw what
happens the song to summon them
is I don't want to sing it because it'll
come
again
for Sandman
song is there an auto heal
no
[Music]
tuna I'm using up all my
food the water looks definitely much
nicer
now oh he does get nak it nice out of
the ocean you can paddle around break
into the brisk front crawl blah blah
blah if it's items you're looking for
investigate in light make sure to mind
your surroundings you'll take damage if
you're hit by any passing
B oh fun yo the water is so
wobbly
wa
over
there someone's drowning oh my God hero
it's the time for the
hero no someone's faster than
me can't believe
it I'm be a
hero that's such a weird way of saving
him
a LIF guard but I'm I'm supposed to be
saving
people everyone speaks Japanese now
yeah even the blonde white
guys
[Music]
for get it I'm a lifesaver
too
not
I saved lives all over the
world
[Music]
Japan yeah [\h__\h]
yeah no when I say I
I that much of a
her I'll save you guys'
life you don't know it yet but you're in
danger
CPR that's not
how you're having a hard
challenge
for let me do it let me
a don't worry I'll help you I'll make
you lose your
job
for facep face
[Music]
face way
left
what now yeah
okay like a mini game like like like one
of those Resturant games but instead
serving people you sa
[Music]
people how's this work
okay do have hydrate people suffering
from heat stroke within 3 minutes it's
like a restaurant game isn't it search
for anyone on the beach who seems weak
or unwell find them and hand over some
cool fresh refreshing water okay I drank
too much I'm feeling
D
here does the time stop when I talk to
them seems like it yeah
okay nice found one immediately nine
more
my vision my vision is
blurry Goku Goku
Goku what uh important to stay hydrated
are you saying you need to be hydrated I
know why am I so lied ah cuz you need
water drink drink drink drink I think
I'm pretty fast I think I'm pretty good
at
this they can't be in the water right
they should be all on the beach
right I'll run back to that person if I
can't find one more it's important make
sure ah okay okay yeah yeah yeah I don't
think that person needs water cuz a lot
of people are saying it like that
earthquake go these people in Hawaii
really need to
hydrate if it's good going that far the
mini map shows them oh [\h__\h] I didn't
realize
I oh but aren't they all blue what
should I what drink should I try no
no this one they're all
blue even the ones that you don't need
to
help they're so
bursting it's important to cool off my
head is burning up oh sleeping from jetl
that one's a a tricky one but no no no
you're not getting any water at least
not for
free four more ah dizzy
dizzy oh or should I give the that
there's also a drunk dude over there he
also needs water I don't know if that
counts he needs it for different reasons
that
one that one over there I don't
know we'll see about
it does he need it too guys he'll be
okay oh he'll be
okay he's
coffee I mean I feel like I would I
would want to give him water
but oh okay here's the cut
off don't walk away so
slowly when he's at the corner of that
the the map there then it will walk so
slowly [\h__\h] I need two more people maybe
it does
CR maybe I should give him
water ah two more and I can't find
him did it go to the other side too
feels hot well you're working out
dude
a you passed a lot from earlier didn't
you think the Hawaiian Sun would be so
harsh
no that's kind of B
right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] should I does it count does that is
that can I have it
wrong or do does he just not give it to
them drunk guy too okay
okay
okay drunk guy oh there's two drunk guys
though let get some water and head back
he probably okay he tells me he tells
me
uh what about this one he even Hicks I
like people who hick I don't know why
but something about people hicking
really gets
me no okay [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm running out of
time I just probably not him either but
I'll talk to him no he'll be
okay no I asked him already losing wait
oh that one that one the working out
one
it wasn't the trunk people it was the
working out I feel like the working out
people they're kind of asking for it the
the drunk ones I should have given the
drunk ones the water I feel like they
needed more cuz these people they still
have control and over
themselves he was still even working out
like he could easily just walk over and
get
water hi
[Music]
a he must be feeling hot
though those clothes
[Music]
yeah yeah I did it it was a close one
though the beginning
was
nice thank
you
if I look really hydrated on the
Honolulu Beach you think that actually
give me free water I
[Music]
don't emotional music emotional
words pass
out
nice hey we finished we did one
side I just wanted to check out the
ocean he he's got a D can I breathe hey
doesn't
I can't cre all of them
so let me go into the water for a little
bit without being distracted by a
quest yeah purple I I don't know if I'm
ready for
purple
seaweed night that like right
away
o mysterious seaweed if eaten raw gives
me 10
HP good
work welcome to
theu oh my God there's so much trash in
the
ocean I'm doing a really good deat
here
oh
no he you swimming too is he
to oh
my
oh you swimming in the woby water
looking oiled
up
M maybe you know K what we forgot we
forgot to put some sunscreen on our bag
should I put some on yours you put some
on mine says
each not me this is ichan talking don't
misunderstand I I think uh K is quite
charming and all that but I'm not I'm
not that crazy about him I will
acknowledge his charm
though does have a
charm the watercolor is so nice it's too
wobbly six out of
oh my my girl I don't know I mean yeah I
kind of uh like my my things didn't I
but out of all of the wasn't there a
different guy that I was more into out
of all of the uh
people who was it
again hey [\h__\h] no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no not
pink number is quite nice too
yeah okay I I don't even remember what
that person looks like but I
guess that must have
been the the
guy oh that's
possible there there's like only pink
enemies here
now maybe they are On My Level now
I'm on their
level hello
bir oh that was a bad guy yeah I know I
know that I remember oh there's some red
ones let's get some
exp what you looking at what you looking
at what you looking
at what you looking at what you looking
at what what you looking
[Music]
at black mail Damon Barney and Dan stick
look at him he moves like a
crab moves like a
[Music]
Crabb and why did I only get like two
hits in
h trap
music [\h__\h]
you didn't know that you're not supposed
to look at
your you're not supposed to not look at
your
opponent I've had to learn that lesson
[Music]
too [\h__\h] but okay it worked
give it back give me my money
no he was so
[Music]
funny now ially pressed earlier but also
that didn't go
well this one's a
do oh he's surfing in this
imaginary
surfing nice nice okay
oh good give me that
exp give me
some more red ones over there
and we got to go
here Family Market
pitch oh a side
quest damn
it
walking is my M I get a
mount did we have
a
wants why does he have so many Bandits
cuz he falls down on it all the
time
he's a
clutz Shing the
street other
choices pretty
only this
one
[Music]
roll
yeah yeah yeah I'm buying it
[Music]
yeah
okay
okay so that's what the bandages are all
about
give me give me give me once you obtain
a street server you can ride it by
pressing down and get around fast by
riding if you press R2 and set the
server to Auto crse it will
automatically panal you to a destination
wow okay who says roads aren't
wave look at him on the on the street
server looking so cool not totally not
like a 40y old midlife crisis Cho
Yakuza of course we'll take
it while riding the street server press
R2 to engage to other the
[Music]
Cruis oh my Gody
it's amazing look can
go he's so cool isn't he right tell him
he looks cool otherwise he he'll feel
like a
loser looks fun though really
Dolphins
so
no they're sitting on this Sur
no how dare you I'm going to punch you
in your face because you said bad things
about some
technology no you can't hurt it it has
feelings
too now he's the biggest
fan
it okay sound like
fun
damn yeah [\h__\h] on a little piece of
technology and look what trouble you're
in
suddenly really should have stayed quiet
there BS
come yeah it did work but I still can't
get the inputs
[Music]
right wait he's [\h__\h]
strong thank
[Music]
god oh there he
is
good job uhoh
uhoh [\h__\h] you you're
HP
[Music]
ouch yeah it's turn base kind of yeah
yep yep as you can
[Music]
see is this
strong next to the
children it's not like we're really
stronger as a brawler are we we're not
going to do necessarily more
damage oh back attack ah
[\h__\h] too
late we turned around only for a
moment help me yeah thank you so
T I love that nice action uhoh holy
[\h__\h] Beast is the best you think
so Rush are better for K
now
okay yeah if someone's
guarding oh right it was alien I forgot
that's
good how much is
it that's a hug charging
station Streeter consumes battery run
motion you can charge and customize your
street Sur you can customize
them
I always
have sking I'm just trying to save time
this is a long playthrough okay and it's
not really important I kind of like
still when I see
something that looks important I can
still somewhat register through it and
stop
[Music]
skiing no oh my God you said it would be
fine
Mama
m nah nah I'm not taking criticism on
that I was 100% fine to skip this this
was just side stuff we're just G given
amount
[Music]
okay so we were going to go over there
okay we to fight we're really low on HP
so ideally not need to heal
[Music]
anyway uh where do you where do you heal
in this game if you don't want to use
items is there a
way oh yeah restaurant yeah but it also
costs money huh is there no free heal
like in
dungeons
oh
Yumm ah it's the bar okay uh anyway
where going
there hey wait oh got a message from K
nice linking out there hi
itan hi hi
hi hi hi hi no I
can't I was creeping on your profile and
saw how many friends you made you must
be having fun there's some more app
stuff I can tell you about it rolve come
talk to me bring
K bring
you nice
try oh we're riding oh
yeah
ooh better prep first I don't like that
sign it's like I should probably buy
some stuff should
I like um
[Music]
food are we going into a
dungeon sa first we have all the
same
indeed this is
it grinded a bit
maybe it's a nice
[Music]
place I think a place like this in
Hawaii
damn it did look like Alexis I was
totally thinking that I was lowkey
thinking
that what is kuu
thinking Milli you mean this
place well
literally right at the
beach you're going to show on
thect is this who you're looking
for interesting
reveal
[Music]
I wouldn't
have I have to kill her
says
[Music]
he didn't keep that misunderstanding for
a long time huh uhoh someone's
coming
oh ooh those
peopleold it's [\h__\h] hot
man oh God I hope I won't die in this
fight
to
poor
boy he is in quite a
predicament
maybe they know him he be on their side
or something so he doesn't want to be
seen or
something no they recognize
him he looks so
funny
GTA in Hawai H purple
guy H let's kidnap
him man just come to our side join
us okay I heard
you is he going to drive and I'm going
to be dealing with this
alone no kidnap
him force him to join
us he's so scared
[Music]
yeah cuz of the hit in his rip
cage gun be
friendly
huh
fore
foree one of us one of
[Music]
us
fore
surprised the others didn't find us
yet
yeah a oh kiss now kiss
kiss oh better cut
scene wow what a scene with K in
[Music]
the from the beginning I
knew join us
[Music]
no something about his character design
just
screams that he'll be I didn't I don't
know it's probably on the cover right
but I I didn't really look at it closely
I mean I didn't even know Kitty was on
the cover
he probably is on
there I didn't even
know at
[Music]
all yeah but yeah his face is detailed
and he's wearing a purple
shirt kind of a
positive
we'll help you we'll help you I'll save
[Music]
you yeah is you see it
now the gray
hair do these two you meet in a
different
[Music]
game
okay well he wants
back his
protagonist
got to say some cool [\h__\h] he son n
N9
[Music]
yeah
aim well he tried he was turning
[Music]
around you did the right thing
yeah like I can't
believe
he's like I can't believe they made a
whole game almost
without newb as the new protagonist I'm
taking back my title I'm important I'm
the most important person here
okay what you got luck launcher battery
sh the tire
tumbler enemy area
[Music]
AOE [\h__\h] okay wait it didn't work as Al
should I have chosen the the one that's
thir Fest in the
[Music]
front for this one I choose the one f is
in the back
[Music]
right M for the tire the one on the
front Okay
okay let's get the let's get the
[Music]
one yeah yeah yeah that's what I was
hoping for and they're still on the
ground
woo
okay
one block at
[Music]
least
[\h__\h] wait he looks like Johnny Deb not
anymore in that light he looked like
Johnny Deb holy
[\h__\h] okay let's finish this
guy did you see it did you see
it oh hi Raiders hello we're in a pretty
cool fight right now we just had a great
Revelation spoiler alert but we still
early in the
game
quick damn it no no death body is
[Music]
paralyzed
can I shoot through
no huh
wait was what I
expected oh this was part of the
[Music]
demo AOE they're so
close uh like him maybe
did it even hitch that guy at all the
one that's
paralyzed pretty sick
[Music]
though how come it didn't hit the other
guy man okay
well still got another turn it did CHP
okay
yeah okay that went fine do we get to
fight yamay now otherwise a big
deal no need to
grind is it
time you want some of
this huh it was the right call but the
car was in the
way oh we're leaving
lame I didn't even finish those
guys and our nice car we're leaving it
behind that was K's car
right
hey we're Bros
now cute yep yep yep we're creating an
idle group that's what what the colors
are about red
purple it's just KY who is too cool to
wear a colored Haw
shirt I
am don't tell anyone it's a
secret
I hope he can keep a
secret little
Japan
fore for
yeah
speee
foreign
[Music]
foree
spe
[Music]
for spee
spee
spee what did she
do my
[Music]
for and then there
was [\h__\h] me
over stand all over my
[Music]
junks that could have just been [\h__\h]
yeah no she's
running so many
Mysteries
also if
sat
foree
[Music]
yay we got a
friend I liked him since the beginning
even though he scammed us and wanted to
kill us but he he has no balls so he
couldn't kill us but we'll give him some
balls we'll teach him we'll teach
[Music]
him new party M oh my God free
people we can have a real party
soon okay where are we
going here Kos Hotel oh I will uh oh
wait that can't take a out
okay this
way whenever the chapter ends I think
that's the end for
today what is
this so
sparkly what is
it best Fortune die k take it to C up at
The Shrine and you can exchange it for
four Fortune points
okay Shrine
[Music]
fortune that costume what the [\h__\h] is
that oh that's s it went thanks for
picking it up
pal a a bunny
cute kind of
cute je don't scare me me like that
don't SC you you're the one in the giant
monster suit
monster hey I resented I'm the world
famous calop jerk don't you know I'm
posted up at The Shrine here oh cop
that's that weird C mascot
right wait is that you
ichang yeah who are you have
met of course we met back in oklahama
you collected all those too Clan crests
from
me I don't remember this
thing you also erased it from your exist
from from your brain me too me
too I don't remember you never didn't me
me neither I
guess no I don't remember
that to keep to Clan relics out of enemy
hands back then he said he was wearing
the calope outfit to hide from the only
Alliance right you're that former too
man under
there I knew you wouldn't forget long
time no see but how nuts is it to run
into each other again here out of all
places yeah sure is wait does that mean
you're still out hunting down Crest in
Hawaii ha no no my respects to the clan
have been paid that chapter of my life
is close for Good I figured it was time
to make uh a brand new start somewhere
else you know as well as I do that us
total guys have things to atone for
maybe so yeah although it it kind of
feels like you're dragging the past
along with you when you still got that
costume on oh this what can I say had
the damn thing on so long not now I feel
naked without
it you probably even went on the plane
like this but took up like two seats at
[Music]
least it's got its benefits though the
priest here he says I make for good
Shrine master got the pays nothing to
sneeze on so now I can make a buck while
staying true to my art plus this outfit
brief surprisingly well in the tropics
really I don't believe it I don't buy
it looks hot wearing a Camal up costume
is your art now well I far be it for me
to judge in honest day work good Lu out
there who who
wait the and you found a second AG go if
you see any more around you think you
could bring him
here I really wanted to impress at this
job so I imported a boat load up the
sucker straight from Japan all
officially Shino blessed they shipped to
my house and I walked over here with
them except well I had a lot of errands
to run and I kind of took the scen
grab oh by the time I got to the shrine
the whole back was empty thing had a big
old hole in it down think I'm starting
to see what is
going I took an advance on my salary to
buy so many I literally don't think I
can live without them plus you know they
make the kids around here
smile don't ask me don't ask me I'm
begging you this little paper SS have
probably scattered all over the island
by now and obviously I can't just
abandon my pose to go out looking for
them
H you understand I can't pay you for
this MoneyWise but I also ordered a ton
of prizes to trade for them we'll do it
on points well it might be exactly as
optional as the previous one huh and
then we don't have to do
it oh sounds of beaches oh okay four
points for best Fortune three for Good
Fortune two for modest fortune and one
for a bad fortune makes sense doesn't it
there weren't that many bad fortunes
mixed in with the bunch but I'll make
sure sure it's worth it for you to find
them I mean I get the feeling you're not
here on vacation you know am I wrong
wink
link poor a guy stuck in a green in
corporate ft he's actually pretty
shrewd anyway May the gods bless you
search you see them everywhere just go
to yeah I'll pick it up like any other
item I
guess
so oh oh
oh oh was one right
there all right I think we have to fight
these do you want suckers I'll sue
you Su
me I guess let's do some AOE I hope it
hits maybe here on
him
what was that was I on the right
[Music]
thing I need proximity for AOE okay okay
birs come
[Music]
upy going
to hold
[Music]
W nice
collaboration he like shot me in my
head just try
me
[Music]
go
on this is the
[Music]
end what he didn't
shoot what was
[Music]
that was like fake out or
something oh [\h__\h] I did AOE still even
though I didn't wasting my
time so he will shoot next
time you're not so
tough guys well is there something you
want me to do for members only tomorrow
like a game with yes what
you want me to start right away I think
we all need some time to prepare
that no I I would want to give you more
of a heads up for that one
um wouldn't watch wouldn't mind the
enime for real I mean but I don't
know really Ain a not a
wait not out
of get my mp healed up
[\h__\h] wait they're in a beautiful line uh
uh uh the front ah they moved so shitty
of
them I hate that
give it your best sh oh he's weak to
it
sexy I thought we were going to
watch oh yeah that's also something we
wanted to watch so many
watchong Indiana Jones would probably be
easier to prepare I think isn't it maybe
even on Disney
plus
huh nice my
body you know
please I'm down for that maybe that's
what we'll do then um we can also CH
chat of course before and
[Music]
after wa only yeah makes sense I I think
I was on an Indiana Jones ride in
Disneyland
before
oh is that even worth it
[Music]
no you making fun of
me and might not fair why is he similar
to Han
Solo
oh it's same act oh well that doesn't
matter as long as the personality is
different not exactly the same
[Music]
personality we we we'll
see does he act like a pickup artist
this Indiana Jones guy cuz Han Solo
certainly acted like
a yeah I'm not going to comment too much
on it because you guys love Han
Solo is this uh is this my the bar say a
oh he's
different he's a he's a chaser they're
both rogish types H has this
Swagger you know on the lookout for
trouble he's literally asking for
trouble I hear Japan's a safe country
but in Hawai things can go R real quick
once you Veer off the main trust me you
don't want to mess with these people
they don't know the meaning of a their
fight ooh a crown icon they will hang
around until you defeat them new areas
may open up once they're finally gone
but beware that they're substantially
stronger than normal accounts okay okay
interesting yeah maybe another
time sounds kind of
scary wait where the [\h__\h] is the hotel d
h I'm trying to follow the
arrow best to avoid them for now
okay
MP I don't have [\h__\h] I need to go
shopping oh there's a there's a shop
over there there's
people I right in front of it you asking
for
a let me in let me
in finally a safe Zone okay I'm here to
spend a lot of money please
Aloha Al
aloha aloha to you too um is 100 like
but too much uh still I wonder I'll take
it oh God we need
money we need money so bad okay H may
have been a little bit
too
[Music]
much oh that looks yummy that do looks
yummy although I don't really like it
when people turn croissant into
sandwiches like that actually I feel
like they should be sweet I don't like
um Savory sandwiches uh uh Savory quas
quas quasa Emoji quas quas Emoji now now
or never
guys 100 Grand money let's get the
original mus be oh these are
cheap these are really
cheap nice
201 thank you but they're great some
yeah I mean they're not bad I've eaten
them before and enjoyed them but gen I
would prefer them with
some more crunchy bread you
know this
one hello you
ask Aloha to YouTube
Sir oh
W moner soda
mustard no understanda would like that
one
banana I should
take for the worst
situation nothing has yet to top
that yeah I mean in
Sans the land of the
qu oh thank God there's a cut scene cuz
I was going to run into those
[Music]
enemies
from a coconut
tree you guys have no idea about
naturee
way
he's so mad let's go get
him we need the money to pay the hotel
dude probably notics this area pretty
good there you
go
what's live without a game of Chase now
and again is that going to happen
several times navigate obstacles by
moving blah or pressing
x r automa so get going okay X and
triangle x triang x is on the bottom
triangle is at the top God damn
it
the arrow went to the right but
I I I I moved it to the left
[Music]
what it still
works okay this kind of fun we don't
need to do it too often in my opinion
uh
Sanic nice
Tommy good job never mind he
sucks still need to grow those
balls
who
Savage that was pretty
cool ke didn't even break a
sweat
that was
intense I don't like you did you come
from the mainland yeah not here a guy
like me won't die of
exposure there's work here too at least
that's what I
heard
yeah for real for
real Let It Go I mean I would let
it probably wouldn't even get to this
point
La I always he
la
people kind of expensive to send almost
person give them the money and let them
where they be where they
are
what it's a
ser
[Music]
kind of messed up
sending people to other states cuz you
don't want to deal with them and
creating a homeless crisis
elsewhere
[Music]
no because real mates go like more and
more cute and they'll make you some om
and all that so if she didn't do that
then she's not a real
M trust me I
know
for okay she'll join our team
[Music]
to
for how dare
he
T what you guys all
saying Jeff name is
[Music]
Jeff in the next chapter please no in
the next chapter not
[Music]
now I need to go to ID
meeting
[Music]
exactly
what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
fore
also real
problem police just [\h__\h]
off [\h__\h]
they are scary I would be scared of
[Music]
f
yeah I'll take care of you hey I'm
walking here not so fast [\h__\h] beg
your pardon thought you'd get away with
it huh what's in your
hand pocket uh uh
taking
away oh
[\h__\h] but don't they all have a homeless
background don't they CR you know like
poor hom you know they do they do these
things you know I mean yeah it's not
great but you know you know you've been
in the same place
before no you just want to [\h__\h] kill
him
what they're on homeless yeah maybe not
right now but it did say that a lot of
these they have like a homeless
background they've been almost at least
once
probably is not what they
said Just Another Day in
Paradise they dragged him into the alley
up not going hurry I thought the chapter
was ending
uh
one my mp isn't heal wait can I eat over
there don't don't look at me don't look
at me why are the enemies always where I
don't want them to
be Donuts aloha
aloha combo meals are thing
again oh [\h__\h]
yeah I did go to a hawaian
food place in uh
Tokyo last year and I ate some amazing
pancakes
fruity pancakes covered in a [\h__\h] ton of
fruit not necessarily a Hawaiian food
but seems like it's kind of their thing
I mean look at
this oh look pancakes PES I did make
pancakes today I made them without even
going by a recipe again I just I just
whenever I make these pancakes I just
mix it by feeling until it has a a good
texture one banana one egg some cinnamon
some vanilla sugar some baking powder uh
a a little bit of milk most of the
recipes for banana pancakes don't use
mil don't use milk but I added a little
bit and then yeah flour flour flour
flour
flour yeah banana p and then I top them
with a
Nutella but not the real Nutella I I use
fake
Nutella uh this is for all of us right
uh I don't know
uh all of this fills us up fully right
okay oh um except
for the
drinks
uhuh combo meal I don't know I don't
want know if I can really I spend so
much money on a combo
meal let me get
this is that okay if I don't take a
combo is that
okay
French I had the worst ever French toast
during my break I was so
disappointed I saw this restaurant which
was literally like advertising it's
french
toast on like the outside of the
building I was like okay I'll go there
and get French sometime and then I went
there and then there the French toes and
eventually it looked fine but the bread
was just
so
hard and I could barely C through like
it was so difficult to cut
through weird like you're supposed when
you make French toast like yeah you can
use hard bread or like even use like
soft bread and then like toast it before
and then let it soak up everything but
it's not supposed to end up being hard
still so bad and then I thought the
topping was nice but turns out it was
like actually not so nice after all it
was like too much way too much but the
bread was so [\h__\h] like what the [\h__\h] I
was like I'm never going to eat here
again and then the waiter asks you like
ah did you like it I'm like yeah thanks
I can't even say but I was so close cuz
it was so
bad like to a certain extent you could
still say yeah yeah it was fine but it
was so bad I was so close to saying no
it was actually really
[\h__\h] I'll teach you how to make real
friends
toast
someday yeah the Brad texture is
important I mean I've I've had a lot of
like different kind of French toast like
everybody makes it
differently but this was [\h__\h]
yeah should have just said no I really
should have just said
no and I even still tipped can you
believe it tipping is not even like as
obligatory in Austria as it is in
America well yeah I still tipped a
little bit but we don't like tip so much
even if we tip I would say we just like
I usually just round up a little bit
Yeah the tip is for the way and not the
chef right depends on the place but if
you genuinely didn't like the food if it
was objectively bad I don't think you
need to
tip in my opinion cuz that's what you go
to a restaurant for for the food if it's
[\h__\h]
objectively then
no come on leave his
ass yeah what [\h__\h] shouldn't be
advertising your French toast outside of
the
door M too late
so
bad
what
[Applause]
what for [\h__\h] pick poock is
[Music]
in
for pancake break was too
long oh my God that's like
insane
ins yeah okay I understand that the
police is scar of
[Music]
that
is it not like reasonable or possible or
useful
to involve
thebi what the
hell
they usually have a relationship yeah
but if the police had a
choice I think they wouldn't want to
necessarily support
that just doing it because it's like
they're too powerful but if they could
take them down
easily isn't that what they would want
to
do
is the FBI even allowed to operate in
Hawai I mean it's America
right no gain from it I mean less less
dead people should be a good
gain still hung up on what they did or
the fact that they got away with it give
away dwelling on it once all the
damn right much as I want to stop them
we need to focus on the task in hand
this guy Jeff you mentioned he deals in
stolen goods yeah from a taco truck up
on VI Kiki Street it's a bit north of
here you guys ready to no no I'm not
tomorrow chapter
and
please ramble while you amble walking
for yeah that's what I was what I was
trying to run towards on the map yeah
the party chat having a Walkin talk with
someone will fill an entry in their bond
Bingo
he wait how do you do this I'm here I'm
here h
it's like
a can walk
[Music]
right
for wrong
direction okay cool he's really into
science ah oh that's what that's what
the Bingo looks like he reads a
challenging book when he can't
sleam does that
help
okay that's kind of cute
that kind of makes me want to fill it
[Music]
out wait I know how do
I how do I use
it was there a special button I have to
press to activate it
down ah thank
[Music]
you yo I want one of these now don't
think you can get away from
me ah they're jealous of my school
I'm so
far at least Tommy is running
over nice
collaboration if you want one you got to
buy one I'm not giving you
my
do come on let's try this again like
like
the probably can only get
two go go go what's the
button
nice come up make my way to
my a big very
important
nice
ah you think you're
[Music]
tough oh still not dead can I car drive
over him
please go one
more maybe a little bit
overkill on the second attack I can Cho
style
[Music]
oh didn't you want to stop soon yeah but
IAP should end
soon waiting for just a nice place to
stop would be nice I don't need to go
that don't
worry wait do the others also get one
they do
look something about all of us riding it
it's really funny to me we're like
supposed to be these super strong adult
men some of us retired yakas or still
[Music]
yakas saving the world saving people
what are you looking
at and this is how we how we travel the
world going to
[Music]
cry this is how we
roll
uh the the one in the back
right I got all of
them
what what what why
B I don't we didn't get a ra
way
[Music]
you guys confus me so much because a
raid from uh formal isn't even that
unlikely
generally
[Music]
nice you guys it's not the first time
you confused me like
this I want to see what they sell over
here
oh wait that's why I supposed to go
anyway do you have a lot I'll give you
50 bucks for it oh come on this is a
genuine driver's license it's got to be
worth at least
70 50 bucks take it or leave it I doubt
someone else that even give you a time
of
day fine T ass I want a
taco
fore
for how
much how
much oh that's cheap
that's not so much why are we acting
like it's
we
[Music]
need Gary's love cam pound
M wait
like
isn't there something similar in
America
bring that's what they
right say Japanese
delivery
number one what a coincidence I'm also
number
one join my
team teammates want to
get nothing
weird
mush hi mush mushy G love
C
oh my God
amazing go thank
[Music]
you
fore okay there
Wy oh wait those are the ones that fight
for me
[Music]
right that's what they
found
he's
checking let's
go she's
free
ofai okay but I'm not in a fight so what
they already going to
help so she's just going to be a p mate
not
actually
[Music]
teammate
no first
timer there's no [\h__\h] about dating
there's no [\h__\h] about
technology the only thing he knows is so
blend is that really her
wrong CH
maybe does sound like
her from above look
up yeah that's not
her
Coco yeah that's not her but same
hairstyle oh my god let's go she will
protect
[Music]
me
for also like
chuckling cuz he actually thinks that's
really her nope that's not
[Music]
her
miscommunication
well she does have the bra hair look at
[Applause]
[Music]
her no it's okay
you can join the team too you look
strong no no no she will stay in front
of
us
forer
help
helpe let's
go
what will be her move welcome back to
pound town on the party leader turn you
can summon pound mates for Help by
pressing R1 these are powerful allies
with a wide range of abilities but their
assistance carries a fee the price
depends on the P mate and will increase
depending on the rank and how many times
you request them within the same fight
okay remember
R
fee okay
[Music]
well Al I have to call her now she's
already she was there I want to man
okay shy
[Music]
pound
b oh it's free but I can't chose with
Benefits now got to be
without is it AOE
[Music]
yeah oh
it's very very
happy
[Music]
be
wo
[Music]
delivery ready sound let's go let's go
let's
go
but just not hitting the one in the back
so
[Music]
sad to
long is she still going to be able to
attack oh she's still there oh ah it
says two on the bottom on her phone so
maybe she gets two more turns
[Music]
this
all
right she got stal man we can learn from
her I aspire to be like her one
day oh that's
it oh no never mind I thought the trophy
means chapter over but that would be a
weird end
of
fore
very
goodbye what a
woman don't you want a woman that beat
you up like
[Music]
her no
stop
yes
yes nice only you can beat me
up I guess I I can with this B I
can looks like we're going to need to
come up with some cash after all how
much did you say we need 30 bucks no poo
give or take that's the ballpack range
oh and if you couldn't guess I'm
broke
right I don't think I've got anything
either wait
huh what's up what do you know turns out
I do have
cash why don't you just say so thanes
care of
that let's be like Jeffs well it might
be it might solve the Jeff problem but
we don't know what to expect there after
we are to save some for future
H think such a big deal out of
this
what kind of under the table work have
you done does picking up cans on a bik
ah yeah they're just doing this because
they're trying to introduce us to game
like money mini games and the
[Music]
pounding so food delivery oh o
o we already saw an advertisement for
that in uh in Yokohama but I wonder cuz
that was I think wasn't that the
original logo must have gotten
permission from Uber
e maybe
even financial compensation from Uber
for
[Music]
advertisement
oh
Uber you can sign up for email and once
you're approved go wait by Ala Beach I
could just shoot that email for you save
you the
hassle okay it's not like I need it that
badly but
okay make some cash at oh my
[Music]
God
imagine a standoff between kidu and a
chicken honly it might have already
happened
[Music]
before
it's really unnecessary most players
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's a weird timing
what are you looking
[Music]
at or is this where
it is that the collaboration name OFA
and
for wow okay you're too good for it
she got to do everything on your
[Music]
own
oh greenhair crazy
man
Che here's the guy in
Washington uh who does I don't know my
algorithm is full of that guy's delivery
videos cuz I watch one now I see them
all the
time he's got some mad biking skills
delivering Uber all over
Washington have you seen
him he's from Crazy Taxi Crazy Taxi r
[Music]
ah
yeah you
[Music]
shorty he also got an English
ACC crazy
okay you guys mind if I
[Music]
some it's story it's not
story
understand
okay okay
sorry I got a cute
outfit first you need to grab the food
try riding the bike straight into some
okay okay collect and meals
R2 wobbly wobbly wobbly wobbly
[Music]
wobbly was
easy now for what say the crazy start
off by pedaling I don't want new
drinks now you've got some speed try
pulling up a trick oh God this is like
snowboarding
czy uh
[Music]
down a free trick czy combo when you hit
stuns in succession you start to end an
extreme state of
mind uh perfect timing bro customer
alert right near him how how
how
super
super okay nice is this how is this a
test to become a Uber driver sheesh
intense is that what they do on their
deliver
ready I didn't think they were pulling
stunts and all that no wonder my drink
SP oh my
[Music]
God turn
around
Pizza where
is oh he need what what [\h__\h] ah get me
out of here wait I can do a jump right
[\h__\h]
oh ah
[\h__\h] um that one I can take probably can
I no wait red does that this one this
one I can
take
yah
dely delivery that's supposed to be your
job
[Music]
guys
[Applause]
that's I think I blue is that good
you're
de but she not that much money
[Music]
huh okay okay okay okay good my quot is
4,000 holy [\h__\h] I'm so
Dum uh
[Applause]
hey this this guy this guy is good
250 take this burger and enjoy have a
nice meal tip me
[Music]
well Pizza he want pizzas he want Burger
oh we still got
time we only T was deliver that's some
nice work splits I like
it what not
[Music]
enough maybe now it's enough turn
around
okay okay okay
okay nice one the one behind us too the
sushi
[Music]
one yeah
styl great
delivery I want that get let's party
let's
[Applause]
party [\h__\h] they all want something
else ah [\h__\h]
ah
up no one
[Music]
here
[Applause]
[Music]
Pizza
uh this one at
least collected way too much sushi for
nothing I'm not ignoring him wait this
is the wrong way right no I'm want to
try
again fun though this is pretty
fun I had so many pizzas I was Hing them
no
no [\h__\h] but hey we got over
4,000 I want to try it again that was
kind of
fun I wasn't I
wasn't oh the red color Oh I thought it
was because I don't have enough yet
[Music]
excellent what 30 bucks for that oh my
God
really oh my God wait how do I do it
again
oh please one more
time
go a that was
easy the quote on this one is 7,5 a c
rank I'll I'll I'll
try should I do normal
or should have done more tricks for tips
I would trying but sometimes he didn't
do the trick he would just
jumped
why are you ready
ready de but do I have to
[Music]
that was good that was good that was
good Prett pretty
[Music]
dope the [\h__\h] is that red
thing genius genius
[Music]
already doing way better
no have
[Music]
enough yes I do yes I do I'm not
ignoring him this
time
the sushi
[Music]
Doo I don't know what it does bonus time
okay
genus ex wait up
give it to him give
it no what was
that I was I was
stuck which way which way let's go this
way
W wo oh de who wouldn't want the
delivered by Takashi kiaha The Stunt
Master I didn't see you
there didn't know they were on the
[Music]
beachi she
does hurry up I thought we already did
enough
7,500 oh I want to go that way
no oh I can go for the
bushes I didn't know that
before
[Music]
the
F oh can we get
[Music]
10, what the
[\h__\h] good oh it happened
to Landing okay 108 snowboarding after
all oh God your pizzas I didn't look if
I had enough but it seems like I did
over
10,000
yeah no give
him
w
like do I get a good one a
be okay that's
[Music]
okay give me those 10,000 bucks not just
a tiny ass cut like 30 bucks no
way that was amazing that was fun I like
it geek Warrior it's dope that you're
working with us P hope I see you again
how much how much eh how much how much
how much how much did they
get just point so
what I got deliver and then you buy the
dollars potato
chips what $5 for a f are you [\h__\h]
kidding
me oh my
God oh my
God oh my God
what a rip
off not worth it even though it was a
lot of
fun like I wouldn't do it for money just
for
fun
damn
[Music]
oh
better to redeem for items than money
yeah for now I'm keeping it we'll
see sometime
maybe what a
[Music]
nice
I keep on turning it off and on I didn't
[Music]
realiz I can't fight right
now I was still pressing that because of
the Viking
oh all right we
bonding
hi got your 30
bucks actually pretty cheap oh not
complaining
no my headache is fine right now
shoulder hurts
though
it's a long
[Music]
chapter feel like it's
ending fore
[Music]
fore the
mdle
for
Fore
foree she's
[Music]
badass
left me on the
[Music]
be
for bring
[Music]
a
I don't want to deal with
the cousin
Roman m
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
fore
foree yeah
[Music]
intimidate this guy knows a lot of
sh like a open book
I don't want to
[Music]
go
I doubt
that I I believe you com
me
did they kill his
parents why is there D
playing
um
back the back
pipes
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
on
trying to do the same thing
[Music]
to [\h__\h]
up
just for
fun
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
you wanted to kill
him you do
it
[Music]
for guy you
know but he need
to
for
[Music]
Fore
mm
[Music]
for
foree
fore
tell
[Music]
him yeah that
was uh
[Music]
fore I'm back to Tommy
We
[Music]
Believe
spee
[Music]
fore
also you can pull out tires nowhere
[Music]
that's also you wear the color purple
and we're still missing at in our idle
[Music]
group
it would be great
[Music]
sales very
pers
[Music]
can I pause the game now give me a
moment to end it you give me a freaking
break
ooh
flashbang all
right this is it for today I thought we
could finish another chapter but we got
really far
though I would say uh we played 6 and 1
half hours oh my God I will read some
super chats but I will take a few bites
from a
sandwich uh and I'll take an idol
meeting break and then I'll see you in
my girly room okie dokie thanks G thank
you for watching uh please feel free to
stay for the Super Chat reading it won't
be too long I won't I won't do too much
cuz I do want to
cook that's also why I'm not going to
eat the whole sandwich just a little bit
just enough to get me to keep me
going and then tomorrow we're going to
do members only I
think yeah uh
we're going to watch I guess we're going
to watch Indiana
Jones in the evening in my evening maybe
8:00 p.m. W time or or 700 p.m. probably
should since it's a weekday should be as
late as possible for you guys uh so yeah
maybe 8:00
p.m. whatever the first one is I don't
know what the first one is
called
Indiana Jones Raiders of the Lost Arc
what
1981 that's holy [\h__\h] that's 40 years
old the first one is from
1981 yeah you lost
me okay is that one on Disney
too it's not
old
it's okay I said we're watching the
first one we're going to watch the first
one it's okay it's
okay 14 years old that's as old as
itan shees she she
she okay
then oh yeah
[Music]
right
right I'll fix you
up there you
go there we go
BRB
meow meow
meow I got a good squeeze out of the
potatoes they were both sleeping on the
sofa so
cute what music do we
want oh maybe something
tropical
I'm
hungry
hungry are you I can't hear
anything why why
[Music]
why squishy
kitties something Hawaiian oh anything
tropical really I'm not going to go on
um on audio stock
[Music]
now what where is it I
here
uh
[Music]
what sorry I was
loud
actually
this is
good yes
[Music]
yes tropical elevator
music I woke me
up
why were you sleeping okay let me open
this
sandwich why the
[\h__\h] what is
this weird
technology
okay we have an egg salad
chicken um
bacon I think yeah chicken
bacon uh sandwich what's that e EB
uh
EBC yes
chicken thank you for your
[Music]
sacrifice hm
m m the egg
salad a slice of lettuce would make it
much better cuz they're always needs to
be a slice of lettuce
everywhere but
okay
he ate bacon but he has yet to eat an
egg what the
[\h__\h] so how was the bacon M
sauce and in what form did you eat
[Music]
it is he
here
[Music]
how can you how old is this
person how could you have never eaten an
egg don't even get me started
again hey you like big Wawa big waha
with the bat is going to beat you up
wait I don't see any answers Z's not
around he insists to remain eggless how
can you be part of kfb if anything you
should have chosen to not eat the bacon
if you're just trying to keep up the bit
then don't eat the bacon but you're kfp
you should be familiar with eggs and
chicken oh tast a
tomato there's a surprise tomato in here
that they didn't say it on the packaging
it's kind of in the back of the sandwich
you can't even see it from the front oh
my
God [\h__\h]
[Music]
tomato
yeah M you know how much I love tomatoes
and like burgers and stuff right
oh
tomato I was already happy with the
sandwich you make it even better tomato
tomato I love you
tomato chicken bacon excellent and
tomato why the [\h__\h] are you even
comparing jalapenos with tomatoes that's
completely
different it's not like tomatoes
Tomatoes yeah I don't understand people
who are hating on tomatoes either
they're so juicy juicy and
fresh M they ate they ate they add a
great component to anything
really the
texture some people people I shouldn't
even be judging because I also like a
lot of people a lot of things not I also
don't like a lot of things for so many
reasons some people really have the
weirdest reasons to not like some
[Music]
yeah you don't like mushrooms yeah I
don't like
mushrooms and that's also so
M partially because of the
texture cuz it's so like slippery slimy
soft when it's cooked like randomly for
example in a curry like have mushrooms
in there
ew it's like I don't know it's like I'm
eating random fish that shouldn't be
[Music]
there
if it's tiny pieces mixed with meat or
whatever I'll still probably like find
them and be
like if it's a sauce though I I like
mushroom
sauce that's that's kind of
different
surprisingly of course I like onions I
am an
onion
ow this tomato man this
tomato
wow yeah
Ms thank God they snitched on you I
already forgot that you were that
person and now I was reminded
[Music]
oh is
she
okay sandwich number one is like the one
half is done I'm not going to eat the
other one even though it's
yummy cuz I want to ideally I want to
cook yesterday I had the tuna yesterday
I had tuna
pizza
and I want to say
something do you guys remember me
renting renting renting renting at some
point about my favorite
pizza uh brand
um changing the recipe of my favorite
tuna Pizza frozen tuna
Pizza
mhm it's not back but I found a pizza a
frozen
pizza from a different like company
whatever that has like the the the the
the floor of the pizza is is not really
good like it's like doesn't get crunchy
and it's like it's it's really mad but
the toppings like the sauce and
everything the tuna and the something
like bamal or something that's on top
all of that tastes the FL tastes kind of
like the old recipe of the tuna Pizza
that I loved so much
before and yeah I think it was for from
leadle I think
so which explains why the the floor of
the pizza is so [\h__\h] cuz it's kind of
like a discount pizza or like a discount
supermarket so discount
Pizza they're not bad do not eat foror
pizza as opposed to Bath Pizza uh but
yeah what the [\h__\h] and wow it reminded
me so much of that pizza so it's like
even though the floor is so
[\h__\h] I I'll take it I'll [\h__\h] take
it take get crispy for you H I don't
know what I did
wrong but I'll try again maybe it'll get
better next
time but damn I'm so happy you don't
understand my whole life I was eating
this tuna pizza from
drka and then suddenly even though
everything was fantastic they changed
the recipe and I I don't know I'm
probably not the only one who's unhappy
with the new recipe and the new flavor
and
everything probably not the only
one and I tried other tuna pizzas out
there trust me other Frozen ones
specifically cuz it's like my go-to when
I don't want to
cook in like uh instant immed OT frozen
pizza we have a big frozen pizza culture
[Music]
here I ate the whole thing normally
normally I I don't like some some parts
of the The Edge I will leave cuz it's
like too much
anyway but for this one I actually even
ate all of the edges just because that
was the only part part of the pizza that
was a little bit Crunchy just a tiny
bit I was so happy it's like I
met I met
like like it's like the pizza Reborn the
soul was transferred into a new pizza
and yeah it's like a reunion of our
souls it's my soulmade pizza and it may
not be exactly the same but I can sense
it it has the same Soul it was
reincarnated
yes I'll accept it and may not have the
perfect
floor but the toppings that's the most
important the flavor
M
amazing I'm so happy I feel so fulfilled
and I've I've been waiting for this for
a long time I also tried to venture out
a little bit and tried other pizzas that
are not even tuna pizzas cuz generally I
also kind of like um you know pineapple
pizza we have some great um pineapple
pizzas too in in the Frozen selection
usually from actually only from Dr etka
I think and I tried others like the
pepperoni and I tried the the one that's
usually like ham and corn because I love
corn but then with the ham and corn one
I always wish it just would be completed
with some pineapple the pineapple pizza
has ham but it doesn't have corn
actually no it wasn't ham and corn it
was bacon and corn which is pretty good
but like oh what if it had
pineapple just couldn't find a perfect
Pizza especially not a tuna
Pizza yeah I never gave up I I gave this
one a chance I didn't believe it because
you know I thought how how can a how can
a little pizza be
good ah
nice
you love Corner never knew can I like
elote
yes I told
narissa about aot the other day she
didn't know what it was I explained it
to her and then she kind of I think
understood what it was but she didn't
know the name of
it I told her I had great elote in
America
before anything with corn anything with
corn
I was so surprised she didn't know I
thought I thought everybody would know
In
America which one is it the Del delosa
or the steinen one I need the cin
feeling Del wait uh I didn't look so
close to it let me
delosa that might be it Pizza little
Tuna uh yeah yeah I think yeah yeah I
think that's it yep yep yep yep y y y y
y y y yep y y y yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep yep
yes and the the interesting thing is I
feel like they must be honestly the
design even looks like it's related to
Dr edka somehow got to look it up if
they're related somehow because oh they
have a Hawaii pizza too cuz uh the
package on the packaging the picture
even the picture looks like my good old
tuna
Pizza I want to see the packaging looks
like it's related let me look that up is
that is that
company Del related to drka and just
like a cheaper version but they sell the
same thing
[Music]
basically okay I don't know I'm not
getting immediate confirmation about
that
I'm going to look more up later more
more I need to investigate yeah I
thought maybe they come from the same
Factory or so use like similar very
similar recipe but just sell one more
expensive than the
other
yeah
mhm let's be Italian now I'm curious of
this
deleta must be Italian huh I don't know
about that Hawaiian pizza is good yes it
is Thea is Little's own brand I think
yeah but but they how maybe I don't know
if this pizza has always tasted like
this but maybe they heard about the
unhappy people that were always eating
drka pizza and then they change their
recipe and now they're like what the
[\h__\h] so they made their own pizza taste
exactly like that maybe they were trying
to save me people like me poor poor
disappointed Left Behind Pizza andoy
like me maybe they found out about it
and wanted to give us another chance in
life with
pizzas which is amazing a hero just like
Ichiban if that's the
case I need to tell my friends cuz they
they also all love tuna
pizza oh almost all of them I need to
tell them I need to tell
them about my
excavations
okay we're going to read some super
chatos I'm going to try to be a little
bit uh
efficient
try yeah discovery of the sentury let's
go yes I'm going to spread the
word I got to read the big one right
that I had like uh what stream was it
again
[\h__\h] streaming
list W
back
stream
mhm I give free super chats at most hey
hey hey
hey rude I I'm totally going to read all
of
them uh wait
how uh didn't I save it a
yeah starting the time now no you're
making me
nervous
that's
me did people say something uh different
about my
neck is something different about my
neck compar to when what's different is
it the shadow cuz I also realized the
shadow isn't moving was that always like
that
H I didn't officially start
yet F of
me no I wasn't able to overcome my neck
cracking
addiction waa with her crack addiction
damn
am didn't notice that before I noticed
before and I was like is is this
a was it always like
this I got to check the
vods so much for stopping yeah no I
never that's also a thing I never
started that run properly either but I
could have tried during my break but it
hurts so much I can't stop it's like the
only thing that somehow gives me a
little bit of relief you know I'm going
to go [\h__\h] insane if I try to not do
it but I I was thinking maybe like what
if I get the doctor to give me um the
spritzer the
injection that I heard of before from
friends that they got from their doctor
and then the pain was away well like
temporarily for a good amount of time
and then let's say they do that and then
I let's say I actually don't feel the
pain anymore that would be amazing but
then I could take that opportunity to
try to stop the cracking as long as
the steroids I don't know if it really
with steroids but as long as that is
working and I'm being fooled by the
injection that my pain is gone maybe
I'll also be able to like stop
cracking Carone
C cortisone I don't know I'll ask my
friend actually if he even knows what
kind of injection that
was yeah I'll I'll talk to the
doctor
I I'll try my best to convey everything
properly okay let's go sky thank you for
two pinkies welcome back you wa wait uh
please see my two pink super chats as a
red envelope
ah yeah yeah tradition because of you're
crazy I mean the passion mon tweet so I
designed pick that up and finish decided
you decided to pick it up and finish the
whole series what you started from zero
no stop watching right now we're going
to watch it
together it is quite enjoyable to me my
top free SE
hey you already watched it
all did you already like get started
before or did you get started because of
my
twe you already watched it
all
[Music]
dude now it's so fresh in your brain
because of
my didn't I say in the tweet that we're
going to watch it together
sky
sky sky just reads part of the Tweet
where I praise monali to heavens and
says oh okay I should probably watch
that and then the end of the Tweet or so
that says let's watch it together just
gets ignored cuz he's already watching
it oh my God to me my top three seasons
are n Nick sh and K now I am looking
forward to the new season because High
chance that you would read this after
14th so in advanced happy contest how
did you know thank you well I'm happy
you watched it but like we're watching
it
together could have just
waited why is this watch long going to
happen soon
soonish but yeah you know you're saying
cuz it's so fresh in your memory or
saying your favorite Seasons I I'm I'm
so sad I can't even really say cuz I
don't really remember what happened
happen when so much I mean I probably
one of my favorites was probably the one
where Nao was a big deal
um and I don't know what else M probably
probably the one with the sisters where
M yeah Phoenix Phoenix
Arc probably would be one also uh I kind
of like the combal arc a lot but you
know I wouldn't know where these all go
in the titles of the seasons and also I
like uh monar math
Arc
yeah I would say math Arc is one of my
favorites for sure oh but also uh what's
her name again the one with the T turkor
hair I love her so much so EV every
everything everything that had
her um what was her name again uh
turquoise hair and orange dress help me
out
here oh yeah Yuki see I love yotsuki so
much but
uni I really didn't like
uni freaked me out but
Yi she's my
girl yeah wait same person wait I'm
thinking of someone
else the one with the
um or is it is it the right one wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I no okay wait what's the what's
the
the the counterpart basically um oie yes
oie oie oie oie oie oino oie freaked me
out I mean understandable
right but uh those two they don't show
up until much later later so
yeah my pictures oh I can't see it right
now does each series have new characters
and are they all
connected they're all connected yeah but
I don't know if each series uh each
season has a new character maybe a lot
of them
do but a lot of them like uh reappear
and you know what I kind of like this is
such a weird thing to like focus on
maybe but I like how for example their
hair there's a lot of hairstyle changes
and all that and it kind of in in in
usually it's like kind of
symbolic like s Gana cutting her
hair the hair changes are usually a
symbolic thing for the
story and I like how their image change
a changes a lot through that
too H there's a a lot of hair cutting
yeah I'm not saying why she cuts her
hair just saying yeah you know I mean
you may have probably already seen art
of her with short hair
somewhere oh yeah hair color as well
exactly because like in so many
animes throughout several seasons I see
characters usually always have the same
hairstyle and it's just always the same
you know they don't ever change so I
really like how they switch it up a
little bit here and there and then it's
not just randomly it's actually it has
meaning I love that I love that so much
oh it's getting me excited to watch it
all over again now talking about it like
this
yeah
mhm yeah they're so dynamic their
designs exactly that's what I love so
much about it
yeah yeah character
development yeah it's realistic too
getting a haircut every once in a while
especially if
something you know even IRL people get
haircuts because you
know
dramatic life changing things broke up
with someone got to cut my hair let's go
new hair new
me so Sky I'm glad you liked it I hope
you're ready to watch it
again did you watch it all during my
break so 3 weeks is what it took you did
you watch the movies if not then at
least hold back on the movies come
on thank you so
much also I want to know who's your
favorite favorite character you told me
your favorite Seasons but you didn't
tell me your favorite character Sky
that's the important one who is best
girl s Ando probably pretty unpopular
choices for me for for like
yeah for for the monali fandom people
always say Sara
Ori yeah I love them too
but soti and not
for
me people really like to ignore the
existence of soda because she just
appeared in the anime and in the I guess
also in the novels so
late so people don't really think of her
when they think of
monar Sky says all of
them and I really like chobu too um I
feel like I like chobu the most in her
middle St
stage maybe ah I'm getting
excited a I really want to watch it now
let's go we're going to watch it soon
soon soon
soon yeah I love the music for saachi's
Arc
mhm yotsuki and saachi are the best
exactly I I really like the those
Seasons
[Music]
mhm
man ah ah so that so that she makes me
so sad you know man I love her I want to
give her a
hug no okay I'm going to
read kad's story is so interesting
everybody's story is so interesting Kam
is like a a tomboy which is never a type
that I really am interested in um except
for Tales of
Asperia uh I guess you she could what
was her name the maid the magic girl I
think she was from T of Asperia was it
tpia in that case I kind of like a
tomboy but generally I don't like
tomboy Rita yeah Rita would you consider
her tomboy I think kind
of but kbo is a real real tomboy and I'm
not really interested but I love her
story and her personality and she's
amazing she's amazing
amazing she do be T boy huh I love her I
love
her
pan thank you for the red super chat
having anime talk from me is kind of
rare isn't
it welcome back Tel did you miss us on
your break cuz it's not like we missed
you or anything not like my days had a
notable void in them with all my laa
maybe we missed a little
bit cute Nathan you're so cute always I
love you thank you so
much I hope the void is filled
[Music]
again I hope it didn't hurt too
much combo is not defined by a of course
yeah I would agree with that she's not
defined by her personality is just
amazing yep yeah yeah and her whole
story MH very full now amazing all right
perfect I'm glad I'm glad that's taken
care of and I don't need to be
worried is one of my faith of all time
in tales off yeah she would be somewhere
up there for me too I mean I think T
ofia wouldn't be in my top three of
tales off games but um as a character I
really like her although tal of was
amazing it's just I love them all so
much
man you love your mini mes I [\h__\h] do
I [\h__\h]
do what is your top free there's
definitely magil L there and
uh wait [\h__\h] what's her name uh mil Mila
Mila magu
and
kisawa although I don't know if for
kisar I'm just like what I'm feeling is
just like you know fully
physical it's
confusing oh you were talking about
games I don't know that's difficult I
don't remember I don't
remember but no I always say Tes of
cilia 2 especially is up there in the
top
three that's
[Music]
getal I I just don't know if my if my
mind is being shrouded
by the physical appeal of kisara or if I
really like
her that much more than
others I don't know hard to judge I
can't know for
sure and R so free thanks for two
pinkies also with a red envelope thank
you so much okay it is pink not red I
ran out of red envelopes so we use a
second envelope to make it up to make up
for it not being red Happy Chinese New
Year everybody knows if you put the same
shade of pink onto another same of same
shade of pink it it it totally becomes
red everybody knows that that's just
science don't worry about it it's red in
my eyes thank you so
much thank
you Happy New Year I guess you celebrate
it huh I don't celebrate it but uh I'm
happy for everybody who celebrate it
good for you good for you I have a
friend uh in Austria who uh celebrated
it
and that friend on uh Chinese or luna
New Year posted uh like stories to just
not because they were in China then but
they were like showing sharing to the
Friends of them to like how it
is uh in Chinese New Year and then it
was like pictures and videos of some big
airport I guess in
China um on New Year and oh my my
God what a terrifying crowd of people oh
God like you know the welcoming area
where people wait for others to arrive
family
members
oh it looks it looks like like Beyonce
Ariana Grande Michael
Jackson
like
20 pop stars are all together at the
same time maybe even
more yeah it looks like a concert it
looks [\h__\h]
insane it's
crazy and then the comment was like this
is why I'm not uh trying to
be back in my home at Chinese New Year
specifically but rather try to go like
at a different
timing I can't imag imagine this is
insane how many people are going home at
the same time holy
[\h__\h] definitely don't want to
be changing airports or arriving at any
Chinese
airports during Chinese New Year no no
no no no no
no don't want to experience that that's
the craziest airport situation I've ever
seen holy
[\h__\h]
H it doesn't choke around for real for
real usually people go back home a week
early to avoid that crowd yeah you got
to
insane you could probably look it up and
find some footage of that it was like
footage from above somewhere above a few
floors above looking down on the people
and there were thousands in the welcome
Lobby all like there was no space
between people how do you even find the
ones you're looking
for
how people crowd surfing yeah yeah yeah
okay everybody who arrives just like
crowd surfs over the families which are
waiting and
then eventually the family will be like
oh oh that's ours all right let's
go oh yeah train station probably too
yeah yeah
that's so
scary why not do it the other way around
why not let the families go overseas
instead then it all scatters around and
it's less of a freaking
chaos but understand you want to go back
home see your family and all that better
to have one people one person travel to
your family then the whole family travel
to the one person I don't know I guess
maybe you can do like one year this way
one year the other
way but I do find the tradition really
nice
like
yeah it's a nice tradition like I I
don't really think we
we is there anything like this in any
other country where so many people go
back home for for one specific holiday
and it's like from overseas cuz they're
scattered all over is there anything
comparable
I feel like there isn't bgm hey you
don't hear it what do you mean you don't
hear it I see it on OBS don't you hear
this well you hear it what what the [\h__\h]
man na M what the
[\h__\h] was it too quiet Christmas yeah but
like in this amount and
like so specifically to one location
[Music]
to one country I don't I don't really
think so not on this
level like maybe Thanksgiving but it's
not like I don't think it has the same
effect feel like Americans
are yes many Americans are overseas but
like also Canadians I guess but like
also yeah I don't know I don't think
it's the same not at
all yeah that's another level
oh damn sheesh anyway thank you R free
you made me call a
tangent but it was fascinating yeah R
fre thank you m jish monkey 20 40 60
that's a that's a red one all right kfp
get us back we all practice this okay
here we go back welcome
back wait where do I know this from from
damn it KY one more time let's go
welcome back pickle why pickle where did
you get that from ah it wants a scrubs
scene I was thinking it must be it feels
like
Scrubs I hope you had a super wonderful
break and if you recognize the scrub
scene I still this welcome back for my
love you exp but did they say pickle I
don't think so but I definitely remember
that it was so
funny I love it I love it I love scrub I
love scrubs so much why why did it have
to be that way at the
end I think
scrubs last
seasons mostly really just one last
season is
really like it's it's like a whole
spin-off at that
[Music]
point didn't exist
I feel like you know those three new so
to say main characters that join um the
two guy two no one guy and two girls one
girl who's kind of like tnd and
serious uh who works with Turk I think
um the douche who works with
um holy [\h__\h] what's her
name
uh what the [\h__\h] was her name Turk JD
and Elliot thank you yeah the douche
that works of Elliot and then the the
the girl that works with JD who's kind
of like JD out of those I only really
like the girl that worked with JD the
douche was yeah douches are supposed to
be annoying but I feel like like you can
do it differently I don't I really
didn't like the
douche um and I also didn't like the
serious tun tun girl that worked with
Turk that much either I don't know about
you guys so yeah she's JD
2.0 so that's why she had a lot of charm
I would say she was okay but yeah I feel
like the cast wasn't so
good and yeah you
know
[Music]
H it's better if the douches drop the
act and show their human every once in a
while oh yeah yeah I don't think he ever
did that did
he don't be silly
now wow ignorance is
bliss okay okay okay okay thank you J
[Music]
monkey [\h__\h]
um happy belated birthday iron V
Al jaob 47 thanks for the pinky welcome
back Tel it's been a rough waight but it
makes the final moment of your return
all the better a lot to work look
forward now H H talk infinite well
whatever else you have up your sleeve
and now we also have ai's life T Joy yes
surprise surprise surprise
that was uh nicely timed with my return
I guess not really actually wasn't timed
on purpose I was I wanted to be back a
little bit earlier
but you had something nice to
watch baby
baby you mentioned whole talk oh my
God yeah maybe we can make a comeback in
in March
[Music]
I was thinking of it
but you know maybe in
[Music]
March hold dog so we'll have H talk and
frogy
waha in March wouldn't that be amazing
oh my
god let's drink some
water was the last H talk the Advent one
yeah I think so so yeah anyway thank you
Jacob I'm happy to be back I'm glad
you're still here too MTL to D thank you
so much and I wanted to ask if you could
already tell us if you're attending any
events cons this year or not
EU I mean I certainly can't say which
ones
um uh but also I think I only have one
lined up right now sometimes you know
they really uh only get decided on like
three months in advance
maybe I think I currently only have one
but it's not
in those regions that you
mentioned sorry it's not in my power I
don't choose where to go um I even
begged to be for example in a Korean
convention and it still didn't work out
so I don't really have much power of it
you got got you guys got to um ask for
me recommend me again I
suppose anime NYC announcing two days in
advance um I think the na cons they know
that people want whole alive and uh all
that but like currently I feel like
they're asking more for people they
didn't have before and like Advent gets
a lot of action I think which is fine
you know they they are jumping into the
market and I'm sure a lot of people want
to see them but especially for
conventions where maybe was in previous
years yeah I I think it makes total
sense that they wouldn't invite me again
over inviting someone from Advent for
example for the first time that's just
fair so yeah I feel like this year is
going to be the year of Advent
probably I know you want to see see me
yeah it's tough it's tough so what you
could do is just uh ask maybe some
bigger conventions who haven't had the
pleasure of having whole life guests yet
maybe maybe there's still some there's
certainly some big ones out there still
that didn't do that yet right so I think
that's what I can recommend
you
sounds like a plan so go message them
tell them tell them tell
them time to create our own
convention maybe you
can I emailed the big NJ Anime Con but
they had to cancel it this year NJ New
Jersey I'll ask for the convention near
me they had Ena and Faun last year o
well if they didn't have me before then
there's a chance for
sure and I feel like there's also like I
often get paired up with uh people like
calling or
coal I feel like I only got paired up
with Amed once even though I love her so
much yeah but the most popular pairing
that they pair me up with is CI
I would
say so could say yeah how about you
bring
Takami or buo and Wawa or so I want to
see those two together and you could
even be like you know those two they're
really a well-known good fun combination
who can have a fun panel any
day I don't know try to sell us try to
sell Ami Sami yes am
too oh yeah me and
Thea or or maybe ooh try to get like a
Holo toy holot toy
panel not probably not all of us that's
impossible probably but maybe Ian hor
panel and Ian speaking H
panel that would be
amazing yes yes yes yes oo I want to do
that um um J Jim Tracy thanks for the
pinky welcome back Yana I hope your
break was awesome and you got plenty of
rest and time to distress we definitely
missed
you thank you so
much I I don't know did I de-stress
partially maybe and then I gaed some
stress again especially with all the
issues I had and right leading up to my
comeback and then also during my
[Music]
comeback I haven't heard from those
people in a in a few days now and it
makes me feel very suspicious
[Music]
again but it's weekend so I'm giving
them the benefit of the doubt that
because like on on the weekend nothing
would happen but tomorrow if I don't get
contacted I'm going to contact them
again I guess and oh my God if nothing
happens soon I I might have to contact a
lawyer my
lawyer cuz yeah we're streaming now but
you know how often it's like buffering
and I can't really do streams that rely
more on internet like P world I think I
don't even want to I don't even want to
risk it I don't even want to try cuz I
know it's not going to work
um so I am restricted in the streams I
can do that
sucks
got to go kiar on their asses I don't
know if I really have the confidence for
it that's why I need a lawyer to do it
instead I know the yeah the ICP is
providing it it's free
too and I I do get um what's the word uh
compensation too but like compensation
whatever yeah I want that too but I also
so I want to see
that something is happening and I don't
see anything happening right
[Music]
now
yeah use your bath for
pers oh well we'll see we'll see I'll
see if something happens tomorrow if
not Mr V Dan J Dan for the pinky welcome
back from your migration lovely Phoenix
I actually I didn't go anywhere really
hope the break helped you reignite Your
Flames though the weeks were long I
welcome more breaks if you stay smiling
definitely missed you D distance makes
the heart grow fonder and mine says doie
doie thank you I'm back I'm back I'm
back I'm back maybe on a future break I
would migrate somewhere but in this case
I was so happy to just be
home I mean literally just came back
from a migration
bird migration to the
males and it was nice to spend so much
time with my
[Music]
cats all day with my cat
potatoes even those like two nights that
I spent in a spa hotel I was seriously
considering bringing my
cats cuz I just thought
I enjoyed every day with them so much I
love them so much maybe next time I'll
bring them
along I don't know if they would like
it probably not see generally I want I
don't want to move them around because
they are used to just you know they're
not outside going cats so I think they
want to chill it's stressful to bring
them somewhere
unnecessarily yeah
but I probably
shouldn't oh yeah I'm back thank you for
welcoming me
back also thank you so much for
welcoming you back for the
[Music]
pinky
for nice
nice
[Music]
J then
this guy went to or or woman I don't
know went to the Tonka place that I
recommended in Japan and said if it was
really fluffy and yummy fluffy fluffy
meat and the eggs cuz it was like it's
not um you know ton KATU comes in all
kind of
forms and this is uh like kind of like
Katon it's like in a bowl of rice with a
layer of egg fluffy egg and then on top
of that the katsu right it doesn't
necessarily always come like that I like
to just have katsu T Shoku which is just
a a katsu meal where the meat and the
rice is not in the same Bowl it's on a
separate plate and there's some a little
bit of like cabbage and yeah it's just
really simple you get a miso soup of
course but it's like everything's
separate I just somehow really like
[Music]
that
I love crunchy The Green Onion yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum you bookmarked it yeah in case you
go to Japan sometime you got to go but
it's really a lot I realized I'm kind of
disappointed in the in the video it
doesn't look so big but in real life
it's really huge it's so much bigger
than any other
Tatu for real even like I had the
smaller
cut than JMA but even my smaller one was
way bigger than normal default katsu it
looked pretty big really I feel like cuz
there was no real size comparison um
there to see just didn't look that
big I remember it being much bigger in
real
life yeah
lots of
meat you'll go there during fifth Fest
all the kfp probably going to go let me
say it's a pretty small store so you
shouldn't go in a in a big
group uh cuz it's going to be other
people
too you know and I don't think you can
reserve I don't think you can so don't
go there in a big group kfb all the all
the tourist
kfbs don't do it
go in like small groups like maybe in
doubles maybe a
[Music]
triple and don't go like exactly at 12:
or 1:00
p.m. then you would probably have to to
wait in a line I didn't have to we
didn't have to wait in a line I feel
like we went maybe at like 2:00 p.m. or
something like
that like a more random time is
recommended and I don't think I do
dinner and Slavic fellow thank you for
the
rainbow welcome back wow wow we missed
you so much I hope you had a good rest
and relaxation lots of cat cuddles oh
[\h__\h] yeah we worked hard while waiting
for your return
yes it's not like we were running KF
while all depressed with droopy wings
and R V
no don't say that I'll never be able to
go on a break
[Music]
again
man no you're just exaggerating right
you're just exaggerating I
know I thought we closed ha no of course
not we got to make
money it says no need to read the rest
but I'll read it uh I know you said you
don't want to do membership tiers but as
you know all these streaming gaming
platforms constantly increase their
subscription prices by a lot while not
really providing that much in return now
if we look at the Wawa streaming
platform everything is always topnotch
full of fun projects and
entertainment why are
you it's like you're my financial
adviser taking that into account I wish
we could support ra more even if we
don't have ideas for funny super chats
oh
so I wanted to ask you to maybe
reconsider adding an extra rank or ranks
of membership tiers to keep them without
additional benefits purely for extra
passive support of Wawa and her projects
I'm positive I'm not alone of the
sentiment Wawa
Love
oh I mean I always say you guys if you
want to you know give me more money just
send the Super Chat and then at least
you can leave a message of it
but h
[Music]
M yeah or yeah you can even send an
empty
[Music]
one yeah I don't know I really
appreciate that you want to support me
like that and and want to like push me
to do that because in the end it's like
good money but I don't know if it really
needs to be
done yeah you can give memberships
too that might
be I I don't know how many people
actually like end up renewing their
memberships probably not that many but
um I think it's always a great way to
support with gifting memberships
remember when when gifting memberships
became a thing slowly on YouTube and
everybody was like no we don't want that
and I think I don't know if you guys all
were like that but the members were also
really worried like ah I don't know the
wrong people might become members like
people who just dare to hate on us and
all that everybody was so worried about
it but now like everybody's happy about
gifting and receiving and nobody worries
about it
anymore everybody was
dramatic it's been fine I don't think it
really
affected
um it in any negative way
like people leaking member info
remember info was already leaked without
that no matter what
so
honestly it's not like that wasn't the
thing already before
so yeah I think it's been
great thank you for the membership
gift
[Music]
it's if the bad eggs get the gift and be
rude or troll I have
never
experienced such a
problem
honestly uh so
I don't even remember ever seeing a
member in general acting
up but if you if I see a member acting
up I can just you know block him
so it's not like you can't just do
something
yeah but yeah I don't know slapping fell
it's really sweet of you but I think
we're probably going to leave things the
way way they
are but
you otherwise would I really see this
beautiful rainbow Slavic fellow I don't
want to miss out on this rainbow
either so thank you for your support and
your sentiment that is very much
appreciated and the way you speak about
my
membership
if you did I would join the higher tear
thank you I'm sure a lot of you
would
but it's okay n m thank you for the
pinky w
wow I love you welcome back thank you so
much I was able to manage these past few
weeks but life just isn't the same
without you I missed my boss I hope your
break left you feeling
recharged yeah part
partially partially in terms of like
work and streaming I I think yeah I
think so um so it was a good break it it
definitely helped me so thank you for
waiting for me and letting me do that
and I'll try my best
to you
know give you good content in the coming
weeks and
months so that the break will be like it
never
happened last member last ASMR I didn't
do
ASMR you always do we love
[Music]
you thank you you guys are so sweet
you're doing a good job already thank
you I'm trying I'm glad we didn't have
to can
uh Yakuza but next week I probably won't
play it I don't
know got to see cuz I did tell I asked I
asked Ena and piju if they are playing
the steam version because I was made
aware of something um and then they said
yeah we're playing the steam version and
then I said okay then please wait for me
cuz they both want to do multiplayer and
yeah so M I guess may maybe I'll try it
next
week it looks like I really like the
visuals and all that but I don't know
I'm generally just like not really hyped
about the game cuz I I also don't really
know what it's about and all that uh but
yeah I guess we can look into it I don't
know if it will be a full
playr possibly not the game screams
K yeah it kind of
does
I I know it's based of a yeah a g game
yeah I
know you don't care about the game it's
just want Ena
collaps
well yeah I mean it it it would be a
nice way of like a nice reason to have a
collab of Ena and pizu and I heard Z as
well I'm guessing four is
maximum
[Music]
probably
yeah then we would be a full
group what the
[\h__\h] I need I need paper
COA he
FL thank you for the red of chat welcome
back T thank you oh that's so sweet of
you
come I really wanted to study some
Korean on my break and I didn't do
anything didn't do anything I should
have not wasted my time reading that
shitty book and should have um studied
Korean
instead but it's not too late it's never
too late it's never too
late thank you Flora for your
support space wonderful than for the
pinky welcome back K waa hope you had a
great break with plenty of rest and some
detoxing I'm happy it was a it was
actually the other way around it was
plenty of detoxing and and
some some rest some good
rest I'm happy that you took a break
from for yourself but I'm also glad that
my tan oi is back oh you say tan oi
instead of Kam oi tanoshi is basically
Kam Oshi at the same time but it means
that you don't have any other o
she very reassuring word choice I admit
I did miss you a lot it's worth it for
your wellbeing though thank you if I'm
your tan oi that means you had nothing
else to
watch I mean you can still watch other
people without oing them
what were you up to while I was gone
[Music]
huh what were you up
to I was supposed to taking care of
myself well I hope you're always doing
that not just during my
break but good good to
hear watching GAA and fauna at times oh
yeah GAA came back she had a k yesterday
right I I I was still awake but I didn't
listen to it because it was already
[Music]
late I saw she was doing the the phone
ratio thing
though she fell victim to the trend
no Studio thank you for the red super
[Music]
ch
thank you so much for
your
studio golden thanks for the pinky W I
missed you but I hope you rech charged
sadly I'll miss you soon but I'll look
out for rebroadcast if you do it oh
you're right I'm supposed to do that too
next week by the way since we'll watch W
would you be interested in doing a f CA
of all openings and endings and do you
have perms uh generally I think in terms
of perms it shouldn't be an issue CU I
already saw you know a couple of the you
know the popular ones
being uh often sung and I sign on to
before and we have the instrumentals and
all that but um I would have
to uh cuz we we have a k application now
right I could request ahead of time to
get all the instrumentals for also the
the Lesser known
ones into the app and then we could do
it yeah just remind me
again I don't know however how long it
actually takes to get a request into our
app because if you remember I tried
early on when we just had the app
created more or less sending um about
300 or so all at once and I sat down and
I took so much time to like write it
also in a organized way and then uh a
while later maybe a week or two or three
later they were like oh um we're making
a new rule you can't send so many at
once anymore and also by the way takasa
all of your requests are not going to be
worked
on at
all they just took my submission and
just
like yeed it we're like nope not even
going to start from the top
no it took me a while to compile that
list
man it took me a
while they fed on the ground
and ever since then it was really like
frustrating to me so I never thought
about submitting anything
again or even using the app I haven't
used it yet because I don't like the
choice of songs so
much did you resend them a few the time
no because I it genuinely annoyed me for
like I sat down took the time cuz cuz
there were no such rules and I I
submitted it in like a format that is
easy to read and like well
organized not going to do it again I
mean eventually maybe I'll do it again
but like it was really
annoying seems like most are still using
cun I would say it's like different
usage cun is for non archived and
ours they add songs that are basically
usually usually it's like being used to
add Japanese songs because why English
songs they're all basically on
[Music]
cun this is like mainly for adding
Japanese
songs which can be
archives so I wanted all the all the
Hello project all the Betty's goo songs
and all
that to do a Hello project themed
k
[Music]
h no it wasn't my fault
no well one day one day one day if I
have time and the mood then I'll sit
down and enter everything step by step
and then you have to wait until those
get approved to add more
[Music]
apparently
but I do appreciate the app and like the
whole process in the first place that it
exists and that they're you know in the
end they're just like trying to give us
more and more tools to work with to
improve our streams uh and that's
great I just really don't like what
happened
there
salty
cuz it's not like I can even like copy
paste my my old application it's like on
gone it's like nowhere it's in the void
I would take it and then put it in one
of my
documents and then just like copy paste
from my previous list and just throw it
in
there like three at a time or four or
five
whatever but it's gone my list is just
gone it's just in a void
I don't know if it was really 300 dude
I'm just like saying it was a
lot it may not have been 300 may have
been less but uh it was a lot yeah it it
was a lot yeah yeah yeah so well yeah
but
anyway arur thanks for the pinky welcome
home boss hope your batteries got a
well-deserved recharge it's really it
really felt like both so much time and
no time at all since you went on a break
like Mom's cramed into just a few weeks
happy your back let's get to work yeah I
like the
motivation yeah for
me for me it also felt pretty pretty
long it was it was chill was a good
amount of
time
yeah no I have to like specifically give
them the song titles and the group name
and all
that I can't just be like oh add some
Hello project
songs interns
n u but yeah anyway thank you so much
Arthur I'm back and I hope the the weeks
that felt like months didn't feel too
painful or I don't know
too
sad the time is over the wait is over
I'm here now no more need to cry my
beautiful chicken it's all good mommy's
back I'll just go back to enjoying day
by day with your little chicken brain
cuz that's all you can take
anyway H Leo thank you for the red super
chat thank you thank you thank
you welcome back to angel I got a
seeping on my birthday a few weeks ago
no and I still haven't recovered oh what
that's a long one can I get a late
birthday song from my beloved oi also
there's a red envelope for you happy
Luna New Year thank
you was it again something Kaa wasn't it
it's written there I don't remember
the pronunciation was it Shin
KO well thank you so much so much for
your sweet message and the red envelope
but a birthday song okay I'll make an
exception normally I don't like doing
them at least not with the bgm but I can
sing it a little bit for
you oh was that really how you say it
did I say it right I said woohoo I
remembered it let's go happy birthday to
you happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear
Leo even though I'm late I hope you had
a great time and I hope you're healthy
again stay healthy
forever happy birthday to
you congratulations I hope I really hope
you do feel better now it's been weeks
since you got the sea
thing it's about
time thank you T you're welcome
did you eat some yummy
[Music]
cake I want
cake I I have cake in the fridge I have
I have lemon
[Music]
cheesecake in the fridge like a small
small one from
hellofresh no you didn't eat cake what
the hell then go go go go treat yourself
to some cake do it for me it's for you
but do it for me if you have to have
some kind of motivation do it for me you
deserve
it thank you Leo when do you not have
cake in your house quite
often quite often that sounds
what that sounds good ah cheesecake from
Hell fresh yeah they have some desserts
they have actually like besides like
dinner stuff dinner recipes they always
offer like snacks and
desserts and snacks could be anything
like soups to warm up in the microwave
or um just like a selection of bread and
spreads and and ham and
whatever there's a lot of choices uh I
usually only order like some of those
desserts still like little little cakes
in like round round
forms no no I don't make the cake it's
like finished little little little small
cakes they're quite
[Music]
yummy
M your cooking is great thank you I try
I
mean I don't know I don't think I'm that
good I also I I take a long time
chopping I don't even have the right
grip when I
chop so so I'm not the most deficient
and also like my mom always criticizes
me when I when I stir something I just
stir too much like my mom would let
things simmer and chill but I would
always want to stir and stir and stir
cuz I just want things to be
even I know it makes me worried I I feel
like I need to stir stir stir stir stir
stir stir and then I don't even when I
stir I don't even
stir like let's say it's not like a stew
or a soup or whatever let's say I'm
stirring like something that's so to say
dry my mom stirs it with
skill I stir it like really carefully
cuz like usually it's like filling up
the whole frying pan and if I stir too
aggressively then everything like falls
out of
it so I'm really careful when I
[Music]
stir yeah mom's cooking is on another l
level it is on another level one thing I
would say I'm I'm better at cooking than
my mom is
hygiene she may be listening in right
now but every time she cooks in my
kitchen when she cooks something for us
when she's here on a visit I always tell
her mom please please please please
please please wash your hands not like I
mean partially because of my cats cuz
like even if you think even if you look
at your hands in first glance don't see
any cat hairs there are most likely cat
hairs on
there and so I between every [\h__\h]
step I I wash my hands almost every step
at least before I start for sure just to
make sure you
know and also this is like a personal
thing that my mom like for her of course
it's fine and yeah it's not a big deal
but like for example my mom
smokes and then you know
after she smoked or so I don't like she
would just start cooking immediately and
I'm like Mom please wash your hands
please and she's was always
[Music]
like although my mom like generally like
she um doesn't smoke normal cigarettes
anymore except for recently more and
more every time she visits she takes
this visitation as an excuse to smoke
normal cigarettes again and every time
I'm like
momz she even has her Vape with
her
somehow she says I only do it while I'm
here when I'm back I I Vape anyway I'm
like yeah
but I mean it probably makes no
difference at that point but you know
for her no not no no no she will she
will like smoke outside no no not in the
place I'm just like this is more of a a
health concern that I
have like no need to if you are very
used to vaping now for many years and
you have your Vape with
you why why smoke normal cigarettes
now I think it's like cuz it's just
easier I guess is it easier I
guess I don't see
how probably cuz liquid needs to be
refilled or whatever
she she I don't know maybe says it's
more comfortable I don't know but you
know I I would like her to smoke as
little as possible for her
health
mhm probably doesn't have much
effect anymore at this point who knows I
don't really know I'm not a health
expert but you know you know how
straight edge I am
how careful I
am my dad doesn't quit and he's getting
there in age yeah you see my mom too
so she sounds healthier than you though
oh that's I don't know what do you mean
with she sounds healthier
but uh you
mean what what's what where are you
taking that
from she's not really
healthy not going to give details
because that's private but yeah she's
not really
healthy the older you get the more
[\h__\h] up your health gets it is what it
is I
guess who would win an arm wrestling
contest
her her she has a lot of strength from
like Garden working and all
that and then again it also hurts her
and exhausts her like chopping wood and
all that and like bending down to like
rip out weeds and all that she always
says that's a lot of pain and yeah
really difficult more and
[Music]
more but she do be strong she do be
strong
[Music]
she chops wood yeah it's like buying
already chop wood is expensive but wood
itself is also
expensive and
electricity uh like heating with
electricity is way way way more
expensive she tried
that and yeah so the choice is
wood that's metal as
[\h__\h]
it's
metal make sure she's not overextending
herself let she definitely is and I mean
I uh we all tell her but it's not like
like there's much of a choice you
know anyway that's enough I shouldn't
talk too much about this
and where the [\h__\h] am
I sorry Mommy for talking so much about
it you know tangent
tangent Leo me for the pink for food and
pink Super Chat welcome back thank
[Music]
you I appreciate it thank you for being
so sweet and for not leaving kfp while
I'm
gone CR thanks for the pinky welcome
back cutie
pie it's been a bit hard to find
motivation to go to the gym with about
your Kiki and my morning dose of
wow but somehow we all carried on
respect glad you were able to continue
hope your break was relaxing and fun did
you try anything new or exciting well I
did read the
book and I could have finished it if it
was
good I'm telling you and yeah there were
definitely some a lot of exciting
things
and yeah I don't know if I tried much
new stuff though did
I I watched a new
movie and I built a piece of furniture
that's that was that was new never did
it on my own like that before I mean
maybe something small something really
small like a like a sample
cloes Clothing Rack like
a
movable Clothing Rack a really simple
one that's just like a few
tubes screwed together it was in total
four
screws that's like the extent of
furniture building I did
before
yeah t to the Builder yes I
have gained a new a new
title how would you rate those screws in
the tier list those screws um they
weren't so different or special to the
others one was really just a normal ass
screw what you would imagine as a
[Music]
screw the other one I don't even it's
it's not really
memorable
yeah mid tier yeah maybe High mid
tier something like
that will you hand Canam build it I was
thinking about that before but I feel
like in order for you unless it's a
really tiny piece of furniture that will
be done in a minute um how how do I show
it without showing too much of myself
and like my head and everything when I
bend over to like you know do
something
difficult as a live stream difficult
maybe with my my action camera if I like
put it on my on my magnet on my shirt or
on my head um on the cap then I could do
it in in a video form probably and then
I could cut out all the parts that are
like shouldn't show
that that I can do but I wouldn't do it
as a stream even if I mount the stream
camera on my phone I don't trust it no
handun building L Ranger would basically
be impossible pretty much yeah I don't
even I don't really
think like as a vtuber it's difficult a
flesh tuber certainly could do
[Music]
that you know those things that get
advertisement for a lot like this it's
like a a
bookshelf um uh nichan opening thingy
like a like a little it's like you put
it in between some books on a shelf it's
like it's like a little like a mini
miniature
like like street corner for example of
like chairs it's like a cafe and
whatever um you know what I mean it
could be
anything they come in a lot of
variations and I always get those
advertisements and people will build it
themselves and then it turns out to be
really freaking cute like you get the a
book end
yeah you get the materials for it and
you have to fold stuff and maybe glue
stuff or so I don't know do you have
many books though I I definitely have
like use for it it's cute and I kind
of thought about doing it on stream
before maybe buying one and and building
it yeah a book Nook yeah
so so so so
this fell asleep to D and woke up to D
good morning K
[Music]
ke good morning for real for real um
where was I oh yeah so there you go Cruz
I feel like the furniture thing was
pretty
big I feel like I leveled up as a
[Music]
human or I put in a skill point in in
Furniture
building yeah
yeah I feel like I actually learned
something it's been 8 hours oh my God
and it's past
me I don't want to
cook don't ask me about the
treadmill
want I stop it there I don't know I
didn't get that
far it doesn't matter I I slept a lot I
slept really long so I wouldn't go to
bed right away
anyway whatever I'll I'll still
hopefully I'll still cook I hopefully
will still
cook you guys know exactly I told you
why I don't have an urge to use it and
why I bought it in the first
place you know so there's no just
imagine I don't have
it just act like I don't have
it yeah CK now I also could just eat the
rest of the sandwich and then I don't
know something else small but um my
recipes uh one of them has chicken and
one of them has fish and the fish is
expiring oh not even today I think it's
expiring on on the 20th and the chicken
maybe after that or the other way around
I have to I have to cook one of those
things
[Music]
soon
chicken maybe there's so many maybe I I
mean because there's so many I should be
reading
more
Lucario CI thank you for the pinky
Faithfully enjoying energetic
tental
H each word is capitalized Iz in the
beginning are you spelling out
feet
why
why what did I
do well thank you I do like those words
on on on its own Faithfully enjoying
energetic
tenture those are some words to live by
# feet I
guess like
# yoke y Yol #
[Music]
W for the py welcome back it's been a
while hope you enjoyed break times I'm
still enjoying my trip to Austria and
I've been to Vienna's New Year's concert
old castle rural towns camping and El
wow it was the best and unique
experience ever wow seems like you did a
lot lot of
things very
active saw a lot of
things
damn I'm happy to hear that so you're
still there you're still in
[Music]
Austria tell me
more I hope you're eating some yummy
food here too there's so much to eat but
don't feel bad like I feel like you may
run out of like specifically Austrian
things to eat if you're here for a while
so don't feel bad like if you if you eat
something non Austrian for once because
Austria you know we're in the middle of
Europe and we have so many influences
from other countries so you should eat
Hungarian food for example too that's
like something Austrian people also eat
a lot
basically European food central European
food yeah we'll just eat the same thing
again
just just don't necessarily eat like uh
food that's from outside of Europe there
it can still be good but like I feel
like if you're in Europe you should eat
European
[Music]
food so I hope you enjoy the rest of
your time there enjoy make the most out
of it and I'm excited to hear more
stories if you want to share Daisy D
thank
you oh
what Star Wars has been dead to
you for theed Super
Chat
[Music]
for
yes sorry went on a Japanese
tangent don't translate
it where are the usual translators don't
translate
it it's
hazukashi
[Music]
no don't translate
that
no well well well well well
well well well well
well
[Music]
yeah y yeah yay di thanks for the rested
of chat welcome back W I hope you're
feeling refreshed after your break m y
thank you yes I mean maybe it already
honestly kind of wore off the
refreshment wore off a little bit
already cuz it already feels like
everything's back to normal um and this
is already a few days
ago but no I'm good I'm feeling good
thank you so much for welcoming me back
with so much love I appreciate it so
much and oh not toas and another
pinky by the way why am
I doesn't work on arring cats why my
German doesn't work
why maybe you have to say it in an
austan accent let's see how would you
say this non-existing but German
sounding word with an Austrian a
dialect and but
actually stop
oh hard no not so
aggressive it's just about the
intonation I guess cuz I can't really
turn this into different words usually
our dialect changes words a lot but in
this case it's just an
intonation normally you say
sh I guess if you want to kind of
pronounce it in an aan way maybe it's
like
like St hard no I don't know it doesn't
it's difficult because it doesn't even
exist but yeah maybe add like an
OA OA is a good word no no don't call
the cats OA just
say a lot of people go but I hate that
why are you talking like that to a cat
don't go what do you know about cats
go and before my cats are going walk
over
now I
go it's easier to make the sound for
sure it's kind of an amateur way of
calling
[Laughter]
[Music]
cats want to fight want to fight about
it let's fight it out let's
fight that made your dog react
cute
[Music]
clicking does work better on mine you
mean
the yeah I guess it's also like if
you're raising the cat it depends on how
you're raising it if you raise it or
then yeah it's going to react to that a
lot more probably but um
yeah if it's a random cat on the street
H
hm hm
H they might just ignore you whatever
you
do I have head headache my head hord is
coming
[Music]
back uh what was that
again hey
dude 13 King dun Sean on a than o I hope
you're feeling better
too Mano Schneider thanks for the pinky
W back hope you had a great vacation
also St to reminder that fan is close to
finishing now if you haven't gotten to
checking checking it out yet yo I'm
surprised it's actually still
running feel like time has so much so
much time has passed these anime seasons
are longer than I
remember
H A lot of my friends like
it
yeah I don't know we're going to watch
mon
now I'll consider it did you like it
Manuel would you recommend
it Dax Jaden should C thanks for the r
Super Chat wow welcome back thank you
I'm back wa back welcome back wa welcome
welcome wa back oh that one works
too thank you so
sweet it's good you can always watch it
after it's done
[Music]
exactly W back wow W is so b w w what
about Wawa's front everybody always
talks about Wawa's back nobody ever
talks about was front is my front not
nice enough for you I mean yeah I like
having my back
complimented what about my
front oh yeah I know my waa back
appeared in on Bas stream yeah yeah I
saw that mhm I mean I saw a clip of it I
didn't see it at the
[Music]
time we can't see your front but you
can't also you can't see my back you
honestly you can never see my back cuz
I'm 2D
usually if anything you should like my
front that's what you're most familiar
[Music]
with good argument I would say oh well
carer abam thank you for the red super
chat chocolate
thanks for the pinky hi La I missed you
so much these past few weeks I want to
let you know that I will be in Japan for
the first time in my life to support you
next month with
fif I am honored can't wait I'm sure
I'll be meeting many more chickens wait
are you going from
America oh my God your first time in
Japan I'm sure you always wanted to go
and this was a great opportunity to
finally make it
happen yay I think it's going to be so
so so great for you so did you get a
ticket for day
one I hope you did I really hope you did
and I hope you can make a lot of great
experiences besides the festival as
well go to places Wawa talked about
before maybe meet up with other tace G
of Beast if you feel like
it stage one two and free [\h__\h] you got
lucky oh my God some people might be
jealous if you say that out loud too
much they might rob you and then leave
you on the
beach let me tell you the beach around
Tokyo is not so
nice the whole
shebang I have tickets for stage one
honey work and 2 days exp but that's
also actually perfect cuz that's where
I'll
be hey
I'm excited to hear your stories
afterwards so write everything down and
report it to me I want the report on my
desk 2 days after you return by the
latest enjoy and have fun and stay
safe I mean Japan is a safe country
pretty much but you
know I'll go k yes please do K is so fun
and they have good food too but there's
many different K places so Choose Wisely
it doesn't matter they're all great some
are much cheaper than others though much
[Music]
cheaper in Exile red d m HD tangon
spider thanks for the pinky welcome back
Teno thank you I'm back I am I am and I
see spider also still here spider have
you Tak taking care of the kfp by eating
bugs that are not
welcome thank you so much Spider Chicken
Spider chick Spider chick that's
whatever a spider chick
does have you thought about doing
[Music]
homework no we'll watch it together cuz
I don't trust you guys to watch it
properly if uh we don't watch it all
[Music]
ever why not just watch it all together
if you're going to watch it
anyway Spider chick Spider chick does
whatever a spider chick does Spider
chick SP
chick I have a head towards New Egg
hooray hip hip hooray oh oh someone
catch it someone catch it oh thank God I
almost cracked it almost dropped and
cracked we got to be careful with our
our new egg ceremony where we go hip hip
hooray and throw it in the air we really
got to be careful I feel like this kind
of a reckless ceremony that you guys
didn't even know existed but it actually
did
exist kind of
Reckless now that I think about it
we've always been doing
it you guys were once thrown up all the
way in the
air it's some Way El maybe a test to see
if you're
suitable if you crack then well
goodbye then you weren't
[Music]
suitable well you were still small when
you went through that you were still
small egg guys of course you can't
remember you barely have even that one
brain
cell thanks for the membership
gift maybe that's what that was yeah
that
game developed by takan shikiar did you
not see that in the
credits typen thanks for the r Super
Chat somehow during what has has been my
most stressful week work week in a long
time my oer returns to give me a brief
moment of relaxation by trilling Chate
back into my
school welcome back we miss you so much
hopefully the tangent supplies recharge
uh yeah I mean I had good tangents for
that stream but yeah I mean because I I
also just chilled for a lot of the time
and cuddled with cats so you know not
not that much has happened in the time
where I was
gone the things that happened um mostly
I told you
mostly so sorry if you guys expected me
to come back with enough tangents for
two months to tell
you sorry sorry it will never leave my
brain that's that's that's perfect
that's perfect then you will forever
wait for me Choate you're forever Choate
in for
[Music]
me that's how it's supposed to
be you can Ted about not life
experiences like some interesting topics
oh hell yeah I can also because I watch
so many random videos today I watched a
video about okay don't even get me
started I'll keep it for another time if
I remember it next
time but yeah I like this discussing
random [\h__\h]
too so thank you Typhon I I'm sad that
you had to um had to had to had to go
through so much
stress but I'm happy if I was the cause
to make it a little bit better and I
hope it
will forever be
better I hope the stress doesn't catch
up with
you take it easy take it step by step
take it one at a
time you always
[Music]
do I'm happy to hear that thank you so
much I'm glad you're still here every
another CL thanks for the red of chat
she's not she's only taking a short
break what's the Worst That Could Happen
me before Ki went on
vacation it feels like there's more in
the Super Chat like
what about after what about what did
something
happen this feels incomplete to me
Abie Abby are you
okay iby are you
here don't worry about it
well
was in reference to something I said on
the stream maybe
maybe no you just cried H eny come here
let me give you a c hug cult I was
reading the name while I was saying
that oh don't
cry don't cry mommy loves you
everything's okay mommy's here it's
okay all is okay mommy's
here don't cry don't
[Music]
cry thank you
do I'm glad you had some sort of an
emotional reaction to my
absence King shiny Groudon thank you for
the pinky welcome back yaa I hope you've
gotten the break that you need and
feeling refreshed your streams have
helped me get up in the mornings also I
apologize to bring this up but I think
you missed my Christmas ah I think by
now that's fixed right you got you you
got
yours yeah I'm sorry I don't know how
that happened I actually I was using H
lier and I checked everything off uh
while I was doing it but I feel like
maybe I accidentally pressed on
yours and it got checked off just when I
was like clicking into the tab or
something yeah sorry I really f thought
I had everything perfectly this time
damn it and then it turns out I had like
four or five
people that I
forgot not really forgot I wouldn't say
forgot I just didn't see it I'm so
sorry sorry I'm I'm glad though that I
caught everybody I think who in
hindsight told me I didn't get them in
the first run I hope I didn't miss
anyone you're titty heart touching
cutie speaking of crying you made me
almost cry yesterday what what what who
who was it the Valentine's talk I'm
sorry I'm sorry don't
cry it was supposed to make you feel
better at least you got them in the end
yeah I I I hope I got everybody if I
still missed somebody please let me know
one way or the other uh I'll I'll of
course make it for
you yeah it's not on
purpose okay I think I'll leave it at
that for today doing Moonlight number 62
you're
next damn it there's still so many holy
[\h__\h] well but I read like half of it I
think yeah pretty much
[Music]
pretty much half of it sorry my throat
is feeling a little bit tired after and
almost almost 9 hour stream holy
[\h__\h] yeah we're uh we're going to start
late tomorrow 800 P.M
tomorrow 8m W time AKA c s
t mhm we're going to watch I guess
Indiana Jones the first one the first
one from 1980 Something Indiana Jones
[Music]
no
mhm okay thank you thank you so much for
today and no schedule week is already
over holy [\h__\h] already
over no schedule
and uh but uh yeah we'll we'll do some
streams for
sure wasn't there something I wanted to
do
[Music]
before did I pay all my
bills I think I did was I supposed to do
something I want to put a Dave to diver
gaming request
in by the way I know I didn't I I
haven't been making stream ending tweets
it's just because I I'm I'm feeling
awkward about
it but I've also been thinking um maybe
I want to transition into something
else I've been
thinking uh the members will P up yes I
reuploaded that yeah yeah I did did I
not I think I did
yesterday uh it was something else like
not what I was thinking about I think
was something
[Music]
else um I was thinking maybe we could
push the algorithm a little bit instead
of focusing on Twitter maybe I mean a
lot of you already comment even though I
barely look at them like only rarely do
it but what if we just like focus on
YouTube like you guys comment on YouTube
there's no length restriction there
too and um I will do my usual like
feedback check whatever you want to call
it on YouTube instead and then leave
likes on YouTube because uh that kind of
interaction also boosts the channel you
guys com will comment more the ones who
have F been focusing on
Twitter using YouTube might boost the
algorithm and me interacting with your
comments will boost the algorithm too I
think yeah should we do that because I
feel like alternate both I can't really
like look at both it's so much to look
at you guys don't even understand uh I
know you can't post images you're still
welcome to post images
though just use maybe the hashtag if
there's anything you want to let me know
about with an image of course also that
the the replies I'm still going to check
the replies but I'm just saying like
maybe as our after tweet after stream
ritual instead of the after tweet what
if you guys what if we just do it on the
board to help
the yeah yeah yeah I mean that's
literally what I mean like heting your
posts counts as interaction so I would
be doing
that it doesn't matter if I'm addicted
to X I'm saying we're moving it over
here so that we can boost the
algorithm solid battle plan
yeah I already do both thank
you for doing
that yeah actually using YouTube
comments in the way they're intended to
be
used don't don't ask so many like Niche
questions yeah if it's an archive un
archive streams whatever we can do it on
Twitter not every stream needs an after
tweet
[Music]
anyway
oh my God
ah ah sorry I'm mightly
annoyed it's been too long it's almost 9
hours and you reply on YouTube you won't
who says
that who says
that if I if I say we're going to do
this whole thing on YouTube that I'm
also going to be doing repes on
YouTube think chicken
think why you got to be so
complicated you'll still get your
replies and your
likes Mama Mia Mama m you but you know I
still love Twitter and I don't want to
completely leave Twitter of course not
and I don't know if you've noticed but I
actually I really like going through the
hashtag to see what you tweeted during
the stream as well like cuz like I get
kind of like a live reaction there again
I kind of get a kick out of it so I love
I love looking at the hashtag too so you
guys should use the hashtag more often
as well Twitter hasht hash your kfp hash
your kfp has your kfp I you
[Music]
as Next Step surprise Discord
DMS yeah but basically I just thought
why don't we do the whole Twitter after
tweet thing on YouTube because with that
we can push the algorithm
probably wouldn't that be so
smart I I learn you like a lot on the
yeah yeah yeah
yeah you should just comment in the and
here during
streams that's okay too however you want
to do it I don't I'm not going to like
tell you you have to use the hashtag on
Twitter and tweet in the middle of my
streams no need at all just letting you
know I check it out a lot
[Music]
actually let look got my waa
PES yeah every once in a while you have
so many anyway I feel like out of all of
Ian you guys have the most
pngs from the
streamer I don't see anybody else
posting so many pngs clean pngs to use
to
save not even in on the Japanese
side
yeah streaming in 720p is bad for the
algo well what can I do about it is that
really true not that I can fix that
right
now move to other social media like blue
sky oh I was literally like what the
[\h__\h] is this again on my break I noticed
something like popping up that looks
exactly like Twitter and I'm like what
the [\h__\h] is
this I'm like oh why why so many new
things why why is old also all the kind
of like apps that are trying to recreate
insta or or Twitter and so on they all
just they're
all the problem is like even if a few
people join it's never going to have
that kind of momentum a big enough
momentum to be an actual good
rival to a site like that and and yeah
especially for people who already are so
active and have like a big following on
certain sites it's just unrealistic to
make everybody move over there
unfortunately really
unfortunately it's really bad to kind of
like push one of these big websites may
it be YouTube may it be Facebook
whatever off of their phone although
Facebook I would say Facebook is dead I
I don't know I stopped using Facebook
long time AG go um I don't know if
anybody okay I think a lot of people
still use it but there's a certain type
of people who still use it and in some
countries Facebook is um more active
than in
others always has
been I think Facebook is active very
active in Indonesia I've
heard yeah but yeah I'm not going to
move onto some random new Twitter clone
that popped up it looks looks nice and
you know it's just
a yeah what would be cool if they
finally give us access to the H life
Twitter there's like a this thing that
we just still don't have access to like
the fans have access to it but we don't
have access to it still and I asked
about it before and it was like I don't
know something something
something but that I would like consider
for sure like we should not like
completely move over there um but yeah
maybe use it at the same time and
then
yeah yeah I think it was
like not not maybe not properly
translated yet or something I don't know
yeah it's currently Just J Japan
only I don't know what's going on at all
but yeah anyway I'm going to go now and
say see you tomorrow for the members
only
stream byebye o me good
night am I really going to
cook I don't want
[Music]
to
w
[Music]
o
hey I wanted to raid KY but I don't have
permission to rate
KY
[Music]
sad I don't see any other live
stream man
[Music]
righta go go or people go
go