[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
ah
kick it again
[Music]
I'm not feeling so well let me just tell
you that
uh I think I might be in the beginning
of
deceiving
round two baby
I was always like thinking oh my God I'm
like
so lucky or
immune because I don't go outside so it
doesn't hit me
whatever feverish but I don't have a
fever yet but I also didn't have a fever
last time I I had to see things I think
if I remember correctly but I really
wanted to do this today because first of
all I said I would do it
second of all today is the first of
Advent so I have to do it today
not that I really care but I didn't use
a cool house
what the [\h__\h] foreign
none of I really care
oh maybe it's the room
I might have gotten the wrong love
oh
[Music]
so so so I'm supposed to like the first
candle on this Sunday
so I need to make the wrap you know the
reef the reef reef reef the roof
um also we have a mongoose later
um because
surprise we're doing a collaboration
with some Ian and some ID members
um some ID members because we didn't
have enough am members
they
um they asked
us to do some amuku streams for
promotion
because some of the merchandise is
running out
um Mia
[Music]
oh
um and I said yes I will do it but uh we
didn't have enough en members so here we
are
um let me try this glove again it feels
like it's not the right right side
am I going crazy
looks like the Red glove to me
is wrong
it feels so wrong
well no don't make these weirds quiet
meals let me let me find it right or
another and I'll be right back
I'll be right back I'll be right back
[Music]
yeah
yes yes yes
I think it's like the beginning because
I know you know my throat hurts from
talking every now and then a lot but
this is different this feels very
different and I'm I'm feeling that I'm
getting weaker so I know
something's wrong
um I'll take tomorrow off most likely
but for now
for now we'll go according to kikaku
because I want to make this I was
looking forward to this yeah it might
also be a cold whatever it doesn't
[\h__\h] matter I'm sick
yeah
but it could be deceiving because I
never get a normal cold never never
never it's
in like physically impossible for me to
get a normal cold last time I had a
normal cold was maybe 10 years ago
the only thing got me once was
[Music]
so
are you here in the BCM
you're hearing the bells ring
foreign
[Music]
I do have a shuttle of tea once again I
also have pumpkin soup before not that
that helps against the cold but you
would think you know soup is kind of a
thing you eat when you're sick and I had
some soup soup
yummy pumpkin soup
um yeah like pumpkin soup
should I like write for people who come
in
uh
am a bit sick
no energy
[Music]
sorry my son
don't have to like continuously
[Music]
but making us because it's not so
difficult I watch the video too
um to see how the pros make it
oh my God
[Music]
okay there we go we put it here so
people know what's up
[Music]
um
how are you guys doing hope you guys are
not getting sick
I might be like always looking to that
side but let me see what I can do oh
sure there we go
uh yeah you know hand game streams
tracking is do you know
mizukasi I actually feel a bit sick
right now
[Music]
okay guys uh I hope I hope I hope that
this camera angle is okay
I hope this camera angles okay
oh hello hi
hello
hi
there's like this paper that I wrapped
this stuff in
um if we take it away
you might see all the mess on the sides
that's not on the table
I'll try to keep that paper there so
that you don't have to
see the [\h__\h] mess that my room is
mostly because of cables and [\h__\h]
um let's not look at that no no no no no
I don't even want I only yeah
I mean I mean over there that's my
that's my printer
that's my printer and that's my other
table you know it's like connecting
connecting here this is the connecting
table
shits no one cares about what is this
random
random [\h__\h]
random [\h__\h] everywhere
[Music]
I said yes
I got some I got some tea
this is Arts night little healthy
this is the holy tea I got it from the
pope personally just kidding but it is
uh called holy tea in German
it's better than normal tea Oh
supposedly we will see how it will
heal me nothing can heal me I am broken
the Presto espresso meow
yeah
so what do we have here let me touch
some grass I'm touching the grass is
this grass it's very Pokey no wonder
people don't want to touch grass no
wonder let me make me stabbing
oh this is the this is the collab Cafe
Cup by the way here
see and Annie plus no that's something
else
[Music]
um so do you guys know what uh whatever
Christmas Adventist
you know what it is
shall I tell you
what's going on
so it's kind of in the thumbnail but
also not really I just chose that
picture because it was you know it had
the decoration materials and all that
kind of stuff there was kind of fitting
but it was missing one important thing
is missing the candles so anyway we're
making a round thing
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
we're gonna do it with some wire I got
some wire
um and we're gonna do it with layers
because
chihuahua has layers and I love layers
we don't know that
yeah I'm starting from scratch I could
have already bought like the circle
thing with the green stuff already and
then just decorated it but I wanted to
start from scratch yeah so now I got
these
these chunks of green broccoli
and we're gonna I already tested the
scissor works
we're gonna use the scissor to cut off
about a size
of pieces these are real by the way it's
not plastic
that's why it was a bit more expensive
but it's nice
smells nice mmm I want a hashtag there
you go
[Music]
I'm gonna cut the pieces up and the
middle parts We're Not Gonna use because
they're too chunky and
um they don't look nice
they're too chunky like you can't you
can't really wrap this only the sides
we're gonna do it you know around the
face and then we're gonna add the
decorations and add the candles and then
hopefully maybe light the candles but I
don't know about that because I have
some I told you before I have lighters
but
um
I have two liners freshly bought but I
can't get them to work
um
so maybe you just have to use
imagination I was like you know the ones
that you like
doesn't like
[Music]
I don't know I did I didn't look I will
try again but I don't see a lot
maybe with the gloves it might work with
my normal skin it did not work
anyway so what what that is by the way I
didn't really explain what exactly that
is so this thing uh I guess is common in
at least in Christian
uh religion
um they uh for four Sundays the four
Sundays Before Christmas doesn't matter
if Christmas is on a Sunday
yeah doesn't matter you know if the if
Christmas is on a Sunday then I wonder I
guess you like the last candle on
Christmas I guess but even if it's not
then you light it before but the 47 is
before Chris Christmas you like one of
those candles and it's called Uh Advent
wreath Advanced guns
now I
I want to say I am I am not
religious but I I I I
in in Austria even if you're not really
religious then you still kind of do it
because it's pretty and I like it and
it's pretty and I like it it's like
Christmas you know even if you're not
really religious you still celebrate
Christmas
haha
um and this is pretty and I also thought
it would make for a good uh crafting
stream for the
um the Christmas season because last
year we did
um
last year we did make a gingerbread
house remember
you Whispering I don't know
[Music]
um
yes so what what's your problem what are
you trying to say
um the the lady at the store who helped
me gather all the materials she did
recommend using
um a hot glue gun for adding the
decorations
um so that's that is fair play okay it
is fair play it's absolutely normal
to use that okay but we're not gonna
attach these with hot glue ideally we're
just gonna use a wire and wrap it around
wrap it around wrap it around because
then you would even be able to reuse the
base a year later if you wanna
then it's not all messed up because
everything is just tightly secured with
uh the wire anyway let me drink some tea
this does not smell good
won't that take a lot of water well I do
also have a lot of wire
um I have a lot of
a lot of
um stuff decorations I even bought like
a plate and let me try to open this
sack
of
um
chunkers go away
I swear go away
we don't need you here
I love you but you scare me if you jump
on this
Construction
I don't know what's going to happen
people gonna see sick pajama kiwawa and
we're gonna
say oh my God
oh my God she's not a phoenix
[Music]
the more I talk of you guys
the better I feel
Christmas miracle
[Music]
I I'm actually wearing partially the
same pajamas as kudos
the pants so okay we have
[Music]
oh no the noise of plastic
the Beloved noise of plastic
[Music]
how many have you ever see the camera
like slowly slowly slowly moving I think
it's stable but just just let me know if
that's happening ever
cable though
[Music]
smells good
okay so I am
um a lot of like
stuff to decorate like these weird
things
and some orange stuff and more orange
stuff and some some small okay
some small little pine cones
and a lot of other things smaller pine
cones some golden stars ah cinnamon
sticks we're gonna use those for
decoration and the candles
oh they're heavy the candles are orange
but they wear a lot of different colors
and this is like a little bit I think it
looks it looks really bright here
but it's a little bit more like a
brownish calm Orange in reality
it's very saturated hair
and I wear some crazy oranges but I felt
like a little bit of a
not so much in your face orange might be
good
um and we have this oh they're a bit
shiny but we have these candles
um
holders that we stick in there and one
other end sticks into the candle
it's cozy that's good
and then here we have the wire I have a
big amount of wire in green so it
doesn't stand out too much but we need
to hide it well
nonetheless awesome
oh one more thing I don't know this
looks good to me because I see some I
looked for some inspiration on Advent
wreaths and some of them have flowers
and stuff too and these were orange so I
thought they're kind of cute I think
they're dry flowers
but yeah pretty I mean looking at this
part I guess they're really dry but this
part looks so it's so bright and
it doesn't look dry at all so I'm quite
surprised they are real though real good
choices
I mean you know I obviously chose orange
because of image color reasons but
um you know I think there might be
better color choices
um
but it fits with one item that I
definitely wanted to have there's
oranges dried oranges ideally in
combination of cinnamon sticks
[Music]
um okay so
um I'm gonna start now
um let me like hmm
[Music]
um
I have a plate next to me where I will
put the all the cut off pieces
okay let's do this
let's start with the top one
see how much we get out of it
this might be a little bit messy because
you know these things that
they fall off so easily and oh my God
it's almost uh November is almost over
oh
can you imagine
[Music]
can you imagine oh my god oh this one is
actually pretty big I don't know if I
should cut it there if I can't even cut
it there
I have one look here it's pretty thick
all right no yeah I don't have a oh it
smells good
don't have a proper scissor for this um
[\h__\h] that one is too thin
[Music]
maybe I'm just gonna cut it off a little
bit more in the middle
yeah
hmm
oh hey I broke it with my hand
when in doubt use voice
[Music]
these are the iron and ideal size anyway
don't need it any longer than that
[Music]
also okay
yeah so what I was saying is it's almost
Christmas baby
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I wanted to say sheesh but
also sheet
I believe it's already
time already the end of the year season
time goes by so fast
[Music]
these ones are all very fake
I might have to get rid of them a lot of
them by force foreign
[Music]
have a home where it goes
chunky wonky that I see you on the
ground
[Music]
I also don't have a saw either
what cannot it goes to time goes to
Canada
uh-huh
is that so
let me try to
start talking here
[Music]
don't worry I have other scissors I know
that this might like make this scissor
useless but
oh wow I'm impressed you were able to
crack that oh
quite chunky not as chunky as chunky
monkey
you might consider different implements
what does that mean
[Music]
well
smells good now
knives I don't have a different
Bowl
except like a bread knife
[Music]
I don't know for how long
looks amazing
these were the last ones by the way that
the store had so I'm pretty lucky where
do I put this anything
oh this one's really thin I was also
kind of dying here yeah this one's
this one's not looking so good I guess
I'll use it anyway
we use everything
this one really looks
sad oh maybe I should just cut it up
here hey hey
what nice I guess this also could be
used like this but this doesn't look
nice then I only
cut this part
has anyone done this before ever
making a wreath on your own
also my tea is already cold I need to
drink more
[Music]
no no as a kid yes okay almost everybody
says no but have you you spawned before
and bought one before
because I mean I've had many before but
I just didn't make it myself
yes
yes no
okay a couple people have used them
before
[Music]
already I have so many like small single
pieces that's not ideal but okay I'm
gonna cut
maybe here this is an interesting piece
it's kind of cultural events fascinate
me yeah I guess in Korea they don't have
this
[Music]
Pam probably also not I don't think I've
seen a an advent pray for the floor
in Japan
oh that's a big boy
there's a big boy
nice
sharing content yeah
once again
I think you know I I just I'm just glad
I had uh no I guess it wasn't really my
idea and some of you I had yet I'm glad
I'm glad you came up with like a nice
hand crafting theme idea
always looking for a good ideas you know
that
[Music]
by the way I played a little bit more
Pokemon today again
when I was like chilling
I was just exploring again though don't
worry no dialogue missed whatsoever
nothing
[Music]
I did catch like a dolphin I caught a
lot of Pokemon thinking that you know I
need to catch more because
otherwise I don't get all of those items
because I caught one of the I caught the
dolphin
with like I caught a lot of Pokemon that
I don't plan on using but I don't think
I feel like you might go into the team
after all
dolphin looks funny
and also oh my God I saw the
I saw it I got spoiled I didn't see it
myself when I saw the evolution
of the [\h__\h] Stone the Tiny Stone
Pokemon
it's a [\h__\h] Minecraft thing
what the heck yeah
[Music]
not so pretty
I guess I'll just cut the smaller ones
again
hi
[Music]
salt crystal that thing is crazy strong
like literally
Golem yeah oh yeah it must be a
reference like that is so 100 Minecraft
you cannot tell me it is not
hmm
stop trying to guess like me
they having me so cute
well I guess if you like Minecraft then
you don't have a problem with him
[Music]
piece that was a good piece
trying to be a pyramid thing lies
gaslighting as I told you lies lies lies
lies lives
don't let them manipulate you
[Music]
these are so
pretty and fresh
the green stuff is so
um
so full of green
[Music]
oh it smells
because I'm gonna get a Christmas tree
this year because last year I got it and
then I immediately got rid of it and
also I mean I got rid of it so quickly
because I thought it might be causing my
cats some allergies but it doesn't seem
to be the case but still it was kind of
useless because nobody ever comes to
visit me
it was
the only time it was saved by people was
when my my family
stay at my place for one night
the only thing I'm considering is
getting a plastic one I had a plastic
one before
so
yeah maybe I'll get another plastic one
that I can reuse
the plastic ones are so much Miss Hit or
Miss but usually Miss
where do you buy a good plastic
Christmas tree
plastic ones are nice these days
like getting small fake ones
I have to create a good and you don't
have to cut
you gotta see him in person first yeah
maybe in like uh does IKEA sell probably
right
I can't probably sells them
I can't imagine
[Music]
okay this is these are so tiny hmm
when I can't just use the middle of
chunky part either
[Music]
she just bought mine at Target
yeah yeah yeah yeah well previously when
I bought plastic ones I bought them on
Amazon
[Music]
chances are you get your shitty tree
it's not very satisfying I think the
small piece
[Music]
small piece is too small but I think we
have a lot of material to work with I
hope this will be
enough
the lady said she thinks it will be
enough so
if not
I will go back and complain
just kidding oh this one's a good one
[Music]
where do I cut this one if I cut it like
here
it's pretty long but it's like
oh my gosh
but
it bends quite well and I could try to
wrap it all the way around
[Music]
normally feel like they should have like
kind of the same length
[Music]
if I cut it here then the rest of it
will be kind of useless
because of the ends looking pathetic
[Music]
best of husky
I have a I've cut it here and if I feel
like it's wrong I can still cut it
shortcut anyway
[Music]
we'll just do this first as a lower
layer
[Music]
okay
oh it still has this other good side oh
that's also a good one I'm also Gonna
Take the Long part here
I want to go to a Christmas Market
Christmas markets are already open
apparently but I didn't get to go yeah I
need to go because most Christmas
markets close after Christmas which I
think is so stupid they should at least
go into
um New Year's
[Music]
some some go a bit longer but not most
of them the good ones the big ones close
oh but I guess it doesn't matter because
after Christmas and after Japan anyway
[Music]
I am being capable
let's go on this part also works
yay yay
good pieces
I dare you
if you even consider coming up here
I think I'm kind of done yeah these
remains are
I think not not necessary
[Music]
let me put them away
come on it's gonna throw them on the
ground for now
don't get monkeys
no phone case no
[Music]
here we have
three face
[Music]
okay
so this is uh this is made out of this
grass or the grass so I'm touching a lot
of grass today
us
how are you so I think we have to start
by
kind of
um
let's see like
ah I posted into my blog oh no we are
going to
um
[Music]
I guess do it at this boy like suing
sewing so close but no I'm going I'm
going inside you can like poke it inside
quite well
and then turn it around
there's some weird fluffy stuff from the
not actually not cat hairs surprisingly
okay okay
there you go this is the start just so
that it's in there put it there
[Music]
um
my mom uses the exact same Wire yeah it
needs to be green you know
so it doesn't stand out
thanks for watching donkey monkey go
somewhere
[Music]
else so this is a long boy but ideally
I'll wrap it around like that and then
put the smaller pieces on top and I have
another long board so we can do that you
know
[Music]
all right you're gonna try let's get
started
do this
I'm not gonna close the door like cats
that's like it's winter
[Music]
you can't close the door on anyone
otherwise the Christmas spirit will
visit you and say oh you are mean
on your YouTube mean
[Music]
no idea so if I do this and I kind of
have to go around double
but I think I have enough wire to go
around double I should feel right
I'm only normally you don't do that
[Music]
of the year
okay the other big one
let's connect it
okay this part doesn't Bend well
I have to teach her how to bend
make it more European
[Music]
okay we'll just have to force to
download The Wire
[Music]
I think today I'm so proud of my camera
angles best angle I've ever had
it's a weird thing to be happy about I
guess
[Music]
obviously we will do our best to cover
the ugly parts
later on
[Music]
let's see for this because I feel like
really uh Clumsy
leveled up my camera
[Music]
but yeah it's easy to see everything
right normally I think we all like to go
a bit closer because we're scared of
showing
too much
I'm scared of it too but well
hi
hi now
bend down your little [\h__\h]
[Music]
nice
I like it obviously we're gonna fill it
up completely so that there's only green
okay okay
now basically we don't do one by one we
we want to take like a chunk
several little pieces huh
I wonder if there's any mommies watching
right now
makes you shake your shoulders
really starting to take shape yeah I
mean it already had a shape didn't it it
was round that wasn't me
I didn't do much
I just made some of the green more
European
okay on this part this part needs to be
held down a bit more chocolate weight
foreign
[Music]
I'll just keep the bottom empty but the
sides have to be filled up nicely
so I guess I'll just line it up
here
maybe one more
a couple of smaller ones
oh yes
it's it's a grass furry wreath
it looks so fluffy there we go oh yeah
and there's absolutely no problem with
it you know looking fluffy towards the
outside
we want it to
um be fluffy I don't know how much to
hold down though not too much I wanted
to be like
feet
perfect and have volume
good we have basically the first the
first part the first round it looks good
I don't see
I can't look at it so well but I don't
see really anything that bothers me
okay
[Music]
um
even if you see the wire if even if I
don't try to hide it so well you don't
see it it's like the same color
doesn't stand out at all and I can still
hide some imperfections with decorations
later
um the branches are triggering your cat
what you mean like here on screen are
they looking at it I've noticed when
I've watched like certain things on my
on my TV this movie will follow it and
look at it really curiously like Pokemon
for example when I show her Pokemon on
the TV screen I guess that one's is
pretty easy to
um follow with her eyes so she looks at
that it's so cute
that gives me like it feels it feels
like you know we're watching something
together which is so weird because it's
a cat and I'm a phoenix and you would
think that we're not capable of enjoying
such things together but it seems like
we are okay
um oh wait
to go backwards and then at the end
you have to go backwards not that way I
have to go this way so that I can layer
like this I can't just I keep trying to
stick it underneath but it's not very
easy I think okay why are you have to
come back with me
I'll be all right oh but then
so
hmm
[Music]
it will be fine I only watched one
tutorial video and that's a couple hours
ago I don't quite remember but I'm just
shouldn't be too difficult I trust my
skills
basic basic skills this is gonna be so
fluffy oh
[Music]
I can't see what the inside looks like
foreign
[Music]
okay
that's fine it's fine it's amazing I can
make this as my new profession I can
make it for people sell it online oh my
God
so no problem no worries about my future
now
I'd buy one you can tell me the color
you want Green Halo Kiana SC yeah please
please I'll give you a discount code for
my Etsy
I sound like a mom
[Music]
well I I am a mom of many chickens
foreign
[Music]
might only have to use this one
oh
what a perfect piece I love how I'm just
appreciating the branches for what they
are
beautiful French
appreciation oh
let me take air on the side very empty
though
[Music]
oh yeah
what's up
finally today mommy said boy messaged me
that's okay yeah Melanie said by message
me you know I was planning on asking
some members do you know to hang out I
don't know already I already asked
Solana members but mommy examples kind
of
um you know messaged me by herself on
her own without you know waiting for me
maybe she saw the clip there was a clip
I think even translated to Japanese she
may have seen it what I talked about you
know wanting to meet with her and do the
sleepover and she asked me
so I don't feel so you know I don't feel
unwelcome she asked me if I want to
sleep over
and yeah she was very
[Music]
excellent she's such a good senpai
we're gonna do the sleepover
[Music]
too much
we can't go back now though with the
wire
hang on maybe I can
[Music]
questions
a bit too much let's let's go back
um
[Music]
okay
yeah she's a great person
um
I don't know if we'll share a bed
I mean you guys know maybe if you listen
to my stories before how I feel about
sharing a bed with people in general
anxious
or many reasons
[Music]
foreign
bye
I wonder how the inside looks
[Music]
this is basically a Christmas tree
okay
[Music]
oh this one's really visible though
actually ah
I do see the wire a lot
I can't hear you
but I can cover it up with decorations
it's
down
[Music]
you don't look in the wrap that closely
Well the lady the lady in the video did
it so well you couldn't see it at all
she had the perfect wrapping technique
[Music]
I see a little bit of a bald spot there
you guys probably don't see it though
[Music]
imperfections is What Makes You
Beautiful
[Music]
philosophical Felix
foreign
[Music]
but I wasn't invited to something
that um that includes like five
different whole life Japan members that
I haven't met yet
um kind of like a dinner party I guess
[Music]
yeah so I'm excited about that too but
it's perfect I get like five birds with
one stone
because you know I wanna meet as many
members as possible also I understand I
also got back to me
[Music]
[Laughter]
the shrine day so
[Music]
everything is going according to Hip Hop
come on
[Music]
very cheap
indeed I'm excited
especially about the dinner party
maybe we can go karaoke too
if they got some time
foreign
[Music]
concerts
laughs
[Music]
that's what I'm doing
um
okay this is a big bunch big bunch of
smaller pieces
[Music]
okay
nice
all right I'm very close to the to the
end
why would that be risky it's private
rooms are you thinking of like a karaoke
bar Japanese Kadoka is all private rooms
and you know
that's why I like it so much
I don't go to any other karaoke
sing Marine treasure box song
oh
foreign
[Music]
Austria we have like
um
uh one like Japanese restaurant that I
know of
that has uh really and it has one room
with really really really really really
really really really really really
really
old Japanese kind of looking machine but
it doesn't even have like the input
system it has like the book and you know
in Japanese it's not even so modern
and they surely had it like 10 years ago
yeah 100 because I saw it 10 years ago
even 15 years ago they had the display
where you can look for the songs by
typing in the title or the name of the
artist now in that old karaoke machine
you don't get that you get like a
catalog that is this big
to go through and it's really old too so
the pages and all the song Choices are
blue and then you have to type in the
number and then remote control but at
least it has Japanese songs and at least
it's a room and it's kind of like the
closest you can get here
um it has some English songs too I think
but I mean I kind of first thing in
Japanese songs
how are we looking here what are we
doing here
I wonder what do I need to cover
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think I'm speaking of caveman Alba
what I love Alba
[Music]
I love Papa no it stops intended
foreign
[Music]
okay I don't have many pieces left but
the pizza that I have left are pretty
big
now
[Music]
it's gonna this is gonna hope for the
best outcome
foreign
[Music]
how's it looking guys from up there
we're gonna meet this
hope the balance is good this part
bothers me a little bit
it looks darker because it's not going
up because I I tied it down too much so
it's not catching the light reflection
I'm gonna try to freeze some of them
foreign
[Music]
there we go there we go there we go
you're free that looks already much
better
[Music]
free as well
I think I said you are too crazy but you
know what who am I to hold you down who
am I to stop you from letting go of your
feelings and emotions I was way too
aggressive here
now hmm
[Music]
there we go
okay
okay okay this
oh God I only have I only have these
spray pieces two tiny ones the one big
one left oh no wait one four one more I
have one here on this side
but we're kind of at the end so I think
it's all right
[Music]
yeah because this is the end so I'm just
supposed to like kind of stick it in
there tie it up a bit more hi hi what up
which part you mean the fluffy ones no
they're supposed to be a little bit
fluffy
man you can also make it really tight
but then that's probably only tight
because you gotta stick up your butt
foreign
[Music]
okay
all right
one more twist
and then we start the fun part
of decorating
give to my personal preference
[Music]
where are you
that was also skin uh glove
yes
[Music]
okay what do I do at the end I forgot
I think I just cut it off and then I try
to like
squeeze it in somewhere probably
yeah
yeah it's okay all right it's okay
I cut it it's like a official
officinating ribbon ceremony
[Music]
kind of untightens itself a little bit
when I
let go of it
might be an issue but
pretty compact
[Music]
I mean it stays where it should be kind
of okay
um
okay yes I know the signs are kind of
yeah bye maybe I should cut them
I said you can go and do what you want
but now I'm feeling concerned about it
I'll try it
huh if you like it this way keep it do I
like it let me look
s are definitely too much but maybe I
can like as I said hold them down with
some
um
decorations now I have this plate that
for some reason was really expensive
14 bucks
to go with the reef
so I'm gonna just place it on there
already I guess
Big Daddy's Eyes
I don't know why it's so expensive I
bought it at the same place you could
definitely get it cheaper but you know
now hot glue hot glue the new one
because the the purple one that you see
him there are some dead
does not exist anymore where do I where
do I
where do I have uh
kill this for once
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
sorry microphone
yeah
and I kind of wanna
it's different tea
[Music]
tea time
you're annoying
[Music]
tomorrow
foreign
[Music]
ah
fluff what time
[Music]
on or off
like a little button here
I think it's already getting warm
a little bit warm
so it's probably on
I'm assuming it's on
okay
okay so
um
should I put the candles first and then
the decorations
probably right that we don't even need
the hot chocolate yet
[Music]
because it's green
yeah I think you know some people most
people have the candle like one here one
across one here one across you know
balance but also there's reefs where
you'll just have them all next to one
another and then they're just focused in
one area and the rest is decorations
I think I'll do the classic way
where I put
them
in the North
uh East South West
that is surely North 100 no
um I think
uh they said the long part goes into the
wreath and the other part into the
candle
it has like a
plastic cap there you go
so I'm gonna stick that into the candle
I guess is that easy
is that going
oh it already has a hole
oh and there's actually like a metal I
think let's see like that's probably not
metal but there's some kind of like base
there
so it's not oh oh it goes on smoothly
and that's actually easy
okay so let's say
[Music]
yeah yeah one just goes here
oh I'm so happy I'm making this I feel
so like
DIY
and the DIY queen baby
fun I recommend doing this
it's a cute Christmas decoration for the
season and if you if you buy the real
ones
um they stay
nice longer if you like spray them a
little bit with water and
um at night time because you know
obviously winter time you want to keep
your apartment warm so a lot of people
uh heat right so that's not good for
this real stuff so you should put it
outside your balcony or turn off the
hitting there tonight or put it
somewhere where it's a little bit colder
if you have some space at the night time
because you're not looking at it during
the night time anyway right when you're
sleeping and that will help it stay a
fresh longer
so some hydration would be good and a
cold space so don't put it right in
front of your fireplace or right in
front of your heater
this one's kind of um
not you know perfect but that's okay why
is it not perfect
I don't know why
[Music]
um okay so directly across
I think that's directly across
[Music]
and they don't have any smell I think
but at least they're a nice color they
were also a bit more expensive
um a more expensive candles the more
expensive candles were the ones that
when you burn them that the inside is
the same color as the outside
but I was like whatever because these
ones if you burn them they're white
inside
that's okay no problem with that it
already cost so much this whole
decoration set the small like little
pieces of decoration they were like like
80 cents each most of them 20 80 cents
each
um I don't I still don't know what cost
so much but overall the whole set was
like I said what 80 80 Euro or so 80
dollars
you can totally go cheaper and just make
a simpler oh sure is that is that a
direct I mean I think it looks good
you can go cheaper if you just make it
more simple simplistic is also fine
yeah
the pockets are white and orange yeah I
wanted to be
I mean because it burns to become white
yeah yeah I guess that's true
it doesn't matter anyway
[Music]
s
you know uh parks on the rack where the
main character character the main what's
her name Leslie was it Leslie I think it
was it was a nutshell or maybe it was a
different similar show
where
there she's like I I don't need a
measure I I can just you know if she
does this and she turns around and just
a completely different size
I wonder was that Parks and Rec or was
it
Arrested Development I'm not sure I saw
it in one of those shows and it's so
true wait maybe that's not even now that
I think about it I saw it on Community
Channel
[Laughter]
them both were mixing something up
completely because the good old YouTube
channel Community Channel who remembers
Australian YouTuber from back in the day
made so many funny little skit videos
she's not active for a long time yeah
nah nah just the best I've been watching
her since 15 years ago at least if not
longer I was so sad when she started
being inactive and stopped making videos
on a regular basis but she made one one
video about measuring just with your
hands and your eyes
what a veteran yeah
[Music]
um
around the time where I'm YouTube was
starting to
become popular and had all these
these famous YouTubers who were still
like mostly
how to say like
decent people
[Laughter]
people who get famous on YouTube
nowadays they just like they come to
YouTube for the sake of getting famous
uh like you know those those two
brothers
uh who are [\h__\h] stupid
do we know who I'm talking about I don't
even want to say their names yes p
those people who like the whole YouTube
presence is about
I don't even know I don't I don't
know like is it about anything at all
besides making chaos and getting Fame
from that
[Music]
and that's that area when they started
to become famous was when all those
YouTube houses started right in like
mostly I mean I only really saw them in
America though
all those YouTube houses where they
bring in like some shitty influencers
who want to leech off the fame of others
and uh yeah so then you appear in the
videos of the others and they appear in
your videos so you can leech off of them
today
one pranks another and every day like
the the main the most famous person of
the YouTube house will sleep with
another girl or whatever so that there's
big drama but mostly only for the
YouTube videos in the end and anyway you
know he thinks he has like the biggest D
in the world anyway so he can do
whatever he wants because he's got the
YouTube money oh so famous she has all
your fans are six year olds wow wow
impressive oh god oh don't even know
um
foreign oh God I heard I heard that that
one wedding that a certain P brother had
with a certain other lady
you know they broke up really fast right
it was all for [\h__\h] like famous like
you know views
have relationships for the sake of views
which is however interesting though that
it does isn't like American YouTube
culture it brings you views but like in
other cultures it will destroy you that
is also interesting isn't it
but anyway I just want to say that
YouTube or YouTubers used to be better
15 years ago when not everyone wanted to
be a [\h__\h] YouTuber for their [\h__\h]
profession but those YouTubers 15 years
ago they who had it as their profession
only got it as a profession because they
ended up luckily doing so well that they
realized oh I guess I can't do this as a
profession but they didn't originally
plan to do it just like Jenna Marbles
Jenna Marbles best best girl Community
Channel and Jenna Marbles
love love love love
[Music]
I did not
like or watch Shane Dawson
[Music]
and who else
I did watch a little bit of PewDiePie
back in the day shouldn't they have
computer pay just fine don't watch him I
haven't watched him since many many
years though
oh I don't watch Mr Beast
um Smosh is Smosh those two British guys
no wait those are the other ones the
British ones who got so popular with the
teenage girls
what who are they again I didn't watch
them and I also didn't watch Smosh I
think there are different couples of
people's
ah damn fell down and feel that was then
a pillow I was thinking about yeah
[Music]
they were really popular also at the
same time
mm-hmm
not done yet we can now I guess start
decorating
[Music]
so we better get started
so I didn't want it to be too
cheesy and cutesy so I got some like
natural elements as well this is just
dried up
um what is this looks like a beehive but
I know it's not a beehive what is it
what was that again
I will place this first
there even so some of them still have
the the the things inside
Lotus
what
[Music]
oh my God wait there's something oh this
is really bad for the people with the
triple phobia right oh god oh oh
does someone have that in the chat like
for real because then I'm not gonna use
it because you know yeah this is
terrible isn't it uh
[Music]
I've been taking phobias more seriously
I do but it's okay really maybe I'll put
them in last okay
I'm so sorry oh I should have warned you
Ah that's right that was a thing
I can understand because I think it
reminds me of like I think we talked
about this before and I said what it
reminds me of I think it reminds me of
those spiders with a million eyes
which doesn't really exist I think but
it's just like there's pictures edited
pictures of spiders which have a million
eyes and that's what I think of when I
look at that I guess when I think of
something bad purposefully
hmm
I'm sorry
I'm considering I don't know I just I
understand I totally like I can see how
this will break up people this is very
triggering
um we'll start with the other things
okay
for sure I have some hopefully not
triggering things I mean if a pine cone
triggers you then I'm sorry you can't
really get around in here
uh I also have I have another weird
thing I wonder if this induces something
as well I I don't know what this is it's
also kind of sprayed White
it's something there's
I think this is a similar thing it also
has kind of holes but you don't really
see it well so okay so hmm and what do I
start well don't you
um
[Music]
actually
I also wonder how to do these ones
because they're very long should I cut
them
[Music]
foreign
yeah I got all the dried Goods yeah
they're good for decorating those stuff
they make a nice orange arrangement
[Music]
don't let the pine cones go behind us
that's dangerous why
step on them and they hurt
have to wear shoes
and I can't I'm too stupid to open this
apparently what the [\h__\h]
there it goes a scissor goes a long way
[Music]
wow they're so orange
hello how do I how do I work with this
and I think I would
[Music]
even like put them in little bunches
we're all in one place
but I would probably need to cut them
[Music]
and Tangled
oh no
[Music]
you little [\h__\h] okay there we go I got a
little Bunch so maybe if I can have them
you know like like this but then try to
poke them into the green stuff so the
ends are not so visible but I will still
have to cut them
you see where I'm going with this won't
that be so lovely
foreign
[Music]
combination with the dried like weird
stuff
well I think give it a fresh feeling
and some good variation
[Music]
I cut them up now they're like all over
the place oh [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
and I didn't even have to use hot glue
okay next batch
[Music]
no energy
yeah
I don't know this makes me happy
I felt like [\h__\h] before the Stream
because I'm okay like even if it was the
sea thing then it probably wouldn't be
so bad last time it was also not like
the worst
it could have been worse I suppose it's
just because I was trying to learn
dances in a short time so it was the
worst timing ever to get the sea thing
for sure and I have no one to to nurse
me you know
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah I'm dragging them out
why did I do that why did I do that why
did I do that why did I do that
foreign
[Music]
don't you think
cozy time
so yeah after I cut them off
speaking of spaghetti
[Music]
I I don't think I can show you the
picture now but
um you know when I was buying a souvenir
for my brother at the airport of Rome
before going back
um I I was also like looking for some
fridge magnets because I started
collecting fridge magnets even though my
fridge is not magnetic
so I'm putting them on my on my
microwave
so
um I actually we found something at
first I didn't think it was French
Madness at all they had like one section
where
um
they had
uh like one like spinny power pillar
thingy with uh everywhere they had like
little items that looked like items from
the grocery Market but in like miniature
size
like milk package and cheese and all
that all kinds of things uh tomato sauce
in like this small
a lot of those items all over and I I
looked at them and I tried taking them
off and it was kind of weird like I
wasn't sure if they were magnetic they
fed like really weakly magnetic but they
were magnetic so I was like it these are
magnets because they they looked really
just like miniature items from the
supermarket because they were not like
so
how to explain people around they they
were like for example one thing I bought
was a package of long uh like dry
spaghetti that you throw into the hot
water to boil right like long spaghetti
noodles
in uh the original plastic wrapping of
like uh uh I guess a popular brand in
Italy
and the plastic wrapping everything was
separate like it moved around and the
spaghetti inside of every single tiny
little spaghetti noodle would move
around too
so it was so detailed and intricate and
I thought maybe you can like really eat
this it's like a tiny cooking thingy
thing you know
but no it's actually Madness so I bought
that I bought the spaghetti one and I
bought a little package of parmigiano
and then I gave the the spaghetti one to
my mommy to put it on her fridge
and I bought uh I bought the parmigiano
from my fridge
yeah it's so good
but I did also get um something for my
brother of course
[Music]
how about this
it's cute
it's so cute oh my God
the Orange is so bright and beautiful
the contrast is so nice
what I got for my brother is
um
um since he's looking for a job and I
was thinking when he gets a job when he
has like his little office table and so
on then it would be nice if I bought him
this thing so I got him a cup with like
some some uh Italian well I think it was
Latin maybe saying on it
something philosophical something like
but it was not vanity
and uh then it came with a a fancy
golden pen
and some memo uh with the pantheon on it
and some little
Post-it notes with the pantheon and some
you know Roman whatever stuff on it too
and a measurer also with a Pantheon on
it the pet
[Music]
shut up
don't like a set like a little mug set
with some stuff you can use when he gets
his job and is in an office or so
he's got his own stuff
[Music]
I thought they looked pretty fancy
spaghetti
okay so two more bunches are pretty big
[Music]
can you guys hold the other side or so
no okay
thanks for napping I guess
[Music]
it's okay I can do it myself
foreign
on a trip too but this year I took my
mother on a trip last year I you know I
also took my my best friend on an
all-inclusive uh saturate remember that
was nice
so maybe next year I can bring my
brother on an old inclusive trip one by
one you know one by one one by one
thank you foreign
[Music]
at least you know there they have layers
you know I don't have them all like here
just kind of spread them out a little
bit but this one's actually a little bit
less than over here
oh well
you can still adjust
later on
[Music]
try one more Bunch just getting it in
place
[Music]
because I set it as layers did I put
onions on it
hey
[Music]
Christmas baby
okay
[Music]
here you are
okay
[Music]
foreign
thank you
doing a couple
[Music]
to balance it out nice to someone is
aesthetically pleasing it matches my
hair well yeah duh I chose this because
of Orange
[Music]
it matches me
okay
I wonder if that's enough
[Music]
okay let me add this on the cut a bit
more off
[Music]
yeah
is that butter
and this one these ones I wanna
bread a bit more
I feel so so feminine right now
[Music]
okay you know what this piece really
bothers me
whoa
[Music]
oh God why is it it's drooping
let's take a bit I hope it won't hurt
[Music]
it doesn't work on the tree
Trey does not want to be hot glued
why not
go stay
use the wire yeah I'm done with the wire
foreign
[Music]
maybe we can hold it down with an orange
hmm
what's the better side
I guess this side yeah
what engine
going to show
camera
[Music]
orange I wish I had ribbons I was also
thinking of ribbons but they didn't have
ribbons so I was like okay I guess I'll
do the valid ribbons
yeah
is it already kind of finished
I just started decorating but you know I
could be already finished if I wanted to
oh no not all the decorations are orange
some are brown and golden and the pine
colors you know are mostly like white
and stuff
so it's not completely orange I wanted
it to not be like too much but if you
look at other
um Christmas Advent wraps reefs they all
have a color theme
and you know that's what you know makes
them look so aesthetically pleasing I
was even thinking of like spraying
the um green stuff with some white color
to give it like this snowy feeling but
in the end I decided against it I felt
like a natural Vibe the fresh rich green
will look best for now
[Music]
it'd be a really good and creative you
can do like a two color Arrangement or
even a free color Arrangement but I'm
going with mostly orange and brown tones
okay so how do we do this
the orange does not smell like orange
anymore by the way but it's definitely
it used to be a real one
all right so you're getting hot glue
baby
[Music]
where do you want to go did I really put
you there
so why did I touch that now it's on my
glove at least I didn't feel it
mmm that's a bad positioning I don't
like it yeah
I did not like that
no let me redo
hot Orange
I don't think it looks good here
and there's also sticks better here okay
I'm so happy
[Applause]
I feel so creative
you know if it wasn't for a stream or
for my streams in general you know the
creative handcamp streams like I like
the iron beats and so on the gingerbread
house making stuff like that I wouldn't
do it otherwise even the Easter egg
painting as well I would not do those
things it was weren't for the streams
so this is really nice to have like a
good reason to do it and these kind of
like creative things as an I guess as an
adult you need it maybe I'm already in
my middle of Crisis but but it's nice
like you know in school you would do so
many of these things school would make
you do all of them but then once you're
done with school you don't do any of
these things right until you're in your
middle of crisis
it's relaxing and you feel like you know
making something yourself like this
gives you a feeling of accomplishment it
makes you live out you're creative
Tendencies
you think about a double oh that looks
good layers oh my god do you see the
layers
because I actually have five because if
we put one here and one here then I have
one left over the questions what to do
with it but in order to not have it too
perfectly
balanced we don't want that because that
will make it look unnatural we need a
little bit of imbalance somewhere no
[Applause]
I'm so sophisticated
all right
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
here
to go on the inside
all the others are on the outside
you're an Insider you know what all this
is have about and what's going to happen
with you
when you're not a good porridge
and then we turned into orange juice
where do I put this I didn't really
think about it
[Music]
this was fine
okay you were here you're there okay now
I'm gonna put a lot of tiny ones tiny
pine cones everywhere
[Music]
like here
I don't want it to be like too much like
overloaded
so it's important to know where to start
but I also you know I bought so many
things so why not I guess the more you
put on it the more
[Music]
um
the more it will
look like it's expensive
you know what I mean
try making them stand up oh you're right
okay
I was just gonna lay them down because I
was thinking maybe they're too exhausted
the stand all the time
oh wait this one doesn't want to stand
anyway
[Music]
foreign
this would be a little bit easier
because I would have a feeling for what
I'm doing
I'll get used to it
this is yeah let's go I also have this
orangish pine cones
[Music]
orange pine cone
it's cute I don't know if it's really a
fine color kind of
has different leaves I don't think it's
actually a platform
probably isn't but it has a similar
layering
[Music]
you don't see that one but it's behind
there
[Music]
open decoration I can just decorate my
apartment with them
[Music]
have a bed of you actually from the
camera the webcam
I don't wanna like maybe this is too
much but no it's not too much
[Music]
it's very interesting
they're orange and they have like some
pattern on it and they're they're hollow
inside
um you know what don't think too much
about it just gotta push them somewhere
how about
here
because I think that's back since I'm
not close to it it's probably pretty
empty
another one
and you will go I don't see what's going
on there but you will go here
how about some Stars some golden stars
[Music]
yeah it's so cute it's so cute
wow it's so cute
this will be a loaded a loaded Adventure
[Music]
go stay there
don't go
[Music]
what's going on over there oh what is
that oh [\h__\h] I can see that
go here then
[Music]
I wanna eat it
I could sell this you could look at this
and think it's store bought didn't you I
look at it and I already think it's
store-bought
foreign
[Music]
wow the layering that's going on here is
is unmeasurable this is my favorite few
finger players
I have a fetish for layers
foreign
[Music]
dried cinnamon
ah well I guess one's a bit floating
oh
uh one of the bad things was
[Music]
that sitting there nice and nice though
I have one more
[Music]
do I even need this one
questions
[Music]
I wonder where it wouldn't look so
unnatural maybe I'll keep this one
I'll keep this one
[Music]
um
I'll Place one more of these I put one
in there
from there right no nothing in the front
okay
[Music]
are you guys looking forward to a
monkeys in two hours
um I think there will be nice
[Music]
you know some ID members
and then I think crony and fauna
on bales
and maybe mermaids didn't answer about
the time I don't know if she can do it
but yeah
[Music]
we are gonna play some emotions together
it will start at midnight for me
it's kind of late but um also very early
for some ID members
I feel sorry
but it has to be like there's a deadline
you know because of the merchandise
put some more pine cones
where do we need phone calls maybe uh
oh it's so pretty
this area looks a little empty Maybe
but not I kind of need to sew leave some
space right for my sorry trigger warning
trigger warning
where would I put them
maybe one
like in there
[Music]
there's actually not much space for this
one
[Music]
there what does that look like from the
side let me check
[Music]
these ones are a bit awkward to place
now it should have made it in place in
the beginning
but I also actually now that I look at
them together
they kind of ruin it maybe what about
[Music]
this
okay these are okay maybe I'll not use
the the spider eye thing is
the phobia people will thank me for that
choice
[Music]
okay
I only have two of those but
[Music]
okay
other one and bye a hot glue
[Music]
I guess maybe you go here
awkward placement
[Music]
yeah that's kind of awkward but oh well
we're kind of like I could say I'm done
if I wanted to I also don't have like
anything else left besides the same
thing
so I guess we gave up on this so I'll
just put them somewhere in my apartment
to you
well finished artwork reads thank you
[Music]
but I can't stop
let me place
[Music]
I think I'll actually
cut something here because this part is
too bushy
[Music]
now it's time to perfectionize it I
guess
[Music]
I could even just
this is on the plate anyway I just even
stick this in where it's missing some
volume there you go
thank you
[Music]
look over there
you know I will
cut this one
[Music]
um
it's like I'm giving it a haircut
welcome to salons
it's a little bit too much
yes
and I will add
[Music]
oh okay
yeah that side needs some fixing
uh this is the one that sticks out a lot
huh
[Music]
foreign
let me look at it from above
[Music]
yeah
oh I just noticed looking at it from
like a proper point of view bird Corner
view
um the spacing is not 100 accurate but
that's okay
[Music]
dang it because it's the first of
Advance today but you know I don't know
if I can really light it
let me try to find the fire
[Music]
I've got the fire
I even have an orange lighter so do
these have a child lock I don't see a
child look
foreign
[Music]
liquid inside
with my with my bare hand I was not able
to do it
with the glove I get a grip so now I can
do it on fire
whoa
okay
wow I want to take a picture before
um I light it for the first time though
foreign
[Music]
unplug the hot glue
so that we don't have any nobody
accidents
[Music]
you know
now let's take a good aesthetically
pleasing picture shall we
[Music]
thank you
it doesn't react to my glove so well
[Music]
that's beautiful
I'm so proud
okay and now we're lighted on fire uh
which one shall it be
which one
as if it's not important it's not
because they're all the same
[Music]
How does it go on I don't I only know
until that point
[Music]
North which was not uh
and we only light one today only one and
then on this next Sunday we light two
and next Sunday we light free you know
huh
if he hollers let him go any money mom
uh catch a tiger by the by his top if he
hollers let him go
and that's it
that's where it ends
yeah okay
that's the tiger by his top doesn't it
always end up when he started
[Music]
catch the tiger by his toe
if he hollers let him go
oh
that's more for you
I'm here again which is where you
started I'm so stupid it only works a
lot numbers huh oh man I remember like
when I was a child we had this in German
so we used but I figured it out that it
always ends where it starts if you know
you do it right so I used it from my own
advantage
all right
[Music]
it's burning
oh where's my phone
where's my phone
[Music]
isn't that beautiful especially because
the fire is also orange or like yellow
orange
it's like as if it was all calculated
all according to keikaku
now I take a photo with the fire but it
will look best when all four of them are
lit which will be on the last Sunday
before Christmas
whoa
[Music]
whoa It's portrait mode with zoom oh
we're getting some real depth here
almost
[Music]
make the photo you little [\h__\h]
it's so moody oh
oh
it's breaking
[Music]
well I'm having a lot of fun being
photographer again
my new hobbies doing things myself
crafting [\h__\h] and taking photos
and layers making layers
oh it's so pretty I can't get enough of
it
just details here
[Music]
wow okay I got it
can we blow it out with clapping
[Music]
thank you thank you
I'm feeling to sit down again
[Music]
I think it was a good choice even though
I I see these in a lot of Christmas
arrangements you know these things
uh I think it was a good choice to leave
it out because it was already getting
pretty crowded
[Music]
and I'm glad I bought these Little
Flower thingies
they're a really nice addition to it and
make it look very fresh and natural
because they don't even look like dried
flowers they look so fresh
this was so chill
hope that's a good thing
[Music]
will you post pictures yes
I think I'll post every Sunday
yeah if I remember you guys gonna
remember me it reminds me because
sometimes
I mean usually I'm fine though
especially because on Sundays I have to
make my weekly schedule
and then I can remember oh I have to
light a candle
one more thing though that I have to do
is I have to buy an advent calendar but
I guess
Advent calendar makes almost no sense
when you're an adult and
especially if you live alone I guess
because you know what's inside
and
especially if it's a chocolate Advent
calendar you could just buy chocolate
hmm
yeah
it makes no sense if you are still like
with a family or so you can like share
it and you can hide you can make it
yourself because there's also DIY Advent
calendars you can hide things and the
others will not know what is inside
like if one person makes it then the
others will not know what's inside
yeah but so I was looking for a special
advent calendar
like something that has some special
stuff that's not chocolate or soap for
tea bags or so
she has on the calendar is a really good
idea but but then again like I can just
get all those but I guess it gives you a
big variation but then even then I could
just buy a tea assortment
I did a tea advanced calendar a few
years ago it was fun you like made it
yourself
[Music]
Lego Lego no I I want what would be cool
as like a Game of Thrones or or Lord of
the Rings that on calendar but I
couldn't find one I don't even know what
I was expecting to be inside like maybe
little figures or so or I don't know
like a coin and then whatever I don't
know I was hoping for something like
that and I looked around online but I
couldn't find anything
anything at all so I gave up a whole
I've had one calendar oh
wait hold on you should totally do
and do like a website
um where you know you have this like big
Advent calendar house with little doors
and you open a door
and then inside is maybe a whole life
member with a message
but
[Music]
you know what maybe I can do it this end
somehow actually now that's a good idea
but I don't want it to be just YouTube
videos I want it to be like a website
with you know little doors like graphic
design you know it's already 27 so like
there's no way that someone can do this
now
[Music]
damn it
I thought about it too late yeah
I was already like a while ago thinking
about making Lulu videos on my channel
each day but then I was like
would be better
oh boy you're right
or maybe she can help for real
[Music]
oh my God
but like how do we like make like a like
don't we have to buy like a server or
something
but I want to ask her and then really
quickly I'll just gather like a bunch of
members who Wanna doesn't even have to
be only and then but
um
[Music]
do you wanna help me with a spontaneous
adventure
does Indonesia do Advent calendars do
they know what that is Advent calendar
idea
I
[Music]
mean not enough time but
oh oh
even Americans wouldn't know okay wait
um what is an advent calendar Advent
calendar
like let me send her a picture
oh that's perfect is it is it perfect
perfect
she already answered what the [\h__\h]
oh you saw so fast
this is an advent calendar you know on
this
[Music]
he's participating
yeah it's like
five six a.m or so
[Music]
this is a gift yes yes yes yes
every day until Christmas starting from
first of December you open one door per
day and
[Music]
when I was thinking is
have one whole life member per day
with a video message
[Music]
um but I want a wolf oh too cold a
website where and there's a graphic of a
house maybe I can do the graphic Maybe
I can try and grabbing of a house we
have doors and then you click on it to
open it and then the member will be
revealed oh
or it could even just link to an
unlisted YouTube video that might be
easier
[Music]
can you imagine
what I mean
[Music]
yeah if you click on it it leads to an
unlisted video rather than just having
it on the same website it might be
easier
um
[Music]
it doesn't have to be I don't know maybe
maybe this is one of those like block
spots kind of websites where we can host
it I don't know
[Music]
and we can get it to work
no there's like no time so if you don't
think it's enough time that's okay but
[Music]
foreign
HTML
cool boy it's too young to understand
[\h__\h] what do you mean
stupid of course you can understand
[Music]
and worst case you guys have to remind
me uh again in a year
and I don't know why we're not even
doing this already this is such a simple
cute sweet idea but maybe it's because
does Japan do Advent calendars
[Music]
don't remember they do Christmas
differently but it's still Christmas
[Music]
foreign
oh it does exist and they know of it and
uh it is being sold and it's not so like
super popular
but it's a thing
one person got the Lego advent calendar
oh
[Music]
um
okay so there's a thing there you go so
Japanese
management and members Church no
foreign
[Music]
have to start on the first day I guess
because I mean it would be ideal
foreign
anyway even if we can't do it we'll keep
the idea for another time
I need to come up with these ideas
earlier we need to do some brainstorming
streams once per
once every four months or so
brainstorming streams plan ahead
yeah
for a project ideas and so on I know
that some members actually do that some
I think some Japanese members I've seen
them do that brainstorming out the
couple a couple of projects
foreign
[Music]
for you Mr hyperchat developer hmm
free free days done enough
[Music]
just you're not just wondering you know
you never know like some people can whip
up things so freaking fast
and I would say in theory it's a simple
thing
it's not a game it's a website it can be
scared
[Music]
people have lives well maybe
maybe
they got some free time right now what
I'm just asked
what's your problem guys yourself
there's no no harm in asking
oh possibly see
they say possibly
[Music]
see it's not impossible
you just have to believe you just have
to believe and if there's motivation and
time on your hands you're not busy with
a different project and let's go foreign
[Music]
it looks as if I bought it at Home Depot
so I don't even know what that is but
I'm assuming it's like a store where you
get some decoration stuff
[Music]
tribe of a WordPress plugin
they already exists what like an advent
calendar
thing yo I've never used WordPress but
never wrapped never tried wrapping my
head around it before
oh Home Depot is for tools oh [\h__\h]
can you go over the details again
[Music]
I mean
we can discuss
uh after the stream perhaps
with manager's son is janma awake
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
foreign
[Music]
I should probably take a break to eat
some dinner and prepare a more Goods I
was uh and maybe I can make my schedule
um
but I also should read some support
shots probably
I'll do it
foreign
I'm not leaving yet still got some time
[Music]
I'm feeling very hot but surely it's
just a candy candle line
[Music]
um which one is um
next thing that I have to read
make sure to sniff the candle the candle
smells like nothing
there is no smell
[Music]
airfryer
a camel's not looking no it doesn't even
smell like him because candle smells
like smells like nothing
[Music]
a hint of pine cinnamon no I need to
spray it with a perfume
uh is it airfryer
Enterprise
there it is
foreign
[Music]
on the Big Orange Artemis one rocket the
name on the other hand is on its way
around the Moon on a thumb drive
but I put your name into another website
for that back in March and was planning
an orange Super Chat for the orange
rocket since August but delays happened
what
[Music]
are you going to inform me that you have
missed your flight around the Moon
on the Big Orange I went around the Moon
you missed it did I not warn you ahead
of time
on the other hand is on its way around
the Moon on the thumb drive then what is
ah maybe you missed your own flight with
your own name but the takanasi one is
all over the moon right now
foreign
[Music]
I mean that's really cute and funny and
so on but um I don't I mean no insulting
or whatever but that is a stupid way to
use uh money
but it's funny
oh
thank you
thank you sir so I'm on the moon right
now let's go
I'm over the moon for kfp
[Music]
weird
Tiny Dancer thank you for two pinkies
just we could learn some new hives were
signed under my supervision and my task
was to Mentor them I had the pleasure of
having to talk for eight hours without
stopping for days and needless to say
my throat is absolutely dead I thought
about how much you talked to us in the
past two years
and then once again amazed by your
dedication and the quality of your craft
Your Entertainment knows no bounds and
I'm so glad I can watch you almost daily
um well yeah if you normally don't do it
you might tend to underestimate it and
then when you have to do something like
that
of your voice might have some troubles
but
it's um I think it's also different for
a streamer or a performer you try to
talk in a way that is like interesting
with big intonations and so on
um
[Music]
so that makes it
um even more
uh straining on the throat you know but
yeah I hope your throat is okay I have
to eat some fruit candy and drink some
tea with honey you know it from me
you know
I taught you
thank you
47 questions
sanitation Master donation Shadow woman
504 Duncan
you always send me pinkies
[Music]
have you have you had one of these
before
you probably didn't make one yourself I
couldn't imagine you maybe had one
before
I used to buy them but this time I made
one myself but may is orange
yeah
I'm so proud every Sunday until
Christmas I'm gonna Light One Candle and
then two candles and then three candles
and then four candles oh
[Music]
I'm gonna keep you guys updated
I've been growing up but this one looks
like it's most super nice yeah it
totally does it's like totally smelling
of cinnamon and orange yes
no no but I could spray it with
something the dried oranges and cinnamon
sticks they're real but they don't
really smell like anything
pine cones need a butt the green stuff
is real and that smells
like what it is like a Christmas tree
yeah
indeed
thank you Mommy I'm happy with it
yeah it was fun making it I like these
this kind of hand cam crafting streams
or maybe it's because my nose is stuffed
and I can't smell well
um
yeah yeah
[Music]
a sprayer I use it when watering plants
potentially uses it when cooking
yeah but now I have to get the oil out
of the sprayer
and then use it for spraying this brief
instead to keep it hydrated
so yeah then I will use it for its
actual intended use
yes
[Music]
oh everybody says what happened
was there 10 people saying kiwawa cute
foreign foreign
[Music]
what did I do
why is
one employee of the year
uh the gamer reduction
did I miss that one full Jack 100
[Music]
Lauren smell the restricted and
restrained thank you
thank you
foreign
[Music]
T you
with the tip of my hot glue gun
I'm gonna melt your beak together
[Music]
oh that sounds terrifying I'm sorry
um
[Music]
Good Times
okay
so don't check your Channel
[Music]
thank you
Patrick
[Music]
I sneezed towards the candle thinking
maybe it will go out but no it didn't it
didn't even move I think hahaha
it didn't work
that would have been funny that would
have been really funny man you got
[Music]
you've gone out and everybody would have
been like oh foreign
ruffle copter
[Music]
amen he had one job
no not because of the spit but because
of the hot shoe the a lot of air also
leaves your mouth you know
foreign
[Music]
oh wait no I already read that one I was
gonna answer looking for the top because
that fan is already finished done ready
I'm just not sure when to use it um I
think I I have to catch up with my
current super chats first
[Music]
but yeah then hopefully if I don't
forget about it but it's already ready
I'm ready to go
[Music]
foreign
thank you thank you for making the last
eight months more enjoyable
um following me for eight months
Eric Barlow thank you soon
[Music]
my mom's family came from the Holy Roman
Empire around the Rhine yeah
sick
for the pinky
Korean heart for you getting hot on my
arm when I'm above the candle
oh
thank you
[Music]
oh
if gorillas can accept a music award
while animated then you should be able
to apply animated oh they did that
that's interesting it's funny but it's
not your revision and action
[Music]
a message from two years ago Mario Kart
HDX 2022 1117
[Music]
what
are like
[Music]
what did I tell myself two years ago to
play Mario Kart
on the 17th of November
[Music]
just maybe see if I improved or
hmm
what
no no these super chats are not from
today anyway they're from
um a while ago but
if I want what I want you don't you're
not explaining you're just emoting
[Music]
anyway I'm done with those super chats
from oh I didn't even have a thumbnail
up I'm sorry and that was from the air
fryer
oh thingy oh
[Music]
foreign
oh that one's more
[Music]
ah
Russia
[Music]
um
so should I leave
I think I should rest
okay
[Music]
okay thank you everybody
on this joyous occasion of making this
beautiful
layered Christmas wreath
um it's gorgeous it's lovely I could
sell it for a thousand dollars and
that's not even enough for this beauty
um now let's light the candle every
Sunday
[Music]
hopefully if you guys have any good
ideas for things like this that I could
make on stream let me know maybe in the
on Twitter on my ending tweet as a reply
so it's good
[Music]
oh they're discussing it with the deaf
board sounds amazing
cool and
come on we don't need only on September
[Music]
thank you for the fun streaming for the
trypophobia
I wonder if anything here is inducing
but it shouldn't be it shouldn't be it's
probably my best love your DIY streams
thank you
foreign
[Music]
mama mama
see you later at Among Us the stream
reservation is already up uh it's
starting in one hour 20 minutes if
everything goes according to keikagu and
we'll just have some fun cozy abugus
yeah late nights
[Music]
um
foreign foreign
[Music]
egg foreign
see you later alligator
[Music]
thank you
Merry Christmas
[Music]