[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
hello everybody good morning it is
8 00 am here
i am oh my gosh but the other girls are
energetic
[Music]
energetic let's go
let's do a little bit of the
introduction while i'm testing the
volumes for you girls
uh let's start from the top of my totem
pole
right
hello
i'm rainey from whole life id generation
2 i am here to
um
make peace with everybody peaceful
monopoly let's go
no no no no
monopoly is war not peace
i'll do my best okay okay
[Music]
today i will be resting well uh on my
pile of money just like i am resting on
right next press
nice
wow
that was well said whoa
let's go only make that money get that
cash yeah
get that win
thank you i'll even be here at them i i
actually built this collab around only
because i said ollie we haven't collabed
yet so yeah yeah let's finally do
kodable
and then i brought over my other dearest
friends so here we are
do we have ame or do we have
it
oh
i don't know man i don't know what's
happening maybe it's because i'm i woke
up early and i just seem to dissolve
into other people
it's your soul
i'mma introduce yourself please
ah hello everybody hello hello this is
the number one detective amelia watson
and i'm here today
uh rule
i'm here to rule the board with my money
oh yes
[Applause]
trees let's go
yeah taking over the block
you should take over all the blocks
okay i will i'm just worried about one
for like me right
yeah
what about one thing me and me and uh
reina are going on a vacation soon so if
today our friends events then i don't
know what happens with the vacation
don't worry i'll step in i'll take your
spot
you take the winning spot so that
there's no salty feelings okay okay
that's very generous of you
okay we have a pangolin duck
roller skate and dog
ah of course um is the don't go
perfect yes
[Music]
and we're doing uh normal rules and
we're doing the um
what's this map called again the
amusement park yeah exactly amusement
park map because last time i did the the
city map so this time we have something
else and uh
yeah shall we begin
yeah
[Music]
please don't let me go last if i go last
i'm already losing
queensland
yeah and what about
oh
if you roll darlings
trading game
oh yeah isn't there f i've heard like
isn't there like a statistic or
something that like whoever wins
monopoly is usually the person that goes
first
i've heard that before oh really yeah
this is my first time i feel so too oh
come on
okay seven is not the worst
i mean it's a lucky number
oh i guess so
okay okay okay okay i'm not last yes yes
that's good already
a decent roll oh
and we have a oh
no
oh
ryan is going last so far
[Music]
the destiny has been decided
don't worry with all the money i'm
making in the game i'll i'll be um you
know treating you to something nice
oh yeah you're gonna be treating me
something nice
massages shake the dice oh yes i love
makeup like monopoly money
no no money
oh my god i don't even understand how to
play this game starting strong
i'm going fast
i hope i landed on the hot dog on the
hot dog oh my god
it's mine
you got the utility already but what are
the challenges of people actually
landing on the utilities anyway it's not
a hot dog you could say nice oh
you guys can give up now okay i'll go
back to sleep
yes
it's your lucky day oh don't forget to
end your turn and eventually you can
also make the turns go by faster
by skipping you don't have to do it in
the beginning but i think lena we'll be
getting sick of it
okay
seven
seven oh you're getting lots of sevens
today uh
what what what's the claw
oh
cute
i wanna
[Laughter]
[Music]
that is the worst start
please
[Music]
i wonder if it's like a monopoly thing
where you actually uh
if you get like a chance versus how you
go to jail instantly because that's what
happened to me a few games ago
what do you mean a few games ago all of
you have played monopoly before
i played a monopoly before it does not
on twitch oh
i mean on actual cardboard am i the only
oh shake to roll yo
i got your first time right now
it's my first
time
seven another seven oh so you laying in
the same space oh yeah we're gonna land
on the same space as kiara but no nobody
you have to get something else though
whatever happens don't draw a car
of course you get something great like
that moon drop
luna tower
no no what the heck no no no no you
don't want to buy it you don't want to
buy it yes i want to violence
[Music]
well at least you all have property now
yeah we all have property let's go
you have to end your turnover oh sorry
sorry yes yes
your time anyways uh how's that how's
jail food
by um
it's terrible they only serve the
shittiest porridge but only with water
not with milk it's terrible i don't even
like coral
is it tap water
yeah but i don't even i don't like
porridge even with milk a goat train
a transmission
no are you only gonna buy the utility
places
i buy five fights
oh yes is it i'm doing it intentionally
that's cool
okay so
i will obviously pay to get out of here
because otherwise i'll be missing out on
everything
it's your turn
go please
i want i need double i need to catch up
[Music]
you don't want mustard orange oh you can
skip oh i see you can skip the little
yeah yeah how do you skip what do you
press
uh b
b b b b okay
okay
i bought something it's orange good chat
i'm in the wild west
is that a good good spot i hope so
it's a common spot for sure it's not the
worst is it it's not the worst orange is
orange is nice
[Laughter]
orange is always good
oh i just like it wasn't it wasn't the
bestest i remember oh
was it all these properties
yeah but
yeah
that's not necessarily good later on you
won't earn that much money from it what
is that what's that mean
[Applause]
uh i wanna buy i think
[Music]
she's a trainer shake to roll
six
seven at six i mean
wow
nice train
choo choose that
oh
yeah
you should just buy everything oh [\h__\h]
yeah i should have explained this game
to you i didn't know it's your first
time
yeah it's our first game oh you're doing
really well for your first game yeah i'm
sorry
your time has come so in the beginning
you just buy everything and then later
you gotta be careful and you want you
want to have at least
um
a full set of the same color and for
that you might have to trade later on
and tell
uh uh yeah discuss it with the other
girls who maybe have a spot in one of
your colors
expensive
look if somebody ah okay i see
somebody lands here they have to pay me
right yeah but i think it's also
expensive to keep on updating it
so getting a whole um monopoly over that
color it might be a bit tough maybe
but you'll be able to do it because
you're winning anyway don't worry
oh oh
no
yellow fittings
fitting for orange okay
i'll take anything i don't need to
understand the colors it is okay i will
um use my uh people instincts my
businessman instinct i forgot the most
important thing when you go bankrupt
when you when you have when you for
example go somewhere and you can't pay
and you even already sold all your
properties and you still can't pay
then you have to go bankrupt and that's
the end of the game for you but it will
continue for the others until everybody
else goes bankrupt
oh okay okay okay now you wanna you
wanna complete your collection of
properties so like most properties come
in uh like three to four pairs maybe
even yeah maybe even pairs uh and then
when you have more that's better
of the same color yeah yeah you can
trade with other players right
yep ollie
guys
yeah what price
we're at price
is a good time to think about your next
move
huh parking what's that mean we're
always thinking oh yeah there's just
nothing happening starts now okay which
is sometimes a good thing
oh yeah
sometimes you even want to be in jail
because sometimes it keeps you from
going on the expensive uh lots but
that's a little bit late game content
okay okay okay it will happen naturally
you know don't worry too much about it
blue blue
[Music]
uh
uh what
what
yeah just press x
or x i'll be pressing y i want that
[Laughter]
this is really slow
you guys
well who's gonna have the highest bid
huh
i don't know i already bid like a
hundred
i will withdraw
really i will withdraw too why
not me i have to save my money
ollie
why is it so expensive
okay let me i withdraw
wait
[Laughter]
you're still going at it
yes
well you paid it you paid much more than
the original value that's okay that's so
cool i love having this let's space base
space pads
you already have another blue
yeah yeah you guys need to trade later
i'm looking forward to the to the
showdown of oh i'm here
getting at each other's fruits
and then i'm looking at my properties
you feel like uh selling your other blue
i want like a full set
what no
over my dead body no
that thing
oh i can't really use that phrase can
she over my dead buddy yeah she's dead
mommy will you sell me your train
i want the train
who has the train
it has a tornado training
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i don't wanna
but why
you could be rich
yeah
which one do you want
you only have one
okay
i'll give you
uh
200.
no 500
no
my my offer is at 200 that's a good deal
i mean i think you only paid 100 for it
no you're getting double no no no no no
all right well i guess it's nothing then
you're lost that was a good that was a
good deal and you missed out on it
yeah make her feel guilty but it's all
good it was not a bad decision
necessarily
it's what monopoly is about yeah
but the thing is yeah if you would
sell her the train you would help her to
get oh [\h__\h] to get the monopoly
so
all right
[Music]
we're already seeing some payments here
people
yeah are you seeing who has the least uh
properties it's me who else
let's see if i can catch up somehow for
a minute i have the most money right now
at least yeah
and it doesn't really mean anything in
that phase so
this means nothing oh fast tracks track
tickets
wait is that one of the uh the black
slots thingies oh utility
yeah i think so it's like the same as a
train shake to roll ah no it wasn't that
one of the white ones wasn't there oh my
god
there's only i see nice
max double
it's a white one
what's that oh you landed on a free
green property glorious palace did i buy
it
do you want the magic forest or do you
want to auction it and make people poor
um
oh
just get it
[Music]
time has come yes oh [\h__\h] to roll
hold the chair
if you get another double you're going
to jail are you seeing this kfc
what's going to happen okay draw a card
advance to robot factory nice this is
all fair
green
i'm gonna buy it
yes oh yeah now you have almost the
complete set for green oh no it's a red
ah mizrah
[Music]
[Laughter]
be careful it's your third role mean
if you get another double you're going
to jail yeah okay
but i don't think it was though
you're fine almost
okay
almost yeah
[Music]
okay we need to work together
for you i want the rails to kiara the
rails well i can't remember i don't have
anything on
that's expensive
yeah the blue ones i think are the most
expensive ones in the game thank you
enjoy
yeah nice hotel here wait wait there's
some cockroaches under the pillow here
what the heck
that's our complimentary nourishment for
you
nourishment
[Applause]
oh celery let's go
yeah
oh no it's not here a lot isn't it it's
not your luck you just always have
[Music]
wait why does all the sweet shops
like steal your money i don't know
i already know i'm losing this game it's
unbelievable this game is [\h__\h] me
over
oh it's not even any of the girls fault
it's just a [\h__\h] game man what the
[\h__\h]
uh-oh i'm going to be packed as well too
early to be angry too early to be angry
hungry you haven't eaten breakfast yet
oh my god
let's share some cookies candy all lame
me and my homies we all hate cotton
candy [\h__\h] games stupid [\h__\h] does
that say
that's uh seven yeah this game what will
get me someone will get me what
it's time to have a strategy meeting
against amel all right
i just had to pay 200 double what you
guys had to pay
oh man come here
mmm cotton candy
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
why did you not ah because was it
because you didn't pass
uh a certain thing yeah
oh cause the dice is just oh dumb
nice come on
come on come on oh oh oh no no oh there
we
[Music]
i love
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you oh no one time i get double i
can't buy anything
what you're saying
i'm the poorest maybe i should just um
never play these games on my channel
maybe it doesn't get me any luck
salary
oh safe
atlantis
nice yeah this place is really cheap so
i don't know i'm not very
very happy you want you want properties
to train with other people like uh
i've got a i've got a nice green
property here
um you know i got the i got
paperwork ready to go
even bad i don't remember
the ice cream
oh i want money it was it was nothing
bad you only earned money
okay
all is good
in the neighborhood oh
okay
doubles
how do you guys keep getting doubles
it's not fair
it's great ollie have you not noticed
it's rigged
it is isn't it
no not the reds i actually like
i don't want to buy too many but i'm
going to buy just for trading purposes
i have a
you have a railroad
a utility
only has the white piece that i'm in
need so you could uh
trade white versus red if you want
your home yeah
i like it on my own
home
yeah
okay i don't know if you guys don't want
to trade i'm i'm i'm open my doors are
open orange i think i'm landing on
orange
oh no i'm not landing on orange so close
successful people make their own lives
oh
[Laughter]
well back to porridge what a diet
what a diet for that beach body from
maldives right yeah
[Laughter]
oh you got a double double finally
it's incredible this is so incredible
ali
only property
yes miami can i um you already have so
many properties can i buy off the orange
one from you
[Music]
um it's a bit complicated um
yeah part of business yeah uh what do
you how much do you want for it actually
no you should ask
no i should ask how much do you want
from it for it but uh
[Music]
i have i'll give you
extra money
oh
i'll i'll even give you extra money
again
you want my yellow one
yeah
chad
uh
how much extra money
i'll give you um
since i'm so generous i'll give you uh
182.
does that stand for anything
yeah
what do you what do you what uh 200 200.
look i i i don't know
two hundred i don't
what would she do the same for you
200 is a little bit too much i'm kind of
broke here i only have 300.
oh
if you look isn't my value higher
isn't the value of the yellow one higher
i'll i'll add i'll add a little bit more
yeah you have to redo the thing
unfortunately it's kind of weird
just add some with him a bit more just
200 it's okay i'll accept it with 200.
like 200. thank you ollie 200.
i'm gonna go i like
even oh
yes
yay
okay i end my friend thank you very much
i hope that there you go
i mean
i'm already losing chats don't worry
about it it makes no difference in the
end
it's not a scam everyone is called a
super chat you guys don't know
as long as you're vegan
how's it how's life
what's up are you picking me up for
vacation so sweetheart oh ollie has the
last dark blue okay ollie
let's negotiate oh there they go
rainy i'm pretty broke right now you'll
have to do a lot of negotiating
um we can go i'll treat you yokiniku and
you will give me that blue oh
real life
yeah real life yakiniku fighting with
real things now i assume
yeah that's dangerous
real money trading
gamble
like you're making some of that money
back ollie
yeah
wait what do you mean i didn't get the
money
what you didn't want money
oh my god you're right i still have 300.
it didn't work
wait wait are you supposed to click on
the money or
i i pressed accept i don't get
only can you are you gonna be honest or
are you go and pay me what would you
still owe me or are you going to um
though no you can't craft this is mine
you don't have to like trade
minecraft buildings you can also just
directly give me money actually so
you can do that yeah yeah you just have
to go put one thing
uh oh [\h__\h] no no no
i wanna
i wanna get out of [\h__\h] ah i can't go
back
oh boy i got double
double oh
my god
am i oh my god
you know i have like this home rule
whenever i play with my family if you go
to free parking you get all the packs in
the middle of the board
yeah there are some uh wait can i not oh
i can't roll again okay but okay only
only can i get my money
yes ma'am thank you i'm very sorry ma'am
i don't know what happened
wait so uh
uh no no no i give uh nothing you can
give me two dollars and i'll give you
two hundred and two dollars
uh yeah uh okay
okay
uh
wait no
i know huh i
i
i off all right i don't understand this
wait why am i oh no i am the penguin
huh oh yeah huh uh-huh i wanna go over
to ollie's side um oh you got to go uh
you press l
l
o all right
l all right sorry all right l or r
right bumper oh okay okay uh
are we doing this right are we doing
this right and then here two
hundred
two hundred two hundred two hundred two
hundred two hundred
my turn will be bypassed
uh
okay
um
this should be right right this is right
yes i'm not giving all your money right
here you go exchange
okay okay okay
that was nice trading with you yeah a
nice exchange it was really really nice
i i noticed i need to choose
kind-hearted people for these collabs
people are you one are you one
yes i am
that actually might be good because you
won't be spending money if you stay in
jail
man i got scammed and i went to jail
i got scammed and then you unscammed me
it's good
[Music]
only let's trade your blue one too
no what the heck
what are you talking about
i'm talking business
oh that's hot talk more business
yeah
fine ollie you can rot into jail with
your lovely porridge then i mean a diet
for the maldives right
are you going to maldives now
go back free spaces
she doesn't need the diet
[Music]
i don't want you to buy the last one i
need the last one and i know if you
would buy it you would not sell it to me
cheaply
me
yeah i mean
i just want a fair price
what's that five choo choo oh why is
everybody landing on on amazon
everybody's kidding on me
yeah
this is a very good strategy for sure
all right
don't let her get the full set it's
going to be uh
yes
that will be dangerous i i get i get the
full set thing now see i'm learning as i
play you know you could get a full set
of green if you traded me that railroad
you have i have the last green property
actually i don't know if you can see
that in my
basically i can't hear uh discord hello
but in truth for your own benefit
yeah beneficial trade
green is like the second most expensive
property
as you can see
and if you have like a full set you can
build houses and it'll like uh triple
the amount not really triple but
i keep paying mommy
maybe maybe elena will buy off the green
one once she gets into a more um
difficult dire situation yeah maybe
maybe maybe maybe okay
options open there's time monopoly games
are very long but the more time passes
the more um i'll think about it they'll
think about it one party will always be
more desperate later on so um
it's the nearest one
and a ghost train
your turn starts now unfortunate but all
right
oh
seven
the lucky number
somebody owns it
oh thank you
persistence isn't it ah it's okay i
still have i still have over a thousand
bucks at least i i can pay everything
i'm not going bankrupt yeah that's okay
that's okay
we're still in jail are you gonna stay
or leave
no i'm gonna stay i kind of like to pour
but but i kind of like it no orange it
doesn't do well too
yeah the orange jail color
shake to roll i'm making friends uh with
the people here uh hello brian have a
good day here brian
not nine what does nine give me
oh perhaps you should oh i own this
property
okay okay okay okay okay
that's better than landing on an
expensive one don't worry
yeah
oh
you love it
i could do that
oh
[Applause]
i can't wait to get everybody to land on
my properties i need that money
[Music]
you guys are rich come on share some of
your money look at me i have 400. the
money doesn't matter
as valuable as the properties
oh four dollars four dollars it's dirty
it's just like the color it's brown
it's better than nothing ollie don't
worry time has come
we have to look at it positively your
time has come a
double you're out of jail aren't you
brian i'll miss you
all right
oh yeah it's my
oh
still playing kiara huh
okay shake to roll
chats do i have a chance
of not losing
one color of prague
oh i got celery
it's mine because it's mine and i'll
skip
i'll roll dice again
three two one play dice
one four three two one play dice
oh 10 10.
are you going to railroad you're going
to that aerial room
is that gonna be somebody else's
probably oh yeah yeah
oh right now i get it i'm a railways
watson rail what was it wait a railway
yeah you need the train station yeah
yeah
i need the last one i gotta collect them
actually i think there's two
oh
i mean if i had one i would totally give
it to you
all right like you that is if you had
one oh of course i would give it to you
here you go ali
thank you for your charity ma'am
watch me i can i can buy myself a better
porridge now
okay
before right before i wake up i was
dreaming um that i was in school and and
that
thank god that i
had a math test coming up so i woke up
and i was like [\h__\h] oh thank god oh it's
not the reality oh
cause i was like already getting sweaty
in my dream that because i didn't study
your time has come thank you
oh no thank you no no no i'm done with
you know
that time of going to school i don't
want to see any more numbers anymore
ever again
mwah thank you
this is robbery
give me money
i don't even like robot
olly you could sell one of your useless
properties to get some more money you
could sell the blue one to me
and you know
can you actually do that oh double i
can't
you wanna i'll buy your uh utility
yes please i need money i'm not gonna go
to jail
hospital fees
finally the bad luck is going to other
people slowly
slowly
it's your turn
[Music]
oh
some pocket money [\h__\h] money for you
turn starts now i can eat something else
can i oh can i only trade after okay
what's that man
i think that's where you put houses and
stuff on when you have like the full
sets
of uh properties
oh okay
what's the move
so that's what you do after you have
stuff oh for ali
everyone's so nice to me
because dears are nice to us
only good good uh original song by the
way great great song
thank you
give me 300 for your utility how about
that i feel like that's over that's it
yeah yeah i pay it back you know i see
um i mean you know paying kiara
this is how it should work i'll even
take like 250 but
300 is also all right 275.
oh you're so nice to me okay
waiting
you're just okay can i get all right
wait are you sure
[Laughter]
are you sure
all right all right over there right all
right all right all right 290.
okay at 294 289
oh okay
oh
[Laughter]
am i doing it wrong oh you're doing it
right
[\h__\h] it wasn't it didn't you say you're
gonna pay her i 800 what happened
what 800 yeah 300 sorry 300 didn't you
say 300
uh oh oh sorry what was that 250 what
was that
why are you going down
what happened what did i say
all right oh yeah okay um so i want the
do i go to yours and
how does this work like if i want the
utility okay you get the money you press
right and then you uh choose my utility
ah yeah
i see yeah
that that's
that's uh sorry
my brain said yellow i want yellow
oh
does that mean that's how much i wanted
uh what
ma'am i i can't give you money i'm
pretty poor
yeah i think i did it on the wrong to
give any money yeah yeah just x before
deal
is
worst case you could still afterwards
give the right person the right amount
of money
yes it's true correct it seems correct
steel
is giving away her properties so kindly
so oh no no no no no no no you guys got
to remember for the utilities the max
money that you can make out of it is
120. oh
where did you use you know it so well
i i play monopoly quite a lot damn
yeah oh my own problem
that's why there's a there's here's my
name in the game
ollie also plays monopoly in her life
because she wants a monopoly over all
the girls by marrying all of them
oh hell yeah
that's why i auditioned in the first
place
it's gonna happen oh thank you it's
gonna happen
[Music]
you can't have so many wives you're
gonna leave some wipes for other people
no
i can't have that many wives but can i
have more girlfriends and i have wives
i guess sorry that's a different
category yeah if you're charming enough
times bad things technically it's
different
but
yeah
although you're watching me
they might leave you if they
i could give you the last green property
to complete your set and then you can
start investing on your property if you
give me that railroad uh what's the
railroad so what do i do
uh you have to do trade with why
why
yay is it happening and i choose you
i'm so proactive phil this this is going
guys the railroads are going to be very
very dangerous it's going to be 150 if
you give it to like amy
what no but she'll have she'll be able
to invest and make money back because
once she has all the green sets then she
can start putting her houses on the
properties
and then click on the green one and then
offer me on your side the railroad
and wrong what's new i'll leave it i'll
even throw in
if you want to you know you want an
extra 50 bucks or something i'll give
you you know extra 100 or something sure
yeah yeah sure i could 100
all right
nine
i think on my side you put one
125 on the right yeah
rainy they're just reminding you there's
a railroad on the other side outside of
the board
there's a
there's a chance of us landing there if
we get a 10 where like
um and and we'll have to pay for 150.
just remind me
i'm paying for 150 now so i'm already or
i'm paying her one what was it 125.
yeah 150 150 150. it's getting out
a free bed all right
i'm a nice business person you know sure
this is
[Music]
i would not be able to say no to ame i
think she's
that's just a good name [\h__\h] did i
press i thought i pressed you were
awesome so cute
you know
this is dangerous what amelia's invited
to me was charity but this
this is monopoly
how you can construct use r to build
houses
i don't understand
now you got a house yeah
now the value is even higher people will
have to
pay more money but
you also no no no you have to you can
only do one at a time
okay and then so i enter now yeah and
you have to put one house on each field
until you and then you can add more
houses if you have
one house on each field then you can
start adding more and so on it always
has to be on the same level
okay okay okay brain and brain just woke
up
oh man
oh man the
i chances i'll buy this oh
[\h__\h]
oh i think this might be good for a
business feeling if you sell me right
now please
uh you do it on your turn okay so i
don't have to deal with that
all right all right sounds good
freaking cowboy promenade of course i
have to buy it off of someone
um
this is one scary game i don't
i'm at bezos
thank you so much for your parody
i appreciate the donation
and turn
it's your turn all right
let's start by managing some properties
shall we oh dear uh
i'll be [\h__\h] at this so please bear with
me
this one right yeah
uh
yeah after my turn
yeah okay okay okay
go go penguin go go go go go go run fast
penguin of your little feetsies oh
oh oh
oh
new property i'm buying it
you have so much money
how can you have so much money
not much
probably okay so i buy i bought that and
now
uh
a train
with the dog no i think i'll spray you
uh that orange uh for the yellow
what
yeah
i want the yellow
harrison pie i'll be here a lawyer right
now
i kind of want to get you know more than
one property you know
do you want to trade your blue one to my
uh pink building
you're also collecting pink right
i don't have a single pink i think
yeah i want 350.
with with some extra money i'll give you
a yellow one
oh well these are your options it can be
yellow or 350. ah
oh chat what do you say
[Music]
wait wait what yeah free okay so so it
means wait what you give me the yellow
one i pay you 350.
what oh the orange one yeah oh yeah the
orange one okay i'll give you the orange
one and you pay me 350 yeah okay okay
okay
you buy it for that
i misunderstood okay oh this is going to
take a while um this interface is really
not well made
no no no no free
you could pay someone's tuition with
that
that in austria tuition is free in
austria
not paying anyone tuition here
come to austria raise your children in
austria
okay
and then uh the orange one
[Music]
i think this is correct
okay
is it correct
i think so yeah you give me 350. you get
the orange
yeah
that works
the hardest it is
yeah
finally i get my orange ones uh okay
oh can i buy a house while i'm not on my
field yeah right
you can oh yes okay so let's add one
here
and then nice add one here
wow
yeah if you have one on everyone then
you can start adding a second one and so
on but i'm just still gonna give it one
for now
okay
okay uh uh i think i'm done okay okay
wow that is wow
okay darling
your time has come
hey ollie want a tray
[Music]
um pink one
uh pink you like pink right ollie
pink to your blue building
[Music]
rather than giving your money to the
cotton candy you give your property to
me here here i i give it to you give me
your offer
okay on your shake to roll
oh
oh poor duck
i know it's just like ah
put up a pulp
oh my god cotton candy
you're looking pretty low on money if
you want to trade i'll buy that red
property off of you for no thanks mommy
i think you need some money manage
properties ollie do you want to trade
okay what are your offers my offer is
only don't be too nice because the chat
already thinks you're too nice
uh i wanna trade with you
um
what do you wanna trade
training is the heart of business
exactly i want this
i want this
and then
uh i don't even want any money you know
um and then
you know you can get that pink one i
don't even want any money
i i i um
give me the pink one and the red one oh
what the [\h__\h] oh
much no no no no pink i'm not even
asking for any money ollie wait wait
rainey hear me out uh so if you get two
uh the two of the blues and if you try
making like um houses you can get like
200 and even up to seven hundred you're
turning no ollie okay fine i'll pay you
like a hundred next turn i'll give you a
hundred but next turn
there's no time probably yeah it's time
to go faster
hurry up
i don't want it and besides
up in the polls here at 10
now
thank you everyone they believe more in
you now
one more percent
you have a chance according to the chat
let's go ollie let's go let's go i have
one more percent of winning yay we'll
show the world
you don't want to give me another 100
you need to get some more if you sell me
the red
[Music]
you like um um charity would be nice i
think
yeah that does sound nice
i ended my turn
i can't i can't go to jail no no no no
no i'm busy i'm a busy business woman
no no no no
apparently i'm so sad
hey
i got robbed once again
[Music]
oh money
goes my money
half of your salary goes to almonds
thank you
nicer
okay
what did i get
i don't even see how many that's like oh
11.
what does 11 get me
oh nice
oh
oh that one is still available now you
can trade
well ollie wants that one too
oh yeah nah that's not no no no
it looks like tap water i don't want it
it looks like tap water
is good just over here
i always drink tap water
yummy tap nope
you guys don't want an indonesian tap
water you guys will get like i don't
know
oh dear money oh oh the money sounds oh
oh
it's totally oh
[Music]
which ones are still available
which ones are the
the gray ones in the right no the black
ones are still available
i think there's one railroad maybe
all right i'll pay this i'll need to get
out of here quickly let's play let's
play time has come
oh isn't that pink one still for sale
the one right next to the jail that one
is still good it's your house
i think oh oh
you're home i mean it's a safe spot it's
your it's your own place
yeah
you have to go on a vacation
on the wild west
i'll just add more money i can always
get rid of it if i need money ally
if you want to trade i can uh trade you
this red i got for the brown
um wait what you want brown go with it
ollie you're taking her train without
taking mine
the brown
yeah brown
uh-huh
ollie look at her look oh
good
i'm just so nuts
i'm at wildings
oh and an extra hundred i'm a big brain
extra hundred
huh ollie
and an extra hundred for the red huh
yeah huh
there's some bigger plan behind this why
is ollie like this like what is what is
she what what what we got it like whoa
she's taking the fall for all of us
eventually
she will she will be the
last ones um no she won't be the first
one falling but uh wait i forgot to
insert the money again
[Music]
what apparently
apparently this is why we can't get this
treatment
like
wow like what nice because
you're
do you like oven more than you like me
this is business
huh i'll give you 169. all right i'll
take it
i'll give you 169 it's your business
the blue is a lot okay i i want to get
hold of you you don't think the brown is
a lot
no it's dirt she wants that color set
ollie just wanted to complete one
[Applause]
now i can build
and expand
i see how it is oh i want to write that
i see how it is no more kindness for you
ollie no more
no really
oh
this this is my favorite
this just got personal you're not the
one who's going to maldives with me
[Laughter]
if it if it makes you better um i'm the
second poorest right now
um i don't care and here you certainly
discord hello
oh nice oh nina thank you for visiting
me hello yeah you're welcome i'm so
pretty damn uh yeah looking forward to
our um family trip yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
right now you're looking pretty long
money there you know i'll buy off that
pink one if you i know you wanted to
trade it to ollie but uh you know i'll
buy it
you know ame um i think you're the
richest one here do you do do you want
to be like you know do some
philanthropist work you know like
charity charity you know i do charity on
the side um
yeah
i'll i'll be on the side for you i can
be your side money receiver
oh no
it's it's just uh paying back for the
the money that i already paid for the
hotel you have to yeah yeah yes
eventually anyway
[Laughter]
yay
it's looking good it's looking sunny
outside
[Music]
monopoly collapse you'll always be
oh apart wait what
is going on
[Laughter]
he's too kind
oh yeah
just
though
listen rainy there's a difference
between kind and stupid okay
what
what are you implying
i'm implying that i am kind i will give
it to you but i'm not that stupid to
just give it to you at such a low price
what do you mean low price
[Music]
no that's stupid
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
oh are we having a meeting again
we're having a meeting again
i'm right behind you
what let's talk about jummy
she's cute isn't she
[Laughter]
do you wanna
hang out
i'll buy something after you you know
make this a fair exchange
what are you interested in you might go
bankrupt sooner
um
she won't get bankrupt if she's close to
getting bankrupt she can still sell her
properties
oh yeah how do i add uh houses
i see it's just our
art
[Music]
now someone else is
uh you wanted to uh you know
you want to make some money because it
looks a little scary or a little low uh
okay okay what do you want what do you
want
uh i'll take whatever you don't want how
about that is am i going for shitty
properties on purpose
what no
entertainment company you can take
man i don't know
i want money i want a thousand
four
thousand you're crazy
you're rich
you can have the
the pink one um you know what just
because ollie won't buy it off me i'll
give you the pink one
and you give me uh 300 or 500 i don't
know
okay how about we meet in the middle
um
i know i don't want you to go bankrupt
so easily so i'm gonna i'm gonna make an
investment in you okay so i'll i'll uh
i'll be pretty generous okay um
[Music]
oh
how high is she gonna go higher higher
that is so much
450 450 450 450. uh yes this is my offer
you can do more you can do more
doesn't bunch all right
i'm gonna never hold it i'm sorry one
second i just messed it up oh oh man
oh sorry
can i buy uh your pink property
you know what i'll let amen win if it
means ollie loses
take my thing for like 4 20. it's fine
okay
okay i mean that's it
what
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
indonesia girls are
getting at each other's fruits again
again
uh underlying the bold italic again i
won't forgive ollie
all right my uh max is 380.
no 420 please i'll um i'll i'll i'll
give you a little something uh in return
you know i think
you can sell me hers for 400 or for
yeah less than what you're offering oh
oh really would ollie do that
oh really olly you would do that
it's 400.
all right four ten fourteen fourteen
fine 4 10.
or 420 please just ten dollars you're so
rich okay fine
fine deal is all right
oh switch numbers that looks nice i like
those numbers
but there's still there's still one pink
property that's not taken by anybody yet
yeah
i won't
yeah i want it and so i can train
but
it's not looking good it's really
difficult to land on specific
uh lots um
here's somebody only you paid me so much
already
thank you
and see what the future means for you
believe
i'm i'm getting scared now i feel like
i'm targeted but love that's okay what
you saw
let's go only with those roller skates
you're gonna get so far i love roller
skating
i was one of my biggest hobbies when i
was younger roller skating oh you used
to roller skate yeah i used to do two
but not the thank you
actually inline skating is roller
skating the one that looks like ollie's
um shoe i mean the one yeah in one side
four mine was also inline skating
england's getting fun
oh nice ollie
there you go
oh
thank you
movie theater poop money
[Laughter]
[Music]
well that's good you didn't go to jail
no more doubles no more hey how are you
doing my best gen mate i hope you're
healthy
somebody said anything huh somebody said
anything i saw my discord
oh [\h__\h]
oh my god
ollie if you need to cry you can cry on
my shoulder
i'll cry behind your head
don't tell her don't
blow your nose in my hair
got some of that back
huh oh i guess i only paid like 300
technically oh oh
you're so rich
wow you're so rich and beautiful and
pretty
thank you
yeah um have you ever considered um
doing charity work
uh yeah you don't look into it
yeah well she hasn't already worked
before
oh
no
well you know if uh if anybody wants uh
this red property i needed an ollie both
uh have at least one other
build house
do you want indonesian tap water i'll
give you both of them they're gonna kill
each other over that oh my god
oh oh thank you oh nice oh
uh
200.
nothing happened all is the same
let's roll the dice nothing i feel like
time has stopped and standing still
so who's gonna get the red one oh my god
you landed on the right
a lot oh oh yes now you hear those
sounds
delicious
i work to stamp everyone i work the same
path
okay wait i'm gonna manage properties
and then buy a house
how do i do that no i got those 200 that
i wanted
i have to what you have to roll the dice
first okay okay okay i'll shake to roll
i'm so tired oh my god i'm so sorry guys
oh it's alright
still waking up
uh
i'm using too much energy so i'm like
[Music]
go to your property so yours would be
the green one and then you can uh
it shows instructions on yours
okay
okay ah then okay i i add house
[Music]
what's happening right now
what's happening oh okay my house i was
doing houses
[Music]
yeah i think you got uh
one house
uh each but you you have still one one
you can put one house on okay
okay
oh
wow yeah you did it
okay
okay so back okay and then i can put one
more house maybe 13 cats
you can actually yeah you can build
another one if you want but the one next
to the black one
yeah that was expensive oh
that's very expensive
ooh
450 oh [\h__\h] wow
okay
we're going bankrupt
oh and turn sorry
your time has come let's play
[Music]
okay
i like watching the dog walk yeah is
that how your dog walks too
slowly
[Music]
how
rng is on my side listen ladies the
market's open if you guys you know well
there's anything you got your eye on
both me and ollie are kind of um not so
kind of low on money maybe a little bit
later we can start fighting about it
give us some time oh double okay oh
double
um oh thank god okay no jail no jail no
jail where are we
going you must pay this one
okay i was hoping for the other one but
okay
thank you okay it's okay it's a little
treasure chest oh once i want the other
one roll dice
i'm landing on
ollie's property again i think
who is it no what is that oh free
parking oh
oh great parking nice all right
to 20
200 okay
oh
plus 100 it's really cheap okay okay
okay
i need to make sure that i can make some
money here
okay the others out of business yes
hopefully hopefully
it started so bad for me but um it's
looking up uh it's looking better now
thanks to all
it was repaired i think the developers
might be watching and they saw oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] this streamer
is gonna ruin our
our um
good i'm gonna get reviews i'm gonna go
to the toilet real quick sell out yeah
you guys keep going okay okay
i'll pour all of these i hope she's okay
can i resell my house or not
yeah you can sell it you can
yeah i don't think it's as much as you
pay for it maybe what really never mind
really not sure i'm not sure i thought
it said that but oh yeah you should have
checked we're just checking the next one
four what does four give me i'll
probably have to pay something huh oh
charge rifle idol meeting oh yeah
let's say ollie how much 12. okay not
bad
[Music]
and she doesn't even know what's
happening she doesn't even notice it
manage properties and then
oh yeah
it's not as much as
that's so mean
that's nice construction costs money
yeah i guess so
yeah
let's hope you don't step on some
expensive lots next turn right now
hope so
can you please step on my uh lot please
thank you i can still i'm going to the
14th time uh no thanks my lot is more
important
what the heck nice yes finally
finally finally she pays her freaking
tax it's only 80 bucks it's only 80. why
you're so close to my space you should
have you know you're welcome you're
welcome here it's the beginning of her
downfall don't worry it comes slowly
[Music]
what comes literally let's see her
downfall i don't know you got some money
only a little bit though
i got some money yeah who gave me their
change
raymond i love you you are you are
a very important friend to me you hold
no special place in my heart thank you
ollie
now give me that red
i have that
oh i guess we broke even on that huh oh
on what oh did you just pay me something
i'm paying taxes oh oh you have to pay
me
it's it's like you paid the game mo or
something alma did you
perhaps offer them some good reward
gotcha
do you have a sponsor
sponsored by
i'm exposed by monopoly
and i'm kind of scared what if i step on
like some dangerous
lots be careful rainey oh you stopped
i'm live oh [\h__\h] that is scary you're
landing on mine
oh god
manage your property to trade with other
players or go through your properties to
find a way to make money and pay your
debts
so
so what should i do you don't need the
light blue one do you maybe give it to
only
yeah i'll buy it for some money sure
a whoops
a trade with
ollie
friendship repairing
friendship repair
thank you i don't get it uh
trade and then ollie
and then this is so confusing yeah
what's your offer and then um
yeah i'll give you this
i'll give you 200 you know what i'll
give you 200. um 250. 250.
okay fine 250.
now you have to press r i think
r yeah and then put in the 250 there
okay
noise only always come back
[Laughter]
don't you want to go to the bathroom
yeah i want to wash my hands give me
that tap water
delicious that water
only get some monopoly finally
yay
okay
atlanta okay
add money and then deal
deal
whole life indonesia so titty
it feels back together hell yeah how how
beautiful to see that now you can
construct
yeah
and now you have to know now i have to
fake kiara
basically she paid for me
oh you paid my debt
thanks ali
justice is served finally
justice smells good again i didn't break
any rules
you're not breaking rules but you're
bending rules
with those buff arms
buffs and
buffs in
whatever happens oh something good
something good
nice if you pack wait who owns river
rapids ride
[Music]
peaceful i feel like we've entered a
peaceful face here in monopoly yeah
we're all winning we're all losing some
never seen this before the game started
saltiness nice
no
guys i'm going
oh no ice cream oh and nobody even gets
anything from that just the city i know
it's just like
hey we're gonna hack you over
yeah if you don't want that yellow i'll
buy it for 150 no no no only don't sell
it to her she's too bad don't don't sell
it to me if anyone
you're just saying that to try to strike
a chord within you ollie to win you on
her side
oh
you want some bread
oh only realistically i don't have the
money
we're both kind of broke right now
no goodness oh she gets a salary
and i landed on my own oh nice
well uh ollie you sure you don't want to
sell any of your properties you know he
doesn't she does
not the yellow one maybe another one no
i mean
you might go bankrupt here
that is true i'm really low on money
later the remaining later
in rates
yeah
i'll let you make your decision when
it's your turn ollie
okay think about it you know think about
it
yes ma'am do you want some money
i i i love money how much do you uh i
don't know i would buy your yellow one
for 200.
i'll give you 300. i'll give you one
minute i'll give you 350.
350 anyone going higher
i'm good
i'm good i don't have money
okay uh okay i'll show your show
your show uh
ollie is the purple one
uh
i give you wait yeah i give you 300
i thought you said 350.
yeah 300
oh
oh my gosh
can i get a 59
lot of money you can
for 49.
you don't want to
never sell the
[Laughter]
ah there we go you need to add it like
that okay okay okay okay
okay don't worry i'm not scamming you
huh see
money is even higher than the value of
the yellow one
yeah do you wish you from bankruptcy yes
nice trying to deal with you i'm i'll
get to you later i'll eat that yellow
one eventually oh okay
all right
i just need to save some money
maybe three turns later or two turns
later
if someone lands on my orange pieces
please
is that
oh that's mine wait no that's not mine
i'm mad
someone already owns this property
this is a perfect example of ami's power
she has too much of it
yeah shake troll
oh my gosh poor duck what does it always
get
uh
seven gets me what
[Music]
yes please nurse me i can only be cured
by monopoly money kiara please no
no
i'm sure there's other ways to cure you
maybe uh
[Music]
oh
okay i don't really care about the pink
one but now she maybe wants the only
pink one
oh well you know i wouldn't mind selling
it
i know
[Music]
maybe we could negotiate a trade or
something
[Music]
how much are the utility
you you would have to ask for a lot
ollie
i want your utilities for the prank no
that's all right i don't mind keeping
just two of them
it would be her third third monopoly
oh you guys got me presents you're so
nice thanks guys
the second birthday kind of sucks is
that really a thing
yeah we're only getting you ten dollars
ten dollars and see what the future
holds for you sometimes i i kind of uh
oh
zeta oh double it was moving it was
spinning
yeah
wow
riggs after all but now it's doing
something good for me
am i going to jail no free parking
parking you're parking
[Music]
okay
she has her birthday money already oh
it's that one yellow that you don't have
two huh oh yeah interesting
tables turn but it's okay eventually
i'll get it i'll get it
uh-huh see there's a upfront payment
up front
i see it's like a down payment right
mm-hmm
24 bucks
we'll uh
just
take that
[Music]
oh this is the one you wanted
i want bread
i'll trade you for the pink
okay
oh no
no
ask for some extra money
sure what do you want
[Laughter]
let me see the value first actually oh
my god
this is mine
and wait but the value is automatically
higher because she'll get a she'll get a
monopoly
but it looks like it's not higher
can i get a 50
sure from you
yeah
seems like a good trade to me oh yeah it
is for you
[Laughter]
oh my god
she has all the pinks she has all the
pinks now
yes you can still build on it while you
guys are losing money every time you
step on it
exactly
[Music]
right now you can you can make some
money off of that if you want to sell
that last property what sorry oops i
accidentally pressed hey
oh you want to keep that red one huh
and the blue and the red trade you could
both get a monopoly from that looks good
to me yeah that seems beneficial
i wish you would pay me a
hundred oh what's happening
what's that i'm just putting some stuff
on my house
oh god um at least you don't have that
much right now to spend
[Music]
okay let's get away quickly
run run run penguin
oh
okay
okay okay
thank you
it's getting scary here i wish you luck
it's smelling like bankruptcy all over
11.
olly are you okay you've been kind of
quiet are you okay
i'm i'm thinking here's what my brain's
starting to learn
[Laughter]
ouch
three
oh oh you really like getting your
fortune told huh good luck i know
uh that last blue place from ollie um
i could
[Music]
or make your green yeah stronger because
now you have some
cats i'll just make my green stronger
wait what my property
can i
buy again
yes i can you can go i can one more yeah
but but don't forget
selling it makes you lose money so
yeah
it's okay i think i'm okay
maybe
oh this is getting scary
okay and then back all right
i think my bankruptcy is close
[Music]
so much to give away
so much to make other people happy olly
like what your properties
ah i i see you mean my big personality
yeah you you know you just being here
makes me happy
don't go straight
okay
show me show me something good
five
i think gotcha
no ice cream
[Music]
that's rough
huh
you decide that i guess you do you
oh goodness i'm safe
okay cool oh nice
i'm going to return turrets now let's
see what did the card say about now i am
the most broke can someone land on
orange
uh eight what does eight do it looks
like purple
[Music]
like 200 bucks
yeah
made out of gold
gold ice cream what would that taste
like what is that
[Music]
i heard that's the most expensive ice
cream is like ten thousand dollars once
what is that made out of
oh so close literal gold okay
food
i hope you wouldn't get sick by eating
that chocolate that ice cream
if there's that much gold in it yeah
yeah like all the caviar oh another
double oh
another trouble
one more double come on ahmed you can do
it i believe in you
no no who goes to jail it'll be on her
favor because she doesn't have to do
anything let's do it oh no oh she'll
land on her thing too
it's okay
at least like some rich person to like
it's a chance has emma ever been in jail
damn that's a lot of money okay
thank
you they vote this with you thank you
i'm the chairman so it's cool that's my
responsibility there must be a reason
why amma never goes to jail it's because
she pays the jail i know um
i'm going to pink i think no no oh oh no
wait what what yeah yeah i'm going to
pink oh god
[Music]
i hope it's worth it
yeah breakfast is always worth it always
gotta start a day with a good breakfast
true hmm
what does everybody eat for breakfast
usually daina you you tell me
um i don't eat breakfast i just drink
like i don't know milk or something oh
i don't like milk drinking it just like
that either
what about ollie what do you eat
oh
[Music]
gosh
oh okay
hi dog
national hot dog day
time
huh what's happening fifty fifty dollars
okay oh
sometimes you have to oh
okay okay that's not so bad could have
been worse
nothing worse definitely yeah thank you
ollie what do you eat for breakfast
um i i usually wake up at 11 so i don't
really eat breakfast i just eat lunch
yeah i mean that's still breakfast the
first thing you eat is breakfast
ah i've been eating a lot of chicken to
be honest speaking again
for you what do you want
you were talking to me
what are you trying to do here
i'm trying to give you um
an offer
i don't need your filthy money what do
you want
me okay
if you don't want my money uh that
that's okay too but i heard that you've
been eyeing the blue for quite a while
now
um
sure but what's in it for me
the red one
yeah wait the blue the red one the blue
one isn't it for you the red one is it
for her
bye
[Music]
is there a reason just just because
ollie
no
you could make so much money with your
monopoly
i guess i'll think about it okay you'll
think about it
that's it because everyone else is
building houses you need to build more
too
it's your turn
true but it's not like i have money to
build houses
room
kind of goes once you have the
blue yeah it's like the blue when you
land on it it already cost us 50. so if
it if you had both of them i think it
increases quite a bit doesn't it yeah
you'll make people go bankrupt instantly
oh that's so nice oh dana
thanks for paying me back
the hotel
[Music]
oh oh thank you thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
all in cash wow again we can roll again
you got a
seven
[Music]
oh
guys we should join forces now we
shouldn't be against each other
yeah are you sure make that parade for
the blue you know throw in some cash i
think that would benefit right now i'm
talking about joining forces with you
[Music]
who was it that kept refusing my deal in
the beginning
okay i'm sorry i apologize that was my
bad i'm just i could forgive you after
the game apology
oh i should have popped i forgot to
manage property
you know what this is okay this is safe
zone
i'm saving money right now
[Music]
oh my gosh i gotta get i got
uh hopefully i don't land on carrots and
you're going pies else i think
bye bye bye bye ollie i'll miss you
i'll miss you
three claw
three claws
oh hey
[Music]
oh
you might be able to yeah in a trade
because i i remember being able to hover
over like the get out of jail card yeah
really oh well but that's like i don't
know i wouldn't really want it because
in the end game you kind of want to stay
in the jail too
oh so you don't have to like yeah yeah
yeah yeah i had that happen
i really didn't want to land on gouda's
lots because she had the whole street
all for herself
oh my god that must have been scary it
would have ruined anybody
very scary
sweet home
[Music]
what do you eat for breakfast
oh um congratulations what do i eat for
breakfast oh sometimes i'll make an egg
sandwich which has like two eggs and a
one sunny side up and one scrambled and
then
gluten-free bread avocado yes yeah can't
eat normal bread
where's my other thingy oh
recently i make pancakes banana
blueberry pancakes almost every day
oh yeah i saw the picture it looks so
good yeah i'm so into it right now
using pancakes yeah banana pancakes
though
the whole batter is made out of bananas
it doesn't even taste that much like
bananas though
what's this that i can't i was like
yay welcome to the world west
howdy
[Music]
my retribution will come
[Laughter]
this is my retribution
oh we're getting closer to
you know trading the yellow one maybe
soon soon soon
um
we'll see i'm on my way i'm just saving
some money how much do you want
i think 300 is good oh okay three
hundred fifty hundred
okay maybe next time
i need some save money no three hundred
you said three hundred
oh yeah but then change my
i would mind your business
[Music]
all right 400 is good too i think but
i'll have to get some save money
somewhere
oh hello remy hi
hi
[Music]
thank you
shake to roll
[Music]
does that give me
eight
let's eat give me
oh nice
oh
she's getting so good hey ollie oh god
ollie's looking dangerously you want to
trade
you know what
oh you want to do a trade-off for the
your your blue one oh shoot i i
accidentally pressed the wrong thing do
you want to trade the blue one for
maybe 200
he was singing like maybe 350 help a
friend 320. maybe what about 320. 320
sounds good actually oh yeah
yeah i'll take 320. that's all right and
then
um
sorry uh so on my side yeah on your side
okay three twenty
three twenty sounds nice or if you wanna
go like 250 and uh the the red one
i'll take 320.
we're not giving her the red one
oh man
oh no oh oh you're losing you're losing
the the one
valuable thing to trade with oh
i know but i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm close to
the background
uh
what it's for times wait what oh no oh
oh yeah
no what happened no
[Music]
everybody else is still in here wait
wait no sorry it's weird
[Music]
oh wait bankrupt i'm
no i don't want to no i don't want to
brag
no what the [\h__\h] no no i i
i'mma rejoin
somebody it says there's an ai no
seraphina who the [\h__\h] are you
seraphina
all right give me a good ai give me good
ai seraphina it's been a while we meet
again
seraphina
wait an ai you think she's gonna trade
me the yellow one
it's pink it's not there
i wonder how nice ai is
i let the robot play for me then you can
you can just pretend you're playing like
yeah
honestly listen to me i've given you all
the tools
what are you sorry that's so stupid
yeah that's so silly
yeah
it says it says please wait you will
join the match ready that's good
[Applause]
i don't know how this game works maybe
somebody in chat knows
oh it's joining a flavor
oh thank god that i have to um i have to
say i have to praise the game if they
actually let us do that because i feel
like if you get kicked out once normally
you don't you're not able to go back
see you later seraphina
hopefully
that was all not very long-lived but
[Music]
okay i think i landed on my own property
i hope oh no
oh rachel and oh
you're just helping me uh buy off the
breathing on me
that's exactly how a dog briefs should
be used to it
i'll see you
what
is is there a win in my future perhaps
[Music]
[Applause]
bank error sounds like dirty money kiara
okay i think i have now enough on the
400 right you're not getting any higher
no no no i i have uh saved money so that
i don't die
so
that you don't die
no you already went from 300 to 400
you're not going any higher around me
no no no not a stupid number you always
love your food
i have to honor the date or else you're
going to get bad luck that's that's the
rule
today is that oh yeah i didn't even
realize
but you have to do it to the meme wait
what am i doing this right
what no you went from 300 to 400 already
what is 420 the chad's gonna be mad at
you if you don't do it now my chat is
supportive of the four hundred
they said they're gonna be like sarah
doesn't even know how to
yeah they mean know that they're already
aware of that i never understand they're
not around
just an extra 20 monopoly money and why
is it so stupid the controls are so
[\h__\h]
um you've been away for too long i'm i'm
moving right now 20 seconds
20 seconds
[Music]
yeah whatever you get this
uh
[Music]
uh you know i think i'll do this uh
maybe on the next turn yeah
why i met
[Laughter]
[Music]
you just want that 420 don't you
you know what you're doing
advice
i think i'm paying taxes
oh seller oh nice sometimes
free houses
thank you three houses
oh goodness gracious
may may mastery be on my side today
your time has come
roll the dice please get me to jail you
only pray to my son yourself but when
it's convenient to you
yeah
where's your loyalty
i love what you've done i end my turn
okay okay oh it's not looking so bad
anymore
yeah yeah we're all pretty
pretty equal except for amen maybe
she has too many properties but the rest
of us are looking pretty equal
you're welcome
um i'm gonna buy
houses do i have enough money for house
it's kind of cutting it close i feel
like but yeah
oof yeah i don't think so
maybe later
yeah yeah intern scary danger zone let's
roll the dice
don't forget at the end of your turn
yes uh what
what
and my turn no no at the end of your
turn we have a trade to do
oh yes what if she's like oops
oh
i am wow
there we go
you gotta upgrade it
yeah i'll upgrade it
all right
[Music]
i'm good
you can operate
yeah i will
aurene
eventually if you if you turn this down
eventually i might not be able to pay
anymore so
better take it now than when i'm broke
i want 450. what the [\h__\h]
all right all right all right
i'll be
generous here i'll lower it to 420.
generous okay 4 20. i'm on my way this
takes a little while
don't waste my time and getting on it
oh no no no no
no no no no think about it
i'm a little bit of a troll aren't you
add money
and then
choosing
this yellow the clown parade
there's demand there will be an offer uh
hold on i'm thinking about it
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't know is this a really good deal
yeah
it's really worth it squeeze though
please what you gonna do with that one
single property here huh
you wanna get all right all right all
right
[Music]
hallelujah two beautiful colors
i will have to wait and hopefully not go
bankrupt now
someone land on orange please please
please no
squeeze here orange is a beautiful color
it's the color oh
[Music]
i have to roll again
yes you do
wait is that yellow
that is yellow
okay okay okay here we go let's go here
we go
you know what i'm going to make a mirror
i'm going to make an updated fold
what the tables may have turned
right you're still ahead by quite a bit
yeah yeah but there's higher chances
if rainy upgrade that's the end for us
because we'll eventually land there
it was that
someone already
i'm gonna manage my property
and i'm gonna
have this it might be working yeah moon
drop this color set yeah this one is
this one
yeah
okay that's it okay filter if i put a
hundred
i'll survive with a hundred i think
okay okay okay um no oh
shake the dice and see what the future
is for you
yes remain faithful yes yes
believe it oh my gosh
six percent you weren't ten percent
before you weren't you were ten or
eleven before hey money money money what
happened oh love what you have done to
the place yes
some people think
is winning
it's
looking interesting anything could
happen
oh dear
she's using all that money from me all
my money all of my kfp money is being
used
in industry
reinvesting
yeah bit well i'm i'm my
where am i i don't want to step on that
territory
oh i'm not anywhere close there thank
goodness
[Music]
four houses four houses wait how much is
it then
twenty what
they're both winners in monopoly
the game could go either way yeah yeah
yeah there's still
wow
a pink vacation yes
oh
lucky
[Music]
okay
don't go too far kiara
nine
oh god oh god
i think i'm passing pink at least oh no
wait oh yeah uh i'm passing brown
okay okay okay okay
we have changed okay
and uh let's manage some properties we
have to
add some stuff here um 150. should i
make orange stronger
or how much is this one 100 oh let's add
100 here
wait these are the houses are so cheap
goodness uh-oh uh-oh people have been
lying the most on this one i feel
the wild west
550.
yeah that'll take any of us out yeah
wow wow wow 550 holy moly oh macaroni
okay but i think i think that's good for
now i want to be on the safe side
um
and turn okay okay okay
okay focus my only hope right now is to
land at 12.
maybe not at 12 but maybe like eleven
what's there oh
eleven please
six six six what's six
what's six i feel sorry i don't want
only to lose because i feel like i can i
can relate to her
[Music]
for too long because you'll get
desperate with it and then you'll give
it away for anything
give it away while you're in a good
position
with it
you know what i mean
it's more uh what's this uh i'll i'll
play again i wish you luck what if i get
bankrupt
you have to sell a
away from property
don't worry
worst case only only will always buy
your red one
i have no money though smart investors
never did bingo dana is my biggest
investor so far
i gotta buy some new floaties
oh fortune
[Music]
what's your problem with
orange content i love that beautiful
that's a cheap beauty contest
[Music]
i'm scared i'm scared i'm scared i need
a big oh [\h__\h] oh five that's pink
oh
it's pink that's big no wait that's not
pink that's no it is pink
there's pink houses oh two houses okay
150 is okay 150 is okay 150 is okay it's
it's not it's not we're all down to 200.
it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay
i'm excited confirmed by the game
but only second no that's wrong there's
something wrong with that i i will be
salty about i'm a winning a little bit
but i will always
do yay
it looks like a lot with the houses but
the amount is
meh yeah
that's pretty good oh this yeah it's
okay i think you won't hate me if you
land on it right yes exactly
shake the dice
it's tolerable
i would be a little bit scared to have
double here um
in the end game when there's no money to
spend nice oh but this is fine this is
okay
this is fine
get me another double please another
double oh
come on
okay here's the jail's over there yeah
yummy
where are you going
oh
oh i knew it i knew everybody lands on
that one
my time has come
hey ollie if you want to sell me that
railroad
[Music]
don't go don't go bankrupt you still
give me 600.
i don't get you out
that's a lot of money but no no no no
that's tempting but
yeah um
you know let other people answer for you
all later sure you want to drop out so
early
as a gentleman i know what's best for
her
i might i might not know what it is
perfectly but it's not selling to army
we might run out of time and get
replaced oh true true true true yeah
just be uh
can you spend your time with the trade
can i actually mortgage this
yeah
but it's probably is it enough i don't
think so
how do i mark it well
l instead of r r is buying l is selling
i can't do it wait but how much will i
give you
huh it'll give me a hundred
that's not enough to pay me
unfortunately
i'll have to to give away my friends i'm
sorry i'm too powerful
how much i don't i can't give you money
honestly i don't have that that much
how do i how do i do this i think chad's
saying you are hovering on the wrong
railroad so try to put it up for
mortgage on yours
oh okay
it might have been i guess
i think this was not that one yeah you
still only get 100.
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
thank you now you've signed the fate for
the rest of us
oh [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] i'm too powerful i
don't know how to handle this palette
i'll even play it together
together
i i i i i don't know what i did actually
yeah
i didn't realize i forgot that happens
too that when you go bankrupt it goes to
the person who made you bankrupt i
forgot that holy [\h__\h]
uh only you playing with me we're making
decisions together now
hell yeah it's going to be the death
phoenix
oh i like that yeah
undead phoenix
undead phoenix oh yeah we're booking i
landed on reynolds maybe
oh that's scary i'll include you
oh it's it's mine oh holy [\h__\h] it's
oh no it's not mine
the one red one from elena 20.
it's a partnership welcome to kfp only
we welcome you
here wow what a cool coincidence i
really like a frying chicken
yeah yeah right you're into chicken
these days
i'm sorry
well chad do you want a new poll now do
you regret not voting for me now
i told you it's redemption
oh my god i i almost don't want to have
all this property i feel like this is
too much for me to own i didn't work so
hard for it but i got [\h__\h] over in the
beginning good again give it to me you
could give it to mickey already so if
you don't want it that way yeah maybe
that's what ollie wanted to happen with
her
ollie i mean
let me ask you what do you want ollie oh
he's right there
uh i wanna eat lunch
you think you think that the properties
would go to next gen mate right inside
oh my first ice cream
no so sad it was it was very smart of me
to build on that one lot the one orange
lot that was just smart in some way i
deserve it for knowing ahead of time
where only was gonna land
well um mccarran you know herrera is
kinda down on her lucky could give her
the
the red ones he don't need them right
both of them sometimes you have to pick
both of them yeah
[Music]
i can't just give everything away like
that
i can
neck and neck now
i'll i'll think about
uh
maybe
giving each one of you one lot
how long does that sound like
inheritance
otherwise i feel like i got too much
from this game
so i get the railroad don't give up
maybe i'll give you the light blue one
the plane
i also have a get out of jail card
maybe
i'll give i'll give some things away
okay i'm i'm too nice
oh you could just not give it kiara
oh
think carefully
oh elena doesn't want the
the property either
think carefully yeah it's okay you can
you can have them you can have them
really really you're the railroad
has the
she has the deadly street she has the
green one and the blue one pretty deadly
yeah those are pretty strong yeah even
if she doesn't have the red ones
um
oh i have to think a little bit chat
what do you think
chad chat what do you think helped me
committing self sabotage
why are you so nice heart emoji because
you're also so nice ollie
i'm just dead
mom
yeah
oh yeah that's the cheap one you're
lucky somebody in the game should go
somebody goes bankrupt like the property
should go back on the market like just
on the board
yeah i thought that was what's gonna
happen i thought that was it
um
i think those are like home rules
[Music]
oh it's cost the same my chance to win
but is it do i deserve it this is my
terrific i don't
i mean you did kind of uh planted a bomb
on the mail i went from the very bottom
for a long time to the very top so maybe
i maybe
i have the imposter syndrome in monopoly
oh [\h__\h]
it was really smart to like plant it on
the middle instead of like the the one
on top like i am again
yummy i i will i would i will i will i
will at least not build on my properties
for a while okay out of of
um kindness
where am i going oh
it should be safe you should be safe oh
yeah
a second
time kiara that's called being cocky
no i mean
she is a phoenix
yeah okay i see what you said
oh
okay i will not i won't do i won't build
i'll give you guys some time to catch up
or or destroy each other whichever you
want or destroy each other or destroy
each other that's a
what's that seven seven give me
i don't even know
i can't tell yeah
yeah i don't even remember like we can't
really see the board at all
[Music]
i think we know how this is gonna turn
out i'm so sorry
but at least orange is the color that i
really deserve the other ones i don't
deserve you do you do you do oh i'm
going to enter and i don't want to build
a house oh your time
died for nothing
holy what should i do i'll leave only
you you got my inheritance uh now you
should win holy
hey i inherited money
nice oh you should join us in the
maldives
i don't have the money to the maldives
it's okay i pay i pay for it
i have your money and your property i
pay for your trip to muldesk
i don't want to intrude on your date
it's okay you'll be on a different
island maldives has many islands
you can try to swim over to our island
you're right to place the last house
glasses can only be obtained
what does that mean
ah it's because uh you know um
in the in the original board game uh
they have like limited houses
oh like only a few houses that they can
actually
oh you can't press anything i don't know
i
am confused
why isn't it
yeah
huh what are you doing wrong
i don't know
uh a and b are both grayed out i can't
impress either house i can't what about
right can you can you press right
[Music]
no
oh this is weird
ah yeah i think it'll bypass it anyway
the brown houses you should put on pink
instead
they'll make more money on pink
yeah but it doesn't let me uh do who
needs to press a
[Music]
and does any can anybody else oh
mine's grayed out mine's grayed out too
i'm bankrupt
okay
all right well i guess we'll
wait just
just i don't know
bypass me but
yeah i press r or a and b and no nothing
happens i'm pressing a but nothing
happens l maybe i don't know
oh wait what happened what happened
what uh
i'm trying to like move my
my thumb stick see but it's not working
that's so weird is it time ticking
somewhere
i think it's bugged
no no
no no no no
oh maybe it'll just skip on its own
maybe
that's what i'm saying
hey let's talk about something
else revenge
it's verafina
seraphina it's your ghost haunting us
yeah i know
sponsoring the last house the hell
ourselves cannot be bought because we
need some ghost extermination ah
call the ghostbusters ghost town is it
time for fasmophobia i don't want to
play it fast
i'm scared
although poor people is perfect
yeah
but i don't like plasmaphobia
i don't like myself no come on come on
monopoly i praised you for letting ami
back into the game and this is this is
how you repay me
what if what i see on the buttons
what if you leave the game once you just
get replaced by serafina maybe for a
little bit you can join back in and
maybe that will let the game do its
thing maybe maybe
it's better than
it's like it's not moving ryan is it
i left
oh yes nothing happened
oh okay okay something happened and then
wait for ahmed to rejoin him yes return
rejoin rejoin
wait well then i have to relaunch the
game
i'll i'll wait i'll write if voice case
will replace with ai and you can come
back in smart
yep
nine there's
you might you might not make it in time
but uh
uh yes the loading experience is really
long
okay you have uh been replaced but we're
waiting i'll i'll waste some time to
wait for you to come back
yeah use the game to play itself
good thinking you forced the game to
move on she's gonna mess up my
my properties
no she just did nothing basically did
nothing oh it's actually the same person
again same seraphina wasn't it seraphina
with e before was it always seraphina
with r it's always sarah with a oh okay
okay
i don't think it's going to let me
rejoin
yeah because before it said like oh you
got you want to rejoin but now when i
try to play online
it doesn't uh offer that
[Music]
just keep going i'll have the robot sit
in for me
okay all right the game was gonna
probably be over soon anyway
yeah yeah i'm sorry i'm still in the
game in spirit let's see what seraphina
can do i will destroy seraphina she'll
never get the the black lot never no
never you know what i'm actually curious
how the bot place
yeah like you know the offers and
everything yeah let me see that
oh it's already built on blue i could
build some more in blue
maybe seraphina is going to land on blue
no no no no
house oh
right to place your last house oh again
here we have option but i can actually
press a press
[Music]
oh now you can break it oh it works host
advantage oh no i don't really want to
do this though oh [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
no
yeah only only one of you can build like
i want to go fast
no then seraphina will get it [\h__\h] you
seraphina [\h__\h] you
[Music]
but i still own the blue ones she's just
building one eh
how's what's up there what are you doing
no
look at that
what did she do
i don't know actually it's not her turn
so she can't i thought she was putting
on the brown one
oh but i'm just watching your stream so
it's a delay
oh all right let me try to
show it to you on discord
yes please
[Music]
oh you also can't see it
i was watching from the stream as well
did you leave you out completely my my
nintendo died oh
okay let me show you okay
okay it's 40 fps fun
yeah yeah okay okay
thank you
wow now nobody can build uh
seraphina what the hell nobody yeah
because there's the last house
yeah that didn't happen when we played
monopoly before did we spend more houses
than last time
did we really get that far
i'mma still win according to the poll
so unless your athena makes like a hotel
then you guys can't make uh you guys
can't make any houses
oh
i feel like the way it is now we can
bankrupt seraphina anyway well she's so
slow and deciding even though she's ai
like just decide like what
faster
not it
i'm i'm faster than your lady
[Music]
maybe amit is actually maybe she changed
her name to seraphina while she was uh
[Music]
hoping that we'll um
well i don't know somehow let's the bots
win for some reason
oh it's my property
automaton ride
house is available again
it should be because serafina just made
a hotel in the brown section
ah
[Music]
fixed it seraphina what you gonna do
how are you gonna
turn this around seraphina
i can do it i like the name
why doesn't she like skip why does she
ever skip oh i can skip for her oh sorry
i didn't realize okay i skipped for her
again again speed run
speed run monopoly any percent
oh that's how we create our legacy
okay bought another house that [\h__\h]
are the houses
we bought another house
yeah
there's only three houses available left
you should try
nah you don't have anything that
seraphina will take right if i was gonna
say try to
somehow trade with seraphina we'll see
if she goes through it
oh you had other plans for your money
[Music]
there's something new on the board for
you to get
oh my gosh
oh no no you can't
wait can you buy it
yeah yeah i don't know how it works i
think so
but it's it's
in the hand like it still it shows up in
her properties oh yeah but it's like
crossed out what does that mean
[Music]
oh it's crossed out from everybody
she still means that i can get it ah but
it's just nobody will um have to
uh she will not earn money if anyone
lands on it for a while
he owns it no it's just like nobody pays
okay
where is seraphine on the board here
okay i'll i will try to destroy
seraphina what is the closest i have no
i i don't have brown i don't have blue
i have this one
that's not
[Music]
not another one
25 24.
wow
your house is left oh last house
actually
i lost no no no action no no no no we're
done we're done we're done we're done
okay
dana try to not land on orange
try to not land on orange you know what
if you land on orange i'll i'll help you
get through the okay we we have to
destroy seraphina first
yeah we cannot have her be second or
anything
you must oh
wow i didn't know you were that
expensive but they didn't
it's for the maldives money
[Music]
what should i sell i think
you could probably sell all your blues
or um
yeah
red maybe smell red for me so serafina
lands on it or something i don't know
we'll just we'll just sell some houses
for now and then see okay nice like
freed up
yeah so
um let's see if we can get to
oh wait what else belongs to me the pink
snow
i can tell the red ones
you know what let's see how much are
they oh wait can i oh yeah 100 10 i only
get 110 from selling one
i'll give it two not much
oh but it's just mortgaging i can't
completely sell it i can only trade it
to dana
yeah you could trade it right now um i
can sell for 110 so i would trade it to
you for 110.
okay
so instead of mortgaging it you actually
oh yeah
you will be bankrupt no no oh god wait
wait wait um i'll i'll
do this for now because there's no time
uh uh
uh
yes desperate times is that gonna get
you enough if you do all three let's see
it should be should be enough or two
you did what needed to be done there's
also railroads there's those they're so
slippery and the other the black the
black so seraphina can't get it anymore
yeah yeah
the one next to rainey's which one is
mine okay yes this one the one next to
mine
so serafina can't ever get it anymore
okay
yeah yeah yeah i i'm i'm i'm stressed
out i don't know what wait wait it's not
enough
you're missing like six dollars
ah
did you sell a house and one of your
properties yeah
i guess
oh
50. get that one okay i'll get the money
back soon probably
yeah yeah am
okay
back
hey
sorry that's a lot of money
i also took a lot of money from you so
yeah yeah
okay
use mortgage
mortgage all right
sorry
go go go
double double is not so good i would say
devil is scary
holy [\h__\h] that's nice
damn
maybe i'm not winning
i'm gonna buy a house
before seraphina gets all the houses
yeah build it on the blues
what uh-huh
we're on the green
okay i think i don't need to be so nice
to nina anymore this seems like a fair
battle now
look at them
wait can i
wait i can't build
house why
wait
wait none there
but
but kirsten buy sold one of the house so
it should work yeah
need three on the other first
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah with my bag
okay
okay at least i won't be passing by
green for a while i think
oh okay
what about the blues
oh excellent
oh
now now there's no more houses um
there's only one last house
ollie i'm sorry i have to win only gave
me all her stuff i need to win
you're sitting by i believe in you oh
a hotel
[Music]
oh my gosh seraphina no she doesn't
deserve it
no she doesn't deserve it and took over
ames she didn't work hard for it at all
i know she didn't even know she's
working in my place because i got
disconnected
okay this is a hug if you approve of her
then okay and i must approve of her too
[Music]
oh
oh um you can either repay yeah i'll
repay it
oh oh oh how the table's turn oh my god
it's your turn oh it's horritory it's a
whole little battle now
oh no i'm just like
is just dead now obviously legacy
i blame ubisoft
whatever happens let's um go vacation
you know
yeah yeah yeah don't worry i'm not i'm
not mad or anything this is just the
interesting interesting
way everything
is ending up like it's it's very
interesting
uh
really unexpected things are happening
happening
here is inside yeah
it's only 200. i can't pay it 500.
my mortgage oh god i just need elena to
land on
on one of mine then i'm good again i'm
one of the orange ones
wait elena is uh down there
i'm where i'm
you're here so i'm so close to the
orange ones though
i'm so close to the orange ones
wait uh uh yes okay
that should buy you some time
yeah how much do i need 200 was it 100
okay
that's enough okay yeah
oh god oh god
oh god this goodness scary
oh god so scary
for all that unpredictable
oh
oh this one's not so bad oh but it's
it's mortgaged
isn't it oh it's more good
i
buy more houses
no buyers oh because i don't participate
in the bidding oh
okay oh so as long as you don't
participate enough you should be able to
get it that makes no sense
okay okay
okay
press a
oh sorry
um if no one wants it it's separated
then it should go toward a name
we should play with house rules with
private rules
i know that i think that's much better
oh sorry um i think i'm gonna okay
yeah
no so i can't buy any house or anything
apparently
huh yeah you have yeah never mind i'll
withdraw withdrawal okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay then i'll just um i'll just back
or you know
shake the dice
all right this is the deciding factor
probably
oh
number is back i think it was just
because reyna didn't actually bid maybe
oh got some money perhaps playing it on
your own space nice okay
that is good i'll i'll just um
you gonna explain it
let's guess what the future holds for
both of us
only happy times
only happy times whatever happens we'll
be happy yeah i'm okay if you win
you owned on the one i didn't mortgage
money
wait what uh so i can build a hotel
where
oh no
no this floor
this is the one with the four houses i
want the four houses green brown
oh okay
oh
okay
oh okay okay okay oh god oh god oh god
okay okay enter
why is seraphina bankrupt because she's
through
yeah yeah she's through she's dumb ai oh
no i'm landing on green i think
another seven uh
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
when when she lands on orange
yeah
if you violate an orange or if you land
on green no no no no that's not gonna
happen no no no
i don't like
green property
i don't like spinach no
come on oh that is uh yeah
hey oh oh i think that's it oh no oh no
oh no oh no oh no
oh
these take money too sometimes
oh oh my cat is coming for emotional
support this could get expensive
you owe 200. oh okay
uh
i just need to get rid of either the
yellow one or the light blue one how
much is the light blue on again
get rid of their houses so you don't do
this yeah too much no no i have to keep
orange strong that's my only hope
you have houses on uh pink i don't know
red oh sorry those
no the only house is on are in orange
now
no yeah no we will do it like this uh
okay
i'm able to pay now
come on cause they're giving me starting
i told you it would give me something
bad too
okay
i'm a joker monkeys hi chunkers
[Music]
baby you're saying hello
started so cute started very bad i'm
happy with the results even if i get
seconds even if i get bankrupt bankrupt
now bad news okay ice cream
spanish property cotton candy cotton
candy
that conden canoe is probably made out
of like a silver line
spider webs
spider web cotton
[Music]
wow he's building hotels oh god
oh god oh
go back i'll hold on i'm so close to the
green now
i want to go to jail i want to go to
jail see this one you want to go to jail
why why would you want to go to jail i
don't know
do you miss the porridge
the port is waiting for you
it's nice and warm yeah
okay that's cool it's cozy now
all right are you okay
i'm sorry um
okay
come on every big roll or a small roll
seven seven is seven is mine my field
seven is mine seven is mine seven is
eight i think oh no wait it's jail
[Music]
killed you really got to jail
[Applause]
manifested that is okay
i appreciate that thank you very much
i'll stay here
yay i'm a jailbird i'm a jailbird
but if you had like a good out of jail
card
i have one but i don't know you can chew
it automatically uh
yeah i think no more ice cream okay good
good good good good good we just wait
and see
don't give up yet don't no i am gonna
roll i can even roll the dice so i can
use the card okay
small roll please no doubles okay
good good good
you're staying
another second happy
and turn
oh
i know what you're doing i am stalling
i'm stalling huh the police is
protecting me by
by putting me in gonna give you some
money
okay not very much yeah hallelujah
[Laughter]
that hurts so much doesn't it
do you still want the red ones just
kidding
i don't have money kiara
yeah me neither
is this this is not
sad
can i stay thank you
oh you're liking the porridge now huh oh
she likes it
yeah
they're adding some strawberries for me
because i'm
so so kind hearted
and such a nice addition to jail
oh
[Music]
yeah
the thing is uh harrisonville has a lot
of mortgage
yeah
i can still get them back once i get
some more money
i think i'm landing on my mind at least
or no i'm
no wait yes i am i think oh no way
oh so how does the jail thing work
[Music]
i have to either pay 50 now or use the
okay i don't want to lose any money so
we're using the get out of jail card
oh that is even the 50 bucks are
important now
all right we are on orange
how close are we to green
naruho
and uh dana is getting closer too
we maybe want to reinstate something
here hoping that orena lands on
something
maybe
one of the yellow ones
yeah i can always sell it again it's
just 13 bucks that i lose maybe
all right high wire coaster okay
this is getting intense so we don't know
him
[Music]
it's endless monopoly it will go on
until tomorrow
please come back tomorrow four
four is it free parking let's be parking
what this is getting way too intense
what the heck
i can't manage properties
okay okay okay oh okay okay we're not
going far um
landing on my property i hope
yeah that street is safe
[Music]
no wait
orange
no no ah but she won't be at orange for
a while huh or or or the teal one the
two ones
teal
yeah the teal ones they're like six
dollars right now yeah
i'll go i'll go for the teal one okay
one dollar short man
it's not fair
okay yeah but she's because she's closer
to yellow then she's too light blue so
okay
yeah that actually makes sense
big thinking
i've always been a big finger grainy
thinking
oh 12. oh she's going far yeah she
doubles
oh [\h__\h]
she's safe right now senpai
oh
it'll be her three on the on the next
few turns it's my street yo
nice
nice and nice and nice and
roll again basically elena and is just
working with amez legacy right and i'm
working with all these players yeah
you're working with my railroads legacy
we're we're a team now
oh nice oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i've been consulted by by ollie okay
there we go
now i'm packing green smoothly
uh you're still blue
it's still blue no no no no no no
every little dollar matters now every
little dollar 69. okay
nice
day too
i'm not going down yet
oh hold up
come to the dark side okay this is six
dollars yes dollars for you
that's okay
i don't think anything
before i was missing one dollar you know
even the small ones matter
and now she's gonna come to orange
hopefully come on come on come on what
is that
[Music]
[Applause]
where are we going oh two hundred oh
hallelujah and it's my my safe space
yeah yeah
are you gonna invest
in your price i should i should but i
think i'll roll one more time
because
um i don't want to land on anything
yummy and then have no money left
for you go go go go six oh six is late
is that green
is that one of the whole green no that's
green
[Music]
um should i risk it
well she i should probably go further
than that
she'll probably land on yellow on yellow
i think so too and then i have a full
set again yeah i am
okay whatever we're doing it at this
point at this point
she is really out to get me here what
about her family vacation it's still
happening we can play monopoly in the
motives
oh sure yeah
oh my goodness
uh yeah i'm upset i'm done
okay okay okay okay what's the duck
gonna do
what if i land on like
i don't know i don't know what i'm gonna
land on what's that eight where does la
eight land me i think you're safe
yeah i can't
oh okay i own this property
okay okay okay
seven yeah
so what does seven give you
okay
um not buy anything this turn
wait for your salary yes yes yes yes
it's coming
almond what you snacking on where's that
oh some leftover arrives
right oh that sounds good
oh my own hotel have you thought about
upgrading
[Music]
super tight
i don't know what else to say
who's seraphina it's um ami's uh
daughter
that's yeah okay we'll go with that
okay
that's nothing against the part of your
stuff
yeah seraphina is the second
name
amelia serafina watson did you guys not
know
[Music]
the seraphina her seraphina
you guys call yourself teammates
[Music]
oh nice i own this property you manage
your portfolio ah how long to rein
[Laughter]
i don't give up yes as as the game says
i will not give up um holy [\h__\h] we gotta
sell a lot for that though
send by it well
measures
do you still believe in me ollie
i believe in you but
no no no
no gg no gg
no stop saying gg chat
[Music]
[Laughter]
why is everybody giving up
oh
oh [\h__\h] i only have orange left no my
powerful orange no
those tasty tasty oranges
[Music]
i don't think it's gonna be enough it
won't be enough but i'll just not make
much anymore from my orange ones
okay
but you didn't realize your money is
going to rain and there's a there was a
band no no it's not it's not no no no no
no no no it's okay it's okay believe me
it's in denial olly
okay well i see it now
oh [\h__\h]
well i wanted to end naturally i want a
natural death okay
okay is it enough you won't declare
bankruptcy i'll keep i'll keep uh 11
bucks
thank you
hey you have the 11 bucks
there's so much i can do with 11 bucks
i can buy 11 cheeseburgers right
hello
cheeseburger i don't know
i don't know are they not one dollar i
can probably build uh hotels every
single property you have right now i
guess so
wow life insurance i'm gonna manage
property
i'm gonna
you know do business like uh the
business uh person i am
oh
wow wow
wow wow wow then i'm gonna make a hotel
um where i wonder
i need the pink oh where's kiara oh yeah
i'm not here i'm not here i'm not part
of the collab what do you mean i'm just
kidding
what do you mean i'm hosting
those blues
should i do blues or should i do ping
blues
[Laughter]
overkill it's overkill
this is so entertaining
and it feels like
she's ground pounding me that's okay
it's a part of
yeah that's true she has my railroads
overkill that's just overkill
[Laughter]
[Music]
you think i'm going to land on that one
huh
don't jinx it don't drink something do
not land on that one
i i will
oh okay no wait no oh
i can't afford cotton candy you [\h__\h]
i don't want to come bye-bye
you get enough you get enough you have
one
i can alright my breakfast
priorities you know
i mean uh good news you're not in the
blues
that's good news
yeah because that would bankrupt me it's
like the game wants us to stay here a
little while longer
they want us to bond make some memories
some nice memories of this amusement
park
what's your favorite thing in amusement
parks um
roller coaster i like holding hands in
the amusement park oh that's your
favorite thing time has come
no not really i like roller coasters
oh
is like your time has come
[Music]
my time to end it you mean my time to go
back to sleep
oh oh hey you got money
someone already owns this property
i can pay it
i can pay you but she can pay she can
pay
yeah she has a hundred one like
dalmatians where are you
i'm there you're close to orange
with the 101 that i have i'm gonna
reinstate
my heart
oh
two dollars
let's go
let's just run hold on to the dream turn
one dollar into one million
no two dollars and a dream two dreams
two dollars in a dream six what does six
get me
love
oh
yes the love of my own property
come on we're winning this
nine let's
go let's
let's go
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm getting these achievements i don't
know what you have the mogul mogul what
is it
[Music]
my house is connected from the game yeah
dc
i think this was really interesting
because like so many times the tables
turned and
yeah i think that made it um an
interesting session to follow let's ask
for your opinions uh let's start from
the bottom ollie k
how was it for you
i uh i shouldn't have simp that much
[Laughter]
but it was fun it was actually really
entertaining and fun to play with all of
you guys i hope we can do this again oh
thanks to you i got to number two olia
thank you for that
and thank you for making the collab
happen
i'm happy to finally collab with you
thank you for coming olly
[Music]
i'm not complaining though
all right and number three the one that
everyone was betting on and thought then
she was going to win seraphina
[Laughter]
yeah well the game is bugs you know if
i'm being honest here i think i probably
would have won uh but you know ubisoft
had to take me out i was a threat to the
game because i was so good uh and i
probably got banned mid game that's
probably what happened and uh that's
exciting
one with my legacy my railroad so you
know i'm pretty happy with that that's a
really fun collab i had a lot of fun
thank you kiara
i'm impressed emma you were so proactive
today
wow you
and you inspired me
can i say them i'm a businesswoman you
know
i will never doubt that ever
ever
such a business women all right i'm
number two i i think you know i think
all of kfp including me were thinking i
was gonna lose because the beginning was
so bad i couldn't buy anything i had bad
rolls i had to pay for everything
and when i would land on something where
i wouldn't have to pay it would just be
my own property
i wouldn't be making money at all but
then the tables turn and i i will say
it's a lot of it's thanks to ollie but
also personally investing in orange
worked out really well we're in power
yes orange is the best and orange yeah
orange orange i'm so glad i believed in
orange um so kfp i finally did not
completely lose at
a board game so i hope you're proud of
me i'm proud of it i'm proud of my
accomplishments and last but not least
the one who played monopoly for the
first time today the underdog
[Music]
everybody you are welcome to reyna's
stream
and with the inheritance of amelia
sabrifina watson
i finally won the game but you know
whatever happens let's all have a great
family vacation again
yeah
yeah enjoy
no no let's play again next time
this was fun thank you girls for
enjoying this together and three hours
of monopoly
it it's it's just what it is monopoly
just takes some time but i think we had
some time to bond and
and talk about business yeah
yeah yeah
and everybody i will go back to sleep
yeah go back to sleep yeah
everybody the channels of the
participants are in the description if
you want to subscribe to them please do
also check out all his new original
songs
[Music]
and with that i think anybody has
anything to say besides that
oh
i do
on friday i will be uploading a
cover song uh together with kelly and
cece senpai
wedding rooms yet but look forward to
that please thank you
why
[Music]
looking forward to it that's a that's a
powerful combination of people
we're gonna be slayed by the power of
the free
vocal powerhouses
gonna die again
[Music]
okay soon thank you everybody for
watching and uh in german we say auf
wiedersehen
thank you everybody
[Music]
you