[Music]
do
uh i want to take off my cat tape
oh should i keep it i'll just keep it
hello
how are you emma is doing such an
interesting stream she's so
she's so creative oh man
oh man you gotta came out of nowhere
that's so cool um but we're reading
super chats
only for like three hours or so probably
and i hope i hope some of you stayed
with me so that i don't read them to
myself only
everyone's everyone who's here now is
committed right we're in a committed
relationship you and me
yeah thank you i had a had dinner
before the stream so i am not hungry
for once even though i i mean i have my
i have my chocolate waffles
next to me i might snack on them
somewhere in between
[Music]
let's play some low-fi music
it corrected me to eofy but i still got
the first recommendation
was still the low fiber when you type in
eofy whole live is it
the same for you guys the first
recommendation i get is the whole live
lo-fi and chill remix
after that comes you know if you send by
yourself oh man i feel i feel um
i've eaten stuff but i still feel a
little bit
low low energy
i wonder if that will change
[Music]
one question do you guys anyone here who
watched
the last yakuza stream
[Music]
anyone yes
uh was there anything i said i wanted to
do
before the next stream because i mean we
did the tower so i would
say that there's not there it isn't
really necessary for me to grind anymore
genuinely like i could but i don't
really
need to ryan if you live i
i don't think i'll really have the time
to be honest
because i start at 2pm my time and i'll
probably
wake up like maybe at the earliest one
hour before
i just need to do the main story yeah
you don't need to granulate okay yeah i
think so
too i mean we grinded for the
photo for the tower for the fighting
tower
yeah it's been oh my god it's been a
month already really it's been like
three weeks
by the way smoothie is with me
this movie is chilling behind the
monitor it's so cute
let me let me touch you
[Music]
you oh it sounds weird but when i when i
cuddle my cats
um
they do this thing where you know i
start petting them normally and then
they kind of like curl up inside
themselves
and then they lift their legs so i can
put my
my hand between their legs so i can um
pet their belly properly so i get the
full fluffiness around my
hand
[Music]
she always does it
she's like yeah if i lose my leg you can
get there better
so get in there
and this is literally what happened just
now as i was talking
so soft you're so soft baby
you're so soft hello
i just want to say something
yeah i can't get my microphone closer to
her
oh my god i hope i didn't break my
ah microphone don't break
mushy
baby yo
also where the hell did i leave up last
time i think i read like
two two sections right that i parted by
myself separated by myself
i am used to imagining some candles to
cuddle yeah
living without cats it must be rough
hey you hear me right
baby she's in a cuddle mood
yeah okay let me find the spot
uh when we try to stop
cuddling my cat although it's really
hard to resist
neko
hello baby oh she's leaving the table
now
i think she realized ah mama is
streaming now i'm gonna leave
she's gonna just be loud all the time
whatever
[Music]
oh you know what today i got another
package
this is the third package from oh
cover in one month and this is not
normal it's the first time i've been
receiving stuff from cover
uh you know what came this time
and again i had to pay 40 euro in
customs
and this time uh it seems to be my
golden
play button yay
i didn't unpack it yet but it's a flat
thing
flat heavy thing that says youtube on
top of it
so i suppose it's the play button can't
be anything else
[Music]
yeah see that's something that i don't
mind paying 40 euros customs for
yeah we'll take a picture like maybe
tomorrow or so
and upload it yeah
okay let's see
scroll scroll okay we read that part and
we
read that part so next should be this
part
[Music]
wow
okay that is a big chunk of super chat
[Music]
damn
color me oh where are the colors oh
there they are
okay okay scroll scroll scroll that's
um about how many is this one chunk
it's a big chunk
560. let's go
we're too much into you oh
well no problem with that did you guys
enjoy
uh the karaoke stream did you get
brainwashed
thank you for the membership by the way
thank you
yeah it was fun it was fun
[Music]
my voice already uh feels better after
the little break
so we can go on for a while i think
senosumi
[Music]
you should have streamed more stream
sparks
don't you wish don't you wish i would
have sang sparks
there was something missing was probably
sparks
that was the last song you sang i want
to stream it on spotify
[Music]
let me check the list that i had on
stream i know it's a bit
uh when there's so many songs 22 songs
is a lot
pretty hard to remember which song
i sang at what time but there was a list
on on the screen
on the left side that was listed listing
up what i was singing
so if you look at that you should be
able to figure out what the last song
was i don't quite remember
okay well let's get started with some
super chat so i
apparently
need to start reading here i hope it's
correct but
we can only find out by reading
orange crash 980 dancing clclc
[Music]
kitty
um text wrapping wrap there we go
perfect
oh by the way i i showed this uh i gave
this
this script thingy the excel thingy
to my other members everyone was seemed
very
grateful about it very helpful
very easy to use too
[Music]
yeah so whenever someone has a big
stream again with lots of super chats
there and then this might come in handy
or
if they just on are sick of using that
youtube
uh super chat review vinda window
because you can't
see what colors uh the super chats are
in that window so using the excel
sheet now that we have it
could honestly be could be a standard
procedure maybe for me now maybe i'll
use it every time now
it's so much easier so much
so much simpler
okay so i'm in lyric with the pinky
thank you thank you soon happy birthday
kiara you deserve to celebrate
and have fun every day not just today
mm-hmm
well if you think about it every day is
a birthday
rick astley thanks for the membership
bring your
renewal wishing you all the love and the
support in the world thank you
so much i appreciate it
every day should be a celebration that
would be nice
thank you thank you vanilla thunda for
the red super chat
hey can we get my cats here
let me get my keto katos
[Music]
oh
ah
[Music]
now
cute babies oh babies
dumb cats so
happy birthday nintendo thank you for
all the fun memories you gave us so far
here's hoping you have a very special
day and a wonderful year ahead
for thank kind words yeah oh
the past few months have been very very
busy i wonder how the
rest of the year is going to play out
and i guess
the whole following year until the next
birthday
hope we can accomplish a lot of things
together that would be nice
and i hope you will be part of that
journey vanilla thunda thank you
alita thank you also for the red super
chat
[Music]
happy birthday tanjo heart heart heart
height
thank you so much thank you
that's all your message says but i
appreciate it thank you very much for
being there
gobbly dunkishin spider thank you for
the red super chat
it says dancho is now eternal plus one
years old it feels like it was just
yesterday that she was learning how to
play minecraft they grew up so fast
oh yeah for everyone who hasn't seen
um
i played minecraft for the first time in
my life on stream
soon after my debut if you haven't seen
it it's it's quite
it was quite funny so
you should maybe catch up on that if you
haven't um
i know
yeah i was so scared of everything i was
panicking so much
i remember i remember being so scared
every time like my tools were breaking
very shook very very easily easy to
startle
thank you spider thank you for watching
me throughout all of these
streams and months
yeah jumpscares mary pippin sankishan
thank you
akker thank you for the red superchat a
big one thank you
thank you are you here i wonder
it says happy birthday i wish you have a
wonderful year more and more happiest
and comfortable glory to care for
thank you thank you so
much i hope you have a wonderful year to
occur
and hopefully filled with lots of whole
life watching
thank you i wish you the best and thank
you for supporting me
very kind of you
[Music]
sense
lord pimple thank you for the red super
chat nothing written here is that
correct
lord pimple all right you'll just get a
kiss done
now thank you lord bimbo
i hope you liked the birthday stream and
the celebrations
and the new song and everything i
appreciate your support
alex thank you also for a red super chat
another fake australian there huh happy
birthday kiara it says thank you
thank you very much for the kind
kind support
hopefully on to many many more dirt days
in the future
thank you alex please stay a part of kfp
we love you thank you carpet absurdum
thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday boss i'm new to gang but
wanted to let you know that
your bright and sunny personality has
truly impacted
so many people around the world
including me hope today is everything
you wished for and let's celebrate again
for many years to come
cheers thank you
thank you very very very much it's very
sweet you're new to the yang huh
a new a new egg a new chick
that's cool that way still growing is a
good thing of course you know i
appreciate all the
the old timers they have been here for a
long time but i also
don't want to forget about the new ones
those are very important
it would be boring if i stopped growing
that would be disappointing so thank you
very much for
joining us i hope you're having a great
time here
thank you
[Music]
ah this is one of the few currencies
that it doesn't recognize i wonder
dkk is that that danish uh
kr500
i wonder does someone know
oh thank you oh you're looking at it
already on it delivers already on it
yeah donkey kong coins
it's a pinky oh thank you so thank you
for the thinking
it says happy birthday kiara thank you
for being the greatest phoenix of all
time
thank you i mean there isn't any other
phoenix so that's that
oh did you write with your wrong account
that's that's all right that's all right
thank you
sorry viable monkey duncan
[Music]
mwah happy birth potential congress i'm
turning
uh another year over with us you
indominus
what is that what does that mean you
can't dominate me is that it
firebird your spirit and laughter is
contagious and without it it would have
been
dull and lifeless oh we can't sing the
votes just wanted to stop by and say
love you hashtag
hashtag oh thank you
that is correct basically really um
that sounds kind of unbreakable that
sounds kind of different from
from what i said
[Music]
it's not pretty much the correct meaning
don't tell me wrong things
thank you very much for the kind words
very very very sweet very flattering
very wholesome thank you
i hope i can continue to brighten up
your
life and your your everyday
life when you have a day off
when you're not working or not in school
or whatever
have fun catching the vods dhk
darkishan sophie duncan friendly
neighborhood lesbian duncan chocolate
insomniac thank you for the red zipper
happy birthday divine and exquisite
phoenix that's me
we care if we can see how hard you work
you so you deserve all the happiness in
the world after seeing the famous clip
of you raging many months ago on mario
kart
you've become my aussie oh you mean the
one where i was talking about
bananas
[Music]
thank you for letting me be your aussie
i hope it will be uh
something you will never regret i hope
i'll never disappoint you
that's the one that pulled me down as
well really
really wow you're fired oh i haven't
said that in a while in my past mario
kart stream so i guess i kind of forgot
about that
next time you all are fired um
just wait for it
[Music]
otherwise you guys just do whatever the
hell you want
thank you chocolate insomniac thank you
peter drew duncan plus good
thank you for a red super chat happy
birthday your wonderful bright and warm
phoenix may your light and love be
failed by many for as long as can
be beared have a wonderful day canada
thank you
i appreciate that i had a wonderful day
indeed
i hope you had one too
thank you i i hope i can
continue giving you all the love and
light thank you for being part of kfb
plus good please please keep on watching
my streams
i said volcano
you were fine too many people so now you
just throw them into the usual room
yeah i guess yeah new tactics new
strategy
it still doesn't work so well though
there's people who come out and they
continue their stupid behavior
i don't know how to control them
yeah patrick chen thank you for the
pinkie
happy birthday phil kiara i have never
been so excited to celebrate a birthday
than i am today
really you bring us so much joy that you
can't blame us for showering you with
love i hope today is a day that you will
remember for all eternity much love
yeah showering me with love is really
the best way to put it
thank you so much
thank you it is uh quite the memorable
day yeah hey i wish it could have
lasted longer i felt like a short
very short birthday like i got
caught up early almost thank you though
for being there on that special day with
me
lingo's
all these difficult names right so free
thank you for the pinky
uh happy birthday tantra though might be
hiding under the counter
i'm just a bit scared of the big influx
of
influx of customers asking for fried
chicken
no don't be scared they they weren't
asking
they were just celebrating with me they
didn't come to order so much don't worry
don't worry they're not gonna use up all
of your stocks
of food oh i know it can be very scary
for a small chicken
oh i should have warned you guys as you
guys should have known though
yeah i know what it means i don't know
thank you ryzen don't worry it's all
over now you can come out of the counter
now
they're gone really trust me
tell me bones thank you for the red
super chat
you didn't have to write all of that i
wanted to say that i hope
you get all the happiness you deserve on
such a special day and i
think whole life isn't just the place
you belong but the place you're needed
most
you're in need at most does that mean
does it you mean that you're implying
that i was needed
in her life it just wouldn't be the same
without you i guess that's what it means
thank you happy birthday thank you
um i wonder i hope i hope i can bring
some
um something good to the table in whole
life
i just i don't want to just be
replaceable you know
but i think i think i have done well
in that aspect
kind of
you're irreplaceable
thank you tony bones very very very
sweet very wholesome
i appreciate i appreciate your kind
words thank you
so much sophie tully thank you for the
pinky
gum i just realized you're the gum under
the table
why would you give yourself that title
how do you guys even come up with these
weird ideas sometimes
i love it though happy birthday so thank
you
again thank you so much
i hope you are having an amazing day
today i have uh
school don't forget on the side though
today is my birthday as well
no i'm so late
i'm so late unless you you looked into
the future and knew that i was reading
your super chat today and your birthday
is actually today but i guess not so you
pro
probably had birthday on the same day as
me oh
happy late birthday
oh there you are oh man
i've i've seen it so late goddammit
happy birthday
happy belated birthday to you
happy birthday birthday to you happy
birthday birthday
happy birthday birthday to you
yeah but that's cool that you have the
same birthday that's always funny
thank you next year
next year i'll hopefully be able to
congratulate you
at the same time when it's actually your
birthday
but don't be mad if i can't it's just
too much going on on birthdays
kate hoshimiya thank you and jenny lim
thank you
too thai tea with the sub account
well thank you for the big big red super
chat
what what comes after quadruple
quadruples four times right what's five
times
triple quadruple what's five dance
queen double quintuple quintiple
quantable
why was i saying queen tuple quintuple
quintable
[Music]
overwhelming support thank you so much
tai chi you're amazing i appreciate it
said it right the first time i had it
the first time
how did i say it quintuple
crank up clean up that sounds so weird
though
alfredo jill dankeshen florian arnold
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
kiara thank you so much
donna catboy's talkation tara thank you
another good username duncan
pudding channel thanks and kill yooka or
kill joker
thank you for the red super chat
it says i wanted to show appreciation
for all the hard work and entertainment
you have provided and the joy i get from
watching your growth
from beginning to now i love how
compassionate and caring you are
for everyone in her life and your fans i
am excited for your future
thank you that is very sweet
i do i do definitely care a lot about
my fans i i probably
like you know i i feel like it would be
cool
to be like a typical celebrity who
doesn't really
reply much to tweets from my fans and
who doesn't
read all of these messages and all that
you know that king can't give a book
it can't give up a cool vibe and all
that but
i do want you guys to know that i care
about you that's why i just can't help
it but
spend hours and hours every day on
twitter
and other places replying to you and
reading your thoughts and all that
whether you'll be at dokomi and
dusseldorf i am one of the
official guests yes yes please come see
me
i'll only be there on one day though
yeah thank you kill joker i hope i hope
that
um my love and all that reaches you
well and thank you for looking forward
to my future
please stay in kfp i i wonder what
the future will bring but i think it
will be exciting thank you so much for
being there
i might be there in this love as well
for real
i'm excited i live near this stuff
really that's so cool are you gonna come
to doko me
i hope so i wanna see you guys
i'm a bit worried that no one will come
to my meet and greet
because it's as i mentioned it's gonna
be
i mentioned in the members only stream
unfortunately it's gonna be quite the
expensive thing
depending on something you either have
to pay nothing or you have to pay a lot
for it
i wonder when they're gonna come out
with the details but
oopsie what did i do
a weird system i know
i know a lot of you are not from europe
so i know it's tough
you know damn but but but one day one
day
i'll come to a convention close to you
hopefully not only online
[Music]
guys you know we got permission for
today
we got permission for this uh
boardgamearena.com
website which has
351 board games on it that you can play
for free apparently
and i don't know
i barely know any of those board games
but they do have a version of uno on
there
which is called solo
and uh i'm going sola la la la
[Music]
this one can be played with up with up
to 10 people
which means we could have a full round
a full table of una we don't have to
leave
one person behind now i don't know
though does anyone know this website
like
when you click play online is it
possible to make a room or does it
immediately mix you with randos
is there an option to to
like play with a
certain people does anyone know
boardgamearena.com you can make a room
one person's uh okay okay people say two
people saying
you can make a room oh
you can make a roman okay we're friends
only now cool
all right guys you know you know what's
gonna happen
i gotta test it out though what the uno
collab is five thousand views away from
one million holy
that was such a
such a interesting collaboration
such a funny collab
you
[Music]
foreign
foreign do you have any tips or tricks
on learning how to sing
i've been singing my past time but i'm
at a point where i don't get better
uh
well you might not just you might just
not be noticing it yourself
um but i guess there's like all kinds of
on youtube there's like
uh singing lessons like vocal training
videos as well i i once
used a few of those to to do vocal warm
up
before it goes like
stuff like that
so i guess you could use something like
that for example if you can't afford
like actual sing vocal lessons
for example
um but honestly for me like even
i i did some vocal training in the past
but
um i think
i think yeah you don't
now this is controversial perhaps but i
think you don't necessarily need
proper vocal training in order to be a
good singer some people just have the
talent
some people just get good on their own
after a little bit of practice
and yeah some people are naturals
yeah um and i
think that like the vocal training that
i had
it did give me it did
help me to be able to sing
um with breath control breathing control
to be able to have like
um you know more control over my voice
while i am
moving my body at the same time so so i
had like training to
sing while moving while dancing and
stuff
um so that kind of stuff that that's
what i was trained for but
i i think yeah you can just kind of
teach
stuff like that yourself you don't
necessarily need an important
er er and expensive teacher
well good luck good luck
um
thank you for the red super chat
it says this is my first red super chat
thank you
i hope all your birthday wishes come
true i want to tell you that i love you
so much and i hope that you never leave
us oh love you mama xoxo i love you too
i will not leave you anytime soon don't
worry
you know i wanna be here as long as
possible as well
and i will do my best so that i can stay
yeah thank you very much for supporting
me like this
it is very very very much appreciated
neville
i will invest in kfp stunts
thank you pinky promise of course i made
up i'm i'm doing i'm i'll do the pinky
promise of you guys
kyle thank you for the pinky
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday boss hope you have a
wonderful year viva la patrona chiara
what does that mean
what does that mean well well in any
case
thank you i hope you have a wonderful
year too
it's so weird sometimes i still feel
like i'm in 2020
but we're already already midway through
it means boss in spanish ah i learned
something new
nice nice
i am indeed your boss
then never forget that don't make that
mistake
time doesn't wait for anyone deep stuff
deep deep yeah
it's always that same thing like by the
time that you
get used to the fact that it's a certain
year
that's all usually always right at the
end of the year and then it's already in
the next year right
oh is it only for me
sometimes i was still writing the dates
2020 in me
and you're constantly writing the wrong
date again again yeah every time
at least like i don't i don't have to
write the date down that much anymore
but
back in school i did that mistake a lot
it's funny everyone understands
by the way by the way i think some of
you guys were curious because i
wrote in the pre-chat of the karaoke
stream that
i was uh up all night again because i
was
i started a new netflix show that i'm
really enjoying
want to know which one
space voice
[Music]
of michael scott
it's so good it's so funny how did i
not watch that until now it's been out
since last year
it's so funny there's only 12 episodes
i'm already at the i'm already
that's like the fifth or sixth episode
i think the sixth already god damn it
[Music]
all that in one day and i've been
holding back
i've been trying to hold back 12 episode
is just
it's just not enough
[Music]
now it's a not a movie it's a series on
netflix
would you recommend it i would
definitely recommend it it's funny
very funny
it's just ten and two teasers what the
no i'm almost done
they better bring out the news uh season
soon
[Music]
special space force
space force
never seen it may check it out go ahead
it's very funny all right continuing
she sent one the day before for the
tales of her eyes
ambassadorship as well and now one for
the birthday
what a chad
thank you this is not necessary
[Music]
spoiling me papa
me
[Music]
imagine just imagine being the the
daughter or the son
of someone so great
it is such an honor so i'm really glad i
was born
as huki papa's daughter he
big papa energy revealing kiara's back
would break the universe one day
one day i'll show you my back
[Music]
you must be proud i wonder i hope he is
i hope he is yeah
okay papa at this point we should never
see it
no you won't
believe in it
[Music]
today you know i
would i would love to show you but i
can't
anyone got close and fan art so far no
not really
but like what i've seen is uh
good stuff
what i've seen from family i i
understand how they would
think that it looks like that
[Music]
they're just forgetting some details
ah i wish i could show you you guys
gotta ask hookah papa
i can't i can't make this decision
it's a meme no
oh man
[Music]
i don't know six pack on my back
what the hell
well a tattoo of cali
no no no no no i'm not that crazy
oh thank you i really want to send you
super chat i know
you could have sent one in the in the
karaoke stream now they're turned off
unfortunately you'll have to wait a
little bit
[Music]
soon but that's very sweet you already
did oh man
thank you thank you this is so sweet but
it's not necessary
tomorrow in yakuza you can spam as many
as you want
yakuza will be a long stream hopefully
hopefully we'll be able to finish it
tomorrow i'll i'll have some snacks
or like i'll make some snacks in between
i want to bake some
bread in between and eat it fresh when
it's still warm
[Music]
so guys uh yesterday i tweeted in
japanese about coronet stream because i
watched all i watched
her stream her morning stream and uh
so it was not no it wasn't even a
mistranslation
it was correct but that's just i know it
sounds weird it sounds so weird when you
translate it that
it would make it seem like a
mistranslation the thing that i tweeted
out
in japanese yeah right there
it's um so it's not rice it's food
food in this case in this case it will
be translated as food
and and then yeah then the thing with
the you know
t-e-t-e air air air
yeah and that basically japanese people
say that like a slang word like an
internet slang word
for um when they see food like
and you know in a situation where they
are hungry and they can't eat food
in that situation like making someone
jealous
by showing food pics that's usually when
people are like oi
oi mester yamado don't do that
yeah so i used that because uh
corona senpai was showing some japanese
breakfast food
on the screen and i was feeling like
eating that
it got jealous that i couldn't eat it
because
i mean i mean okay um japanese breakfast
probably if i wanted to make it i could
make it because it's
quite simple
that is i know it's a really weird slang
word everyone was so confused they
they everyone tweeted back at me like
the translation is so weird what's going
on
it's not right it was actually correct
it's just yeah
it doesn't get it across that well
[Music]
ah food porn
i like your name thank you for the red
super chat
oh thank you for the membership carefree
project channel
thank you for the for the support
also yeah um five says happy birthday
chiara
in the red super chat thank you
thank you for the kind kind support
rocky fan 2006
thank you for the pinky
happy birthday thank you for you did
everything
i'm so glad you thought you saw my
minecraft art on twitter ah
sorry i tried to do my best but it was
not very well next year i will do it
better than this one happy birthday
again wish you have a nice
day thank you i'm actually not sure
which one exactly you mean because there
are some minecraft arts uh every once in
a while
sorry i'm not sure but thank you
nonetheless for whatever you created for
me
thank you thank you for spending time
to make something nice for me i really
appreciate the fault
and the effort it's very sweet
very awesome i appreciate it
[Music]
i appreciate it thank you for being
there on my special special day
i hope you had some fun and partied
and celebrated together with me let's do
it again one year later
i hope you'll still be there on that day
[Music]
oh korean name i think you are here in
the chat too let me try to
translate the name
thank you
are you hearing the chat let me try to
recognize kim jong su
no you are not kim jong-soo
[Music]
where are the korean people
is
[Music]
not many here today it's a chill super
chat everything stream
thank you
oh there are here there are some here
wow uh
how do i say good morning good morning
really really is that good morning in
korean
tonight
how the hell are people awake at 5 00 am
and watching my stream
crazy
is
[Music]
too early too early way too early to be
awake or way too late to be awake both
both apply in this case
[Music]
xdgxmon oh that probably means sticky
mine
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
happy birthday thank you so much
also a little cake icon thank you i'll
eat that
itadakimasu thank you thank you for
being there
on my birthday
final flight so fancy donkey thank
you also for a red super chat
thank you so much for all the laughs and
smiles that you that you have brought to
your loyal chickens
so many more videos
motivation in this super chat thank you
ah thank you for being a loyal supporter
thank you thank you so much let's let's
go to many many
more warriors together carefully
oh thank you for being here for a long
time
flannel flags are fancy oh you are here
i love you too
i love you
i'm happy to have you here all of you
thank you for the membership
wolf and sheep's clothing
[Music]
three days thank you and so southern
lord dankeshen
[Music]
foreign
a
[Music]
wait that was a pinky by the way thank
you thank you
glenn wilson 97
[Music]
happy birthday attention we actually
share a birthday which is crazy
it was also your birthday happy late
birthday
i'm again very late to say this i
remember realizing that at your debut
i'm thinking about how far
away this day would be so happy birthday
twin
wow you watched my debut and you're
still here thank you
so much that's amazing
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
i am one
[Music]
thank you
i hope you will stay until next year as
well then
let's celebrate all our birthdays
together
[Music]
okay by the way my nose has been
constantly itching
i don't know how much longer i can take
this until i have to wash my face
[Music]
um
it's weird i have nothing on my fingers
[Music]
as far as i can tell but when i wrap my
nose
[Music]
i just
it's like an eternal fight eternal
battle against cat hairs
they fly through the air yeah they get
stuck on my nose
if only you bought something that helped
with cat hair
[Music]
i don't think such a thing exists
there are even like in my current uh
view view uh site of
view you know what i mean
yeah isn't it the same with you know
with
figurines like you don't want to put
them out of the box because they'll use
value
and all that you don't want to you don't
want to put them outside
keeping them in the box is the best way
to keep anything right
okay shikoto
[Music]
you know i feel like it's gonna be a
pain in the ass to set up that's why i
didn't do it
there's probably a lot of pain in the
ass
[Music]
that's why i stopped using my humidifier
because i have to keep on switching
out the water and the good
it's annoying how would you know if you
never opened the box
i just have a feeling for it
yeah i know it doesn't use water but i
i'm sure it uses like
filters and yeah and i don't know
[Music]
okay okay
live unboxing
okay
hello i will now open this box so
you're sure oh hello
yeah what do we have we have some uh
some explanation we don't need that
we have a plug nice
we have some cardboard eat
we have the the thing and that's it
okay
uh now there's plastic wrap so let's get
right on the plastic wrap
[Music]
uh let's see
cute it's cute but is there it
uh i guess oh it looks like there's some
classic
inside so let's open that up yeah
i was right about that the filter this
this seems to be the filter
okay let's unwrap the filter
and put it back in i guess that's
probably all i have to do
oh yep okay
okay turn that around okay
okay now
it seems actually quite easy
oh my my dear moms please
bad everyone who's making fun of me
trying to open up the plastic thingy
it holds the cable holds the cable
together
okay now
where that where does it go here
okay now where do i have a plug
uh electric socket let me go look for it
[Music]
okay i'll try to turn it on now
seems to be all i have to do
okay i turned i turned it on to a
turbo mode
okay
[Music]
doesn't really do anything honestly i
kind of doubt it
doesn't really do anything at all
[Music]
it makes noises and it's like it's like
let me actually
[Music]
read the this thing here
foreign
three in one true hepa filter improve
your indoor air quality with our new air
cleaning system
hi cat she's checking the smoothie is
checking out the thing
oh she's she's like very slowly tapping
towards it
like kind of like lowering her back
and doing a sniff snuff
very careful
he's so cute
[Music]
oh my god be careful you're gonna get
sucked in cats this is apparently
against cat hairs
she seems fine with it though
yeah she's fine okay so uh multiple
levels of cleaning include a combination
of pre-filter that traps big particles
activated carbon filter that reduces
odor
and true hypothesis that captures micro
particles
er the pre-filters filters out
abrasive substances as a defense for the
true hepa filter
the activated carbon filter removes the
large dust particles
pet dander what's that and household
odor
the true hepa felder eliminates 99.97
percent of pollutants as small as 0.3
something
or larger pollen and dust mites and
filters air pollution of
pm 2.5 a pet hair really i really wonder
if it's gonna do that though
i kind of doubt it
[Music]
i doubt it but okay i'm gonna give it a
chance
i don't think i'll actually notice a
difference
[Music]
it seems like you have to actually buy
new filters you can't really clean them
um not hold up okay
[Music]
okay i turned it on isn't that
unbelievable i did it guys
i did it i will i guess
those are at least easier to handle than
the humidifiers
i guess i'll unpack the other ones later
wow what an accomplishment
[Music]
i think i actually bought for the big
one i bought it in a set with like extra
filters
that were like on sale
i don't know what i'm gonna do with the
small ones but once it needs no filters
i'll buy new filters whatever
you read the instructions i'm so proud
[Music]
thank you
dark souls why why why why do you want
me to play dark souls
i am not the right person for that i
think
i think a bunch of the other girls where
did any other whole life english girl
play dark souls i almost feel like they
did but maybe they didn't
so proud of you angel well thank you
no maybe that's one of the games that we
don't have permission for
well then don't expect me to play it
it's not happening
okay sean that cool donkey shin typhon
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
and it's a quin quintuple
super chat thank you so much happy
birthday may this be the first of many
birthdays we share with you
i hope so too i also made an equal
donation
oh in your name to the shelter i adopted
my dog from
yo 500 to the dog shelter nice
thank you for being you may your flame
continue to burn ever bright your
singing continue to enchant us your love
continue to delight us and your
personality continue to continue to
inspire us thank you
you're amazing typhon you're amazing
good job
i think that is so great that you did
that
that's the right thing to do i'm glad
you're helping others
thank you very much i love you too
i hope those doggos in that shelter will
get a nice home
sometime and until then i think your
donation will help them to stay alive
very very very kind of you
i'm very happy to hear that
see we have great people at kfb really
great people
good good good humans good chickens
have me kathy pay me back a lot nice
awesome who
[Music]
so now thanks to this uh d love uh excel
chart
i i did see the color on yours but thank
you for still clarifying
happy et channel plus one birthday canna
i wish you all the best for every day to
be blessed
for nasty oh wait this is so this is a
rhyme for nasty pain to disappear
i hope so too for lots of moments to
cheer for vacation with hollow crew for
all wishes to come true
wow that was good that was short and
cute
thank you very much
i ah vacation with holocron would be
nice there
one day one day we'll go on a vacation
for sure hey
thank you for the well wish islamic
fellow thank you for being so sweet so
kind and so caring
i'm so happy to have people like you
here
very happy you're so sweet let me give
you
some kisses
please stay part of kfp everyone's such
a
sweetheart here make me so happy
sweet chickens i'm gonna make some nice
nice fried chickens out of you
thank you yeah yeah you are more than
just decent people
you are the sweetest
that there are
[Music]
yourself you wanna stop moving the
microphone
excuse me i never warn you before i do
that
calling also that case that's no no no
no no no no no no
[Music]
mugs
i literally candle i literally could
but i will not because i love you
[Music]
thank you flopping fellow thank you so
much
brandon maldon and then duncan no one
thank you
an electoral
[Music]
is that the one that's here right now
the one with the two the two korean
signs i'm not sure
i don't recognize them yet ah there you
are no
no that's not you i need to learn how to
read korean
that would be so helpful
zero thank you soon
[Music]
wow
we have to scroll back up i went all the
way to the bottom
there i am okay
it's all good i think brown thank you
for the pinky
happy birthday attention cheerful love
always warms our hearts let this day
warm yours more than any other thank you
and yeah it was a very very
very amazing day filled with
lots of love and lots of laughter
[Music]
hope your birthday is as much as a light
to you as you are to us
with that little german there thank you
thank you very much
hey i am glad that i am able to bring
something
to have some kind of effect in your life
with my streams
i hope it will always only be positive
thank you so much for watching my
streams and supporting me
will every part fury possibly
atomic finance love thank you luisa
aksgf2 duncan rick james thank you for
the red super chat
very special phoenix you mean the world
to me and kfb hope you realize how
special you are to the community
and we wouldn't be the same without you
keep being the ultimate boss and maybe
don't
deep fry me yet oh yeah you you don't
look ready yet you need to
fill yourself up with some more corn you
know
what do you guys even eat what do
chickens even eat
corn right you like corn don't ya
i feed you just the bestest coin in the
world
[Music]
i mean you're welcome to eat kfc burgers
and stuff too sure
[Music]
no don't eat legal legal bricks what the
hell
they eat everything do they do you
and the phoenix nuggets free supply
for the end of your life
cookies sure get some cookies
from the cookie drawer
draw what rub rare
oh everyone knows that they're there for
stepping on exactly
will we be reborn uh that is something
you will have to test
out i guess
you are not a phoenix though so
you might get reborn in something else
though
not necessarily at the spot as yourself
again but as something else
[Music]
i'm not sure though that is really hard
to prove
[Music]
me
love me
[Music]
i may recommended a game that we should
play together
because she was thinking about it and
she made a suggestion
let's go let's go i'm not going to say
what's going
not yet but i'm excited
[Music]
mm-hmm
it has been such a long time yeah it was
about time
let's go chess no no no
no chess a cup hat that game looks
really cute but it also looks extremely
stressful
[Music]
hmm yeah not since bunny man i mean at
least no one-on-one
collabs you bounce off each other so
well you think so
i guess we do i guess i guess so but
there really have not been many
collapses on it which
has no particular reason i love ahmed
there's really no reason but i hope you
can do more
i i love army she's so funny
she's so funny and so creative
i also especially liked our bump defusal
collaboration yeah
i know that we should build something on
minecraft together i feel like me and
ame
i mean is there too up there too but me
and
i feel like we're the biggest um
functional builders
like i mean you know builds like her
house and all that that was really cool
no actually never mind she built the
sheep farm and uh
the iron farm never mind i take it back
you know it's insane too
[Music]
yeah mmm true all right all right i
think
i guess it's just it's me amen
the minecraft triangle
[Music]
i should build more thumbs the thing is
still like i want my farms to be quite
organic as you can see
the only thing that i automated uh
in my farms is like the the egg
collector
underneath the chicken house
but i generally i just i don't know it
hurts me to
have that kind of stuff be so automatic
or automatic and
uh i don't want my villagers to be stuck
in a in a one block thingy
fix it no it doesn't need fixing
because i don't want any more eggs
i have more than enough i have like a
five year supply of eggs now
now i want phoenix then to
stay the way it is i don't wanna
make it and i know it might be like
easier for people to get around but well
it's not that hard there's signs there
but no one looks at the signs i put
signs there that say you know go that
way for the city center go that way for
tetsuo i'll go that way for
uh some book dudes and whatever
but i guess they're so smart small i
need bigger signs but
minecraft only has such tiny as signs
[Music]
but it's okay i eventually they'll all
figure it out
anyway back to superchats thank you
again rick james what a sweet sweet
message
thank you so much i love you
martina cortes thank you for the pinky
happy birthday yeah i hope everything
goes well not only today but every day
of your life thank you for all the loves
and good times you have given me i love
you
my english is not very good i hope you
understand your english was perfect
no problem at all there thank you i
totally understand you your feelings
have come across
thank you for watching my streams yeah
thank you for being there
and and enjoying the streams here with
everyone in the chat
thank you so much martina
[Music]
english
a pathway with a shovel what do you mean
[Music]
well william there is there are paths in
phoenixton
already you mean more obvious pathway
[Music]
i think the next thing i want to do is
build um
an ice ice highway in the
in the nether
[Music]
cali proof paths there are no calipers
yeah if they're gonna ignore doors and
signs they're gonna ignore paths
as well like it's just gonna blend into
everything when they look at it i
understand how
you can be very overwhelmed if you come
to phoenix then the first time i don't
get that because there's a lot of dudes
with no job as well and
they all like cuddle around in the
middle and it gets confusing i get bad
but you just have to look around a
little bit
tetsuo is generally very far apart from
everyone else so he's easy to find i
would say
i want to give more more of them a job
yeah that would be good
but hey i already at least i already
gave them i gave them names
that's something
i collected so much iron traded so much
to get all those name tags
yes you made the hole right next to the
actual door yeah that is uh
that is genius but the door
does blend in a little bit with the
wall because it's a white door
more iron traders yeah maybe maybe i
feel like free is already good but
no why not at some point
[Music]
yeah tedzil's house should be easy to
fight now because i can just say
it's under the ferris wheel because it
really is
on the the ferris wheel
[Music]
you just have to look for the ferris
wheel and ferris wheel
is something you cannot miss
decorate the shops yeah i could put like
signs
um above the
above the houses like uh or like
right in in blocks right i run
petul or so above the houses
iron or
[Music]
books uh whatever
color code ah i could
oh i could um make the roofs
in certain colors yeah
but the problem is just that because
they roam freely they're often not in
their own house
i guess they would be in their house
more often if i would put those
um work benches workplaces
inside their houses
[Music]
if i if i if i
mine one of those workplaces in order in
order to move them
if i break them will they lose their
jobs because that's going to be a
problem
will they lose their job immediately
yes no
if we already tried it with them though
okay okay okay okay
okay that's easy okay
[Music]
thank you so much thank you for watching
my stream thank you
for the support
[Music]
i hope you had fun in the birthday
stream
and hope you enjoyed spikes
soon
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday kiara i hope this day
will be amazing for you
viva la red thank you i now have colors
so
you don't necessarily have to put it
there anymore i think i'm gonna use the
the excel sheet always now but
if for a while you i guess you can
continue if you wanna that was very
helpful thank you i'm sorry if i ever
missed your
your super chats um
[Music]
good morning the people coming in
good morning sunshine
sparks is an absolute banger i am so
glad to hear that thank you very much
anyway ellis thank you for all the
support
you've been also around for a long time
thank you for staying so loyal
for still being here it means so much to
me
i am glad to to you know see those names
every once in a while
and makes me happy reassures me
thank you
[Music]
empty bottle of monsters thank you for
the red super chat
happy birthday to mama phoenix the
hardest working burp there is you give
me a reason to smile every day thank you
so very much
thank you really
i give you a reason to smile you give me
all the reasons to smile i wouldn't be
able to smile
if it wasn't for you guys but i'm glad i
can give that back to you
thank you i will continue working hard
thank you for noticing that
thank you yeah it's nice that we can
help each other
that is very nice thank you
and rocca diar sanja thank you for the
pinky
okay i just wanted to let you know how
grateful i am to you you've answered my
questions with the utmost chair and that
always makes me
really happy no problem no problem
happy birthday kiara i'm glad that i've
gotten to know you
i'm glad that you came here and found me
thank you for finding me in the first
place finding me is already
a mission on its own in between those
millions and millions
millions of youtubers
[Music]
some people even find me even though
they're not actively looking for
youtubers that's fun too
thank you thank you
[Music]
thanks for the membership welcome happy
birthday from the usual room oh no
it's just me and myself and i to tell
tantru i am not sorry
for anything that i've done but i'm
really happy to watch the birthday
stream from the usual room
yeah birthday stream is uh the only
exception
the only kind of good entertainment you
get down there
you better appreciate it
although since you don't seem to be
sorry for anything you have done i guess
you need
one more extra week down there let's add
one more week
write it down guards don't let him out
of there
yeah i don't know how long
you were supposed to be in there but
it's definitely one week longer now
congratulations that's what you get for
being so cheeky
and thank you though for the birthday
wishes
i have the elements duncan red duncan
that is a pinky
thank you happy birthday attention thank
you thanks for celebrating with me
buy another player thank you and fire
the elements down
[Music]
wait
yo
[Music]
where's the red one is there one is it
is that yes it is a rainbow
just very spaced out thank you for the
rainbow
happy birthday to attention here's a
rainbow super chat for you wish you a
wonderful birthday
thank you so much i appreciate it thank
you for the beautiful rainbow
i hope you have lots of fun watching my
streams
i hope to give you lots of content that
you will enjoy
in the future please stay a loyal
carefree employee
forever and ever and
memo
i keep on forgiving uh for forgetting if
i did give them a kiss or not i have
such a short time memory
watching your stream from miami beach
that's cool
mama thank you for the pinky happy
birthday tanjo thank you for everything
you do for us thank you
for everything you do for me
just even if it's being here in chat
that is huge for me
i have amazing memory i guess i cannot
do depends on the thing
[Music]
happy birthday to my aussie my number
one uh to my favorite and the most
cutest film
you always make every day brian and i
hope we made this the best birthday ever
i love you always thank you oh and i was
wondering when are the cats birthdays
ah
i don't think they need up and uh their
own birthdate
uh yeah let's let's just not have a
birthday for them on the stream
but thank you for caring about them
cats have birthday every day because you
know as a cat owner you have to fulfill
all of their wishes at any get any time
when cat says meow you do meow
you have to follow their orders
[Music]
every day is a celebration for a cat i'm
spoiling them every day
yeah anyway thank you bradley that is
very sweet i was so happy to hear that
it's quite flattering to hear it to be
someone's favorite
and i'm glad i can make your day
brighter
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you for all the love bradley
i still remember when you were when you
turned into whole airlines that was
funny
[Music]
i remember that very well
for that waiting room that we had until
i arrived
in australia
[Music]
yeah hashtag never forget
did you enable super jack super tags are
currently disabled because i have to go
through
a lot of them from my birthday stream
last week
but we're getting there we're getting
there i already am
at 355 i went down from 560 or so
562 that's already like 200
i already read 200.
thank
i see you in the chat too i think you
were here
yeah there you are nice
now i'm still learning but thank you
hopefully i didn't mess it up so forgive
me if it came out wrong no no
not at all thanks again for all the
smiles and loves and i hope the rest of
your day goes well
thank you thank you sweetheart
here's the kiss
are you are you trying to practice
german
or just that one phrase
i wish you the best of luck if you're
trying to learn german though that's
gonna be tough
thank you though for trying to speak to
me in my language
thank you
please keep on supporting kfb and takana
yara is a usually
night owl always a week until
6 a.m
awake until the morning and always
wake up in at at 1pm
[Music]
yeah i i can't sleep early
for esd you have a normal sleep skate i
have a healthy sleep schedule don't i
owl phoenix yeah
i'll always halo phoenix
kst yeah we call this time zone kst
kiara standard time zone
[Music]
da
thank you if you like my m2 if you buy
my voice pack
uh for my birthday there is a the voice
pack is
about me going to the zoo with you
and it's funny because i am the one
making the animal sounds
you should listen to it i think that one
is really good
i thought it was pretty adorable
youtube
[Music]
voice pack was super cute thank you
so figuring out my finances to get the
merch don't worry about it although i
don't even know
how long the sales are one month maybe
is that the normal sales time that's not
very long so
unfortunately y'all if you want to get
it you'll have to get in
in that time but i'll remind you again
before it's over
i want to get those samples i hope they
sent them to me because until the real
production starts it takes a while
like i don't want to get my own merch as
late as you guys get it
you guys probably don't get it until
like winter
so sorry about that that's really late
um i hope
i hope that that can be improved at some
point
but i i will ask to get my samples you
know the ones that yago
touched getting a signature of yago
while i'm at it
ships end november early december or did
it say so
oh yeah the slippers will help in the
cold weather i agree
never wash it
those jackal crumbles emerge
unfortunately not
yo yago must be so busy now because like
i feel like it was whole live
english who started asking yago to model
the merch
i don't think yago did that for her life
japan previously
right it started with whole live english
with with you not really i feel like
i've seen it before ina
but that might be my imagination but
anyway definitely started with all of
english
and um now
the whole of japan members are asking
him to yeah i've seen it
so i feel like from now on whenever
any whole i've remember brings out
her life marriage they're gonna all i
wanna ask
jago to model it
[Music]
and he's never gonna be free from it
he's gonna be bothered with it all the
time
that's what he did it before too
muhammad
yeah because like there's not really any
other choice
and it's pretty neat to have some actual
like to see it on an actual person it's
definitely
um makes it easier to imagine it
so yeah and honestly my apron looked so
good on him
that looks so much better than just
having it flat
on on a table on a photo he said he
likes it yeah but he's also a busy
person so
with all those birthdays and whole life
every goddamn week there is a birthday
so
sometimes there is free birthdays in one
week so jago's gonna be modeling a lot
of things
oh man he's just gonna
at one point be like i want i'm spending
so much
time for this i'm i want to make this as
my job now so
you better pay me for this and then all
he'll do every day is model birthday
merchandise
his new job it's his destiny
it's his true calling and his facial
expression was also pretty good
he looks kind of happy wearing that
stuff
[Music]
now what we gotta do is make merchandise
aimed at him wearing it like knowingly
creating specific merchandise that will
be funny if
he wears it
i don't know what that could be but
maybe a t-shirt with a bikini on it
like you know those t-shirts where it's
a naked body but with like underwear or
t
or a bikini top on it
[Music]
stuff like that
or like actual laundry as a merchandise
yes yes
we need better ideas next year
birthday merchandise let's think about
it
an idol dress candy on oh candy g string
let's go
height yeah go high height
height hank
[Music]
thank you for watching thank you for
supporting
thank you for the big big big support
and all the love you give me
logical paradox also with a red super
chat thank you
happy first and timeless birthday to you
potential
may you be blessed with a long life
without any bamboo slings
yeah hopefully no more bamboozles my
birthday gift to you is this red super
chat using
all 27 270 characters
wow honestly i could write an entire
novel but perhaps it would be the
be for the best if i didn't
i feel like you could have filled that
up nicely i feel like you were just
trying to trying to
you know fill up the characters
could have done better send me that
novel i will not
read it but i just want it anyway
thank you logical paradox are you here
now
maybe not but
thank you nonetheless maybe you're
catching up on the v.o.d
you are here hello hello big chicken
thank you for being here
[Music]
what a loyal kfb employee
honestly what an example
of a perfect employee wonderful
crab kfp's vet dankeshen
nika dafkas thank you for the pinky
happy birthday attention i hope you have
the most amazing day to celebrate i made
your very special cover of hinotoyi it's
on the birthday hashtag on twitter
i really hope you enjoy it have a great
day was that
was that on the page
did i listen to it
i'll tag him over again right now
perfect
perfect i i love how you guys are
actually here
when i'm reading your super chats that's
insane you're here for hours and hours
and hours
and you're actually there when i ask for
you guys
most of the time
wow that is amazing thank you
i am waiting i'm refreshing my twitter
right now
there it is sorry that i didn't listen
to it
trumpet cover
trumpets you should have covered heart
challenger
that one's all about trumpets
okay every costume
that's my song that's my song
why does he playing it it blended in so
well
[Music]
oh
i love your unicorn is that a microphone
stuck in your trumpet is that how you
record trumpet covers
[Applause]
i
[Music]
you're so good
sounds so good
[Music]
foreign
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
ah
[Music]
could you tell me
but not quite that good next year
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
nice
that was absolutely amazing
thank you
wow
that was really cool i love trumpets
thank you that was okay but this
is just divine
exquisite
good job one day you're going to blow me
away with the
trumpet solo right i'm waiting for it
she said the thing 10 out of 10.
thank you so much
[Music]
fire the elements oh yeah i already read
that one steve
thank you thank you for the red super
chat steve
happy birthday kiana there is a bunch
that i want to say but i can't find the
right word so
uh to say it so i'll just say thank you
for everything that you've done
oh your hard work is incredibly
inspiring and
i can't wait to see on stage one day i
hope that day will come
you know when i'll actually be like in
3d on stage doing choreography
performing my own original songs and
perhaps even with the other girls
together
something yeah that would be amazing
that is the goal i think that is the
goal that we're all
aiming for
and i think it will be worthwhile yeah
it's i feel like i feel like if it
weren't for the sea thing
it could have already happened
it probably would have already happened
um unfortunately that is just the way
things are but
if we all do our best then we can make
it happen
sometime soon let's do it
i haven't been practicing your dancing
no not really but
i am still in the middle of uh
having my my choreography is created
and um i gave feedback and i i'm getting
some corrections made because
uh i am very picky
when it comes when it comes to
choreographies i give i like to give
um creative input i don't want to just
take it
the way it comes
i wanted to um
really be something that i feel that i
vibe with yeah and that fits my
my image of it
yeah heart challenger and hinotori
choreographers would already
already be finished if i wasn't so picky
i mean i wouldn't say i'm picking them i
just it just didn't
100 percent come up to my expectations
so
uh i am i'm gonna get those changes
and then i'll learn the cardio and
practice
and goodbye singing is a completely
different story
completely different that was about the
music video
[Music]
now i'm talking about choreography for
my original songs original choreography
[Music]
you know what i hope that people will
actually try to learn that choreography
and then dance it uh as well i hope so
that would be cool
so yeah um mailman9812 doncaster
ellie smith thank you for the pinkie
happy birthday thank you
thank you ellie you uh
d um do i want to read that
u d e g e n s thank you for the red
super chat
happy birthday to the cute energetic
burp too many more years of dodging the
usual room with hot wings
you think you can dodge the usual realm
no no no no when i
want you to come to the usual room then
you will
have no choice it's not yummy
yeah but i thought in what maybe means
like it's a short
short it's telling you
you know i thought it was insulting you
so i don't want to say it out loud yeah
so anyway thank you for all the support
though
thank you
it's meant in an affectionate way i
don't want to say it anyway sorry
because it's gonna be like oh kiara was
offensive
we don't want to have that
sorry kiada is in control
i love that i love i love how that also
became a meme
kiara is in control oh my god i saw this
clip
was it from i'm not sure from who made
that clip
but i saw this cup of uh you know cali
and gouda
in minecraft and me showing up and
logging in and when i when i wrote
something in the chat it was like done
and then i wrote something again it was
like again the sound effect added to it
done
and it was like so scary it gave you
this google google vibes
and that was sashimi i thought so i was
good editing
and then at the very end you just see
like it it there's not even like any
attention put to it
but you just see me running uh past
gooda without saying a word with the
villager and the boat
silently sailing
back trying to get back into the village
[Laughter]
actually that was really difficult i was
really struggling there um
because i somehow couldn't get it over
the sand for some reason
but eventually i got it i got him back
in there i got him back and he's safe
no phoenixtonian will have to be in
danger
outside of phoenixton i will protect
them
[Music]
with my life big angry mom energy
eh what haven't went to that stream what
did they do ah
they were building like a ferris wheel
next to
phoenixton the village that i was
building that i
i'm done building kind of uh
but while they were building it
they did some damage to my village
uh mostly like like i mean callie kind
of like
just didn't know that it didn't realize
that it was my village she thought it
was a random village and therefore she
thought it was okay to damage so she
just went in there and then
when she when she went in there she let
out villagers and then she wanted to
kill the villager by putting him into
the lava
uh but then
i was actually surprised i didn't manage
to do that apparently they had struggles
and then they gave up just right in time
uh so my villager survived
and i just put him in the boat uh but
then i i logged in
and i put the wheelchair back in there
but oh by the way
someone tweeted to me that uh
uh you did you broke the elevator
yourself
uh they didn't do anything you know i'm
not mad or anything and that was totally
an accident but no um
do you you can see it in the stream
gooda at some point like it
it works in the beginning of good stream
but it doesn't work later on
you know we could have placed i think a
torch or something
and that kind of destroyed the airflow
uh in the in the one that goes down
and then additionally she also you know
you could still go down with shift but
she also closed the trap door
which was the problem for me like when i
went down the elevator i was already
like i didn't
something's weird with the airflow but i
can still go down
okay but then i arrived down there and
i just can't get out and i i started
panicking i tried
i tried opening up like with my pickaxe
by the way i wasn't streaming i was just
casual casually
trying to fix things so you don't have
footage of that unfortunately
but i was like what the and i tried
to open but
i don't know the blocks didn't react i
was trying to break the
like anything in front of me with my
diamond pickaxe but it just didn't react
so i was stuck because of the trap door
uh it wasn't so much the water flow but
the water flow was indeed broken the
airflow
um so yeah then i died and i was like
what the
did you break mine did someone break my
elevator and then that's when gura was
like uh
because she didn't even realize she
didn't even even know what she did
honestly i wouldn't have i probably
wouldn't have realized eva
that by placing one torch you destroy
everything i wouldn't have known eva i'm
not mad at her at all this is totally
fine but
she was like that's the moment when she
realized oh that must have been me
and then she just panicked and i was
like kiana you're so amazing you're
great another why did you not open the
trapdoor uh it was not possible i think
that's literally the isn't that
isn't that literally the one
functionality of trapdoors that if
you're behind them
you're trapped doesn't that make sense
the reason why they were trapdoors door
there to begin with they were never
supposed to be closed they were they
were just there
to stop the water from uh overflowing
you could put something else there too
but at the moment i only had trapdoors
so i put trapdoors there
i didn't think that you know they
someone would just
put them down and then you would be
stuck there no i wasn't able to open it
for some reason i couldn't destroy the
blocks either
because i was in the water i think when
you're in the water then you know
things are way more difficult to break
so that was an
issue it's all good though i got my
stuff back i think
i think i got all my stuff like but i
think
gooda still has something for me but i
don't care it's okay she can keep
whatever she has
it probably wasn't such a important
thing anyway
yeah what makes breaking stuff much much
much much much slower on you
i don't know i couldn't get through eh
was it diggy call me if it was ziggy
comey then i would think
if it was a named tool then i kind of
want it back
i'll get it back eventually maybe maybe
when we do end the dragon because we are
doing and the dragon
next week i think maybe yeah next week
did i lose dickie call me oh no oh no i
gotta get it back
also yeah for the minecraft stream this
week i kinda wanna like prepare
last things like i wanna um get a
ton of iron
and get a ton of diamond armor for
everyone
yeah thank you for the membership thank
you
and yeah so that whenever we die
and lose our armor uh we can still pick
up more armor and without having to go
back to phoenix then
just want to prepare everything uh
because everything else seems to be
already prepared so i'm just gonna do my
thing
with with equipment and stuff
[Music]
maybe uh maybe fire
potions could be useful could that be
useful
fire potions or nah do we not need fire
potions
arrows yeah yeah yeah i already put a
ton of uh
uh arrows a
bose i think in the community chest
no fire push not useful okay
[Music]
i wonder what else i should prepare but
yeah i'm just gonna do my part in
preparing and
if we scaffolding oh that's something we
can
snowball for the pillars ah
i mean if we have arrows and bows
i guess snowballs are not really
necessary water bucket
um
i do one of my villagers one of my
traders
sells feather fall boots right
i know one of them sells it
oh yeah lots of food yeah oh we'll just
prepare a lot of things one after
another
the the boots should be useful right
because the
ender dragon just like when when he hits
you no like i've seen
uh at some point in the end the dragon
fight you fly like really far and really
high
and that's why you get a lot of damage
and often die yeah it
hits you and then you're dead so if you
have better falling boots i wonder if
those help a lot
if they at least keep you alive
[Music]
that would be nice
or wanna bucket yeah but i think for one
of buckets you would need some skill i
think like people like me and callie
i don't know about the other girls but i
i
kelly definitely can't react so fast put
what a bucket the moment she
falls down
same with me though i can't i can't if
especially in a
stressful situation like that i will not
be able to do that so feather falling
boots will just do their thing hopefully
yeah i'll prepare lots of gear and lots
of uh
food and
yeah uh armor and weapons
and whatever we think of whatever else
we think of
no i don't i don't think we necessarily
will do it with beds
but i think we'll just do it normally
bring the carrots in and then connect to
japan's area that's the plan
[Music]
slow falling potion i wonder if i can
get that from one of my merchants
if i make more of them
thank you for the membership
um
[Music]
be certain iris will not join no iris no
no
collaborations yet and we were planning
this to do this together
for a long time so we're doing it
as five we have been preparing for it
we have been talking about it for ages
actually it turns out she doesn't have a
one month
collab band with her live english
if i understand correctly she now has a
one-month collab band with will live
japan but for
us only two weeks
[Music]
which i think i'm i think it would have
been fine if there was no collab
bandwidth whole live english at all but
that was i guess their decision
a management decision if that's how they
want to do it that's fine
i feel like it would have been fine
especially especially because management
says
oh whole live english has no generations
then then why do the collab families
well if there are no generations then
you know
this is your logic okay i i didn't come
up with this
sorry i'm roasting them but uh yeah
i still think it generally i think the
collab band in general makes sense
because you know you gotta
build up your own you know
start start getting used to streaming
build up your own
audience and uh
all that but since she's alone it has no
other member in a generation to
collaborate with it's
i i see how that can be a bit tough
but she's doing fine from what i've been
seeing
she streams at times where i can
definitely not watch live though
yeah very early for me 6 am
and so on
she's zooming through those subs too
[Music]
and they're just drinking water
you're very good for sea time zones i
hope y'all are having fun
sorry i kind of uh betrayed my sca fans
by leaving
that time zone and now now i stream at
horrible times for you but hey you got a
newcomer that
streams at your times
well you can still watch your archives
if you can't watch your life
i think there's definitely no issue with
that
i wanna watch your streams that's fine
you're welcome here anytime
[Music]
the rest of the chat
happy birthday kiara your shining warm
light in all of our lives
even if we may be chickens our love for
you as eternal as you our majesty
phoenix
are romantic thank you for being utensil
thank you for accepting me
the way i am honestly that is
that is really really special to me
a lot of people don't like me because of
the way i am but you guys
chose to support me exactly because of
who i am and
that is the biggest gift you guys could
give me thank you
makes me feel a little bit better about
myself that there are
so many people who can actually find the
liking in me
i love you guys thank you for taking me
the way i am thank you for not
having me change myself forcefully into
a robot without
feelings you know i
i even though i wish i could be a bit
more
like that a bit more not completely it's
a bit more controlled but that's not me
i cannot control myself
i just can't i said
and i regret it a lot of times
but yeah this is just the person i
am um thank you for all
all of the love and
accepting me thank you
that's why you might wanna see i love
you
[Music]
thank you when i'm looking over here i'm
looking at the chat by the way
even though it's the opposite direction
thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
i just have this feeling that one day
being so honest and being so emotional
and all that will
will bite me and my ass will backfire
yeah i see that day coming but we'll be
there too
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank
i don't know why i just said it like
that le blow
weirdo um
[Music]
your bread thank you my name is sir
rodin
thank you dad did i see you in the chat
i feel like i did
watching you grow has been an emotional
odyssey
hallmarked by the many loves and tears
you've shared with us
these beautiful inhuman moments have
been inspiration to me every day
you always push so hard for so much
surely you're the rarest bird in the
world yep i mean the phoenix is
as rare as you can get there you are
thank you you know we could have called
kfp fandom bird watchers too but uh
i guess that's that probably it feels
like it's also
already taken well thank you
for the support i i
i hope you say that watching me grow was
an emotional obviously i hope it wasn't
frustrating or anything to you i hope so
it was definitely emotional though i can
see that thank you very much
big kisses to you thank you for
being a loyal supporter always there
no matter what thank you
it's been rewarding really really
i i i i see how it can be kind of
rewarding
especially if you are here from the
beginning or like the
the beginning times
yeah that's good
um
so much love is in this chat room
sleepy pod dankeshan alter chemist thank
you
wk wong dang a crowd
carl call photograph thank you and flame
muffin thank you for the pinky
happy birthday thank you for watching
thank you for supporting me please
sangrita rockefeller 14
there's a few less reds here that's
really good i'll drink sea
thank you for the red super chat are you
here too
so far like a big percentage of the red
ones are
actually here
[Music]
you're here you are hello
thank you for being here which kid is
which uh and the
the greenish one is smoothie and the red
one
is um chunkers but that's only the
on-screen stream names they have they
have different names in reality
don't wait a second i have discord
[Music]
messages
i mean you are like the japanese
word ame you are sweet candy
when i talk to you it feels like i'm
eating sweet candy
getting a sugar overload
from your cuteness
i'm a tony shepherd's going crazy
is playing celeste is she streaming
oh she's about to stream five minutes
[Music]
she's streaming in five minutes guys is
this is it putting on celeste or celeste
ame i love you
i i i don't know i have these um these
these tingly feelings
is it love
it's a list i may stream so much like
she often does like two short streams in
one day
i i used to do that too didn't i i tried
a lot to
have like two streams in one day back in
the day
now i'm too old for that
oh yeah anyway uh happy birthday to your
attention i never thought i'd find an
ocean here
you mean here as in whole life or even
know what one was but here you are ah
my birthday wish for you is for that
spirit of yours to keep burning bright
forever
here's a gift to you for being such a
precious gift to all of us
oh that was a cute flirt i was cute
i love you thank you that is very sweet
thank you i wonder how you found me
tell me dragon shell how did you find me
got yourself
tell me now that you're here i interview
you you tell me
how you find me i'll drink water
sip some water while i'm waiting
word of mouth from a friend to his way
into the stuff
rid of mouth was that expression just
someone who told you
someone told you about whole life and
then you were like looking into it but i
guess you already had some kind of
interest in like
anime and japan perhaps
that's why it spoke to you did you not
look into
her like in into youtubers at all before
that then
it's really surprising that that
actually caught your interest
i'm glad you gave me the chance
a cooking show
that's exciting right i'm a bit of a
lightweight oh
naruto hodor well well
well i am very glad that if you got
dragged down into this hole
thank you for being part of kfb
you are a important precious
member and we value you
even though i will eat you one day but i
still value you yeah
food must be valued
[Music]
straight
lazy inquisitor thank you for the pinky
[Music]
happy birthday my queen
may you reign over us for eternity
you know you said queen
now and then you ask for me to reign
over you for eternity the only reason
why i am able to reign over you for
eternities because i'm in phoenix and
not a
so i hope that gets into your brain now
thank you i love you
tapioca xyx
hello dancing this
[Music]
happy birthday to you i want to tell you
the true meaning of
is you grow one year old okay is the
joke i hope you're always loved and
healthy
thank you yeah someone already told me
about that
and i read it out loud and then everyone
laughed at me
thank you thank you for supporting me
and watching my streams i hope
i hope people watch them forever and
ever another
i i need you i need you to work for ksp
and stay here meet my loyal employee
chickens thank you very much nini
alex
[Music]
thank you scott king thank you
thank
[Music]
very interesting donates an rub
then write something in a german dialect
and then something in japanese but the
name
von peterhof sounds very german so this
is all very mixed up but
thank you oh there you are and it's
babish
you are here in the chat everyone's in
the chat all these super chatters are
here that's so cool we can have an
actual conversation oh
my comfort stream oh thank you
i need to know
mister von peterhoff help me
big love from canada thank you
[Music]
ah ferguland that does sound like that
makes sense yeah
i hear the similarity thank you very
much for the support
thank you soon thank you soon
i hope i hope you will enjoy my streams
i hope i can give you some happiness and
some entertainment every day
please come to my streams whenever you
need some some
happiness some excitement some laughs
hopefully
[Music]
whether you're laughing with me or at me
both is very possible in my streams
thank you friends crew thank you
for red super chat dear tanjo you've
become the surgeon of my day
my every single second with you has been
worthwhile
and i wish you a happy birthday head to
my place in phoenix thank you
that is great to hear that's
literally what i was just talking about
i am glad that
you are enjoying your time with me
thank you so much i hope that this will
never fade away
whenever you're lonely i hope i can be
there for you
thank you for supporting me johnny
two zero two three thank you thank you
for the pinkie obrigada
i'm not very good with words so i'll
keep it simple i hope you have
another wonderful year full full of love
happiness and joy
yay thank you i hope so too
and i hope the same for you as well
and william gates thank you
[Music]
nice name you mixed everything in there
very supportive
and thank you for the red super chat
first principle
happy birthday thank you thank you for
broadening up our days
thank you thank you very much
thank you thank you i am glad i can do
that i'm not doing it
uh on purpose not doing it
consciously but i'm glad it's it's it's
happening
thank you thank you for celebrating with
me and spending your precious time with
me
niko dankeshun nick hood hood
thank you jason thank you also for red
super chat
and happy birthday mama thank you for
continuously brightening our lives
you're a majestic phoenix and we love
you so much keep growing
and burn ever so brightly we will always
support you viva
thank you
i hope i hope i can be
[Music]
a source of entertainment for you
forever as you say
thank you for being here and watching my
streams jason
hopefully one day you'll lose that
trainee uh
title and become a full-fledged
chicken
[Music]
chicken excuse me i am not the chicken
you guys are the chickens not me
not me
thank you for the red super chat you've
also been around for a long time thank
you so much
happy birthday to you tanjo i love you i
love you too
drawing is too slow so super chat first
love you love love love i'm looking
forward to the drawing i wonder if i
already saw it
there's been a lot of fan art each day
and i really appreciate it it's really
great to see what you guys create for me
you all are very very creative and
talented
and it's nice to see what you guys make
thank you please keep on creating thank
you so much
little slillies dankeshin dong dankeshon
a feral dream duncan bad boy creeper
[Music]
ah it's that clay dude again
small brain thank you for the red super
chat
happy birthday kiara thank you
i'll jump to you that's you in the chat
ah
i need to remember that yeah i read your
super chat
thank you but you don't have permission
to leave yet
you better stay but i'm not gonna do
much longer
uh will i also read the birthday
collapse of
no probably not getting there but i'm
already down to 276
and we started out with 560
almost 300 red smoke
thank you for the birthday my message
thank you so much
thank you for the membership welcome
i'm saying so thank you and lyrical
jesus duncan thank you for the red super
chat
happy birthday boss here's my birthday
tithe
what's that get yourself something nice
on us thank you
i actually didn't get myself anything
nice for the for the birthday
[Music]
like nothing specifically i mean i
ordered something
uh in general from amazon a few days
later but nothing
that was supposed to be a birthday
present
tiff a tif is a payment ah
you guys already treat me every day like
i don't know i don't know
what i need but i want to eat cake
i said i still didn't do that
ah ah money given to the church i
see i see i see you i said we're not a
cult
ah wait that makes sense because his
name is lyrical jesus
oh the connections thank
happy birthday on behalf of your
filipino fans oh thank you td
thanks mate i appreciate that
777 volatile it's a mystery duncan morph
ball
thank you for the pink super chat
from korea
uh happy birthday and thank you so much
kiara i could hit over 100 likes on my
twitter's artwork for the first time
oh unless you clicked like on my artwork
it would never have happened ah
i will keep practicing and drawing and
make more better artworks for you oh
thank you i'm looking forward to it
oh yes lyrical jesus i just read your
name you literally just missed it that's
funny
sorry just remember the time stamp and
morph ball comes anita i'm very happy
that you feel motivated to draw i hope
you will continue drawing
i am looking forward to whatever you
create
please draw takana in many different
situations
and many different outfits
and i think it will be interesting to
see
what kind of progress you make and how
you get better
and evolve thank you stefan stephen
thank you
j slug thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday attention thank you
very much thank you for being there on
that important day
it means a lot to me really thank you
eternal dive part
part 2
[Music]
in hungary
thank you happy birthday good luck
reading this six hours into a 12 hour
super chat reading
by the way how's your neck you know what
that's actually pretty accurate
how long was the last one three four
hours now we had three hours
this is pretty accurate
[Music]
i was right you oh my god
how the hell did you like guess that
oh my god five hours almost
eh really the last one was for almost
five hours
yeah i've been taking my time with that
one but we're a bit over six hours
oh well this one is more i think we've
read more
in a shorter time in this stream
[Music]
thank you good job on those calculations
you math genius
a little bit off though anna thank you
also for
being super chat happy birthday kiara
i'm watching you stream at work so i
can't watch all of it live but i hope
you have an amazing birthday
thank you for thinking of me on your
busy day of work thank you
see i i think that all of your time is
very precious
and you guys choose to spend it with me
even when i'm doing ridiculously long
hours of super chat reading
and still you guys are here and that
means a lot to me thank you
pat square thank you
thank you soon
king naruto the tyrant
[Music]
amar thank you for the pinky happy
birthday kiara you have been a shining
light of positivity for everyone since
your debuts
are your openness and genuineness is
refreshing and beautiful and part of the
many reasons you are my oshi
phoenix thank you
[Music]
again i've been called oshi
it's my favorite word now
thank you so much i love you
gohan pan thank you for the red super
chat
um happy birthday wishing you always
happy
as long as you are here i am always
thank you wiki tunes also with a red
super chat thank you
wiki tools are you here in the chat
number one wait why is this title number
one
i never would have thought the day i
first super chat kaito i'd be stuck down
a firebird hole i could never escape
from ah you are here
what i thought would be a simple run
turned out to be so welcoming
i had no choice but to stink
oh you thought you could just
send a little super chat and then
disappear forever no no no i guess
that's not how it happens
that's not how it works i guess
[Music]
simple one i like that word
thank you for staying does this mean
that there is more oh yeah this is a
rainbow i just saw
when i scrolled up a little bit it seems
to be a rainbow
and i'll look forward to the rest of the
messages then
psycho fire thank you for red super chat
thank you for the wonderful streams mama
birth thank you for watching them
what i admire most about you is being
headstrong even in the face of youtube
travels yeah youtube
thank you for being on phoenix oshie the
skies belong to you kiara oh the skies
do belong to me especially
once i stop playing zelda skyward sword
let's go
[Music]
oh by the way cass makes it's your
birthday right right happy birthday
i just saw you in the chat i remembered
now sorry
thank you for being here on your
birthday
are you eating cake you better be
you better be some yummy cake
hi chokers chocolate is saying happy
birthday
who else's birthday
[Music]
i'll tell september mine is on monday
it's mine actually really
really happy birthday
[Music]
my birthday's in two days
there was somebody else earlier who
i'm a licensed fan
well if you show up again i hope i see
it
wherever you are happy birthday
this is my birthday too now i don't
believe you guys anymore
if it is then happy birthday matteo's
elves
it really is
okay um
i'm gonna enter soon very soon
i thought i could at least finish the
ones from this stream when did i end
okay okay okay um thank you again
psychofire
23. i love you thank you so much for
supporting
thank you for letting me be your number
one i hope that will never change
pinkerton is sending her uh
a rainbow at the same time as wiki tunes
is sending one but pinkerton did it way
faster than wikitools
oh i see what you did there pinkerton
that is a rickroll
in in in all in one two three
four five six languages each line being
in a different language
thank you pinkerton for the rainbow are
you here too
youtube simp noob you didn't type it out
beforehand huh
beginner noob
[Music]
a rainbow rickroll a classic
bang you know i don't mind it i like
regrow thank you i love the song
and the meaning of it you're basically
telling me you're never gonna leave me
pinkerton and i'm gonna take you by that
word it better be true
thank you back to wiki tunes who writes
your interactions with your fellow kfp
members in other whole life and they're
so heartwarming it would make anyone
want to be part of the community
that's what makes you so lovable and
special
how sweet thank you
wait i see your next message just read
that you have inspired me to look more
into life today and other types of art
projects
so once my current project is over i
would love to commit to being a bigger
part of kfb
interesting i think a lot of people
um kind of like started like
who who were people who were already
kind of creative
started doing much more once they got
into her life
and tried new friends as well that's
really cool
happy birthday thank you for all the
amazing streams so far and for the
banger hino today oh yeah
hope you have an absolutely amazing day
in future days to come
thank you i hope you you mentioned
hirotori there but that's probably where
sparks was not public yet so i hope you
enjoyed sparks as well
i hope you found a liking in it as well
even though it's very different from
hinotoni
but thank you for supporting my music
and for supporting my streams
walter jackson thank you for the pinky
happy birthday mate i hope this year is
filled with happiness and fulfillment
for you
take care of yourself and be the help of
phoenix that you are
ah thank you i will do my best but you
better stay healthy
and happy as well walter jackson
otherwise i'm not gonna be happy
thank you
talisman g1 thank you for pinky
happy birthday and congrats on being the
ambassador for the new testament right
thank you so much
i guess i'll need to move berseria out
of my backlog and finish it yeah
do it and then play tesla for rice with
me how about that
thank you i am really excited about that
that is really a dream come true
it's like a birthday present on its own
thank you and i'm glad that you are into
tales off as well let's enjoy this
journey together
sold out on 94 danger and eating
[Music]
actually oh wow that's uh oh my god
um
[Music]
sorry there's a part that he doesn't
want to want me to read out loud
i'm reading it quietly but it's quite
long
[Music]
is
of a sweater tilly
uh invested in kfp
and uh yeah hopefully he has no
filthy fearful spars with her life with
me
[Music]
thank you so much ah oh
that's cling criticism
[Music]
okay let's do a few more few more super
tattoos
[Music]
terrific mr t danger and amber man
duncan wikitoons
continuing again finally
thank you for bringing me down the whole
life hole you're amazing and deserve all
the support in the world i'll be looking
forward to the next year
and going down the bird hole even more
thank you is that the last one ah and
happy birthday to the best bird boss
around thank you
oh it goes deeper and deeper and deeper
trust me
bring some uh torches with ya
doesn't have to be torches can't be like
one of those uh ones that
work with batteries okay
thank you what he wrote that
what do you what are you kiaring me
for
a flashlight yeah that's the one i was
looking for
what nothing's your bio about that you
guys are just being
dramatic again wiki tunes thank you i'm
glad you're here please enjoy your time
lay back put your feet against the table
to repeat of you on drum
and chill i'm glad to have you thank you
so much mwah
thirsty hika thank you for the red super
chat um happy birthday hot wings
this is my first super chat ever oh and
i knew it had to go to my oc
i'm your aussie here we go again you
have been my favorite since i started
watching whole live in october
oh i look forward to continuing my
employment at kfp very
very polite i like i like me some polite
chickens
thank you very much thirsty hiker
thank you for giving your personal job
ever to me and for supporting me for
such a long time
already um
i hope you will not leave me about and i
hope i will never disappoint you
never let you down never run around and
desert you
thank you so much for letting me
entertain you
thank you thank you for the thank you
for the pinky inky thank you for the
pinky that
rhymes did you did you know that was
going to rhyme if i reach out for your
super chat out loud
and it's ruined nothing's ruined
happy birthday jenna it also just so
happens to be my birthday as well
oh happy birthday birthday you've made
us love countless times my birthday
wishes that you preserve very
preserve the rare continue being the
best you
and follow the happiness in the world
for you thank you
[Music]
i feel like i can you say continue being
the blessed me i feel like i could be a
better
version of myself for that i was i
always try to be
at least i i strive to be the best
version i will try to become better
though
thank you for supporting me um
thank you for the red super chat happy
birthday attention
almost 10 months ago i took a gander at
the fledgling phoenix
who spread her wings eagler to take
flight
i've all observed you sore through
pheasant blue skies foul rough well oh
you're really going in this time
filed for rough weather
[Music]
warbling in the dark shining brighter
than any stalling in the sky
trevor j i love you
enough the most beautiful words the
the most best beautifulest wordest
everest spokenest
yes
i love this owl oh it continues wait is
that a
no no it's not a rainbow is it just add
a little pinky okay
and the pinky i don't
well you continue oh my god you really
continue i
don't regret a moment of this
i've had so much flocking fun bird
watching never
knowing what to expect and i'll never
stop
raving over how proud i am of you and
how much you have
crowned are you even able to say the
things that you want to say when you
keep being bound to punks
i love your attention i'll be looking
forward to whatever's next oh i like
that one
that's a nice end you're the best person
the best owl ever thank you so much
you always make me laugh even though i
should be the one making you laugh it's
difficult but i try
damn what dedication
wow too powerful i found the inna out
it's so good i feel like maybe some of
these don't even
come across when i read them out loud
that's why i try to wink
i hope you guys can imagine what he's
writing there what a crazy album
don dev danke shown as arrived eight to
five donkeys
chrono crash attacking c dot c
dot cc thank you for the red super chat
happy birthday thank you for lighting up
my life hope you enjoy the day
thank you you're the ones
who light up my life without you guys it
would be so
dark thank you very much cece
[Music]
please stay part of kfb and keep on
supporting and i will do my best every
day
for you guys thank you
thank you clever name for affordance
and armored golem big luck
hilarious and super talented all the
best thank you so much
i'm sure i could say all the same things
about you
thank you so much for the support
hey that's two pinky so one red one
thank you
oh my god happy birthday you probably
don't remember since i don't super chat
very often but i've
actually been here since the second fire
emblem stream
whoa i discovered you after my favorite
podcast stopped updating because you
talked so much during your streams i
started listening to you at work instead
because you talk so much thank you for
making my work day so much more fun your
attentions are my favorite
i look forward to many more years long
winded super chat reading to come
thank you are you here alexander are you
in the chat
thank you that's funny i'm glad i was
able to replace something
to fill up a hole that was empty
something that was missing in your life
thank you
for letting me be that replacement don't
replace me though
all right thank you you are here
everyone's here got them
incredible incredible absolutely
incredible
[Music]
daisy are you here daisy
i think i need to send you to the usual
room
you know exactly what you did
you are here uh-huh you are i see you
you sent two 500
red super jets every quick
look at least they're not empty i guess
i guess i'll have to keep you up here
over the surface
because they're at least not empty oh
wait
what is what is this message
ah let me rethink okay it says uh since
this is your birthday i wanted to write
a long window
i wanted to write a long meaningful
message but what
but i'm not very good before it's when i
need to come up with something on the
spot
i've already used up most of my
characters oh no anyway where was i oh
yeah birthday messages so while trying
to
damn i'm out of space i have to send
another chat to say
next 500 super chat happy birthday
you know you see you you you you know
running out of space you could have
filled up the second one
you could have easily filled up the
second one just be honest you had
nothing to say to begin with besides
happy birthday
oh man how many letters is happy proof
to have one
hug
ah i guess more than ten you could have
sent one one
100 super chat for each letter and
written
h 100 a 100 p
100 and so on you know what i mean but
unfortunately has more than
one in ten letters so that doesn't fit
so well
that way you could have trolled me even
more
but you already controlled me well
enough you truly truly daisy
always trolling unbelievable daisy
oh well you next time huh next year
it's never here to troll me
well i want to send you to the
usual room i want to
i have to it's bad behavior we cannot
let the chickens know that this is
acceptable
uh one month for you
[Laughter]
one month the problem is i don't really
take
uh uh keep track of um everything so
tell me when you're out
and then apologize i hope you learned
something this time
you never seem to learn but thank you
for the insane support
absolutely crazy i hope that
my content gives you happiness each
day
because otherwise i don't know how i
deserve that
uh crazy amount
i i hope you laugh your ass off every
day
so much that with each stream i do i
lengthen
your lifespan for one day
if that is not the case then i don't
deserve this but i hope i hope this
is the case thank you so much
they're laughing now for sure well yeah
hopefully you might we'll see
you have you heard i love you
[Music]
it's so nice to be someone's favorite
i wa i always wanted to be someone's
favorite
[Music]
i just wanted to be someone's favorite
don't have to be everyone's favorite
just someone's favorite
thank you
[Music]
honestly all of you
you gave me a place to be guys
i'm so far with the super jets hmm but i
need to kind of
get going because like i need
you know you know me i need to watch
free episodes so
five episodes and netflix
thanks for the membership it gave us a
place to be too i'm happy
to hear that
[Music]
but you know what i have to do and i'll
do it on stream now
because i'm scared like because i i'm
i'm i suck at catching up it seems
let me just uh
save what i still haven't read
let's see how far we go i hope i i mean
it should be fine
after the birthday i really didn't
get like crazy amounts so it should be
fine let me scroll
we we read the super chats from the
members only right
and then is there anything else i read
no is there anything else i read besides
you know the ones that i'm reading now
oh only the members only no well i'm
oh god about the ones from today i'm not
reading right so that's that
okay here we have whole talk minecraft
[Music]
still scrolling still loading birthday
collab
okay but did i save the birthday collab
once
no i didn't okay well they better be all
available then uh birthday collab
scrolling scrolling scrolling
birthday collabs crawling swirling
scrolling i'm just
i don't want to lose them because no
matter how long it takes i just
i'll catch up eventually i just don't
want to lose them okay sparks
okay okay they're all there they're all
there no problem okay let me just save
these
um
okay saving
okay let's put those
okay okay there they are
perfect saved them all there is no risk
of losing them now but
i hope that uh
no not yet not yet over i still have uh
how many i wonder let me see
i read until
uh that's one dagger
and simply thank you thank you soon
okay let's say simply single
[Music]
okay here is simply cinco
so let's do some basic math
um okay
from that part it's uh
wait
okay 186
plus 186
plus
uh
[Music]
a plus eight
plus
plus 32
plus 54 plus
oh plus six
calculator
uh oh 286
that's really not much that is not much
and then and then we read sparks
super chats and collaboration
birthday collaborations of with chance
and super chat reading super chats
and minecraft super chats and whole talk
super chats
and uh
yeah oh yeah
[Music]
and sparks two hour endurance super
chance
oh that that adds uh
that adds
[Music]
320 plus
no wait no no no i counted in the sparks
ones accidentally
oh thank god i said i'm not reading
those
wait wait wait wait wait never mind that
number ignore that number
oh super chat reading
[Music]
is 200 wow
but not so many red ones we can go for
those much quicker the birthday ones
just had
an insane amount of red ones and pinkies
and then whole talk and minecraft
combined with birthday collab
and sparks music video are 389.
what was the other number i just said
plus that
if so that makes 589
or something like that wow
no no regrets we'll get through there
eventually
[Music]
i just have a bad feeling about tomorrow
because after
we'll probably be playing yakuza for
a long time and i'll be too exhausted to
read super chats after that
so they'll pile up again
and but let's see
i could probably read them after um
minecraft and after knockout city collab
and have the sims fall we'll just part
them
we'll just part them separate them
nicely
[Music]
we'll get through there at some point
and then next week on
ah no monday i'm not there but we can
put in another super chat reading
next week and a stream that is only
super chat winning
we'll be fine we'll get through it it
just will be all very
delayed not as delayed as me getting my
fan letters though
[Music]
okay i will
snack on something because i'm a bit
hungry again
and then watch the rest of that netflix
show i'm into right now
i still haven't finished watching the
hand myself by the way i never watched
the final episode
of the most recent season because i just
never felt like
uh watching something depressing
i i just felt like i wasn't ready for it
yeah even though i loved that show so
much i just didn't want to watch
first of all just the fact that it's the
last episode of something just means
that i can't watch it for a long time
after that so i'm trying to keep off on
it
and also generally recently i just
wanted something more
cheerful so i've been re-watching scrubs
and
and but i'm almost done with that too
again
i've i've it's not depressing the last
episode is not really
but still i don't know i don't know i
just don't want it to end though like it
will take at least another year at least
another year until they
get another season out
you know find new shows well that's
right but
there again see you when it's a new show
it's just immediately you immediately
done with it 12 episodes or 10 episodes
is nothing you finished that in a day
[Music]
yeah i'm just rewatching it i just
recently rewatched arrested development
i recently re-watched the office i
recently rewatched
uh friends i recently rewatched how i
met your mother i recently rewatched
everything everything
help me get more hobbies
no i'm doing that to chill that's my
hobby
malcolm oh actually i've been trying to
rewatch that i guess i could get back
into it it's kind of stupid
bit bit too childish but it's still fun
it gives me nostalgic feelings
i know breaking bad kind of doesn't
speak to me the good place i
watched that already i liked it um
atypical oh i haven't watched that one
parks and rec i recently rewatched that
people keep on mentioning brooklyn 99 i
guess i have to watch brooklyn 99 broke
girls no
i tried watching that but i cannot stand
that show
it's horrible sorry umbrella academy
i've watched it but i'm looking for
something more
like comedy comedic
at the moment
i'm not gonna watch icarly no
over my dead body which will never
happen because my body is never dead for
very long
but also the good thing is at the moment
i can uh sometimes instead of watching
netflix i'm playing i'm playing
tears of hearts r on my on my
on my on my ps vita
i rarely play games off screen but this
is a good opportunity because often
even if i wanted to play games off
stream most of the time it's games where
i'm like but i kind of also want to
stream
that game so i don't play it upstream
but
tales of hearts was a good choice
because i don't i don't feel like i want
to play that one on
stream it would be a pain in the ass
anyway to stream ps vita like how the
am i supposed to do that without a
pstv thingy yeah
rewatch monogatari
no no
yeah anyway so i've been enjoying that
because like i can do that like
without talking to an audience and
that's fun too to be able to quietly
play a game for once
uh and it's a tails off game that i
didn't play yet so
maybe after i'm done with pairs of
hearts are i'm gonna
tackle one more that i didn't play yet
and that way i can overcome some time
where there is no good shows that i
haven't already watched big bang theory
of course i've already watched that also
fairly recently
oh thank you for recommending me
takaneshi kiara
nichijou i love nietzsche's one of my
favorite animes
okay when you say go do something else i
will send you to the usual room
[Music]
because you're not getting this
conversation
you don't understand i already turned on
your freaking air pure fire will you
never be happy
[Music]
you'll never be happy you'll never be
satisfied
anyway thank you guys once again for
uh spending your time with me there was
not many tangents
huh oh i'm absolute
you guys come here for detentions and i
barely give any to you okay let me see
um uh
uh at in in greece at the beach
me and my roommate we were panicking for
a little while
because we were hearing this sound we
were like um
we were on this island and
we were on this island where there's
like
uh only nature and on a tiny island
there was
there was only an atom we went there
with a boat and uh
we were chilling there but because there
was no nature there was like
no like sun umbrellas and like we
had some umbrellas we rented them but
they were crap
so we tried to find shadow under
under some trees there were not many
trees
but so we tried to make like a kind of a
fort under some trees
[Music]
it was really all nature it was pretty
cool but
because of that we got kind of
suspicious when we were
when we were under that tree chilling
and
started hearing a noise
[Music]
a really loud buzzing noise
and it sounded to us because we were in
the middle of the nature
under some trees we thought it was a
swarm of
bees because it sounded like a million
bees and we were lost we started looking
around like huh
where's that coming from we got up from
our towels
we still couldn't find anything but we
got really suspicious and cautious and
scared and anxious
and then turns out it was a
drone
turns out it was just a drone
i thought that we were about to get
killed by a swarm of bees
it was just a stupid small tiny ass
drone which was flying around above us
the whole time and we couldn't see it
most of the time like
i think i never saw it yeah but it was a
drone
so that was uh irritating we got so
nervous that was like five minutes of
pure anxiousness
anxiety yeah
yeah yeah also at the hospital
here i have i have this memo with random
tangents to tell you guys
but most of these are already talked
about uh at the hospital
tangent number two at the hospital when
i was there for my neck
remember when i was chilling there
this is really random but i write down
even the smallest things
four times when i'm desperate and there
was this little girl
and she was there with her papa and her
mama
and uh she went in
and then she she when she went she went
in she seemed kind of scared
a little bit but then she came out with
a
with a brace on her arm and
and then and then her papa were like
it was so cute like they were trying to
influence her in a way to make her think
that that's cool
they were like oh wow that's so cool you
got that brace now well
you live such a dangerous life know that
wow wow
and then she was like she she bought it
and she was actually like
yeah it's so cool isn't it
i'm so proud of it it was a really cute
situation okay i just wanted to tell you
that
it was right in front of me and it was
really adorable and i thought that was
cute goddammit
i also want that i mean the
the thing on my arm i want to break my
arm and then get a brace on there oh
is that you even call it a brace am i
using the correct word
i want to be cool too and they were like
yeah i can get all my friends to ride on
it
a cast that's what i meant yeah
i didn't get a cast on my neck
either
i mean that would have been pretty
difficult to stream in but still
yeah also one more thing last last
tangent of the day you know what i hate
you know what's a pet peeve of mine
in tv shows
you know how sometimes in tv shows like
uh the characters the people
they try to they wanna they need to call
their parents or whatever
over skype or some different
some similar and it always
makes me angry because
both them and their parents have like a
tv quality super hd webcam
that is perfectly lit up with perfect
studio lighting
it's just all so high quality
and it makes me so mad i mean okay
maybe the child maybe the the adult
child has that
okay a good qual but even
it doesn't even make sense because they
show that they're using a laptop
where there isn't even a webcam mounted
on it they're implying that they're
using a built-in
webcam a built-in laptop webcam
and we all know that laptops
built-in webcams are the most useless
webcams that exist like it doesn't even
make sense why they're building it in
there
because no one's gonna use it it has
such a freaking
bad quality that you would think it's
from a million years ago
or that someone is calling you from
underwater or from
space for moon or whatever even in the
moon even in the space they have better
quality according to space force but i
don't know about that
okay it just annoys me
it's it's so unrealistic that the
parents who are
like most of the times they're like
definitely not tax
tech savvy tech savvy tech savvy
and you notice that because often the
those parents are portrayed as
like that way and they show it by being
like not on camera sometimes
and they're like oh oh this is the wrong
side oh which which is the correct side
why do i have to look where's the camera
okay okay okay you're telling me that
you don't understand how all of this
works
would you have this super
high-tech
camera built in into your
laptop somehow and have the perfect
studio
lighting in your room and the perfect
inter internet connection no pixels
whatsoever
60 fps tell me where to get that laptop
with that built
in uh laptop camera i
i need it i need it i need i need to
know where to buy
it it's just a ring light
what
every time i see that that bothers me
does that not does that
thought never crashed your guy's mind
does it not the other thing
this is kind of connected the other
thing in tv shows that bothers me as a
pet peeve of me
is when there's food on their
plates
and they have conversations and they
just poke their food
and never eat it and often leave their
food
without eating even one bite end the
conversation and leave the room
they never eat their food
they never eat their goddamn food
and it bothers me so much that i pay so
much attention to it like
every time they cut to the other
person's angle to their face
when they have a line they want to make
it look like they just ate
because they take uh they no but it's
like it's like they they poke their food
and then they're about they're about to
about to put the
fork to their mouth but that's oh that's
when they have to speak their line so
they put it back on the ground
and they keep them poking poking poking
while they're talking talking talking
donkey talking
and then that's it
it's just they never eat their food
they never eat their food it's
such a waste
it's so unbelievable like are you never
hungry why are you not hungry
i am not hungry
[Laughter]
eat your goddamn food i mean i can
imagine that you know because they're
recording scenes there and and probably
have to do a lot of retakes
the food is probably cold
but come on often it's just like
sandwiches
like blt sandwiches they often have blt
sanders or whatever
you could eat that eat it for the sake
of acting aren't you trying to make it
realistic
i will not believe you for a minute if
you use a high-tech
webcam or if you uh not eat your food
and just keep on poking around in it
you're not even you're not you you're
probably
unconsciously influencing young children
who are
watching your series your tv show
and making them into picky eaters like
me
this is probably the reason why i'm such
a picky eater because you see them not
eating their food and just poking around
with it
you know they could be some stop cr
subconsciously
brainwashed and that is why a lot of
children don't eat their food
and in germany
[Music]
the last episode what will the last
character weapon be that i'll use so
damn
hard to choose bye-bye
[Music]
awesome
bye