oh
[Applause]
[Music]
pap
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
k
k oh it's
[Music]
loud K it licky was that fast no it's
already been 5 minutes loading actually
six maybe no
five hello
[Music]
W whoo
wo is a little fan game that we're going
to play today isn't that exciting you
know I can make my own ad bigger because
the game doesn't take up so much
space wow wow wow advertisement
[Music]
how big can we make it very big oh maybe
this this
big I mean I could even move this whole
game more to the left side but no this
is okay whoa whoa whoa we have the
perfect
emote
nice it's yub yuie
time you paid for YouTube premium what
is this chicken
you should know you should know this is
how we
do sorry I'm picking off the cat hair of
my
[Music]
microphone
um
hello this game is old as
[\h__\h] what are you talking
about I mean
it what what do you mean
what it came out recently but I guess
it's a
remake yeah came out recently at least
on Steam so the game is too big it's
taking up space can you please make the
ad larger okay I got you I got you
fam you're so
right let's switch
places hey this is how it's going to be
imagine I just
[Music]
imagine imagine
imagine the important things in
[Music]
life send then got to got to advertise
my merchandise it's still on sale guys
it's still on sale how much longer I
don't know by heart but I don't know
can't be that much longer we must be at
least halfway
through the uh link is in the
description I think 15 days okay so we
have for for two more weeks for the fry
begin as merchandise I still don't have
pictures of the other two items uh IRL
pictures so that's unfortunate but oh
well uh soon TM question mark anyway let
me switch it out
again h
the there's one part of this song that
always makes you want to like flow into
a different
song can you understand what I
[Music]
mean what am I
doing can you hear Too L I'm going to
try
to when it comes up going to try to do
it
[Music]
I think it's coming
soon yeah the court progression where is
it
[Music]
yeah are we thinking of the same song
Let's
see it's an anime
song oh where is it it's coming
soon ah it's
coming I
[Music]
think uh it's that that song uh da da da
da da da da
da you know what I
mean you know what what song I'm
thinking
[Music]
of yeah Aquarian aquari I'm piing of
Aquarian ah now I need to listen to the
full song
[Music]
yeah
yeah that chord progression is just like
really short but I can't help it okay
okay okay now to the actual game it's a
little little pixel game uh which is a
little bit like bullet hle what was it
what was it like gun I would call it Gun
and Run I don't know if that's really
what the genre is called it's uh it says
here shoot him up that that's that's a
genre to me it looks like you gun and
you
run run gun oh wait that's actually run
and Gun it's that gun and run it's
running gun oh I was close
enough I was close enough I hope it's
okay to play with a keyboard not
controller I hope that's
[Music]
okay H it's going to be a relatively
short stream because you know I have to
find a good balance of short streams and
long streams but okay since we're on the
beginning of the week on the first day
let me actually show you my schedule in
case you haven't seen
it and now today we are having w w
wow and tomorrow we
have cuz my mom is coming over so I
chose to
stay on Wednesday we are having members
only freeing dancing I'm going to as you
already know if you were listening to me
in the past couple days I'm going to put
on my
accents and learn a few popular dances
from H life members uh at the
spot then on first day you guys really
enjoyed my EUR truck simulator stream
and we haven't done a cut Oak in a while
so we're going to combine it your truck
simulator meet unarchived
KY it's going to be unarchived but I'll
will probably rebroadcast it so don't
worry about it if you miss it and then
on Friday it's finally the come back of
G girl
St or girl
St with M and Cronin
[Music]
quason
yeah I I've been noticing more and more
the girliness of quason so I invited her
to talk about what girls do mhm I want
to hear all about
it and then on the weekend we'll have
like a dragon infinite wealth finally
yeah we're going to finish it I know you
don't believe me some of you guys don't
believe me but remember when previously
you didn't believe me and I did it
anyway in a different game and then oh
my God how much you regretted your
words so this is the
week
guys hopefully it goes well so we're
going to play this and then I'm going to
go and I'm going to leave you alone
until Wednesday oh my God so sad I have
no reason to doubt W thank
[Music]
you stream Chimera why did I say Chimera
just because other people are saying
Chimera you guys are confusing me
Chimera Kima are you ever going to do
another whole talk I'm I'm trying to I
was trying to schedule it for next week
but
uh
unfortunately no I asked two people and
they didn't have time
and and I'm not going to I'm not going
to ask a third person because I want to
do those two people
first anyway let's go how does this game
work stage oh oh There are stages just
like with hure huh okay I'm guessing
this is the simplest one bread box I
love
bread I love bread normal mode oh wait
there's actually normal mode for all of
these but I still think Bread Box must
be the easiest let go oh tutorial
no okay uh is there anything I need to
know
besides ah can I like in Holo cure can I
what is this Arrow can I like run no
okay that's fine what is this Arrow then
Yi yipp ah but that was fast only I'm
done thank you forever no confidence
game over without collecting a single
Cod of the Box wait I got an achievement
for being a loser wait wait wait wait
wait
wait arrow is for the next box what what
do you mean
box do I do I need to collect the Box
okay cockroaches W wo wo wo wo wo wo W I
need to collect these boxes
wo wo wo whoo c on it box what is what
are these
things whoo who I must have broken a
record no you would have never thought
you'd see me die without collecting a
single thing huh that's pretty
impressive
right dual finger gun oh I got a new
weapon wo wo wo dual finger gun small
small t house I love that one that's my
favorite C on the phrase everything SW
SW t house why why SW SW t
house maybe I should practice cor
impression I feel like I have
potential thank you forever I'm done
thank you forever try right click to oh
okay first time I tried it I didn't do
anything differently Dan have cence okay
if you say it then I think think I can
do it oh
shotgun oh no I don't think I like
shotguns but
okay right click what does that
do ah have coffee
dance well when you're really
caffeinated I guess you could
dance thank you forever dog why amig
Sunshine what that's cute Sunshine Amigo
Sunshine machine gun let's go wait do I
have to SW I I guess the goal is to get
as many as possible but what if I really
like the weapon that I'm
using no that's like ah okay okay okay
where where did the hammmer
go than you I'm really bad at
this but hey I got an achievement for
collecting five weapon unlocked yub vver
let's go let's go switching weapons part
of the challenge okay okay the hammer
would have been would have been not too
good to have forever shut
theun did she did she record voice LS
for this or
ah
ah or is this cut a thank you for oh my
god let's
gosh Hammer pretty good Hammer deflects
oh I see it it sends them
back yo you revolver
SC
who what what is that the king
why King in the Buu why Buu in the
king yo the revolver it the Pew pews
they they Bounce Off the Wall can they
hit me too
ah but it's like the hammer is so slow
oh no oh no go away where's next Basu
next
B that's ni
ni the
CES I ran into the king all those holes
is where the enemy spawn from okay maybe
I should not stand on top of
them yeah totally ran into that yub
yuie oh
no okay let's let's quickly get the next
B I don't like to have a machine gun
yeah stand over them to assert dominance
yes spawn camping let's go so what kind
of connection does the king have to put
on it I need to know
y it's actually funny because those
bullets the ues they look like normal
bullets so if you don't look too
close oh
no then you might think it's actual
bullets or if you play this game not
knowing about the yub
yie
phenomenon oh they don't even want to
fight me these
boys wait what's next
go next go next oh no the doggos are
really rough
rough finally out of the usion room oh
you were in the usion
room hope you had fun or not I hope you
are suffering the consequences of your
actions you be
where
is is the high score just getting more
boxes or does does the amount of enemies
that you kill also count I
wonder maun surely gets more and more
and more the more maybe the more boxes I
get the more enemies they will send out
just boxes oh okay so maybe dodging
mostly not trying to kill any more
enemies than
necessary is the way to
go what what's
what I never I ain't never seen such
beautiful dual wielding accuracy oh K
King nowadays he's didn't seen that much
but used to be one of her mascot
characters in her
ah this kind of stuff she should have
told me about the king and H talk X
potato cannon but nine nine he's my new
high
score have
confidence did you guys try the game yet
oh there it is did you guys try
it wa [\h__\h] let's
go but already goodbye
yes I did it was fun not not yet it's
free on
Steam can't believe like we we made this
deal with creators to like uh I don't
really know what exactly the deal is but
like they're they're releasing games
under the Holo Indian name right and
because of that they would be allowed to
charge money for their game
if they release it under Holo
Indie and yet they all still don't
charge
money they're still all
free you you you're welcome to charge
money but you're also welcome not to
it's nice not having to pull out my
steam
cards oh
oh [\h__\h] where's the bule
s okay okay okay
[\h__\h] W wo
wo okay okay okay oh another one oh
number eight number eight number eight
Dogo is
dead Alexa play espito you guys maybe
some of you guys uh would like to know
why I tweeted uh Spanish or vanish
yesterday it's cuz I watched this video
from Dual
lingo H nine can I beat my high score
yes 10
and what the
[\h__\h] what is
this what is what what what what what
what
sad got to keep on
going that was a post yeah I know I know
but like I it was busy but yeah dingo
posted a
song oh wow one
hit on
YouTube it's it it sounds like a really
professional
song
and wow and the lyrics are really funny
and the MV is amazing they're like ice
skating and the duelingo oh
mascot the dualingo mascot
oopsie in the big mascot suit is also
ice
skating and then and then in the song
you know they're like singing basically
they're like threatening you
really in a in a scary
way ow play
Spanish or
vanish they're really saying some messed
up [\h__\h] especially in Spanish so if you
didn't Spanish then you might vanish
because you don't understand the Frets
uhuhuh but it was really
funny and it kind of motivated me maybe
I should Spanish or
vanish I'm
inato kind of always wanted to learn
Spanish now that they're threatening me
me to eat my children or
whatever that's a that's a fret that I
do not
forget y y
[Music]
evolver sorry that was really random I
see I I got a lot of a lot a a lot of
Spanish replies that I did not
understand D what
duck you must die you must die I died
too let's go thanks for the membership
welcome Amigo let's
go potato punk punk cute she's so
cute ah I sent them in the I'm so stupid
[Laughter]
I'm so stupid goig you no longer blink
when I Dro random twitch wasn't random
though you just didn't watch the same
video that was so funny you guys got to
watch it I was so sad it was so
short thank
you are you
winning not
really oh I love it when they're close
to together
oh speed running the colon
box y
y buk
b let's go Amigo wow by the way the
title is also a colon a quote actually
no not a colon quote but it's from the
stream where she was looking angry and
the viewer an English speaking viewer
asked her why why is she angry and you
saw the comment and she read it out loud
why is she angry ah no happy face ah ah
I'm I'm ah ah oh oh many people many
many people chainsaw let's go let go
let's go Tony happy face Tony happy
face what was she trying to say chainsaw
but it sounded like chant
s what the [\h__\h] hey
Amigo let's go okay Amigo let's go ch ch
do ah there was an extra word there that
I didn't
recognize from Doom ah Chaw
W get the [\h__\h] out of the way wo wo oh
wo wo wo wo wo wo wo
wo Stupid King get out of the way I'm
taking your crown and then you'll be
calling me
king and you're going to hear him all
sing my tummy hurts my tummy
hurts my
tummy where is it up
up what the [\h__\h]
next please I don't want the hammer you
guys like it but I don't like it I don't
like the bunk
Hammer W explosion
into let's
go okay we're up to nine
now how high can we
get maybe I should just shoot randomly
more like instead of being so like
careful of where I'm aiming towards okay
10 at 11 I think the boss
came thank you I didn't know it would
explode but I should have known
confidence it's the B on and by mascot
it explodes I should know I stayed too
close a more than
what what
no
way what you no no way no I don't
believe you Super
Chat no
4,900 boxes in 12 hours Let's goshine
Amigo
Sunshine no no how how crazy would that
be I don't believe
it okay sometimes they're really close
together and that's really nice but but
but the game gets tougher well you must
be like really used to Bullet maybe
maybe you're like a Toole
addict maybe that's the only not in one
run ah you mean in separate runs
maybe maybe that's what they mean true
true could be that would be more
realistic
ah stop it kingshine Amigo Sunshine he's
coming for my crown he wants it
back you're getting the crown
backkkk wo wo
wo ah the main menu keeps count
oh but then you could have just played
like up to 10 boxes like like
me 490 times oh wait how much did he say
49,000 or or
4,900 and then that's not so impressive
in the
end 4,900 okay then 490 time 10 I guess
right
math I know math I know oh M oh yeah I
let me through let me through oh it's
all the way over here oh the
[Laughter]
king okay okay it's hard to look at the
chat really in this
game but I I don't care if I die a lot I
don't mind you'll be over although I
would like to get over 11 I would like
to kill the
boss o
some some weapons they don't go like PE
Pew PE they go slow and they need a bit
time to charge that's why I'm like
trained to uh not shoot constantly like
shotgun
too K me oh [\h__\h] umbrella Dark Knight oh
my God I'm so scared I'm so scared ah
what it's a different wait a second
that's a [\h__\h] different enemy
[Music]
right oh okay I got some hits I got some
hits where's he going okay he's going
there okay I think I can take this enemy
w w w w w w w
w no I like this one I I feel like I
could handle that one
no
sorry I'll try
again it cannot be so difficult but I
also want to say I don't have much
experience with bullet hell
games it may it may not be the same
genre but it does give me the same kind
of stress of running away from lots of
enemies and danger as Holo cure also cuz
it's like the same
angle and also pixel so The Vibes are
like incredibly
similar right too stream
when I don't think I don't think there's
any point in me streaming I love like
too in general and like too music
Arrangements that that's more where
I my interest in
too comes in play ah [\h__\h] I I know and I
like a lot of to Project Music
arrangement
[Music]
CES and then any I guess any
tole oh [\h__\h] there was something coming
out any Toole
like uh how to say spin-off game that is
not bullet
Hill happy birthday Jesse we did play uh
a [\h__\h] I need I shouldn't run into those
holes even when there's nothing there
we played we were sponsored before by a
tillo spin-off game so to say the spell
bubble one but it's actually kind of sad
that I bring that up because I I
saw I think the other day I saw an
announcement of them saying that they're
like their services are are being
ended or so something like that maybe
the maybe the community is kind of dead
no
Chaser yeah remember Cy playing that
yeah me
too it was
sponsored no characters are so
cute I really I really mostly just like
the
songs all of
those all of
those
soundtracks people are making the most
amazing and different sounding uh
songs and it's it's really cool like
with one soundtrack you can
get so many ah [\h__\h] different vies it's
fascinating
amig w w i
potato she's so cute why is she so cute
why is she so cute guys how how does she
do oh oh what the oh w
[Music]
w [\h__\h]
dog that's why I'm a cat person that's
why I'm a cat
person wow that placement that orange
oh
R RNG is on my side we don't have you
yeah you guys are not in danger when it
comes to coron I guess
[Music]
you are you be not
n I'm Zinda not saying I'm a chicken I'm
a
phoenix I am in danger you guys have to
protect me I do have
[Music]
fingers it's down here again
seven you are only in danger from me
yeah not from cor don't
worry I am your savior and I am your
danger I will be the end of you and the
beginning of
[Music]
you now I said you don't maybe have to
care so much because it doesn't add to
the high score you don't have to focus
on killing enemies but then I realize
they're just going to spawn more and
more right and then it will be uh
difficult to run around so we should
kill people we should we should
ah I have the perfect weapon kind of I
think I like having this weapon
here a [\h__\h] just need to aim
uhoh I did it wo wo wo D is dead
confident let go sh Amigo
shsh wo wo wo what on
book y
y
wow
wow well I'm proud of myself
anyway
y careful too much confidence shut shut
guys I I was cooking before the stream
and cleaning but I didn't finish cooking
but I fried
aatu a snitel aatu call it whatever you
want and then when I'm done streaming
I'm going to resume
cooking oh it's the B bone merang
cute I it kind of Suits her new um
outfit the oh my God this confusing
W
her Viking outfit so cute but yeah I
still I'm I suck at uh unfortunately I I
really
suck at
frying like KATU I
guess I
can't get it to be like done on the
inside this was a pork katsu by the way
way but
then not completely burnt on the outside
but it's really all about temperature I
guess this is my
problem but I tested the waters aka the
oil with
uh ah got stuck I tested it by by
dropping some pkle in it oh oh pinky BL
oh no not this one
ah is it you is
it give me the other
one I'm do I want the other anyway that
I don't like this
one keep PR mixing so much easier yeah I
don't I already have so many different
kitchen actually why did I not use my
air
fryer because it's annoying to always
get it out but also I don't have the
like a
spraying oil spray
thingy that would probably make
everything a lot
easier I should use my air fryer for
these kind of
things is it Gathering dust oh yeah 100%
of course it
is but you know what I do use from time
to time
my what do you call it my
kitchen AEG oh what the [\h__\h] is that
kitchen AE kitchen the the one that goes
the one that can make
everything what's the name machine yeah
the mixer the stand
mixer that I use even when I just need
to make some whipped cream because my
hands are way too [\h__\h] weak yumy
yummy making whipped cream I mean I I I
can probably oh make it happen but it's
way too painful why would I do it chase
a w chase a
w cute I need to get myself one of those
you should but also you can just get
like one of those small mixers that you
can hold in your
hand I want to get a small one too so
that I don't always have to get out the
big
guns y y it's always in the same
locations y y y y
no I walked into it again have
confidence yeah hand mixes are very
useful this
now but yeah so today I'm cooking um the
KATU is a topping
actually for
some something Asian like they're having
like an Asian month or
so in Hell
fresh it said something about about lxa
does that mean anything to you guys
lxa shut the
G no a oh Singapore there you go yeah
but generally so far from my experience
whenever a dish is called something
specific in hellofresh it's mostly uh
just inspired it's not like
100% like accurate so I don't want to
get your hopes up that I'm really
cooking something from
Singapore but uh from the picture I can
tell it's some kind of noodles in like a
orange soup
thing some kind of something like that I
can't I couldn't hit
[Music]
anything okay okay it's with with some
glass noodles
I think y
y yeah yeah rice noodles and Curry yeah
yeah yeah that's that's what it is
that's what it looks like even mhm do
you guys normally top it with with Catu
I'm surprised so many people in here no
is must be popular food potato egg
potato yeah yeah yeah don't you don't
have to tell me to try lxa I'm making it
tonight it looks so delicious in the
preview
picture I hope I can make it as good but
I'm leaving out the spinach there's
spinach in it a little bit I'm leaving
it out no spinach for me I eat it with
shrimp oh just normal baked chicken a
that sounds good too but I mean you got
to admit
KATU KATU as a topping is always
amazing you know I would I would always
top my curries in Japan with katsu if I
didn't have such a small smaller
tummy small small
time let's gosh amig sometimes I still
do it but then I'm always like so
[Music]
full small small tmy
how
Kim potato potato I love it when Seafood
well Seafood is that um really my
thing um but when I see food I usually
eat
it unless it's Seafood but I like to eat
food when I see it yeah just like anyone
else really I think
oh okay that just it I I just had to
because I heard that pun today and now
you're serving me on a platter no you're
serving it to me don't serve me on a
platter you even faked an allergy to
avoid it exactly what do you mean faking
oh it's it's a it's a real issue
allergies are
real have confidence
Phoenix for
dinner what What's the phrase How does
it go again do you want a bath dinner or
me uh
uh-huh oh uh can we switch weapons
immediately I I would like something
where I have where I feel like I have
more control over
[Music]
it ah
I am dead thank you
[Music]
forever I don't want to say this this is
embarrassing I feel very
embarrassed oh I don't want this bone
merang it's cute but it feels so
difficult anyway I was uh talking about
um cor this Viking outfit it's really
cute did you watch it
guys
Vikings how does she is she into Vikings
or did she watch the Viking show I need
to ask
her I I like I like the idea she looks
so cute as a viking more like bar
Barbarian ah yeah oh my God you ah she
has to play um um she has to play
Diablo she looks exactly like a
barbarian no not really exactly but she
got the
B fcking piece of [\h__\h] ah
[Music]
Ragnarok I I guess she played a little
bit of Dia huh she played the
Druid that also suits her I like the
idea generally
now now you're making me think of all
the like you know RPG classes
inspired
um outfits that one could do freest drew
it made uh
warlock succubus
lady uh uh
tank oh no stuff like that oh my God
what was it hexen Ma in German in World
of
Warcraft what do you call that one in
English hex and Meister I think
warlock
maybe ah so it is
warlock that's what my mommy always
played I I played uh what did I what did
I say I was playing a I think Mage when
I was younger in World of Warcraft when
I was like [\h__\h]
baby I played Warcraft World of Warcraft
and I was so
like
13 13
[Music]
14 I was so useless I was so bad at
games oh no no
w i was an infant yeah was I even
allowed to play the
game [\h__\h] I I I scratched my my face
have confidence too young to be gold TR
and yeah
yeah uh yep you are so
right meat shield for raid no I didn't
ever I didn't ever get to raid in the
first
placee I I wouldn't have wanted to
anyway scary
scary reject Diablo Embrace Pap of Exile
why did I read your Comet
let now you must go to Exile usual room
one month
[Music]
H did you make it up of course I I made
it up to level 40 back then when max
level was
60 which is actually kind of impressive
40 42 or 40 something around that
actually but then I would always make
new characters after that after I reach
like level 40 I I I just made new
characters because I think it's just
like everything got to too too
difficult and I just wanted to create
characters and treat it like
Sims Yum Yum yumy yumy Yum
[Music]
Yum yeah yeah too many macros man I did
though I didn't even get like these kind
of
plugins to have more like mac Crow bars
if you know what I mean and was that
World of Warcraft where that was
necessary to do I think so I think I'm
talking about world Ro yeah like
addons so that you can move the bars and
add more and Salon oh
Joshy what
the thank
you the [\h__\h] but I have to say it's
really cool that the the bosses are are
like
random you get even if you don't proceed
much in the game you get to see a lot of
different
bosses oh nice
actually
y we need frd Adams to play effectively
now wow wow
really I thought they would have added a
lot of things to improve quality of game
life without having add all these things
on your
own I created like 100 characters for D
and and never played them I just really
like coming up with characters and the
maging staries for
them understandable you need lots of
atems for World ofra why there for real
well I don't know they're not it's not
not a big problem there's so
many different addons you can get
actually might be kind of fun to play
around with them find the ones you like
[Music]
wall
okay we are here once again pinky
PL oh I can do it I can surely do it
doggle [\h__\h] off
get woohoo and another one W high score
equals a
a 14 14 woohoo finally I'm
processing
progressing not processing progressing
those two words I always have to think
about which one's the right one for what
I want to
say okay 15 let's go let's
go wao new enemies W wo wo wo wo wo
Yep this one sucks oh no oh W
wo oh got to go down got to go down it's
over here wo wo bunk
[Music]
Hammer okay
okay just got to use it wisely uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh please let me for oh I
just ran right into it that was so
dangerous we need to clean up time to
clean up oh
[\h__\h]
19 you boss
soon
potato
it okay
here uhoh W wo wo wo wo
wo we're gaming we're so
gaming okay okay okay okay okay [\h__\h]
dog I didn't even see the Bus Let's gosh
that was too much that was too much oh
there we got so far we're probably never
going to get so far ever again are
we but we'll see we'll see maybe maybe I
can recreate
this w w w w w nice run though yeah my
best
run I believe in a 25 M 25 would be
pretty sick that was an awesome run
thank
you and what's your guys as Max the ones
that did play it when want want
to don't come on just say it just say it
make fun of me 35 oh that's not that
much more
yeah sometimes you need to clean up a
bit 25 47 76 40 14 5 16 oh four oh a bun
of you are just as bad as me if not even
worse wo woah wo let's go oh [\h__\h] it's
already boss time uh-oh Joshi that one I
never beat before I
think and I will not this time
either
[Music]
so H you can right click some ah the
switch okay yeah some you guys told me
to do it and it didn't do anything so I
was
like
n or this one it does
something this one doesn't seem
different y y
why did I why do I why why why why why
why why why W wo
wo nice
nice I want to tell you guys something
that you already know if you are on
Twitter but it was just announced before
the stream that I will be at
ofai a convention in
California California
[Music]
here we
go off guy
xall I'm excited I heard about it in the
past years apparently this is only the
third year though and it's a event event
that is um focused on vtubers in
particular so of course I got to be
there I think I'm the only Holo as as
far as I was
informed and and they announced me
today after they announced already a lot
of other participants so it's like it's
like I'm very
special oh Kyla there too oh really oh
[\h__\h] I didn't know Kyla was announced
too oh no
awesome y yeah oh [\h__\h] thank you I'm
[Music]
fris
special oh they announced her with me oh
didn't some people in the chat just say
she was announced a while ago what do
you mean a while ago and recently so
okay today is the announcement of Kyla
and
kiaha
woo I got tickets nice apparently um
there's still tickets but there might
not be more much more tickets for much
longer so if you want to go if Offa in
California what was it birming not
Birmingham B birmingh birming something
wo
cute if that sounds like something you
want to go to it's an end of uh end of
May beginning of J
[Music]
June uh yeah until like I think 2nd of
June Berling game there we go just
outside of San Francisco oh
really it's that
area
oh now I understand San
Francisco
California what San Francisco is in
California
what
what what are you sure
y
y here get the bone get the bone dogle
get the
bone don't don't be like why does she
not know Dragon mute what the [\h__\h] is
this and why am I fighting it with
Crispies oh oh okay okay here we are oh
this is this is to project yeah let's
[\h__\h] go yes I did it I
let's goshine Amigo
Sunshine
[Music]
confidence
why
man I I would welcome that enemy again
though because it was easy relatively
easy
what the fck oh oh what the
[\h__\h] uh what I saying oh yeah so off guy
and I will have meet and greet and a
panel or panel I don't know if I would
even call it a panel this time I mean it
will be only W solo I haven't had a
solo panel in a long time did I did I
ever why am I shooting the
Box did I ever actually I don't remember
it must have been a long time
ago ah well doig let's
go DOI DOI is a long time ago too it's
it's pretty rare for me to be alone not
paired up with someone
so that means I can do whatever the hell
I want and you know what I'm I'm going
to do you know what I'm going to do so
recently maybe you have seen H
live
uh sometimes for some
[Music]
conventions they manag to do a little
bit of a 3D performance recently now
it's not like this is being prepared for
me in this case so if it if it were up
to them but it is I mean if you know
with the means that I I'm being I'm
being
given I could just do a normal life Tod
panel uh but I have an accent suit and I
am more and more figuring out how to use
it and when I heard I'm being invited to
off and it's like quite a while to go I
thought okay that's enough time for me
to
prepare my suit in a way that I can do a
3D appearance at the panel now
don't don't even dare to expect
something as dope as what they prepare
when when whole life is actually behind
it and supporting the whole thing and
giving them proper motion tracking and
whatever don't dare and also there will
probably be not even a special
background maybe I'll just do it on a
white
background and probably not even camera
angles but I still
thought and I should give it a try
to I'm going to sing my songs obviously
so I might as well try to do it in
3D thank you yeah
I'm just trying
to make the panel uh a little bit better
with the means that I have with what I
can do but it's you know I'm doing it on
my own I'm doing it it's my own choice
to make it 3D if I if I do and um it's
with my own equipment and my own
software
Hardware so don't expect anything too
crazy okay that's what I'm saying but
I'm going to try
to
dance yeah
finally finally a panel in in
3D
yeah broadcast I don't no have
confidence no that is uh I'm not going
to record it and then broadcast the
convention people are literally paying
tickets to go see it so I can't just
broadcast what I did there for free on
YouTube
um but obviously since I want to get my
money wor out of my
suit even even this week already I'm
doing uh 3D stuff for my
members my own
skill my own fris can hurt
me oh oh I V oh do does ofai stream
their panels on their twitch
okay then maybe you guys can see what I
I'll be doing and see my scuff and
probably my tech issues and
everything maybe you will be able to see
it let's go the main stage is Wonder do
am I main
stage am I I have to ask I would hope
so yeah I already told jenma like oh
okay maybe I'm going to do it in
freie so
I hope I can do something
cool I'm I'm a bit nervous about it but
I mean we'll we'll probably with the
memb stream we'll already figure out
like what's in the realm of possibility
roughly because if it's something
pre-recorded if the motion is
pre-recorded then I can still somewhat
have it be cleaned up you know for the
MV for example for era that motion is
not is not completely Raw it's um
cleaned up a little bit here and there
and then it looks a little bit better I
don't know what kind of U does to clean
it up but that means when it's live it's
not going to
be
as perfectly beautiful as it could be
when it's
pre-recorded so for
example I don't know heads uh hands not
not lining up exactly where they should
be and so
on [\h__\h] bird get out of
here nice the way he gets yeated let's
hope for the best yes I will try there's
still still plenty of time so I'll try
to improve my setup and everything and
and practice with the accents to even in
144p you're always thank
you thank
you doesn't have to be thank you cor
Frey for anime NYC it was super scar
wait did she use home Frey like the the
you know our little M the the scuffed
ones did she
I did not know such a thing
occurred just going to place this
everywhere until I switch my
[Music]
weapon ah she used VR back then ah ah
you mean those okay the the VR uh things
that we did before yeah I I did one of
those too
before in VR VR wasn't even that scuffed
generally it's better than the home 3D
honestly
yeah but then yeah the second time we
did these this like VR team up with VR
chat uh I think I just did a normal 2D
panel because I was I think I was in
Japan at the time and it was like early
in the morning or something like that
and it was just like I don't I'm not
even at home I don't don't even know I I
no no I'll be so [\h__\h] tired as well
[\h__\h] the Frisbee I don't want the fris
yeah was with
[Music]
GA the I to do with GA V was fun thank
you yeah good times good
times okay okay let's try let's try to
do better okay
I'll
try I
will fake it till I make
it no one here no
one's here to kill
me
yet wo wo
wo y
yum okay
where where is it
here die
already that
King really did not want to die here
tonight on the
battlefield but you have no choice
speaking of Kings
dying ow I finished watching The Witcher
Netflix show
yeah the end was pretty predictable with
um spoiler alert with Siri not being
Siri it's okay my it's really vague what
I'm
saying was pretty obvious cuz the the
buildup was there and they didn't even
show her traveling while being cap
captive that was so obvious but season 3
honestly it was really good um I know I
know I know it's not like the books and
so on but it was really
good actually was perhaps one of my
favorite
Seasons no not because of what
happens but because of
[Music]
how how it's played out how it's acted
out how it how it's
inia w wo
wo yeah oh no I don't know they were all
pretty decent I going to play the games
yes I got perms for
us cuz we only we only had the console
perms so once I
realized I went right in and got the the
PC
perms don't fret when you see no perms
for one specific platform my dear
co-workers it doesn't mean necessarily
that we can't play
it let this be a
lesson to not give up w w never give
up believe in the
BMS which one is getting a remake oh
yeah but everybody says The Witcher free
is the one I should play so that's what
I'll do cuz I also already bought
it
ah stupid
freisy what is the box
here see I find it weird that the bone
for example doesn't hurt me cuz it's a
boomerang but the frisbey hurts me this
is why this is why the boomerang will
always be the superior toy it's not
really a toy though is
it music really cute by the way I like
it really
chill not again the Frisbee no from
frisbee to from to
frisbee it knows exactly what I just
said and it's like okay I'll give you
more I'll give you more you have to get
used to
it
nice okay I think
we're I was going to say I think we're
having a good run today ha
right
now oh this is the run this is the
run a tell me this is not the run
without saying this is not the run
because it is the Run
woo y
y guys I want everybody to uh take oh uh
take their
wallet take it take get from your bag or
from your
pocket take your wallet right
now yeah you got your
wallet y
y okay now open the
wallet and
check have confidence do you have money
[Music]
if yes you're ready for something if no
then you are not
ready s
[\h__\h] too bad um yeah tomorrow
um you might see another way of spending
your
money being
announced for for me in particular
oh no not again money spending I'm so
sorry don't please don't
feel you know pressured or obligated you
know there's so much
merch and I'm always happy if you guys
can get something you know to support me
but um if you can't then you can't and
uh that's just how life is you know
money is a resource that is not easy to
gather and get your hands
on yeah just a warning so you don't get
a [\h__\h] heart attack
tomorrow or if you were about to make a
big spending tonight maybe if you were
about to buy a big TV or so or a new
graphic card maybe maybe don't maybe
don't
wait wait you actually appreciate that
really
[Music]
give me the W merch give me give me oh
I'm done thank you hey I was about to
say yo that frisbee is doing a good
job yes please oh my God please make
pump
maker you mean like um uh uh a tower
defense yes oh yes please make tower
defense
game I love tower defense game
I mean I didn't even know that I liked
the genre until I played Ark Knights I
know there's this Plants versus Zombies
that I also played as a
child uh online on the
internet and it it's it's uh fun but
uh if it weren't for Ark
Knights I could not care less about the
genre arite just
absolutely perfected the
genre
M really really intricate
strategies and amazing characters of
course and a cool story and you know
overall it's [\h__\h] amazing I love it
love
it no it's not just the anime girls
honestly it was really
[Music]
challenging there's some crazy
strategies and the cool thing is always
that um you know you can usually not
usually by
law you can always clear everything with
like
The Not So Rare oopsie [\h__\h] the not so
rare characters as well sometimes even
they are the meta which is amazing cuz
you usually have all those cheap ass
characters but if you have if you have
some of the you know stronger ones of
course course it will make your life
easier that doesn't mean that you
necessarily need
them and if you play it for a while
you'll end up having plenty of
them studying The
Meta where the girls aren't everything
the story is the strongest part don't
know if it's the strongest part I think
really the gam play is the strongest
part part in AR Knights not the story
but the story is cool
too I'm scared I don't like the bunk
Hammer cuz I have to get so close to the
enemies oh my God no not the
best anything me take
[Music]
potato
potato the free mus husketeers what the
[\h__\h] is that what what what what no no
no no no no no no what what what what
what what I
mean I cornered I was in the worst
position to fight that at that corner
time the
corn I love corn I cannot fight
corn how could
I there it is wo wo wo immediately
switched it out for the shotgun
yeah okay now I need a new cool show to
watch guys
man I'm even considering even though you
guys said it's
[\h__\h] I might even watch that spin-off
from The
Witcher I know I know I know I know why
is it [\h__\h] why is it you guys said the
show is [\h__\h] but is it even based on
anything thing or did they make up their
completely Own
Story Breaking Bad I want something
fantasy though I need more Witcher
there's a spin up yeah it's
called Thank it's called blood
origin Shogun a it's on this plus some
one kfp always mentions Shogun so
actually yeah I I'll consider it I'll
look it up Asian history
uh wait is that like based on real
history or uh madeup history I like both
I like both so I'm fine with both you
know it made it up blood orang and has
terrible acting writing and production
value and the story is little little
garbage okay both based on a book uhuh
realish
interesting thank got weapon I
[Music]
had it's so bad it's kind of fun for a
few
episodes I might give it a try anyway
even if you say it's
[\h__\h] just because I need something with
that
Vibe I feel like
I'm I'm catching up too much with all
the shows that exist that have this kind
of vibe I need I need a new
a new season of House of the dragon
and everything else I'm watching rings
of power I know I know I know
controversial to
say if she liked rings of power
anything's
game God damn it you guys
[Music]
Fallout is good watch Arcane
Arcane fallout
[Music]
Fallout what's the Fallout show is it a
new
show why do they make a show but not
make fall wait is there Fallout
3 no wait Fallout there's several ones
right there's 60 whatever it just this
came out last week
[Music]
W there are five oh have you I watched
Vikings yeah
yeah the thing is with Vikings um I
liked it until I didn't like it anymore
honestly it's it's fascinating but
Vikings once the uh what was his
name
rard what was his name once he
dies the show just yeah r the show just
goes downhill his sons especially the
one who uh was he in a
wheelchair something's with his legs
right he's just Absolut
unlikable as a
character as a personality which just
really it gets to a point where it was
just painful to
watch
ow yeah EV the Bonas
just you know you can make
villains like watchable although he's
not like I don't know is he even
considered a villain he's the main
character at some point and like I don't
think he's that's the irony you might
even think he's like a villain because
he he has the personality of a villain
but he's not really a villain he's the
main
character and
yeah wo wo W
well it's just a piece of [\h__\h]
though shotgun is telling me to watch
shunshine Amigo
Sunshine he's
insane and it's so unfortunate because I
really liked it but then I also watched
like the similar shows that you get
recommend recommended after you watch
Vikings um I think I watched the one
that's called last the last Kingdom I
think I watched it and the bunch of
other similar
shows shun is really good okay you make
me very interested how many seasons are
there that was feeling so good Amigo
sunshine
sunshine that one time fall f it could
be Bower skate
interesting why is that dog
so w such a meat
Shield just the one is celebrating new
show okay so Shogun and wait what was
the other thing
Fallout and what was the other thing
some other show what what was
[Music]
it I'm surprised you like to watch shows
that that are mediocre excuse
me it's the vibe Arcane okay I wasn't
considering that for real for real
but my head have confidence maybe I'll
consider
it
potato Arcane is very good isn't that
like the the League of Legends show or
something like that
[Music]
yeah I don't know guys I don't
know okay maybe I'll try
it I'm getting really desperate after
all in terms
of shows to
watch I might start with SH
though makes me want to eat
chocolate
chol
chol excuse
me passing through potato X
potato no don't take that's my favorite
weapon it feels so
strong don't take it away from me
especially now one we're so close to the
bus now not the [\h__\h] oh okay
I I didn't want to fight with the
frisbey so my mind was like [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] also the free what was it
husketeers
was that the one I I killed really
easily or the one that I died
immediately
[Music]
to I'm not the [\h__\h]
frisbey my biggest enemy although I did
hit hits that enemy just now even though
he was off
[Music]
screen let's go Sunshine Amigo
Sunshine ah they cornered
me thank
you no you're not a
duck I know she's saying dog but now it
sounded like I'm duck no K you're
delusional sh is D hold on it is
dog
y
wo okay okay okay okay
okay I thought you was
dog oh yeah there's a meal Senai Cannon
right I saw it in the
screenshot oh yeah I want to get some
cool weapons I need to get more but I
need to
advance but in same you don't need to
know anything about the game the less
you know the
better the less I know the better okay
interesting thank you
confidence is is human human
is many true statements my friend
[Music]
I want to say by the way thank you guys
for streaming Chima it's doing so well
it's over
560k now I thought it would slow down
more but it didn't slow down that much
at all thank you
thank you for
supporting it's a b it's easy when it's
such a good song Thank
you for everybody's who who's going to
offy make sure to
practice the dance no just
kidding coefficient I saw in the cro for
tweets
coefficient
reacted like like
yab to my offy appearance announcement
so that makes me think he's going to be
there so you guys are in charge of um
he's going to be there okay you guys are
in charge to take a video of
him make him dance Chima I will Dan I
will perform
Chima so keep an eye out for coefficient
hopefully he will have learn the Coro by
then and will be a great asset to my
performance
no he should hopefully be there in the
audience giving us a little
taste of his dancing skills is this
considered
fooling group dance yeah no the thing is
because this is a solo panel I was
actually
thinking maybe instead of just you know
only only singing through and through
through maybe I could do like a little
bit of a uh dance l
simplified dance lesson for everybody to
stand up and participate and then also
just like a general like
chanting guide
also like first before I sing I teach
you like small important vital parts of
the dances so you can maybe move your
hands along don't worry not not nothing
too intricate and then also you know
obvious chance like he
[Applause]
[Music]
stuff like
that oh oh
wait
huh y
y you said hand instead of hip no no I
mean hand don't worry you're welcome to
move your hip too
though free body problem what the [\h__\h]
is that a book
free body problem sounds like a really
weird
title
wall I can't even stand up without the
groan same though
same uh maybe maybe I can start up ah
the panel with a little bit of you know
stretching
exercise everybody stand up now let's
breathe in deeply and breathe out while
opening Your Arms Wide Open open your
chest
bones like you're giving the world a big
hug and then we go back and create a
little bit of a a bump in our
back yeah so we go towards the opposite
basically yeah good job guys good job
job
imagine wow I I I'll have it all I'll
have stretching exercise I'll
have oh oh crazy
duck I'll have guide I'll have dance
lesson
everything you'll be so ready you'll be
so ready once I start
singing go [\h__\h]
yourself you'll be
so you'll be so
[Music]
ready do last night did you guys
see do you do you say do
[Music]
you me like a Fame I know never feel the
same oh do you do you
say yeah she kind of requested that we
sing do you she was like ah do you wna
ah Johnny hi do you w to sing on
something together for my birthday C
okay and then she just
[Music]
suggest
suggested she suggested she
suggested do
you and I
mean I would like to hear everybody's
rendition of do you so gladly and then I
don't even have to learn a new song I
can sleep do you eh I can sing do you in
my
sleep more or
less so it's no effort for
me yes I want to hear them all singing
all of them all of
[Music]
H honestly um when I first started
releasing songs oh my God can you guys
all [\h__\h]
up rabit die let's go Sunshine Amigo
Sunshine yeah Johnny you too
uh Johnny's a really good singer by the
way Johnny Johnny is part of the Kiwa
Angels team and is an absolute
allrounder kind of insane K too both K
and Johnny don't only make songs but
also sing really really well and they
mix they do everything what's what's
wrong with
them how can they mon is also [\h__\h]
all around all of them it's like
dangerous this team is
dangerous too much
power jack of ult Trades
absolutely
wall
nice oh do you see how they're putting
it right into my hands oh my
God Kiana is our
mic
stop I'm so happy to hear that what was
I saying though oh
yeah uh thinking you know with like
several people even the ones who are not
fluent in English like laas for
example wanting to sing do
you
um it made me realize do you has has
really reached like cult status as in
it's actually actually you know so what
I'm trying to say is after hinotori I
released uh oops I
released uh heart Challenger and then
Sparks and Sparks did really well but
until that point I thought okay I I
hinoni is like the song that kind of
represents me when people think of me
they think of hinoni also because it
made such a big impression at the Holo
Fest where it was also the first time I
showed my
fredd so I thought oh it will be
difficult to top the hype of hoton and
the the iconic of hinoni but then Sparks
came out and I think just because it was
the first English song I did and it went
in a very different direction people uh
were really celebrating that and and
Sparks became an absolute Anem W
for kfp and and me and my streams and I
was really happy about that too
everybody was vibing to Sparks and
honestly I was so happy to be able to
again and again
um kind of uh outdo and improve myself
and have people enjoy my newer songs
because that was really the one thing
that was scary to me that after
releasing the first original song that
people
ah would would
uh would maybe not care so much about
anything that comes
afterwards um but yeah uh ah
not the coin let's
go but that wasn't the case and then was
Sparks uh I think after Sparks was fite
right and unfortunately I really think
fite deserved a bit more Lu but then I
went back with do you or was it the
other way around might have been the
other way around I always mix up those
releases
it what was first feite was first okay
okay okay amig let's go yeah and I got
to say I was a little bit
um like my motivation was a little bit
kill where were you when kiwa's
motivation was kill I was I was
releasing beer Knight and I was I was
also scared that okay maybe maybe this
is now the time
oh maybe after a couple of successful
music releases it's over now I can't
release anything popular
anymore who knows
so I was really worried I was really
concerned um and and my budget was
affected
by you know this is real talk my budget
was affected so when I decided to make
do you into a 3D music video it was
quite the risky thing to
do because that cost me a lot of
money and you know
I could only hope that it would do well
and then it did so
well it did so well ah do you absolutely
killed
it and now you know I have so many
bangers that people think of when they
think of me but I thought cuz it was a
long time uh sorry that was
unexpected it was a long time um between
do and my
album what the [\h__\h] is that eye doing
here it felt like it was a long time
potato
so yeah I was I was worried about how
the album would
perform and everybody kind of
like already I feel like had
do
you burnt into their brains when they
think of my
music
yeah what am I trying to say I lost my
my my train of
thoughts I lost my train of fault but
whatever what I'm saying
is that I didn't think that again I
could do it with
Kima because I feel like I'm doing it
again
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's you know I
think it's just natural that it doesn't
work with every song not every song can
reach such a iconic cult
status and be like really popular and
everybody listens to it and and thinks
about it you know go
away that is difficult to recreate
thatall
[Music]
this kind of Miracle several times it's
it's difficult and I I don't I don't
expect it to happen all the time but of
course I I hope for it because I need I
need the music to do well in order to
make more music uh on on good quality
you
know so now I'm really happy with
kimar's
[Music]
performance and
yeah I was thinking about that because
um beu was saying oh I want to sing Kima
too although she said
CA she pronounces it ca there are many
different ways of pronouncing Kimera I
guess you do you
be uhoh oh Dragon mute okay not not the
not the
FRP I five been cornered stream
camera
no give me new one give me new one give
me new one why is it so far
away you did not know what a Kim was
when when you wrote the lyrics M wrote
the lyrics I hope she knew what it
[Music]
was you can I tell you do something um
so I I like to Ego search in Japanese
because it's it's more likely that I
find someone talking about me rather
than in English when I look up
kiata uh there's a million tweets that
include kiata and it's really it's
really hard to find you guys talking
about me and but in Japanese it's easier
CU I type in K Chan what's that's
usually the go-to for Japanese Bros to
write about me
and that was one Japanese
bro who was really excited about me
releasing a
song called
Chima and was getting really hyped up
and was writing stuff like yo Chimera is
like my favorite thing like it was
literally a Chima U
like it's it's a Japanese girl who I
never saw talking about me before you
know but me releasing a song about a
Kima apparently
really got this this fan interested and
hooked and and like oh my God she's so
based for releasing a song that's called
Kima because Chimas are really cool and
they were getting so hyped up and then I
released the MV no at first it was
before the MV released I did this stream
right where I put on a few cute
pngs um onto my body and I talked to moy
and stuff remember that stream the
release
party uh and and the fan the Japanese
bro watched
it and was a little bit disappointed he
was like oh I wonder why why did she
choose
the I think it was the dragon that he
had an issue with thing or or like one
of the animals he had an issue with
because that is not the
Chima that he thinks is the the the
typical Chimera but but I know there's
like the typical Chimera out
there
um that is like seen the most but that
doesn't necessarily mean why bone Cammer
for a [\h__\h] boss it's so over no
confidence [\h__\h] that I'm dark we told
you but but B that you don't have to
there's you can make a Chima out of
anything you know and there are okay
there's like a Canon one but I would say
there's at least two Cannon
ones one is more Canon than the other
maybe but you know but anyway I found it
funny because he was was literally
confused and was like oh I wonder did
she make a mistake did she it must have
been a mistake like why I wonder why she
did it but she must have done it by
accident or she didn't realize that what
she put on there was the wrong
thing
and and then the MV comes out and I see
another another tweet from this
person and
okay I feel so bad for disappointing
himself several times with my non
Canon Chimas but the next issue was that
the Chimera in my MV has it's free
animals yeah but it's the three heads
are right next to each other that's not
Cannon and yeah I kind of agree with
that but kind would have made that and
um I wasn't going to say hey can you
like remodel that completely
yeah because it looked more like a
cus
whatever yeah I can see that normally
well it depends really in then it
depends on what animals are involved in
your Chima if it's if the snake is
involved then yeah the tail will be the
third animal and then the head is just
like there's just two heads in the front
then it won't look like a curus but in
our case I don't know I didn't even tell
kanuru which animals to put in there but
uh I think he also put a dragon in there
a goat and a lion and a dragon but
that's not the cannon one but well
obviously you're not going to put like
the dragon on the butt or
so I understand that
choice but yeah so the visuals and the
MV were disappointing once again ah I
had a good run
go will Manor be Canon if I make a song
that's called manticor I'll try my best
to be more
Canon didn't know JY didn't know but I
know I know but I'm not I'm I'm not
letting myself be chained by the by The
Meta of mythical
animals look up the Wikipedia
IAL it is not decided that these certain
animals have to be in the
Chima but yeah what I'm trying to say is
I'm sorry for getting your hopes of
Chima U
son for making you think that I'm super
based and I'm creating this thing that
is
literally your favorite thing ever and
then I keep on disa recing
you it's but it's so funny to me cuz I
was so surprised that somebody would
just get so hyped up about a chimera in
the first place like that's the thing
that's getting you hooked about this not
not the sound or whatever no no no it's
just the fact that there's a chimera
involved but the Chima is just a a a
metap metaphor anyway well I actually
wanted to ask Mooney Johnny if you're
still listening can you get Mooney in
here I wanted to ask her to explain to
me I I know you know the meaning of the
song lyrics and all that but how where
where does the Chima come in am I the
Chima why am I the Chima what part what
why why is the song called Kimera just
because it sounds good why did you
choose to put Kima in there oh no
I was
stuck okay Johnny is on the way to ask
Mony the person behind the lyrics if
anybody knows why the decision was made
she must know I am theim okay
why do are you saying I'm not only twoof
faced but free
faced but the point of the song
it's something else it's like saying you
[Music]
know I don't need your stupid attitude I
don't need your hate and blah blah blah
uh I'm better than that I'm not going to
even like deal with that because yeah F
you you know it's an angry song Angry
song why am I Cima maybe it's the power
the power that I have but why ca I still
don't understand
this we're all ready I'm speed running
this
now not the [\h__\h] chain
tle oh
no I can't I can't even reach
it so
unlucky she's into it hang on okay she's
you mean she's onto it
okay no there's there's other levels I
chose chose this one and I'm too lazy to
switch huh chainsaw eats projectiles oh
okay I'm still kind of scared to run
into
that in the
why m in VC yeah having her in VC would
uh be helpful but it's okay it's okay
she can explain in in form of text
actually she's oh I got a
message ah oh never mind that's not
about
that nice
[Music]
position where is it where is
it friendly fire with those frises is PR
for real I don't want those stupid fris
go away
[Music]
let's go amig let's go change
of um
scenery ooh and music this looks like a
Pokemon
game okay I need to learn what is where
how big the map is
ah where I can get
stuck where the enemies
are need to learn it all need to study
it guys if I miss mony's reply uh let me
know
me oh going going good for first try on
this map but you know I'm already like a
veteran at this
point yeah oh shot gun okay Pinky pledge
uh uh uh uh wait what the [\h__\h] sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry I can do
better I can do
better I can do better I
promise I would have preferred the
Bazooka though for the boss fight why
did I switch out of it cuz I have to
this potato I got some potato this one
bazooka maybe it is not even a bazooka
but to me this is what what is called a
bazooka y
y yby
y no is ity
[Music]
okay
roeter ooh ooh ooh
[Music]
no let's go the term bazooka has a funny
history to oh
really dodging into the bullets isn't
what do you
mean I'm always trying to dodge away
from
them oh could it be all hey I was about
to say that this map is nicer for frises
because maybe the frises get sent out
into the water and don't come
back well only in some cases I
guess y
y get out of way get out of my way hey
I'm walking
here hey I'm walking here
woo oh is that one a little bit more
scattered no is it felt like it the
right click on the
shotgun feels a bit
oh really is that a thing you can
actually do with the shotgun like
influence
how how spread out it
is I have silenced
him New York
W I know that's the the New
York phrase to
say the only thing I know how what to
say if I want to sound like a New
Yorker it's time umbrella got okay okay
okay okay okay
go that one is okay CU that one follows
me and I think I can handle him
now how much longer will I
survive I haven't seen you in a long
time Mr Dark
Knight this game is so cute I have to
say like I I don't know everything about
coron sm5 but I'm assuming that all of
these are like some dorky drawings she
has made before and and it really just
references to the years she has spent
streaming characters that showed up in
her in in games that she really liked
that she gave funny names and so on so I
don't know what's going on a lot of the
time with these bosses
especially
[Music]
but
wait I feel the love
this [\h__\h] duck the projectiles from
the duck are really like difficult
y all the way over
here are you for real oh but actually it
might actually be kind of good the
position
because the trees lock the projectiles
oh oh he's
moving I was so close
oh okay breaking out was
unexpected I thought I could cheese it
forever that was actually the perfect
position did you see how easy that was
for me
[Music]
walk
okay almost cheesed it who could have
known I never got that far I think with
that boy with that
Dragon you were close to getting it for
real yeah I was I was trying to shoot
while running backwards but the bullet
the big bullet came faster than I could
run he's okay you do be like that
sometimes yum
[Music]
Yumm one has more bark than she
needs I wouldn't say so don't
underestimate
her
Y where are the
enemies Maybe maybe I shouldn't shoot
them then because they they disappear
when I shoot them it's so
lonely not a stupid Boomerang weak I
don't
like w wo wo
y y have you seen her new song ah I
haven't gotten to listen to it yet I saw
like Snippets of the MV it looks really
stylized really
cool like she always has like a a funky
look going
on really
unique I can imagine that it must be a
great
song like old Astro Boy style
M yeah I love the nostalgic
Vibe always love her mvs
I heard it's all in
English
interesting cor English she knows what
we
want wonder how the Japanese Bros feel
about feel feel like ah when they
hear cor is English how do they
feel how does it make him feel
[Music]
everything she does is cute
yeah
[Music]
it's the same when you hear me speak
German
[Music]
so this map definitely is a bit bigger
than the other one so that all already
makes it a bit more difficult cuz
there's more like you have to run
further to get to the
boxes but there's also you know more
place for the enemies to spread
out maybe that's a good thing
the thing that we just had happened with
the boss definitely made it easier for
us for certain certain amount of time so
I see that as a
win okay we're almost at boss again and
I almost ran into the
projectile I am a menace to myself
o oh it's the eye one isn't it no not
the not the
boomerang where are you
anyway no go away go away go away
no how did I how did I survive this and
how did I oh my God how am I ever
hitting it by just oh my
God I don't want to fight the boss of a
[\h__\h] Boomerang no frisbey I mean
oh the
RNG the RNG
man it's all about the
RNG
Rus
please I don't think I'm incapable of
killing that boss I just need the right
weapon just get lucky easy
[Music]
y y y to me this is like a mix of Holo
cure and Hotline
Miami Holo
Miami and to wo wo
wo no no why did I run into it
so
sorry hotline cure oh that's
[Music]
cute no I was actually good at Hotline
Miami but yeah you guys were saying when
I was playing holla Miami 2 and losing
my mind because it was like you guys
were saying it's okay because holla
Miami one was better and it's not
entirely my fault
it's just it's just you know w w w
sometimes you need to
know where to stop for your own good for
your own
enjoyment I didn't want to force myself
to finish the game just just so that
it's on the finished games list of
takanasi
Kiana don't need to force myself when
I'm not enjoying it a [\h__\h] bone
versus a dragon mute okay oh god oh
[Music]
it was going to be difficult
anyway probably wouldn't have made it
yeah it's a little M
right now it was like really out in the
open the opposite from
before yeah I don't want to ruin the
game for myself too yeah I was having
fun like a lot with Hotline Miami
one and Hotline Miami 2 was fun
too it wasn't bad it's just something
about it I don't even know anymore what
was wrong with it
but I think it it just got uh difficult
to
unlevel that was not feasible anymore
what's
here the levels are too big yeah they
got really big too
H too many open AR
yeah
so the level design was soundtrack was
bomb as always
[Music]
okay thank you no that was so dumb dum
dum I was so ready to switch my weapon
and go to the
boss
[Music]
yum sorry stupid
duck what people announc wait I don't
even
know JMA didn't tell me
JMA didn't tell me that there would be
so many other
holos I thought I was the only
[Music]
one I mean no problem with
that I thought that was the only
hulo and now you keep on proving me
wrong and embarrassing me for my
statement
what the uh one of the organizers is a
kfp yeah think about
that think about that for a minute
y ow why did I do that good question I
was about
to yeah the
co-founder
kfp coold
founder when and and I saw a
message like I I I saw some of uh the
messages she I think wrote w w
wo uh about being able to invite me to
ofai or whole life in general and she
was like saying ah can't believe after 3
years now we have come so far to be able
to invite my oi and I'm like oh
oh like this convention exists only for
like 3 years maybe that was the goal all
along make convention to eventually be
able to invite your osie host your
oie what a what an insane
plan and then to make that actually into
reality wa why is not every every single
one of you making a convention for me
huh just
kidding KF
convention
KFC KF convention short KFC can we do it
or are we going to get sued H what do
you
[Music]
think wo
right w w w lots of kfp are running V
Expo in the
UK really lots of
kfp all you guys got to become bigger so
you can get
me I'm
awaiting your
offer
European uh kfp are
very
desperate very desperate to to get
another European convention
going but European conventions they just
don't care about
YouTubers that
much that they would you
know take the
wall give What It
Takes do what it
[Music]
takes die
y
y I'm never going to meet K don't say
that you will you
willk
bunk okay oh it's a dark knight okay
okay okay okay
do I feel a lag or is it it's just me
right
no
wall honestly I I I I I need
to I need to get good
I'm going to get good I'm going to get
good now this is this is the moment I'm
going to get
good
sh telling me to watch
shun Disney plus Channel wo wo
wo wo wo
W
ah it's the landmines again okay okay
when I have them I spread them
everywhere
nice why do they always B on me right
there when it's time
11 is the magic number
no it seems like 11 is my unlucky number
I I'm writing it down now your screams
are keeping me awake while driving are
you
driving drive carefully
B do me the favor thanks for the Super
Chat
May the May the gas prices be on the
lower side for
[Music]
you or maybe you use electricity card
then may
may electricity prices be on the low
side for
you gas prices should be in your favor
amen hey man I'm walking here oh oh are
you religious
want to go to church together that's not
what I meant man I was just saying hey
man why am I making up scenarios in my
head let's goshine
Amigo potato potato
[Music]
me no I was like man I hate
myself no no no the Red Bull from
yesterday has nothing to do with my
behavior it's just because um I'm
actually pretty awake because I had my
nap after I woke up
early man the feeling I had the first
money okay and yes
money
yes did you just write Kima like put the
Chima word in there because you thought
it was cool did it not have any
particular
meaning let me know
yum it's understandable I get
it it's okay you can
it so this is what I was yeah I wanted
to know why what has Chima to do with
the overall meaning of the
song what made you think
ah this song is going into this
direction so we need to implement a
Chima maybe because Chima sounds like
Kiara now that I think about it I just
realized that just
now maybe Kima is just
personality of takanashi
Ki like Ki kou K
you the way I say it kind
of I'm H talk with money because of all
your animal personal I don't think she
was all no it has a meaning it's just
meant in the different or unusual way so
basically the song is about two sides of
you coming together the weak and the
Bold to create the strong you the
Chimera but you know a Chima has free
sides
right let's not let's not have the the
Kima otaku the Japanese bro who's really
into
Chimas read your statement just
now but that's cool though I guess I am
the third okay the two together makes
the third but then that's just one
that's just one in
end but I get it I get it I get it the
way you are trying to make it make work
make makes yeah makes sense I see what
you're trying to
[Music]
do Kima can be too I think and let's ask
the Kima otaku in on
Twitter now M I was saying I was telling
everybody that I saw a Japanese bro um
getting really excited and hyped up for
Kima because he's a Kima
otaku like a chimera
nerd particular this thing Chimera is
what what gets his
gears going you know and then he was
pretty disappointed by my depiction of a
chimera in my uh
party release party and then again
disappointed um but I find it really
funny by the 3D model of the Kima in the
[Music]
MV [\h__\h] let goshine Amigo
sunshine I'm not I'm not mad or anything
I really just find it very amusing if
anything I'm
sorry T and
pun you know yesterday was Doom posting
to narissa I'm not going to tell you
what about but I just suddenly had this
thought in my mind that was really
unlikely but also not completely
unlikely and I was like oh God if this
happens I'm going to morb and I wrote in
the WR like oh my God I sent her this 5
minute voice message of telling her a
scenario that we have absolutely no hint
or clue that it would happen but I just
thought it might just happen and I was
like I'm going to Morp so hard if this
happens I'm going to be so angry I'm
going to be so pissed and she's like
yeah I understand I I get
it and then it's okay I was like very
aware that this is really unlikely and
I'm like sorry this is so unlikely but
still I can't help but think about it
right now the scenario in my head is
making me so
angry I'm already angry at it even
though it didn't happen yet
anyway thank you mon
for
explaining it's it's cool let's do a
manticore next
time
y let see if the manticor
otakus show up from
[Music]
somewhere that's what your shampoo
bottle are for what do you mean to talk
into the shampoo bottle
what what is this placement and why do I
have a frisbee again I just switched it
out and then it became a frisbee again
where is it is it there again oh oh okay
interesting y b this is kind of
difficult with the [\h__\h] fris be
though can only hold a
no that some of them hits the dragon
I'm
11 he was on the island but not in the
good
spot that blocks all the
[Music]
bullets I don't like these reminder to
take your vitamin D or you end up like
yada no no no no no no no no I'm just I
like the Doom
post anyway I was going to
say before Mooney showed up today I woke
up early to do the thing and I did the
thing and I'm so proud of myself for
doing the thing and I was also Doom
posting about doing the thing uh cuz I
thought I was like I was like too late
and I'm going to get in trouble for
being late but then didn't even matter
because nobody asked about nobody
questioned my
lateness not the lateness in time terms
of time but in terms of date but anyway
it didn't matter and anyway I woke up
and when I woke up I woke up before
10:00 I slept like 6 hours or
so and 6 hours for a lot of you is
probably what you go by on the day
daytoday basis when you go to work and I
don't envy you and I know you'll be like
oh 6 hours oh that's plenty it's not
plenty for me cuz I'm not used to 6
hours I I make my own schedule and I
sleep how much I I yeah well that's not
true often my sleep gets interrupted and
it's shorter than I wanted it to be but
anyway for me 6 hours I feel like [\h__\h]
and when I awoken from my Slumber you
know that feeling when go you wake up
and you're like no no no of course
everybody knows that feeling right is
like no what what I have to get up
no I rarely get this feeling because
most of the time I get more sleep and
then I don't get this feeling but today
I had this like
absolute terrifying D dread of having to
get up when you still want to sleep and
you just want to not get up it's
terrifying it's the worst feeling and I
was like I'm okay I have to get up so
I'm going to get up but the moment I'm
back I'm immediately going to go back to
sleep because that's how tired I am but
then usually once you do the thing you
get up you do the thing and then you
come back home and you're actually at
that at that moment you're not that
desperate anymore cuz your mind has
already woken up and you don't feel like
you need to immediately sleep again so
it was never really this dramatic you're
like oh my God I'm so tired the world is
going to end the moment I get back home
I'm going to fall asleep for 10 hours
but no no no no no I got home I cleaned
my apartment a little bit I I had
breakfast and
then and then I watched uh the the last
episode of The Witcher on
Netflix and watched more some family
guys and
ah oh oh
oh okay okay good
[Music]
weapon I need to find it where is
it
[Music]
get What's happen
happening what's wrong with me why is it
always like
this
why have confidence last run
[Music]
potato try using a high level of
gameplay where's my Dev where is my
beloved
Dev I want that Dev to be in the chat at
all times not just when I play their
[Music]
game I love the
SAS I absolutely love the SAS
come back to
[Music]
me we're
already wait it's up there what the [\h__\h]
what
[Music]
what one more let's go amig let's go 11
1 2 3 4 5 6 seven you make me feel like
[Music]
11 please make the next song be called
11 she cannot she cannot
Hey Moy let's just copy that
song 1
2 you make me feel
[Music]
like why does it sound
familiar one more because it's a
well-known K-Pop
song they sample in that song they
sampled um what song I I Will Survive
was it that
one a lot of people seemingly didn't
even realize it was so obvious that it
was sampled no problem with sampling
things maybe we should do that too it
might be fun you hear that Johnny are
you here should we try sampling like a
famous but I guess you got to buy like
expensive licenses to do that right
unless is like freaking Mozart should we
sample Mozart or B can we can we can we
sample old to
Joy Johnny Johnny Johnny Johnny Johnny
please oh that's after like yeah let's
let's please oh people would freak the
[\h__\h] out please let's let's put o to Joy
melody in one of our songs next song
ideally oh that sounds so fun it is a
great
Melody
OMG let's
go I don't think we have to pay right
it's like free free for
all my own very own all to join personal
ult
Joy classic Melodies are copyright let's
go let's
go okay Pinky pledge again what the [\h__\h]
they
what the [\h__\h] land mine
no wasn't going to
happen land
mine
[Music]
land for an enemy that stays in the same
position
too let's
goshine last one
so [\h__\h]
mad no for real for
real for real for real accept the
reality nice
aim let's go s amigo
[Music]
what with all the
Cockroaches it's the uprise of the
Cockroach oh not you again okay why do
we keep on getting the pinky FL it's
okay I
uh no
[Music]
I
despise the number
11 from now on number 11 is
banned
understand
Bend no
[Music]
more no no get out of here I don't want
to see that shitty number worst number
ever I hate
it employee number 11 who do we have a
employee number
11 check the list
[Music]
guys but 11 chol no I'm 10 ch
what if it's your birthday date I don't
care that's not my birthday date so it's
okay so who is who is now 11 do we have
an 11 magican is 11 okay are you here if
not then it's
[Music]
okay skill issue stop get that ugly
number out of my face I don't want to
see it no more oh but hey it says I have
boxes
889 almost 1,000 almost a
th000
no what how did I get so many that was
for thinking for a moment I should get
another 100 oh
111 exact oh what a what a disgusting
number
111 to 1,000 that's where I am at 11 to
11111 I'm not doing that cursed what a
coincidence that we stop at this point
where I would need such a ugly number to
get to a th000 I I refuse it's making a
mockery of me this
[Music]
game stop sending 11 super
chats I hate
it cute game though really I just don't
understand why I get stuck at 11 I did
make it
223 before and there's definitely
potential to get much
higher but
[Music]
alas one one wo you're like 11 wo oh
no 11 month Mom oh yeah is there any 11
month
members get that number out of my face
7-Eleven per rip no I love
71 but from now on it's just 7 to me I
cannot say the rest of this store's
number
[Music]
it gives me the
Shivers okay Chima Super Chat how nice
10 memberships or you're so nice for not
gifting 11
memberships oh wait we do have an 11
months member jaquas jaas
jackass congratulations on uh me hating
you o motion
motion why do you have to add on to it
why' you have to ruin
it thank you guys thank you oh my God or
thank you
not thank you
[Music]
not no please
stop Super Chat there's a few
ja for the Sal K St than Jones thank you
for the red super chat is the best know
you un no first card thank you so
much and you didn't even listen you
didn't even see the MB at this point
[Music]
yet if you think about it 11 is just a
Chima of one and one no it would have to
be
111 we're different number numbers
anyway any free numbers are a chimo of
numbers then what are you trying to
say thank you B and dougle
Jones Jackson a free thank you iron vad
D thank you top free let's go gold Bo d
g d for the pink thanks for cheering me
on D and Cruz danim thank you for the r
Super Chat
Kim I love it K you really outdate
yourself I love to sing along to this
Kim thank you by the way I was thinking
the a capella version just because I'm I
really don't want to ruin the momentum I
never know with YouTube um so I'm
waiting I'm waiting I I'm thinking you
guys already heard to an capella so if
you want to listen to it you know where
to listen to it in the vaud um but the
capella I think I'll upload it once
Chima reaches like 1 million
probably yeah I just want to make sure
we get there we're on a very good path
to 1 million I think it will actually
happen within very reasonable time
because it's still growing really fast
knock on
wood so please continue watching the MV
y
and then I'll upload the
aella which is so so beautiful people
have to listen to it let Chimera cook
yes let's cook the Chima the Beast must
be
cooked you can use your second channel
to dump random stuff in yeah but yeah I
guess no it's okay I want I want more
people to have it in their inboxes
so we need sleep talking Acappella too
[Music]
true but uploading it publicly now out
of nowhere is kind of random did I say I
might upload as a members
only what did I say what was my plan I
don't know anymore but now it's it's
kind of random if it's
public I
did what about uploading as a file in
the community post for remixers I don't
know if there's really that much
demand can just rip it off of
YouTube uploading a capella members only
is something other members have done oh
really
H
interesting but Kima I want to make
public just because the timing works
right now when it's still fresh you know
anyway T thank you
than J SW than for the red super
chat make it a reward for a million to
force people to listen yeah I mean it's
not like you can't already listen to it
that's why I was like holding back on
saying as a
reward it's already out there it's not
really a reward but
yeah there's probably about a 100
different Kias in this MV right yeah
Kima looks awesome it's nice to see it
all finish yeah actually there's so many
Kias in Kima you're right all the aren't
all the kneeling people also
me so much self
love and self-hate cuz I fight myself as
well oh my God I'm My Own biggest
supporter and biggest
enemy Wawa kneels before Wawa I'm
appreciating my myself as I should as
you
[Music]
should multi faceted
faed love hate all the same if you know
play the
game those are your brain worms
kneeling there's so many waas so
many fascinating
I always appreciate you so much thank
you please don't lock me up
inside wait are you quoting my
lyrics am I locked up up inside yeah
yeah yeah you
are no I can't fight the feeling and I
won't
try okay thank you J swur
gold thank you for the pinky that was
fire definitely my favorite even before
the MV and this just made it so much
more spicy damn awesome job you really
outdid yourself thank you I'm so happy
so many people were putting it on the
top of the top of their favorites of my
songs I'm really honored appreciated
thank
you I I told you before it wouldn't have
been my first choice to put out as a new
song um but maybe it was
Destiny if it wasn't for your vision
this would have most likely not been my
next
song What A I'm going to upload it but
I'm going to wait for 1
million what if you did a medly of your
OG's I want to one day yeah sleep
talking well I said I'm uploading that
one too but it's just uh I'm probably
just going to make it members only
because I don't want to spam my Channel
with random a really random Acappella
now I'm thinking of the algorithm you
[Music]
know yeah I should have done that during
when the album released but then back
then I didn't want to like bother the uh
algorithm with all the other things
related to my album that I was uploading
cuz I already had plenty of things to
upload so there was no space to upload a
a capella at the
[Music]
time yeah anyway
uh L moonight thanks for the pinky I
want to mention that you were right that
shot of kuraa looking for the chains was
really cool right and for some reason
she's so [\h__\h] hot I don't get it
congrats on new bang Ki thank
you yeah black Wawa and white W back at
it again fighting and dancing at each
other what's what's what's the deal with
them one day I need to interview
them they are giving me very confusing
Vibes what's their
issue we'll never know or will we
H SP waterful Dan and
Alim wasn't there a blue one too no no
no no no blue one no no no not yet at
least maybe sometime cuz I was saying I
want to see a a jeans a denim
texture
version I think that might be
interesting
[Music]
but generally I would also just like a
new outfit and not always have to use my
default
outfit although it is kind of Genius the
way we
used um the OG outfit and Chang the
colors it it worked out so well for doy
you better than being
orange pink and black was definitely the
right choice instead of being Orange H
it made it also more iconic having these
different color variations it's like I'm
a Super Smash Bros
[Music]
character Versa color pallets yeah it's
cool because it feels like an
interconnected world of songs yeah I can
see that even though that wasn't the int
intention and I don't know if it's
what I want to go for just because I
have nothing else to
wear I do want to wear other things so
in the future I hope we can you know try
the the the thing with other outfits
rigged onto my body I hope that works
[Music]
out I need to get full eight alts I at
is it always
eight eight different color variations
really was it
[Applause]
eight really was it that many oh at
least pineapple is in a different
Universe yes pineapple is so perfect
with the swimsuit I'm so glad I had a
summer fee song to use the swimsuit
for and after a quick look I saw my
favorite number which is the most metal
number still available waa 666 that
number came up uh yesterday didn't it
sure you can have have it metal Squatch
please go
ahead but be careful of of the number it
it may be
dangerous El
Diablo vamos El
Diablo someone released a metal Chima
remix today today
[Music]
today Kim medal
6 hours ago
[Music]
the
the voice is kind of quiet a little bit
too drowned
out oh it's better
here make you
[Music]
cry he didn't use the
capella
what made it more difficult for
[Music]
yourself oh
nice sounds really cool wow so much
potential wasn't
there Chima Loi yeah yeah yeah cow carot
made a Loi one let's play this cuz this
one's also pretty good C carat learning
how to do everything crazy crazy crazy
lad Link in chat ah wait I already
clicked
way the this was
the metal one just
now and now I'm playing the LOI
one Loi is good for Super Chat
reading I like it I listened to it
before
can you hear it well
enough I'm going to read super chats
from by the release party of
Kim H
thumbnail is this one
yeah also just a reminder because we are
I have I have barely been like showing
it off but just to put it back into your
brain the jacket art is so
cool just trying to remind you that it
exists because it's not being used for
the thumbnail it's only on I guess the
streaming services maybe you guys are
seeing it maybe because like I don't
really use like Spotify Apple music Etc
so I don't get to see it that
often any chance that we can get it
without the logo oh
sure uh but no point in me putting it on
the stream right now right cuz you have
to like screen cap it it might not be so
pretty yeah yeah so if you guys actually
stream my song you get you get to
probably see this art more often than
me yeah there's been a lot of fan art
too even though the only source of
reference is this one picture so thank
you and I'm really flattered that
there's so much fanner part of
it so
cool I'll make you
[Music]
cry tearing it down just want to keep
calling let me see where is it I here
this one
well this
is the no logo
version manty an anti
[Music]
core you're not my
eny baby that to me here my voice just
screaming out loud no yeah
[Music]
y tearing it down do
just keep calling me
[Music]
a it's almost like a lullabi
cute okay so uh release party Super Chat
for7 d py d c d for the red super chat
unfortunately won't be able to make the
live release but I'm still so hyped for
Cima been rep playing the F with for it
and can't wait to for it to official be
added to all my playlist thank you I
hope you did that I hope you're
listening to it lots thank you so much
and yeah I think a lot of you have been
replaying the Fest vid until that
point I'm sure I'm sure that was worth
it like at least you got the most out of
you got a lot of value out of your
streaming
ticket nice nice C thank you for the
rest J pety action Z
for con performance
[Music]
to you
hi
hi thank you also for a pink Super Chat
kima's vocals are so intensely
percussive each line pulsing like a
series of hammer blowers on an anvil H
along with the sassy inflections on each
note your voice is such an intense sexy
Vibe amazing song and your best to date
instant favorite thank you
you chose some really fancy words to
describe my song
wow
damn thank you very much I'm
gladed glad that it's your favorite now
too once again Chimera has taken the
crown and now you're calling it your
favorite wow think about it I also
really love the the scene at the very
very very and where it's the doyu throne
have you guys noticed I'm sure you guys
have noticed at the very end Wawa sits
on the doyu
throne yeah she is the
usurper she took it for
herself and thus this Kima Wawa took the
crown of being your favorite song as
well oh my God all the connections wow
Game of Thrones Game of wers wa old
FRS wa takes what she deserves
exactly
period I love the scene on the roof of
the umbrella it's really pretty but I I
did feel like the umbrella is kind of
random cuz the umbrella is a freaking
plastic umbrella but we're in like a
fantasy environment felt a little bit uh
random to me but it was pretty so I I I
had no issue with it
[Music]
marry Poppin
wa who will take the crown from Idol laa
in the next
MV are we going to have beef
[Music]
again well tonight I'm having pork
yeah I I I do like the scene where first
they show the arena the Coliseum with
the swords in the ground and then the
waas walk in and then they point the
swords at each other that one is pretty
hype building pretty
epic makes you feel like oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] is about to go down here
[Music]
no House of
the like a
rade make you
cry tearing it down just
water keep calling
me J Tracy thank you for the pinky K are
so awesome I love the live and fifth
Fest and the single version just as much
of a banger thank
you it definitely went hard on the
vocals and kiala angels went all out
with the production lyrics so [\h__\h]
true Did you you didn't even hear the a
cappella yet at this point so oh my
God I I just love what we create
together each time it's it's selfish
because you know I'm just doing the the
kind of songs that I want to do but I
mean what kind of musician are you when
you're just making music that suits
other people's needs you should make
music that um you want to make
right I mean it's also smart to go do
stuff that other people will enjoy but I
think you can be the most satisfied and
the most happy when you do the things
that you want to
do I did like to I did enjoy to venture
out a little bit and do different things
in my album but when it comes to the
singles I feel most confident as I told
you before in doing K-pop Style songs
kada pop as we might now want to call
it also just because it works so well
with you know dancing alongside it which
is one of my specialties that I like to
um use
yeah and I'm just so happy because I
found the perfect team to work with with
for this kind of stuff I know I can rely
on them I know that if I ask them for a
song no matter what it will always be a
banger I will always be happy with it
like honestly I'm always like
overwhelmed with the things I want to
do with them because when sometimes the
songs are created from scratch and
sometimes there's like already madej
demos that they have that I can choose
from and when that's the case it's like
oh my God I want to do all of these
songs that you have shown me cuz they're
all amazing you really struggled with
them for real for real yeah I still
remember when I was
struggling uh like trying to find anyone
who could make songs like this who who
are not like really unreachable or super
expensive because they work for big big
big K-pop artists that I can never reach
that are out of my reach and then I
found kiwa's Angels first with K and
then more and more the G the the team
has you
know taken
shape and now I'm just like wow I
feel like in perfect form ready to run a
marathon so to say metaphorically
only yeah they know what I want and yeah
it's just a a perfect
perfect team up perfect
collaboration we're just vibing you know
yeah I have the I just have the perfect
reliable production team yeah for what I
want to do
mhm I'm so happy it's my team they make
the waa sound into a
thing isn't that nice
[Music]
like a
renegade I'll make you
[Music]
crying I don't know you're calling me
King you going to hear him all sing now
singing
louder
[Music]
like nice this is so good I love this
Loi
remix I just
R you're not my
enemy baby dad to me hear my voices
screaming
[Music]
out you're not my
anime you're not my anime
wifeu hey I already mentioned my some of
my favorite lines before you now my
enemy baby you're dead to me is
like I think my
[Music]
favorite yeah it's ice cold I love I
love the ice coldness I don't think I've
had such a
aggressive uh lyric before in my songs
so I enjoy singing it when I think of
angry things
H uh so yeah and moving on thank you Jim
Tracy crayons at thank you for the red
super chat cute profile picture by the
way while releasing her new song on my
birthday the 6th not the 5th I don't
have Spotify but I'll buy the song when
it releases on iTunes the perfect gift
to myself also here's a yearly reminder
that you're doing amazing my Koshi thank
you I agree that's a perfect gift happy
birthday I'm so glad I release it on
your birthday nice
congratulations MW MW MW
M happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday crayons
18 happy birthday to
you
congratulations thank you for supporting
my music and for supporting me I hope I
can give all that support back to you in
the form of
entertainment you're the
best keep on being you and doing what
you do game 8910 than moonight than for
the recip CH let's
go indeed indeed I'm a beep than MF Dan
moonat Dan gold boom Dan thank you
and Cruz Dan Sky Cadet D thank you
[Music]
and oh no oh wait that's not the part of
the
[Music]
song game 8910 do you ever remember the
super chats you
send feel like you
don't okay next up is like a dragon part
five now I can show you the thumbnail I
made for that in case you watched it
live and you never
saw what it turned out to be it's it
turned out to be these the casino and
our unfortunately
now not with us anymore friend who first
was our enemy first enemy then friend
then dead
too
[Music]
bad you're not my
eny baby you're dead to me hear my voice
it's screaming out loud no doubt
yeah yeaha Yeehaw
yeeha Texas version Chima
yea Yeehaw
partner what's up Kima version of Texas
what Texas version of
[Music]
Chima you're going to hear my
sing horsey horsey horsey horse
horsey horsey horsey horse
or
Li Callie Cy Cy op cie Cy I op c i
op oh
no Chad died where's the reaction to kop
version there it is
threee horses tied
together that's all you know about Texas
um
uh I don't know I I know I know it's
very um I know I know it's very uh
conservative here and I know there's
maybe a lot of sand and and little
tumble weeds going
around probably not anymore that
much and the guns and um you know
there's um that one place that we had a
convention
in young Sheldon grew up in uh Texas
there
saloons old western movies yeah
um
that's that's it Texas has a funny shape
Texas has a really funny recognizable
shape that's one thing and
um
yeah uh yeah that's all I can really say
cows and the the the male version of a
cow
hats yeah hats
indeed they probably like barbecue I
would
imagine but that's just you know
my imagination Cowboys
Bulls
mhm mhm Texas is the America of America
really it is very American out of all
the states that America has I would say
Texas is like in a top free of being
American it's very
American yes everybody surely wears
boots of Spurs mhm Pro propane propane
tank yeah I don't know how that connects
to Texas but I believe
you Sak didn't I say steak big belt
buckles obviously all of this is very
much just um cliche
[Music]
what is King of the Hill is that a movie
I don't know about
that haven't seen
that a cartoon a TV
show animated
uhhuh I see I
[Music]
see okay moving on unknown D unknown D
unknown d unkown d Unown thank you I see
you're singing my
song you already know it by heart more
than me probably take a for the s d Cruz
D Jack Redwing thank you for the pinky o
from Europe K today is my birthday and
you're my greatest present today thank
you happy birthday Jack belated but
still better later than never
congratulations I get to be a present
but you can have me anytime every day on
YouTube just have to turn on your
YouTube and then I'll be on your tally
or your
phony or your
PC anytime W
[Music]
underand Unity chat than you for the
pinky you and your team have created a
masterpiece of Kim right my favorite
homo song Now The Hook is so hypnotizing
and the song is powerful and caty M the
MV is crazy it has some really sexo but
also Beautiful Moments All Tied
perfectly to the song Thank You O I'm so
happy to hear
that I'm glad you like it I'm surprised
really I didn't think so many people
would um like this type of K-pop cuz
this is like called kind of girl crush
black pink Vibes you know
I didn't think uh it would be this
popular with y'all I'm
surprised H seems like we chose the
right
[Music]
song we have a crash on you side makes
sense I have some black Pink songs in my
library also you you do like this
direction you absolutely killed it thank
you it has dark energy yeah yeah you
guys just like the dark energy you like
to be edgy
chickens it's powerful and I like that I
can see how that speaks to you guys
yeah
[Music]
nice ooh this part is
cute nice arrangement
[Music]
I'm a chicken hear me
book you guys want to feel more powerful
by listening to Chima if you guys merch
you can become a Kimera maybe or is that
just a triple chicken I don't
know Kim chicken chicken chicken
chicken chick chicky chicky chick a
chicky chicky bang
bang anyway thank you un chat and I'm
moving on to spank andhim with a red
Super Chat thank you than
hearty heart eyes and cat ears in a
baseball bat could this be any more
perfect no it could not I know
honestly this is Peak waa
Peak thank you you are cultured you
understand what is Peak thank you so
much stenheim
Cardinal crowbar D Jimmy weep shooter
Dan link
D Jimmy we should again thank you D
Michael H
D oh thank you eating my ass check D
lunch box D rice of D tro d d and again
thanks for the pinky MV might be too
powerful it had a guy my size on my
knees oh then knocked me onto the floor
and I still can't get up oh my god do I
need to call an ambulance your dancing
was divine the backgrounds were so good
your team jels so well to ever and it
makes absolute magic happen 100 out of
10 exactly that's what I'm
[Music]
saying thank you so
true yeah I already talked about how how
happy I am with my destined meeting with
my current
team I couldn't be more grateful thank
you
jow jow wow wow I can't get up still
okay I'll be sending that
ambulance oh God I hope you're going to
be okay please wait please hold on a
little
longer Wawa ambulance is coming we we we
we we
we knock knock
knock who's there W ambulance is here
let me in oh I'm on the floor though
ah what the hell am I going to get in oh
well [\h__\h] I don't know ah well okay um
well
um [\h__\h] uh damn well I guess I'll guess
I'll guess I'll
go can't help crawling to the door don't
leave okay faster
faster okay okay
that was the door opening okay
here look in German we say h when you're
about to do something that needs a lot
of
strength okay now you should be back on
your little
fees okay goodbye have a nice day um
even though ambulance time is over I'm
going to turn on the siren when I leave
okay byebye
[Music]
[Applause]
okay a in oh good good greeting good
greeting you should always say Al in to
your ambulance when they
leave HCK check cups D oh you were also
there let's go just another K Dan Jimmy
we should Dan
I dewi which means you little [\h__\h] oh my
God I win in time means your little
[\h__\h] Thomas the thank you D Nova floresa
thank
you Brandon poell thank you oh favorite
let's go lunchbox Brandon power again
thank you so much w
flattering
Lord 4
water to the pinky just got home right
on time to see the kfp timing brain
strike again what are we doing I have no
idea what I was up
to thank you though for the pinky that's
it
I'm going to go now and finish my
cooking I'm going to make the
laxa
laxa and I'm going to show you a picture
probably but I'm going to turn the going
to turn the the the the catsu because
one side is a lot darker than the
[Music]
other but I already cut it open and it's
at least uh the meat
is
through I don't know if that's how you
say it in English probably not in German
we say it's
through
basically when it's uh yeah yeah you
know U it's it's done it as cooked for
yeah yeah okay okay okay yeah so now I
kept on teasing you but now for real now
now for real for real we can say it are
you ready I'm going to see you on
Wednesday for members only I hope I'll
get everything
working I'll try my
best the thing is my mommy is coming
tomorrow she's already here uh but she's
at my brother's place and tomorrow she's
coming over to my place and I'm going to
do some stuff and I don't know what time
she's leaving on the day after tomorrow
um we're probably not going to be able
to prepare that much while she's still
there but I think it'll be
fine I hope she compliments yeah I want
to show her the table and the chair and
everything yeah it's going to be good
say hi to her okay S no regards to M and
BR yes I will I will although I'm not
meeting my
bro not this time I mean he's I could
always meet him but
uh I she surely she's seen Kima yeah
yeah yeah but I mean it's not really her
kind of music so um I'm sure she
appreciated it though for one it
is have her try frity
Trucking been a while since M told came
here well she's not going to be on
stream she's just going to be at my
place and I'm going to not
stream maybe the metal remix yeah maybe
or even the lovei version
metamor the metaphor he has got his own
place my mom's first at his place
because um she's helping him get some
stuff done at his place like shortening
the
curtains tearing it down yeah we already
talked about B going at going to
ofai you need to go me okay me too
probably then in German we
say see you tomorrow today after
tomorrow for H members
only but you know I'm always on
Twitter chronically on
Twitter thank you for watching hope you
had fun go play the game it's for free
on Steam
[Music]
oh bye bye and
stream on YouTube and Spotify and apple
music Amazon music Etc I want you uh it
to go to 1 million on YouTube but we
can't forget about streaming it on the
streaming services every now and then
please thank you I love you you the
best byebye
[Music]
for