[Music]
[Applause]
a
n
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
e
[Applause]
n
[Music]
ke
K Hello Hello Hello Hello
Ki
and
Chima but but I'm my own version of
Chima
[Music]
hello what does Chima make okay okay so
number one
snake no that's a
b number two lion
wow yeah good and
dragon good morning
[\h__\h] and together we are
Mima yay I mean what else uh otherwise
it's kind of difficult to make a track
and talk I mean some dragons they're
like uh don't don't take my my money Mr
Hobbit uh uh well I cannot quote
anything he
says uh but he sounds very grumpy and
low voice and uh what does he say what's
the famous word he says again uh like me
deep uh talks about the me deep what
does he say give me a famous famous word
I am fire I'm deaf cumber batch
noises oh that's that's a famous one
huh I I am fire I am death I don't know
I I can't go that
low my teeth are Spears Spears spares I
never I will never figure that word out
my claws are
swords yeah um so some people may say
this is not how a Cima looks like oh um
well I say to you maybe not your Cima I
think if I actually I'm not sure in our
MV I think it's this consolation but
honestly I might be wrong no actually I
think I'm wrong I think in the MV it's a
different
constellation but there can be several I
think I've seen this constellation
before but I think the most Cannon is
the one with with a goat a lion a goat
and a
snake m
but I chose Dragon cuz dragon is way
cooler like a goat what the [\h__\h] that's
not
really scary to me and snake kind of
also I honestly got to say it's kind of
lame also our Kima our Kima is like
three heads next to each other we had
this conversation
before uh discussing how I
think you know for me I I thought that's
more common but the that's less common
appar
it's two heads and the snake is just the
tail of the animal which base bases on a
lion I guess mostly I don't know no no
actually no I don't know who
knows in the end it doesn't exist so we
can create our own version right the
snake G gives the Venom poison
a you know what you could have possibly
done then you could have oh a scorpion
tail would have been sick oh [\h__\h] yeah
Manticore no you could have given it
like bat
wings then then it's got
Wings one won't show me like what your
feet look like in the other I think it's
just um pretty much no shoes is from
what I've seen in the sketch
but he might have just not been finished
and then we cut it off
so yeah manticor from AR guys is so cute
that a man well I'm not a manticor I'm a
Chima but maybe next song maybe I should
follow a pattern like Ena and call my
songs from now on like mythical
creatures like Chimera manticor is that
even a myth is that even considered a
mythical creature I know I am a mythical
creature thank you you're welcome yeah
you're probably happy with that answer
just just make me bare
Foods oh what the [\h__\h] is a cockc what
that sounds like cockroach or something
with a chicken a male chicken magic or
is mythical let's go I feel like that
would be a cool title I think um kiwa's
angels are listening to me right now so
write it down write it down write it
down Manor could be a pretty cool title
for a
song and what would it be about maybe
poisoning people or some a person in my
life who's poisoning people that's what
you could make it
about
H maybe cockatrice is a chicken with a
snake for a
tail uh is is the head of the snake the
end of the tail or is the tail of the
snake the end of the
tail probably the head right basilisk
basilisk yeah that one I
know that one why is there so many
chickens involved in these
things interesting that's two that's two
of these creatures that all involved
chickens maybe they were just like you
know all over when these words were
coined chickens were already I mean
chicken a chicken was the first animal
on the whole wide world after all
everything starts from a chicken or from
the
[Music]
egg that aside put putting that aside I
think chickens were just around
everywhere they were mingling they were
mingle kfp rise up we are we are strong
kfp
are you guys hearing the beautiful
instrumental of Chima right
now D it down
just yeah it's so dope if you want you
can listen to that on your own side as
well it's uh been released alongside the
real track so you can listen to it now
I'm using it as my bgm cuz uh I don't
think I'll ever besides today do that
but it's [\h__\h] dope don't back it up
don't back it up keep that aim I got pH
drop you insan the backing vocals are so
good though yeah well the backing vocals
are not in this instrumental because
that's you know usually we use a clean
instrumentals with no backup vocals for
these releases but I have my own version
with backup
vocals yeah love that we got a timer yes
I prepared a timer it is 48 minutes
until uh the release of the MV then I
will serve you the MV I will serve you
the MV okay I will serve you
theera MV
Kima start to Ste has a CO sound I will
serve the Kima MV
yeah okay I
[Music]
know
and in this stream I'll be um just
talking a little bit about the song and
showing you some stuff and let you
listen to some stuff ah Johnny in the
chat Johnny in the chat let's go Johnny
Johnny Johnny Johnny oh
Johnny I think there's like a German
song with your name k might know it
although K is pretty young maybe he
doesn't know it why is Johnny not a mod
Johnny WR ah there we go are we can make
Johnny I
[Laughter]
mother I'm I'm
old okay I made you made you mod so now
you stand out better you're already
shining on your own so you don't really
need
it yay oh there we go oh K is also okay
K is a mod from before nice what do you
guys think about Manticore did you write
it down
yeah okay so number one on the list is
also by the way K I like how you always
put in like a k i r a in there it's like
you're jyp I know I see what you're
doing I see what you're doing can we get
a griffin next oh no Griffin as a song
title sounds kind of
lame no I reject this
offer I
reject so for people who don't know
but I think by now you should definitely
know k k made a lot of my songs a lot of
them and uh is also the producer of
chimera and also made Wild Card which I
performed with Chloe in the Fest but we
uh that was not an original song from us
no k's original song If you want to
listen to it it's on K's YouTube channel
a cabus ooh that's kind of cool yeah ah
could put that into
consideration amazing producer for sure
yeah also the the creator of four
blood and and many of my other songs as
I said Sparks Sparks do you some album
songs yeah
pineapple audio
St wife wife Wu wifeu wife I close
enough okay okay okay enough suggestions
let me show it to you you've already
seen it on Twitter woo cute oh my God
cute
cute this is the new
updated
logo kiar takanashi is not allowed to
exist takanashi kiar it is it has been
adjusted so this is the new jacket it's
drawn by one bin Lee W Lee my my my my
my my choice of artist has gone through
thank God it was a little bit uh sudden
I organized getting an artist a little
bit a little bit too late um which was
part of the reasons why you know it took
a little while for releas sing the song
and the MV and the uh logo and the art
being a little bit late while the song
was done ages
ago um but yeah this is a artist from
Korea who I've had my eyes on for a long
time because um they draw a lot of cool
gijinkas what's the English word for
gijinka again
um humanized versions of like uh before
they did
like
po I think and P world you know and um
oh damn in the same sentence Oh [\h__\h] we
still say ginka I also say ginka
yeah not fies no
anthropomorphic interesting word and uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I've been following
them
forever uh and I just really like their
style yeah and I thought for this
uh jacket I would like uh maybe
something that Strays away a little bit
at least from the typical anime
look and this one does that it's really
cool wait let's look at it again from
bigger
size so we have like a cool arm that is
seemingly
cursed has some magic in it or so lots
of golden elements really nice a
microphone that is aimed at my crotch or
should I say no I won't say it
today h yeah overall the outfit oh it's
so
beautiful it's so elegant so mature
isn't it my feathers look a little bit
different from usual the top head thing
I'm not sure what it is it could be
chicken wings it could be different kind
of like it reminds me I think a little
bit of like Fire Emblem
um um the white-haired chick I feel like
in in her one of her outfits she she has
something that reminds me of this but I
might be completely wrong right now yeah
but I I just look so good yeah speak
your truth w
w w w w
what okay okay so far so good then I
want to show you some
screenshots of the MV ahead of time oh
my God spicy sneak
peek let's
[Music]
go the warm speaker of here
leaks
leaking Le I'm leaking some stuff now
okay so wait I made a I made a little I
made a little thing T oh that's um I
think that's the last one I wanted no oh
no it's the wrong
order uh then I guess this way a yeah
okay okay okay okay something like this
you've seen in
the it's all cled make small no like
this something like this you've seen in
the uh uh teaser already right should I
make it you know what I'm I might just I
might just make it big for
you I'm I'm not sure why hands are
involved it's just cool okay maybe Cano
has more thoughts behind why hands are
involved but it's just a a cool element
and yeah here you see a nice silhouette
but my eyes are glowing uh is just a
little bit too far away to see it but
that's one thing that caught your
attention I know one good thing sorry
moved my microphone one good thing about
this default outfit W is you can see the
shape of my body is so good yes hands
are for serving yeah hands are used to
serve I don't think that was really the
intention the thought behind it yeah
sure I think it's just supposed to look
kind of mysterious and stuff
yeah hands oo hand fetish people are
being
served yeah but really cool lightning
here um I like it next we have this is
by the way in the order of what appears
in the MV and we have more glowy eyes
waha but in a more abstract kind of even
even more or less I don't know also
abstract uh area yeah I like this I like
this this oh this is like um dusk I
don't know what do you call this kind of
lightning I feel like it may low key
appear
IRL uh under the Moonlight I don't know
is it is dusk dusk the right word maybe
haze h Haze okay yeah it gives me
Twilight Vibes maybe I'm a
vampire I'm coming for
blood I might be coming for blood oh
[\h__\h] next you saw this in the teaser too
I think wait can we see what the [\h__\h]
those animals are there are some
wings uh I think the middle is a lion
but it doesn't have the the the
wave
wave main I don't know and I I see a
dragon and I think the right thing might
be a goat actually there is no snake
here unless unless it's at the tail and
then we have four animals
involved I can kind of see the main not
it's not as fluffy as what I have on me
right now but yeah this is our cool
Chima um we are together with the
release of the MV we are releasing a DIY
paperfolding origami
set with instructions you can create
exactly this model of a Cima yourself
approximate hours for creation are uh
tested by um aan and
yo uh and they have come up to uh 23
hours
without
breakes I did not let them go on brakes
so that was a lot of folding involved
and a lot of a lot of looking at the
instructions mhm just kidding we're not
selling this but it would be an idea a
little bit too
intricate oh next wa let me see am I
still on time okay not really but that's
fine I I have some extra time and this
is Wawa the white Wawa really cute cute
with her pinkish Vibes again but you see
I have some backup dancers now yeah
they're just silhouettes of
me but I think it's pretty cool yeah we
we we have a hired a few dancers a few
versions of myself we have acquired to
dance together with me I I think in the
MV has a good impact um also the
location is kind of like a big big
castle so to say with lots of shiny
floors
yeah lava
Blanca we're going to have a fight again
who who likes whoos more more if W
Blanco or what's the other one what's
the other word which one's more
popular don't
fight another white Wawa as I so happen
to be kind of white here okay I took a
closeup because it's so pretty I took
these screenshots by the way there was
so many screenshot
moments wa The Blanco and wa Noir M but
I'm actually on a car here I'm sitting
on a car yeah this
scene it's it belongs to the rap part oh
yeah so the song is already released
worldwide on Spotify and and uh uh
YouTube music so you can actually listen
to it even if you don't have Spotify you
can just go on my channel go to releases
click on gima it just doesn't have the
MV yet the MV is coming in 36 minutes
but in theory you can listen to it
worldwide already uh Amazon music Apple
music and iTunes are lagging a little
bit behind those will be indeed locally
at midnight in each
country so if you live in America and
you you don't use Spotify you use iTunes
then just wait for midnight okay thank
you for the support so far thank you for
listening to it so far on any platform
um if you could listen to it on any of
them I would be really
grateful H the The Comeback of laor I
like this scene there's this this is
like uh a little bit more from fur
further away but there's this one scene
where it's like closeup and I'm peeking
through the chains and it's really cool
you guys got to take screenshots of that
too looks really nice trust
me yeah I am in Chains and now I will be
the breaker of my own chains let me
free more waa no here it's a little bit
more like fantasy setting but we do have
laser let's go laser laser party I think
we can throw a Rafe party
here I'm dancing by the way this is me
dancing and here we have oh [\h__\h] shit's
going down they're going to fight who's
going to
survive Idol WWA by the way that was a
like a Coliseum kind of setting which I
think is really cool and is where a
Chima fits right in yeah this is after
we already took down the Chimera and
it's only us
left so I don't W this is a really cool
scene that partially a little bit in a
tiny way was teased in the teaser and
then this the the last one I show you is
mean on an elevated stage and this time
the castle is kind of like darkened wa
it's like
goofy let's go spoiler there is a Chima
I'm the
Chima okay 33 minutes you know what time
it is
now I'm going to play you something
really
cool remember for previous releases I
let you uh listen to to the Acappella
version of songs that we made with the
kian's angels because the the Acappella
versions are just so [\h__\h] dope
because we do a lot of backup vocals a
lot a lot really many many muchos Becca
vocals which is good because it's just
on its own even without the instrumental
it just sounds so good
so let me
let me uh take you on a journey with
your I think I can play it over here I
will shut up and you shall enjoy this I
think I will upload this separately on
YouTube so maybe people can make a remix
out of it if they want to I don't know
okay listen to this
masterpiece oh wait it's too quiet I'll
I'll restart
[Music]
oh no fell into the unnown left me
bleeding heartless all
alone no
control don't you dare
apologize turn my back and the cold
night listen up cuz here's some advice
you're out the time way out the line
it's taking over like r i for a night
I'll make you cry C teing it down
just keep calling me no think
so got me
Twisted taking the crown now you calling
me King you going to here Sing Now
[Music]
sing don't back it up don't back it up
keep that aim I got thought that will
drive you insane come over if you like
we'll have a lot of fun but I got a lot
of B do what I want make sure you don't
forget it's an Army on my back sick I'm
just sadistic not living in the life in
the I want to see the way you
bleed it's taking over like r i for
night I'll make you cry C tearing it
down to just water keep calling me no
think
so got me
Twisted AIT taking the crown are you
calling me King you going to hear him
I'll sing sing
it L
life I want it all so give me some more
Flames bur me up down into my core oh
you wish I'd stay down but then I just
R you're not my
eny baby you're dad me he my voes
screaming out loud no
[Applause]
doubt
tearing it down
just keep calling me yes
think
got taking the CR now you calling
meing
[Music]
hear
oh it's so beautiful isn't it oh my
God a it's so cool
wow so sick thank you
big shout out to
Johnny who did all of the mixing as far
as I know it's fine I
know yeah and and K and money they're
crazy because they come up with all of
this holy [\h__\h] how can you come up with
so many different voice topl lines
harmonies backup vocals oh the goats the
absolute goats of myera but oh yeah no
goat here
Johnny the goat W Angels slave once
again here the W angels are my
Chimas which one is you he wants a
stereo version uploaded I'll try is this
stereo I can whatever you want me to
upload I'll upload on on YouTube yeah
cuz this stuff is so good I always love
listening to these Acappella versions
from our songs yeah did you did you hear
all the overlapping amazingness M all
the overlapping vocals you have to
listen to all of them okay take them all
in yeah sleep talking is a wow wow wow
wow wow sleep talking is kind of crazy
so juicy yeah so that was that uh it
will be uploaded separately so feel free
to listen to that and if you want to
make something out of it like a like a
little little bit of a remix then you're
welcome to do so couldn't it
did we ever get that aella oh sleep
talking yeah for sure I'm pretty
[Music]
sure oh Johnny is crying in my DMs he
really wants the stereo
uploaded let's fulfill him that wish all
right okay guys I'm going to mute the
bgm because now I'm going to call a
little special
guest uh first time I think audible on
my stream I
think
H one of K was angels and a genius oh
but wait wait before I call Moone I
think I was going to read out the
statement wait wait sorry sorry sorry
for the teas money is coming but
actually I I have statement I asked for
statements from K and Johnny uh who
worked on the song so uh let me read
that out first okay otherwise I don't
know when I do
it okay so let me quote
Johnny quote working with K is always
the best she's someone we never want to
stop working
with this song is pretty different for
us when it comes to our work with Wawa
but I think the sound really ended up
working so well for
her it felt really different for me too
I mean for some of you guys maybe it
sounds the same or so like K-pop is
K-pop but no even within K-pop there's
different Vibes and this is a vibe that
I I wasn't really planning to try out
yet but you know the circumstances uh
continuing her vocals on the song are
some of her best if not the best yeah I
got praised so much for my vocals this
one my ego is blowing up help
me yeah thank you Johnny for your sweet
words I feel I feel
flattered and I'm from K we have also a
statement here we go I quote I had so
much fun working on Kima it sounds
pretty different from the stuff I
usually make and I think with this song
kada was able to show a brand new darker
edgier and more powerful side and she
totally aced I also think vocally this
has to
be her best performance yet which is
really impressive oh my God that's two
people saying that oh really tells you
something yeah and they they were the
ones who heard my voice raw okay raw
like that meat they served us
inik okay K Johnny thank you so much so
sweet yeah it's a it's a different kind
of sound but it's really badass and now
it's time to get uh the opinion of our
beloved lyric
genius
money going to
[Music]
call there she
is
hello my girl
Mone hi how you doing I'm good I'm good
how are you my love I'm I'm happy you're
on the T money you're on the T yeah
we're so close to the release guys are
you excited who's
excited well most of them already
listened to the songs of well the Envy
the Envy Envy very special Envy yeah
yeah Mo maybe some of you guys don't
know Mooney relatively recently started
like V tubing right when did you
start February oh oh that is really that
was really more recent than I thought it
was yeah like end of February it's been
like a month oh how is it going you like
it it it's I love it I love it I love it
you're so
cute this is yeah our first time like
together on stream like this yeah yeah
yeah thank you for asking me to be here
you're welcome you know you being uh in
life to D now makes it kind of like
easier because it's it's less weird than
if you were just flesh
person a flesh person okay yeah yeah
this this way we we fit we're both anime
yeah yeah we we we're anime girls yeah
so first of all do you want to like cuz
I was just giving the opinions of the
others do you want to like add something
to it oh oh oh okay I have to agree this
is by far your best book of performance
you did so good my girl and when we were
when we were recording
um yeah we were we were together so that
that was something different for this
time too yeah I was in Japan and uh
should should we kind of tell the story
about how this came about yeah cuz
normally I just record from home but oh
God okay okay just I mean I already told
the story a few times so I think most
people know why we made this song in the
first place but just really quickly to
give you a rundown uh I wanted to
participate in your original song
contest but I realized the deadline was
coming up really soon like we had like
what five days or so maybe originally
yeah and I was with you uh in Japan
hanging out and was like
money do you have can I Window Shop can
I Window Shop do you have a demo that I
can maybe quickly record and send in
your vision even if we don't make it we
can just release it as its own
song yeah and and and you we went
through a few and you were like that one
yeah that one and it was mind you it was
half done it wasn't complete it was like
completely like not to a point where we
could release it and you're like that
one and I'm like okay so I messag I
messaged the others and I'm like we got
to we got to finish this and I couldn't
Rec it was a mess I couldn't record CU I
was in a Airbnb
in but we did it we did it it took we we
finished the rest of it in like 2 days
and then we came together in person to
record and we did so good the
circumstances were kind of scuffed and I
felt bad for rushing you guys and then
in the end we didn't even make it but it
might be better this way um no no this
is good yeah uh so yeah you you guys had
like two days to finish the song and
then how I think Johnny mixed it in one
or two
days
yeah yeah speed speed it was really fast
speed ran and I was so pissed off cuz
they extended the deadline by was it a
week or a month
a week maybe I think like a like a week
or so maybe two and I see it and I'm I'm
like no [\h__\h] way and I write to you
guys I'm so sorry we rushed ourselves to
do this in like 5 days because now they
[\h__\h] extended it for a week oh my God
yeah yeah but like we we sent it in on
time but yeah this way we had a little
bit more time to polish but it came out
so good and um there there's something I
must expose you I must expose you there
something there's something I know I
know what it's going to be you know what
it is you
know so guys at the the beginning of the
original version there's an
alib you can do it then you shall do it
then okay okay okay ready
[Music]
ready oh
[\h__\h] in the very first like 3 seconds
right of the that was yeah that was the
first alib and uh you you do it so well
I tried so hard but you were sitting
next to me and I was so
embarrassed it was so funny I wish I
wish I have recordings of the attempts
but we sat there for about 30 minutes
trying to figure out what to do it was
so funny and then you came up with
something new like the uh the the uh
what did we do in the end the The Higher
One yeah like a note there but but can
you do it
again again for free yeah okay for you
yeah now here okay
okay that was that was lacking now you
didn't have the the
the there it is there it is and I just
couldn't do it because it was
so even though she gave me a million
examples I was just
like but it came out good it came out
good the end result is good yeah we had
to cancel that part the other parts were
cool you you you you really praised me a
l when we were recording and this is the
the one time where I had like feedback
kind of I mean I feel back in the day
for hoton and heart Challenger I
recorded it with the producer back then
too but ever since then I've been
recording from home ever since I moved
don't call me Minecraft
villager I should have just challenged
my inner Minecraft
villager yeah it was really nice to do
it together with you on my side and
giving me like some instructions
yeah you were you were you had um you
had some confidence issues I think
because you kept being like oh that
wasn't good that wasn't good let me redo
it and I was like no stop it you're
perfect yeah actually in some parts I
was like trying to do more new takes
even though you were already satisfied
yeah you you need to have confidence
you're so good and you know we've been
working together for so long now since
like almost two it's coming up on two
years in a few months
and uh your improvement has been just
crazy and I'm so happy to always work
with you thank you I'm also really happy
that I found you guys because this is
like you I don't even you just I say I
want a song and you throw 20 songs at me
that I like and I I don't even oh it's
actually overwhelming I like everything
you guys do and you're like you're like
the perfect team for the direction I
want to go towards yeah it's perfect
it's a match made in heaven
yeah also one more thing for like
embarrassing stuff people were saying in
the chat when they were listening to the
a capella that it's oh so lud when you
know the part that goes
like and then the example from you from
your demo was however way more lud
though no com it sounded like you were
like going to heaven and that moment
speaking you have you have spread this
agenda about me and it's time it's time
we clear the air okay I am a wholesome
girl I did not do
anything what about
[Laughter]
those you were too embarrassed to even
do those in front of me yeah but I I
like I think I was able to do it but
just like less less loot than you yeah
you ended up being able to do it but at
first you were like I can't I can't do
it you have so much you have so much
like I don't know not like you in your
when you sing you show so much
confidence and it really blows me away
it's so cool I oh I Aspire and guys she
writes the lyrics and stuff but she also
you create like a lot of top lines too
right yeah so so basically to clear it
up uh Kira does the production so the
instrumental demo and Johnny played the
demo let's play it by the way Johnny's
singing in half of the demo um and then
Johnny and I do The Melodies and then I
do the lyrics and then uh then uh Johnny
doeses the mixing yeah that's generally
how it goes sometimes we kind of share
some of the roles but generally that's
our role so but one big part um that you
do that really really helps me is you
singing the demo for me so I know how to
sing it but you have so much personality
in your voice like I've heard I've I've
received other like demos from other
producers and like you know other people
where they sing it or they let maybe
sometimes they let like Vocaloid sing it
and so on which when K does it it turns
out really dope but you know sometimes I
get really lackluster demos and I I
don't really have like uh something that
inspires me there like I just have to go
off of how I I think I should sing it
but you you sing it so I want to be like
that I aspire to be like that you sound
so good you actually your versions are
always better than my versions but yeah
it really helps me it gives me like a
direction to go towards and makes me
feel less embarrassed when I try to do
things the way you do which maybe
normally I wouldn't do it no you see you
see the there there's a there's a
double-edged sword to everything you
might think that but you know what you
have a a higher range I struggle to say
some of the things you do then do you
you're like and I'm
like no your range is strle your orang
is really big I don't think it's I don't
think mine's bigger no I think I think
so I think so well thank
you I love you m I think you were you
were a big reason why my singing in my
singles in my original songs improved I
would
say well no yeah yeah that was all you
that's why doy you has so much sass just
because I was copying you
we we we
serve something see you we're serving
[Music]
something today we serve Kima and later
also see and a little bit of
that well actually I have something to
um play for you guys um okay we'll just
say it's pre-recorded because it's a bit
difficult when we're not in the same
place we we had stuff uh uh issues but
yeah yeah if it's not an off collab then
singing together kind of difficult but
we sang Kima together for
you do you want to hear it yeah do you
want to hear you want to hear you want
to hear right okay but then with that
I'll I'll kick you out so you can say
your
goodbye okay goodbye I love you wa and
bye and everybody else Johnny said I
hope you guys
enjoy thank you so much for coming by
bye-bye bye-bye cute sweetie
girl she's so cute she streams regularly
now so go check her out guys uh check
out her Twitter M yeah I'll I'll
probably um retweet something of her so
you can find her she's so cute she's
such a good
singer she also uploaded uh her own
version of was it was it do you or was
it
Sparks was it sleeptalking one of my
songs she has her own version on the
channel yeah do you I guess it's do you
it do you do you sleep talking do you do
you yeah do
you so if you listen to that you'll be
like ah okay I see what Kiwa meant with
um the demo is
[Laughter]
better yeah okay okay so both of them oh
okay there you go I do want to hear a
spark Mar's mody version one day so we
have 11 minutes to go I'm going to play
the of us together uh just give
me one moment to put it on OBS uh what's
this one what's this
the ah this one okay I think it's this
one
[Music]
filter chroma key sorry the
video still need the
chroma really
quickly
oh the grandma
key yeah there were some fun Parts feel
free to listen closer to the a capella
where you can hear it clearly
okay
um might be a little bit loud in the
first moment we'll see we'll see how it
goes let me let me let me play this
let's
go
or yeah wait wait wait actually I think
oh okay let's
go three two one go oh
[\h__\h] I'm so sorry money I forgot about
that okay
I'm so sorry what I have done to
you I
I sorry you were crma key a little bit
too hard what have I done to
you I have I have oh my God I feel
really
bad okay now we can do it and fixed
it right here we go
startle 2 one go
oh no into
the let me bed
in
not you are time way out of line it's
taking over like a
renade for I'll make you
crying it
down keep calling me
[Music]
think the crown now you're calling me
King you're going to hear a Sing Now
sing it ready
[Music]
y don't back it up don't bre it up keep
that aim I got thoughts that'll drive
you insane over if you like we'll have a
lot of fun but I got a lot of I do what
I want make sure you don't forget it and
Army on my back say I'm sick I'm just
living in the light I want to see the
way you
B it's thinking over like renegate I it
I'll make you
crying it down
just keep call me
think
[Music]
got the now you're calling meing you're
going to hear s Now sing
it Lou
like
I want it all so give me some more
please me up into my oh you wish i' stay
down but then I just
R you're not my
enemy baby you're to me
mying out loud
[Music]
no
weing
[Music]
call the call me you're going toar
sing
K la la la la la
k
oh
oopsie yeah H I was saying here Link in
the chat for money I will add it to the
VOD later uh so because this was a
surprise so it's not there yet but if
you're watching the V then go to the
description now and you'll find her but
now now now you can go through the link
in the description if you didn't know
her Twitter already now you know she's
so good
right oh yeah hey the the one Mooney
there commenting that's her that's the
real money yeah she's so good she's so
good I wish I was more like
her yay new Kam Yoshi
no you to you two tored up we
did yeah we we need to sing more
together don't we I love her she's such
an inspiration to me she's so good and
the lyrics She rides are so good
too thank you so much
guys yeah thank you Mooney for doing
that together with me we are so close to
the MV
release four and a half
minutes and then there's like a little
obviously Premiere countdown and
countown countdown
and I will uh redirect you sometimes it
doesn't work the redirection for some
people it doesn't work so uh just go
there on your own please don't miss out
on the premiere of Kima so um yeah I
want to say thank you to everybody who
was hyping it up and getting really
excited for it since ever since the Fest
um cuz I performed it um in the Fest and
everybody was like holy [\h__\h] she's
serving she's mothering uh I recorded
this in a uh like with my accent suit
which is not as good quality um some
parts are like a little bit wobbly um
not as good in terms of motion capture
but I think uh it still turned out to be
a really dope badass music video so look
forward to that I'm just so happy to
finally be able to bring to you this
masterpiece that we have had ready for a
while now because we wanted to release
it actually way way way
before yeah and then we were like okay
well we're we're not making it into your
Orion song what else do we want to when
do we want to release this you know what
I want to release this for the Fest and
show you guys a completely new song at
the Fest yeah oh my God okay I think I
got a like yeah ending screen
soon um but make sure guys to check your
favorite streaming music streaming
service uh when hits midnight unless
it's Spotify and it's already there and
YouTube music is also already there and
make sure to watch the MV many many
times let's get it to perhaps even 1
million at some point would be really
really nice and and keep on streaming it
so that I get a higher budget next
time
everybody also speaking of 1 million uh
Fire and Ice reached 1 million today
which I mean this almost seems like all
of according to kak you
know as if it was on purpose that we are
you know we're done with streaming fire
nice next is Chima
yeah oh yeah don't forget about you know
every once in a while you can stream
pineapple sleep talking and so on as
well yeah yeah don't foret about the
album
songs yeah oh my song with uh with cie
yeah yeah yeah the MV is on her
Channel yeah yeah okay so I guess I
guess oh my God uh clap clap next MV
exactly I'm so nervous now you guys
really love the song so far and I'm so
happy um for getting so much positive
feedback a lot of you guys have been
saying this is now your favorite W song
which um is difficult to top you know
until now everything was a banger so
that is quite the achievement I would
say oh might be my favorite song Thank
you please listen to it lots of times
okay I go Kima bye-bye M Kima see you
tomorrow for Yakuza and yeah enjoy the
MV stream it stream it many
times byebye