[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
and welcome to the first I would say
full collaboration but now we have
Council so it's the first almost full
collaboration of Halloween
[Music]
[Applause]
this is actually
probably watching this
like this card I see the tweet from
Discord yesterday with all the screens
like I guess
so we're glad to have the Discord
support today and hopefully also the
viewers support today because uh today
will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting events
[Music]
exactly and the drivers no not here no
no not here everybody is here I may be a
bad driver but I'll drive you guys nuts
I think we shall start with some
introductions of each member and now
let's start with um Indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
second generation thank you everyone I
can't wait
um to not be um the last last place at
least
okay what about
oh oh hello oh officers
IUD generation one so my motivation
tonight is
um to show you my practice I guess
that's all thank you oh show me what you
got
[Music]
hi attention please I'm popular Rainey
from whole life ID generation 2. my goal
today is to be number one in your heart
and also not that last in the race
yeah I've heard you were good you and
Iris have heard good good good news
about you I'll do my best
yesterday right right yeah we did
nice thank you for joining
bye
hi Moon Moon
hello my name is
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
[Music]
what's the motivation for today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay but in the middle it's okay
not last oh okay
become the last in your heart
the blast in someone's heart is that
such a good thing
yeah okay
how about
hi hello hello everyone I'm Ariana from
Whole Life Indonesia and thank you so
much for inviting me to this collab I'm
so happy though I'm so excited let's go
thank you
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right it will be fine it will be
fine
hi guys
hello
what
for my motivation I plan on ranking pop
so that you guys become my bottoms that
is my motivation for today
from your motivation
I'll turn you guys into bottoms
we want to be dominated that easily
senpai
and I think
that's just one ID I think I did
yeah
let's introduce the inside let's start
with Iris okay hiris it's Iris whole
alive English Project Help V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
and looking forward to your driving
skills
thank you so much for having me here as
well I heard that you waited for damn
come on we were literally in the last
question that I needed because before
you it was we were elf uh elf and that's
what that was German we were 11 people
understand German yeah
yeah
thank you next up how about
[Music]
um
today I'm gonna win probably okay okay
okay
girl I love these episodes
I heard you only played Mario's card so
far in the members only stream but
that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay
I see oh then you might be the hidden
winning Choice
a wild card player amazing
thank you thank you next time
English
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not last
and to be first so I'll do my best
you know I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of Ina I don't know
I was still falling off Maps it's fun oh
yeah it happens oh Kelly joined yes nice
Thanksgiving
I'm here
hello everyone my name is Calliope my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning Maury
nice to meet you
because it's a bit early uh so excuse me
for that guys but I'm very excited just
to be here I really didn't think this
was gonna work but it's working I love
it today
thank you for joining even though it's
such an early time and to kind of
troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
Whispering you know that kind of just
twists but everyone yeah
[Laughter]
all right let's go gouda introduction
please
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard I'm sorry please well it
was not my phone am I in control right
now so anyway I'm PNG tuber Doma summer
does a PNG tuber Let's Race today baby
I'm the one
it does
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway I
think it's fun I'm curious they want to
look at me right guys
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me I think yeah
yes
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today
organizing yeah
I think we will go to the roots but
before that let me say thank you as the
hats and the cards are sponsored by
ninoma in on his yeah
you look lovely so cute all right let's
uh everyone switch to the rose image
please thank you
all right okay tournament rules easy
there's not many rules basically uh all
characters all courses are allowed
however if you choose uh please do not
choose random courses please choose a
certain course that you want to actually
erase but if that course has been used
before like if it has actually been
chosen before please do not choose the
same course again alrighty
understandable yes
and number two items are allowed number
three we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistance I think you
can check that pressing
all right
now okay I don't see it if uh wait a
second it's if you press Y and select
your character at the point where you
select the card you can press on a plus
the plus button
when you see the the three options on
the right side if you press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh Auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay okay so
it's supposed to be passed down put the
correct out exactly you can ignore yeah
okay
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
I also want to quickly let you guys know
yes I'm on I'm gonna be on like Auto
mute this whole time so unless I have
something to say I'm gonna be muted
don't worry if I'm a little quiet I'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay okay no problem
and next oh yeah there's no more rules
there's basically it's just a system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer for racist battle and then we
get we will mute each other by the way
during the race and just to focus
everyone on what we're driving and then
we get back together and Discord talk a
little bit then we go to the second cup
which is e n versus ID six times six yes
yes that's when we will separate each
other in uh The Voice channels by team
this one in this one we will actually
talk with one another if you wanna and
then we uh give some comments together
again when we get all back together in
the same channel and then we do the
first cup with random randomly thrown
together teams know me and versus ID but
like all mixed together naturally
beautiful yes
random random we will just like I'll
count down and and then everyone joins
Eva voice chat room zero or voice chat
room one no who's this one
everybody wants to be one well done
we're gonna have to do it again and
again and again
those like team cups would basically be
um like the same system as all versus
all the difference is just basically
like if you throw items like red shells
or whatever and there is a teammate in
front of you it will not go to the
teammate obviously it will go directly
to the closest opponent driver uh that's
around you so yeah that's how that team
system works I think yes okay nice
is everyone ready
I'm ready
then everyone who's ready mute yourself
on Discord if someone's not ready and I
will ask you why you're not ready
wait guys how do you wait guys uh how do
you go forward in the game
thank you thanks guys love you okay
man
and thus it's only us now guys
so yeah
um today we'll be playing Mario Kart and
well
and while the system here is that we
won't turn on our voice uh chat it's so
that we can focus on the game
man I gotta go pee
can I go pee I wonder if I can go pee
but I don't want them to wait any longer
we're kind of short on time I guess I'll
just hold my pee or a p on the floor
that's also an option hello everyone
we'll
hello everyone welcome to
come to Heart
Felix this is your captain speaking
English
let us do our best and enjoy the show
thank you
foreign
thank you so much for coming everyone
thank you for supporting hopefully we
get the music park because I am very
good at Music Park called Music Park
like it's really easy to drift
like I've been doing time trials there
for like countless of times so if you do
get it it'll be
I'll be very very lucky also the hat is
made by Innocent by Enda steering wheel
is made by azamrid by the name of sun
pei-san thank you so much for making the
steering wheel alright so uh one thing
for sure I am very scared of Iris
Rainey and also Ina Senpai very very
scared of him I heard that they are a
very very good crazy good even well I'm
going to shut up now so that I can focus
[Music]
oh well that's okay
sucks
[Music]
then please easily six by seven please
we're doing good we're doing good so far
like I got that bad
the whole starts on the whole ID collab
I got so traumatized that I actually
practiced so much
foreign
[Music]
what's up
no someone supported someone's a bullet
that was close
[Music]
why is there so many
memories
items people are crazy
and that's my name
[Music]
whoa sorry Iris Iris a virus
whoa so many bullets what the heck
oh there no
no I got karma real bad
Mommy
okay next one
next one for you what is it called again
that thing
to get at it
sucks oh someone someone oh you have
yourself the the bike one the bike one
is really really nice
assistant
Mama and Papa
after
Rainey did win look at that big foul
full
how do you say it again
I have both of my parents here
oh
I got blessings for my mother and father
I need to win this one
I love algorithm prices to scoot
I switch
noinis just are
mom
yeah
[Music]
she's really really is really good at
this game mind you
Ernie is good at everything actually
okay second place not bad let's not
oh
yeah bye-bye
[Music]
come on
boom
second place not bad not bad not bad at
all unless someone goes bullet I hate it
when someone goes bullet like this makes
sense
like that's basically a trap card hit
Iris
awesome first place first place awesome
buyers
[Music]
why do you do this to me
move it
[Music]
Karma came in fast
boom virus I love bullying my clothes so
much
[Music]
the Karma's real
boom
sorry
[Music]
six six no six six game okay we're we're
moving up we're we're slowly but surely
we're moving up let's see we are and
please everyone do not use cheap cheap
beach or a Mario Kart Stadium anymore
for your race collection thank you I'm
gonna try and remember that but I don't
know yeah
nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life place right okay there are multiple
Beach
uh yeah but the cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the DS version
not anymore oh okay okay okay are we
doing team wait what are we doing teams
no we're still doing that we still have
two races to go yeah
wait I just remembered I'm still muted
Discord
nice hat oh she's muted okay
are we mute oh sorry okay
probably my first time collabing with
Garrison plot well I mean this is a big
collab so like
we don't get to talk much about but
person plays really cute
but I keep remembering Yago in this one
probably just me though
like oh no every time I'm every time I'm
in like this
this map every time I'm in Toad Harbor I
don't know why but it just reminds me of
Yago
yeah I go this one's for you mwah
boom
rainy is really scary especially since
he's dry bones
[Music]
he's up shoot
what the heck what the heck happened
what died
[Music]
oh man it won't reach oh
my
God
the virus I get I get I get I get Harman
this time I make fun of Iris seriously
man iris is blessed
[Music]
like usually I get like third place or
like yeah I get like third place are
like second place in the first time but
like
after that
and I'll get eight please Seventh Place
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
go go
cheating
you're definitely cheating
why is it six again
man give me a break
boom
[Music]
it was easy
I'm coming for you Iris
is coming for you
[Laughter]
goodness it didn't hit me
let's go
[Music]
everything
whoa
whoa let's go let's go turn please
like I'm not first but then I made
people on my bottoms I mean a lot of
people in my bottoms
okay iris is above me because she's
basically an angel she ascends and Enos
invites basically got yourself too so
like it's not it's all that it is it's
not bad if I do say so myself
[Music]
I want music Park why would
you have to use that one that's a very
difficult map
baby Park please you know what we should
collectively like vote for baby Park
like I think that'd be pretty cute
it's still topped I still topped the
girl we're eating is grossing by raging
I wouldn't know
I'm not watching
you can get first Ali I can I can if I
wasn't attacked
man
what you're talking about I have Sound
Performance ain't no totanga going to
normal me
oh this is
one that uh Rainey and Iris recently did
[Music]
boom foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
following me nothing by footsteps well
not really
done
yo yo no what
was that Iris you just ended virus
so much I'm so sorry
thank you
man everyone's so good it's not fair
shoot shoot shoot out
that was not supposed to happen but
firstly it's not bad not bad as I do so
you still uh myself
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go man no no no
no
I hate it so much when people use
bullets only I can use bullets like I'm
just doing
it
[Music]
hi Dad
guys I got disconnected
[Music]
but should we finish it it should we
finish ready so oh no maybe got
disconnected
foreign
[Music]
excited
okay fourth place
the number of death that would be proud
of me
anyways okay about the disconnection I'm
yeah I'm not sure like normally it seems
like in in the whole of Japan
tournaments they automatically give the
one like well the like this
qualification like last spot if you uh
oh if you are oh middle wow uh
congratulations
now oh yeah okay Blues
[Music]
I got disconnected but she still was a
fourth or what yeah I don't remember I
think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is
[Music]
so uh let me let me just uh enough was
number one right number one
[Music]
I I saw you kept on selecting Rainbow
Road
uh
you know
everyone you know rainbows
yeah yeah she practiced on that one a
lot I think that's the question okay
okay
something happened with my okay
no problem
[Music]
I hope you guys
well how did you how did you manage to
get number two today I I did bad on the
first race so that really pulled me back
but yeah Ina Senpai was very quick uh I
thought I did my best I did my best
[Music]
oh wait me and Elena were third are we
tired
Hollow birdies hold the Third
wait wait are we complete in the lobby
right now one two three I am in the
lobby yeah okay I guess we're complete
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
but Muna Senpai is currently unavailable
it's a low battery but I don't know my
my battery is 100 but it's a low battery
so I didn't know which one is low
battery oh
the ones that you like that
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time I I think I think it
should be fine okay so we're making
coffee right now yeah
everyone who needs coffee go get a
triple cup of coffee
shakes already so I'm banned from coffee
I was actually really surprised about
ama's driving too like I thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
play the game a lot I was like in third
place and most of the races until the
end when I got over
that's playing right now
blue shell yeah whatever yeah
casted how you uh suggested uh I mean
because you're such a good driver we
need you we need you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to an idea James are
we picking teams like dodgeball no no I
don't want that because that gives me no
that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that
my Nintendo again please
pick last and I don't want that I'm
gonna go at my full power now because
now I'm fighting for the en ladies
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah we need to defend the honor of our
teams I was just warm up now it's the
real game yeah this is good because Ina
and Iris the two of the strongest ones
are in Ian wait me too
[Music]
that I can I'm I'm okay at not getting
last place so that's good news yes
is a good asset to have I want her in
our team hell yeah
Dana will have to carry uh Indonesia's
uh back yeah I will support
after all this I'll be good all right
I'll do what I can as long as we don't
get disconnected again yeah oh my gosh
yeah hopefully yeah
I hope you don't get it are we on a
break right now God may have forgiven
the disconnection but I didn't
uh please split into teams by I think
let's just um Ian go to a voice channel
oh one thank you okay okay oh
and I guess how we're going to stay
yeah
unless unless if you want to wait
Kelly wants to be now
um
here are famous for like their super
Reckless way of driving
no mercy like they run over everything
Supremacy
very dangerous
did you know
yes uh there's a problem with my
Nintendo's actually what should we do
it is
um
I'm creating a room right now
sorry girls I did a little mistake
because like I thought uh yeah you know
uh oh but I'll actually just opened the
room okay
[Music]
okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it closed once you
can join again
okay so sorry
[Music]
all settled
are you gonna be okay controller yeah
um
[Music]
I think that we actually need to buy
separate uh what is it controller
another one controller yeah controller
yeah
[Music]
I was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had problems
when we were collabing 100 right yeah
yeah
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so
um
okay now I think it's the same thing
guys
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
don't miss out
whoa
um
[Music]
goodness
yeah all right oh my God
goodbye everyone
I have no idea
[Music]
District
s
[Music]
like Mario Kart you know
um
[Music]
I think you have to be at least good at
Mario Kart because this kind of
tournament is gonna like happen in the
future
it's gonna happen again
it will happen again
tournament you know I kind of I'm kind
of thinking about maybe playing this
again so oh my God I bought the wheels
for that
Wheels but it's not arrived sadly oh
yeah I don't know I'm just I'm just
using is it is it gonna be difficult
this one is difficult is it it's hard
yeah
to be honest
[Music]
ly
I can't see I don't have eyes
glasses
[Applause]
I'm not born
[Music]
oh
yeah
hey kirst hi how you doing
I'm doing good okay somebody just like
stole my items that's not cool
it's okay final love guys
okay
[Music]
I don't understand
problem in this map
yeah we have problems so I don't like
this one
yeah where is this
I'm dying I'm dying
[Applause]
this one
I'm fine
everyone good morning everybody
[Laughter]
oh my God
I don't know where you guys
I have no idea what you're going to
talking about
so where where are we going what would
what did we choose again I still want
cheese it doesn't matter honestly cheese
land
do you plan again
oh that's a sixth traditional
we got this oh my god let's go oh my God
why did they pick that place oh my God
[Applause]
rainbow because it's all sunshine and
rainbows right now please
happiness that is fun when I saw it I
please she's land
wow
gotta get that cheddar delicious
I don't even know what are you guys
talking about
randomly screaming at each other at this
point right
yes
I don't even know I
celand
a lot of cheese cheese
[Music]
okay
it's okay it's okay it's it's I think
it's okay I I did hope it's okay though
and I fall okay
oh yeah oh cheese
okay Hollow ID let's go inside that was
for you
me
I just want mushrooms where do I keep
getting like weird slash bad items and
everyone else gets such good items
I get items
you guys get items wow
seriously I'm asking you guys got an
item
nice onion is trying to kill him by
flying you know but I failed how
I believe I can touch this guy
well you are an alien so you can't touch
the sky basically
[Music]
bananas delicious bananas foreign
yes
is
oh no I gotta drive honestly
[Music]
I'm not liking this I gotta drive honest
here
again
oh yeah yeah
that's dirty that's so dirty
yeah I'm sorry because I failed you
I failed you guys I'm so sorry oh God I
had potential
oh no
who knows
[Music]
let's try popping top five of all of us
please
okay we got cheese land so uh oh I'm
hacked
um okay let's do the airplane stage oh
foreign
[Music]
oh it's gonna be Rainbow Road
oh it is Rainbow Road and I look so good
too yeah especially this one this one is
especially hard
[Music]
that one's easy but this one
what was it the simplest looking one I
like that one is
so I wouldn't drive
there's like shortcuts here and I have I
still have no idea how to get and how to
get it I don't know
oh
going on
what is even going on everybody
oh my God
[Music]
oh look at it please
I don't know what is it called
and I kept falling again
[Music]
baby
you guys know how to stop
what do you mean stop what do you mean
like I mean stuff do we stop here not
like like you you know how to stop the
car like kind of like that uh what what
is it um
yeah yeah
I I oh I'm so bad okay I'm just I'm just
matching
[Music]
the button right at yourself
yeah I guess you're some huh
oh no it fell
sorry
[Music]
oh no I fell again
it's loud it's loud what what is it's
allowed because of our ID
what does that mean
s
I think it's okay like if if it's
Michelle yes let's go what do you mean
let's go with so which one is not okay
English Indonesian no English is English
is not good because YouTube YouTube AI
is bad bad right
but cursing in Indonesia is okay
you guys see
what's this
okay in moderation
congratulations wow congratulations
[Music]
Indonesian team uh what was their
reasoning behind choosing uh the cheese
one and the baby Road I like cheese
that's all
yeah
I was the one who told them cheese road
because I like cheese
tasty so yeah
was somewhat in control there because
like It's gotta be a road where Elena
knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah yeah
yeah
I wasn't the one choosing it
uh do we have uh some uh comments from
the winner Ina it was number one I think
ah yes uh I would like to thank my chair
mates
um
for this opportunity because because of
you Yago I was about to be like yeah go
let's go okay never mind okay thank you
[Laughter]
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate it
um
what did we choose
oh I mean well even if you accidentally
choose one that has been uh chosen
before don't worry it will probably not
be selected so let's just let's just try
to not choose the ones that we have uh
raced before then I will do the random
teams now actually there is uh we don't
have to do the voice chat thing because
there is actually a way to do it here
and then once the themes are selected oh
there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero zero zero one we want uh gura
and your feet all right let's go
huh wait do you know something rainy in
one team
yeah we're gonna lose
guys wait guys we still have hope
I don't I'm not really confident in
winning against the ER right now what's
your favorite map
my favorite map has to be uh probably uh
the airport right now okay airport oh
sunshine airport yeah airport airport uh
okay oh then how about we choose the
iPod where is it we haven't played at
one right
yeah
what is it on
oh
well this one
[Music]
[Laughter]
is packed with like the really strong
ones I'm just like
we can just say at least we are top 10
right you can do it
let's go
let's go also Iris I'd like to apologize
to you personally because I kept
bullying you in the previous rounds I
got Karma a lot
I did not know
[Music]
but now we're together we got this let's
go we got this
We Believe Darkness
[Music]
wait I hate this map so much this one is
particularly hard for me I never went in
this battle Yeah well I never went in
every month
right in front of me right now uh okay
it's okay it's okay we still have hope
it's if
but if if the Hops not with us uh at
least I don't know
sorry did I just beat you what
oh
okay oh he's in front okay
no no please please no please
okay it's pretty good
this is bad
like even the song is distorted
[Music]
wrestling
wait I just realized it this this one
feels like a Toy Story
it does look like Toy Story doesn't it
hold on
go
home
okay
it's literally nobody in here I'm so far
waiting yeah I am then get all of the
items
then get good items oh my God oh my God
[Music]
oh
that was close that was very close Okay
uh second uh Ina I think yeah I was
seven
oh yeah sorry
sorry
it's good it's good uh it's fine
it's not that bad right now yeah yeah
it could be worse
that annoys me yeah
items okay airport the items can hits
please
it's okay guys
it's okay
foreign
time so that we can like redo that and
win
wait I can't do it for everyone just me
Amelia's don't need to watch right yeah
she can go back in time and practice a
lot yeah
foreign
[Music]
this one is like futuristic water
parkish
oh
ah
okay I think what I don't like is that
the NPCs keep harassing me
[Music]
oh I love this music though oh yes it's
a Bop
[Music]
oh
you're different okay cool yep I'm in
the front right now but this is very
early game
yes
oh
my God
there's somebody's acting flying with
bananas
well that's me
I'm gonna be careful okay
I hate it when they minimize that
yeah
really destroys my Pace okay
[Music]
come on come on I want to see I don't
see it
is
okay
[Music]
ow
oh he's using a shortcut oh okay
that's how do you skip the the shortcut
really helped though
legit
I did not make it uh
no no no I should have studied more
so cute sorry
oh
I'm nine
I I don't think you've ever played this
map
yeah this one's yes
lucky number seven maybe
right now I'm being very salty right now
guys
we need two more let's get the airport
yeah airports Airport
airport will do Us justice will ascend
and be embarrassing though you got
airport and I still do bad at it
I believe
believe
it
oh everyone's choosing airport
I hope I helped God
wait is this the third race or the last
race is this third right I think it's
third it's third it's third ah we got it
yeah okay we got this we got this we got
this okay
Sunshine Airport
[Music]
I think she does yep
do you guys know how to not use the
items that we got
like what do you mean by losing uh like
thunder stuff there's no way to really
prevent that no no no I mean like if we
got something but we don't want to use
it how how can we
you know move it to the trash
[Music]
because there is some of the items that
I don't really like to use
it
[Music]
I don't really get all this music like I
have this like speaker looking thing I
don't really know how I'm supposed to
use it
if there are like a lot of people around
here
everyone's just like I'm just gonna hug
it
[Music]
yeah
let's just use it I have a bad habit of
holding on to items yes
[Music]
are you sure
no
my item is good no okay
you win
[Music]
I see you now she's in third place okay
oh
ouch
oh my God I hurt you okay yeah we're
doing good so far okay
[Music]
whoa battery percentage oh better try
again whoops I'm sorry that was close
okay we got this
stop
no
[Music]
wait wait
it's okay we're in the same team okay
just gotta make sure it's not enough
[Music]
um
foreign
okay okay I wonder how this looks right
now
[Music]
okay I kind of like being right in the
middle okay
confidence in
Stadium I
like it
should be able to join before we pick
the next one oh wait wait wait I'm gonna
join
I'm chasing the music part Music Park
okay yeah
oh no can I can I join before this ah
yeah you can do it oh oh I'll tell I'll
tell first all right run for it it's not
ready yet
right yeah hopefully not yeah
there we go
wait I just realized we got the crown
Yeah Yeah by six points
oh six points we gotta keep this up it's
a very close race
we got this we got hope
uh okay every Point counts ladies let's
do it not not the clock not the clock I
don't like the clock
[Music]
yeah
this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys uh yeah just get ready
for a lot of different things do you
know the shortcuts for this okay there
there are a few shortcuts but they're
actually pretty tricky so I wouldn't
recommend them
okay yeah all right let's go let's do
this let's go recognize this place but
let's go
I'm gonna win this
oh no I just passed I'm gonna yeah I
know
okay over here the piano drift
[Music]
okay
then that girl when you're in the
priyana place now you later
so you gotta drift in the front
and then another one drift
don't forget to drift again
oops
oh yeah this is a lot of Dripping okay
yeah this place is kind of tricky so
please be careful
okay there's the shortcut over here but
it's really really tricky
[Music]
yeah shoot
okay wait uh who's first right now
how can we know who's the first
[Music]
because I saw them
oh hello
oh god
oh now girl's in front of me
another
ah
that's not good
shoot shoot shoot okay oh you're our
last hope right now I'm I'm doing really
bad I'm a Zombie how am I hope
it's okay I got Nina
do the items
so we're good
hope has consumed zombie meat a lot so
[Music]
good job
okay okay
oops did I accidentally hit someone
nope okay be careful
[Music]
did hello
I got disconnected
Destiny is in your hands
I got number one yeah sorry I'm sorry
one of your
perspectives to see what's going on
so when I eat okay
[Music]
well it was a valiant effort ladies and
144 hey that's two fours in there it
four is a good number I like it I can't
say I'm unhappy
don't forget
okay so yeah we did great I got kicked
out of the road we did great
yeah
and we had two disconnections so it kind
of doesn't count yeah
[Music]
and when I rejoined like my points are
are reset yeah
um
yeah we had two disconnects two yeah I
got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh no that was me or my Shark
friends
[Music]
but that probably means that you know
the last round if if these two you know
got disconnected and the points got
deleted that means that the last round
final result is not really accurate yeah
but that's okay but let's just say the
last round was an extra Encore for fun
and yeah and I would like to give out
some golden yugos
so okay they're not showing up on your
stream they're only on last name but I'd
like I would like to give one a golden
juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
congratulations
[Music]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago
um as uh to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
another golden juggle goes to Dana for
being I guess the strongest in the ID
team holy moly
ideas
another golden Ninjago goes to gura for
being absolutely the speediest shark
I've ever seen
[Applause]
participation award
messy with a kid now
[Laughter]
for being Supreme a big surprising uh
what do you call that Black Horse Wild
Card damn Wild Card yo honey
[Music]
another golden juggle goes to Muna for
being a
baby
[Music]
I didn't see you that much on the race
but I think you were still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
Michael goes to ollie for being also
surprised damn good yeah
[Music]
speed squirrel
s
[Music]
painting
and another golden Yago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprised me you surprised me Cali I was
I was looking at you driving there and I
was like damn well what the hell man she
didn't even do practice arcs is she so
good
my mom was playing instead of me that's
why I was so good
didn't I didn't get last place even once
guys that was my goal
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you
don't mind me uh chat I'm not gonna be
able to fix that now I think one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
wait who did I not give up
ah you weren't you were surprised me too
sometimes I have I had an eye on you
thank you
[Music]
very much everyone
um
can we get like a
last comment from everyone let's start
with Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more
Maybe
maybe I will definitely be a next time
yeah
it's always room for improvement
um
tell me what's your closing comments
oh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organize the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast thank you I'm so glad you
enjoyed it yeah thank you Mom and Dad
moment yeah thanks for everything
it was fun to organize
closing comments please oh
thank you I want to say thank you also
to Ina and Kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and I'm very I'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as I thought I
would and I would like to uh say that it
was probably because I fixed my switch
legs so I didn't have any lag let's go
Gamers like school
no excuses I watched and I won though I
can use that excuse me
in a long time I think yeah no practice
that's cool
Rob challenge
[Music]
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this and now we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh Beyond but
yes thank you for this golden young I
will cherish it and talk to you tonight
thank you so much
thank you
okay I've completely disappeared I'm
sorry guys
[Music]
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament Kiara and
thank you so much Ina for the very very
cute assets and yes I will practice more
so that we can I can get go against Ina
oh no yeah my goal is
to do this again hopefully one day yeah
[Music]
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina too that's a big vehicle
that would be a big accomplishment it's
not that big of a goal
it's not confident anymore I'm so glad
I'm so glad you joined Holo Ian because
that's what made this uh tournament
possible
I'm really glad to be able to join this
wonderful Tournament being part of the
cool kids yeah
[Music]
thank you
all right clothing
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go through for like
the logos and stuff and even the
thumbnails those must have been hard and
also for innocent fight we're making all
of those assets so quickly like you guys
really um how do I say it I really
appreciate it a lot and I'm sure all of
us do so thank you so much for your hard
work it was really fun playing with
everyone and um I may have not popped
everyone but one way or another you guys
will all be my bottoms
I forgot about that goal yeah
all right
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organizing and thank you so
much
I mean I I don't think without without
you organizing we will don't be like
this I mean it's it's it's rare to
gather all the whole life Indonesia in
the whole event together so I'm so
thankful for that and also
um big thanks to inatu for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and I hope uh in the future we can
be like this again yes
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve we
should do something
okay Inna closing comments please yeah
I'd like to say a big thank you to uh
Kiara for organizing it of course I know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and my schedule is
really really difficult but you really
put a lot of effort into organizing it
commissioning like the logo and
everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario Kart
streams in the future too
thank you and uh yeah thank you everyone
for joining us today like it was so much
fun like playing with everyone and I
hope we can do it again definitely it's
been a pleasure thank you thank you
cooperation this was a great
collaboration between uh kfb and Taco
Taco Bell taco eats Stefano yeah yeah
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed because we're
faster okay
closing comments please
okay I know you said stuff but thank you
Kiara everything
and also in a senpai uh thank you so
much and I had a lot of fun uh there was
a little miss out there there was a
little disconnection issue but overall I
had a lot of fun and I would love to
have this kind of tournament again in
the future let's do it and by then yeah
okay
training so I'll get better and I'll
write everybody next time
[Laughter]
thank you
baseball clothing comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like these are amazing and
also okay I I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like well
uh I'd appreciate it more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate oh yes thank you so much I
love you guys
okay
please closing comments ah well first uh
I'd like to apologize
or if I was salty if I curse that you
guys oh no yeah
[Music]
uh and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and
Inna you guys worked really hard thank
you guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs because everybody's so busy and
different schedules so thank you and I
had a lot of fun thank you
[Music]
we can like we don't have to relay on
these exact 12 members anymore so next
time if you want you can do shout
casting oh yeah
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities to Fan communities of
hello Ian and her idea together and just
feeling United definitely and I am
always glad to do stuff like this again
so I would gladly invite you guys again
whenever you have time for it and want
to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so I'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that I'm so sorry I
know it's tough it's no problem it was
fun
I just wish my parents could watch the
news
it's okay I hope your mom enjoyed the
tournament I think she did I think that
she enjoys it as well
well then with it I would like to
officially close to Holo Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone be take
care of your golden yagos polish him
every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly and yeah I'll see you guys soon
[Music]
bye everyone
Mario Kart tournament a deluxe thank you
so much everyone for coming through
today
[Music]
live
thank you