[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
no
oh
[Music]
hello
oh
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
ah
welcome everyone
and welcome to the
first
i would say full collaboration but now
we have council so it's the first almost
full collaboration
of hallelujah
[Music]
support today and hopefully also the
viewers support today because uh today
will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting
event yay it's race day baby
driver but i'll drive you guys nuts
oh oh is that sound
good
i think we shall start with some
introductions of each member
now let's start with
from whole live indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
anja melvisa from hello life is second
generation
thank you everyone i can't wait what's
your what's your goal
what's my ikigomi um to not be on the
last last place at least
[Music]
okay what about
you senpai
oh oh hello oh
officers
from whole life i read generation one
so my motivation tonight is um to show
you my practice i guess
hello
oh show me what you got
[Music]
up how about rainey
hi attention please i'm pavilio rainy
from whole life id generation two my
goal today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
that last information
i knew you were quite decent
oh yeah
yeah i've heard you were good you and
iris have heard good good good news
about you
[Music]
nice to meet you
what's your motivation for today oh well
i i want to be at least not on the last
but in the middle it's okay
[Music]
laugh in someone's heart is that such a
good thing
yeah that doesn't sound like a good
thing
yeah okay next up
hello hello everyone i am
indonesia and
thank you so much for inviting me to
this collab i'm so happy though i'm so
excited
my motivation for today is that i would
like to have fun though although yes i'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
it will be fine
as long as we all have fun that's all
that matters
second generation hi guys
hi
motivation i plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms
that is my motivation for today
[Laughter]
oh
thank you
and i think wait did i get
all the introductions from id i think
i'd hit
yay
[Music]
let's introduce the inside let's start
with iris
oh yeah pirates it's iris hololive
english project hope v singer here um my
goal today is to get first place
victoris
[Applause]
thank you amy for participating and
looking forward to your driving skills
thank you so much for having me here so
i heard that you waited for it yeah
for me to come on
we're literally the last thing that i
think did because before you it was we
were elf
that was german we were 11
is
[Music]
okay
i heard you only played mario kart so
far in the members only stream but
that's about it
yeah i won and that one too
oh
oh then you might be the hidden
um winning choice that no one is
dark
a wild card player
thank you thank you
next stop
i mean
english
um um i'll do my best i think we have a
you have a piercer competition to be not
last and to be first so i'll do my best
i was also
taking this very seriously in her
practice round so a bit scared of you
know
i don't know
i'm still falling off
oh yeah it happens oh kelly joined us
nice thanksgiving
[Music]
thank you
nice then let's start let's continue
with the uh introduction from cal iop
maureen
hello everyone my name is calif my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning maury
nice to meet you
because it's a bit early uh so excuse me
for that guys but i'm very excited just
to be here i really didn't think this
was going to work but it's working i
love it
thank you caroline for joining even
though it's such an early time and kind
of troublesome with some setups and all
that i'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
oh
[Laughter]
english and i'm kind of sick today and
if you're watching on my side i just
need to say this now
i've had some technical difficulties
very suddenly so i am made of cardboard
i'm sorry please bring well i it was not
my fault it's out of my control right
now so anyway
i'm png tuber domo somebody does a png
tuber let's race today baby i'm the wild
card today
[Music]
well you know on the screen there's
there's going to be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so i think it's fun
i'm cute
of course they want to look at me right
guys
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me i think yeah
okay guys
yes
welcome everyone i wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time i i
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and i'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so i i don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some
more often in the future so please don't
stress yourself out let's just have fun
today
[Music]
i think we will go to the roof but
before that let me say thank you as the
hats and the cards are sponsored by nino
ma inaniz
thank you
thank you you look lovely
so cute all right let's everyone switch
to the rules image please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however
uh if you choose uh please do not choose
random courses please choose a certain
course that you want to actually erase
but if that course has been used before
like if it has actually been chosen
before please do not choose the same
course again
already
understandable
items are allowed number three we are
racing in 150 cc with no assist everyone
please check if you have turned off your
assistant i think you can check by
pressing y
all right
now
okay
wait a second it's if you press y and
select your character at the point where
you select the card you can press on a
plus
plus yeah
and that way you see the the three
options on the right side if you press l
if if there is a
if there's a
sign that says no
then it's uh
auto steering off that's how it's
supposed to be okay okay
oh
done i also want to quickly let you guys
know yes i'm on i'm going to be on like
auto mute this whole time so unless i
have something to say i'm going to be
muted don't worry if i'm a little quiet
i'm still here with you guys in spirit
yeah okay
okay
[Music]
oh yeah there's no more rules this looks
just a system we're doing the first cup
all versus all big mixer four races each
but can we get we mute each other by the
way during the race and just to focus
everyone on what we're driving and then
we get back together and discord talk a
little bit then we go to the second cup
which is en versus id six
yes yes yes gentlemen we will separate
each other in uh the voice channels by
team this one in this one we will
actually talk with one another if you
wanna and then we uh
give some comments together again and
when we get all back together in the
same channel and then we do the third
cup with random randomly thrown together
teams no envelopes id but like all mixed
together naturally beautiful
it's the random
random random we will just like i'll
i'll count down and and then everyone
joins either voice chat room zero or
voice chat room one no this is this guy
but what if that's not even what if
everybody wants to be one
well then we're gonna have to do it
again and again
okay
sounds poor proof perfect
perfect okay
just just so you know the the those like
team cups would basically be
um
like the same
system as all versus all the difference
is just basically like if you throw
items like red shells or whatever and
there is a teammate in front of you it
will not go to the teammate obviously it
will go directly to the closest opponent
driver uh that's around you so yeah
that's how that team system works
yes
okay is everyone ready to get started
who's that
ready
i'm ready
who is that random dude
who is it who's that
oh
okay
okay that's random duty slowly all right
okay doggy then everyone who is ready
mute yourself on discord if someone's
not ready then i will ask you why you're
not ready okay
bye-bye
okay wait guys how do you wait guys uh
how do you go forward in the game
you push the a button you can't go
anywhere right now you can't move in the
world right now okay that's what you
need gotcha all right understood thank
you thanks guys love you okay love you
too
okay
so yeah so
it is mute
it's all of them is mute so you cannot
hear because
because it was um
it's a little bit challenging if we
we
unmute
so that's why
yeah
okay
nothings
not items
no computer
overshields
for races
great
i'm gonna
choose watch what you want to watch what
you watch
[Music]
i think
i think i like
these dry eh
dry dessert
i don't know what
did they really choose that one
the eovn inna
that is that is the real real heart
good luck okay thank you
i will try my best
i've i've been learning with the
hawaii
okay okay
the pot
okay
oh there's another boner who is that
who's choosing the bowser
kali
come on
holy
[Music]
[Applause]
no
no i don't want to be under seven
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on
no
oh my god my hand hurts
my hand hurt
thank you for your donation
sinking thank you
thank you
yeah
i want to take that coin but
come on
no
what's that
come on
yeah i think i think that is because of
my own fault
oh no i'm just
[Laughter]
oh my
all right let's let's choose um
what is it
i i think i'm gonna go with the
um
animal crossing
just just i want to try the animal
crossing
do you like animal crossing
[Applause]
i know it's raining is the best rainy is
so good when we're playing together
she's so good
oh
what is that
water chip beach
the beach is so cheap
okay
come on
oh sh
lights so long
come on oh no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
yeah
i i i i i i i i i i i
i missed that one
i missed that
come on
hey racu hey anya
oh my glass
how are the last
i am the last looks like i'm the last
ah
sick
how can i
come on
give me the things that i really need no
no not that not that not that
not bad
please everyone do not use cheap cheap
beach or uh mario kart stadium anymore
for your race collection thank you well
you try and remember that but i don't
know
yeah nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy
nightlife
place all right
but isn't there multiple beach
uh
yes but the cheap cheap beach the one
that we just did from the ds version not
anything yeah
okay okay
okay
wait what are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go before
all this is all right
okay
hmm
it's the same that i choose
to harbor
is it just me or they they they all
choosing
the small small small character
yes yes yes i missed that one
that's that's kind of sad that's kind of
sad but okay but okay
ticket
ticket ticket
[Music]
oh my
god i want to try this one
i just want to
why you didn't lend me
is this
what is it
wow
[Music]
mama
oh wake up one
why you do this to me
will you do this to me
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
why why why why why why
why why why why why
come on
i missed that one again
wow
[Music]
hmm
[Laughter]
foreign
let's change my character
somehow
um
nail bolster shitty
oh ina is the first
that's cool
[Music]
oh
i forgot to use coin what's what's the
coin
what's the coin for
what's the coin for again
hey am i 11 forever
oh i missed that one
yeah yeah yeah oh that that is that is
not good
that is not good
wow
[Music]
okay
that's what i love
i just
oh
the handling's too bad
oh rainy hi
hi
did i did i dry
did i did i guys i got disconnected what
what rainy
rainy got disconnected
rainy
i i see rainey
oh why is not moving at all
oh
ah you're so reasonable
oh at least i'm six now
yeah
i'm in the middle okay about the
disconnection i'm
i'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well the like this qualification like
last spot if you
uh oh
if you are oh
wow
everyone cannot mute themselves now
[Music]
who is this again
wait i forgot
who is this
i was very impressed
lena got disconnected but she still what
a fourth or what so
yeah i think that's just how we're going
to take it it is what it is
it is what it is
so uh
let me let me just uh enough was number
one right
number one
[Music]
i i saw you kept on selecting rainbow
road why do you want to say
[Music]
yeah she practiced on that one a lot i
think that's why she was going for that
okay
something happened with my well hold on
something happened with my channel my
there's hold on
we'll get it
okay i'm gonna have to
uh yeah wait um
something happened with mine
no problem who was number two though
yeah
[Music]
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today i did bad on the first
race so that really pulled me back but
yeah ina senpai was very quick
but i did my best i did my best
you know we're amazing both of you
oh wait me and elena were first oh we're
[Laughter]
good tied i wait wait are we complete in
the
lobby right now one two three i am in
the lobby
okay i guess very complete
okay well then shall we uh continue what
muna senpai is currently unavailable
i i cannot
it's a low battery but i don't know my
my battery is 100 but it stayed low
battery so i don't know which one is low
battery
what should i do with that
do you think you're fine to go or you
need something i i think i think it
should be fine
we're making coffee right now
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
i have the caffeine shakes already so
i'm banned from coffee
i was actually really surprised about
amma's driving too like i thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
playing the game and to begin with a lot
so it was like really good most of the
races until the end when i got over
yeah whatever yeah no it would have been
a waste if you would have shout casted
how you uh suggested uh amer because
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
all right then let's uh okay ollie okay
okay ollie is going to pick any teams
are we picking teams like dodge ball no
no
no that gives me really bad flashbacks i
don't like that um hold on i'm gonna i'm
gonna chase my my nintendo again please
wait because that means someone
picked last and i don't want that
i'm gonna go at my full power now
because now i'm fighting for the en
ladies
[Music]
two of the strongest ones aren't ian
wait me too no
no
oh my god
[Music]
i'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news yes
morrison is a good asset to have i want
her on our team hell yeah
guys
will have to carry uh indonesia's uh
back
yes okay
i will support draining
i will as long as i get a good bath
after all this i'll be good all right
i'll do it i
as you don't get disconnected again
yeah oh my gosh
yeah hopefully
[Music]
oh i hope you don't alright are we on a
break right now
god may have forgiven the disconnection
but i didn't
everyone uh please split into teams by i
think let's just um ian go to uh voice
channel 01 thank you okay
and i guess so we're going to
we will stay we're staying to zero
yeah we're saying
unless unless if you want to wait
wait wait wait almost more
marie unless kelly was
i
moms here are famous for like their
super reckless way of driving
like mercy like they run over everything
supremacy
the auntie very dangerous
yeah
did you
there's a problem with my nintendo's
actually what what should we do
does it already start is it already
started
should we go there all right
yeah
i communication has error
[Music]
god
okay
i think it's back
maybe
hey baby
and i don't have i think though i think
that i think that we actually need to
buy separate uh what is it controller
another another one right
controller yeah controller yeah
controller
i was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had problems yeah mine is good though
yeah
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so we might
want that um
it's it's it's okay now i think it's
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
please
[Applause]
ring
how do i do this
[Music]
good
i
[Music]
everybody
district
[Music]
is fine
[Laughter]
cheeseland
[Music]
thingy like mario kart you know
where we are
i think you have to be at least good at
mario kart because this kind of
tournament is going to like happen in
the future
it will happen again
like a new mario kart didn't you i kinda
i kinda thinking about maybe playing
this again
so
i bought the wheels for that
you
is
[Music]
to be honest
i should have worn
[Music]
it's glasses but i'm not born
is
[Applause]
i'm doing good okay somebody just like
stole my items that's not cool
it definitely was not me
oh my gosh somebody something happens
it's like a 5.
[Music]
in this map
yeah we have problems too i don't like
this one
yeah where is
[Music]
oh
my god
[Laughter]
i have no idea what you guys are talking
about
so where where where are we going what
what what did we choose again
it doesn't matter honestly
season
again
did they pick that place oh my god
rainbow because it's all sunshine and
rainbows please please cheeseland please
anytime when i saw it i
please cheeseland
no
yes
gotta get that cheddar
randomly screaming at each other at this
point right
yes oh it looks like
i don't even know
cheeseland
oh let it change
[Applause]
baby controller
oh it's okay it's okay
it's it's it's i think it's okay i i i
did hope it's okay though and i fall
okay
god's damaged
that was for you
keep getting like weird slash bad items
and everyone else gets such good items
you guys get items
you know but i failed
out of it how the [\h__\h] how i believe
i believe i can touch this guy
well you are dead so you can't touch the
sky basically
oh yeah i can bananas nice delicious
banana oh everybody ouch
that's it
for everybody
oh no there's a blue shirt i'm so scared
blue shell is the scariest thing and you
know it is yes
yes it is
oh no i gotta drive honest here i'm not
liking this
i'm not liking this so i gotta drive
honest here
again
that's dirty that's so dirty
yeah i failed you
oh
[Music]
please
okay we got cheeseland so uh oh i'm
hacked
okay let's do the airplane stage
sunshine
airport
okay well where is that they really want
to do rainbow road
wait um
airport
yep sunshine okay okay
sunshine
[Applause]
oh it's going to be a rainbow road isn't
it oh it is
yeah
me too especially this one this one is
especially hard
it is hard
that one's easy but this one is
this one is another oh what was it the
simplest looking one i like that what is
that i believe i can fly
so i won't drive
[Music]
there's like shortcuts here and i still
have no idea how to get how to get it
yeah
[Music]
said
oh
i don't know what is it called
and i get falling again
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
hmm
[Music]
do you guys know how to stop
what do you mean stop what do you mean
like what do you mean stop stop do i
stop here no like like you you know how
to stop the car like kind of like that
uh what what is
okay
[Music]
yeah i guess your thumb huh
it's loud because we're ideas
what is that we were not supposed to
curse indian nation because in english i
thought i think it's something like like
if if it is written
what do you mean let's go away so which
one is not okay english indonesian
no english is english is not good
because youtube youtube ai is bad bad
right awesome
but cursing you mean
okay
um
i expect
you guys
[Music]
you have a chance in the next race
because uh we will be
[Music]
indonesian team uh what was their
reasoning behind choosing uh the cheese
one and the baby road
i like cheese
i just follow what they choose that's
all yeah i was the one who told them
cheese road because i like to like
cheese yes
she's tasty so yeah i knew dana was
somewhat in control there because like
it's gotta be a road where elena knows
the shortcuts and stuff yeah yeah
yeah
well
i wasn't the one choosing it
do we have uh uh some
uh comments from the winner ina it was
number one i think
uh yes uh i would like to thank for jen
mate um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay so we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that i would appreciate that
um oh can you even have yes
what what what did we choose
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be
selected so let's just let's try to not
choose the ones that we have uh raised
before then i will do the random teams
now actually there is uh we don't have
to do the voice chat thing because there
is actually a way to do it here
yeah
and then once the themes are selected
oh there it is okay so
uh in voice chat zero
zero zero one we want uh gouda
and
yeah
and yuffie
all right
wait what
huh
are you innocent and rainy in one team
we're gonna lose we're doomed guys
guys wait guys we still have hope
[Laughter]
my favorite map has to be uh probably uh
the airport right now
okay airport
sunshine airport
yeah airport airport oh okay but then
how about we choose the ipad we haven't
played that one right let's go let's go
yeah
what is it on
oh
well
what
uh aren't those like the
the the you know the
the top ten
from the back
we can just say at least we are top 10
right
let's go
also
i'd like to apologize to you personally
because i kept bullying you in the
previous rounds i got karma a lot
i did not know
so we got this go we got this
we believe
together we'll fade away
your
where is this
wait i hate this map so much this one is
particularly hard for me
is that someone in this map
well i never went in every month
it's again
right in front of me right now okay
it's okay it's okay we still have hope
like reese is saying
but
if the hopes not with us
uh at least i don't know
did i just meet you what
yeah ollie's in front okay good good
good um
no no please please please no please uh
okay
ready good
like even the songs
wait i just realized this this one feels
like a toy story
does look like toy story doesn't it yeah
no come on
what
[Music]
okay
there's literally nobody in here i'm so
far waiting yeah i am
i didn't get all of the items
i didn't get good items
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh that was close that was very close
okay uh
second
uh ina
yeah it could be worse
that annoys me
yeah
the items can hit a friend
airport please
airport sunshine airport
[Laughter]
it's okay guys
you are our
[Laughter]
how are hope so strong
amelia's invite can't you rewind time so
that we can like redo that and win isn't
that cronie's job
what do you do for everyone just me
yeah yeah she can go back in time and
practice a lot
yeah
oh uh
oh what is this
blue i don't know
i see i haven't tried this one what is
this this one is like futuristic water
parkish
okay i think what i don't like is that
the npcs keep harassing me
oh the ones in the map man
[Music]
oh i love this music though oh yes
oh
shoot iris you're in the front okay yes
i'm in the front right now but this is
very early game
yes
[Music]
oh no
oh there's somebody's actually flying
with bananas
well that's me
[Music]
i'm gonna be careful
really destroys my pace ah okay
yes i don't see enough come on come on i
want to see inna i don't like them
i see right
really really really now really really
really
i'm sorry
sorry i didn't mean to oh i see her okay
oh [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
i should have studied more
it's alright cute
sorry
i am missing him
[Music]
oh
i'm nine
i don't think you've ever played this
map
yeah
right now i'm being very salty right now
guys
oh no oh no
right now yeah airport
airport will do us justice we'll ascend
it'd be embarrassing though
airport and i still do bad at it
okay
again
i believe
let's believe
believe it
oh everyone's to the airport
oh my god
i hope we got it
wait is this the third race or the last
race is this third right i think it's
church it's turret
ah we got it yes okay we got this we got
this we got this
sunshine
let's just hope that ina doesn't really
know this math but i probably she
probably does
i think she does
yep
do you guys know how to not use the
items that we got
ah like what do you mean by lose as in
uh
from like thunder and stuff there's no
way to really prevent that no no no i
mean like if we got something but we
don't want to use it how
how can we you know
move it
to the trash
because there is some of the item that i
don't really like to use
but i keep getting it
i don't really get how this music i have
this like speaker looking thing i don't
really know how i'm supposed to use it
oh it's like uh if if there are like a
lot of people around you you can just
like honk it
and everyone's just like i'm just gonna
honk it uh
okay
let's just use it
i have a bad habit of holding on to
items
yes ollie go ollie okay
okay
[Music]
low battery he said
oh battery again all right oops i'm
sorry oh that was close
yeah
okay we got oh
god i stopped
no
way
rainey sorry i guess
it's okay
we're in the same team okay
just gotta make sure it's not enough
thank you
oh my god
okay okay i wonder how this looks right
now
oh yes
you know
i kind of like being right in the
just fine for middle
what is it yeah in the middle east okay
okay oh what are we gonna do next what
is it anyone have anything that they're
confident in
music i'm very confident
which one or where are your
[Music]
yeah oh no can i can they join before it
is ah yeah you can join
oh oh i'll tell i'll tell first all
right
it's not ready yet
it's supposed to yeah
there we go
wait i just realized we got the crown
did you get it yeah yeah we're like
six points
oh
six points we gotta keep this up it's a
very close race
we got this we got hope
uh
uh okay that's not going to come back
let's do it not not the clock not the
clock i don't like the clock
[Music]
yes this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys uh ah okay just get
ready for a lot of do you notice
yourself okay
there there are a few shortcuts but
they're actually pretty tricky so i
wouldn't recommend them
yeah
all right let's let's do this i don't
really recognize this place but let's go
i'm gonna win this
oh no i just fast i'm gonna yeah i know
in the beginning okay over here the
piano dress
okay
then let's go when you're in the beyond
hopefully
and then another one drift
okay
well
yeah this is a lot of different things
okay
yeah this place is kind of tricky so
please be careful
okay there's a shortcut over here but
it's really really tricky
okay
wait uh
who's first right now i see inaudible
how can we know who's the first
[Music]
because i saw them oh okay
oh god i don't like this map
oh no guru is in front of me
that's not good
shoot shoot shoot okay oh you're our
last hope right now i'm i'm doing really
bad i'm a zombie how am i my hope
that's okay
i got inaudible
hope has consumed zombie meat a lot so
we're good
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah okay
okay
did i accidentally hit someone
no okay be careful
yeah
oh
who got disconnected i got disconnected
wow
good luck guys
destiny is in your hands
i got number one i'm sorry i'm gonna go
watch one of
one of your
perspectives to see what's going on
so when i ate okay i'm last so
[Music]
well it was a valiant effort ladies and
gentle four hey that's two fours in
there four is a good number i like it i
can't say i'm unhappy
yeah uh was it great we did great
yeah
we had two disconnections so it kind of
doesn't count
yeah
and when i rejoined like my points are
all reset
yeah we had until we got disconnected
i got disconnected like right before the
last lap
oh no that wasn't me
that's friendly
cables
[Music]
but that probably means that you know
the last round if if riso you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round uh final
result is not really accurate um
but that's okay let's just say the last
round was an extra encore for fun
and
yeah and i would like to give out some
uh golden yagos
golden yellow
right
so okay they're not showing up on your
stream they're only on my stream but i'd
like i would like to give one a golden
juggle to ina for winning almost
everything
oh yeah
good job
[Music]
and i would like to give uh another uh
golden jaguar um as uh to iris for also
being absolutely amazing
goes to dana for being i guess the
strongest in the id team holy moly
thank you
goes to gura for being absolutely the
speediest shark i've ever seen
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
damn wild cardio
[Music]
[Applause]
another golden yogurt goes to muna for
being amazing
i didn't see you that much on the race
but i think you were still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
oh thank you the darkest time
and another golden yellow goes to ollie
for being also surprisingly indeed damn
good you were number one at the end
there
[Music]
goes to euv you are amazing so thank you
for participating
[Music]
and another golden yago goes to cali for
actually really you know i don't
you surprised me you surprised me callie
i was i was looking at you driving there
and i was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arcs is
she so good even though yeah
my mom was playing instead of me that's
why i look so good
good job kelly
didn't i didn't get last place even once
guys that was my goal
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you we love you moving don't mind
me uh chat i'm not gonna be able to fix
that now i think one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven
uh
wait who did i not give up
you were surprising me too sometimes i
have i had an eye on you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
everyone um i hope you all had fun um
can we get like a
last
last comment from everyone let's start
with uh anya
oh me
okay um that was so much fun but i have
to practice more
it's gonna be next time i don't know
maybe
there will definitely be a next time
yeah
there's always room for improvement
um
[Music]
kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is kia
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all this stuff ina as well for
helping with the assets but like
oh my goodness you organized the whole
thing and it was a blast and i just
wanted to have fun with my friends and i
was able to do that because you
organized this amazing thing just thank
you so much for for working so hard on
it because it was a blast
thank you i'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
[Music]
thank you i want to say thank you also
to ina and kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and i'm very i'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as i thought it
would and i would like to uh say that it
was probably because i fixed my switched
leg so i didn't have any lag let's go
gamers let's go
i'll excuse i'm sorry i watched and i
won though i can you said excuse me
yeah you would be so good
even though you haven't played the game
in a long time i think yeah no practice
baby
let's go raw talent let's go rob ellen's
charm
well well
from the last place
closing coming to you
ah yes so i'm just uh thank you for uh
organizing this i know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh beyond but
yes thank you for this golden yellow i
will cherish it and talk to you
thank you so much thank you too
thank you thank you okay i've completely
disappeared i'm sorry guys
[Laughter]
okay iris closing comment please
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament kiara and
thank you so much ina for the very very
cute assets
and
yes i will practice more
so that
we can i can get go against inaudible
[Applause]
thank you i hope yeah one day i want to
win against
inaudible that would be a big
accomplishment it's not that big of a
goal
[Laughter]
i'm so glad i'm so glad you joined holo
ian because that's what made this uh
tournament possible
i'm really glad to be able to join this
wonderful tournament be part of the cool
kids
okay i'd like to say a very very big
thank you to kiara senpai for organizing
this i've organized it once and it was
really hectic so i can't really imagine
the links that you go through
for
and even the thumbnails those must have
been hard and also for innocent wife for
making all of those assets so quickly
like you guys really um how do i say it
i really appreciate it a lot and i'm
sure all of us do so thank you so much
for your hard work it was really fun
playing with everyone and um i may have
not popped everyone but one way or
another you guys will all be my buttons
i forgot about that goal yeah
thank you
thank you all right
um first of all i'm thank you for you
kiara for organizing this thing and
thank you so much you guys can stop
thanking me
i mean
i i don't think without without you
organizing we wouldn't be like these i
mean it's it's it's rare to
gather all the whole live indonesian
whole event together like this so i'm so
thankful for that and also
um
big thanks to inna too for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and i hope uh in the future we can
be like this again
thank you
yes yes yes i hope so too definitely i
was thinking like maybe on on like
around christmas or new year's eve we
should do something
that sounds a great idea
okay
closing comments please
yeah i'd like to say a big thank you to
uh kiara for organizing it of course i
know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and
like schedules is really really
difficult but you really put a lot of
effort into organizing it commissioning
like the logo and everything really
thankful um and everyone feel free to
use your hats and cards like in your my
card streams in the future too
yeah thank you everyone for joining us
today like it was so much fun like
playing with everyone and um
it's been a pleasure thank you
thank you thank you nothing good
operation this was a great cooperation
between uh kfb and taco taco bell taco
eats definitely
we all blaspheme so well together you
know
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed because we're
faster
okay
closing comments please
okay i know you said stop but thank you
chiara
nothing
and
also inna senpai
uh thank you so much and i had a lot of
fun uh
there was a little mishap there there
was a little disconnection issue but
overall i had a lot of fun and i would
love to have this kind of tournament
again in the future let's do it you are
so good
yeah
thank you
i'll keep training so i'll get better
[Laughter]
okay so it doesn't end there i would
like to say thank you
to
everyone here also especially uh kiara
and ina like those are
amazing and also okay uh i'm really
happy because i could actually uh gather
and play with all of you guys here yeah
yes like
uh i'd appreciate more more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
i
i'd love to actually i would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much i
love you guys
thank you
[Music]
well first uh i'd like to apologize
if i was salty if i could say you guys
uh no
[Music]
you guys work really hard thank you guys
thank you everybody for participating is
really fun and it was hard to organize
these types of collabs everybody's so
busy and different schedules thank you
and i had a lot of fun thank you
thank you amen
now that we have home council we can
like we don't have to relay on these
exact 12 members anymore so next time if
you want you can do shoutcasting
thank you
thank you everyone for participating
today um i hope i hope everyone had a
great time even if you know maybe you
were not number one number two number
three that's fine i think today was
really just about getting together
putting um two communities two fan
communities of hello ian and whole id
together and just feeling united
definitely and i am always glad to do
stuff like this again so i will gladly
invite you guys again whenever you have
time for it and want to join and i'm
sorry that you know because since it's
such an international collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so i'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like 6 7 a.m or
something like that i'm so sorry i know
it's tough i it's no problem it was fun
i hope your mom enjoyed the tournament
i think she did i think that she's good
[Laughter]
hey
well well well then with that i would
like to officially close to holo ian
whole id mario kart tournament everyone
take care of your golden yagos polish
him every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly and yeah i'll see you guys soon
[Music]
you