hello world
workman
delivery date
Raise
my self
keep repeating
Nenorude
[music]
Now
Wait for the delivery to finish
The water was clogged because I didn't want to use it.
[music]
Gabu cat
The head of the global pandemic
It doesn't hurt, it doesn't hurt
I'm jealous
[music]
hey
Ganemoga
[music]
Misa, today, people, tomorrow too song
Don't make me feel like this.
What a hello world
Give it to me
Waldo's
There are more play screens for Mr.
Teda
Sleep together
ni name yabu
[music]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Aonya hello
Hello everyone, this is Elite Mikasa Mika.
That's why I'm here a little late.
What is it, Holo-sama hard call 1 day?
eye
So yeah, let's do it today.
It came in at noon, but because of the settings, it was today.
Karane Hardcore Hardcore Hanemiko 2 times
Chinami also did it
Survive with hardcore during summer vacation
That's what I've experienced so far.
Let's do our best to survive, do our best
So somehow the Nether is open today.
It's been done, it's been done, it's been done, maybe
It seems like it has been fixed, so I'll do my best.
I think I'll go for something daily.
Apparently there are missions and events.
That's how Pawpaw became a star.
I did it
Why is Panpan gone?
Why did the attack happen?
Yes, there was a precious victim.
I heard there was an attack.
There was an attack
What attack?
It's an attack
How many battles were there? Did they kill each other?
Attacks by villagers
It's a bit scary, so I'll go in for a bit.
change
[music]
picture
Ashiaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
It's like I don't know anything, but what?
Everything that happened is now over. Poloka is dead.
When it's all over, Po dies and when it's all over, it's Polka.
died and aa died
You're amazing! Hello, it's just me.
There was an attack event there, an attack.
That's right, it was scary, seriously.
Emiko is naked, but she's seriously too equipped.
You're seriously going to die!
It's dangerous, you better get ready. Seriously, how many shots are you going to take?
Looks like Runoe is coming suddenly.
It's a feeling, be careful, don't listen to it, wait.
hand
I'll make some iron equipment soon.
What kind of locker is Miko's locker?
Temiko's locker is Aramiko's locker
A locker at Kanakamichi
I don't know what locker I have yet.
I guess it's okay since I just came today.
I think it's good. I'm going to make this location for you.
Miko-chan's
Ah, this is a locker.
Is it okay to expose your neck? It looks like it's true.
I've always thought about Subaru's exposed head.
I've tried this once before.
It's funny, I'm a luggage dad, Kokohama
Where is good here? Anywhere is fine.
Okay, let's leave it here.
That's what we're talking about here, here, here, here.
It's okay, it's terrible
Here it is, after all, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is.
It's Haiho-chan's locker, so
Diamonds will be given here.
Please tell me a little about the diamonds etc.
Please, I don't understand Miko either.
Maybe you'll be like that, huh?
What is it today?
What are we doing today?Amikodaa everyone in the nether
Even if I say that everyone is
I guess I should go to the Nether or something, but it seems like it has been penetrated.
So it's 120 then?
Catfish is kind of like that regulation with someone.
Is it the easiest way to get that item?
I thought
I talked to 200 people in one day.
Yo
What, what, Mikochi Eata won and got the equipment.
I'm sorry because I was told to start from
Miko-senpai is like Miko-senpai.
Nyan please give me something please
I'm sorry, but that's fine.
I'll give it to you
Yes, it's an iron sword. Thank you very much.
Miko came late, almost unable to give something.
from
There's nothing, okay, I'm at fault.
After all, I returned it and got this from Ao.
Can't you even give me a dandelion? Yes, this.
I'll give it to you, red Poppi looks good on you.
Poppi won't do it either.
I'll tell you where to find the iron
You told me where to find this rule.
Have them read Rule Rule Mac first.
I want a rule book or something.
It's a rule, right? I didn't read it. Change the rules.
The book was taught to me by that Peko-chan.
This is the only rulebook
Thank you. There have been some changes to the rules.
But please stop reading this.
Well, if you read this,
That means it's okay, right?
So, senpai, where is my voice coming from?
What is this signboard? Is this a bulletin board or is it my voice?
Where?
Kanankamitchon Akorekamitchon
Yes, that means it's true.
I've probably heard the voice in many places.
By the way,
This is this, this is this, this is some changes.
Changes to Yatsune
This is the mission
Yes, this is today's mission.
There's a mission or something.
Well, it seems like there's some sort of event going on.
The Nether was opened today, so I went to the Nether.
Daya everyone goes to get soul sand.
I want to ask you, but I don't really understand.
What good things will happen if you line up diamonds and diamonds?
of
What good will happen if everyone has these days?
Manufacturing logbook What's Minecraft life like that day?
It happened, survival
If you don't have a diary, you'll get a discount.
Fuuchinchiro where you can make Masuchinchiro
I can do Chinchorori
I see.
You are free
You can make Nakai or equip it.
Let's Survive Glowstone
You can go to the Nether and get Sol Sand.
Go to get glowstone
A dangerous beginner to Minecraft who creates potions.
People who don't know how to get involved and have never been involved
and the two of us go to collect frog eggs.
Hechamichi enters the center of that hut.
So I finally drew a diary and here it is.
So please submit it here. That's true.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you for your support
Masu
Is this okay? Let's have some frog eggs.
Yeah
Yeah, are you going on that mission?
Something went wrong during the mission.
Let's go, wait, Taru's egg daya
It's 10, but seriously go there.
Please, please, can I say that too?
I want it so I can go to the frog.
How and where are the eggs?
frog eggs yes frogs
I wonder what the English language of Egg Mystery is.
I forgot where the eggs are, but I can see them.
No, wait a minute. Yes, wetlands.
The body is a wet body with diamonds on it, a wet body.
It looks like there is a silk touch in the blow belt
I have Silk Touch, but I don't have it.
Eataan hasn't been doing this since the first day?
Oh, I died.
That's why I became that lucky dog.
Yes yes that's what it says
It's here
Thank you very much, please.
I guess it's okay to make some equipment for now.
wait a minute
Wait a minute, that girl falls asleep so quickly.
I don't have a bed, but I'm a bit of a beginner.
I'll explain it to you, come here.
Thank you for coming here until now.
Polka-chan is that basic lifeline
He's got everything in order. He died today.
But Popo-an made a little comeback.
Get it
I wonder if there will be a revival or a revival.
Yes, it's possible to revive it depending on the paper.
It's up to God.
Yes, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you
Hello, hello, I was born here.
Please meat please meat please meat please
Did you hit me just now because you wanted meat? That's wrong, Miko.
Now that Kapon is hardcore, Kapon is
I really can't hear it, ginger fish
I also take Sakae DHA.
DHADH Oh fish too
A kind and good girl, a good girl, this one.
Please don't forget this.
Maybe it's loaded with food first?
Somiko Even since today started, everyone is da
I wasn't running, I was hit, I was hit, I was hit.
It got worse in numbers.
Thank you very much and keep up the good work
And papai papa
I don't know who is saying what.
Don't be silly
What do you mean, your speech is bad?
Oisho Oisho where there are a lot of people
Hamiko-chan seriously has that one-chan equipment
I feel like I'm going to die, so here I am.
There is a free one
Thank you so much Kyukyu Chanane
Oh, there's meat too, I received it, Ochan.
It's on the way
Either way is fine. Cut it in half.
Tokoseka made it, that's amazing
I thought they would give me the ball boots for free.
I'll get this too. It's warm and I can carry a bow.
I wanted to give you the bow, but my voice couldn't reach you.
Thank you Yasuma for crossing over there.
Hey, I'll have some Tenkyu right away.
Yes, yes, that's it, thank you.
Looks like I'm some kind of hired dog.
Thank you very much for your support.
Well then, I'll just introduce the equipment.
Miko-chan, thank you so much, you're so kind.
There is an iron trap, so take a look.
It would be really bad if chan died like that.
Yeah, let's just fix that iron equipment.
Well, here it is. Come to think of it, the iron is splashing.
That's why I heard about the iron Suma-chan.
Hey, today at noon, that's all I heard, okay?
After getting the iron equipment done, I felt great.
Please let me know if there's anything you don't understand.
You have to take care of your life, it's dangerous.
[music]
I'll get 10 diamonds anyway.
I wonder if there is a wetland that soon?
Wait, this isn't it.
for now
Leggings like this
This way, this way
Wait a minute
Stop feeling like a creep if you don't do it.
No, that's because everyone is there.
I think it's a little sad because everyone is there.
Thinking
Don't put it away
Hey, let's do this
Seriously, I don't know when I'm going to die.
That's what I said, but it's true
Miko has been pulling out the hand feeling.
I'm really trying to survive
I'm going deeper into the Nether.
Even the fact that I went to Oishi is true.
There are quite a lot of different things available
Where I want to do my best to catch up
be
Washing
Well then
picket
Mimiko
Shibeko
I'll just get together with Zuko and see later.
vertical
I want a key. I have a key.
I heard that today
noon
Something I don't understand about Oishokta-chan
Please contact me if you have any questions.
Masuoshi
Okay, yes, I've equipped it.
There are two Tademi rule books.
Wait, I want food. Food.
But today I'm going to play that Mitch for now.
I decided to go to that Nether as well.
I don't know if it's okay, but that nether too.
I feel like going for a while
Can I have some food here?
I don't know, I can't bear it, but I'll take it.
I'll get it, I'll get it, Adeko's chicken
Is it okay to buy
Kapiki
Oishokoshi
I'm sorry.
Oh, now that I've let you go, I'll have to wait a little longer.
Wait, wait, wait for the chicken, you
Miko needs meat
That's okay, I want to bake it.
There's no fuel
someone's
Tokorooishooishoondechomo 1
Check out the bulletin board
Let's go, it's raw meat.
I feel like I want to solidify my equipment a little bit.
I feel like I want to solidify my equipment.
I've heard about the Neso-so diary. I've also heard about the Neso-so diary.
Tayo's diary is this and that at the end of the broadcast
Should I draw it?
Fill in
I want to build a house.I certainly want to build a house.
I want to build a house, I want food, and I want armor.
I want something strong
That's what I want
It's right at the end of the neoshi broadcast.
I'll do it at the end of the broadcast, so leave it for a moment.
Isn't it a good idea to lose it like this?
Today is the first day of Ruhrbok, so let's start with
If you have trouble keeping it, you can look at it.
Jande
[music]
Yes, that's right
Well, let's just take a look around here.
Let me grill it over there.
And what is this?
Soraya This is Akiya This is Akiya Self
I want to build a house on site.
[music]
Bunny wants to build a house
A garden bunny garden has been created.
First of all, go to the Nether to get Sill 30.
Go Daya-san Glow Stone You can also do this.
With this and this, you can kill 6 Jangusts.
This is difficult and scary without a bow and arrow.
Na
Defeat 3 skeletons
Ugh
Skeleton Skeleton may be removed
Well, here, here and here, 16
I don't know, but I don't know.
Amiko Tepae How are you all doing Diamond?
I got all my equipment and I left it underground. Diamond equipment is
That's right, everyone probably went to the ground and dug.
And there was a dick yesterday too.
It's a dick, after all, it's a dick.
I don't know if it's that guy.
I don't have it, but oh yeah, that chichichi and all that
Where is that and the attack base?
Yes, I wonder if there is? Look, I see.
Please, what is this, what is this, what is this? I bought a lucky Tsuruha.
enemy
Ta
What's this? It's twice as many diamonds, okay?
If Tajanja is going to be doubled, then that's it.
Give half to Miko
It can't be helped
Just for a little while
It's okay to give it some time, like 3 real diamonds.
Three diamonds or something like that.
I wonder how many diamonds I have right now, even one.
I don't have it
I can't use it, no, no, it's a different Lyrica-chan.
I don't have one question because I saved someone who died.
Yo, I'm lending 30 yen to Rade-chan.
It's 30 yen and that's fine, Emiko Senpai.
What is your senior?
Yes, what is that?
Lose
Is that okay? Yes, you.
Is that okay? That's true. I'm in my 30s.
I'm the type of person who likes it best, isn't it?
I'm a small fry, yes, it's true, I'm sure, it's fine.
Kayo asked me if I could just leave like this.
If it's Akani, this is also necessary, right?
I'm going to Nezha after that, but I'll be with Mikoka.
What do you think? If I do this, I'll go where I want to go.
I want to go to the village without getting hurt.
You want to go, right? I want to go too.
Let's go to the Nether from there.
Let's go to the Nether, where can we go from there?
If you pick up this sand or something, you'll get diamonds.
Yes, yes, yes, by the way, the fortress.
I mean, someone found it, but it's not like that yet.
I haven't heard of anyone discovering it, seriously.
Ekore one-chan is available reading diamond 30
I want to become an individual, I want to become a 30.
I seriously want to reach 30, I really want to be lucky.
I'm sure there's something like this out there.
Wait, what? By the way, if you go backwards, you'll be fine.
Chan, I just want a little block.
But there are stones and other things everywhere.
Is there a stone?
Yes, it's not a cobblestone.
That's the kind of stone I want too.
I want a stone, I want it, I want it.
please
Please, me too. Is this life? Please, me too.
Of course I want it, I'll give it to you. It's infinitely mysterious.
Give me anything
I'm not saying anything, but I can give it to you.
I said "only love" "woah wow" it's crazy
There are dangerous enemies, there are dangerous enemies, there are dangerous enemies.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous.
The colored one is so hot!
Yachi yabee wa Ouk go Ouk go take it
No, it's okay, I can go ahead.
There is d
It's not a good idea
Hey, let's go somewhere a little brighter.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
There's only so much I can hear.
Oh, I heard it around here. Okay, these things.
Where did that guy go?
I guess this is what I want to go to, Mikochi.
oh
Hello, is it okay to use this equipment in the Nether?
Eso
Is it moyai?
hey
Tanki
[applause]
I want to do it
[laughter]
Let's find it together.
Sure, let's all divide the pile.
By the way, that means if you defeat one
Something like that, yeah yeah, maybe one person
I wish I could defeat him, that's what happened
Let's all go on a mission together
It doesn't matter if you clear it or not.
Right, this probably won't work, wait a minute.
Rather 303330330 without 150
Isn't that right? That's not true. That's not true.
Isn't it 5?
I'm good at begging, so I live by begging.
I'm sure because I've been living only on eggs.
By the way, Subaru also had a lot of trouble yesterday.
I'm sure this is a bit confusing.
It doesn't say that everyone who can go is 30 or one person.
If you say yone, it's yone deto or us.
Can't we get 150 yen for the team, Shirayuki?
We've gathered too many people.
It's a little messy
Yukimo-kun
So let's go snowy, let's go snowy, let's go snowy, let's go snowy and snowy
Let's go
It's like snow, Religo.
Hole is a little dangerous Shin hole is a little dangerous
Well then, I'll wait a bit and go to sleep.
For now, I'm going to sleep one time at a time.
After all, if you say you're staying overnight, talk about it.
What would you do if you received 30 yen?
Let's talk
That's right, you're in debt, Nasu-chan.
After all, I had zero plastic yesterday.
I went back to bed and picked up some music.
someone is picking it up
Shall I go get some stones tomorrow?
I'm not home for now, okay?
I'm going to go get some stones, so I'm going to explore 4 again.
I'll bring some stones for you, cobblestones.
I'll give you some cobblestones.
Wait a minute, didn't you mean to die?
It's because everyone at home is digging a lot too.
I thought that would be the case, but I'm grateful.
I hold the cobblestone like some sort of Subaru trash.
I feel like where is that garbage?
Yo
I smell a lot of them at home too.
There's a lot of cobblestone stored there.
I thought it was me there and there.
It's my own land
I can't let you get caught here
It's a Subaru because everything is included.
That's how I use it. All I have is a diary. It's a lie.
I'm keeping it at home with you.
I see, I also have a Nema Subaru at home.
Well then, there's something about Subaru-senpai at home.
It looks like a half block so I took it from the house.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, huff
Block Block This is it, right? Hello!
Nya hello
[music]
I'm new, please be kind.
Please, what are you doing? Let's go to the leather.
I thought and equipped it
I'm aiming for Too Ikkaku Senki, Ikkaku Senkin, no.
I can go, Ikkaku Senki can go, I have good luck
I can go here, here, here, here.
64 stones from Subaru Senpai
Yes, is this cobblestone enough?
Maybe I need to stop cobblestone.
To be honest, today's mission is difficult.
That's enough, I can give it to you.
That's about it, but there's still a lot more.
Masuyo
Wait a minute, am I like that?
Let's have a half-baked meal. It's better to bring it blue.
I think it's good. I understand. I'll make it a little bit half.
Everyone, Senpai-kun, and Subaru are in a huff.
I'm not going.
Hey, just now, let's take a quick look.
I came. Was it too scary?
Let's all defeat the enemies in the Nether.
It seems like an exploration
If you find the exploration fortress, it will cost you 30 diamonds.30
Diamond for sure
After all, when I told them that I had found it, everyone
Can I get it?
This is my first discovery
30 Where did Nese's senior disappear and what happened?
Where are you, where are you saying?
Meow, meow, this is my first house.
It's a bit annoying, so don't worry.
I don't have it, so I decided to get a diamond.
I didn't know what to say, so I took the trouble to answer.
It's like I'm going to go there, but it's true.
I have to add this myself
Equipped with dayadayadaya
Please protect me a little bit, Spa-chan Miko.
Today's equipment is just poop, so please protect me.
I see, I have some diamond money, so let's lend it to you.
Is it okay? You can't win for free.
What are the conditions? I can't lend it to you for free.
But now I have 5 diamonds.
This is already the final diamond.
Final fire, the final final
fire final fire final
Because this is fire final fire
Well, well, there's a little bit of interest.
But if you say that's fine, then fine.
in
If you get 55 pieces of rice, you will have one now.
I want to make at least one piece of equipment from
That's right, that's good
Okay, well then, Lissie is fine.
How much does Chinami look like?
Well, even if it's only for one day, it's Sebal for one hour today.
I dug it up and found about 10 of them.
It looks like it's good, so Mikochi too
If you work hard for a day, you'll probably get about 10 pieces.
a
Unjae to toe 1 and 1 and 1
and 1 and
That's right, the moon doesn't look blue on the first day.
I wonder how long I can go here
It's so good that I feel like I went for a round trip.
No, that poop is in the nether too.
Let's go together, let's go, okay, okay.
Janko okay okay choo okay
Well, Hina-chan is probably back home now.
I'll take it home and lend it to you for now.
Thank you, thank you too.
Oh okay, Miko-senpai, Subaru-senpai is attracted to me.
No, it's not the same, brother, let me lend it to you now
How much is Toton no Somiko and Minami?
which one
About
No, now Miko, by the way, that unknown person.
It's in good condition, but it's hard.
The core is experienced people, so yeah yeah
Yes, my reliable cat will survive.
I think so. I don't know if there are 4 or 5 days left.
But then, are you okay at all? That day was okay.
Yes, I'll lend you this.
I'm ready, Aki, please go home.
Just a little bit here
Wait a minute, wait a minute, let's go to Senpai.
That's what I said.
Thank you for this Senkyu Senkyu
Thank you, I'll wait a moment.
don't die
I'm dying, there's no way I'm going to die. A cat is an experienced person.
That person is you
You rolled up this guy, how did you get all fired up?
Maybe
I'm thinking of making a meal, so I'm ready to roll it up.
You're rounding up Tae, that's what you are after all.
This server is so tough right now
Because he is a dog, he was criticized for being harsh.
I was told to wrap this up okay.
here
That's the way I play baseball if I want to get into it.
Looks like it's round.
No, no, I don't care whose evil it is. Wait a minute.
Just a little bit
Wait a minute
That face is so cute, it's impossible
is cute but no, she's not bald
So everyone,
I got it
You should check it yourself
[music]
Minozou hat skin is much more accurate
It's getting better, it's from a different setting.
My
A rolled up thing is a rolled up reflection.
Maybe everyone should roll it up
Teda
What did you do? How did you do it?
What happened to that setting?
I don't want to be like that.
It really suits you, Yada-chan, with black hair in the front.
Be like Gerardon
I'm going to go. It's good. I'm going to go.
Masu
Yo everyone let's go
Yoko option option is not available anymore
It's already buzzing
It's dangerous at the office.
Dogi-chansu
Come on, I'm going to live now
I want
Anenankaikai
It's cute
Chane everyone group photo group photo and group photo
Koreru
This will be the last time as there is a possibility that he has disappeared.
There is a possibility that this will be the last group photo of
There's nothing wrong with bangs.
It's cute and red
It's a cute loge
Ochimo
I feel like I'm going to survive by waiting, I'm definitely going to survive
It might be the last time. Can we wait? This is the last time.
Maybe it's something like that.
It's like he's looking at Kia-chan.
Enter the name line of the teru lie
So
Roge Sugi-chanwa Minato
Let's go, let's do our best, let's enjoy my summer
Please wait for me at the door, Anji.
I guess Sani wasn't coming, right?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming too
If you're going to go after Ina comes, what should we do first?
What should I do with my diamond equipment?
What are you going to do now? Go to Nezha now.
A path to explore
The fortress is coming down, and I haven't found it yet.
It seems like there isn't, so when we all looked at it, we all saw it.
It seems like I might be able to become the first person.
You didn't write that there was only one person here.
Stop doing that to the dog, come over here
I don't have work here right now so I won't bother you for a bit.
Can I do that? It's a bit of a hassle.
I want to see everyone's food, everyone.
San that diamond
If I could get two boki diamonds, that chisto
You can also get a plate, but that's true.
There's something
I'm pretty sure
Senpai really hasn't come to chat.
Wait for it
Te book pop!
Hey, someone please give me one diamond please give me one diamond
I have 1 seed of Suma-chan, but it's gone.
Oh my god, what are you going to use it for?
I wish that outfit was a little more like that.
I borrowed diamonds from Detsuba-chan and now I have 6 diamonds.
If you get two more, you can get a test plate.
I can't do it
Thank you for this as well
Well, it's 10 times more in one day, so please give me 10 times more in one day.
double 10
Multiplying 10 is 1
I'm sorry, but can I go to E-chan?
Are there any diamonds? No one has diamonds.
What happened to Kana, why did Mikoto equip it with just one?
I can make it! What kind of diamonds can I equip?
This plate is like a jacket plate.
A little bit of a blue
Thank you so much, what's going on with your smile?
It's a bit difficult, but even if I really quit
Threaded Tsuko-chan
Noi is so kind, Noil, right?
One more thing, it's true, it's true, there's only 7 left now
There are seven of them, so yeah, that's it.
It's okay, Omiko, it's starting today.
From today onwards, I'll make a comeback, thank you.
I'm going to grow up and repay you.
Mom, Iyaso, Suba-chan, Noel is
He's such a good kid, he's so caring and kind.
Channia
She's a good girl
No, I didn't have that kind of heart.
It's okay to be like a no-no boyfriend.
Oh
Nemino
My friends are saying they like it, but I'm going to eat it.
Perfect, perfect, perfect, everyone is so kind
N
Yes, it's more like Alone Hardcore
I only have 10 pieces of meat, which is better this way.
I don't have 203 I have this.
After Polka-senpai died, did everyone else die?
I wonder if I have a dream or not
Rummy's meal, anyone? Akutan Supermarket
It looks like TTT made by Akutan.
Hey, but it's in the Nether, so let's go.
You can go from the Nether, then from the Nether Nether.
go via nether
hey
I'm sorry, I'm Misumi Mizu.
Is it enough that I made a mistake in getting wet?
I wonder if there's not much in the Nether.
Nami, wait a minute, I brought some milk or something.
Is it better? When I found the point, I did it.
That's it
Is the milk okay? I've already brought an infinite amount of cobblestones.
Well, I'll share it with Anya-senpai.
What should I do with the rice?
Thank you, the center of the village, the center of the village.
Shall we go? Shall we go to the village?
[music]
Big sister with big sister's breasts
I'm glad I can go, Kia is fine.
It's probably okay
It's okay, it's okay
I want a bow that I can go to, but I don't have a bow.
Is it better to take it with TTT? Even without a bow.
Let's hit
I don't have a sword either.
Wait, can I just make a workbench?
I'll just make a workbench for a moment.
There's a lot of people there. There's a lot of people there.
You are here, so what will you do? Keep your eyes open.
Mikoto's cherry blossoms
I guess Miko's body is similar to Sakura's muscle type.
Who is this?
I'm sure this hasn't turned into a green pumpkin.
I don't mind if I meet his eyes when I wear it.
No matter what I look at, Anya-san is no good.
That's what Anya looks like.
That's right, I'm wearing a pumpkin right now, so why?
If everyone is facing the ground, what are they flying?
Let's go, let's go, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Let's go let's go let's go let's
Go
I'm scared of the bed, so I'll leave it there.
[music]
What is this?
If there's something like that, it's okay.
It looks like it will be used, so I'll leave it like ``Senri progress fast''.
mosquito
Popi holder I received from Najasuma-chan
Tokoyoshisho egg mojakka let's go
Let's go Let's go
It's okay, it's okay, it's time to start fighting
TTT is here TTT
It's here TTT I see it's here
There are still fortresses in fortresses, what's that junior doing?
I heard a rumor that it's near a portal.
There are times when I have a junior close to TTT.
There was a portal on this side.
Isn't it?
Thank you everyone for preparing it.
TRUE
It's boring
This is really helpful.
trap
You can go from here
Okay then which way should I go?
I like that it's a place that hasn't been fully explored yet.
Well, it's true, it's scary, but it's all on the wall.
Don't push it just a little bit.
Yeah, but I'm actually exploring.
Well then, dig it on the other side and do it the other way around.
How about digging here or there?
Even though the ghast's voice sounds dangerous, it doesn't kill the ghast.
And indeed, if you kill a gust, it becomes a diamond diamond.
Karakogga makes a lot of noise, but...
I went inside quite a bit and I also rode everything.
Kurendami-senpai asked Matsu to do his best, Matsu.
Yes, Matsu is coming. Please help me. I'll just wait.
It's the thinnest but it's okay
[laughter]
Souko's feet
I'm fine. Please take the scary money.
Oh, that's the entrance
Saehako makes a sticky noise
Wow, what is this fortress? Is that Kamimichi?
What kind of road is that? It's not that different.
Isn't there something different at the top?
The one on top of Moa isn't a pig's block or something.
Takana
It's like a brick. I understand, I understand.
The scary magma won't fall, so I guess it's okay.
Miko-senpai: It's true that Policebar-senpai is the one who killed Matsu.
Oh my god, this is so dangerous Zabu
stop stop stop stop road making
Yes, I understand. This is a good message.
It's a game, this is that shift shift let's
Go Shift Button Shift Button Shift
Button Let's Go Shift Button Let's Go
Shift button
Go, I'm in danger, I'm in danger, so I'll save you.
Disidence
Ne Game
I have no other job than playing gruesome games.
Let's do something.
I'll dance, I'm saved, I'm saved, I'll collect this, I'll collect this.
Tetenka's voice
What, pipipicjipicjipicjipicji
Zipicji
Pick Pick is terrible, Ji Pick is terrible, I opened it.
Big hol big
hobihobi
holby
Sifrecitre
It's dangerous
Dangerous Shift Shift Pressed Waiting Fee
If you don't press the equipment button, it's okay to equip gold.
gold equipment gold equipment large gold gold
Equipment Gogolets Golets Golets
Golets
Go, how are you doing? Everyone, how are you?
Somehow, there was a glow tone
Stone, just go get Glostone.
It was like a roasted stone.
Is that really bad on that one?
Wait, what's that? Oh, what's that?
That's all I can do, even if it's just for a moment.
What is that? What is that?
Is that the one from before? Pick it up!
Nii's Fortress Janpic's Fortress Fortress
Maybe this is the way to go
Can you please block this?
The point is this is dangerous and the actor is here.
It's really strong
Awesome
4 I don't think I'll get this
I'm sure I should take some pictures of this too.
Everyone at Minade-Nami watched Minade-Member at the same time.
Everyone let's go let's go
[music]
Maybe later on, I'll attack the money here.
There are some really good ones too.
I wonder if I can go to Stone?
It's already far away
It feels a little dangerous, though.
But I'm sure
I'd like to make this a landmark.
It's totally fine, just say it's fine.
Good understanding
This is so refreshing
I said, ``I haven't heard of a fortress.''
Well, it's true that the reason why the fortress sleeps
I'm the one who finds it all the time
Try going to the other side
mosquito
Yeah, wait, let's move forward.
Actually, I want to go to the other side, but as expected.
That's scary. Gust has come. Where is he? Go away for a bit.
It might be good to take a look here.
Go glowstone take yeah take glow
Glow because you get a stone diamond
How many stones did it have? There's a hole here, so I'm curious.
Please put it on everyone
[music]
Yes, Ron wrote that he just put it in his mind.
hand
I don't feel scared
I feel so bad
Follow me, everyone, follow me too.
Wow, what are you so scared about? Come across.
I'm not scared. I'm not scared.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm waiting
That's not good
This one is the scariest, gosodemiko push
That's true, but I really don't push it.
I'm really pushing it, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's scary, it's really scary
I mean, push it.
Or are they just comedians?
There are some red lumps that are impossible.
You can go, right? Distorted Nomoruka?
Even the distorted mushrooms should have gotten diamonds.
That's the red mushroom.
Be careful with the red one, there are pigs there so it's dangerous.
That's what it looks like, so I went a little further.
If you look at it, the red mushroom is a distorted mushroom.
Isn't that a distorted mushroom blue?
Kino is blue, don't call me that, shall we go?
I'm sure it's all decided for you, but there's nothing to be confused about.
Cat is okay
Nakochite
I have to go get it
Good luck
Oh my goodness, I came here.
Wow, is this enough? There are enough stones.
I got a lot from chan
Nami will write for them as well.
Okay
Isn't it good to waste money all the time?
Good job
Okay, take it.
[music]
Neoi
Mito comb
Tae Grownstone Block Everyone
I guess glowstone dust won't do it, I'll die.
Things are new
But my eyesight was so bad that I couldn't touch it.
It's okay if it hardens. It's okay if it's hard.
Or just lend as much as you want, as much as you want.
Block ah oh oh nice nice good good
Okay, take it.
[laughter]
Everything like this
Okay, I wonder if it's falling?
Na
Oisho
[music]
Did you get it?
Na
Too scary
I don't want to name it, but I'm using it as a shield.
I haven't done it
Teyoshiko's haha is the beauty of hardcore.
Isn't it the joy I feel?
Is Yoshiko okay?
In this way
Everyone got theirs
this
It's okay
[music]
Okay uncle
chan soul
Danger
[applause]
[music]
I'm alive, I'm alive, I'm alive
Teru teru teru teru teru from where?
I forgot what I said
It's dangerous, I'm glad I'm alive.
If it wasn't for diamonds, I would have died.
I also collected the cha lines.It would be better if I had this and that.
It's better if Miko-chan has it.
So if it's dangerous, drink it.
Please help me, my hands are shaking.
Huge yes
This is crazy
It might be better to cut it red, too.
I think it's better to go because it's not.
I was shaking.
It's best to avoid the red forest.
hey
What should I do with this? It's so red.
Mon-Are-senpai, what were you looking at when you said it was a book?
Is it true here?
It's okay, it's red over there.
Looks like it's going to be red this way
Let's go, let's go, even if it's impossible, it's red
There's something about the forest where people are bound to die.
There might even be wild boars.
The fake one is
There's no way I can defeat it.
Oh no, wait a minute, Ina is fighting.
Ina, what are you fighting with? You're a shitty mushroom.
different from
Oh it lasts quite a while
Is there a book? It's true.
Oh, it's a blue kino. One by one, it's true. It's distorted.
You should pick that up too.
I'm sure that will make money
You look scary, lay on the bed, stretch me out.
Let's connect them together and make some stairs here.
Maybe it's okay, let's make these stairs here.
Maybe it would be nice if my dog could pass by here.
Although there is also
[music]
I'm going to go there and there.
That's right, yeah, probably. Seriously, the pig is serious.
Strengthen yourself
Kukamiko who is doing this blog from Karako
There's no way I'm going to make the bed explode.
absolutely
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
But just now, I really thought I was going to die.
I'm glad to be alive
Teyoshiyoshiyoshiyoshiyoshiyoshi
By pushing
Now how many makon can I have?
Did you have too many things?
Neyoshi
Google
It's stuck in my butt
I did raggu
senior
It's a lag, it's a lag
So don't press it. Don't press it. Don't press it.
Don't push it, don't push it, drop it
I'll give it a little bit. I'll give it a little bit.
Okay, we're doing it. We're alive.
That's too bad, right? Hey, there's magma at the top of the stairs.
This is going to turn out to be scary, scary
I feel like it's always going to be great here and there.
I will
I will kill you.
[music]
It's too ok to do this from here, it's powerful
It's not true, it's true, it's true, it's true.
I can go there.
You can get off from here.
Wait for it to arrive, nice nice ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Okay, let's do this, let's go.
There is a green mushroom in the red part of the pickle.
It's over there. It's over there. It's over there.
There's one on the back of the jama.
I have to collect all of them at some point.
Hey too
Taoisho
Explored with Koe Mochi Red Forest Hardcore
No way
Oh, I think it would be better if it went through that wall over there.
I will
Na
[music]
hey
It's okay, it's okay
Kamikochi is scary, Subaru is scary too. Who is he?
The one who said go to the red forest, Aqua.
Aqua Aqua, what are we doing here?
If it connects with the mushroom, it will connect with the mushroom.
I see people who want to pick mushrooms.
I said go get me some mushrooms.
Let it flow
I'll connect it with the mushroom and get it for you.
Goya
I'll wait for the bag to turn upside down and come back blue
Yo the best, the best
Best
Damn it, what should I do with this?
If you cut through this, it's pretty red.
hey
I have no choice but to go slowly, passing by the top all the time.
There's one more. Stop.
This guy is too light and dangerous.
Stop it, this guy is going to the Nether
I'm not the one, but I'll give it to you. Good luck.
I'm giving it to you so I'll pass it on to my seniors, that's amazing.
I'll give it to the amazing Picochi Akimasumi
Thank you to my seniors for this
I'm a little scared so I'll do it in that safe place.
That's right. If I drop it, I'll pick it up again.
Yes, I was really scared. Let's connect next to each other.
There was one more item.One more item.
Sorry, it's okay, I'm not around here.
Magma is terrible, I want a little more depth.
It's probably best not to rub your shins too much.
This dangerous go, oh, there's a go there too
It's better not to have it because it was there too.
I'll go get some.
I'm going to go get it as if I were using it.
This isn't a place you can just walk to.
Yodou each other
corner
Yes, it's really far away
Very
far
The sound is really scary
But
Right side okay blue
Oh, it's okay to fall. It's okay to fall.
I want to fall down there, blue
I'm back
There are two mushrooms here.
I have two more to give to you.
There is also one pig, so if you defeat the pig, you can go.
Nebutabuta is dangerous, this is also true.
I feel like it's probably better to just push through.
Either way, I'll cut straight through once more
I went straight and crossed
It's better, okay, okay.
This way is straight, I think that's good.
Oh, we'll be the first to find the fortress.
Is there a fortress?
Believe me there is
What kind of place is the fortress near?
It's hard to find a place nearby.
Yeah, I'm sure that pillar is scary, I'm already scared.
I'm scared of talking on shift so I'll take a detour. Thank you. Thank you.
But there's a wall over there. I can get across it. This wall is coming.
It's almost here. I hope everyone's okay.
Teruaki
Come with me
There are good and reliable mushrooms.
But it's the first day, and I'm sure they're doing it on the first day.
It's not a thing
What to do on the first day of
Not good?
Don't wait a minute, that's great.
There's Sol Sand, there's Sol Sand.
I'm not saying it was a collection match, but it's pretty good.
Toko that T
The water elevator is definitely okay, isn't it?
Namire
Should I put out the fire or should I put out the fire?
There's enough distance soon.
Oshio
Oh, I wonder if we'll be able to go home properly in the first place?
Well, I wonder if anyone has the bait coordinates?
It's okay, I've taken a screenshot so I can go.
No, Asasuga, I forgot about Sasugami-chan.
I'm sorry I'm a little off here
I've been called, so I'm going to come.
Give it to me
Leave it to me
I don't want to die. Press shift.
That pinky is so cute, I'm going to catch a fish
fish
Yoshidondoma, yokodondoma
Hey, are you okay? Yes, he's a dog.
Poor guy, he's a dog, get it.
Done
Seriously killed
If I don't kill you, I'll kill you, I'll die, I'll die.
What did I do, what did I do to get that soul sandwich?
Let's go get some soul sand, I'm sure.
I guess it's okay to have as many soul sandwiches as you want.
Maybe I should get some soul sand.
No, what is the target? Is it a mission target?
This also has soul sand as a mission target.
That's right, there was only one.
There wasn't just how many, so how many?
It's scary and dangerous because it wasn't there.
Oh, you're too bold to fall.
Don't die today. Predict who will die today.
Let's go, what's going on, who's going to die today?
I can't predict what will happen in the movie.
Well, there are some who will die first.
No, I think he will survive until the end.
I'm sure you'll survive and be strong, thank you very much.
fence
I'm sure there's no dog left at all
It's like something out of a horror movie.
[laughter]
Mostly in taxis
Zahanimase
That's right, I'll protect you.
When you look at it from behind, it looks amazing and your ass looks amazing
It looks like it's waving
Funny frilly frilly dangerous
Oh, it's a dead end, it's open, it's open
Hmm, seriously, it's too open, there's nothing there
It's an open type one, isn't it?
Hey, there's only one with messy hair.
Behind
Not okay
It's coming, oh, it's so open.
It's amazingly open.
Great job
If there is nothing, go up or up
It's true that it's wrong, but it's dangerous, it's dangerous
If you go to the top, you'll end up on the other side.
That's right
Well, on the contrary, the situation is more like
I don't know and I'm scared, wait, wait, I'm scared
Seriously scary, seriously scary, what's going on?
Climb up or go straight to the side
Scary indeed
Emiko's
intuition
Thinking about Eno falling here and there
Let's turn a little. The soil over there is green.
Yo
Eh, somehow the soil over there has turned a little green.
The terrain is red, green, and green.
Apparently there was a terrain. Green terrain is no good.
It's not even in the green area.
I have to avoid that area because of
I see.
Okay, let's go this way.
Can I rely on Miko-chan?
I'll leave it to you, my senior, who is doing Matsugakari.
It's scary, it's scary, it's scary, it's scary, it's so shaped
Yay yay
oh
Hello, I'll delete it for a moment, it's dangerous.
from
Okay
Is there any?
red here
It's Kaamada Red Forest. It's Red Forest.
Neyo doesn't like anything else over there.
I wonder what it is like?
What do you think? What do you think?
We shouldn't cross to the left.
left red forest
Even if I go straight, there won't be anything.
It's scary, isn't it? I'm sure there's nothing there.
But isn't it a little far away?
It's too hard to see, so if you're going to go, go to the left.
I find it easier to bend straight
It kind of looks like it's definitely brave.
If there is, go straight, it's scary.
Can you hold my little finger?
No, it's true that I'm holding it down with my pinky finger.
Take a quick look at the half block.
Okay, okay, then everyone will be there.
I think I'm going to go. Looks good.
Well, if you say that, I'll follow you.
We'll be in danger together when we die
Oh, nothing, nothing, absolutely nothing, nothing.
No, nothing, no, I'm going home.
Return, return, nothing
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm too scared.
I was surprised even though he was a bit of an elite.
There is something beyond the forest where there is a forest.
Hey, that one on the right is probably a forest.
If I go straight to my back like this, something will happen.
That shadow seems to be true.
Maybe it's on the other side.
I'll go and see you. Wait a minute.
Well, let's prepare the block.Mikochi is sure.
I have quite a lot of mikone with blocks right now, so I'm digging them.
I guess he's digging there because he's doing it.
During the live broadcast
I just don't know the way home, the way home is already
Let's trace this, that's the only thing
I'll leave this behind on the road like that.
It's pretty easy to get home without getting lost.
The terrain is really strong, it's strong, blue
It's reliable after all
It's actually blue. It really stinks.
It's amazing, so please change the top one a bit.
Please leave it to me.
I'm starting to relax
Take a break
In this way
I hear the voice of Eigast, but it's not there.
Maybe the time will come when we have to fight
Maybe it's time to prepare.
Maybe I'm reliable.
I wonder if I'm bad at reading stairs.I went out.
I'm scared of Nenebuta.I wonder if the pig will open it a little?
Let's open it, how scary
What a mistake I made
Let's open it.
It's a little scary, right? I understand.
Oh, green mushrooms near Glowston
One person found a green mushroom and said that green mushrooms are also good.
I feel like I'm going to play without one, so there are four.
I'll do my best to make up for the only thing that's mine.
They are collecting it.
The mushrooms aren't far away.
To go from
wait and see
Let's see now and this pig
teeth
red likely
So what?
Gachan's work
Shall we go over here?
[music]
There's a pig, there's a pig, wait, the pig's voice, the pig's voice, the pig's voice, the pig.
Very close pig pig pork pork pork
Pork Small pork is terrible. Pork is absolutely terrible.
Kane
Wait a minute, they're shooting, shooting, shooting
It's okay, it's okay, you found it well, Chiara.
That's great.
Nice, nice, wait, it's dead, it's dead
dead
is
Chi
After all, he became a victim of a terrible death.
A death that is too close to home and dangerous is a physical death.
Oh no, oh no, come back,
Let's go home, don't become the next child.
It's raining, wait, hold on a second
Wait a minute
Tete pig
pig pig dies
Ah confirmation confirmation battle confirmation death
I thought I was going to die
As expected, I am living as a bulwark.
I got scared.
It's okay, it's okay, everyone's okay, everyone.
Are you okay
It's amazing, who's doing it now? What's going on?
Even Kia, which is happening, only has a sword.
This is better
It's too much to knock down
It was Senkyu Magic Panic!
Hey, there are quite a lot of Gigtato here, so it's really sad.
It happens to me a lot, probably a lot.
I'm so scared, somehow I'm still alive
Wow, nice. I'm glad you're alive.
Good
I really want a bow. I want a bow. I want a bow.
I want a bow, right? I want a bow.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
The ones with bows are Chiara and Ina, and it's dangerous.
I have it.
As expected of a bow 2
Books
Do you want one? I have a broken bow.
But one more thing
book
[music]
It's okay if the magma doesn't feel very good.
It's okay, it's okay, I guess there are other directions as well.
It seems like everyone is watching, but I really want to go.
Okay okay okay here, magma
Apparently
But if it's a little broken, there's another one.
How about Masuyomasu Kanakakurakaraa?
When you're dead, it's already time to die.
It's true, I'm going, wait, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Danger danger
Aomee
hit back
It's perfect
It would be dangerous if it came in sideways.
[music]
It's normal, nice
I am so grateful, so grateful
Too true
[music]
Before I knew it, I was covered in netherrack
It's getting better
Hey, it's okay, you won't get lost.
I remember the way, somehow, somehow
I'm trying my best, but I guess I understand somehow.
I wonder if it's okay, it'll turn out somehow
I guess it's pretty much all right.
I'm a little worried, pig.
It's a book with a voice.
It's money, it's money, it's money, it's money, it's money, it's money, it's money, it's money, it's money
It took
Rutte
That's terrible Popo Straight Ghost Straight
What if I open a hole and find magma?
No, it's puffer fish right away.
[music]
Yes, but there's something about cutting through a wall.
Hey, it's connected to the fact that I'm a little angry.
I don't think there's a connection.
I wish there was a picture of this
It's true It's making a strange sound It's strange
A strange sound, a mysterious sound, what kind of sound is that?
I might have opened something, wait.
stop stop stop stop
The stop voice is so loud that everyone laughs.
Space feeling empty inner attack inner attack
Now Now Winner Attack
Seriously, I'm so grateful for that flight.
I laugh at something like that, but somehow
Savvy attendant, leave it to me in a loud voice
Attention please, it's eco-dangerous
Okay, but it's still a forest, it's still a forest, the forest is too deep, isn't it?
Akamori Akaakaji? Akamori is too good to be true. Fly away.
It's like a light called Puapuwa that comes out.
When it's red, it's like a red anesou. It's not red at all.
There are many red, wide forests that you can't escape from.
strong
Nesenkyuu
[music]
Senkyu
Are there any traces of food?
It's amazing that you have all the subjects. Don't say "all subjects"
That's different.
I wanted to say that I can rely on you.
That's not true, Red Red
Foresta Red Flesh Red Flesh this person
It's coming back, there's a real possibility of that happening.
It's annoying in my voice, it's just in my annoying voice
red
There are a lot of Frestredfrests.
Wait, it's a mushroom.
I don't think I'll be able to go this far.
Kake
It's scary
I guess it was that sturdy.
It's not a good idea to jump into something like that.
It's equipped with diamonds.
I'm coming back, I'm coming back
It's so weird that it's so weird
Ze
Yes, I think I'll just put up a pine tree.
Hey, thank you
There are more Koushi
That's helpful
Helpful, no help
It's scary and scary when I get out of it
Well, it seems like it was different at first.
The number of mushrooms that were harvested
123456 Do you have one?
Okay, now all the mushrooms are mushrooms.
It's the end of Nopact. I did it.
Ta
Now stop it.
Well, it looks like a staircase.
It's quite spacious and is popular.
Nene, look at Miko, whoever it is, it's definitely us.
I wonder if it's wrong. It means I'm back.
Please leave a comment.
Don't come back
It's not like I'm home, but I'm back.
This is it
Once you receive the email, what should I do?
The only thing I found was Kino.
It's so hard to deliver, I wish I died.
Because it doesn't become so Kino
I also went to Glowstone.
It's Gusto, I'm sure I can go there.
Gust, something's not right around here.
Sansa, this is the road I was thinking of going on earlier.
You can go and check it out right away.
Just the straight ones, guts and fortresses.
Return
Okay
It's a waste of time, I've come this far.
It happened
of
Yoshikoshi
That's hardcore
Yes, I'll definitely take a look
Just take a look
I've become yonaka 1
Where is Takoko?
here or here
Let's just take a look
Just a little bit
[music]
Na
Ai
Namashita Kocchi Kocchi
Everyone went back to the village
Taaaa
[music]
now
Oishokocchi
way to
Thank you for joining
Senkyu, mine
It's good, I'm good.
Na Senkyu
Is there something?
It's fleeting
Is there a fortress or not?
Now if Miko finds a fortress, she will get 30 diamonds.
Mikoga
Let's get it
Tenatsutsu
It's a joke
But
Are you afraid you'll fall?
tto
Tsuruhashi
Wait, this one is better
Hurry up
I found it
But it's dangerous, Pig's 4-year-old first witness is stolen.
Where is it bad?
Where's the pig? I'm not going to take the credit for that.
Zakoshi
Okay, wait a minute.
Yeah picket
Pique Is it okay to do this? It's okay
[music]
Apparently there's photographic evidence.
Hey, did that take time?
Hey, that's pretty deep.
It's quite long
Magma is suddenly dangerous here.
[music]
Yes
Yosho, it's dangerous
They're dangerous, but they're amazing.
It's the end of today, so don't worry about it first.
Is it okay if I take it away?
I'm sure the reward is
that kind of thing
mosquito
Eh, this is red, maybe.
It's not deep. It's not deep. Yeah, I'm a little shy.
It doesn't look like it at all
[music]
Yeah, amazing.
I guess it's long
Let's go here
Good morning
digging
It's okay to dig
Will the ice ax that I've been working so hard on be about to run out?
fear
It's so scary, so scary I had to hold down shift while doing it
Okay
[applause]
[music]
It was dangerous to eat
Eh, I'm glad you shifted, Washin.
Holden okay, I opened it, oh my gosh.
[music]
Is it a forest where you can't see anything?
I can't see anything
hey
I might want to go up.
[music]
I feel like August is generally on top.
Oh, Gusto, yeah, I definitely haven't seen Gusto either.
Yeah, yeah, I'm just asking Miko.
where
[music]
Well, I went that route.
Stray
I'll go pick you up
I'm going to pick you up here a little bit up the stairs.
I might make a way back
[music]
from
Good luck to you
I thought it would be great.
Ta
noishooisho
I'm at Oisho Half Block.
That's it
Tekochika?
And so on.
How is everyone?
Kaoishooisho
Oisho everyone
where here
I guess it's on the other side
[music]
Yeah
It means that this is not the case.
Looks like there was a shipwreck.
What's good?
Gas came
Oh, be careful
hand
Take care, be careful.
It's okay
Yeah scary
one person is scary
Yominna
where
I've become a cat
Ta
Nkoko
Where did you go back here?
[music]
Hey, I've arrived
Is it a little scary here?
[music]
N
Yeah
[music]
circle
It's scary
Wait a minute
[music]
I was there a while ago
here
more visible
Iruka
It's scary
scary
Hey, I just stopped on the road.
[music]
That's the location of the half block.
Oh I see
I felt it
completely
this
Over there
That's scary
Wow, that's scary
cormorant
It's scary
Seriously, it's scary.
Be afraid
I'm being targeted
You're being targeted.
[music]
Wow
Tasty
bad
I'm nearby though
Pig is digging now
[music]
It was scary
It's on this side, right? Gust's voice.
[music]
I can hear it, it's right
Gust
There is
Eh?
Teru
I'm scared, but I'm willing to do this, everyone.
I wasn't scared because I was there, but it's okay.
like this
Gust around here
[music]
Everyone who's not around here
this
[music]
Is everyone okay?
Everyone
Not here
It's this one
Everyone is gone
Maybe you should sleep?
[music]
Teru
Everyone can't go down here.
Neya
[music]
Yes, definitely get off the boat.
Even so, there is a gust now
Too bad
It's dangerous, everyone
death
Toko
Yes, it's Minity, which one can I go back to?
It's okay because I can go back there.
[music]
Maybe they're fighting right now
I feel like everyone is like that
I'm being targeted
Everyone
Dangerous Kia
It's okay
[music]
Na
Aiaiai
[music]
This is terrible
run away
te te te
That's it too
Iimikobuta Nifubuta
and gust
I can't go there because it's blocked, please.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
Great win
Great win!
It ends when you fall
[music]
What should we do? Everyone go home.
do not have
Please explain it to me
O
Oooooo
Yoshikia
fart
I came here at the right time. What, what, what?
Oh, I was about to get killed by Ii-chan.
Thank you, why did you say that?
No, why would you do that? Around the walls.
There's only a wall, and Mana-chan is also a wall
That's what you said earlier, that face is terrible.
Angry
Teru
A yamikochi girl defeats one gust.
Tandabut yeah nice nice one shot
One shot was a headshot.
Wow, gas heads are the only ones.
Is it true that it's only a head?
I don't have one, but hey, there's a lot of pigs over here.
Tanoaja
Helmi
It can't be helped because it's a special attack. It's a special attack.
Their lives are gone.
Octopus, octopus, here, right here, right there.
I'm here because I came from here.
I'm here because I came from
Daoooooooooooooooooooooooooooo ok
Near the end
Okay everyone, I think we can do it.
I'll go that far, nice.
Nice hey oh good I'm with people after all
I should have been there. I was scared.
Alone
Forget about the Jamiko small fry equipment.
It's okay. Thank you for your hard work.
Nora
[Laughter]
Come and sleep now, Jesus.
Aja
In Yoshi
road
Orut a straight
go go go go go go tunnel
[music]
Go Go, Yosu-chan is here, Kanae team.
do not have
Where did the jump go? There's a ball on the opposite side.
I did
But that's enough
ah
If I wait over there, I should just wait here.
mosquito
I haven't made the stairs here, so wait, Miko.
Senior, yeah, there's a road here
I just realized that.
There's another way here, what do you mean?
It's true here too
I wonder if Mokocchi was doing this?
Ejakocchi is Mikotachi's path
There are three roads
There are three roads.
Why are there so few demons?
Where did Subaru-senpai go?
I don't know where it is, I guess it's on top.
Atekakochi is what is this?
This is not the way
The door is on, so I'm on my way home.
I'm on my way home, it's a lie, it's convenient
[music]
Why did you go so far?
I'm back, but
cormorant
[music]
Is that Summa-chan okay?
Why are we here?
I'm back to Yeah Goes
It's okay if there's just some meat, Rudo.
Put it here
[music]
Tokoa Pekora-senpai is back again
died, so when that person dies, a rabbit will come.
Oh god of death
oh
dead
You can also rap
I'm crushing it
Dachan says I will go home then.
Oh, what should I do? What should I do?
I'm still looking for it. I want to see Gusto.
It's nice to see
I guess I was walking in.
Well, I don't remember this one, but I think it's this one.
Yeah, this is it, right, left, left, how did we do it?
I've been protecting it
Probably
It's so funny
If I do that tomorrow
Eh, why don't you go to TTT?
this side
Yeah TTT
How far is it?
mosquito
Yoshiun will meet up with Sama-chan.
Kaa oh
[music]
Where is Suma-chan?
You can go from home.
Hey
Where did we come from?
That's right, yes yes yes
Jesus is this way, I'm sure
Yeah here here here here here
He's fighting a ghast right now.
Subaru Kast and
Now during the war
It's here.
Taoshi
Oshika after all, that place from before?
Are you okay?
Good job
Oishio, if you come this far, you're inside.
Maybe it's this one
[music]
Yoisho, this is the pig below
It's already dead
Or if I'm not the top, I'll kill you right away.
Senkyu is okay
I'm making stairs now
Oh, I returned it yesterday.
hey
[music]
Okay everyone, Ao-kun goes home first.
I was selling it in the chat.
TRUE
But I've come this far
politely
No, please come
Oh, I can't hear it, maybe it's too close
I feel like I'm nowhere.
[music]
But where did you go?
Is it good?
[music]
I got the hang of Huffblock.
Where is it going? Where is it good?
Should I go upstairs?
I feel like we're on top of each other, we're passing each other
I see
It's not there
hey
This is what happens if you get separated from Gust once.
Things to remember
Communicate by mistake
Rutte
It's hard here Oh, and then I go over there
After all, it's not this straight.
Kayo
I guess so, it's far but I should go.
There may be something
Wow, but Gust looks scary here.
If you get shot, it's over.
Just leave it half a little longer
There are still a few blocks left.
There must be a road over there.
[music]
There was a road to Kia and the others.
mosquito
Located at Nakoacchi University
[music]
do not have
Hey, scary, scary, scary
Yo
picture
I'm back, I'm here, I'm here, I'm back
Oh my, are you alive? Yes, are you alive?
I'm glad I'm alive
challenged
Yo
I was in trouble, but I was going somewhere else.
It was a completely different communication, yeah, seriously.
I ran away when I was alone.
Well, I guess we ended up going.
After all, I reached that goal.
The last place we broke up was Anjan Yappa
That's true, so we have to move forward into the unexplored area.
I mean, that's the portal where the onions are coming from.
I said I got an onion portal. It's a little blue.
But for now, I'll just let you deliver the mushrooms.
If I'm sure, then I'll go home for now.
Ah Thor Sad
Oh oh this way
or
Okay, there's a pig over there too. After all, there's a dangerous pig here.
It was so scary, I thought Mimomi was going to die too.
There's Terushi-chan
Let's do it, I'll do it for you.
It's you, please be strong
Go back, go back, go back, it's not here.
Wait, wait, wait
dangerous
That's a lie
I can't pass that kid
Comfortable person
[music]
Wait a minute, this is the second time, so this is
There's no coming back now.
[music]
Not
I became angry
Please God, why don't you collect diamonds?
Our
[music]
All of us who are friends can't move
My friends, it's a lie. Go back home safely.
I'm sure
For now, let's get home safely. It's dangerous here.
This is Suma-senpai
Surusuma lent it to Dadaiya.
[music]
Let's go here
There's a lot of air in the air.
Are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay Ana, that's nice. That's nice.
[music]
You're such a nice guy, you can't protect anyone with a bow.
lost
go back
Don't worry, I and everyone else will die.
Everyone would die, but if they had more power, they would have equipment like this.
didn't come to
It's not my senior's fault, it's my fault.
No, everyone has their best bow and arrows.
I lost the good guy because I didn't have it.
It's delicious.
I only count what I've lost
Looks like I have no choice but to survive to the tune of my seniors.
He did well, lived well.
That guy who was alive lived well.
I can't believe Minami died that way.
Wait, I hear the pig's voice again.I hear the pig's voice again.
There is a pig that can hear the pig is scary and hungry.
Teru
I'm close to eating
Pig O Pig Pig
Pig, pig, pig, please, please.
a
Where is this?
nice
[music]
nice oh
There's another pig we can't let our guard down against.
It's a dangerous road, I'll go home
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's normal
Pig, here it is.
Let's go here, here, let's go
Nekocchi or Kocchi Miko Senpai here
Okay okay okay
Okay, I'll go home and get this.
Senpai, Senpai, please come back.
[music]
I'm back
Power goes to the grave, goodbye
Koyoga was given to me by Arasu-chan.
poppy live here
Shou-channi
senior
Here's Su-chan's
Flowers
[music]
I can't stand it well
Tahohoho
Ah, don't you want something a little more beautiful?
Eat something
That's it
I'll put up a sign so
Okay, it's getting misleading
[music]
Senpai, I have a lot of power, so it's good for me.
red
Just a little bit
fire
If only I had more power, it would be a little more red
Do you have mushrooms? If you have power, it will be red.
Mushroom, that's the last one.
This is a childish thing.
Oh well, if this is it
Thank you, I got this from Suma-chan.
take care of diamonds
[music]
Hey, I'm going to die
Hey, he's already dead, he's already dead, he's not making a sound
Wait, it's okay to do this.
Wait a minute, it's more than small.
death person
Ares-chan, Ares-chan, Subaru dies
It's okay
I'm sitting
Why are you alive? Why are you alive?
There are so many decorations, even just a little.
yeah
Otherwise, there's an iron nether boat.
I want a nether boat
Even if it takes me to come back to life, I'll come back to life
I'm glad to hear that.What are you doing?
I can't tell you otherwise.
Thank you for your hard work, Cha-chan too.
The Subaru that came is no more. This is also true.
do your best
Return to Subaru Mario World
You forgot too much, look at me like that.
I saw my heart, stop flattering me
Don't be too quick
Mushroom and sweet bean paste
[music]
There was also sole sandwich.
In other words, everyone hasn't found the fortress yet.
Right?
fortress
We still found Green.
But I'm going to eat pom-pom rice.
Ponpon rice for rice
I know I have to follow you
Tapopo also died, didn't he?
Popo died, died, when I came in
I'm glad he's already dead. I can't see Popo again.
I thought there was a ring on my head
Dechomiko becomes stronger
I understand, I want to become stronger, like this, a ring
I'm glad I don't have a ring on my head
No, no, no, I can see it
Only Hamiko
Only Miko-chan can see it.
Hey, you're back! You're back!
Chako died
I have some rice here as well. That's good.
How much can I receive from you?
That's okay, I'll get you a baked potato.
That's fine, don't take it, daddy.
I got half of it. I want that item.
Hey Miko, I got the set amount.
I wanted to do some Paw Paw work.
I wanted to do it.
Thank you, Yamiko-san, shoot me if you want to do it.
I can't play a bow right now. If I have a bow, I'll have to sleep.
It's okay, I'll have a hard time picking it up.
If you get that, I'll make a potion.
He wants me home
Zeo
If you're bothering me, I'll get in your way.
Go back and endure
No, why?
[music]
Hey Popo, what are you doing now?
It's only one death, so it's still an acceptable death.The next death.
A lot of systems have probably changed during the end.
But today's polka is doing something on its own
I hope I can come back to life
Yeah, I can do that again if I die next time.
I guess I don't know at the time
That's how it feels, isn't it?
Because it's haku haku, it's important once
Yeah, it's tough, but it depends on how hard you work.
I understand, I understand. I was just filming the grilled meat.
Thank you so much for just that.
I gave it to you. I used the extra diamonds to make diamond equipment.
It's good to make it, and popo is also mixed in.
Now it's over
Thank you, I killed your cousin without permission.
It's okay to ask, just keep doing it.
thank you
I left it in the egg, so I brought it here.
I'll leave it alone, thank you very much.
from
If I go out, I won't be able to shoot a bow.
Oh, I think I can do it.
I'm going to go, I'll do my best, I'll do my best.
I can't help but try harder.
I'm coming, I'm going
I'm going to go
All the bows and equipment are ready.
Teguga
The sports club before the game.
No, this is your chance to build a fortress.
Let's find it!
I'm good
good news
I wonder if they didn't notice me. It's dangerous.
Don't forget the dangerous mission
What will you do if you do that? I'll write it all down now.
I can get diamonds, but I can get diamonds.
Tomorrow, I'll go to the locker room with diamonds.
It's a sandwich and it's a sole sandwich
[music]
Eh tomorrow tomorrow diamond
taste mushroom
Ah, distorted
Thank you for the mushrooms, I applied.
Of course Miko Kureta is also a university student.
This is what I'm talking about.
Dust, everyone get glowstone.
The one that doesn't exist
Piglin, I have, I have.
Or am I?
It's a glow storm
Hey, here it is. I got three. Yes, I made a mistake.
I'll leave it here just in case.
No, I couldn't defeat Gust, Gaani Sword.
Give me a sandwich, of course, of course.
This is a lot of chatter here
Because it's around here, this is Seoul.
Sand and
Senkyu, this is a mushroom. Thank you.
I'm throwing away some things, and now I'm Nemopan.
wait a minute
[music]
Not even bread
in
Delicious
You can give me some mushrooms.
I want that diamond, it's blue with mushrooms in it
Yes thank you thank you thank you
thank you
Misoka Sole Sand that the broadcast ends
Sorun is right.
Looks like everyone is going to disappear.
No, I'll do it some more.
Listen to the sound of the sound
strange
It's strange that Ka-chan suddenly came. It's true.
is
Where did you appear that day?
I have to write a diary
Nehi Amiko-senpai Miko-senpai What's wrong?
I'm going over there to look for Chiara and Gust.
I'm going but I'm coming
4 I wanted to find that bow, nice Yami-san.
I thought I'd make one, so I got a bow and I don't have one either.
Karamia Oi
I'm sorry, I'll bring your luggage.
[music]
I feel like sleeping, thank you
Thank you for the book
[music]
Thank you so much for the mission.
Thank you Oshi
Thank you very much
There's not enough
Minamiko Miko-senpai, thank you for your hard work Omiko
Miko is back. It's great that she came back.
One person died. Oh, I see, it's Suba-chan.
We were in the same group. We were in the same group.
Even though I didn't get to meet you, I didn't get to meet you.
I went to Mario's world.I went to Mario.
What happened, everyone?
I don't know if it won't come back again, but
This is the second time Sasu-chan has said that.2
I wonder if it doesn't work the second time2
I wonder if it's the second time. It's weird because it's a real diamond.
I said please give it back, so in kind.
what's the real real diamond real
Give me back diamonds
Eh, that's the original one.
Well, if you die, you're dead.
Does that mean Daramikochi is a widow? What now?
Are you doing that? I'm going to TT now and I'm going to play the bow.
Get it
I think I'll look for it in the Nether.
The first person to discover something has 10 diamonds.
Apparently I can get it for 3030 lines.
What are the other three going to do? They'll run out of iron after this.
It is possible to increase the amount of iron resources that are currently available.
I'm thinking of making another trap.
I'm gonna make a truck yeah trap yeah now
There's one over there, but the other one
Make another one in the back.
Thank you, it's a diamond chance.
I guess the lack of it is on this side, isn't it?
Use your head
Is that so? If you find it, please let me know.
Please, it's a shame. Yeah, I'll try my best. It's a shame.
Yes, do your best, do your best
Don't be stubborn, just come back
Teru
Just don't die, everyone else will be sad
Even if it's flattering, it's dangerous to say 64.
It's hardcore, this is dangerous, it's next time.
Shall we go get one stack and half a roll?
I understand that you just did that.
Straight
I wish I had it here
I died while raising the flag that I was alive.
Stop living now
It's like I'm already dead, but next time I die
It's too bad, I'll probably die already.
I wonder if that's the case, then what are we going to use that extra life for?
From now on, earn experience points and become stronger.
I'm thinking of becoming one.I want to earn experience points.
I was thinking of going to Titi together.
Let's go, Miko and the others were thinking of going too.
Is that so? I want to read it.
Same thing, I wanted a bow, but only the bow burned out.
Yeah, actually, it's sad. It's really sad.
Okay, let's go together, Shokocchika.
I'm getting it, but it's amazing.
Akoya-chan has come back to life
I'm glad I met Nami-tan.
I'm already sleeping today
I'm glad you sent me a DM.
Yes, that's good, that's good, that's good, why did you die?
Yes, why did he die? Why did he die?
That's why Lami-tan, U-tan, and the three of us died.
I went there and a gust came, so I guess I can protect it.
When I was fighting a gust, it turned into magma.
I thrust into it and it looks like it's going to get wet
Burning death
I'm the one who calls it mackerel.
It's so harsh that I can't get sleepy
That's right, so I'll stream after eating.
Do it
Come on, let's go together
Please, it's really strong, so awesome
It feels like two kids.
Where are you looking? Where are you looking?
Teru
Seniors, seniors, we are cool representatives until the day
4 days left
But Popote, I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
I'll give you some food
Tami is my senior, in order of order, and Aneshi is my junior.
from
[music]
What are you doing, Pan?
you
I left it on Mmika's bedside table.
I'll bring it soon.
circle
I left it at Yoshipo.
Yo
Okay great name
[music]
Everyone doesn't have to go to sleep right away.
This is the world line.
Yagami World, even if everyone doesn't sleep, 70% of them
When I go to bed, I wake up in the morning and I feel like God, that's very true.
to
It's okay, isn't it? It's on the line.
I'm just scared, I'm scared right now
[music]
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I feel like the one who got the points was the one who went home. Earn rewards.
yeah
No
What's this? I always do this.
I'll kiss you when I go
So this was Miko-senpai's chi?
I think it was Kato who did it.
After that
Actor
Oisho
right now
They don't want me to go.
The one who noticed that the grass was different was Hachama's dislike.
They say that gari is Tunde's expression of love.
It's okay for a little while
[music]
Hey, I'm back.
I need to find a fortress. I need to find a fortress.
Isn't Endora Momiji also in a position where he can do the same?
Okay, here you come, my arms are already so numb, sorry to keep you waiting
I brought a bed and some food.
It means you have to eat. Eat rice.
You can get protein before you do muscle training.
I'll drink some protein. Let's go together.
Drink protein and become handsome
I wonder if it's this way or where.
I don't know, but I'll make a road for TTT.
I think I can go since I was there.
Yeah, wait, how much money did you get?
Unto court trial
I want to meet up at the Nether Gate
I'm sorry, Nether.
gate go nether gate nether gate where
You know, right here?
I don't know.
Takara
Wasn't that other guy there just now?
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's like that.
Someone came from behind while I was there.
[music]
Thank you for your hard work. There were also deaths over there.
I went back and forth, I went back and forth.
Tametekine died, no, he died.
Negi's friend died. It's the second time.
No more
I don't know, it's the second time, so what are you all doing?
go
I'm back, I'm back, I'm back
Should I write a mission that I won't forget?
What should I do? Bring this back.
There's nothing in the way.
Let's go to the TT made by Sakuatan.
Thank you very much, thank you, I'll wait
What happened to the guy who defeated Gust? This is the first time.
yeah
It's an item and a mission.
Be sure to take a photo while you're there, as a souvenir.
This is probably because there is a photo spot
Please check out the spot and get it.
Yes, of course you don't know that.
I don't know, that's good, that's good
I'm scared of that, it's a little scary.
I'll do it already
Anchan is on her way, so please come with me.
It's okay, I want to go with you, I want to go.
i wanna go
[music]
Return home
Bitten
[music]
Reading
That's right, because that's a flag, senpai.
It's definitely a flag, it's also a flag
Are you okay
Will it come?
[music]
Here
I want a diamond diamond
So many amazing diamonds
Kara
Awesome, don't be so flirty
Well, Karakara, thank you for the sweets, Unkara
sweets
Senkyu Un Senkyu World
Sweets Senky Nice tomeyou
Senky nice me nice
Zudomasozdon
Masozudonzudonmasomaso I know you very well.
Yeah, it's so reassuring to have Kara behind me.
I heard you better close the door, Dodo.
Oz the Dolphin Crowd is also amazing
I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.I took it.
Oh, it's too early here.
As expected of Janko Chikao
As expected!
Wow Kame Oruko Yay here and there
dakamo camolets golets gokamon
Come on let's go let's
Go Oisho
That's amazing, why isn't it connected in the middle?
Sure, but can we proceed from there?
Mone
search
What's more, it's open and it's a fortress
Looks easy to find Looks easy to find
That's right, there are even places that are open.
I couldn't meet you at all, right?
It's always been a red forest
I'm so scared that if I go somewhere else, I'll be serious again.
red
teeth
fear
KNOWKNOW Dono
Kakura-chan wasn't netherite yet.
Green onion
Ha hey sled
If I don't get that much sleep, I'm going to go.
Nodase
Oh everyone, this is an actor's grave. Oh, it's a grave.
This is the place I came to take the photo, it's too hot
A-senpai Ah, I read that A-senpai fell down.
It's hard for people to come, so I'll stop here
I wonder if I'll go to the grave PT sao here iron
[music]
There are a lot of swords
If I don't sleep, I have a bow. It's a little infinite bow.
I want to make
I want an infinite bow. I have an infinite bow.
Well, today's infinite enchantment is chan
There is an infinity of power
Seriously, even green can be turned into gold.
I just have to replace it.
As expected, the infinity in Yasou-chan's house
That color free free free free
I don't need Kara Emerald
is a crow
Can I get it without the card?
At a disco, if you make the bow turn like this...
[music]
Flying away
I want to do that too.
You've defeated so-and-so skeletons.
No, definitely, definitely, definitely
That's amazing, everyone, take it!
I will recover
match
Everyone take it and take it
I can't help it, I took the baby.
I took it. I want to give it to Nico too.
There's a monster that wants to take it too
I can't sleep because I'm so close
Take it, take it
Please send it to me
I took it.
It's back, I'm just waiting for a while
Wait a little longer than what's flowing
But no, it's not flowing, it's just my imagination
I was so surprised that I fell into water when I slept here.
I feel like I've been washed away
Ta
So where is the edge? It's a spot.
This is a nice tourist spot.
Okay, okay, send me a photo of your sister.
I'll send you a cat in the warm place I'll give you
yes
I want to make a bow and arrow.
You need a lot of it
The cloud goose doesn't come here.
I'm sure that's true. It's special, so it's true.
Yes.
I wish there was a place where I could change my bow and arrow.
The arrow is
It's pretty easy to make, no need for rice
picture
It's hard to see what's going on.
It's okay, the bow is
[music]
It's a cloud, isn't it?
I might buy a different bow.
hey
If there is a palm there, change the bow.The villagers wait.
Hey?
Are there any raw palms?
Is it there or not?
But I definitely want a bow.
That's right, that's right, me
I hear you want to make a bow soon.
hey
If the burning tree is so strong, why do you make it?
Well, I have a villager device, so I can make one.
certain
Ninanda Yashie was able to make it quite quickly.
I might be able to make some memories today, those palm trees.
Blocking is easy
I can't find a comic that can make anything.
Maybe it's not as good as the cat.
Wahichito
Because it can be made with
Yes, I probably have some left over while I can.
Let's make something together, shall we?
What should I do with just a little money?
get something
What does it mean to turn into gold? Bones turn into gold.
what
[music]
That's it
I want a lever
[music]
Nede
Burn
I don't know which guy I can use this for.
Shall we go back?
Yes, where is the infinite place?
of
I'm on it
Yay no Kaela
Ha, this is it, the place is Kaela House Go
Now
Oh man, let's go
It would be helpful if you could let's go tomorrow.
have let's
[music]
Go Ocha
Wasagayade
Good job
What do you want to do when you get home? What are you doing when you get home?
Tokona
Ta
Return
It's okay. It's okay. I'm going home. It's okay.
I heard some kind of scream
Are you okay
Eha
I'm drawing a lotus dolphin
It's okay
It's free
Hey, maybe Miko is doing drugs.
Good evening, I'm wearing this cute one today too.
Hey, what's that?
Something is wrong with Sui-chan being a little silly.
Takana is still a cute Sui-chan, Ponkosi.
I do, but it's a bit clumsy. It's my fault.
I can't count what's going on, Yose-chan.
That's right, Sui-chan didn't understand at first either.
[music]
[laughter]
Formerly fake
Dada
Bye-bye, I'm going to Kara's house.
Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye Let's
Go, Iida-chan and camera properly
I took it, infinite darkness, I got infinite darkness, infinite darkness.
Bows too
I wonder if Uncle Now has any left? Tato House
Ototle House Spor
Oh my god, this is Tato's house.
I feel like I'm just being pushed.
Looks hard
No thanks
Haslets
Golets
Golets Golets
Where is the house on the go floor?
Hey gust ah gust gust eh but
Run away
I died because of that ghast.
Daede mo gust fear fear rama rama rama
death
Teru
That's scary if you defeat the striker
Gust when you get the bow and arrow that you must get
too
I guess I'll die even if I try to get it and do some gusts.
Na
There's no way to save this world.
But I was saved and survived.
Yonema is no more, but Koyori is no more.
Sorry
So it's only through hardcore that people can become stronger?
I don't know if
My sister almost died once, but she won't die.
[music]
From now until it enters the magma
There may be
I'll go pick it up when I don't have it.
[music]
Masumi's comment, Mikosa, does it make money?
Was it Mr.
church people
Only that villager can do it.
It's okay, it's okay
If you have iron, exchange emeralds with Gozal.
I can do it.
yes
Sussu good sho
[music]
Stay
Can I get emeralds here?
mosquito
[music]
How much iron do you need?
Iron is running out
[music]
Hairy hair
You can have lots of curly hair
Janamo hair style and get
let's
to
[music]
Yeah
Let's go
Where is ka-rokka-rokka-ro-rokka?
[music]
Also, Kopo or Kopo also makes money.
mosquito
[music]
Yoshimotai
There's nothing left to throw away
How about some short pants?
Miko-chan's pillow panties in Kyoto today too
What is it?
everyone
Okay, this is it.
Hey
oh
everyone disappears
An old man with a silk touch
[music]
Ako
It's only 1 yen
Strong
[music]
Uncle Teru wakes up
That's a lever
Wait, Miko 2 also has too much bread as expected
There's so much going on here
It's time for repairs
hair
Meow
[music]
17 infinity device here
Maybe I'm sleeping here
This is the infinite device
Can I do it the next night?
hand
sleep
sleep well
more carefully
let's
Good morning
aquatic
Real aquatic real water-chan is not dead
infinity of
[applause]
Where did the infinite return go?
everyone
Where is everyone?
[music]
Opened
Ha, Amiko-senpai is here, Curacuraoooooo
Let's go Let's go
I got Naio Emerald 17
Is it enough for 17 pieces?
Is there enough?
good news
Where is my home?
of
ha village
The village
A certain wait
Jumpin'
jumpin jumpin
Jinta Jump Jump Love Aki Senpai
Take care
[music]
Senior male
senior
I think it's okay, it's okay, what are you doing?
I was wondering if that was the case, but now I hear Kara's voice.
That's it!
Welcome
Karakul yay
Nonono, welcome to the Imatetsu Trap.
I'm making it, thank you very much.
I'm planning on finishing it soon, so I'll do it tonight.
Thank you very much. Tomorrow, today.
I want to catch a zombie tonight, so please help me.
Please o
Hello, I'll go.
thank you
Oh, I see. Is it a zombie or something?
It's true that it's dangerous because it's low key.
I no longer want to be
Chiara is gone, Kiara is separated.
Taso
I can wait for a while, it's so fine
Are you okay
Have you already gone ahead?
N
Ohteru
Rashi
Oh this is
[music]
Kaa
Say it
This is the road
[music]
Kanekone ah, I can see the house over there
Taareka, yeah yeah yeah
[music]
I'm here
Wow
Pi
Quietly
Thank you very much
Should I take the damage I received?
shrine
[music]
hair
The strongest, the strongest, the strongest, I found the strongest
Infinite
infinite
Until infinite day reinforcement
That's it18
There's 1 missing and 1 missing.
But emerald
Wawa
Ohhh, will you trade me for some hair?
[music]
Nice
I received up to 17 items.
Diamond attack
Get a diamond fishing bridge with emerald
Can
Ta
Wow god gonnono
God
Awesome
[music]
thank you
Alright, that's it
enough titi
I can dig this I can dig this
level god
[music]
got it
infinite exchange
Ta
that
Senior, can I ask you to translate? Ahain
is
One of my uncles is a NEET and I'm currently working as a vegetable driver.
Is it okay if I break that?
I'm doing everything right here and there.
Nice that you brought it quickly.
[music]
Oh no no no
No, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, there's no village left.
Soon I'll block it. Okay okay ah
But if you do this once, the villagers will always be wild.
Well then, I guess so.
I feel like it was true after long negotiations.
But I guess it won't go back to normal.
I'm sorry, but I don't know what happened.
What happened to everyone?
Wait, it's coming out. It's coming out. I replaced it.
It looks like it might be fixed after all.
Even if I don't replace it soon, it will become fixed.
If you try to use it in multiple fields, it will become difficult.
It's going to happen
From nothing to nothing
Mugen Ahon
That's a human being out there.
[music]
Where are you going? It's okay, go.
Go home, go home, go home
Go home, uncle, uncle, where are you going home?
[music]
I went home
Even if it comes
I should go somewhere
Is Kako okay?
Na
My go
[music]
Nara no Ie
So when I got home, what happened to my sister?
Comb
Wow
It's true, wake up
Okay
That guy has to bring me a stick.
There isn't one.
I bought some wood over there.
I don't have enough money, or I don't have enough.
grow up
[music]
No, it's 32, but this guy is just gravel.
It's better to replace it, since it's out of place.
Okay, what's going on? Well, everyone's asleep.
Yes, that's wrong, but things aren't good here.
At this time
It's better to change it to an arrow trade that can't be done
I have to break that block once.
Hey, it's either that or that vegetable.
I broke the block. Wait, where are the zombies?
Maybe Kara-chan will make it for me.
That's right
I'm not using it right now.
Nokoko
Kakokona
It's tonight, so nothing has changed, just replace it.
I feel like I'm trying to
There's an arrow that says "infinite", but the arrow is infinite.
I don't need the infinite one.
I might try to destroy this thing here once.
After all, you should definitely replace it from the beginning.
[music]
Ganenankata
Toto Oh electricity
tree
[music]
That's helpful, now I'm an unemployed uncle
Hey
Senior Ni is going to pick me up at Imakane now.
I want to go to the Nether after this.
That's right, I want to make a bow and arrow and go to the Nether.
Oh, I haven't made it yet. Please make it.
It won't change unless it becomes a morning that I can't make
That's right.
If you follow Akara, Kara will probably make a bow.
I think, senpai, really, I'm going to make a bow.
Nono's dream
Come on, wait a minute
O
Oh wait a minute
Wait a minute, senpai Miko-senpai, above you.
Read this in English
[music]
I want it
Nice. You can bring me now.
[music]
Oh, it's okay. Oh, I'll be back in a bit.
Nemo
I'll go pick Niko-sanha up too.
All these people don't sleep
perhaps
I think it would be better for Yoikomoshika Miko to sleep.
Hey, I see, it's a zombie. I caught a zombie.
is
Oh this
So it's 70% but 10
people
Here we go!
Do you understand Yomiko Michi?
Everyone turned into princesses
For a reason
[music]
It's good Shokocchi
hey
[music]
It's probably this one.
Maybe I want to go back to the village.
But this is it, right?
Probably good
When I go to the other side
After all, there are some parts where I get nervous.
Karaaaa here it is here
is
It's ecocchi
It's Kekocchi
[music]
You passed through the cat village, right?
warm
[music]
Good job, good job.
I came to see you
Is it okay?
Na
Good job, I don't need some meat.
Let's finish it. Sorry for the wait.
[music]
height
Oh, that's [ __ ] again.
memory
talking about
Sorry for the wait, I didn't give you this.
Please keep me waiting
Hey blonde Domiko
Sorry to keep you waiting, Senpai, I made you wait.
Neine, this is good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Don't be silly
I can't help it, Chama-chan from Okaka High School.
I'll give you some too, Ha-chan. Here you go.
I'll wait for the meat, then I'll put my stuff somewhere.
I want to do this rotten rotten thing
What's this about putting rotten meat here?
You can't eat anything with 64 pieces of rotten meat.
[laughter]
I get food poisoning
Okay everyone, let's get ready now.
Chandaaki-chan, leave it as it is
Today
I'm going to go to the emotional diary I wrote earlier.
Let's go here, Tetra Otetsu.
Trap No. 2 completed
[music]
A lot of villagers
Villager Ekade Mikoyo is equipped with a nice house.
Is there such a thing? I borrowed it from the bancho.
That's right, I borrowed it from the manager.
Yes, I was told not to die any more.
[music]
That's right, I disappeared too. It's a baby again.
Well, I changed my clothes to yellow.
It's running out
But
It's Kekocchi
Yo
I definitely don't know Yoisho Miko's senior.
I ask you to
There's no way Masumiko will die.
That's a big deal, I guess.
[music]
Have you been able to stand up quite a bit since you came in?
Mika is Miko Hane Count 3
Time: 3 hours Yeah, it looks like it's less than that.
Because from today
Yeah, but I have diamond equipment.
I made it from the debt of
Yes, I owe money, but that person is already dead.
That's why I'm the one who binds the sky
But I heard about Subaru's Diamond.
made from
The ridiculous world of Mario is back.
I hope he's doing well.
Why did you come back?
Good job
[music]
I got it, I got it, I got it
Nono
[music]
God in
This is not God
[music]
Please take care of this guy
What do you think?
[music]
If you grow this, you will get a bow.
Should be babo babo
Miko also looks like a tadpole
This is Miko Nonono who is a bit of a good person.
Desumiko baboon here here here here chao-chan
Hello, Dad.
Oda
good for the whole body
I can't hold the shield of
[music]
That's right
I didn't have it
[music]
Tajami
But already
I can defeat it, I can definitely defeat it, I can't forgive you anymore
I'm sorry, that guy is serious, I'm falling down too.
Oh oh, nether, nether, go, nether, go.
Let's go to the nether, let's go to the nether
Let's go to the gozaza
I don't think I have a shield.I don't have a shield.
I don't have a shield
That's right tomorrow
Dada Let's Go Let's
Go die Let's go Let's go go
Maybe it's too much
Oh no, stop it!
Naka na no no
Read the card
[laughter]
[music]
No no no thank you, this bow is important
I want to add some more. This is it.
It's up to me to defeat Endora.
Let's put it on too, we'll beat you up later.
Let's be serious, let's live.
The last day I lived without it
until the last day
I wish I couldn't reach this place.
I think we'll meet here.
[music]
Teruyoishokocchi
I'll guess
[music]
Nekocchi dakocchi
is
First of all, it looks like Subaru's enemy.
N
There is still one season of Yoishomiko, but Iyamiko
I don't know what it's like to live in period 0 and feel that way.
Feelings make people strong
I feel like that
do
I'm going to take on the challenge with that feeling.
think
Oishoyoshi, I'm already playing Mario
Great, Mario characters are happy with this too.
Subaru's Mariji is what Yomiko also says
Because there was a place like that
I wonder if everyone can come?
I'm looking forward to it too
Good luck, this hardcore sadness
I'm sure Bowser as Mario Mario
I've come to overcome, I've come back, here's my senior go
Beck direction is different
Other people's shrine maiden
I came in vain, I tried to follow you
I'm sorry
Thank you for your hard work in Iaao.Thank you for your hard work.
Tired of the traps? Yes, the motivation is complete. No.
For now, I have a favor to ask of you.
Yes, why don't you lend this shield to a rich man?
Could you give it to me?
Oh, I want you to be a shield, that freebie.
It's better than going to get the one you found there.
I wonder if I should ask for something, but this is what I'm going to do
Kari
I'm sorry, I might have brought you here.
The infinite bow of Miko no President has been raised.
Hmm, my skin didn't fall off, I came back to life
thank you
I haven't done anything though
a
I wonder if it's 80 diamonds. Did you fall?
Also coming
This is Takore, I'll make you a potion.
You can take it, but I haven't taken it yet.
Wherever you go
Moyoshiko is really big in Endora
It all started with
from
Yoshiko
Toko
[music]
Okay, this looks like it's going to shoot something.
I feel like I'm going to hit a member
Is that scary? It appears when I don't sleep.
Yatsuo, I didn't sleep at all.
I just want to say thank you to my senior.
Oh, Mika-chan, that's right, I was looking for you earlier.
But I feel bad that we don't get to see each other very often.
That's right, I was digging a little downstairs.
Thank you very much for everything
Not at all, I'm glad you're back
So I borrowed it and started using the shield.
I borrowed it without permission, but this is also for the baby.
Isn't it better to just get it?
Who is the baby? Of course, Acha too.
I didn't have it so I got another one.
Give it to me
Bring me the shield, hold on a second.
Please, it looks like I need a shield over there.
[music]
Ayoisho
There's one in here. It was fine anyway.
Don't say anything, it's just another bad thing
This is for my sake so please forgive me
Please, it's totally fine, thank you
Let's go and make sure to return this one time.
Okay, I hope you'll see.
hand
Thank you so kind, so kind, so kind
This world is so kind. I met my senior.
Ki-senpai Kira I'm sorry we got separated.
No, no, that
I got separated somehow. I'm back.
chan nice acha nice nice nice
I want to defeat Gust this time.
About cat voices
Wait for the cat's voice
I want to make an ice ax
But I have iron
I don't have one
Hey, I need picket.
Neat aa kill or oh yeah yeah ah?
Please take a moment, thank you
Yes, it was originally Chiara's iron, Chiara's iron.
Secure
Ok, now I'm ready.
[music]
Okay ready okay
Yo, oh, there's this, now that I think about it, it's from there.
shield
Oh, I got it because I was coming home.
I have one, thank you, I'll go.
Oh, this time the demon will find the fortress.
Just go this way, the fortress has yet to be found.
It's not there, where is it?
But I don't know if this is better.
Boyfriend
Both Kaela and Doraemon God are so kind.
Or something
Everyone can rely on Caro, he's so kind
It's Yayoi Shoge.
I think you understand, but you can get your own bed with money.
Don't go, Dan
I understand, just leave it here.
Is that so?
That bed is terrible
There's also a cat
I put a lot of things there
This is what a pen is like
Okay cat maybe
Good evening, see you next time
Let's go to the back of this TTT
That open space looks nice.
[music]
Neoishi
Oishii, the one that stands out hasn't been explored yet.
mosquito
I wonder what's going on
let's go let's
go early kia
Jump early
However, since the strength is low, you can go very quickly.
It's definitely coming
Did everyone leave it behind?
[music]
be able to
Yeah
Where should I go?
It's probably better to go straight here.
I guess it won't hit the route here.
Looks straight
Let's go here
mosquito
Yoisho, this side
Something seemed strange to me, so I rejoined the path I was on.
That's scary
hey
I feel like it's moving forward better this way.
It feels like if we go sideways, we'll win each other again.
Yeah, I should go straight now.
early early early
Ane
Bye nice, I'm going next to you.
Is this too dangerous?
Oh no, I'm a little close to death
Ama-senpai when it matches the magma
Thank you very much
Is it me?
Please take care of Namatsu.
Masu Stella
Stella was quick
It became Stella Stella
[music]
I don't know if it will come back, I guess
Hey, I was back.
Thank you for your beautiful work.
Nesui
death
Did you leave the stone behind?
I'm glad I came and lived.
Taya
Beeaa
Ooi no Ooo
fear
Wow
It's amazing how the stones were placed properly.
Ma
Hey, it's broken.
It's not like he died normally.
yeah
is
That's what happens when you live with the intention of dying.
I'll die in the wind
Well, the feeling of living is important.
Namiko-chan has a lot of desire to live.
Yes, Miko will live.
Wait for it to dodge, it will be a plus, so wait.
This is so bad, magma is falling.
I've come to a place where it's not strange
Oh my gosh my scary
Okay, on the contrary, I feel sorry for the broken thing.
Oh no, if I'm going to die, I'm going to die, and my arm is properly broken.
It's okay, it's still there
There's also Yochi Daimon's picket, so I'll hurry.
I'll dig it, please. Me too.
I'm scared of steel, I'm scared of it breaking soon.
Yo
I should have had a new one.
What a disaster
Because it's so big, it's really fast.
It's so fast, it's like a cat moving forward
It would be much faster if Kia advanced.
As soon as I had it
too much
Oh, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
My heart is pounding
My heart is pounding so bad
[applause]
[music]
I can't do it
Tananka
The road has come
There's a lot of amazing magma
Toko
Dala
It's dangerous around here
[music]
I'm using magma to keep the cat from falling.
hey
Ga-chan is taking care of me and I'm dying
That could happen if I was stuck.
[music]
Oh, I didn't bring any blocks.
Take the blocks on the side, he's dangerous, he'll attack you
It doesn't come
Danger, danger, come here
mosquito
Wait, let's
go until it's over
Stairs let's go
Nice
It doesn't matter
[music]
in
Oh, there's a way, right?
Is that right? Is this a path that has been explored?
That's not our path, so beautiful.
I haven't done it
G
[music]
I just did it
mosquito
nice nice nice
tenkyuoh
wonderful
[music]
Oh hello
Don't come near me, I might hit you.
It's okay
mosquito
fear
Yes
[music]
Because it's good
Thank you
[music]
It's so scary
It's scary
Lever
It's a big guy
Amazing, they've made a proper road.
It's made properly
That's really helpful, even if it's a mess, I guess
If I go here, I won't find the same thing.
It's better to go somewhere else.
I'm watching both upper and lower.
That
I want to
Where did you come from?
I guess it came from over there and went over here.
Or is it?
[music]
What should I do? Where should I go?
Hmm, what should I do? Where should I go?
That's right, let's kill Gato, it's okay to kill him.
So where is the gust?
I already have one killer, Gasto Yatchiri.
Mika Spear
Tai Gusto
Camast
Where are you serious?
I can just build that house. That's true.
Hey
[music]
Sleepy
Hey, it must have come from here.
I came here and went over there.
mosquito
Please
Nyaha
[music]
Yo
Okay
Achievements are not removed
of
Wow, I defeated him so well, nice
Nice, I defeated it. I defeated it. Nice.
[applause]
[music]
Kioooo it's okay it's okay
Where should I go?
[music]
cormorant
What's wrong with Gusto 4 No, someone's face is too serious
I don't know, it's dangerous
What to do before departure
Rinse and go straight, there's no such thing.
I borrowed the path of another person along the way.
[music]
Shall we go?
I was so surprised
Ta
a
This way
[music]
I'm going to ask you how straight is this?
I guess this is why I came here
I feel like I can go home, for example.
But it's definitely a jump, but it's also the other way around
That's right, that's right.
Go straight here.
Someone said, ``Let's go and see.''
Everything I made is safe, so this is the way to go.
If I go, I'll probably come back.
Kaa
I don't know how to go back
If I do that, it will probably come back.
Is it no good if I take that or that glow?
If you pick up the stone, you'll get 2 diamonds.
That's right, come on, come on, let's go over there
Maybe I'll go back.
I think it's on the way home.
I had to take it off somewhere, somewhere.
Where are you going?
Oh, I wanted to see it tomorrow.
I don't mind if you say that here.
Na
[music]
That's amazing!
I can see everyone's names here and here.
From here
Oh that's weird
I guess it's all going back.
It's back, I guess.
Back to
Ta
Wow, that looks dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
It's dangerous
What, what, what happened just now?
I thought I was definitely going to die.
It was so fast that there was another person in front of the magma.
I can come out
After that
Why?
of
What do you think?
I don't even know what silk tachi is like.
I was provoking him, but he started laughing again.
in the nether
I think I'll go back with the cats.
This is the first time for this cha-senpai on that road.
That long bridge from earlier
I think it's good, I think it's totally good.
Kahacha no Hacha
It's just that Chacha died.
I happen to have no friends.
It just so happens that I don't have any friends.
I guess this is it
Once again, all my friends should be careful on their footing.
[music]
What's going on? Don't look at me.
Hey friends
Dying one after another
Magma fell in front of my eyes
I can't do anything
I'm dying
What is the purpose of the Shrine Maiden?
mosquito
recommend
Let's make a road
make a way for
Good job
That's really scary
If the scary Miko isn't scary, where should I start?
I think it would be better to make it there.
It's okay, it's really okay, that's it, or that wall.
Nakawatari or this wall?
A little scary goge caught in the middle.
Michin
here here here here
here, here, here
Ah, maybe next time money will die. Stop it.
Come on, you're kidding.
[music]
I'll do it, no, no prophecies.
I'll light up, I'll light up the way
I said yes.
[laughter]
twice
Called by a peer
[laughter]
Second time
Because of that
Yeah it's okay I love Chiara
Miko is happy Miko-senpai I love you too
We played a game together.
Itamon
hey
Hey, Miko-senpai, what's going on today?
I really follow that group
I was worried about whether it would be okay, but today
I'm happy to be able to hang out with you for a while
Yes, I'm happy Miko and Miko are both alone today.
Monmiko thought she was going to get lonely.
You won't be alone, Ka-chan
Oi Dragon Ball This World Dragon
Looks like it was a ball, Dragon Ball
Yes, and I'm solo. I don't have any solo friends.
Dobo
at
No, I've never seen Dragon Ball
I can see something
Tanka
[music]
Master
dangerous
Dangerous
[music]
Good job
What was this place again?
Na
Eia Charima Senkyu is possible
[music]
Lately I've been saying Indiana for the first time.
I've seen Jones' movie.It looks like it.
I thought it was the first time I saw 1 and 2.
I haven't seen it yet. I've seen it all. I haven't seen it yet.
It seems like everyone who hasn't seen it has seen it.
feeling
I guess so
Well, I saw 2, but I think I'll watch 1.
Yeah, it's fun, it's hardcore.
I see
Mikomi Rosa I saw it, I saw it all.
Aziz ni saano
Yeah, but I feel like that's the case somehow.
That's right, but even if I look at it, I don't understand it at all.
It doesn't look like it at all
That's not true. I'm a lot younger now.
Not
circle
Dare that's amazing
oh
Senkyu, I'm sorry, I was scared, I was scared.
It's scary
Naika will immediately place a block.
Unlike you, I don't want to die.
I don't want to sleep anymore
No, be careful with Kaka too.
KesokS is okay
burning
What's wrong? It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's amazing, it's amazing, Yu-san
Cool, cool, cool, cool, I'm used to it, I'm used to it.
It's time to go home.
perfect team perfect team
this
[music]
Hamikochi and Miko's judgement, courage, everything
Feels good
queue
Leader Leader Senpai Ni
Emi-chan, who is not on our team
It's okay, it's okay
Are you okay
[music]
Oh, hurry, go home early
Sukie-chan
It's important to stay calm
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
[music]
Are you okay kid?
I'm a brat, I'm a brat, I'm not a brat
I don't want to be called red.
Ah, I learned pro wrestling.
Don't say that, you remember the pros like a master.
Something
This is the first time for Minoko and Achan.
Naso
Na
[music]
This is my first time seeing the number.
It hurts when I can no longer match my opponent.
Hey, that bread doesn't hurt at all, thank you.
Yes
[music]
He's leading the way so I don't fall.
Nekaka
Block
[music]
The magma here is crazy.
It seems like moths can easily release magma, right?
Miko also remembered that, I remembered it.
Because the club I remembered is not bad.
[music]
Na
Uncle Hisa Eternal Uncle Hub Eternal Uncle
Mr. A little something
Core to meet uncle and uncle
My senior wants an uncle
That's what I think, uncle.
That's right, I was wondering what this was all about.
I was wondering what you were talking about.
You're talking about your uncle, right?
That old man is actually still that Miko-senpai.
You're cute today too
There's no such thing
Yo
Chaa
I know it's okay because I'm watching you
It's dangerous! I kept looking behind you.
Good
Hey, there's a possibility that only A will be swallowed up by magma without dying.
Yes no no
[music]
Don't look at me Gust Chance Gust
A chance has come, a ghost chance
ghost
Chance Gust Chance Gust
Opportunity for those who haven't yet.
This thing seems okay
Try defeating a certain
Hey, senpai too
Still me too
[music]
[laughter]
voice
[music]
Dano's chin is dangerous, but is it okay?
I'm falling, I'm falling
What are they doing?
I got a gust
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Gusto Challenge has begun
It's weird
Hey, I'm right, I'm right, I'm right.
I did it
[music]
nice nice
Nice
[music]
Mission Yata Yata
I don't need anything anymore
I feel like I'm looking for something.
Well, please spend the time with the same same as the same senior
I'm so happy
Ushimikaane, it's scary here, it's not dangerous here
It's scary. It's dangerous here. It's okay. I'm on the right.
Hey, even if you're on the right, the road already ends here.
yes
Oh wow, this is such a dangerous place.
It's scary from above
[music]
What?
Nai-chan isn't doing it?
[music]
Yes, but maybe not here.
I thought it was the same area, so I came straight to it.
It's scary here. That's a fortress. It's a fortress, a fortress, on the bottom right.
te 4 datte oh ena da te 4
I'm 4 years old. I'm 4 years old.
Under there, under there
Why can't I see? Look, look over there.
It's murder, oh it's true, there's a bridge.
Hashi is 4 years old and I found that. It's amazing.
Taya
Ta
Amazing chin, amazing but extremely low place
What should I do? How should I go?
Hey, how do you do this? Those are bones.
No, you can't flush water through bones.
I brought water from the ship, but it fell off the boat.
If you make stairs
[music]
If you make a mistake
Mom stepped on the wrong magma
Sleep a little
[music]
Ah, what I found
I seriously got 30 diamonds, I did it.
Everyone, do it
What what
I'm here, gas gas gas
I'll kill you, Gust, I'll kill you, Gust.
I haven't killed him yet. I haven't killed him yet.
Kill me here
It looks like he doesn't have it now.
It would be scary if it exploded while I was handing it over.
That's right, you should just lend it to me.
I wonder if it's okay to lend it to you.
I don't think I have the strength to think it's possible at all.
It's okay to die
The footing here is so bad it's hard to escape and it's dangerous.
It's scary, I'm scared I'm about to fall
bubbles
Wow, I can't see it. Nice one.
Chanaah, that's nice, wow.
Na delicious
Umee Kara-chan
or
It's so delicious
The sea is dangerous
from
I don't want to die
Oisho
Wow
Thank you very much
Good job
died
[music]
Nomadapoi
It's dangerous because it's raw, so I stack it here.
Thank you very much.
There is
Get in
There's nothing left to do. Don't die. Don't die.
Oh oh
Shishia Karu-chan did it
Genius wakokomiko senpai fried there
There are also potatoes
And there are french fries on the bridge too.
French fries came
Brave Blaze Blaze is the purpose of
Nemesis
So please make a potion for Miko-chan too.
Let's make it for everyone!
Noa Skeleton Skeleton E Skeleton
I have a mission so this is TTT
Wow I did it
I was pushed and fell by a creepy skeleton.
Hey, big skeleton, let's go downstairs.
Niko Senpai Skeleton Leather one
It's only
I'm good at everything, even in the village.
Oh, this is so bad, he's a visage skeleton
There it is
wither
sultan
It's nice to have a head full of wizards coming home.
Let's catch it, Prai.
I want potato potato potato this goes down
Make a way under the gas swanga still
Gusto Underneath this, A-senpai, A-senpai, ah
[music]
the law of nature
Masu
Let's go in behind me. I slipped in behind me.
It's okay, Kara is here. Do your best, Kara-chan.
I think there are two of them now.
Nice to know
Nice
It's ok to be stubborn
Nice nice nice oh thank you
Thank you very much nice
Nice, how much did you do? Is there more to do?
[music]
It looked pretty low, right? It's normal.
If you're digging, this is the place you'll arrive at.
I think I'll get there in minutes, but I guess that's probably it.
I don't know, maybe
intuition intuition
Let's look at it from a little above.
It's true that Noa-chan is making it.
It's dangerous there
hey
Should I make this dangerous one too?
Just in case
It looks like a good match, but it's still in the right position.
Thank you very much for making it.
Let's make it here too.This is also made of diamonds.
Tsuruha is so strong that those stairs are decent
Make it
It's not going to be strong today, I'm really digging it
It's true, but it's dangerous to interfere.
Are you okay now? I'm okay.
Don't die, kill me
I'm glad I can't beat you. It was too much.
mosquito
It's pretty low
I won't come
Na
Hey, I want to explore a little bit, right? I'm dying.
Kanachida
Wow, scary
Nade Blaze is also scary but I want it
Hey, it's true
It's not like that, but it's gotta be potatoes.
That's right, the potion is right here.
Tennoukai can go, right? Sade has come out.
Let's take a look below.
3 more months left that I haven't been able to go yet
AwesomeAwesome
[music]
Yes Pi
too
scary akishi
After taking a break
No, no, I have it on hand.
Toyoshishoyoisho
[music]
stairs
I used this
O
My sister was a crazy person.
I'm peeking in
hey
Pop-pop-pop-pop
I wonder if there is
More
I don't have any milk, even if it falls off.
Okay, just have one.
Naoru Kin-senpai
Hero Oruoruoruha
Yukoko
I probably could have come.
Oh blue wailu oooooo
Ugameta
If I play Paoko's cat, it'll probably be this way.
Hey, Omishi is delicious.
good
Because it's O, I guess it's all about my friends.
Yes, it's true.
Extremely reliable
Oh wow
I want a head like that too, even if it's a mushroom.
Garnish with different mushrooms
Only Oishomisu's head gets Miza.
It's possible because it seems like it's possible
According to the rules, I have to defeat Endora and Mether.
Because it was written that
I wonder if I'll need the head too.
This is for everyone
[music]
If you have a visa, you can handle it.
from
cormorant
I want a place for Teku Fortress Potato.
[music]
Yay!
The place next to the fried potatoes is blazing.
Blaze might be over there, right?
do not have
Is this the cat side?
[music]
Anyway, it's not connected there, it's here.
What do you think? What's going on here?
That's right, it's a hole here, isn't it?
That's right, my sister is reliable.
I'm going to build a wall with this.
It's so reliable when it comes to Minecraft.
I wonder if I'll do Hadoko twice.
I saw it, but it was my first time, so Endora
I ended up getting beaten up like it was a bonus.
Teru
It's painful, I don't do much.
That's right, I feel like I'm about to fall, but Nemisu
If it comes, you'll really die. Run away because you're really dead.
Thank you, but I couldn't go.
Is it possible that the potato is redundant?
I want potatoes. I want everyone's potatoes.
oh
Gusto Gust Yada no Gusto Yada
Yo
Hoyoyo
It's not good
I have nothing to go to.
Wow wow
Wow, so light
I'm not scared, it's scary
Naao magma
Prim potato
[music]
Hey, what is a thermometer?
I want a Nether mote too, Nether.
Mort and magma cream are also helpful.
Is that something made of flame? I wonder what it is.
Potion, yes.
Please make a Nawaiwai potion.
make
[music]
Oishoeeeeeenakune potato
Baba Potato Habanai
Hey, there's no potato, so it's kind of quiet.
But I was there earlier.
[music]
This is where I came from
The connection is
Oh, it looks like something could happen. Let's go inside Honor.
Does that mean Blaze Teru was there?
[music]
Passive Ma Passive Ma
difference
[music]
Yes, I don't have it
I will eat rice
Explore here and there
A passive masochist, a passive masochist
This Mike
[music]
I wonder what Tadoko is. Looks like Pia found it.
But hey, on top of that?
It was hot
Get Jin
[music]
It's true that it was warm here.
Thank you very much!
do
But I shot something that didn't look like a spring.
It's over there
There are
Where are Toko Kiana and the others?
Where is it?
Kaki's place
I was told there might be wart around here.
I feel like I actually saw someone on the stairs or something.
That's right
It means you're exploring, right?
Probably a
Ta
The cat is being searched for
Not here
Something like this
Is it just there?
I feel like it's definitely up here or here.
Suruochi
a
Yes
[music]
hello hello hello
Don't do it today
[music]
Masu Aichi Aichi
Oh no no no no
close
What is it here?
There too
Ta
Yes, there was
Read here.
Yo
I can hear you here, Senpai, I'm upstairs.
Fly here, here, here, here.
here
Yay, my senior, I almost died from a pigeon. That's dangerous.
It was dangerous
Yo, there's Blaze Rates Go Les.
There are so many
Ashi lost
Yondake Potato Potato Endless Potato
There it was, Endless Potato Eles.
Shiny
I wonder if I should follow.
I'm here, I'm here
It's true that I'm here
Dayton
[music]
oh
There are lots of them everywhere.
It's okay, there are a lot of people burning.
quite dangerous
The magma cube also attacked the cat's cube.
Not coming
When you knock down a fish
hey
Akare-chan's head is about to fall off
Narui
Where is the distance?
I have 2 of them. 2 of them are amazing. I have 2 of them. Double.
double
double uh endless
potato potato double
Seeing it for the first time
Ta
Amazing
Senkyu is amazing, amazing, amazing
It's called Pocket because it looks like a fly.
Terupuyo Senkyu
Double YE is difficult, so I'll close it for now.
Thank you very much
[music]
Oh, it's adjacent, so it's withered.
Maybe the opposite
Niete
[music]
Don't die, don't die, it's so scary
It's amazing! I'm coming from behind.
this
If you drop it, you can easily borrow it.
There was a better
Zukoko too
Is it okay to block it?
circle
Let's eat some food
This is seriously going to kill me
or
Scary Uwa Spon
I'm sure
It's burning, it's burning, it's okay.
I understand it now
Ta
Yes, it burns if there is no grass.
Teruke calm down
Takoko
I'm feeling a bit chilly
Chiochi
I want a belly
Nekore dodo
There's a blockage
I have to
Naooo
[music]
oh
Please be careful
Oh, you're angry
It's dangerous, it's dangerous
[music]
I wonder how all these kids are doing
It happened aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Ah, this
Yes, it's okay, there's one on the left too, but that's nice.
Oh, I don't want you to die, Senpai.
Yes, it's too bad, it's over there too, behind me.
The back bark is true
It's about time to go open even if it's a mess
Looks like we're about to run out of food.
How many potatoes do you need?
Anyway, I need the Ender Eye.
Hey hey hey hey
[music]
Kaakaaakaa
Come on come on
Come on?
It's definitely the most efficient way
[music]
Hey, even if I try that thing, I can't pick it up.
I guess there must be a way to pick it up.
just look for
Miyocha name
What is that enemy's name, Blaze?
blaze blaze book
Niina Blend
trap
Haria Tutorial
oh
Dust
Oh, it's Gusto. Gusto is here. Gusto's older brother.
Oh no, I need to kill someone. Defeat everyone already.
Not even here
It's true I put it here but it's true
Coming
knock down the top
Nice too
[music]
Oh, what was that?
this
It's okay, it's a Calabreze trap.
That's it
[music]
Oh yeah
and try again
Potato potato, this, get about three potatoes.
did
[music]
Yo
Yoshiasu
trap
Ore's Trap was really horrible
It's so simple, but it's disgusting
Well, I don't have enough iron, so I guess I'll go home.
Yeah, okay, okay, it's really deep down there.
Even if it seems like I have to
I just put a half block.
So suck up the spores
It's easy if you give it to me or make it, but I don't have iron.
Yes, can I go back once? Yes, I can go back once.
On the way home
Let's clean up a bit on the way home so everyone can come.
Yes, I'll definitely come. I'll wait until here.
I don't even know the way
Where is the road that isn't that?
If you go to the fuel road, you'll be at that splendid bridge.
Will we reach it?
Oh nice
see byebaaa
It would be impossible if I did. Did you have the first coordinates?
I can't help but notice what's in there. Make a note of the meat too.
Apparently that wasn't the case, nice one
[music]
That's because I'm at home
Not here then
hey
Yeah, it's hard until I get home
core
Let's go to Oishoki
Kaokodoko
I guess I want to connect the gate.I'm sure the gate
Squid squid
rice cake
Chako is not exploring
That's right, Netherboat
nether boat is
Nether mote is owned by Kaji-chan.
I have
[music]
Poop nearby
I don't know the way home.
It's not necessarily true.
Search
[music]
It looks like it's going to dry out, so make this into a potion.
You can do it.
[music]
I feel like I'm not there, so I'm wearing a mug too
I thought it was somewhere, but everyone there is Miko.
I don't think I've set up a timer like that.
This one?
Is this it too?
Maybe this too
What are you doing?
I feel like it's this way
Hey, but
yeah
Haniare Senpai Help Me Help Me What?
It's okay, help me, milk, milk
Milk please, milk please milk please
Yes, yes, yes, it's okay, I dropped it.
Yes, it was fine. I was almost killed in the winter.
It's become dangerous, yoga yoga, live
Teoisho
I feel like I'm in danger, I don't know where to go
Since there isn't one, we should just make a new path.
I see, wow
First
Genius Genius Divided
If we go here, we
As expected of Go, Okay.
It might be dangerous if there are 15 places over there.
Hey, I need to find my way back there.
I can't go home
It would be easiest if you just dig in a straight line.
There is, right?
If you know best
I'm sure I'll leave this to Ka and Kara.
Let's leave it to the professionals
[music]
Yo shift
shift
Thank you very much
Go home safely. Go home safely.
I'm going home even though I'm going to get a job.
Diamond returns
I promised to go back
Go home
[music]
Oisho
No, I see it there
Hey, is that where you came from?
No, it's different
Hey, it wasn't open there.
Moncolle
What is this? I don't know what this is.
This block is not a block.
It's dangerous here
Senkyuaraba
But it's not there, maybe it's from higher up
I'm sure it's come
dapia's kaelasenkyukade
Senkyu sekyu senkyu thank you
had this
But I made a wall like a landmark, so if you look for it there,
Go home
That's right
[music]
Oh my goodness
Looks like there's a poll.
[music]
Isn't it wonderful?
Random
[music]
Na
It's not really here
I see, it's better not to use it.
Beginners with Minecraft
Is there such a thing as "I can't do it"?
Even if you use a portal, it's still a long way to go there.
I guess so. I don't know if there are Yoishi or anything like that.
No, no, no
Yes, it's okay, but I'm over there.
Even if we connect
I'd be very relieved if I could go on good ground.
Yeah, but in this world, it seems like a really long distance.
It's a huge distance
It's probably 4,000 or so.
Oh, that's terrible
who
It's okay now, no one's gonna die anymore, no one
do not have
Apparently
Well, we've already lost two people.
expedition
Thank you for returning Diamond's clothes.
It's a debt
Hey, it's okay with that diamond
Nobody
Darita
Keja
Did you get 7 good diamonds?
Nahaita Yochi is a mess today
Earn diamonds. This is a bonus for high contribution.
That's what I'm talking about
Yeah
Didn't you exchange it for Oo?
It's okay, it's okay.
Do it here
hand
Do you know the coordinates?
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
It's dangerous here
Believe in the dangerous karaka. It's natural to believe in the karaka.
I believe it
let's go let's go
Good job
[music]
I Love You Love Guy
happy happy happy happy
Oh happy
happy happy happy ha ha happy
[music]
Hahahaha I'm happy
I'm happy.
Happy I've already heard the cat meme
Yo
Hehehe
[music]
It's Biff-kun
hey
Take care, guys
Hey, wait
With a lie
Thank you very much, thank you very much
Thankfully, it's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
Why are mushrooms growing here so dangerous?
That's because money is stupid.
It's all money and you're an idiot.
Okay, don't push, don't push.
Yosenkyu
Eh
My aunt is now
Don't get too close, idiot
let's
Wait for the tongue twister that I learned from a good lady.
I forgot, everyone please tell me
It's like something like that.
Na
I was there
Kokake
Kakakakake
Kakaka
Koka
mosquito
Wouldn't it be better if it was only in a place that looked okay?
Okakako
oyster
credit
Cue it's about time
Block is gone
[music]
Honan
But there's still me
block
[music]
Don't bub, don ...
here you are
[music]
Thank you
nice situation
When it falls
eat taitai rice
I want to eat food in real life, I know, I know.
I'm not hungry so I'll have food when I get home.
I don't think I'll eat it. It's okay.
Eat enough to go home
I read a lot of books about eating and eating.
I'm doing a lot today, but today's result is
That's amazing! We're amazing!
I'm sure it's the one
[music]
It feels so good too
Me today
What time is it in Strania?
It's almost 7 o'clock in the evening. 7 o'clock in the evening.
That's right, it's golden time.
Hey, I usually start streaming at this time.
By the way, that's right. Usually, this is a character.
It's time, I definitely have an image of midnight.
Yeah, European
It's Go
[music]
Well, it's the same as Kara.
It's like opening up
Hi Ayate
Yooooo
That means I was stuck, oh
[music]
of
Pillow
[music]
I got caught in Tanela slime, magma Wow!
It's coming from
[music]
It's coming, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Danger
It's delicious and dangerous, no one will disappear.
Yo no one dies
[music]
hot tourism
What is this?
[music]
[applause]
What, what, what? Come to the green.
All biomes in the nether
Because I went
[music]
That's it
Ikun
[music]
Only blue
yes
Yes, but I got a lot of them.
mushroom blue blue
[music]
Mabam
Blue and Aomori
[music]
Just too
Manomada nonono still
No, I still want money.
It's here. It's here. It's here.
Hey, be careful, be careful.
hand
It's scary here, be careful
Is it okay to be so big? This is not good.
Yo
It's okay. Kiana made the stairs.
Gave it to me
Please, okay, that's it.
Give it to Yo-chan
Good, yes, yes, silk touch blue earth
If you have it, you can increase it as much as you want.
I got this
I guess I haven't made it yet.
Ba
[music]
Polets Golets
Go
Oh this is rhinoceros
Everyone got it!
I'm making a lot of money today.
[music]
Khao
It's a good time
dangerous length
[music]
scared
Subaru Subaru Subaru senior murderer
Unfortunately, Subaru fell into the lava.
[music]
[laughter]
Ah, ah, ah, scary cat, it's not feeling well, it's terrible
is
Length
Kuno
Makura God Deva
This is on top of me
Because it was
[music]
There are only 4 Tai-chan and only 4 Tai-chan.
There is security
[music]
Senkyu, I'm no longer here, I'm leaving behind me.
He did it
[music]
Chan
I never put ramatsu
Apparently magma pine call magma
Ikomagma
Magma is powerful
It's too strong, it seems like it's too strong
Neo thank you
[music]
Pig
Shout out
Don't be scared
Tete
scared
I'm scared
The original that has been lost
It's strong not to put it on
My baby died.
Now that I think about it, I wonder what happened to Senpai.
Yes, but I have to have diamonds
I guess I was supposed to collect diamonds.
I guess it's abandoned underground.
In that service, it's a normal day, then it's a normal day.
There's no one there even if it's normal or not
I'm going to fight with an axe.
[music]
Oh, I made a mistake, I made a mistake.
Everything I do in my house
I stopped breaking it.
[music]
Oh, I'm calm
Calm down
I can do it
I can go
in
False report
[music]
Ra-chan can feel safe, it's safe.
Hey, I'm walking down the road while looking at the signs for attacks.
That's amazing, I have to thank you.
When I was shooting it, it crashed into magma.
That's kind, this is an honor of honor.
Yeah, I'm sure it's something cool.
It's cool to be praised.
Cool through life Cool through life
protect my wife and baby
I came knocking
Senkyu here if you have any trouble overseas
I'll do it
La support
Support is here.
Over there
here here here here
here
Oh nice nice
If we keep going like this, if we keep going like this,
I can go, Senkyu.
Thank you
happy happy happy happy
happy
Okay okay okay okay
I won't cover it
[music]
Na
Good morning
Good job, I did it.
[music]
What kind of voice is Castle in Oh Fortress?
end o
Ohpi-chan Piku-chan Piku-chan and not
Epic
Wow, such a small place
in
If you remove it with a photo-picture-picture solvent
Good it's true
Too good not to take it
I ran away and came back, please.
Nice job, I got it. There were 6 people.
Yay, yay, yay, okay, let's go home.
Let's go home
[music]
O
Hey there!
Ta
Wait a minute, the arena has been built!
The place is dangerous
What are you trying to do to the Netsu no Ma?
[music]
I'm doing it.
I was on my way
hey
Ta
what to say
[applause]
So, I see that the martial arts are nice here.What will happen?
Is that so?
Well, I probably shouldn't watch it yet.
I guess I should just not look at it just yet.
I was on my way
Sorry I didn't take a photo. Just a photo.
current
I took the photo. Can I ask you a favor?
It's okay, it's not out, thank you
Thank you, yes, thank you, yes.
So Miko and the others are safe.
That I accomplished it
Thank you so much thank you so much
return
Thank you thank you
[music]
Kyukyu Aani-chan and Ani-chan
Thank you for your time writing Kochia mission
Don't forget to write the mission mission
Do you all write in comments?
Yes, both are good, but that's all.
I'll write it down and write it down.
Arihacha
No longer
Come on, come on
Okay, say hello, Kakohacha.
Kakakoha Chama Pure Ozora Suba Pure Heart I Oku
Even when we went there, our names were written.
Because it was written that
That's right, we're talking about Piglin Fortress, right?
I would like to request additional Gusto Gas as well.
I wish I could write Gusto myself.
If you don't understand, you can't do it.
Iguri doesn't have a diamond reward.
I thought it looked good, but there is no diamond reward.
Yona Pirin
is okay
tsumaki tsumaki tsumaki tsumaki tsumaki
firewood fireworks
One roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll, one roll.
Rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls
I was alive and I came back alive.
Yomiko welcome home
Let's just leave it alone
It's okay if it's hardcore or text.
Type it in. I get it from the text, then I'll go.
Yoo
Tsutsu
Rock, paper, scissors
Pa
Takashi
[music]
Listen, this is how I will survive.
Thank you, thank you, damn I'm dead again
Maybe it'll happen
I'm going to Meza tomorrow, right?
I might die from this
I played rock, paper, scissors, so be extra careful.
So be careful, I found Kaname.
Hey, how was it?
It's a phantom
a
Phantom, I wonder if he still wants to be alive?
There were others on their way home, so they're still alive.
Everyone is different. Everyone did their best. Nade Kamidama.
Moha-chan died too, Haa-chan too.
died
Why, why, why did you die?
Ha-chan also misstepped and fell.
He's dead, he's a veteran.
Yeah, I died. Go to bed. I'm dead.
is
Yes, it was fun, but he was a good guy.
quickly
No, he died very quickly, right now.
I'm looking for 7 diamonds alone to live
It seems so lonely
Looks like it's coming out after I lost my strange house.
comment
And the strange one is gone
It's true that there are no strange people here either.
It's written, it's common as written.
This is common. I lost something strange.
That's funny, I didn't act like that.
It wasn't great. Mikone did her best.
Very
Yes, yes.
I even found an amazing fortress.
I can't help but get such a great souvenir.
This is a souvenir, a souvenir, wait a moment, treasure.
Treasure
this
Oh, just one piece is fine.
Just one, how many? You'll have to go and get the rest yourself.
Oh, I'm sure it's just one fried potato.
Maybe I can make a potion.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm happy.
Thank you, do your best, I'll survive
Tomorrow, I won't die.
Oh, I can't wait. It's like I've lost my guts.
Well then, let's play rock, paper, scissors again.
Yeah, I survived. Yeah, I survived.
See you for rock-paper-scissors
[music]
Let's see another one
Let's go, Tetsujo Seijo.
Kaoshisho
Let's raise each other's flags. You did your best today.
Seriously, I'm glad I found the fortress today.
It was fun
What is this?
mosquito
This is this
[music]
What's different about Rika-chan?
Is it like home?
I think I'll do it tomorrow
Maybe tomorrow I'll meet a certain member of mine.
I'm talking about playing with my penis.
I'll do Kara Piki's too.
Report tomorrow and get a diamond.
I packed up my equipment and took care of the weather.
Let's do it
Miko's house isn't there yet.
I want to make a house too
[music]
Na
An automatic potion
Machine a
Where?
Oooooo
[music]
Go, it's okay
Ah, Ako-senpai, I'm going to make a potion now.
But it's a disgusting potion sol stand
potion potion potion
potion
Asu Ako Ni Akore Potion
Location for Asenkyuoouii
If you put it there, it will become automatic.
Oshi
Amazing automatic
What is this game that has an automatic?
Automatic!
automatic potion maker
A unique potion, a bone potion.
I really did it!
That's right, because there is a mission for Shi.
Nemo that is
Daimons too divine
The accuracy of the sewing is really good. I was told to wait.
I guess you just have to wait.
Oh yeah, I said I'd bring that.
Oh, it's so tiny.
It's okay, it's not Hikaru's song.
Otomatic Oisho
Everyone is eating cake in this house. Eat it!
No red stone blocks donated
[music]
Where to trace
house
Gozaa Gozaru's Kaya is stylish.
Hey, even Kaa is funny.
Hey, let's do it
[music]
Build a house too
But it's really late today, so maybe
I might make some in the back.
Will you make it for streaming tomorrow?
I wonder if it's okay, 2nd time senior, whose is this?
Kado Uncle House Who is this Uncle House?
What is it?
a
Someone made this
I'm saying that I don't have it, so it's okay.
Chan's
Yes, I see
It's a villager generation facility created by Ha.
[music]
this
Neyokuni
and feeling
Kaya Kingdom and That Day
[music]
Yeah
Yoisho Point
[music]
I got some points so let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Write rock-paper-scissors overwrite rock-paper-scissors
It's a rule to make fun of me when I meet you.
That's right, let's go. Okay, next time.
Hoitsu no Makitsu no Makitsu no Makitsu
Rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls of rolls
Rock, paper, scissors
Ah, there's next time, right? Next time, next time.
Let's do it again, okay yeah, if it happens next time, yeah
It's not just me, it's not happening again.
[Laughter]
What kind of relationship do you have with the trainer?
It feels like
But okay this
[music]
Kasate and Emiko's ore
Tamiko's
ore
Oh my whole body
Yes, there are things like that.
There is also full body equipment.
Dafunfunfunfunfun
[music]
Fun Ho Ho
Wow, that's amazing
[music]
month
Sakae everyone, tell me what you did all over your body
The equipment mission is something like that.
Well then
Um, what?
Not a Whizzer
te gust
[music]
Defeat
Eh, square roll rock, paper, scissors
Cato
Well,
[music]
skeleton 3
Animals
subjugation soul
[music]
Please report Sandwich and Groust.
Did both of you report it, Groon?
Three people can go with just one stone soul sandwich
Na
Wait, Pinga 4 found 20 pieces.
No, the lies are increasing, increasing, increasing, 20
Euchi made a lot of money today, then.
Isn't this the mountain division I've been waiting for?
Yes, I don't know about that.
Yo
[music]
Yeah and the rest
What if I found a pyramid?
Dafunfunfunfun
For the Funa team, the missions are divided into different parts.
I would like to thank the person who made this useful trap.
Retribution without incident
That's dangerous
It hurts, it's okay
[music]
Stoya Ya Mushroom
mushroom
[music]
It's mushroom evening
I didn't go get the poo eggs.
in the end
Oh potion
Create potion Create potion
do not have
[music]
I want to create a motion now.
Is this okay?
Is this okay? This is okay.
Everyone wait, there's something strange.
Octopus
mosquito
It's okay, there's no cover
Oza
[music]
Masu-nee-san can make a potion button 1
I did it there
Diamond is also here and there
There's something different about that
[music]
Can be done
Teruba
[music]
Good
I can't fight
[music]
If you write this three times
It's true that it's hard to understand in a group.
I'll write it down
Kaunto
[music]
What is Agoro Stone?
Carestone and what was it called Sol?
sad soul
Sado aso da soul
[music]
This is sad [ __ ]
Oh
[music]
I'll make it again
Should I add more water?
Too bad, I have one less Ra. I don't have one.
Ishiyosho
I wrote a picture of how I found Oisho Kaname.
Ta
Yo
Good job
Mon
Maybe it's okay
[music]
yeah
in
I'm going to build a little house. I'll put some wood in it and make it.
Hey, that's scary
[music]
Tomorrow, 14 tarts will arrive.
That's no good, right?
[music]
This is in magmaku
mama rest rest rest
I'll adjust it a little later. Everyone is touching it now.
I don't know if that's because
Hey, sorry, I'm touching it right now.
Macma cream and yes someone
If necessary, I'll include Adaya's reward.
I see, that's what it is.
Or okay
Okay
Yoisho Senkyu
Thank you, I might wait for the best potion.
If you don't unlock the achievement, it's probably because you made it.
There isn't.
Hey, it's okay
[music]
I don't know, I'm making this too, so it's fine.
I pressed the button.
Shimi also pressed the button.
Isn't it okay to press a button?
[music]
Also write
Toko Nishi is placed in a block on the bookshelf.
I understand, just like that I made a potion.
Ta
Oishionde
writes meat
Although it is late,
This book is not in a box.
It's not a book, it's here
absolute
There's a note written on it
Mon
Oh, it's over there, right?
This thing I came up with is increasing my imagination.
I can't put this in there.
Door here
Because it's inside, it's perfect when you open it.
Homo is back
draw a taoshi
[music]
Travel Keno
Eh, is the date 16th okay?
[music]
Is it enough for 16 days?
Na
Okay, wait, where are you writing this?
Take a look
Look at me, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Mom doesn't know if I should write it in the wind, that's amazing
I think it was a pretty good trip.
Who will be my role model?Who will I die next?
Hey, I'm just reading someone's diary.
Don't die, it's okay, but it's okay, the captain says.
Maybe it's because of that person.
I'm sure something will happen again.
I think it will probably happen again, so I'll participate again.
Neneooh Nene Shikunene is doing great too
Mon
That's right, this is page 11.
[music]
It's not very long
Everyone everywhere
I wonder if everyone in the comment section has a different opinion.
I'm sorry in advance.
It's Makotoko's diary.
Apology Apology
Non
[music]
May 14th
It was raining today, but I was alone with everyone.
chan started to flatter me and became an ass, and
dead
Nene-chan, who was revived from the dead, caught the leader.
The leader who came here is a little confused when he speaks.
Yan elementary school student
Did you do that?
what
[music]
There's no Captain Non drinking Captain Marita.
Is that what it is? Is it in here?
This is someone's diary. It's really interesting.
A treasure
[music]
As soon as the diary begins, I am regulated to the potty.
When I tried to do so, I joined the group and the button was pressed.
Hit the button that lived under one roof
Up and down movement on one bed until
The archives are zombies from people I've met.
and
My habit is the worst, it's all loose, it's all loose
Everyone spreads their money around and makes money.
I've been educating Spartans a lot.
Buttonhole with diamonds sewn in
make a clean hole
I also did a sloppy flared ana.
All you talk about is your cat allergy, so tough.
We all went to Aqua and had a good time.
Shocked by the lively kid Suzune
It's huge
Damn it, that damn thing has to lose its precision twice.
Don't come, I want Manny to come.
Stop the bagomi-hane system.Think about this too4
page
[music]
I just don't understand everything, hey Anya Marin
Tan's diary is crazy, what is this?
Episode 8 was an erotic novel.
I want to read something like Gabagaba or something like Gabagaba Hole
Tight holes and all that stuff.
It was at the level of Is this okay?
Moreover, this is definitely delivered by Pecola Senpai.
It's like reading inside the diary, all of us.
Pecola's entire diary has been read, hasn't it?
Yes, yes, that's what my senior said about news distribution.
It's not good, then this Edo of Marine
Novel reading party
Hey, wait, Mimiko's bed is gone.
Let's go look for a bed.There's a bed.
It's gone, okay, I'll go find the bed.
Okay dude
It's no big deal
Na
good food
Teoisho
[music]
Go with me
I'm sure everyone's sentences were quite long.
I put it here
Neyoshi
come morning
Do you want to write
[music]
May 16 Elite
Late on the first day
This came over
world
Yes, it came in
It's a moment, isn't it?
the attack was over
No, I was attacked.
Tapopo
died
Ta
The cruelty of this world
truth
west
Notice
and
That minato aa
teeth
Becoming a dog
The head too
reasonably
hand
Completely different person
[Laughter]
is
[music]
Yes, everyone is in a good mood too.
Roll it up with
I don't like these people
Like
Hanara
[music]
hey
Well, what happened after that?
I'm sorry it's gone later.
Contains Tenmika
I feel like I haven't stopped by since.
do not have
Suddenly Slora dies.
[music]
Everyone looking for it
I was working hard at
Life or death?
Kuchitchi
[music]
lend me a diamond
It was given to me
is this
Become a sneak peek
Thank you
[music]
[laughter]
Suva
Ma
Let's have fun!
I borrowed it from this guy.
[music]
may have been correct
Hey
[music]
Scary too
and
Chima died easily.
daminna
And like that
[music]
You can discover our
It's going to be a sape
this
Eh this
Miku
is edet
E Dragon
until it's toma
of
story
picture
Mikokoukao
Obestus, please come with a new novel.
Hey!
I wrote a novel, but this is different.
This is wrong
Mia also died once
I'm home now
Welcome home, I wrote a novel.
novel
Yes, it's good to read the countermeasures.
Yo
Waiting to read
hand
Rano I wrote what I'm writing now.
This is my first diary, so I'm going to read it.
Yeah
May 16th Elite
The moment I entered this world that arrived late on the first day
This is the shrine maiden who died when Popo was attacked.
When I realized how cruel the world was,
I became a dog with that port.
The dog's head is curled up and he's a completely different person.Everyone is also in a good mood.
I'm not going to end up like this when I'm curled up.
Subaru is dead
It's a sudden development, the next page is dead.
Even though we were all doing our best, our lives were short-lived.
He lent me the lost diamond, but this...
Thank you for chatting with Subaru Am
I'm going to have fun living in Subama, this guy
Maybe borrowing it was the right thing to do, and
Asari Chima is dead too
That's how I was able to discover the fortress.
Until the shrine maiden subjugates the elite dragon
Story: It's nice to have friends in this world of survival.
Why is it not 0 points?
It's not included. I forgot about that. I forgot.
Don't forget, forget
Na
I put the square roll in and put it in and wrote it differently and won.
Just this
Wow, that's all it takes
I'm not acting a little crazy here.
The one where I'm going to go
Rock, paper, scissors
papa
Yeah, it's a victory for Jawatame.
This is Ununma Miku and Unako today.
Hey Kotekamae, let's do Maokone today.
Overwrite rock, paper, scissors, overwrite rock, paper, scissors, you
I'm sure he said something strange at first.
I thought it was a game of rock-paper-scissors.
That's right, it's overwritten. It's bad, it's bad, it's not bad.
Well, what I said at the beginning is restarting.
It's restarted. It's restarted. I'm planning to restart tomorrow.
Okay, this one has restarted, that one has restarted that one.
It was Hero Taneaka and Hero was there.
Hello, it's here again haha hello meow
Hello to hello nya hello teru ya Nemikono
I heard about the potion too, so go get it.
It says how to make a potion.
It's written, it's not written, it's written.
Yes, there was, maybe someone wrote it.
No, thank you very much for this.
Thank you very much for your chair.
I would have been scared of the Nether if I couldn't go there.
I'm glad you found it.
I was really happy thank you
This guy is making a little potion.
Thank you for that visit.
Let's play together again, Masukoroko-san.
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you for your help. Thank you again.
We look forward to your continued support tomorrow.
Yes, let's play again tomorrow, thank you.
Thank you, it's done
Not yet, right?
Isn't it okay here?
Written by Diary Aa Yai Kore Koyori
I feel like lol
That's why I went home.
Did you find it?
I'm glad I found Natsuso now.
Chamachachamaaanitai
I'm glad it was okay
Let's do our best and not die anymore, yeah, tomorrow
Let's do our best, don't die, do your best tomorrow
Let's do our best, be stubborn, don't die
I completed the mission properly. I'm going to die.
No, I don't know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't know.
Good night thank you very much
by
Miko is also around here because she is bi.
Shall we finish?
So,
There was a lot going on.
But so many things happened on the first day, until the last day.
I will do my best and be strict. Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much. I'll go back to my room.
Nishikata Nishi Aetaji
[music]
hey
Delicious
[music]
I'll be right back