hi
[Music]
well we have gathered here today to
present to you a new feature that just
was updated in Among Us for the whole
life Cosmic Cube
then you can like get outfits from
selected members from Whole Life en ID
and Japan this these streams are not
sponsored but we just really want to
show you so good look at everything so
introduce themselves and they can also
show off their sexy outfit while they're
introducing themselves
I might get kicked out of the room
eventually but let's just start oh let's
start with almonds
uh number one detective I'm naked
um
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah okay
hello everyone I'm shirakamian today
nice to meet you guys hello
[Music]
foreign
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why yeah screaming but yes also my mommy
hooked up my Wi-Fi would you think I was
streaming 480p to be honest why even why
even [\h__\h] bother why even bother me
mommy I'm gonna get some Hollow swag As
a sheriff let's party
[Music]
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now we're written
Among Us
[Music]
welcome how does it feel that now you
can have so many imposters of yourself
to even know who who is you anymore I
love it there are many sharklings around
there's one right here right next to you
is cool please introduce yourself
who is you well I miss you
hey
[Music]
amazing
seems like an imposter
and then we have Mona who is also part
of the people's outfits you can get in
the game
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you you're wearing your own hair
yes
I'm wearing a scientist outfit right now
I feel like I'm I'm doing a touring love
in the Among Us
yeah yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
I know yeah I'm chocolate ice cream
today
chocolate ice cream we're working on it
right mommy
[Music]
who are you going for what outfit do you
want
uh whichever is the closest on the tree
yeah
understandable all right and then we
have a baby
hello Live ID today I'm cosplaying as
Section 8 with money in your area
was so good what the heck that was
really good I thought she was here wow
okay yeah and then we have
[Music]
hello hello hello I am I will be the
second the shiraka musica today
the organizer of today's event the
sponsor of today's event
[Music]
the reason I'm laughing is because this
has happened to her about seven or eight
times every time she's we've been
setting up for like over an hour and
every time Kiara is like okay is
everybody here and ready okay I want to
go over this and then it cuts and we get
kicked out I'm sorry oh the brother
makes no sense okay hold on let me put
the let me put the color
took too long the chico show Kai is
always taking too long
taking too long
take a show Kai okay let me get back in
the room do I have to hide anything I
have stream remote turned on also I'm
kind of sleepy oh sorry hold on let me
hide my screen because I don't know what
I'm doing
where is my
yeah hey where is the game hold on let
me turn this off
don't go
look at this circle
oh I could show it anyway oh well look
out there's a Segura
I saved up all my points well most of
the points so that I could show you guys
that on stream anyway we're back in
you're gonna hear it now
so much I can do this
[Applause]
yes
um I will now change the row settings we
will have everything included we'll have
scientists in case you don't know the
scientists can see the vitals at any
time not at any time well there's a
countdown but you can see if someone's
dead before finding the body and then we
have the engineer engineer can uh is a
crewmate who can jump into the vents so
you can maybe with that I got that a lot
in practice yeah or you can maybe find
some other imposters because of that
might be happening in the lens oh no
yeah face to face spicy for you too very
spicy and now we have the guardian angel
which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
and I only have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is oof that that
calls for a lot of
fights
[Music]
it was you I knew it was you
shapeshifter can be only an imposter but
that imposter can change the looks of
themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
but just so you know all of these rolls
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it might happen to you now
let's okay
[Music]
oh
yeah
come on
everybody everybody
[Laughter]
see you can see it now
I can't there's no mini game because you
need to have a task I have it it's
because I'm an imposter you tried that
last time wait one minute remember wait
touch my back burn tomato tomato burger
bun
no I need a I need a I need a listen
guys I learned from my last time I need
do you need a are you like Webkinz
oh yeah
wait don't don't that's embarrassing
oh I'm just kidding look it looks like
Lego floor it's so far away oh yeah they
look like little the light the lines are
off
oh no
also I need an alibi
as you go ball
hello short hello how do I get to the
lights
oh okay
wait oh my God
that was quick
that was fun um wait where was it the um
where was the body Armory yeah
I think or was it Ollie Armory tasks
[Music]
like uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory but that was the
beginning I was in the back room when it
was for now well she got killed fast
you know anybody want to step up and be
like yo I'm something I have no idea
though you can uh if if you are you were
telling me that um I was in a Armory you
can ask a gura because I saw Guru also
in uh nearby there in the kitchen
[Music]
nine seconds guys
I have no idea
I need it says
Saucy oh no
girl you right next to me or something
again
oh I don't know where to go this game is
overwhelming I always picking the
kitchen
I'm going where the food is
okay I gotta go down here I have that
one too are you
we could be Alibi if I don't know what I
am wait what the heck
I'm uh can I tell you I'm I can go
through event I'm engineer oh wait so
there are some people who think because
I don't have anything yeah something it
might just be a regular crewmate but I
don't know I feel like I'm gonna mess it
up oh no lights are going out way I
don't know I need to go to the armory
over here
hey why is it not wait what
hang on did you pick them up wait I'm
doing this I can't put them away now
pick them all up putting the guns away
my guns
oh wait I think we all have the same
test I don't know how to play Among Us
one run while we were practicing I kept
on screaming
uh yeah but there's a task yeah
oh my alibi is gone
my alibi is back hello
my only blue janitor oh
wait I need to go do a thing
wait okay I'm
I'm um
[Music]
hi
putting the files away you scared of
some paperwork reading
parks are scary
oh I'm just doing paperwork wait what is
this what does this do what is this
oh
somebody's in the meeting room three
people are in the main hall wait am I in
the main hall two people are in the main
hall no I'm in records two people oh
I know this was like what was this Kobo
I don't think of the guard with you guys
come on man oh my God
is that is dead
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical I was going to the viewing
that I was with a roommate and Kelly
Senpai I mean
I passed by I passed by I think it was
Watson or and
angura yeah in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw Zeta they were in
the main hall with Kobo
Cobo
I was listening about global because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now
um
yeah no okay
yeah she left
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobble yeah
so any last words
like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh see herself like just what
she said and then after that I go up
right near the lounge that was beginning
though that was the very beginning
after that I go up
I go after killing her you mean that's
something
we have like we have little short time
uh choose uh who's you're gonna know
I have enough information yeah I have no
idea
I haven't heard
I don't know
at the very beginning
[Music]
I'm just gonna make a sandwich
I'm going back to records baby I need my
alibi
I don't have an alibi uh
hello hello hello
[Music]
no no no no no no no
rain is safe right raining can't be that
bad Mommy hello I wanted some people who
bought more
videos stab me
I need to go to electrical
electric girl hello I'm doing electrical
oh
wow thrilling
This Is Love
yeah yeah yeah
I'm so lost oh this map we practiced on
the like default
who killed her who killed her
no okay that's insane Watson is dead uh
I found the body
oh is this
last time yeah oh
um okay I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
came in right after while I was figuring
out how to do the mini game I was like
how do you do this then mume ran in hey
and was like hey he eats he and doing
things and then I walk out and watch
this dead body is there
because you would have passed Watson if
you were entering the front of the ship
you would have passed Watson how did you
not see her well I don't know I did pass
I want to say I passed gura and I went
beep up we people people didn't
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about I don't know why you
remember so much Kelly I'm I'm just
surprised I got a lot to say I don't
okay now listen here's the deal so the
amount of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
I just don't believe it
wait
I I don't know where the body was I
don't know I was
[Music]
oh
it was Ruby she was on cooldown what the
[\h__\h] give me my points now
yes multiplier multiplier no multiplier
[Music]
calm down
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately
I think I think Kelly you should go for
it Amelia wants some detective outfit uh
yeah
thanks are you guys ready for another
round
[Music]
oh
oh what's up
[Laughter]
this is
a million times perfect
ah oh perfect
look at me saving the day oh God
okay I always have to remind myself it's
just a mobile game I can do it it's a
mobile game mobile game let's check the
cameras
this is useless too on the viewing deck
3 and the viewing deck
okay well two in the kitchen hello
hello
hi I need to do my test I'm so okay oh
why are there so many wait no no no no
no no
um hello
oh God I don't know where to go in this
map I don't get anywhere hello
it's easier to remember people when like
you hear their voice I think I'm trying
to find an apple pie would anybody like
to be my alibi
what do you mean why an alibi that's how
you so you don't get caught in a I don't
know never mind I'm going up to meeting
I don't know how to get there
oh hello hello
what
oh God
oh I have to clean that I'm not doing
that I should do it though because
there's nobody around
it's okay it's just me here
Moshi moishi Pizza Time
eight one four one four have you guys
seen that
have you guys seen that like what is it
called I don't know is it called rotor
scoping I'm not reading chat by the way
I just want to ask you I saw this like
video where they took all the Spidermans
hello
Joke Man
oh that's awake
that was crazy so I don't know the map
super well but I left the shower so I
put away all of the washcloths from the
shower and then I walked up and I turned
right and I went down that long hallway
and found Ollie's body right in the
middle of there but I didn't see anyone
coming down
so like above the shower house above the
shower knives
that you remember well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she did pretty close I think girl was in
the shower as well but she like went
down to the left no oh I was up in the
meeting room with full Bowl
you said who's gonna be delay of the of
the of the kill because because if if
it's really if it's raining if she
already killed only probably she cannot
kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like you're gonna vouch for me she
was trying to tell me a joke and then I
ran away from her oh yeah
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below hey
why are you stressing me out huh no I'm
just like saying uh so probably saying
that you are nearby the the place I just
like thinking oh true I'm true you're
also there by the way but I I don't
remember I saw moonassemba in the
middle-ish or on the left side
by the way um
oh my
sandbagging Sandberg
it's not teabagging yeah the Spider-Man
the various Spider-Man actors rotoscoped
into Mario Kart pretty funny oh
good taste everyone good thing people
kitchen
okay I'm going down
I have no LOL oh no I'm just a little
shark it's so wild saving myself here
hello munya
a little girl
I'm following hello
goodbye
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
like literally
yeah I can't do this one I will do it
leave it to me
I fixed it we all stay together
[Music]
my alibi I'm going to do this
shall I be your alibi well I just want
you to know that I'm I'm yes I'll see
you very clearly downloading files
secret files when are you downloading uh
pictures of you uh nothing secret
recipes
[Music]
of you you were filming creatures of Me
Maybe we can share that indirect
directions
yeah once we get how do we what is use
the card like me
hello person
boom
why would you vote for yourself I can't
get out you're scaring me
think long and hard about this decision
fellow crewmate
[Music]
blah blah
blah
oh boy
I don't even know I didn't understand
nobody you me oh my God where
no no
[Music]
very bottom of the armory
what um
I was anybody else Kiara I was with
Kiara and we confirmed each other as
alive
actually I was on the way to the kitchen
so any any sooner I would have found the
body but I'm from the engine room I saw
you I saw you at the right side of the
map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know there's the touch oh okay
cool
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have some kitchen and viewing deck and
then I was about to turn to the Armory
and then bomb that body oh pretty close
by yeah
went past me and it was the first voice
we're gonna be there what I also saw
that but it was like way back
inside it's not me I don't know
trainer's voice it was zetta's voice and
I was like I went like what
inside
what what the fun moment
you've been popped your last book babe
I gotta go
is moving
I hope my Wi-Fi is good over here oh
good oh where's the perfect
hello
I'm doing my tasks oh hello hello
please don't disturb me
I need to find Kiara let's look at the
cams let's see
it's me
hi hello thank you
okay I don't know what I'm looking for
I need to do my task guys I'm so sorry
okay I need to get in here and do this
because this is important
oh
use
what
it's a mobile game it's a mobile game
it's a mobile game it's a mobile is that
a one
one
oh come on
three
colors prayed of me I mean uh two
this task sucks three
four where's four
this house is sucky
five
well now I'm useless because I can't I
have no idea what's going on five
six all night oh oh it's closed on your
safe on your safe we're doing the same
task
hi hello let's go to the shower in the
engine room right now
okay wait I need to do this one wait
wait wait wait
oh
about you
mommy mommy you stink mermaid stink
Mommy
no
no no are you actually are you are you
bluffing
maybe I don't want to find out no that's
okay
no no no no no no no no hello
watch our movies in there hi
hi
wait send it back
where who's there
[Applause]
[Music]
wait where
I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical test with Anya and I ran into
Renee and mume
um
for a while that's uh technically that's
true I I'm thinking why I think these
three a two Row in the back is always
you guys always spots us about rainy why
yeah read it yeah
it wasn't me it wasn't even me reporting
I don't know where the body is this time
yeah
shifters don't forget shapeshifters
we're not MediCal guys
where was it
wait I want to ask uh Arena where are
you at I'm at Medical I came from cargo
bay
Uma was like going from bottom to up oh
yeah I saw her in the cargo bag and
where was the body I literally have no
idea
for a little bit but then I was down by
electrical like down the ladder that's
where I was coming up when it was
reported
I don't know why it sounds like a
protective now I'm so serious why I want
to ask why is Mermaid so always so
afraid of me or is she just afraid of
everybody in general she's been pretty
quiet yeah I was thinking
oh my voted for me last time the body
boy
wait so do we have an answer where the
body was I missed it probably yeah
where's it where's the body was I was
gonna see the body both the body is
I don't know what should I choose um
sorry boy
I don't know I mean she could have
killed me
now we just need to eject one more
I feel bad but if that wasn't all right
I need to do my test too I kind of suck
oh no
I didn't I just do this or was this the
last round hello hello
what's this do
you do all your stuff you're lucky I'm
on cooldown
ash shut up uh
wait what this is not a this is not a
desk what am I doing wait okay no
there's another test
oh okay
wait Vault how do I get to the Vault oh
I'm so lost I don't know what it should
be the map girl just read the map girl
look at this look at this look at us oh
funny hat
oh hot pants wow the internet smell what
it where is that where is that at the
meeting room or the the gab room oh I
really need a oh I don't want to do that
one I'll wait till the very end for that
one I don't want to do it
look at me do it with times wow
noise we're gonna show you the among us
huh
they're off
hello would you would you like to be my
alibi
hello
okay I need to clean this vent it's
gonna make Jesus I'm not sauce I need to
clean it how many times you got weird
echoes in here
[Music]
it's definitely it definitely wasn't
rated then I thought it was her maybe
but uh I found her body in the kitchen
but I saw no one else around
I I I heard I heard brain is so
doppelganger of me
so yeah
[Music]
of me
so I don't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see Randy
running from Luna but maybe it wasn't
Muna Muna
oh wait who yeah I saw I saw you too I
mean Muna is like oh whatever was with
Reyna for a while so I'm not not this
time but I was with her often enough
wait was that the previous run I'm
mixing I can't remember yeah was that
like
it might have been last game when I was
a lot with rain was it I ran into Kobo
Kobo was something very scared though so
I was like for a while together she
could have killed me she didn't so I
think she's fine
um
recently I think we already voted one
out so there should only be one imposter
yes there was a couple of times a couple
of times I go with Ahmed but but she
didn't kill me neither
uh I have a feeling that
maybe but they're not but then it might
be um I got a doppelganger so I don't
know I don't know I just wanna because
last time
in the weapons like it's not all right
can anyone anyone vouch for Ahmed and
say like she's safe I was with Gouda
didn't kill her mom and she did threaten
me though I was fussing about Kobo
though because
I don't know
I chickened out
she always threatens to kill me
I need to clean this stupid vent who
wants to come sit with me while I clean
the bed it's my last task oh God this
face is so cute I just wanted to say oh
hello how do I get there again okay okay
moon is going up there I'm going to go
sit here and wait till somebody I run
into somebody until not
I wish I had a secret power
God I hate that task God I hate that
task I hate that task I hate that task
can I ride this
where are we dads are done yay
should we ride in
you were on cool down
she was on cooldown all right
damn it
it hurts multiplier
[Laughter]
oh well
yeah
[Music]
wow
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me yeah
it was really hard to watch I was barely
doing nothing it was so easy to do
yeah
I was like live and then I saw something
I wasn't supposed to say thank you
[Music]
hi okay
nice
so bad like
early in the game
no evidence
[Music]
I have a question on there because I
heard you in the in the selection screen
where you choose where to go next I
heard you say something that sounded
like something
because I felt like you might have been
acting
I thought you were like aware that we
would hear you and you were on purpose
saying something that only a crewmate
would say
let's go
oh my God are we waiting for Moana right
now I'm ready
let's go
yes you see it's like the Webkinz bun
onion wait what the [\h__\h] bun tomato
onion onion fun ew puts iron onion yeah
I know I like the taste actually I'll
order it with onion but then I'll take
it off it hurts my stomach
onion hurt
hello hello I have a gun
don't touch me I got bullets
come on mobile gamer let's go okay
a viewing deck oh my favorite
what is this wi-fi downloading
I'm downloading okay files right now
okay okay you're viewing files oh my
Wi-Fi
where's the perfect
oh
Grandma
um
that you will know um
yeah uh going to the Armory and the
kitchen when when I want to go to engine
room so I didn't I thought you were she
from cockpit or main hall
I think
she went to the left side so she was
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Hallie do you have an alibi maybe
I was going out to get service I did
pass you Watson I was worried you were
gonna follow me outside but you didn't
uh you probably weren't that worried
since I decided success
right by the body because uh I was the
one who ordered her coming up the ladder
yeah I couldn't see because it was
really dark and then
you went on I went up
[Music]
I'm just gonna like skip yeah
I have no idea
don't kill me YouTube don't do it hey
whoa don't do it
[Music]
I'll spawn hello
Chad spawn in the kitchen
every round
wait did I do that I did okay oh good I
don't have that smelly electrical task
is that like
come on
uh I'm electrical 15 minutes
electric wait how do I get in here
oh wait
uh oh
I'm just doing tests
I want your camera again
hello
hi
what is that distance my guy
okay Zeta has a long range uh bolt
action rifle apparently
she kind of sounds like fun
nice
I'm shower
I'm watching them in the shower
dude who's gonna find my body
anybody go find my body oh Ollie might
no
attack
oh my God that's like Kelly wouldn't
find my body zeta's a monster
okay
where's that where's the body uh
showers
Lounge Lounge yes
dolls are
[Music]
um
the last time the last time I went near
the shower
[Music]
with anyone they can't hear us
I was getting some Giggles out of Kobo
though yelling at her the entire time so
haunting people does really work like
psychologically
she's innocent yeah listen to me I'm
always us when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm uh so keep that
in mind now you're saucing me which
means I'm a crewmate it's always like
this the reverse I don't think that's
gonna worry
about it
because why the [\h__\h] why aren't you
providing an alibi instead of Defending
yourself huh
I was only the secluded room where like
she would have killed me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh of course those two
oh
come on punch someone
I volunteers
spotted in the kitchen
thought of everybody now we're here oh
God I'm so good at this game
look at me I'm just a little man I'm
just a little guy a little funny little
guy doing my funny little tasks
do my little funny task
look at me
you want my preschooler triangle to
Triangle
[Music]
see okay listen see I might not be like
you know uh doing anything like that but
at least I'm contributing and watch some
shop don't kill me
no I'm not I'm uh doing a thingy
is the thingy killing me uh nope okay
oh good to know no give me more drama
give me draw do something
yell at each other kill each other I
don't want to stay with you ready
me
I do all my tasks
okay it's Zetta for sure I'm voting no
really oh really
okay
you you found a buddy three times in a
row now yeah because I just happened to
be a detective
bodies
say some scary things but I don't know
man Rayna could I have killed you or
would I have it's an idea if I was with
you and in that room for like over 30
seconds
I don't know uh you want me to be honest
um what you said was oh just kidding I
was just waiting for my cool down too
yeah but I was already in the room
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jetta
no
no no but I mean I was kind of running
away from the body well Reyna and I were
both up in the room like in the meeting
room and then as I went down the whole
time and then we saw Zayna pass Us in
that hallway
yeah I saw Kobo take the little elevator
yeah
[Applause]
30 seconds 30 seconds
[Music]
[Laughter]
10 seconds who
11.
oh no
is that the only one
massive hands
spawning in the kitchen oh where's
everybody I hate lights out
color ball
nobody's running here where else can you
spawn on yourself oh I wanna see
I want to see the action
[Music]
oh my God that's such a horror movie
what
horror movie
map is too big can you imagine this like
you know I need four movies through here
like
okay do I shut
traits that I may always repeat it
[Music]
what other test we have one more over
here
[Music]
yep I have two more
okay I'll follow you in one two three go
yay
I'm also here in the afternoon
oh no there
good someone is going to the other side
Iceberg Captain oh okay oh wait you can
go you can go other side oh
so she's doing right now
[Applause]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
I don't know okay
come on
okay okay
[Music]
I keep pressing the wrong buttons
I don't how long does it last
wait wait
[Applause]
I'm sorry
we could win I have no idea what's going
on
[Music]
um
trust me bro
bro okay
[Applause]
you just didn't have an opportunity
to kill but I was constantly with her
[Music]
but why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you oh true that
was such it took so long after couple
went over to that side but Tyler was on
that side too right now
I was just being stupid
oh sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place just because
all right because we want to develop you
off yes
it's not me
because I kind of feel bad for her
because
[Music]
that's so nice of you
sing me finally
you know
you're dead finished I did finish just
want to make sure
apparently nobody likes playing no I
feel good very nice but not voting for
AMI
why why do you keep closing hurry
Aloo I swear I hate this game I hate
no run oh God did you do your task
s
where is everybody
bro
swipe it
I know
you want me
I mean who is it oh
rainy doing this
I'm so tired
why did you run the road
where are you here
oh
okay I'm gonna go up back to the
emergency meeting okay
because I only have one emergency
meeting I already used it so it has to
be someone else
thank you oh now pushing hard on this oh
there's someone coming over someone said
welcome
[Music]
back
who hasn't finished we could we could
win
[Music]
who isn't finishing because we could I
have guys
you see me
wait so was it Clara senpai
I have no idea why camera
watch is that excuse me
I done all my tasks
they have left
all right
you're done but that would mean because
we're all around who it is probably
foreign
[Music]
oh no
you're ready
[Applause]
to go
ask her
[Applause]
that's cool who was it it was global
oh yeah big points baby oh just kidding
I want that multiplier
was so intense
but to be honest was so spot on
that's just her personality it's not
that she's the Imposter that's just her
personality
he's saying hi to her and I was like
doubting myself
you would believe me
[Music]
um
hello there's a lot of people here
we'll stick dang it I have the stupid
electrical task
I'm gonna eject myself God
oh okay
oh towels the leather glove is Two Doors
Down
oh this one is it weird if I sniff these
before I put them in the wash is that
weird is anybody here to hear me oh
laugh
s
pick up the towels shark
I'm gonna sniff them anyway no one's
here to stop me
sniffy sniffy
I'm gonna attack myself in here because
then if somebody has to come kill me
they're gonna have to walk around first
sniff
oh sniff hmm
that one smells like
chocolate ax why oh sniff hello
okay let me go get this electrical task
out of the way how do I get there
you're stuck in here
hello
what is that hello Miss Cuba
it's oh God I hate this one what is this
seven
two
wait seven two
what is this one
or
fingers
oh my God
whoa whoa
yes
okay you watched her die
where who said that where oh ah maybe we
should vote mummy out she really wants
to die oh okay okay
I didn't pull this [\h__\h] before the
impulsor though I want to be killed
though um
killed please
she said please wait you want to be cute
all right we'll give you some more time
to get some kills
you want to be killed or or Kiara Kira
just uh go to mume so if she was the
first one or maybe we can restart the
games
[Music]
you're killed I mean you're suffocate I
want to watch me get like you know
beheaded or whatever okay then I'll I'll
grab one here but she have my world
moving all right we'll give you until
the next meeting and then okay
this combo wanna talk about it because
she reported so yeah
oh yeah yeah where was the body where
did you find the body Cobble I found the
body in front of Communications between
Communications and Communications and I
was oh I was uh
I don't think um left side
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
near me we'll give you until the next
meeting
[Music]
I don't know oh
I don't know if anybody asks I'm still
stuck in
that place
right now oh kitchen oh
all right nice oh back to electrical
with me
she's a little guy just a funny little
guy he's stuck in electrical me
I get too overwhelmed with this game too
much to keep track of okay wait what did
it start it over did I even start this
six
three
that's a one or a seven that's a one
oh
I get tangles in my feelings but I think
that's the electrical current passing
through my body
I get the tangles in a silly place
that's not a
that's a five
on you it's not a two thank you
that's a 40. hello
that's two
that's a seven oh
okay so that was that was who was that
that was alien
somebody else
together Roy Senpai
where
oh my God
okay so let me bounce I was with uh
Grayson Bayern munas and find electrical
yeah
they didn't kill me at all he was pretty
quick to get an alibi there huh wait
what wait who found which body though
there's three bodies right I found
zeta's body in cargo bay and it wasn't
there a moment ago I think but the
lights were out oh
because I saw them and we were we were
near the kitchen first and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
for a while so
I'll buy
um
I want to ask and also why Kiara is not
screaming at all
yeah
usually when when she was the crew man
she always voted she always screamed
whatever she meant somebody wanted to
cut me off I did scream are you sure
about that yeah what the [\h__\h]
I've been I've been I've been uh
watching all of you guys
um you know
and
Sound by on the previous uh previously
where Kiara Kiara really loves to scream
whenever met anyone that's because I was
scared that's because
you're scared and now you didn't know so
far you didn't show that you are scared
do you have an alibi no no because I
didn't see
I
don't know
ah
a
I'm scared for my life I don't know how
to trust anymore
am I in danger
I might be in danger
I don't know if I'm in danger
am I in danger
there's an animal in trouble there's an
animal in trouble
there's an animal in trouble it's me I
have to do this please don't start it
over did it start over
I don't know what number I was on
oh no no no no no it didn't start over
Okay wait one two three
oh
[Music]
do do
oh
feeling so alive right now wait four
wait oh
[Music]
wait where is that
oh it's so far away somebody else would
do that right where do we get there can
I even get there from here
ah
[Music]
how much time do we have for this
wait ah
60 Seconds
I'm going the wrong way for it it's done
okay
it's too early in the morning to be
streaming
somebody's avoiding the cameras
okay finish this girl oh my God five
six five where's five five
five five five five five five five five
seven five
five
must be down here five five five five
um
no
wait where is it
this is seven there's a six here
oh
freedom freedom
oh it's called Bobo going down
uh
hmm
okay I have to do this one
I don't have an alibi I've seen Cobo
that's it
going up
what the [\h__\h] why is it like that
I'm not doing my desk
there's these two traveling together a
lot there's Kobo
oh
what happened hello
it wasn't
yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai going
towards where Ollie was and that was the
last time I saw her but
alive oh really did you see on your way
there or over there wait where was he
actually split ways no I didn't see the
body I pressed the emergency button
oh okay I didn't see the body yeah
um
it really went to check if anyone's
did by pressing or you're the last one
left and you want to try to vote people
out
every
it's cool but she didn't say anything go
ball we're we're in the same room shark
yeah
I didn't know if you were uh uh uh uh
what is it called what are they called
oh it's it's skin consumer skin wearing
shape shape shifter because you didn't
say anything but I guess it's fine oh
yeah why'd you call a meeting what the
egg yeah why did you call me to stop the
tasks is that it okay fine well you know
what I'm done with my task anyways so
like maybe I can just go chat with the
girls you guys can vote me up if that's
what you guys saw
I might just talk with the ghost man
um
yeah they're like no
oh all I wanted to be is us the whole
time
[Music]
very loud usually
what I mean I'm allowed now whoever what
is it that said the rhyme did that I
have no idea I've been stuck in
electrical doing this stupid
um
I'm sorry Molly I have no idea
Ollie
somebody eating I just hear me
pots and pants
I don't know
oh it's me now
well I might be dead
somebody did the lines
come on
that's Amelia then because Coco didn't
kill me
is that a baby a mollus in the corner
how do Among Us make new Among Us
it was global
okay interesting I know kobo's so quiet
I I don't know how I would uh
gotten that one
stupid electrical task
I gotta save it for last or get out of
the way first or something anyway
s okay
every time Kobo is the Imposter it's
incredibly difficult that should tell
you whenever people are dying really
fast it's definitely Kobo she's so quiet
she saw the crime scene when goes to the
emergency meeting and then Ahmed Changes
Everything by sustaining the innocent
ones yeah yeah exactly
remove her first one
I was right with you Kiara salty wow
I'm probably like one last round
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go
[Music]
oh
I have my favorite task in collecting
towels
uh-huh
I'm gonna live for a long time
my towel doesn't want to give me this
towel I'll never forgive myself if Gira
kills me I'm just collecting towels no
need to fear me
just this little shark howl why can I
not pick this towel up all right uh one
and a half okay yeah I think what this
is every time oh my God what is this
bugged last one oh I'm sorry what what
what
take a shower
what was your body I thought it was uh
no raining is dead so here's what I
found I was picking up all of the towels
and [\h__\h] in the shower and I said I hope
girl doesn't kill me a girl is fine I
don't think that she did it but I went
to the left okay
um we were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta
you just immediately jumped on me
from the left from the left of the
shower walked up and in that photo room
we're all like it's like a dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report I clicked report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there
okay the lights
at electrical
electrical I was at electrical showers
okay I was at electrical and I saw no
one yeah I saw Zetta but I was there
where where I was at electrical I have
my I was at the bottom right of
electricity
no I didn't finish picking them up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels
because I was in the electrical I saw I
was in the electron I was in the middle
I was in the middle bottom and see that
he was in the bottom but I didn't see
anyone
I don't know
no one is rejected
too much all right bro we gotta turn
these lights back on
ask it you shall receive
time to pick this up oh
in the hamper
what oh there's another towel where this
one
oh
this one it's a wet what kind of animal
leaves a towel on the wet floor hello
interesting
yeah over you oh yeah over you I want to
take a ride in a a a laundry Rollie
Rollie laundry or laundry man
laundroman push me in the cart laundry
man
I will be your shirt
I hope no one finds out about me killing
other people
oh no that would be surely suspicious
Ollie
oh no guys guys guys guys guys I I I
pass uh on Ollie's I pass on Ollie's uh
in the in the electrical I was doing
what I wanted to do and then and then
after that she's going up and then I saw
I saw
I ran into Ollie after that and she was
saying and I quote sure hope nobody sees
that I were hoping catches me killing
people
the first time the first time all he
said is she was an electrical but I
didn't see it and then the second time
you know we we had to teleport first
right and then after that he said you
know I'm an electrical I find you and
after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh only passed by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
I just couldn't resist to him
[Laughter]
I wish your partner good luck Ollie
whoever was with you
hopefully can do this alone
gotta be careful the next one might be
same gen Bond
is it actually the next one might
actually usually got this one wrong
though I'm 14 but what if we got it
wrong is it actually Ollie
she would defend herself more if it
wasn't her
yeah
[Music]
she sounded like sarcasm
torioli
that's okay well I've always wanted to
recessed anyways
so this will be in cute doll
find the process of elimination
wolf
oh God okay
oh God wait where okay wait oh okay it's
80 Seconds I can do this
I have time to do this I haven't done
any of those helping things
[Music]
could it be
not a true crewmate
[Music]
I want to get my hood because I have my
tail I have a tail thank you where am I
going okay I need to go here
you're woozy
um hello
the pistols
you chose me with a gun right
about four
I was a sharpshooter back in Atlantis
where
I just saw her like a second ago running
away from the alarm like as she finished
the alarm and then she walked to the
right side towards uh Records Lounge Etc
we're bodlers there where's that
the body
records I was in main hall going to
showers and then set up Best Buy and
then contact I checked like around the
showers and then I go up a bit and
there's Anya's body there are you saying
so the last time
yeah yeah but I was but I will meet
again
uh-huh
[Music]
what if
is everyone
everybody because we know it's not
ourselves I'm as voting for me again
isn't she
um
[Music]
thinking for a while I'm sorry
I don't know
oh I have no idea
how many times can I say that when I
play this I don't know
[Music]
full bookie
we won nice
now we end on the four times multiplier
yes
a dome
okay that's fine
oh I have enough fur too
no
wow great job everybody
[Music]
that was a great job
that was my alarm sorry okay
is there anyone who didn't get imposter
every single time me me
[Music]
I like doing my tests and it helps
cussing people out you know this game is
like never end I feel like I want to
play it until I got a major imposter it
yeah
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know
for me it's fine because I usually sleep
at morning
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah okay one more
[Music]
you guys want to see a magic trick never
mind please no I'm not the magic trick
right now
[Music]
immediately um load it out immediately
oh
gouda is not it no Gordon Ramsay's gonna
kick my ass I can't make this burger
tomato onion onion
okay
I did it hello hello
lights are off oh
no
like no no no no no no trap
I can do the magic trick right now
wait who is it I'm opening the door okay
thank you
I really don't want to do that task
again
what is this is this one like yeah I
said I was saying
I swear
self support
it was in the hallways it was in the
main hall actually yeah okay
yeah so uh I was I was I actually uh saw
her through the showers I went to
electrical a little bit then I went back
to the main hall and guess this I
actually met another Ollie so if you
guys said anything like oh my God no
there was actually a doppelganger and I
actually met her she was chasing me down
you know what even if you guys
know I don't mind
even if I
like
it I believe you though okay
[Music]
because I don't know yeah I don't know I
don't know either
desperate whenever she's just like this
herself and whenever she tries to defend
herself always just like very very
desperate yeah
I'm gonna skip
nobody voted
a freebie round look you see my cursor
look I'm breaking a heart rate writing
making and writing I'm making and
writing a hard shoe
what happened last round I'm always the
Imposter and he didn't even she didn't
even try
I don't know
I got a glitter reviewing dick hello
hello
how do I get there oh
for me you shouldn't have oh
gameplay like last round like
okay where do we go viewing dick
huh
no
hi bubble do I have to be down there I
don't know no this one I have to do
I'm downloading my files
oh there can only be one
I have to redownload all of my files now
dude
it's true though in the words of a wise
zombie now we can hurry up with our
tasks
oh oh
now I can read the chat man guys imagine
never getting imposter once
imagine
it's fine now we can do our own no this
is actually gonna be easier now this is
for the better
oh and then
uh
couldn't save them
it was a double cake I would only get a
pretty name plate like oh it was good
um
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main oh I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something
and then there was also Zetta or
something but there was like a bunch of
people there
so who killed you I feel like Yeah I
wanted to show them like I'm not
accusing anybody I'm just telling what I
saw okay I feel like I mean um
[Music]
to save her yeah but the thing is I
don't know Anya Anya was also there but
Anya's also there but girls also dead
I don't know
um
because everything will be used against
me again
to do another
interesting
mama okay I'm zooming now
I'm zooming
one ha ha ha
do oh
yeah
no
four
yeah
huh
seven
yes oh sweet release from here
I'm like I get really aggressive I
uh
um meeting room okay
[Music]
okay and then
eight seven one four one eight seven one
four one
Speed Run I need my points so I can get
my own skin when I saw that they put
mine all the way at the top I was like
haha oh cause now I'm gonna have to I
don't know I was like man
guys
didn't take so long to get my own skin
baby
one more
yeah right we got the wrong guy well I
don't know actually there might be one
more
I honestly don't know I didn't get any
well we were plaque design well we were
practicing I literally got a engineer
like every single time and I've gotten
nothing interesting awesome
interesting
[Music]
I'm trying to figure out who oh yeah
yeah I'm zitas
I don't know I'm pretty I couldn't see
it
can I can I shower in peace please
don't approach me thank you
it's funny if anybody else was as quiet
as Kobo I think they would be kicked
immediately
no I have a feeling
correct
the soup how many people died actually
yeah that's a good question almost like
you should call an emergency meeting
um
I'll kill fish okay cool
ability to find the goddamn imposter but
they're not anywhere
every time
[Music]
anyway uh okay I need to go up anyway
for a task I'm gonna go there now
also we haven't found a dead body in a
while yes
for safety
let's go I was gonna be there though
isn't she no interesting all right
I can't oh I can't right now no do it
now
can someone fix that or is that oh
I I was gonna call it an emergency
I want to say it's cool
I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Cobble
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one yes to do it and wait no
not once you would stand there for ages
thinking about what to do next and I
literally got off her doing that thing
now but like she was there I said hi I
ran away because I was wondering well
she's always there when she's planning
something I know no one died but that's
because she's a very hesitant killer she
did that before too I was watching her
and she passed gura alone a million
times and she just would not kill gouda
for whatever reason she's very hesitant
and she goes always always sort of
electrical to
as if she's doing that task but it takes
one second and she waited one minute
there believe me
I don't have any proof of her
the only thing that's like for me
suspicious is that uh she's she's being
like awfully quiet yeah she hasn't
really said anything up until like in
the discussion at all do you have a
defense for yourself yeah do you have a
defense for yourself like why are you so
quiet or you know um
she's got that imposter luck goodness I
think
absolutely I know it takes one second
are always together yeah
the shark hoodie
goodbye I would like my skin back
oh my God
buddy I don't think all right yeah that
was freaking [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm so happy that was big brain yes it
was
well I don't know who else it could be I
can follow you all day long and you will
even get killed
thanks
giving me
I'm gonna chase somebody else why are
you chasing me
Walter's alive
my head hurts all I've had is coffee I
think that's probably why oh brain hurt
Buddha
Anya
somebody must fix the lights
nobody is down here they must not be in
the main hall
how much coffee just one just one coffee
there we go
okay okay
[Music]
the last one
okay um
[Music]
I opened it
it's raining
[Music]
I didn't get the toilet test
hi
oh
[Music]
baby yeah go to the other side please
thank you
we can finally be alone I am
okay two seven not Watson I guess
[Music]
I'll keep her safe
you you better go minutes
what am I looking at
my magic trick oh
is it somebody over here is it rainy
order some pizza
no stay together down here okay
what was that where was it okay okay
where was it um
okay I just saw Luna it must be Muna
definitely don't you see that um I was
from the Gap room and I passed by when
you are fixing the electricity and I go
to the shower and then I go to record
again okay I wasn't sure there's earlier
I I saw I saw I saw I think it was Kiara
and then Zeta is from the shower too and
we passed right okay
where is the location of the body
um
in the cargo bay between the door of
medical Tucano Bay Reyna and Zeta which
way were you guys going through the
showers like to the left
I was with you sorry
was with me we came from the top to the
bottom from my glasses we saw kind of go
the other way or you saw her going with
you I don't saw her I didn't see her at
all which is the problem what number one
illiterate literally I saw I saw like um
I was in my room I wasn't breaking I'd
go to the bathroom
I think there goes some of them going to
the up to go into the records and then
after so after that I saw man I bet
in class
[Music]
let's go
oh wow
give me points it's pulling you in like
gravity
well that was a good game
that was a good game today I I'm I'm
really bad I'm really bad at being
Foster
[Music]
yeah
you guys you guys like playing girls
like you guys going to two two groups so
yeah which one should I yeah
during the meeting was actually really
scary
videos
[Music]
I'm so proud oh my God okay that was
nice
a great a great round
excellent I think
so as much as I want to continue playing
I don't wanna you know force me yeah
yeah
we don't even have to play on stream to
be honest just together
Google
this one too long
[Music]
[Applause]
Gamers
I want to hear a goodbyes from everyone
if that's okay bye okay
[Music]
let's start from the top again how was
it today oh yeah it was pretty fun I won
and it passed around and then won all
the crewmate rounds or pretty much all
of them so it's you know pretty good day
pretty good game thank you for inviting
me Kiara thank you for setting it up uh
yeah thank you guys for playing thank
you for always sussing me even though
you almost never with me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I missed you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
it's cool thank you so much see you next
time
together thank you
knew it was fun
we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
I don't like playing imposter anyway so
I had a good round um really only one
super good play in the beginning and
then everyone gangs up on your boy
that's fine
and then everyone killed you early
thanks yeah
whenever you like explain something it
was really easy to listen to you and
like we found it so convincing and you
are not lying
us I just gotta work on my longevity in
the game
let's do tasks and I love doing tasks so
it was fun
I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damnedest best teammate that I possibly
could oh yeah
a bit relieved I I was scared to see
what happens if it's like especially
like shape-shift there killing all of
you without a second second edition oh
my God
that's terrifying I
really want to be a safe shifter I
haven't got that yeah
[Music]
we'll take over the world
Coco killer killer can you give us a
statement about your actions today how
many times were you imposter
a lot many three times
yeah
together with me because I cannot
um I don't know why but I'm playing on
this room like uh there's
maybe pressure
[Music]
for a long time because uh first I I
don't really uh can make a good execute
yeah I will buy maybe in Bahasa
Indonesia uh um it's so easy but
um I don't know that's fine you can
always use that as the excuse like
literally just say I use that with the
JP no English please
you did a good job you're really good
yeah you're really good I love skills
yeah
who gets just so many times
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought Tim I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually asked us and say oh I've
actually says that would make you guys
ah Ali's just messing around but nah but
that's what I was thinking like I pray I
feel like you oh
thank you
maybe maybe it will fix itself in a
little bit Yeah and uh I actually want
to thank yours invite especially because
uh organizing these source of collabs is
like a big castle in here and well all
the most utmost respect thank you for
accommodating all of this song okay
Kiara thank you thank you
[Music]
I'm happy that we had a good reason to
play along this again after a long long
time
for a second and go to oh mum is not
here anymore
oh hello yeah I start the stream naked
in the end of the stream naked even
though I unlocked the outfits
we're inviting me to the collab it was
really fun playing with you guys was fun
or suit to all the crewmates and also
the Imposter you guys were great oh yeah
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few imposters
feel free uh two or three I don't
remember
it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you for
hosting it and I want to apologize
because my stream died six times oh my
God how did you survive
um
yep
[Music]
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah and um
are you able to talk
oh there she is how fast are we
traveling Oh Oh Discord oh yeah
let's go to this chord everybody Discord
all right
like this Discord
uh anyone
um okay
um
[Music]
thank you
um
I have fun uh actually uh the first time
I'm doing uh the to become an imposter
with I mean it's really fun
because because I'm just the one that
I'm I'm usually afraid of whenever I
become an imposter and because you know
everyone
if I make it a list it's probably a me
Kiara and then Kali is the one who can
like talk a lot that make me you know
so that's usually the person aggressive
protective Sheriff
I'm the sheriff hey what was that
surprise there oh well anyway we can
just talk in here yeah yeah we can talk
in here yeah but now we can talk in any
way I think I got to hear from everybody
[Music]
came together for another big Enid
collab I think the last one was Mario
Karts
it was like a year ago
it was a very very long time ago let's
try it again sometimes yeah
sure yeah true
yeah let's do it I'm coming to watch
Power streams today thank you
I'm having so much fun thank you and I
really don't have anything else to say
besides good job everybody
[Music]
and yeah see you again soon sometime
goodbye