[Music]
k k the other day cie took me and some
of the other Ian girls to do some
acrylic por which is something I wanted
to do like forever let's go so basically
here I'm already doing it you take some
colors that you like you dilute them
with some water and then you put them uh
you layer them in a cup and then you put
the cup on the canvas you turn it around
and you just swoosh see what happens and
I turn it from one side to the other so
that it like stretches out you can add a
second layer of color um maybe even some
sprinkles like I'm doing here sprinkle
sprinkle and then there's a special step
that you don't have to do uh you can use
a torch blow torch and then it will
create some bubbles only if you add some
oil right before into the color and it
creates these beautiful like gem like
bubbles amazing threedimensional isn't
it beautiful I'm going to hang this up
immediately when I get home