[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
so
go
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
how is it
hello
okay there you go the pcm
hello hello hello
is it is it good is it is it fine
is it fine hello everyone it's anya
melvisa from hello live id second
generation
it's probably night time at the game
right now because it's it's pitch black
it's like literally pitch black there's
nothing to be seen here
hello it's animal visa from hawaii
second generation
hello hope you guys are doing good today
um
yeah
waking up she'll be fine oh
i can't see anything
foreign
train his doubts about the game but i
think she's having issues with the game
right now
yeah so i don't i don't know if she can
play in like an hour or something
so i i don't know what to do now
i don't know what to do now um i shall
probably do something about my house
cause wow would you look at that eight
hours left
holy heck
i only have eight hours left damn it i
need to do something about my house
such is life
grinding again oh my gosh i'm so sorry i
feel like i grind like every every time
on stream like i should probably do that
off stream and maybe do something more
exciting on stream but no i have to
grind
i have to cry in the game
gosh dang it
is
around this area but apparently they
exist
dang
i'm gonna turn off the flashlight
okay
oh
yeah speaking about scraps muna simpai
muna senpai actually went into my dm and
then she was like anya hey i'm selling
my c4 because i don't want to like i
don't want to fight with anyone else so
i'm just going to be
i'm just going to be collecting money
would you buy my cevo and then i was
like oh oh yeah that's cool maybe later
because because i barely have any scraps
right now
and it's sad you know
i'm so sorry
how much is munoz for that's actually a
good question
how how expensive is this like
how much is moona soompi see for she
said to like check the map
here
is it here
polka team shop
shop coco is it is it here
coco
robo shop
dang everyone everyone's everyone's
opening shop what the heck
i don't want to i kind of want to open a
shop too
wait what
am i
shop
how much are you gonna be selling it
i don't see any other shops
[Music]
m
as well
the hololive fishing place is gone
hi hi hi toyota
[Music]
we need high metals as usual and maybe
some stones as well
you spicy
spicy
[Music]
um i don't think so
i don't think we can use this um
i'll just go the traditional way i guess
traditional way of doing stuffs
me and my rock best friend
okay okay
nicer
okay
[Music]
who is online in the game right now
who's playing the game right now you are
not a stone
yeah i do have a jackhammer i'm just not
using it
why it makes you guys mad it makes you
guys angry that i'm not using my
jackhammer
good
stay like that
it makes you guys angry oh my god oh no
you have a jackhammer at your house
why are you not using it
good
good stay angry
cute mouthing i love to see it
i love it when you guys melt
mold i don't know oh
straps
foreign
[Music]
um
oh hello
it was those fast
the heck
that was way too fast
um
i need to do something about my house
rather than rather than the scraps you
know oh hello
okay
nice
if i see one i need to take them
i'm just foreign recycle them just in
case
okay
better scrapless than homeless i don't
know about that cannot scrap you good
one thing see
scrubs are also as important as the as
my house
both are important things
all right
okay
i'll put stuffs on my pc
[Music]
yeah why don't we have like proper
proper actual doors here nice
yuppie
oh god i need stones
yeah i need to look for some stones
oh god
then we should be fine like high quality
metals wise
we have stones here no okay
three
i'll only be taking this i guess okay
i'm gonna wait
okay
i just have to find them
where's the stones oh these are stones i
think no
nini
these are stones
[Music]
amazing wonderful
amazing wonderful we love it
nice
by the way
[Music]
if you don't think otherwise then i
don't know what to say about you
if you say otherwise then i i don't know
what to say about you chief
okay
all right
nice
okay
among your nervous
i am enlightened
i love this
okay
not gonna lie man
yeah i'm not gonna lie i'm gonna be
honest with you guys
you know
yeah this is what you call us but
reception let's go
you know
i might not king shame but i do battle
shaming
that's what i do
oops
how do you do this again
okay
hmm
cargo ship
[Music]
knowing
it she'll be dropping stuff here and
like
in like any second now what shall we do
should we go get the crate or
what to do
volleyball i can see
i'm gonna drain my
hello
hello i'm back
my
just in case you know
just in case don't say something
hello
foreign
there's probably gonna be someone over
there
i don't know though
um
oh god anyways um
okay
i can't buy anything from muna simpa's
house you know
well opened
[Music]
if you're listening to this do you want
to like get get that crate with me
except please shoot anyone please shoot
anyone you see
oh my god
beside for me anyways
we can like you know we can work
together and like get that crate don't
you think that's a good idea
should anyone beside us who gets to the
box by the way
do you think that's don't you think
that's a good idea
you know
we can share the inside of that of that
crate together
we can work together you know
is the proximity microphone on like
she's not even here ok
all right
m
i don't know if she was talking to me
though she probably was right because i
was talking about umami
speaking about team
um i got invited to matsuri
and there's also mikko senpai as well it
seems
i don't know she's probably gonna invite
me like formally like when we when we
got online like together at the same
time and she's probably not online right
now
um
gamble team not really
and then i was like
and then i was like it's like
it's like betrayal alone that's like the
worst thing i asked
and then she was like um yeah if if you
do that on the last day then i guess why
not and i was like cool
cool i'd like to join
i was like cool i'd like to join then
unless day only it seems
okay
i did nothing wrong
[Music]
foreign
please i don't get i don't get looked
boxes that often you know
i don't get loot boxes that often please
let me get one at least
okay
if zetta is online right now though that
means i can raid her house
that's probably my footsteps
no i don't i don't even have c4 that
much you know i don't have my rocket
launcher though
okay
foreign
my
is that a beer is that someone running
mona has c4 before but piccola about all
of them yeah because muna senpai
actually sent me dms and then she was
like anya
buy my c4 i need scraps and i was like
wow unfortunately for you i'm i'm i'm
kind of poor right now i don't i have
nothing you know
oh my god
[Music]
did she get it from like loot boxes
or what
[Music]
foreign
you're grinding and grinding it's fine
also i mean like i unlocked c4 as well
on my workbench
i don't need to buy
i don't need to buy them but i guess
they're like fast alternatives
they are like fast like alternatives you
want them like as soon as possible you
know
i think i unlocked like the important
stuffs on my
on my you know workbench already
so like
i think if i get more scraps i'm just
gonna use it for stuff like
i
okay
foreign
did anybody of you count like
how long do i have
how long do i have for the box
ten more minutes yeah i guess
not only
crystal
the box respawn which means it has been
five minutes
yeah it has been five minutes ish i
think
it should be like five minutes
foreign
you gonna teach the turkey that was that
was the plan
that was that was the plan but i don't
know if she can log in to the game or
not
so we will just see
i don't know if she can lock into the
game or not
but like i think it should be like in
like a few minutes 14 minutes
oh hello thank you so much for the akka
spa thank you
i'll be reading them after the stream
thank you thank you
no she changed the game all right
who's online right now i wonder
i wonder who's online right now
i know
[Music]
um
oh it's so dark
hanging
foreign
[Music]
foreign often i've been pressing the
temp city rl button for like
minutes
go yes a ghost
foreign
god i can see
i can't see
if i bait people like this will people
shoot at me
so that i will know there's like people
beside
i don't know if there's like people
around here
hey shoot at me
strategy you know
gardenia monument
shoot at me
oh man
anyways
my usual strategy is like even even when
the countdown stops i usually wait here
for a while
maybe until like a minute or something
and when there's like
when there's like
someone trying to like take the loot i
shoot at them
so that you don't go to the box
immediately god
damn it
so like you don't you don't like come
out immediately
you know
that's usually
how i do this and usually that's usually
how i do it
is
don't do that
on
yeah that's kind of what i did with
choco sensei as well
[Music]
god okay
it went away
what it all
anyone coming
foreign
don't do that to me
oh for god's sake
no
when you see me
oh no
hannah
mama
i think it's going away
not really
it's not shooting at me anymore
it's not shooting at me
but it's still here
[Music]
m
what shall i do
will it like go away because like it's
not shooting at me
you know
but it keeps coming back
the hell shall i do
what shall i do
like
it's not shooting at me but
but yeah
hello ouch
what's
up
my
it's not going to be that easy you know
he doesn't
[Music]
foreign
i don't know man i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna wait i guess
[Music]
wanna try take down the heli bro i
literally only have a
like a sniper rifle and also my ak
what the heck are you talking about
[Music]
i'm gonna wait until my hp
like
recovers until like full oh my god
oh my god did you guys see that
did you guys see that for now
[Music]
foreign
what if i move position
will it make any difference what if i
i stay here
it shoots but it doesn't hit me
and then they have to go back to take
more ammos
you know
nice
put on nice
i don't know man maybe it can run run
out of ammos and then ouch
wow
okay fine i'm gonna see
i'm gonna stay here and then and i'm
just gonna i'm not gonna do anything
i'm not gonna do anything i'll i'll wait
nani
okay
nice try though
empty but that didn't hit me
empty though
it runs out of ammos i think
and then it needs to go back ha sucks to
be you
sucks to be you bro
bye
told you guys
told you guys it runs out of ammos and
then
and has to go back or maybe i don't know
it's like in a shock state of like not
being able to hit me with that bomb
which is like their fault you know
their fault for having such a bad aim
you know
okay i'm gonna go back
any kind of
i'm gonna go back home
you know
what what is it
okay
nice
muna has rocket launchers i have like
two rocket launchers
i have like not only one but like two of
them
okay
i'm gonna go home for now
and put my stuffs
away
usually i go through the snowy area
because like sometimes there's like no
one here you know
mama okay
guys
all right
yeah usually no one is here you know so
like it's it's like 70 percent safe
safe
hmm
yeah people usually avoid snow
but like you should be able to like
survive in snow even with asthmatic suit
as long as as it's not like nighttime or
something because like
because usually when it becomes night
it's like minus 25 celsius or something
minus seven should be
manageable in there even with a hazmat
suit
yes no night time is not really it's not
really nice
okay
i actually thought about like
building my building my
base in like a snowy area you know
but then i was like
how worth it is it gonna be
you know i guess it's gonna be much
harder to like for like people to date
me and stuff
that's true
like
i
hmm
i guess next season i don't know next
season we can probably have
you know multiple bases and maybe one of
them one of them can be in the snowy
area or something like that
that sounds nice
beautiful
oh
[Music]
okay
you have to put it manually like what
what
okay
over here
[Music]
oh i heard something what is that
oh spicy
fancy
foreign
okay
yeah i guess no one goes to the
supermarket at the snowy area
which is nice for me
yeah i guess next next season or
something i'll try to think about
building something on the snowy area
yeah that sounds like a good idea maybe
i don't know maybe a sub base or
something
there you go
my
i'm not sure
alright let's go home
let's
i need to go home
i need to go home but like
i don't know does it have a box
i don't have any horse with me so like
oh no what is it
oh there you go
also my hp is not really looking good
so hp taking a shoe
[Music]
foreign
i guess
so call me
[Music]
can i just shoot at it so that it will
drop faster or something
i don't know is she online right now i'm
not sure
it's kind of worrying for me
anyone coming is anyone not coming only
one way to find out
only one way to find out
put it
but
at the same time i need to be as fast as
possible i guess
is it scary
why i don't usually take stubs
immediately you know
nice
[Music]
get as
far as possible um
oh oh seven
somewhere between o7 i think i need to
take my ak
i need to take my ak
at 07. remember when i die remember that
guys
what is it guys
oh no
i need to eat but i don't have food this
this is too
uh
if anything comes to
yeah
i'll just give her i'm just gonna give
her the ak
if it comes
if it comes to that i'm just gonna give
her the ak i guess
i mean i have like i have like six more
ak's
in my house
yeah i do have a bunch of aka so
if she found if she found my ak i'm just
gonna give her
i'm just gonna give her the ak
you're not you're not taking my raw cat
no that's the one thing i'm not gonna
forget oh no
okay
her about that ak as a gift no that's
that's not a gift
that's not that's not a gift i wouldn't
give that to anyone why would i
it's just that i have no choice right
now you know
but fine
why won't i give my ak to somebody else
oh
i'll pin back at her
can we please have oh no it's gonna be
night soon
i'm going to do this i'm going to do the
gotcha
nice
mama
okay okay okay
oil
more
okay
thank god i still have like scopes so
i still have like scopes and everything
at home
whose house is that
tiny tiny little house whose house is
that
nice uh
but i only have a pistol with me
but
i guess i have no choice but to use it
something for solar panel i guess
o7 i'm gonna go back to o7
okay
oh seven oh seven o seven
around here i think
i'm going to eat the kinokus
okay
uh
who is that
a
is
should be somewhere around here right
yeah i'm gonna ask her for now because
like
i don't want to waste my time like
looking over stuff if like if she took
it then i should just go home you know
thank you
oh yeah can you guys see the chat i i
should move myself
i should move myself maybe over here
uh
there's so many houses here oh no
then i shall
foreign
shop
just village
yeah
i
foreign
hinokos
five with a pistol
only one way to find out i guess
only one way to find out
hmm
well you still have sniper but sniper is
like very situational you know
like
the fastest way to kill people like near
you is not to use a sniper it's to use a
in an ak or like smg is fine too you
know
if you try to kill people like very
close to you you don't use sniper you
use
normal guns
use normal guns like sniper is like
for people far away
yeah close range aka is like maybe one
of the best
it's not the ak that i've that i'm
frustrated about it's about the inside
because like you know i i had like four
full steps over here if you guys didn't
see
if you guys didn't see in my ak like
this four slots are like fully built
like i had like a lot of stuff inside
for the ak she can take it i don't care
yeah the attachment
i had like four full stabs on my ak
[Music]
funny
all right full
full stuffs
she's so slick
mama
[Music]
this is this is the even better scope
all right hell yeah
okay
at least i didn't i didn't take the
the scope that i had
on the on the ak was probably a
different scope and not the
on the eighth
on the eight scope one
no or whatever
oh yeah it was the whole side
it was the whole side elijah i should
probably deal with this
do i have a hollow sight and other stuff
look at the oil
i don't think i have a whole side with
me
oh
i think i got one but it's probably in
another storage
it's probably in another storage i don't
know though
it's not anyone's in the first place
what do you what
what did what does she mean by she gave
it to me
what does she mean by she gave but she
gave it to me
oh my god
yeah yeah yeah
do i not have a homicide
really
i guess i do not have a whole site
i can probably
ah
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna tell her
who's gonna tell her
who's going to tell her not me
what is this
what's the threat stuff
what's with red stuffs
oh no
oh no buck tester
laser sign
why do i have a laser sight it wasn't
here before
this wasn't here before
this wasn't here before what the heck
okay
all right
in the game
[Music]
really
yes
we
are
friends
okay
let's go
oh i need this
i need this wait what
do i have one already
i can equip it
ah laser light aha
we can use them together okay
[Music]
yeah let's have the laser one again
okay only only one thing all right
fine then um
my explosives should be
exposed
where are my explosives
all right there you go
[Music]
oh
well then i'm just gonna put this in my
inventory i think i also
i think i have like two of this now
i'm not
no i didn't recycle that
for now
all right where is
i'm gonna i'm gonna put all my stuffs on
an event
m
is
they are holding hands oh my god
god this is too spicy oh oh just a
little bit more and they will be holding
hands
well good luck
dang this is too spicy even for my
stream what the hell
what the hell
can do this to me this is so spicy
foreign
i don't have any more space for this gun
so i'll just i'm just going to give this
ring
i'm just going to give this to rainey
does she have it done already should i
get like an smg or something
it's like this toe is trash
cause like pistol is trash maybe i
should i should i should probably get
her an smg or something
i have a bunch of thumbs in
bro without ammo this guy has animals
look at this it's called ammos
and i have so many thumbs and i don't
know why i have like five of them so i'm
just gonna
i'm just gonna give it this
i'm gonna reload this with ammo
no one want my way to p8
but that's not near enough
i'm gonna get for this smg and put the
pistol away because
we don't need that
okay
you can't really see the laser like at
daytime
this kind of sucks
i wonder if it does something like i
don't know i wonder if it it will blind
like opponent's eyes or something
can you blind like your enemies with the
laser or something
this kind of sucks bro you can even you
can even see it properly
my god
p8
fed
spicy
does it have like an hp
oh only the muzzle boost
so we can have this on any time
okay
hey
[Music]
oh
that's a new house that i haven't seen
before whose house is
we didn't see this before house is this
okay
jana senpai
let's see
i think she she's away right now i don't
know
is she away right now
whose house is this
foreign
[Music]
muslim
right now we're staying
[Music]
all right cool
oh
oh it's probably going to drop something
in water treatment plant because of
course
everyone's everyone's favorite place
oh
[Music]
foreign
hello
i couldn't figure out the voice chat
because i keep hearing you know other
people can hear themselves from me even
though someone said it correctly i can't
hear you though
i think your voice chat
kind of equals when you're talking i
think
i think i'm the one echoing ah okay
uh uh-huh yeah i can't hear my own voice
i'll give you a gun because i i have no
space in my house wait
i'm gonna give you an smg
there you go
spicy
it should have animals inside
me too
oh i'll have to go and grab one in my
house
it's gonna it's gonna fall away not
really
yeah i guess i can give you one
game
when you have a house already
you have a house already
i don't know kiara senpai do you want to
like practice to get the 5 15 minutes
box
we can get the 15 minutes box together
but the thing is usually there might be
people and so you will you have to be
ready to like shoot people who wants to
get the box
it's usually at water treatment plan
there's usually guns inside
[Music]
um it's not it's not here yet but it
should be dropped in a bit by the
helicopter can you see the helicopter it
should be going to usually water
treatment plant
yeah we can team up and then get the
yeah get the loot
no i think i'll just take care of elena
for now
okay
okay then
it's okay i mean thank you
thank you
thank you thank you too
thank you have fun
[Music]
i missed on purpose just now
can i can i hit them
i'm sorry that was that was friendly
that was that was a sign of our
friendship
did that one hit just now
i was just testing stuffs with this
laser
i was just testing stuff with my with my
laser by the way
yeah that was that was a little friendly
friendly tap you know
nothing nothing much
more
[Music]
oh i think i hit oh no i think i hit
them because
because the red thread button
red button on upper upper right
i think that one i think the last one
the last one hit
yeah the last one was like a serious aim
[Music]
i'm sorry
it's okay think think of it as a you
know training
training in this in this harsh world
it's a training
you know friendship
friendship sign
i
at least i think she didn't die right
okay
i'm not really um because like matsuri
senpai actually invited me to her team
but i think she's not online right now
so in game
and game i'm like currently solo
i'm like currently solo right now
but matsuri senpai did invite me to her
team and there's also mikko senpai
inside
foreign
so
i also want to go to raid or something
are we ready for that
are we ready for like days i don't know
[Music]
me
i don't have a sniper with me
oh no
foreign
it's morning oh my god i'm gone
thank god
e4 is now on sale can buy it in muna
shop
i think it's not touched yet
[Music]
foreign
hey you know
wow must be nice
must be nice to be rich
i am bimbo
know
[Music]
foreign
i thought she was i thought she was
gonna recycle my ak
looks like that's
yoga i need to eat
can shoot the timer i know pekora senpai
literally showed the same thing to me
but like
so like that would be a waste of ammo's
like only have like one minute one extra
minute or something
but
okay
[Music]
i don't have any food with me i should
go home
or something
everyone shall be there either
um we are going to be collabing like
this week
it's going to be on zeta's channel by
the way
it's gonna be on zeta's channel we're
gonna be we're gonna be playing quarry
again
and we're gonna be continuing the game
i don't know i'm gonna hide over here
cuz
what is this oh
naruto
foreign
ouch
and have anything with me
i'm naked yes yes yes that's exactly
what i'm talking about
don't have anything with me i'm naked
i didn't shoot at anyone i didn't
on any animal today exactly
exactly
yes
mama
okay
nice
okay let's let's go home let's go back
home
we are friends
yes
military
foreign
all right
[Music]
recycled
military
[Music]
foreign
uh
nice
foreign
okay
tonight
it hasn't been 15 minutes
i need to get food
hydration we should be fine
hydration-wise
human meat
yum
okay
mean to
is
nice there you go there you go
i'm poor
um
foreign
[Music]
gun should be having fun now
i gave her a thompson
kinokos
hmm
[Music]
is
oh that's probably the shelf
what shop is this it only says it only
says a shop
it doesn't say who has
wrong
foreign
oh
i have nothing
foreign
hmm
oh
i'm gonna shelter here for a moment
oh it's gone
it's gone someone is here
[Music]
foreign
i'm gonna wait i'm gonna wait until it
goes away
yeah cause it's coming back
i knew it
i'm gonna wait
why is it suddenly so fast
foreign
i think someone should be nearby but i
don't know shall i wait here for like a
few minutes
yeah maybe i should wait here for a few
minutes like
just in case
yeah because the boxes are gone that
means that means someone someone should
be here until like a few minutes ago
maybe i should wait until like
night comes
hmm
is trading right now
so if anyone is
who is she raiding on npc
yeah she's raiding an npc place right
now
i'm gonna grab some water
while we wait
so
just gonna be watching from the window
that wouldn't be cool
um
if they are waiting for me they should
be waiting from over that direction
boom respawn
so
upper
and we should probably wait until
nighttime
yeah if someone is waiting for me they
they are probably waiting for me from
the
from the left direction
not from the right direction
you know
pinto
foreign
yeah hopefully hopefully they're
probably they probably think i i went
home already or something
but like the thing is i'm streaming
right now
i'm streaming right now so like
stream sniping is a thing
yes stream sniping is a thing you know
hello solo as in offline
yeah they're probably not going to
stream tonight because
it's against a little bit
just in case you know
nothing wrong to be safe like
i don't want i don't want to lose my
weapons again like the second time in a
day
like that's that's what i'm avoiding
right now
i lost my weapon my ak already like once
today
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna lose it the
second time you know
well the ak is fine but the insides
i also have a few stuffs inside you know
i have a i have a rival too with me like
a sniper i will do with me
hmm
yoga
um
more
be
i guess if you play long enough you know
like which sound is whose
you know
yeah every step is different
even the animals you know
i don't know i think i waited long
enough you know
i think if they're waiting for me they
shall be waiting at the left direction
so even if i stand here in the window at
the right direction
they're not gonna know
that was a person
i saw a person
was it pink
is
saw someone
so maybe they went back or something
i think they probably went back
anyways they're not coming here
they're not coming here so um i don't
know i'm gonna eat my kinokos
yoda
goodbye
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna go home and then
what it's just me or senpai as usual
it's just me or senpai
put it
oh man
come on
josiah
look at this
oh there you go
okay
all right we good
usually at night time like this there
will be there will be scientists
near my house but hopefully i didn't
change that one oh
i shouldn't be walking on the snow
yukiwa
foreign
all right
why you built the house in snow i didn't
build my house in snow
that actually sounds like that actually
sounds like a good idea though like
strategy wise
you know
i actually thought about filling my
house in the snow
but i did not
yeah it's very safe it's actually a good
idea
like i'll probably try that next season
or something
um
snowy house sounds pretty nice hello
zetta i know right
i know right
and that show it sounds nice
supermarket
[Music]
good
morning
good morning
at
[Music]
zetta do you want to raid military base
with me right now
if not then i'll i'll just go solo or
something
but i know
and oh i just looked off sorry haha it's
okay
so mommy
can i use umami
oh my god good morning
hey aqua boom recycle i haven't recycled
i need to go and recycle
you can borrow my umami all right
[Music]
i'll go inside
uh
nice so
nice okay
foreign
i actually didn't make a promise with
mummy to like i think we i think we
promised to go to
great subway
we made
foreign
is
museum
[Music]
foreign
here
okay
foreign
three
nice
mustache
storage
is
foreign
okay
um
nice
b
obviously
is
foreign
okay
nice and nice and nice
uh
what is everyone doing
[Music]
i'm gonna go to the village right now by
a village i mean um
somewhere
around this
like
this coordinate this direction
come on guys there's nothing wrong with
like
eating human meat you know
i'm doing this for survival
[Music]
there you go
nice and nice nice
what is
[Music]
people right now
foreign
yeah maybe let's let's not go to
let's not go to military base right now
and then maybe
on the next stream or something we can
do
we can do small oil rig
solo
oh it's fine
ah
uh
okay
nice
um
foreign
okay
[Music]
foreign
okay there's so many houses
over there
whose house is this again
um i'll see if they have
i don't know a sign or something
gotta be careful though
oh that looks so fancy
that rooftop actually looks so fancy
even the door looks so fancy
oh my god
he's got car dang
i didn't
all right
my
[Music]
foreign
what is that
[Music]
what
okay
a nice unit
i'm gonna take the box
hmm
nice
electric views
foreign
[Music]
no idea
be
i think
[Music]
zetta's house should be
brown
noble shop
house right now so let's go to zeta's
house
whose house is that again
i don't know
what way number
okay
[Music]
foreign
it's only the plane though
okay
is it dropped already because i don't
see the
i don't see the box
it's a shop
not welcome wow that is
what the hell do you even go up
what the heck
me
is
have a nice day
understandable
[Music]
foreign
um
is it like another house
oh it's
senpai's house
um
or is it
did she say
i don't know something eight
okay
was it k8
there's something eight so um
let's go
it
okay okay okay
nice
nice kinoko oh no this is the
bandit camp
is am i holding a weapon right now
i'm holding a weapon right now i don't
want to go to the safe zone
all right
[Music]
houses should be over there as well
um i don't know
i'm gonna do this just in case
oh whose house is that
that's also a shop
a shop is
i shall sell something too
foreign
i have a bunch of egg case maybe i
should like sell them or something
that's so fancy what the hell
that's so fancy yeah i have like a bunch
of eggs
and like i don't know sell them or
something
you know
around this
round somewhere here i don't know
if
i don't think people will go to my house
because like it's really far away
you know
my
foreign
[Music]
that is water treatment plant
um
supermarket
i'll take it
please don't kill me
foreign
house should be i think it was fk
have a
pouring twinkling
oh that looks so nice
so you say senpai
is that sweet senpai's house
i don't want to be too close to it
yeah i don't want to be too close to it
all
you know
foreign
this one i think
please don't break
i work long shifts
[Music]
tax you know
send by tax pay your senpai tax
um
[Music]
is this um
five
food
foreign
[Music]
um
that's cute
open
oh my gosh
foreign
[Music]
oh my
swimming god
what the heck
this is fancy
pool party
if you show me something as neat as this
i kind of want to rate it you know
open
uh
what's the purpose of that door how do
you even
i guess you can go up by opening
from this
but is
i'm stuck
never mind
okay
mama mama
ouch
all right whatever
is
[Music]
that one
this one i think
be
oh my god
out of stock
can award
[Music]
i don't know i should probably sell
animals for like the news you know
because
maybe maybe they take the box
they have the gun but they don't have
the ammos
yeah i can like sell ammo and stuff
i don't know
it kind of sounds like a good idea but
um
[Music]
in case
just in case you know
oh
you can just make
foreign
it's been a while it feels like it's
been a while since i went to bandit camp
m
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
okay
gang
too
foreign
[Music]
okay
nice
okay okay
[Music]
okay
yeah you know what it's like if you play
long enough
i guess you don't really need scraps
that like that much because
you already unlocked like a bunch of
stuffs from the from the workbenches
and like you already researched like a
lot of stuffs
so it's not like
you need them scraps anymore you know
yeah it's not like you need straps
anymore like even if i have a lot of
scraps i think i'm just gonna spend it
or like on like
helis or something cause
i already unlocked like most of the
important stuffs on oh my god
i already unlocked the important stuffs
on the
on the workbench you know
hmm
yeah helis and other stoves
the next one is going to be gny
[Music]
okay
okay okay
nice
let's go
some people are still playing i think
oh
oh my god
there we go
huh
like
nice
nice nice knife
speaking one for god's sake oh is that
not one
how is that not one
no
no what
like
[Music]
m
oh my god
baby steps you know
baby steps
foreign
probably probably the boars
but probably the boys i don't know
[Music]
one and three one and three come on
foreign
there you go
nice
santa
hi
foreign
well it's gone
[Music]
if i fail this one
i'm gonna go home
if i fail this one i'm gonna go home
god
nice
that's what i'm talking about
hmm
let's go
i don't know though
that's what i'm talking about
see
you guys see this
um
you know
[Music]
i thought that would be safe zone area
what the heck
should be over in a bit
[Music]
i'm the one who will die if i didn't
kill that boar you know
i mean i just i could go to save zone
but
delay
okay
be good
we good
i'm gonna leave the i'm gonna leave the
box now
i'll be taking that
we should be good
okay let's go
let's go home
huh
that was a private dude though
for my
okay
maybe later
foreign
okay okay
oh
damn it
goddammit
oh no
power plant
has like some radiation places
hopefully it's not gonna find me
okay we could
okay
man
why is it coming back
[Music]
foreign
there's also subway over here
how dangerous is like subway
like how bad can it be for like
people trying to do solo
how dangerous is it
you're like solo
[Music]
transportation
if you're terrible it's not too bad
what's with transportation like do you
like
drive something while shooting or wet
you like drive something while shooting
or wet
you can try to train like in half life
that sounds that sounds interesting
you can actually drive a train
i wonder if rain
i wonder if reyna wants to
rate the subway together with me like
now
you know
foreign
[Music]
but i think she's not feeling well today
so
let's save that for another day
she's not really feeling well today
foreign
[Music]
is she like building a house over there
hmm
i don't see anything nearby
you know
this gun with the scope is like insane
see
see how far i can look
it's like insane
can we shoot that battle
does this does this window have like
i don't know glasses
um
hey
rooftop
if there's people coming anyway
there's people coming
you know
okay
you know sometimes it falls on the power
plant
nice
i think we can end the stream today
and we can end the game here for today
this week i kind of want to try doing um
a small oil
small oil rig like solo
[Music]
is
which means i can finally post my
schedule
i'll i'll let you guys know maybe maybe
tomorrow
uh
schedule you go to
go fix some logitech
and then next next dress we can probably
try like trading small oil rig
both
[Music]
rival is dang
this rival is godly
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna do that on the
next last stream
mano
[Music]
now just reload
it can go up until up until five animals
unlike the the the other one with like
only four amps
up
all right i think that's all for the
game today thank you so much everyone
for coming thank you so much and i shall
probably i should probably change the
title cause
i should probably just change the title
because in the end i ended up doing my
own thing
yeah i'll change the title
anna
and you click bait scalia title here
[Music]
thank you so much everyone for today
i'll be reading super chats and
donations after this
thank you so much everyone for coming
have a good day have a good night also
great students for leaving thank you and
see you guys in a minute for some sushi
and donation trading
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
hello
um
i'm back
hello hello hello
okay let's get the super chat
[Music]
all right let's go let's go let's go
foreign
[Music]
me
okay um let's train cells
is the best full life costume i have
ever seen pedestrians
for minor criticism what about goggles
make anya look like she's ready for
anything your streams are always the
highlight of my week thank you so much i
didn't think about all those but
um unfortunately you can't have that
many accessories like i have
i have a lot of stuff in my costumes
already
so like for now for now this should be
some
kind of thing
thank you so much for the super chat
super chat thank you
thank you so much for the spa
nissan
v get well soon thank you i'm actually
okay though i'm actually okay just
decide
thank god for that
thank god i can still talk like usually
thank you so
much yeah sometimes it's like
anything else is fine beside for your
throat
sometimes it's kind of like those things
but for for like hell i'm actually
pretty healthy
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
i know right
thank you so much
[Music]
um
unless i guess you can call me if she
wants to like learn about
the more pvp side of the of the game
yeah i don't know how far is senpai into
the game but if she wants to learn about
the
more of the pvp stuff and also npc i
guess you can come to me anytime
yeah thank you so much
but
i'm supposedly from what she said about
about not not wanting to loot the boxes
i don't know though yeah i was like hey
let's put the boxes
[Music]
foreign
underwater lab
is it like a heart npc place i don't
know can you can you even throw that
thank you so much for the super chat
thank you i do want to solo the oil rig
next time though
thank you so much for the subscribe
thank you
thank you god thank you so much for the
super chat thank you
hmm
[Music]
foreign
all right
muhammad
japanese like a native
i i don't know man
i don't know you just you just talk and
play i guess
thank you so much for the super chance
okay thank you
let's go to steam labs
i don't know though
i might be wrong but i feel like yara's
empire doesn't really want to like
actively engage like the pvp staff
now i might i might be wrong
let's go to the nation
[Music]
thank you so much thank you so much and
have fun if you're watching the aircraft
have fun
thank you
thank you donation thank you
[Music]
thank you for coming to my petals
foreign
[Music]
thank you
donation thank you
so my friend recommend me to watch you
he said you're the cutest and funniest
expert
oh my god thank you
what if i sell my ak
will people be interested in my egg
place
they're my babies still my aks are my
babies
my aks are my babies i kind of don't
want
even though i think i don't i don't need
this much i i don't need this much of
egg like until the end of the end of the
season
[Music]
at the same
time i don't know but then again then
again i always i always bring ak with me
so if i get killed and my ak got stolen
like just like yesterday like what
happened today
yeah at least i got like i got like
replacement but then again i can i
should be able to like
i should be able to make something
i should be able to like
make a case because i unlocked it at the
workbench already
anyways thank you so much
was surprised that you decided to stream
instead glad to see you today cheers
thank you
thank you so much for coming yeah
i'm really really started the game so i
was like hey okay and she was like she
needed help and i was like okay cool
let's go
yeah
and so i decided to stream today
thank you so much for the donation
donation you
foreign
okay
um let's see
check laggy super shot done i see
thank you
all right
i think that's all for the super shots
and donations
i'll probably i'll probably try soloing
um
a small oil rig or something next time
so that the next stream we can finally
have something to happen you know
it's like farming all the time is
probably not that in the game
it's not that exciting though i also
want some excitement
i do want some excitement and so i will
i will go
to an adventure to seek excitement
thank you so much everyone for coming
[Music]
and i think that's all for today
that's all for today tomorrow tomorrow i
will see if if my clothes gets better
then there might be
[Music]
um
i think
we should i shall be good enough so
yeah we will see
thank you so much everyone for coming
and this has been on your mouth signing
out
thank you so much everyone and see you
guys on the next stream bye bye
bye
everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
you