[Music]
me
be
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
me
[Music]
be
uh
[Music]
um
the
[Music]
me
uh
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
good morning
i have something new thank you
[Music]
take away this butter knife
all i need is a fairy nah i won't even
need the ferry
[Music]
um i love this music so much
i'm gonna miss it
on your home
i wish we could play this game forever
[Music]
okay so i have this fairy
we shall use it if necessary
that's fairy ha ha
[Music]
it's always wild princess yeah
i don't mind playing twilight princess
at some point so this year
um
i'll miss this game me too
yeah
in the jar yeah of course the jar
where else would the fairy be
[Music]
i'm done with the i've never done
it with the funny
i don't i didn't even start
[Music]
today we will play until the end which
kanashina i am very sad
oh so sad
things you don't know the meme of course
i know the meme
i played the game right there dunny with
the bunny
[Music]
i'm currently in bomb island
oh last time we played i was kind of
sick but it still went well although if
i remember correctly right after the
stream i
completely
died which is fine because i'm a phoenix
i killed
two flies yesterday
after the stream successfully
fat
disgusting
one i smacked of some object
uh on the ground
now first on like some
some box and then it didn't quite hit it
so then it
like it
tried to fly away but it seems to have
like lost its sense of direction so it
just like turned in circles and then
landed on the ground and then i smacked
it real good and then i was kind of
disgusted because
that fat fly
lost quite a bit of blood when i
when i smacked it
incredible
yeah
[Music]
froggy i really need a frog and then
just let the frog roam around
freely
[Music]
that's a good way to segment into the
beginning
what is our current
job uh
ah we have we have all the what is it
the dream or do we have all of the
fry forest
[Music]
wait where do i see that again i here
yeah whoa
whoa i did some good homework last time
i can't believe it
that place over there
why is there still
a stone like that does it like regrow
when you once get rid of it
then you have things you wanted to leave
for before the last dungeon oh perhaps
i'll ask you in a second missing hearts
yeah i don't know if i'll get all of
them but
they do oh okay
um so what did i want to do
godzilla's list no i don't have it
it was a list
i guess it was the level 20 necklace is
a rich old man on windfall is a side
quest every time there's a cute and
funny cycle okay windfall
20 necklaces we have 20 necklaces right
uh which necklaces not the butterfly
ones right which ones wipes tomato
i have 15 skull
necklaces that's not 20.
oh
uh where where can i farm 15 uh five
more skull necklaces
where should i go why why do what who
which enemy do they come from again
oh correct 15 years now 20. moblins
uh
the fortress
fortress
but if i go to the fortress now won't it
trigger gadondor
oh no
maybe not
buckle bubbling go back to the sunset
island dungeon
[Music]
aha only in hyrule okay
um
yeah there was a dungeon where you just
fight a bunch of enemies yeah we already
went there and survived pretty long even
though i was there way too early
uh
[Music]
hello korean viewers
and konnichiwa konbanwa to my japanese
viewers
hello slop this is so pretty um
ah i can't decide
youtube
um
how do i make a song again here there
you go
uh how do i
how do i teleport a lot of girls
[Music]
i have conducted a lot of games
oh
[Music]
where do i
go caught night joe
where am i going
top left
thank you
[Music]
so we're going to
the
first
um scary place
brazil no no no
no although brazil right now
is
oh
hi fairies supposedly like something
like winter wait how do i leave from
here again ah
you may look sick
uh
i uh going to say brazil was like winter
time now which is still warm but at
least it's not summertime wow
hi baby
no
oh yeah yeah yeah enjoy enjoy the ground
that is
filled with
all kinds of presents
kitty cat
huh can't i'm a kitty cat and i mean i
don't know how to leave this place
anymore wasn't there something with the
like with getting to the
i top to warp out
huh
there's only
what
i'm gonna teleport out
ah
i have to get into the boat oh god damn
it
do you have an empty bottle right now no
shanna
you're currently
oh
oh god
uh
i have
two fairies and one soup so no need for
anything else
why did you tell me to come here
[Music]
why don't you tell me to go here
i did not count the one i have in my
hand
uh
i can buy the fairy
fair fairy
i don't need another fairy
well you need another one
ganondorf will be a piece of cake
why am i
what if i warp here am i landing outside
[Music]
i hate this place
sorry was it you
wasn't you
is this i buy the last uh bottle perhaps
because i'm here so i might as well buy
it but i don't need it
no i don't need it
okay we are going this way
i'll take the fall
that is very very brave of you
[Music]
a donkey
is so sweet
all night she was i mean it's always
like this but all night she was sleeping
all night
i was awake most of the night
she was sleeping on the fat letters that
i had laying on my bed
uh she slept on them
instead of her usual place the box
because whenever there's something
like on the ground or
on the bench or so like for example my
laptop sometimes i have my old laptop
on the
on the on the band
and she would like
lie down on the laptop but now there
were lettuce so she lied down on the
lettuce
right next to me curled up so sweet
and i don't know about the second
fastest in general maybe the
maybe the second fastest in hollow i
don't know but yeah kobo is doing really
well
pretty impressive
i'm happy for her proud of her
uh
definitely we've been like
indonesia she was a great pig
great pig
i'm looking for the fish here
because i still don't have this piece
of the map oh oh
can't see the face
[Music]
yeah yeah i was thinking like
call me crazy oh there he is
call me crazy but
looking at
oh god oh god
[Music]
oh my god
it's so far away what the man
um i was thinking quite a while ago
already
uh
[Laughter]
how
you know
most viewed in whole live english
is the blue girl
most viewed in whole life japan is the
blue usada peculiar and most viewed in
a whole live indonesia is the blue
kobold
and i've noticed a pattern and i think
i've been thinking
that
you know since our audience is
let's be real
mostly
um male now that's just the truth
and that's fine
i was thinking you know a color like
blue is just
um
it speaks
it speaks to you guys
uh more than like a color like pink
now obviously that's not the only factor
but i feel like it's
subconsciously
easy on your eyes
and will
um give you
guys a better um feeling when watching
than some super super pink
cutesy
design
with yeah i don't know lots of whatever
okay that's just my theory
plus of course
other factors like being funny and
personality and all that but i don't
think it's a coincidence that all the
popular ones are blue
i don't think it's a coincidence
and maybe they're also kind of all
i don't know
i mean they have like maybe some sort of
similarities and
some small
similarities in
personality i wouldn't say they're all
kusogaki
i mean maybe hey maybe
maybe
no crony is dark blue i'm talking
actually specifically about light blue i
think light blue has this
subconscious effect on everybody though
light blue is just such a
such a color that
everybody would like
it speaks to everybody
but she's also not dark blue like crony
um she's like maybe like an in-between
no her hair you know how her hair is
like mostly white and then the blue tips
and all that it's it it gives her a
brighter image than
the dark blue of crony or whatever but
crony is still blue
and that might just be why she's also
doing so
in council i'm just i'm bullshitting you
now
but i mean
i mean
[Applause]
[Music]
i i really and do you guys
no it's not it's obviously not like a
recipe for success to be blue
not an automatic success recipe
that's why not everyone who is blue is
uh has 5 million subscribers
but i'm just saying i think it adds uh
positively
you're not totally wrong thank you who
agrees
[Music]
yeah it doesn't come just from that
obviously
there's more
than that to that have i been here
before
i don't remember like ever
making this go kaboom
of course i hear you
yeah i think you know because colors do
have um all kinds of subconscious
effects on people
you know how like
red and yellow
and and green like depending on what
it's such a psychological thing but
depending on what color you paint like
um a dentist lobby or
i know a hospital wall whatever
it can calm you down
or it can make you aggressive
a little bit without noticing it
yes but actually no
no no no no no yes
[Music]
yeah
the whole life logo is light blue and
you know why
i mean it's not like i've asked yahoo or
anything
but i'm just saying
it's a good choice
because
because how do you put it down again
there you go because it's such a good
color
such a good color
nani
huh is this look to plant trees or
oh the weather is terrible
why why what is this place
what do you mean i'm becoming
increasingly unhinged
i'm just saying the truth and you can't
take it oh no
oh no
okay practice uh fighting because we
haven't done this in a while what the
hell are they coming in listening
next afternoon we blew
up
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't stop running
oh they're leaving
what
why did they come in the first place
hmm
ah that episode of scrubs i mean not
recently but yes i've watched it before
and i think it only proves my theory
what is this
of course people stay for the
personality but it still gives you i
think a good feeling watching someone
who's blue
it's just a good a good color
huh
i hate them
[Music]
come on
it feels like nothing's happening
hello
is this another like arena kind of place
[Music]
wow
so i'm just talking to my cat
yesterday you know i fell asleep early
again but then i woke up at like 3 30 or
something
and i wanted to continue sleeping so i
got up and i i i
turned off the lights and all that
because it was still
it was still on
and that
woke me up unfortunately
kind of because then i was i started to
think about a lot of things again
and then i was wide awake and i couldn't
couldn't fall asleep again until
what was that
until like
six or seven a.m
yeah so i slept until right before the
stream kind of
it's it's a it's a meow wow it's a
wonder that i'm actually here
on time relatively meow baby chunky
monkey
hmm
a big oof
beautiful meows today donkey monkey
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god i didn't even
try to get that wait a second my chunky
wonky wants some belly rubs
once i move too much she runs away that
little no oh no she she ran out of
the room and then now she's peeking into
the room again and walking into the room
again she wants something from me i
think she wants a snack or something you
got food though
you confuse me baby
no no baby i know
i don't know i don't know what you want
from me
i don't know
i don't know oh fanny wraps
oh don't run away
i'll give you belly rubs
oh
yeah who wants betty whips you on belly
whips
[Music]
hmm
capture the cat
oh
sorry for the cat intermission
[Music]
cute kitty cat who's a cute kitty cat
chunky wonky is a cute kitty cat
no i do think ganon
might
if he sees my cute kitty cat
i think he might reconsider being evil
i think he might want to stop being evil
and turn to the bright side
always look on the bright side of life
you know i'm dancing with my cat right
now right moving her paws
unleash the
bright side of life
[Music]
ah she has such soft paws
cats reforming most of evil hearts yes
life of brian
wait what's that movie i don't think i
know it
[Music]
i don't think i know that movie life of
brighton
although the title scene seems
well kind of familiar you want to leave
i'm singing it
i just know the song
from like
eh
i don't know
but just it's just one of those songs
that you just kind of know
what are you doing link
oh okay i'll let you go chunky wonky but
you'll have to let mama work now okay
[Music]
and she wants attention oh
i feel so sorry
i feel so sorry but you know what chunky
wonky who knows maybe the stream won't
be too long
i could already go kill ganon now if i
wanted to
so i got a piece of heart
by coincidence
oh the waves are
huge here
okay
opposite direction this way
we now have
16 of those skulls
[Music]
second time they got me green miles
whale their white alert wilder thank you
rainbow oh my god it's rainbow time baby
oh
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'll be reading that during the super
chat rating i think
[Music]
oh my god
sided rainbow
thank you
wow
thank you so much that's so generous i
appreciate it thank you
what was i saying though i forgot oh
yeah we need four more necklaces
[Music]
hi fish
i hope we get them are they from the big
ones right not from the small ones or is
it the other way around do the big ones
drop the
uh
butterfly ones
the big ones okay
big ones
[Music]
is there grass growing here
it's us where are the enemies
let's go maybe inside here
[Music]
if i can
they're not here anymore
[Music]
where else am i gonna
fight them
[Music]
where else am i supposed to go get them
cause ganondorf is not here
i can still find the piece of heart and
trust him
what which one
where
now that it's i guess abandoned it might
be even easier to find it under the sea
ah in the high road empire yeah where we
made them like stop
in time
[Music]
okay
i guess we'll have to do that and then
leave first before going to ganondorf
directly
where do i go for this
treasure chest
yeah this shall be my fort then
[Music]
first because i don't want to live with
all these bats
[Music]
well there's a chest there
hey go down here oh okay
all right
hello
[Music]
oh i accidentally wandered into
the right area
[Music]
what am i fighting
don't go
[Music]
it was carrying the heart
that's funny oh can i enter
how do i enter this
is a key
[Music]
oh
wait i do have fire arrows maybe
what the
[Music]
oh it doesn't look like what
not the torch move the bears what the
so misleading i thought you guys
all are giving me good advice but so far
today you guys have been pretty bad at
giving me advice
oh my god
comment
oh it's that easy
[Music]
how much more do i need
or a full one
ah i need oh i just got a new one i need
three more
okay i'm out of here
bye bye oh
how do i get out of here where's this
door
interesting you run around here without
being super stressed about being
found out about
we apologize that the backseat service
today isn't up to par would you like to
upgrade to baxi plus for higher quality
yes please
i'm great please and i expect it to be
free of charge because
um otherwise i'll turn into a karen
because so far you've been very
misleading and wasting my
time yeah i think i deserve it
okay so
high rule
where is hyrule
where is harwood in the middle right
somewhere in the middle
is it though
how do you get there again
power of the gods can i fly there
[Music]
here we go
hyrule is
not hidden very well these days
but i guess it used to be even less
hidden so
why are we so slow
oh there we go
oh the game thinks i'm coming here for
ganon now
oh
uh
what
oh
my effects are not working
okay well then without effects well done
quinoa you must show the drivers piece
you have assembled to the gods
there it is your gun's right so you can
see it like wherever i am
now my um go xlr didn't reset properly
when i restarted the pc
oopsie
whoa
oh what is this there on your hand the
driver's piece now dwells within you
it is the triforce of courage prove that
you are indeed a true hero
you've controlled the wind and crossed
the seas
and here near the end of your quest the
power of gods has been bestowed upon you
surely from this moment on you shall be
known as the hero of winds
wind waker
go forth
try rude until the side
[Music]
nice music oh
that's a new one
they let me out though right when i need
to go out
i hope
they will let me out i hope
maybe
so useful today
i'll be able to leave later what do you
mean later
whenever okay whenever wherever we need
to be together i'll be there and you'll
be here and that's the deal my dear
by the way
um
where the are the enemies here
they're nowhere to be found
where the ma where was the mustard in
there in the tomb
[Music]
um
okay um i was gonna say i have
been
feeling
undermined
what's the right word i feel
i'm not happy about
how
my butt has been treated these days
so
i checked out
[Music]
there she is
[Laughter]
today this morning i took a close look
at my model
on my 3d model this morning right before
the stream i mean it's not really
morning time
um
and it looks like that thing that i said
wasn't my butt crack but looks kind of
like my butt crack in that screenshot
may have actually been my butt crack
that is my verdict which means my ass is
just placed differently but still
pretty much there
yeah when i took a close look at it it
really looks like it
youtube is silencing me what the
people seem to be able to watch it
though mostly
sounds like a coke no i can show you
it looks so much like it
oh
was it a phantom
like in the phantom game
i need my effects
maybe if i uh
sheesh
is is it a bad idea to like
[Music]
hmm
wow
[Music]
um
wow
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
me
so
[Music]
ah
can you hear me
let me just get my body back give me my
body back body back body bug money
actually i need to go to an island
meeting anyway maybe
oh god
i'll go
in a second let me just
bring my body back body bug buddy back
to my hair
[Music]
sorry um
i have deceived myself
i tried you know um
uh closing the go xlr process and all
that manually
and then
i tried like unplugging
plugging back in etc
but it didn't it didn't do the trick i i
know i've had this before like i need to
restart it once something is wrong with
it i need to restart the pc
for it to properly restart everything
else
[Music]
none
this is what i'm scared of when like
are we back okay okay okay uh then
while we're at it may i take a quick
idle break
uh hopefully
the stream is
running well while i'm gone
okay
yeah wait i'll turn on the do you guys
hear the game sound though because i
think i'll need to fix it for myself
again
um
[Music]
i need to open the game capture
i think there's a delay
delay
of oh you mean
ah
it's not too big of a problem right
okay brb
[Music]
me
wow
[Music]
is everything alive
uh
ah
we back again wait what happened what
what is my chat
what
hello hello hello
my chat is just not up to date
let me go grab
hyper chat
has
has youtube
been taking days off again while i was
gone
um
rachel
hyperchad
stream was fine okay
[Laughter]
you may or may not call this the wind
waker we can curse yeah yeah
it's okay
so i i have apparently indeed deceived
myself i wanted to get out my voice
this is this is gone on right
it's probably gone
yeah
you have to save yourself
did you think you'd be safe inside the
castle
foolish put your foolish ambitions to
rest
now that my power has been restored
there was no safe haven for you
always foolish i have taken your
precious seldom
[Music]
are we like already getting into it i
had other plans man
good start good start
i won't give me that oh there we go
[Music]
what are you doing
looking for your weapon huh
i'm doing pretty bad yeah
oh i got my sword
[Music]
undressed up yes got naked
no need to panic
[Music]
i never had so much trouble with these
bastards before just kill this one
go get him
he's still alive
[Music]
the what the i can't turn
around
[Music]
yeah okay finally is he down yeah
okay
okay got the important stuff now fight
here
one down
[Applause]
[Music]
he's
is easy
epic fight no not not quite but
i think i needed a moment to get back
into the game now here we are
what's this oh yeah that's why i'm where
i got my sword huh
okay
are we leaving this place no
going outside
what awaits me
i'm supposed to go outside right like
out here lagging like crazy really
i mean the stream is off and keeps
popping up randomly
[Music]
is it for everybody or
whatever
this is for everybody final mai and not
for me okay okay then it might just be
like a regional thing
wow why did it teleport me to that one
door
some lag but it's fine okay
why does the game want me to go
uncle in australia all good in germany
okay okay
[Music]
the bridge the way link ran i was a sign
that the
the thing is gone now
not that it's still there oh it looks
like it was still there to me
okay now there we go
they removed it
nintendo 64.
world let's go
oh
why did it want me to go here
[Music]
what
you guys still helping me with the
obvious things huh
intimidating
oh wait i'm breaking it it's a good
thing
that was easy
oh all those glass shards
this is the point of no return
oh
i really wanted to
go get the necklaces though
if you break it you buy it
no not yet okay
oh i don't remember this at all that you
are actually able to leave and like go
through here
it comes university
ah wait boomerang boomerang boomerang
boomerang where are my items
[Music]
at least this one i remembered
um i still can't find any necklaces
though i hope we've kept them before the
no point return what
[Laughter]
no point
[Music]
wrong back seating advice
thank you thank you
yeah i mean
in any case if you haven't ever played
this game before you should play it
because
it's my favorite zelda game
okay
yeah there's no point in returning
[Music]
come on come on come on come on
yeah
or maybe i just haven't fought that many
[Music]
come on one more one
ah
use the uh grapple guaranteed necklace
oh well i've just been really lucky so
far the grapple this one
or this one the first one right this one
that's the grapple
three more or is it three more
two more two more i have 18 now
uh
uh but there are no if i if i re-enter
this area they should be there again
or do they not refresh respawn
they do okay let's see
[Music]
there's more inside the dungeon
and it would be nice to get them before
like going too deep you know
until i'll leave the area probably just
go for it yeah okay
let's see
speed run stretch
are they back
butter smashing
ah they are back
what do i get if i use that on them
the feathers
[Music]
can i do it again
very cruel but
nice
best ones okay well that makes sense
[Music]
i'm finally using my tools that have
been given to me
[Music]
oh by the way today is sunday and i want
to start uploading the
um countdown videos but
uh
emma didn't send me them yet i recorded
them at her place in
3d and she kind of forgot to send them
to me and now she can't
reach them
so we'll see
she said she'll try to get to them
somehow
i hope
i hope i can get them ribbon today
i have to go back to america
on y'all
[Music]
nice
what the just happened behind me
don't you dare kill each other
[Music]
huh did i get it
i think i got them all
[Music]
nice cool
action
[Music]
let me check i think i got them i think
i heard the sound
[Music]
twice so yeah that's funny
upload the one on the final yeah but it
says i i said
uh
three more days and then i said two more
days and i said one more day but i was
planning on re-recording the audio for
one of them anyway i could in theory i
guess re-record the audio for all of
them and then be like two more days one
more day zero more days
but zero more days is like
what
zero who needs a countdown that says
zero more days it just doesn't sound
right
today oh i guess today okay today
ah i don't know
i don't know
it was gonna be on both twitter and
youtube we'll see you'll see if i got
the move in today then no problem
we'll see
dawn of the final day
24 hours remain
before the moon
lands on the earth and destroys
everything
today
tomorrow
okay
uh
i'm bringing them to
which island windfall island or what was
it again
[Music]
oh
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
where's my island again
trying to drag this out as long as
possible
majora's mask um
i don't think i've ever played it myself
maybe when i was really young and i just
don't remember but i feel like it was
always too scary for me anyway just like
um
just like
[Music]
twilight princess so if anything i
this guy knew i only watched
um
somebody else play it like even my
brother or
some
let's player
huh is this guy new yeah he's new right
oh and who are you really why'd you look
at this strange film that we've met
before what's you the little boy who
promises big brother sister that fails
to deliver hey
[Music]
too bad you couldn't save my daughter
fortunately not everyone in this world
fails to deliver
oh
wow this little this big
as it turns out my new meela was saved
by a group of kind pirates ahoy
pirates are the leader tetra i believe
she said her name was
uh i was most grateful
she did demand the rubber heavy where
now you go
my fortune has vanished oh wait are you
the rich guy
he's the rich guy
what
oh
he's still a piece of you would
think that someone an who's rich
would become nicer once he's
you know
been stripped of his money
but at least the last sentence was on
point
[Music]
donna is worth more than money or
something like that
so
who needs the
skull
[Music]
burrito necklaces why do you want ah
you're the guy who keeps on bringing the
love letters
[Music]
joy pedestals
it's part of this grand plan to help
decorate the town anyway they're
brilliant i may as well tell you that
both myself in china
[Music]
the other old guy
meanwhile enjoy
this beautiful music of windfall island
hello
[Music]
have you ever played miniature the one
where the link has ah
uh miniature cap or stuff like that i
watched a play for a little bit
i'll play through yeah
i watched basically a playthrough of
every freaking zelda game even all the
ds games
because like there's this one let's
player who
who's zelda play throughs i enjoy
in particular
[Music]
because like he also does like kind of
like voice acting and all that when yeah
when he reads the the
messages you know the scripts
yeah and i always thought like that's so
entertaining like so much more
entertaining no don't tend though
so much more entertaining i'm close to
it
so much more entertaining than like
other people who just
read everything normally
which definitely influenced me to
like when i play stuff to
do my own voices
i can't find the do
no app
no i'm saying no don't go up oh he's
saying no yes go up
maybe here
it enhances it
no up
where the rich guy used to live
oh there's a lady
what
bunny ears
yes you have bunny ears
oh
don't think that i would survive my
ordeal and return to this town and to
think that i would ever be able to live
in such a beautiful opulent house it's
like a dream come true
but no no it's a nightmare without him
by my side it's like a rainstorm rages
in my heart it was so kind to me in the
forsaken fortress that sweet boy who
gave me all those expensive necklaces
when i fled from the cursed island
just hearing his name lifts my spirits
that wonderful moblin from the forsaken
fortress oh my
i'm always writing heartfelt letters
filled with my overflowing emotions but
why don't you answer me more
[Music]
who's talking
hey who's talking
this is bad or terribly bad i've already
drifted off into my own dream world oh
it's her
oh by the way i have a request for you
could you take the letter i've just
finished inking and delivered to the
post box for me
please i beg of you
what really you're such a dear you've
made maddie so happy
is it too moed
oh it's so cute it looks like a letter
that pekora would write
[Music]
she's down bad for an orc
orc yeah or mo moblin yes
so nice i'm so nice pickle
but you know it's cute she loves like
this is like the beauty and the beast
although i mean she's not much of a
beauty herself but
you know what i mean
[Music]
what did i say huh it's just the truth
i speak the truth that's why people hate
me
because i speak the truth people are
scared of me
but all i do is speak the truth
all i do is speak the truth
[Music]
don't you dare forget but you must
probably must promise not to read it the
secrets of a girl's heart are to be
shared only when she still desires
so you're telling me to read it
what about this guy this is the one that
needs the necklaces
you don't look like someone who wants
skull business
oh you're just some red straight urchin
i thought you were the
postman thankful because if you were the
postman i would have showed you out of
here because before you could say
well say you look rather familiar for a
street urchin have we perhaps met before
someplace
[Music]
outside
read me outside how about that
yeah that's i i suppose that's him but
let me write the letter first
[Music]
oh can i read it when i'm at the mailbox
okay
where did he go okay so
you don't meet my daughter do you
because my daughter has already been
rescued from the forsaken fortress
why she even returned with a huge load
of lovely glittering delicious treasure
thanks to her little incident we've
become filthy rich overnight i mean
filthy
why there isn't a girl in the world
who's such a good child as my maggie
you may not have been able to help me
but there is no harm done i'm sure
you'll accomplish something in life
someday
look at my hand i've got the
triforce
in the meanwhile my daughter has
blossomed into quite a little beauty run
along go spend some time with her
[Music]
oh thank you
you want this
is one of those skull necklaces that my
daughter maggie brought back from the
forsaken fortress
they sell quite well at antique shops in
fact it was thanks to these beauties
overnight i became so filthy rich
overnight oh i read that twice
and for the looks of it i'd say you have
about 20 of these
[Laughter]
yes i have
exactly 20 even though i'm just showing
you one and my inventory is invisible
you still seem to see it
they aren't easy to come by either
frankly i'm amazed you found so many it
took me a whole playthrough
oh
i'll be bathing in money yet to get who
said i'll give it to you the money path
the only bathroom gets you filthy filthy
rich
all right boy i'll give you this as a
tip now i'm not thanking you or anything
i'm just feeling good today
treasure chest
okay
i was once quite poor myself you know
back then i used to dream of loading a
boat a boat i could use to go off in
search of treasure and now look at my
favorite stuff
shut up man
and
i wonder what the reward will be
[Music]
we'll go look it up in a moment let's
just bring the letter to the post box
no fear rich he says filthy rich
[Music]
hopefully a piece of heart
good morning
here there you go
there's post boxes near the mail center
on dragon roost island posted i have to
pay postage okay
[Music]
you process hey why would you accept it
for delivery thank you for using the
other postal service what now
i didn't read it
i don't get to read it
come back in a bit
okay let's go look for the treasure
okay
[Music]
that i can't oh
that is what you are
how do i know
which treasure chart does this because i
have like a million ones
and i don't know which one it is
do you guys know the number
though
number two
okay thank you
okay
uh
[Music]
ah okay
okay
that is correct i know it's surprising
for once
[Music]
foreign
something i wanted to talk about i'm
trying to remember
[Music]
i have yet to unpack my suitcase
although i didn't i did take out all the
clothes
to wash them
at least something
where's this treasure
does it have to be night time to see it
properly
[Applause]
of course yeah
but
i mean
i'm by far not the only one who takes
days ah there it is to unpack
their suitcase
oh
[Music]
always takes at most two weeks yeah yeah
if not a month yeah unless like if i
have to go somewhere else
before
those two weeks or three weeks
then i'll
repack
would earlier
nice to get two more before going to
ganon
okay now i go back to windfall
[Music]
took me a moment for the committee too
because i'm talking myself i still
haven't unpacked that
[Music]
lego quest gives me one nice okay then i
just need one more
[Music]
oh
what is this island
i don't remember this place
was that dude
what is this island
cute bridge
what the
the beetle shop in that square had a
special shop
really
i'm looking at the chat
dude
i never talked to him it's a mini game
can i get a heart piece
[Laughter]
wow need to talk to him from the front
oh never mind my mistake uh yeah yeah
step right up
if you have confidence in your target
shooting why don't you give this a shot
50 rupees per game
all right
all right so you're the little shrimp
fixes the target shooting yeah and
you say there's no full well that we are
pirates who are so frightening to cry
babies shut their mouths when we step
into the room huh this should be before
you find that hot shot
if you can manage to sing to fight
pirate ships you see off on the horizon
we'll acknowledge your skills in the
cannon you shrimp your landlubber
however we won't tolerate any comments
about how the pirate ships look like
barrels and you get only 10 shots to
hurt me
you can move you can reveal and fire
travail watch the water blooms carefully
when you fire yeah
you gotta shrimp
if you manage to sink all five five
pirate ships we'll give you all the
treasure we stole it up until now good
luck to you shrimp you leave it here
what what am i
shooting i don't know how hard to shoot
[Music]
if i want to win now then i have one
more miss
but yeah that's not i'm not gonna
not gonna be able to make it
[Music]
but these ones i think a little bit
further away
right i had to figure it out first you
know
[Music]
ah so far away
oh
what if i hit the fish
this one is a little bit closer
yeah but i'm not gonna make it because
i'll have to experiment with the last
one
ah
i don't know
i'm gonna miss it
ah so close eh
not bad for the first time
yeah not bad at all
it's 50 rupees per game want to try
again
all right
i'm not going to listen to you again
you're further away yeah oh
helmet
it's so far away
oh close baby
come on
okay now this one looks a little bit
closer a little bit
[Music]
and this one looks maybe also a tiny bit
closer
maybe like this
maybe not maybe it wasn't the same
height
huh holy though
no this is much closer
uh i have to first get a feeling for it
again but we're easily making this one
okay way too way too far
i just did it so roughly
i went down so roughly with that okay
now this one i'm not sure now i have
nothing left to compare i'm not sure if
this is closer or further away
i think it's a bit further away
maybe
[Music]
oh my god
[Laughter]
pro gamer let's go pirate queen i'm a
lady pirate queen lady kiara
lady pirate queen kiana
let's go
beautiful shots thank you thank you
well that was some impressive aim i know
thank
[Music]
you there's a second big prize oh okay
easy easy let's do it i'm having fun
with this
huh
this tetra
gonzo you're at least an honorary member
of my family are you not
so act like hey don't lose your head
you're a talented little kid i like you
as we promised here's our treasure it's
yours to take it
piece of heart
yeah he wants me to leave and only being
a ladder behind you will climb down in
an orderly manner if you please
but i heard you've got more to offer
it really
this is still 50 rupees though
does he really have more to offer i mean
i got the money
[Music]
huh
do i have to
do it with no mistakes
[Music]
oh do i just have to do the same thing
again basically
[Music]
i don't know
how am i even able to do this now this
one i'll oh up
so far
i'm using auto aim
might be
okay that was quite far further away
quite a bit
ah even more
what
that's really far
sorry now i'm up everything
[Applause]
that's maximum oh this is
maximum 50 50 degrees is maximum
the other ones are closer though
wow okay
oof
so you maybe
around here
49 what these are all so far away
and this one
i'll say 47.
yeah baby now it actually looks
about the same
i have two more tries
so
yeah okay 48.
well now you're gonna eight
forty-nine
nine nine nine nine
[Music]
the first shot though like because in
the first shot you have to first figure
out like
where the hell you are you know now this
one is freaking close
[Music]
that might even be too far
oh
holy
lucky strike
[Music]
i love my run five
so this once again i don't know
it's hard to tell with this one because
if you go from the very left to the very
right
yeah it's kind of confusing misleading
i'll stay we'll test it we'll
test the waters literally
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
baby this one might be
maximum again i'm not sure
[Music]
well i have so many shots to miss how
about we try with
46 first but it might be maximum
[Music]
my first intention was correct
oh my god
what do you want don't you know how to
keep quiet your scurvy dog uh i was just
wondering who was out there and look at
this it's you again look at you and then
adobe cute face of your eyes i can't
help but give away our treasure to you
it's yours to take it
[Music]
doping suspicion
it's it's the the cat fur that i've
inhaled
you're going to be on the ladder
off now okay bye-bye
that was close it was fun
that was fun i like this mini game
yeah do you guys know which treasure
chart that is
it's hard to tell cause there's a couple
that i just haven't used yet
hmm you guys know
oh
17 really did you look it up
it's just rupees i guess i don't really
need rupees huh
is it close if it's close
if it's close i'll check it out let me
see
[Music]
do i even have the map like the
can i even find it
i don't think i have this one and this
discovered yet
okay whatever let's go to the windfall
island this was just so a lucky
lucky strike
a lucky find though
i'm glad we found it
because we got the last heart piece that
i wanted
hmm
exploration is mostly pointless
unfortunately yeah that's that's
definitely one point to criticize they
should have
put more stuff into this world but as
we've heard before
seems like this game was kind of rushed
why am i twice on the map
there we go
kind of rushed
wasn't it
try to meet the deadline
it's so sad because think of what this
game could have been i already love it
the way it is but
when you think it could have been so
much more
i wonder what we missed out on
it made it big to let everything reload
but what we had at the time it was
insane
yeah i mean i'm i'm generally not really
the type of person to criticize games
like this too much so
i'll wait does it have to be daytime
because what what happened with the
leather did i just go to the girl
i was gonna say i'm not so critical
usually
for me this is amazing
but now that i know
that
they didn't have so much time i do
wonder
what else they we're gonna do
what's the cafe
why
two more temples
uh yes i did ask kobo like actually she
asked me like a week ago
mommy kiwawa you're so busy when are we
gonna finish portal and i'm like sorry
when i come back from america so we're
gonna do it soon this this month we're
gonna continue
maybe next week maybe the week after
what's up here
my daughter and i have managed to
eek out a decent life in the process
i've realized the great truth there's
something more important than money in
the world i think our long-lasting
finally come to understand just what
true happiness really is and i'm
thankful for it okay
what do we want to talk to here
it's so lively in the nighttime here
are they drinking coffee
they look like they should be drinking
um
meat
what's made in english again
what's brett did you just call me a
little brat squid you haven't been all
laid up but one of the squid out on this
crazy uh i think yes
meat mate is mead
yeah they should be drinking mead
don't you gonna lie now why stick early
order sailor out there in my position
and he'd be belly up he'd have been
finished finished i'm telling you it's a
darn good thing i'm about as rough and
tumble as a sailor a sailor as you'll
ever meet oh you better believe it
have you ever seen what i call the
frightening fishman
check this out
it's got quite the chest
the other day i was out of sea on a
cruise and without thinking much about
it i tossed some leftover bait out on
the way
a fish came yeah okay wow surprise
what about you
just a second there kid look this isn't
any time for a kid like you to be coming
in here just trust me okay go on now go
home why do they come here just for some
dialogue
[Music]
and they're not very kid friendly
it does not roll off the tongue well
i i come here later oh interesting do i
need to wait for daytime perhaps i will
um just make it
i'll just make a daytime
[Music]
[Applause]
that was a good stretch oh
good morning
[Music]
honestly you just don't understand do
you open up your ears silence i'm
telling you we don't allow postman here
be god be gone don't be ridiculous i
went through great trials and
tribulations to go all the way to the
forsaken fortress and return with lois
letter
then please be reasonable can you at
least sign for the letter
sally
[Music]
just acknowledge i was here
foolish men now you've made me angry i
cannot even look you in the face any
longer or happy or i might i must go
somewhere to cool my feathers
on a rich unruly postman i don't know
anything about mr moe in any forsaken
fortress and yet he always comes here
bringing his
letters oh he always does
and i never reached maggie huh cause you
always belong him
so now he's probably going to the cafe
not a hodor but during night time or now
he might become postal
does that have an actual meaning
should i under 20 skull necklaces now i
already did he gave me the the treasure
chest
it tries to
charge
now
the wake postal does have a meaning oh
oh hello
oh it's you i'm so you had to witness me
fly off the handle like that at maggie's
house fly
is he making bird puns
i'm most embarrassed that manchester
never mind him to tell you the
truth though i came to deliver a letter
addressed to maggie from a muslim named
mo but as you saw the girl's stubborn
father won't permit me to give it to her
with a stubborn meddling old man
refusing to accept letters from the
postman who's heard of such nonsense
i went to the great trouble to go all
the way to the forsaken fortress and it
was a most frightening orgy and let me
tell you why it's abandoned right now
there's not even
wait game logic there's no one left
there besides bats and um mice
and rats
there's no
such
marbling as mohandar anymore
then then it mustn't have been that much
of a
ordeal
there's nothing to be scared of
unless a bat or a rat wrote the letter
maybe moisture lives there in secret
maybe he's hiding yeah
dude
[Music]
but surely you will give it to her right
what do you say of course
[Music]
oh
the mobile's letter and this letter has
to sort of stink to it
stink you stinky leather ew
ew
put some perfume on that please before
you send it
[Music]
so now we go back and hopefully we can
give it to
milady
little small lady lady lady
i'm late hello welcome
hi rachel
oh no i'm not really tired but the air
in this room has been really bad
really
bad
that voice sounded so again
maybe she sounds more honorable my dear
sweet burly bully
well when will you respond to me i don't
know what voice to do for her now
okay
here you go don't tell your dad
is is that could it be the letter from
more than i saw in my dreams let me read
it this instant
this is more
i like you maggie
so much dad i want to eat you for dinner
[Music]
i mean
maybe it's um
maybe
maybe that's not exactly like literally
what he means
did you hear that those words this means
i mean it must be could it be is this
his marriage proposal it must be at last
my feelings have been conveyed to my at
last he understands how i feel this is
the happiest day of my life
from here on out today will be the
anniversary of true love for me and more
oh i completely slipped my mind i must
thank you for your role in this to
commemorate my anniversary of true love
i give you this
another high piece
[Music]
nice i got
the hard piece
now we have
more
13 heights i guess there's still some
out there
but oh it's been exactly an hour
according to my obs really oh it hasn't
been an hour since i restarted my pc
should we go to ghana now
oh it's been two hours then oh okay well
then i think it's about time we go to
anon
ganon
[Laughter]
it's been two hours all right
uh i'll go now unless there's something
you definitely want me to do
something specific
in particular that is really worth it
something that's worth it
[Music]
pick up the last bottle oh yeah didn't
you guys say it's here
wait where are we going this is drifting
i'm not doing anything
go back
[Music]
carry the pig around at outset
oh
um
i do want to carry the pig at outset i'm
not sure i
have it
correctly in my memory what happens
but i like the thought of carrying a pig
i also need bait for that i have bait i
got beds how much bait do i need
requires a big thing
that kind of gives me ocd though if we
get one heart piece
then we have 13 hearts and one heart
piece
it's
useless it's useless
i don't know what i think about that
where is this fat pig
also let me say hi to grandma
grandma grant my grandma grandma and
because i'm saying hi to her i shall
drink this
[Music]
if i get back my i get i get another
soup
just so that we can have some
interaction you know
because my soup
old anyway i want some fresh one
[Music]
grandma i am almost done with the game
then i can move back into your place i
think
i'm almost done protecting the world
i wanted to mark it and now
[Music]
don't drink it by accident
hot
hot hot hot
this cursed journey is almost done where
is the fat pig oh there it
is what happened with the fat pig
now where do i need to bring it
come with me
where are we going
[Music]
where are we going with this thing
other side of the island okay
is there a specific
is there a shortcut
i need to go all the way all around
the really dark patches of good okay
okay
i don't know which ones you mean but
let me tell me when i'm going the wrong
way
i'm guessing i need to go over there
[Music]
so fat i love it
[Applause]
you calm down
there's one on my right
[Music]
i could make so many schnitzel out of
you i could make the world's biggest
schnitzel out of you
we're eating good tonight
am i going the right way
[Music]
that's just stones
so put him down here
i put him down as and i kill him
and then i do something with the with
the bait
what
to make him like
uh
dick fruit maybe
okay
[Music]
honey
just didn't land properly i guess
what are
[Music]
i guess you guys told me i got a
heartbeat from that but i was so
surprised
good job
wow
[Music]
how does anyone find that out yeah
that's a good question like out of all
the
places why is it this this spot there
must be some kind of hint because you
often think in these games that
that like yo there's no way i would find
out about that on my own but
if you really
ask every single npc and all that then
there's usually something that hints to
it
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
now i want three more heart pieces so
that i get another one
is there something else on this island
where i could get a heart piece
or we just ah
nah it might just glow i might just go
look on
did you left the face touch did i
i think i did
[Music]
yes you can chat yeah i turned off the i
didn't know it was turned on so sorry
guys
turned off the subscriber mode
let's go
let's beat this game
now we can move on to
new adventures
and i'm going by ship now
gundam is going down
yeah
[Music]
i'm sorry that the wind waker weekends
ended up being so scuffed always like
they were not really
proper weekends most of the time
and they were interrupted
i only needed like seven parts i could
have probably done it even in six parts
um
so i could have if i would have done the
windbreaker weekends properly i could
have done it in three weeks
goddammit but you know things happened i
got sick
then i went to america i wanted to
finish it before america you know
[Music]
ah let me talk to this fish here
cuz i still got some paint
[Music]
yeah
a lot going on mm-hmm
maldives stuck on me wait was that in
between two
does it still hurt no it doesn't hurt
but it's still like i
definitely have trouble
again
breathing properly
[Music]
it's just a circle
eyelet of steel have i ever been in
there should i go inside
[Music]
can i go inside
that's gotta finish the game no i'm on
it right now
[Music]
i wanna go in
i already went in oh yeah there's an
open chest
i have to go to austria so i'm so sad i
come
what do you mean you have to go to
austria during my birthday
you're trying to be closer to me on my
birthday
why are you going to austria
this that's a funny coincidence i'm
guessing like for school or for work or
for something
but if you're going to austria but
you'll miss my stream no you'll miss
this stream but you won't miss the
birthday right because flight doesn't
take that long
immersion yeah
[Laughter]
when you want to be so immersed in the
kiana experience that you go to austria
for it
so dedicated well
no no
i'm not going the right way now i think
i am
[Music]
let's all go no please don't all go to
austria
i beg you not to do that
[Music]
which is the best city in austria but i
really i said this last time
but i really haven't seen much of my own
country
and also depends on if you're asking
about best city to live in or best city
to visit
i don't know i really have barely seen
my own country
like i've been for example i've been
also to
um grass
and uh lintz
now i wouldn't really recommend linz i
know from linz that it's like
just more of an industrial city
and grass is pretty nice it's pretty and
small
but nothing too special compared to the
science book i would say
but maybe that's bias
i loved it both times i love austria i
wish all streams were real
what
i wish all streams were what what
what what
what do you mean
you we're there
obviously we're real
it's a
meme why do i not know about this me
[Music]
what would you do if another german
austrian person would join whole life
um i would create whole life german with
them
whole live deutsch
and uh yeah i would be happy because i
have someone to
like hang out with i guess
do a lot of off collabs
mandy manny off collabs or like it
doesn't have to be someone from germany
or austria this has to be someone from
europe
that would be nice
no
i don't know why
we just can't get someone
from europe so far
like
even
a certain
competitor
uh en competitor if i understand
correctly they have several europeans i
think
i've heard so i'm not sure
but i think
they do right
only in the
in the boy branch though right
i don't follow them at all so i'm not
sure but i've heard i've been ah
i've heard
i think
[Music]
no i'm not talking about lumi
maybe after
july maybe after august or i don't know
maybe after the
summer would be cool
hi guys
[Music]
time for more attention runs on
homophobe
i've heard that i'm not so strong after
all what the
people have lying to me and uh
apparently i'm the weakest now
um creator of honor cure
what the why am i the weakest
excuse me
[Music]
i'm planning to play horror cure
tomorrow so you better fix me until
tomorrow
what the
[Music]
good i wanna do some cool attacks let me
know
[Music]
you're so fun to play us okay
sad
[Music]
it's not that you're weak everyone else
is too strong
i never played like the the other one
vampire survivors but
is it like since it's a fan game did
they just make everyone much stronger
than
they are in like
i mean which one do i use
in vampire survivors are they much
weaker in vampire survivors
[Music]
it's just mechanically based yeah yeah
yeah yeah
i get that
oh look you're easier
that's good
look here is my difficult game
look it was easier
which one
has less variety in builds what hulu or
vampire survivors
my special attack is insane yeah let's
go
good to know
final dungeon it's the final countdown
[Music]
oh no it's like a fire dungeon wow of
course it is
and that looks like
the dungeon i've been to before
roommate is the strongest damn
oh
what is this
hmm
okay why don't we go first
let's go here first is this door open
is invincible with the right build
you guys really have to like help me a
little bit because i never played
vampire survivors i'm guessing that it
helps a little bit if you played it
because then you get the gist of the
game but in general i assume it's not
such a difficult game in general like
you just have to like um
run around and
yeah not get hit too often and keep on
upgrading that's that's what i
understand from what i've seen so far
[Music]
okay
pretty much right
simple
he's a peasy eh what did that do
what did that do
i don't see that doing anything
ah but yeah it makes me fly that was the
thing with this
okay so it wants me to
go fly somewhere
uh
i'll go
[Music]
what the
is the other one
does the other one let me go
up
no they both pushed me down
that though
uh he's back
excuse me i thought this was easy
come here you little
or i'll shoot you with my
arrow i hate
this like focus sometimes
[Music]
okay i'll take this heart thank you
okay so i i guess i guess i gotta go
land somewhere first
don't you put
[Music]
land here
ah there's a
something to use here
kind of hidden
and then maybe i try to go up here
maybe i could have gone higher and i
just
used the leaf too early
no
chad's dying no chad is here
what am i missing
can i just go in between really does
that work i was thinking that too but
then you guys said
i don't know stop before
okay
uh i have a bad feeling
[Music]
or so i don't know
because i need to go higher than that
nope that didn't do anything
hello hello hello
i see you now
yeah yeah i saw us also
okay
are we fighting someone
what are we fighting
what why did i reset
what are you my
i don't like this
i want to jump in there but it looks
familiar
i don't know what i should use
[Music]
okay go
one or this one they seem so similar to
me
[Music]
was it the right weapon though
i think that was a skyward sword thing
dude
vacuum in the sun
[Applause]
hearts
[Music]
why
it's always the same mechanism it's
always the same
question
okay
[Music]
and we should just ignore the small one
i don't like the camera work here
why does it not
[Music]
house
remember this part
he's gonna go do the same thing again or
oh there we go
can i just ignore the small ones
[Music]
i can't like get him with my thing
i hate this weapon
at least in this fight
[Music]
it's so
stupid to use i'm gonna die
pressing too lightly
i've been trying to press it longer like
experiment a little bit but it still
doesn't quite work that well
okay probably last hit
i don't want to use up my
fairies here
[Music]
holy
okay
i know this is really hard to watch
probably i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm trying
however my hands are getting really
sweaty my god my hands are so sweaty
sweaty spaghetti
stop the pain in the ass this is such a
pain in the ass them
them i'm going no no no
[Music]
okay i'll rely on the fairy then
[Applause]
oh my god
why is it such a pain in the ass
what
at least i didn't get eaten this time
[Music]
look these bastards it just doesn't work
it doesn't work
[Music]
what is
flopping that
like that
[Music]
one more time please
no explain this to me
oh no not this boy i want the big boy
no
hell
not just flopping around
and just throw bombs at it please
[Music]
i hate this so much
i'm pressing it once but then once it
doesn't work so i'm pressing it more
often
it doesn't yes
[Music]
he's gonna respawn them immediately
isn't he
come on just
this wasn't such a pain when i first
tried this boss was it
oh my god
i'm
didn't molding give me something to heal
myself now
yeah i tried to dry them on my t-shirt
i'm wearing
i'm wearing i think it's like an anime
expo shirt from last year
oh no
oh no i always reset the items
in the beginning
okay
yeah with the last name initially yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
let's see where it goes
i think i just gotta go further
okay
let me on you oh thank you thank you sir
thank you kindly
now ah there's here's the other one okay
okay
uh but i can't reach it from here i have
to
go
there it comes
there it is
okay hey that was drifting
i swear that was drifting i wasn't
moving
gamepad
hell i wanted to wait longer
gamepad has no patience
the hitbox is really nice though
hey hey hey hey stop moving
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on
[Music]
wait a minute
okay
uh
[Music]
oh it does work from this distance
which is not hitting it right or
whatever
okay now if i
fly
now sasugani from here it won't work
anymore right
yeah okay uh then i just fly over
to one of them
okay
here i am and go
it's easy
don't disturb me thank you
okay
now i finally at least got the gist of
how to deal with this
okay is there some hearts in here
perhaps
no but magic
smooth oh thank you
thank you thank you is it boss time
i guess they all repeat the bosses that
we fought before so which one is this i
don't remember
guy oh that one is long long time ago i
how don't we if we just gotta cut off
[Music]
it actually takes away my weapons ah
that's why it's doing that
wait wait wait wait wait wait i think i
understand boomerang yeah
[Music]
at the top
the top ones okay took the weight
so easy
[Music]
so easy what
he wouldn't do that
[Music]
how fast you want to go
i can't go that fast
[Applause]
[Music]
oh he ate me
one more
but what's going on
[Music]
i like the sound that makes
it feels so good
[Music]
it's like if i don't hit one for too
long
it will start with rolling
[Music]
yeah baby
two more
that one was fairly easy
i say that was the drifting once again
for real doll like just now as well
uh they respawn too right so where did i
not go here here i think i'm gonna go
here
no there's no ping i'm not gonna blame
it on the pink there's no pain
[Music]
so finally i don't pick them up but
actually destroy them with the sword as
you guys have been telling me to do do i
just
[Music]
whatever the right way to fight them is
i still don't know
how to get them before they stun you
that's something
i would like to know
um
there's a berry
if i drink my another soup then i could
pick up the berry
wait for me fairy should i should i
because now uh
is that worth
it ah it's flying away never mind
no no
okay
oh hello
is that true no
[Music]
literally what i sound like
when i fight boss monsters
what you got what you got
what is this is this supposed to be
challenging or something
yeah huh
well now you come
is it supposed to be challenging
i hear no difference right
don't
do you want me to get something from
over there now
carry something
up there
oh this thing
so put it on the button
that'll go fast
[Laughter]
go go go go go go really
wait i don't know if this is like
something i had to do
what what is this for
and i forgot how to use my
[Music]
shield again
why i can just run through
don't do it
the enemy's ahead
ah
that boy
okay first let's take down this one come
on come on
come on
oh wait wait this one too
[Music]
hard to aim really
ah
[Music]
but this one
that ghost one also reacts to light no
[Music]
tamiya
it's hard to get them though from here
why is the light in such an awkward
position
i can just run right can i not just run
through yeah
wow
okay maybe not the smartest
give me give me uh hp
why won't it give me hey
[Music]
okay i did it
stupid
do i need one
so
i think i understand i need to get one
of these in stone form
put them on here
but okay that's
[Music]
i need to bring them over to the light
now that'll take a moment
oh there's so many of them
okay now one of you
will be the lucky candidate
well that's all the enemies that will
spawn here that's literally the only
ones
um i wish they were faster why they're
not faster
there we go
now you run back
to
the beginning
[Music]
and drop them
low and there we go there'll be stairs
yeah
what
oh they unstoned themselves
[Music]
wow
they're just with me
it's good that we've finished this game
today because
the combat has been triggering me hard
today
[Music]
okay let's try to get um
this one
[Music]
take it take it wait i'll do it again
don't do it again
[Music]
oh just put him down
i can't roll while carrying them
[Music]
oh
you just have to be in the beginning of
the stairs because we'll bring you
upstairs
i thought it was a bug for a second
oh
what a pain in the ass man
all right what do we got
what do we have
okay
[Music]
okay maybe not so smart
but that worked i guess
chat is dead ah now i have to kill those
[Music]
and there's gonna be less and less yeah
yeah okay it's been a while
at the small ones oh yeah the charged
one
i've i've barely used that before
[Music]
i only got three
i don't need the boots oh really oh
okay
i want that
but at the cost of what
[Music]
i
am
ah there
go
[Music]
go get that chunky
chunky boy
ah that didn't quite do the trick
where is my gotham
well the lights changed
[Music]
not this
it left my body very fast though
don't be such a pain in the
ass man
[Music]
ow ow ow ow
that's my chance
he said i don't need to wear the boots
so
i guess he's less heavy than he looks
like did that work okay
[Music]
yeah
that's what i'm talking about
one more
how many did it go back inside three
maybe
[Music]
easy
this one's so easy
[Music]
charge
i dare you i dare you don't go back up
[Music]
shut up
i'm not making hot it hard the game is
sometimes stupid okay and i didn't make
it that hard it was fine
that was not like
a painful struggle the first one okay
i'll give that to you
that was a painful struggle but also i
think the the controls for that
um weapon are pretty scuffed
partially my fault maybe but also
partially the fault of the game i will
say
you can't
tell me otherwise
i don't give a anyway nope
thank you little
these paths are really dangerous
they need better bridges
not that i need them anymore
i was here before
this one
ah that one
which one is the last one
wait what's osha
is that something american
safety something
something safety
something something
what's the last one did i go for another
one
i went for that one
maybe this one
occupational safety and health
administration
yes exactly i knew that i was just
testing you
guys is this it
yes okay that looks new
so we have
i don't know what do we want
oh water
gonna make platforms i don't like that
in particular but do i have to can i not
just uh swing from one to another
no what the is that
stop stop stop i'm not moving
there we go stop stop moving stop
i think you can just swing yeah but
maybe wait
okay yeah climb to the top i wanted to
stop but i pushed the wrong button i
wanted to stop my swinging
i forgot which button it was it was b
nope
uh
it was not b
then r okay that r it is
it's been a while since i used that you
know
yeah we thought that's what i wanted to
do all along
doesn't work
what does that sound
i don't like this
i'll just land on the platform i guess
but do i need more than one
[Music]
platform oh
this
does not have to be
such a pain yeah i'm thinking of using
the leaf too
i swear to god
this gamepad
stay no
stay you see how you tried to walk off
again
that's not on me
where am i where am i where the
wait
chill chill go up go up go up go up
maybe now
oh hi
oh i think we need to go higher
i'll leave from the top oh okay no more
swinging
required
bye-bye i'm not even gonna bother with
you
get it after this dungeon oh it's
probably restricted in this fight though
yeah i only have one
we have this one that's all i got
that's the first boss
ah let's see i think there's a moment
where
i can like you know uh-huh yes
actually
[Music]
what
all right let it go i let it go i let it
go and it straps
oh hey the dragon is back too i guess
this is just a memory because everything
is so sepia colored
uh
wait
[Music]
i could land on the platform
and now
same thing again or
i guess same thing again
okay
i recommend staying up there
it's dropping anyway that's okay
do it again until the shell breaks again
one more one more one more
[Music]
here comes the tail
i'm on fire though
bus rush i guess it's something like a
bus russian
[Music]
is gone well let me take a moment here
too
we come up
okay should i oh hello
hello
maybe i should have stayed up i don't
know he scared me he intimidated me
[Music]
can i not
fall into the lava please
oh he's just coming on his own now
what so easy so easy
yo you
there we go are we ready for ghana now
[Music]
oh
the path has opened
it's time to become serious well i have
two fairies and i have
one half of a soup
i think
will be fine
hopefully
i will save though for the first time
today
okay um
29 is the same shield
there's more oh
multiple gannons
it's it's uh usually like that though
isn't it like you'll have to
fight several stages of him
but they're all weak as
drift
that are those are his babies that's his
baby form
if i understand correctly
cute babies
one hour of gameplay left oh really is
that
so sad when you say that it makes me sad
oh
okay
uh-huh
guessing we go into the small doors
first
boom around
is there a specific
order i wonder
there is huh
where's the hint
are the signs up there to hint of like
which monster i fought first
um
wait
this one no that's the worm that's the
sand worm
and this is the first i think and i
don't remember it's been so long because
we spread the game apart for so long i
would say
um
i don't know maybe
actually i really don't remember at all
let's see if we get lucky
enzo avoid tonight
that was not it
middle rat is first
it's in the other room
explorers hinters in the other room
this puzzle is optional oh
oh
one ah
okay
two
three
four thanks for reminding me
i know i know
what
you are
you are what you are
you
you chihuahua you must remember well the
appearance of this room the shape of the
floor the number of items hanging on the
walls such things are the keys to
solving the riddles that lie ahead
do not overlook anything yeah it's okay
i already know what it is for
so uh
one
two
three four
okay
forgot no just kidding i remember i
think
one two three four
one two
three four
faster before i forget
i know
yeah it's showing me
it's it's reminding me again
that wasn't necessary
one
two
um that doesn't look like something i
want to go into oh about we get both
what's up
don't go in there it looks dangerous
i see
so this is the portal for which ganon
was able to seep into the unsuspecting
world above
kiwawa we shall make use of this path
that ganon created for himself if there
is anything from the world above ah
[Music]
that you believe you need and climb into
the boat and enter the column of
darkness
so this is just if i want to go back
oh
i see well if we need like more more
like healing items or so but i think i'm
good
i think i'm good i think i'm good so i'm
just gonna go then
but
it's nice that they give us the option
um yeah i'll be fine
sound this way
things
i'm confused
isn't that where i came from
it is where came from
i need to jump down
i need to jump down here
let me rate that
i'm pressing a
the sword hills of my servants who lurk
deep in the darkness shall be the
guideposts that point to me
the sword hilts of my servants
who lurk deep in the darkness
shall be the guideposts that point to me
what does that mean
[Laughter]
just remember okay jump into the dark
pit do you mean this one
no way
how do i fight this group
[Music]
oh reflect with shield
we're doing the
the ball fight ah we did that in the
beginning didn't we
vod was correct
no what the
is that did i hit him
can you reflect those two
[Music]
can you face to the front please you
little
[Music]
okay oh i can
didn't look like that he would be
hittable
pick up the ghost sword
what did it wasn't
they all look the same
[Music]
leave it
remember the hint
wait a second
is it because it's pointing towards that
door
what if i
told
somewhere else though
it's too late because they moved it
[Music]
i shall guess
oh come on
was that correct
baby
don't underestimate me kfc
hell
rally
[Music]
so that way
right
intuition wins the day exactly
this is wii sport yeah
okay
[Music]
i'm so bad at this
hey i did so well like before
[Music]
why do i always miss the third one
just spam
oh one more
one more red one
[Music]
how often do you want to do that
spin
i wish he would just do the
the other one again
mamma mia
[Music]
i'm so sweaty
[Applause]
can you do the other thing please
i'm not confident
[Music]
that's like a cheat
for
when he does it again i'm just gonna do
that because then i always hit him
hey why did no one tell me that works
i expected the red attack but then
suddenly he switched back to the other
one
um sorry i wanted to fix the audio
really quick
because it's sounding correctly
yeah if i knew that earlier
i don't quite
okay
okay i'll do this right away let's test
it out let's test it out
surprised
[Music]
okay now it was too
early let me try oh
[Music]
just in the last second
oh my god
oh my god i hope two ferries is enough
at this point
[Music]
i don't know where he is but
it didn't work
it didn't work i hit him but it wasn't
all of them i guess he knew all of them
oh i got this oh oh wait
[Music]
okay okay i'll do it properly
i'll do it properly
[Music]
i think it's you know i'm getting
nervous so i up the timing
an empty bottle also works what what
oh my god how long this is
[Music]
i want to figure that out there was like
a crop there i wonder if i could have
ended the battle early
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
how long is this
the end is never the end it's never the
end oh there we go it is the end oh
i'm so scared i'm so scared
[Music]
okay
who would have thought that it's that
way
oh my god oh my god i'm sweating my
hands are sweating
oh man
he sometimes did it faster though and
sometimes he did it slower didn't he
i felt
that way at least
almost there
knees are weak palms are sweaty ah the
light error
looks like a boob
looks like a burp that goes really fast
[Music]
speed burp
a light arrow
oh yeah now it has the the third
thingy
on its icon ah
it's easier when you're not close yeah
yeah yeah
okay
sounds like you
it's gonna go fast
gotta go fast
okay
i'm gonna have two messages on this card
what is it
yeah yeah
[Music]
is this the real battle
yeah
i feel like we need to fight in a more
fancy place
[Music]
oh my god oh my god
oh that's so cool
okay ganon is dead forever
thank you forever
i am dead
that one's pointing nowhere
is he
is it trying to
hmm
can i shoot for the wall
i think i can or maybe not eh
huh
i'm talking about this door
i'll use this sword
hey yo what
what's up with that oh i don't have
much health i don't have much energy
what's up there
what's that thing
okay give me something
no not arrows i know i said something
but i meant
hearts
[Music]
or magic energy but that's still not
much okay let's help the enemies drop
something
something good
this really reminds me of the super
mario
stairs to
to bowser
but honestly every every kind of stairs
reminds me of that
i'm just traumatized by that because i
was it was always so spooky to me
[Music]
i'll take it
i got there i just
never went
further
oh ah that's what that was
what a huge damn sword all right fight
me
don't embarrass yourself
[Music]
yeah
okay
nice
[Music]
you want more you want more there's more
where that came from
[Music]
yes heights
heart challenger
okay i love conqueror can i insist um
shoot them like this
what happens when i do that
oh
what does that reach do i have endless
or does it use my normal arrows
that's quite the fancy way of killing
them
[Music]
oh
one shot kill sasuka i mean if it can
kill ganondorf then obviously it has to
kill these monsters with ease
again
okay
i think we're there
oh there's some more oh hi guys let me
try it
that's way too open
that's way too old
come on
they shouldn't let me use that besides
for ganondorf like what the
i've reached enlightened finn i'm too
i'm too strong
i wonder if there's fairies in one of
these
just in case let me open them all
[Music]
oh thank god oh yeah now i feel much
safer with free fairies now
i should
just to make it very clear for people
who come in because you don't see my
inventory
this is my fan
there we go i think that's very clear
now
i couldn't
if i'm in the middle of a fight and i
use one then i don't think i'll have the
time to update it though
so
anyway
and you guys it was they they activate
automatically right just to make sure
just to make sure
horrifying no
save okay
[Music]
what weapons do i want um
i think this is fine i just need to know
the light
arrow
oh
that's a nice
like
what do you call these beds again in
english
because in german we say himmelbet
heaven bed
nice name rain
nice
he prepared a nice place for her to
sleep
i cannot be bad oh yeah
is that him talking
do you sleep still
i can see this girl's dreams
she's dreaming of me
oceans oceans
potions potions
oceans as far as the eye can see
they are vast seas
none can swim across them they yield no
fish to catch
what did the king of hyrule say did the
god sealed hyrum away
and they left behind people who would
one day awaken high rain
how ridiculous
so many different creatures scattered
across a handful of islands drifting on
the sea like fallen leaves in a
forgotten pool
what can they possibly help to achieve
don't you see it
all of you
your gods destroyed you
[Music]
do not betray my expectations
verbal city and yes it's the words i've
proved it before
what the aisle
can we like move
move zelda
what you look like a pokemon
[Music]
how do i fight him
why ah okay
i mean like repeating all the gimmicks
from previous bosses
[Music]
are wait are we actually doing that that
would be fun
[Music]
i just get that can i like
fast he didn't even cut it
no don't go
what are you doing
it's making music i like that
okay so far he's no threat to me
maybe i should keep him on the strings
maybe he's less dangerous while he's
tied up there oh
come on
[Music]
ice walking away from me
stay here
it's on the ground it's on the ground
there's only one
do i hate it now what do i do with it
[Music]
white arrows
lucky hits
lucky hits the snare
[Music]
can i just do i even need to take that
down can i just like shoot him why is it
showing at his mouth do i need to shoot
inside the snow
[Music]
it's hard to shoot like that if you can
hit go for it
well you guys know i have a good aim
what is this camera
oh my
god oh what the what the
[Music]
so far it feels like really easy though
oh
just hit this one
nah don't go up just hit that one
where's my boomerang
huh
[Music]
no
i mean
i'm i'm having a hard time yes but in
theory like it's easy
cause like he doesn't really disturb me
much
it gives me a lot of time
um
[Music]
can i not like focus on
god damn it i want
[Music]
stay on the
did it ground
i'm not sure
yeah
did that work
i can't target the ball yeah
he wiggles so much i think i did get him
yeah that's why he went up one more hit
okay
is that all you got those bats
come on
try harder
[Music]
okay back to business
i like it
[Music]
yes yes
what's your next place huh don't be
happy yet link it's not that easy
see see see
should have expected that don't you play
video games
[Music]
okay
yeah that looks familiar
okay okay
[Music]
that's all you got the bats
okay i miss that one
hesitated
[Music]
kind of hard to reach
come on the first one's kind of lucky
sounds like circus music
i was going to say nice service for
letting it come so close to me
[Music]
ow what is that
he goes back so fast
[Music]
yes okay
what reflection are you talking i see
the shadow
oh you mean
[Music]
oh
out of here
i didn't have enough time there
just bats
[Music]
i should obliterate download my light
arrows
did that work i don't think it did
i just was like shoot indicate just
shoot
[Music]
but he was cornered there was not much
where i could shoot at very good thank
god
ignore the bats now
okay now now is the sand worm which i
hate so very much do i have to
this one wasn't again
[Music]
what if i just aim really well
no he's way too fast
[Music]
i need to shoot
but it aims at the front
[Music]
um
wait i'm not sure how to do this
i am not sure
what
was that the key
because i made him stop once
[Music]
[Laughter]
it takes so much time
[Music]
i need to hit his head though
now how do i how do i stop myself from
doing that again because like
i don't have enough time to
actually shoot
huh
just shoot
what do you mean just shoot
my spin attack because it made him stop
but
i changed my mind i don't want to do it
anymore
[Music]
the hammer doesn't work
oh
[Music]
look at this
we'll be using a fairy it seems
[Music]
i mean
what is this
[Music]
it's about time
they give a lot of hearts stop that now
maybe we don't need the flurry
he's probably just sending out so many
because i
needed to heal
[Music]
just not now really
uh
[Music]
and magic please
nothing
now it's raining though again
i'm molding
i'm sorry this is still painful but
i don't know
[Music]
i'm not it's not even dropping what i
need but okay
okay
[Music]
i can't see it
no no did it hit i don't think it did
how did
[Music]
i'm
come here
oh the timing
okay this is the most annoying form ever
am i the only one
who hates this so much
what how is he
[Music]
this one is the worst everyone hates
this one okay thank god because i feel
really stupid right now
[Music]
at this point i just want to rely on my
god aim
i need some hearts
drop me something
why don't they drop
no i don't want to use my fairy
i'm using my fairy yeah
yeah it seems like it
unless
unless you come here now bastard
let me get those
i didn't get enough
i didn't
[Applause]
got another chance
what
[Music]
just shoot
just aim
i mean i should just randomly shoot and
then hope that because it's hard to aim
[Music]
and what if i
stand here he will always bonk again no
he won't
[Music]
bomb in the space
wait a second
throw bombs everywhere
interesting
i can't throw that fire it's delayed
well i do have a lot of bumps
oh that was close
okay i like the bump uh strategy
thank god i have so many
i need to get rid of these
[Music]
hi nina i'm currently suffering
this
i'm so mad
then i need to i need to watch animal
videos with you
[Music]
what am i doing they're gone they're
gone
yeah
why is he going in circles like that
come here
oh the game is lagging
are you seeing this kfb are you seeing
this
okay it's
what is going on
is this just his first face where he
goes so fast
the explosion
oh but he's got another face right but
it will surely not be as painful
as this
you're suffering me too when are we done
the salt
thank you ayna
i'm so salty
yes you surely are the hero of time
reborn
[Applause]
your time has come
come now stand before me
[Laughter]
this reminds me
sky looks sword now cause all of the
pain but this fight will be easy
all right
i need healing
where do i
where might i get something like that am
i supposed to climb up there with this
but how do i get up to these platforms
ah do i bonk against them shoot them
right there
no
yeah i thought that would be crazy
and i like
[Music]
i need some healing
ah and then i just bring it down
no
[Music]
no give me that
no
okay that was arrows but
i'll shut the torch i'll go good
[Music]
ah it works even when it doesn't give me
the signal
ah that's not what i needed kind of ky
gotta say
yeah link is not having a good time
[Music]
wait
give me some hearts man
hearts
heights
these
mugs jugs they need to stream hard
challenger because they don't know
what hearts are
[Music]
there should be a ferry up tub
i don't have free fairies
but
[Music]
like for healing me now it would be nice
maybe they just don't come with hearts
okay
i want to
can i
how do i climb
[Laughter]
job from the platform they're making it
way too
complicated just give me like a button
or like automatically climb up
oh man
cool link yeah i mean
i feel sorry for him too but
i tried my best you know
[Music]
i know it looked like really shitty
gameplay but i tried my best
i tried
the other ones were okay just that
oh wow
just that snake at the end
don't you let go
is that the drift why can't i not just
where's the ferry
i don't want to hear this sound anymore
[Music]
not some random pro zelda play game
player thank you
um
oh wait i see the
i see it now
don't fall down
where was it here
about it the other one
[Music]
oh
motion controls
never want to play a game ever again
those motion controls
yes no trip
well i mean now we don't have to listen
to this obnoxious sound anymore i guess
no more bleep bleep
unbelievable this is such a pain in the
ass when the controllers are just
drifting as if they were on a
highway
listening to eurobeat
one fairy god yeah but i heard there's
one up there that we can catch
oh
man
grab what he did was
yeah gravity is stronger than ganon
catch up old man
okay
it's in my brain now the same i hear it
too
i'm scared um
don't you dare walk
this is the real boss fight
really
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay chill chill
chill chill
i'm scared
i'll fall down again won't die
you're so scared
oh what is this i hate this
[Applause]
[Music]
where's the fairy
one of this
is a fairy that's hurt
lies
now
here we go
oh
wait
needs to be closer
[Music]
i don't want to walk up here too much
god oh god scared if you have if you
have a fear of height then um this is
really terrible
[Music]
now it's uh up to date again
now it warps you back up if you fall oh
thank god okay
are you ready
do i have to do it from over there
can i do it from here
[Music]
the time has come
um
ariels
probably that's really the only thing i
need i'm assuming
was just for the sake of variety here's
the boomerang save oh
wait don't oh my god i'm gonna regret
that so hard i'm gonna regret that so
hard why did you say it earlier
[Music]
when the sun grows into the sky a
turning wind punished my land searing
the world and when the moon climbed into
the dark of night a frigid gale pierced
our homes
no matter when it came
the wind carried the same thing
death
but the winds that blew across the green
fields of hyrule plot something other
than suffering and growing
[Music]
that year i would again gather the free
with the quests
that i should lay my hand on that which
grants the wishes of the beholder
that when power wisdom and courage come
together the gods would have no choice
but to come down
the power of the gods the triforce he
who touches it will have whatever he
desires granted
already the quest of the wisdom is mine
all that remains
[Music]
oh
do not fear
i will not kill you
[Music]
i nearly have need of the power that
dwells within you
[Music]
now let us put an end to that which
binds us together
someone's gonna wake up isn't she she's
gonna wake up
wake up
okay
yes yes wake up wake up
wake up
oh
okay
oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh
no don't take it away
what's gonna happen
i don't remember this at all by the way
for some reason i've completely
lost all memory of like
the last part of the game very last
parts
feel that which i desire
[Music]
expose this line for the ones that are
same against here at the bone fields
[Music]
i think
is that someone else is that daddy
he who touches it will have whatever he
desires granted
is that what you said is it not
ganondorf
[Music]
but that didn't sound like english to me
huge ad which i desire
[Music]
desire desire to
let a ray of hope shine on the future of
the world
[Music]
um awkward
put silence
and let our destinies finally be
fulfilled
ganondorf may drowl with hyrule
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
back stab stimulus stab go go google
google use the arrow whatever you want
this is foolishness a future
for you
what are you laughing at ganondorf
you're insane
yay
[Music]
mama i'm sorry i overslept
like ina thank you for covering for me
sasuka
i think it's time for us to say goodbye
to this place
we must return to the world above back
to our ocean
his face
[Music]
oh dear oh dear i didn't save i didn't
save can i save someone
thank you whoever said that i wasn't
even going to try if i didn't know
okay i'll use this ball to cover you
attack him as best as you can
huh are you using the light arrows
she used arrows she used to took my
bow
that was by accident i guess i'm just
that much of a raw er
that was awesome by accident i'm just
button smashing
down
[Music]
i'm so good
oh
[Music]
sleepy head
hello
[Music]
how much time are you gonna waste
speech slapped here
[Music]
out of the way
i'm getting close to the first
it's not so ferry though it's kind of
fun
to make him stop like
dodging
hey he don't do anything he wasn't even
looking at that although you have eyes
in your bag
[Music]
and she does it with one heart left
lonely said
oh
hey wait that's it really come on give
me another face i was having fun
i didn't even use a fairy i was so close
though
cute
sorry for falling asleep again i must
have some kind of illness i'm gonna go
to the doctor afterwards to check up on
that man what do you call that illness
again where you fall asleep randomly
there that exists indeed i must go to
the doctor
oh my god daddy
my children
my children listen to me
i have lived regretting the past
and i have faced those regrets
[Music]
if only i could do things over again
not a day of my life has gone by without
my thoughts turning to my kingdom
i have lived bowed to hyrule
that sense i was the same as ganondorf
but you
i want you to live for the future
there may be nothing left for you why
does why is the voice so
but high that you must look forward and
walk a path of hope trusting that it
will sustain you when the darkness comes
back
[Music]
farewell
goodbye auf wiedersehen goodbye
this is the only world that your
ancestors were able to leave you
[Music]
forgive us
mike
you could you could come with us no it
ain't that easy
[Music]
yes of course we have a ship we can find
it we will find it the land that will be
the next hyrule
westeros so
please stop
[Music]
ah but child
that land will not be hyper
mommy it will be your land
and fish
daddy bye bye
it was nice meeting you
so i take it i have
your approval of marrying your child
thanks dude
i'll make her happy
blah blah blah
blah blah
who's the hussein is the dad
i have scattered the seeds of the future
[Music]
oh this is back to her usual form
thank you
thank you thank you for the super
chattel
ah she even did her hair damn
i'd say you
hello
as always the burps are the saviors
there it is
hey guys
oh
happy endo
[Music]
i can finally take her back to grandma
oh now it's a remix oh that's so nice
[Music]
i'm so hungry
ah
cute
wait is her dress now something with a
skull on it like she's like a pirate
girl now oh girl
oh and my my my cook friend
ah
wait don't we say the rain on the end
with grandma
are you kidding me
[Music]
cook is that clock
hey you're not gonna give me a reunion
okay okay i would hope so
now
[Music]
guys
oh
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
that's all bad
that whistle sucks you suck
up
i love this
last remix
i can't whistle you just heard it
[Music]
wow
that's my favorite ocean video
oh i feel sick and i bite into my pear i
had a pear in that powder pale blue next
to me the whole time
i want to bite into it
i i love
[Music]
pear
hmm
[Music]
i got louder and more
inspiring
oh my god
oh yeah
that's the good stuff
[Music]
i want to go to a zelda
like orchestra live concert
[Music]
mario club
special thanks oh my god
i'm so honored
it says tacoma
right there
ah you're welcome you're so welcome
so nice of them
they didn't have to do that
battle house entertainment that's german
bauhaus
[Music]
wind like original stuff what happened
with the original stuff
why are there only in the special things
is this the segue into the
ending scene
[Music]
ah because uh-huh gamecube
cute i love them so much
[Music]
i'm eating with my mouth close by the
way even though it looks like i have it
open
i really don't like it when people eat
with their mouth open
oh
this really has a little skull just
now oh
window
[Music]
i guess i'm leaving
again the we go
the wind will guide us
i wake the wind
wake up
grandma i'll be back i'll be back
but we dropped off the daughter at least
[Music]
i love this game
it was worth the suffering
[Music]
[Applause]
the endo
no play sky resort are you new here i
already played for the whole game on my
channel you can watch the vlog
[Music]
this is now the third zelda game that
i've cleared on my channel we did
skyward sword and we did um what was it
called again
what was it called
uh
[Music]
all right link's awakening um
now we did
uh
my favorite from my childhood
the wind waker and i think we might play
uh twilight
princess
sometime in the future
within this year
um i want to play them all
[Music]
twilight princess and then that should
be around like the time
uh where we got closer to the release of
breath of the wild too
and even though i didn't play breath of
the wild one i watched like three
playthroughs of that so i feel like i
could
if i just dip my toes a little bit into
the first one then eventually i can play
the second one without like clearing the
whole thing because i know the story
yeah
yeah yeah
i know it's really good but i never got
to play it myself
yeah i don't know well we might do like
a few streams on it but not like
not like a whole playthrough
[Music]
speedrun i don't know if i can speed run
i'm not really
such a skilled player i would need to
practice and all that and then if i
would if i had the time to practice
speed runs
then i might as well
oh my god that's cute
[Music]
i might as well um
play the whole game
anyway
uh i guess that's it it took me uh four
hours 20 minutes today
i think
[Music]
i think enos
is she even gonna play it again
mummy also plays it so so rarely
man these girls need to finish some
games like me
it just feels so good when you finish
them
yeah
it just feels so good like after a long
journey after
a long adventure
it's so nice like seeing the grandma
reunited with my sister
isn't that worth playing it until the
end up now about super virus 64. well
that's i mean another story but i mean
we can
i don't
it's i think enough time has passed to
maybe go back to
revisit super mario 64.
maybe maybe
i'll think about it
[Music]
yakuza
oh
i don't mind playing another yakuza game
but i don't know if i'm ready for it
already now
zelda wind waker took me kind of longer
than i thought it would just because we
spread it out because of so many things
getting in between
i'm not quite sure what's next i want to
revive hello talk like in
august uh so my weekends
will have one more thing
um bi-weekly again
um
uh we're we're not gonna you know pick
up
the next game immediately
uh
we'll see we'll see um
i want to get get back into minecraft a
little bit because there were some nice
updates that we have barely
seen yet and a whole live in indonesia
wants to build a portal
so
i think we'll spend some time with that
this month
and some smaller games
also hollow cure yeah
yeah
and uh oh
[Music]
oh yeah
it's been quite a draw of minecraft yeah
and i mean i think it was good to like
it was good for everybody to adventure
into some other games
but i also understand the people who
want to see more minecraft there are
there are some weapons it's a good game
for like random interaction
with others unexpected collaborations
and all that
uh not really for me i guess because i
mostly miss out on that due to time
zones but
yeah i like one-shot games yeah well me
too but i don't wanna you know do them
all at once and
like then don't have any more left
because now for example all those good
narrator games i'm pretty much done with
them i did i did stanley's parable at
the portal one and two
i did um
super liminal
see that's what happens when i do them
all that's what i don't want to happen
and yeah
so i don't want to do too much at once i
want to like use those for like in
between
every now and then
yeah yeah yeah yeah
why don't you play titan soul because i
don't know what that is
metal
gear yeah
[Music]
yeah now i'll um
i have some ideas for now which is a
holo cure and minecraft
and also i want to play sims 1
because it's more difficult and it's
nostalgic
um
and some i think i have some other ideas
[Music]
yeah sims one i need to get it to work
first but
uh maybe sometime within this month
or two i don't want to play or two but i
think i don't have permission for it
i'll need to look into that
will you make ian girls and sims one i
could try but it's really difficult
also like it's already difficult to play
with two sims
playing it with five sims holy that
some
some are gonna die
definitely
[Music]
bastion ah the game that ina played i
don't know i don't know
catherine
oh yeah right we got prims for those ah
i forgot i forgot
oh that's right oh
hell yeah catherine hell yeah
sounds fun
oh i don't want to play catherine i like
the whole
i like catherine i like the the crazy
woman
hollow seems one model myth survivor
edition why are you guys coming up with
the same title you're so in sync
free hopes uh firemen free helps me
i'm interested but i don't know if i
want to do a full playthrough
yeah oh yeah
hey you share one by yourself
yeah i forgot to
okay let's do that let's let's let's try
to not forget again remind me remind me
next week or so i think like the coming
week
i won't be able to start it oh yeah yeah
i think my next week is already packed
um the warden in minecraft next
perhaps yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
i like i like to play that one sometime
[Music]
i'll punish my what do you mean
punishment graham
schedule tomorrow i think oh no wait i
can do it today i got the art oh yeah i
got the finished art
oh yeah yeah i can do it today
i still need to figure out something
with um
collab time
[Music]
i used to
i wanna do my
schedule
later
just about there
it's i'm planning a collab with reina
next week i'm not sure yet what we're
gonna do i just wanna oh yeah the goose
game probably
like i said we should finish the ghost
game
it might be on her channel because
wasn't it on my channel last time do you
guys remember it's been so long it's
been months
over half a year maybe
[Music]
next week it's kind of packed holy
um
there might be a surprise collab next
week too that you guys don't expect
[Music]
okay
so
i think elena fell asleep she's not
answering me
ah
[Music]
okay
okay okay then i shall go to my office
now and we will read superchat those
because i think we're done here the game
will save you
okay uh
[Music]
i guess
what are we doing
[Music]
1 30. that's too early for her to sleep
yeah yeah yeah too early
i freaking killed my sleep schedule last
night too
i'm just i'm lost i'm lost forever
okay let's go to office
ikea
[Music]
i'm so happy we cleared windwanker the
last fight we've gone on was actually
quite all right i would say
the previous like battles leading up to
that
the the worm was really painful
really painful
okay i think we only need
need this here
because animal i don't know animal's
already out
maybe i'll
oh no oh no should i put it somewhere no
no
okay
waking up early ones doesn't destroy it
but hopefully hopefully you're right
you guys want to listen to this
beautiful
fairy fountain while reading super chats
as long as we have the opportunity to
use it
[Music]
well thank you goodbye
yeah yeah what what did i ask
wait what did i ask oh yeah you want to
listen to the vgm okay
short time memory let's go
[Music]
let's try to sleep earlier today yeah i
think that won't be a problem like i
said i have
i said i recently i'm able to fall
asleep so early what i mean with that is
not quite time wise but like um
like
once i am in bed
and like start watching netflix
i fall asleep so fast that's what i mean
not like oh i fall asleep at 8 pm or so
just that once i try i fall asleep so
fast recently
yeah
i don't know why
ring fit question mark
uh i want to do ring fade er when i get
my suit
yes
we'll get very sweaty though very sweaty
[Music]
very sweaty and very hot
wow i would never do ring fit
yeah i mean
[Music]
i feel like at least if i can do it in
3d at least it would make more sense
because in 2d you don't even see what
i'm doing
so i just feel like it makes no sense
and it's just like loot noises that's
all it is
using voice effects
it will sound like a gorilla
[Music]
improvement
you sure
but i feel like
people could
[Music]
kind of get rid of the effect by making
it high-pitched again
i don't know if that works well but i
can see people trying
[Music]
don't underestimate those peeps
that's a lot of work
if you know how to do it i would say
it's probably not a lot of work
anyway we gotta go and read some super
chats i think uh from this stream and
the one from before the members is all i
need to read
i think
[Music]
and the one before that really what the
i did the chill talk
super chats right the one yeah i think i
did
so the chit chat back from usa
oh i do have to read three of them oh
okay
it's just the one
i mean that the chill
after the after i came back home okay
okay okay
okay
my youtube channel super chat so i can't
send i'll top off for one week
that's okay thank you it's a good
relaxing series thank you i'm glad you
liked it
i had a good time mostly
today was just kind of painful
let me put this i don't have a
transparent i tried to save it from
pixel but it didn't give me the
transparent one
i wanted to put it on the table but at
least it's on the thumbnail
[Music]
so
we're gonna read this first sakini
kodena superchat yummy title
[Music]
if you tried to rush your last name it
would have been a miserable oh yes yeah
yeah if i imagine i would have done that
last time
[Music]
yeah i think it's good that we separated
it
in the end um you're not in the u.s
anymore huh
you're just kidding right
of course i'm back by now
[Music]
merch is better margins for the talent
everyone understand correctly uh it
depends
i can't give out details but i'll say it
on which merch
there's differences
[Music]
but i'll say birthday merch is good yes
i'll say that
the pants no it depends
[Music]
voice pack
yeah i guess because voice packs are
like
basically no no production costs
basically
i'm so laggy i'm sorry actually i
ordered the the cable
for my thingy but it didn't arrive yet
um so i'm still using the different
method so it's kind of laggy right now
but at least it worked so far i wonder
how much uh
oh i'm still i still have quite some
quite a lot of battery left so it should
be fine until the end i'm just kind of
lagging but at least i'm moving
[Music]
it should come soon
i hope i ordered the right cable
[Music]
no birthday merch is not out yet but
birthday merch will be um announced
not here but in the countdown stream
before that so the day before
you'll see it
uh
if you watch both
i'll see snack review oh yeah oh before
i forget let me put that oh god there's
so much i want to do next week
[Music]
there's so much i want to do
there might be like two days where i
have two streams
[Music]
yeah maybe maybe i should move this to
next week
okay let me
ah
that's a bit too much let me move this
to like
[Music]
this
maybe this day
okay that could work
yeah i'm back and now i want to do so
much
[Music]
countdown stream will be at 4 pm cst
yes that's the plan currently yeah
it will go on for like
maybe three hours depending on how many
girls are gonna call in
might and earlier if not many people
call in
[Music]
yeah i'm that's why i already scheduled
a super chat rating for next week
i'm thinking ahead one day is being
taken up by super chat reading in my
schedule
yeah yeah yeah okay let's start writing
super chats as we speak of them
kingdom hearts that's never going to
happen
[Music]
so you mean extinction skydiving
you must have had a wonderful time
moment in the u.s that is so touching
that you finally met all the myth girls
p.s peak court season in the u.s last
through september
congratulations you are officially the
tallest girl in myth uh
you mean
from what ami said
yes surely you're sure sure yes i am
yes i am tall yes i'm very tall
yeah yeah whenever um one of the myth
girls
wanted to take something from a high
high shelf
of course it would be me to reach for it
yes
100 accurate
[Music]
i will be the one
yeah
reaching for the stars and then i give
it to them and i'm like here there's a
star for you
yeah
who opened jars
[Music]
i don't remember us opening any jars at
all i remember
opening
a bottle for someone what did i open a
bottle for oh was that for callie when
she was in austria i'm mixing up
memories because the time that cali was
in austria was so close to us meeting in
america it feels like it hasn't even
been a month
[Music]
yeah it wasn't even a month it was like
two weeks or something she came like two
weeks before i went to america
i opened the gush's pack it's kind of
similar
yeah i did
you open the bottle for elena yeah i'm a
bottle opener
you've done quite a lot of stuff in a
short time mm-hmm
no
[Music]
yeah i told you guys i told you i warned
you guys that in june i wouldn't
be able to stream much for many reasons
for off offline meeting travel reasons
recording reasons now i didn't know that
i would get sick so that made it even
worse
that was not on purpose that was not
planned but anyway thank you skye
[Music]
right the arm wrestling brought a lot of
new eggs are you sure
that's while you were in america i
completed a year of being a member oh i
was sleepy fell into the fryer and
landed on the bucket noise it is
somewhat comfortable i'm glad to be a
part of kfb welcome home thank you
that's great to hear thank you soon
ah that's actually maybe the most
comfortable way of having it happen
overnight while you're sleeping
yeah
you just wake up and it happened
good very good the best way to die once
and then be revived
congratulations thank you mwah
gerard thanks for the rest of the chat
thanks for visiting the us branch i hope
we passed inspection and the statue was
tall enough
i am happy to see you dance that can i
dedicate my kiss to sona he had a
birthday this week oh no russian super
chats oh yeah i remember it was his
birthday yeah yeah you've been busy yeah
yeah but don't worry
all good all good
well then happy birthday soda once again
congratulations
[Music]
yeah he can still have it you're so kind
you always give your kisses to somebody
else
so sweet thank you thank you
my birthday is so soon too
i'm excited
[Music]
i'm so excited
oh my god
in in three hours it's
uh already
monday for me i need those countdown
videos
oh man it's not gonna
make it in time i think
[Music]
what time is it is it in america
like noon
or like afternoon
[Music]
rebranded yeah
ah
almost 3 p.m 2 p.m
oh well
at least
within american time zone the countdown
is still
would still somewhat make sense i guess
all right uh
trevor g thank you for the
red super chat and the pinky
so happy you made it book tns save and
sound
my bae love it
absolutely ecstatic to hear about your
goodnight
[Music]
recon immigration
where you ina and out of california
or swoop by phoenixton
arizona
yeah pet bubba there's so much iphone
unknown
it's driving me kia razi
[Music]
what there's so much iphone i know
what what does that mean
i see you try to implement everybody's
names like bay gura amina kelly
for some reason
phoenixton
boba and fawn yeah makes sense
i wanna know ah so much i'm fun and fun
it's quite the stretch
you could have maybe talked about
the fauna that i saw
i mean you know the plants that i saw
possibly saw like the palm trees
in
l.a
i didn't see palm trees i did
[Music]
well why are we talking about
arizona
swoop bye is california close to arizona
i have like absolutely no image in my
head what the
what the map looks like
[Music]
that would be flora
ah whatever
they're next to each other
[Music]
arizona has a city called wait i was so
close to phoenix
small smokers
junkies
uncles
it's me like meow okay yeah i should
have gone
[Music]
smokers
all right um anyway it continues corny
puns decide whatever happened i just
hope you had a difficult time with your
girls you're continuing you say corny
plums aside but you're continuing
and were you able to enjoy your first
room visit to this cool country maybe
you'll want to visit again someday if
not for the fans for the corn
yeah i've heard you guys like corn quite
a lot too
so that that is a good reason to come
back to eat more corn related things
but no i was um
actually that was quite nice
i
want to go to more places but the
problem is i don't
know
like anyone
in other places in america
i want to go i don't know i think i know
someone in new york
[Music]
yeah i don't know if i know anyone
anywhere else where i could go to to
like do some sightseeing i wouldn't want
to be all alone you know
ah but yeah maybe maybe one of the girls
would just join me wherever i go
[Music]
maybe they would be open for that yeah
as long as it's in the same country yeah
yeah yeah
i might
oh so thank you travertine yeah have a
good time
um
i'm not like i was i don't know there
were a lot of like pleasant surprises
like people were really nice in
l.a
um
food was
pretty good
oh
[Music]
the weather was fine
not too hot
but i mean it was hot uh when i was
dancing but besides that it was
just fine so it was not like suffering
you see yourself coming back soon well
not super soon i have other trips
planned first
but yeah i'll come back but maybe i
don't know when
it's hard to tell
because it is
a long distance flight and it takes up a
lot of time
um
people are really nice to their l.a it's
the phrase i never expected to hear
yeah have you been to l.a and had a bad
experience there
[Music]
yeah next year is definitely impossible
yes of course
so many dms what's going on
[Music]
thank you
coming in
in the clutch with the clutch how do you
say it oh chunky she's lying down like a
good girl on the cat tree
right next to where i placed the the
gamepad
the wii u game oh she's sniffing it
she's like i'm gonna play wind waker now
i'm better than you
i'm with the clutch coming in clutch
coming in clutch
that's how you say it okay
okay great um it's not uploaded yet but
it's uploading
uh it's on the way i think so when we're
done with the stream i can upload it yay
[Music]
thanks everybody for the sweet welcome
back thank you
[Music]
miniature pension thank you for the
pinky science what is that is it
delicious i don't know what it is but
always pray for everyone is healthy
thank you thank you i hope you're
healthy too i hope everybody in kfp
korea is healthy and happy i forgot to
chew really trevor jean
trevor
[Music]
happy wellington who got all kia's pets
not only wellington henry got more pets
because henry didn't hide all the time
celebrities beat stun kishan missed a
big donkey
down nene diesel duncan where are you
going chunky wonky
now just stay where you are
you want to go here on this table oh
so cute
[Music]
she's lying down behind my monitor
oh yes
belly rubs i can give you belly rubs
from this distance wellington was a bit
shy a bit
way more than just a bit
wellington i don't know melody was
really really oh
[Laughter]
i got another dm i'm so popular today
what the
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
coyotes
[Music]
she's asking me to explain to her
the whole lady thing
don't do it
[Music]
i will try to explain it to her in
japanese
once i'm done with this stream
you know
i mean i obviously also understood
totally 100 that this is more you know
like
a jork
present and um yeah i'm not like a real
lady in every country like legally i
know that it's like to preserve the
[Music]
nature and all that but then you know i
saw like on reddit and so on so many
people being like smart asses like um
well i think that she doesn't quite
understand that this is this doesn't
give her like legal rights to anything
well duh
obviously
obviously i'm just you know because the
certificate looks so legit
it looks so fun
i just wanted to have some fun with it
but some people are being smart asses
[Music]
just let us have some fun now please uh
um actually
actually this doesn't mean anything
[Music]
duh
yeah maybe i should tell you
that it's legit
like how they all believed i have an
actual raccoon which i totally do
but anyway
[Music]
love funds oh you're using the
sims 4 version of bubba
you know that bubba is really cute
thank you and happy wellington who got
all the kiara pets thank you thank you
and they're fighting
mr ants ay and zed dankeshin
what is this currency i've never seen it
before
[Music]
this is fine
indonesian
wait
this is new isn't it
[Music]
it's new i don't think indonesia was
able to super chat normally before
it just got it ah
it's about time
oh thank you
soon
dislike victor definitely or vic
whatever his name was
[Music]
it was wonderful to see you all get
together i think you ladies had as much
fun as we did maybe more because you got
to meet each other new pressure but i
know i can expect more mythical
experiences from you all in the future
collaborative cafe and whole life move
yay thank you
ah yeah we had fun and it was about time
it was about freaking time that we met
so i'm really glad that everything came
together like this yeah thank you soon
thank you very much for your support and
your patience
been supporting me for so long but you
know the fact that we had to wait so
long made it all even more special right
yeah
yeah yeah
we've overcome
so much
and we'll overcome even more
[Music]
joestar hero thanks for the pinky
welcome back then too i heard you had
the unfortunate experience of going to
walmart in america as someone who works
in an american walmart oh i would like
to extend the
i'm glad though you were able to enjoy
your time with your friends thank you i
mean it's nothing that you can do
anything about i would say
like um
the only really painful thing uh during
that walnut um visit was that um there
was like
no
human registers i think at that moment
no we're human cashiers
and the line was like a million meters
long for the self-service ones
yeah so
uh
it was so long
that was annoying but i would say i
would say that's you know a lack of um
employees and that's not something you
can do anything about
[Music]
yeah the employees that i talked to were
fine though i would say
yeah i think i asked
one dude
like where
uh
the thing was that i was looking for
i had uh i was looking for
adapters
yeah and then
yeah then they told me where it was and
then i didn't find it so i went back
i was like it's not there
it was just out of stock
they were fine though they were all fine
the employees themselves were fine
[Music]
and then i the one dude
i saw him like with this huge
roller thingy with a ton of items
that he had to stuck up somewhere
and he was pushing it or pulling and
then
like a lot of stuff falls off of it
and i turn around and i'm like oh i
want to help him this is kind of awkward
i feel sorry for him because like there
were like two other
[Music]
visitors
who were like looking
at the walmart employee and kind of like
grinning or smiling you know like kind
of smug like haha
you just dropped some
and that made me feel sorry for the
guy
i wanted to help but it was kind of an
awkward situation because i wasn't too
close
yeah and he already started picking up
his things so
[Music]
i didn't end up helping i wanted to
if i was closer i would have
tried but i kept on looking back i was
like oh oh i feel sorry for him because
i feel like it's so embarrassing like
when i used to work in a restaurant and
i would drop like a plate or something
that's the most embarrassing thing to
happen when there's like guests around
because then they must think like not
not all of them but many people they
like they look at you and they're like
oh you suck
um
i kept on looking back
like i wanna help you are you good bro
so embarrassing
[Music]
but then once i had a co-worker who
um was the only other dude in the shift
of me
the only other person
because i was still a trainee and he was
like
some older
guy who thinks he's really cool and all
that
i hated him and he dropped something
because he was drunk
did i ever tell the story like he kept
on
um
taking the beer
from the counter
drinking it
during his job and i was so pissed off
because of that because i really hated
his attitude
and just because we were basically like
alone there
he
kept on
yeah drinking
the beer
i didn't tell this story what story did
i tell
the
the grabby one
what's he allowed to know of course not
that's a reason to get fired right oh i
didn't tell uh that one either huh
what did i tell you uh i really hated
that dude
i was a young trainee
and he was like a
40 40 to i don't know
45 year old dude if not older
and
uh yeah he used to drink that bear and
then he would drop
plates and we were busy
on that day
[Music]
yeah
and i won't tell the details about the
gravity one
but then i went to i went to the bosses
and i told them
and you know in austria when you're in
that kind of like apprenticeship
training
um
it is it is very important
that you treat them well
because
the
how to explain this
[Music]
is very very very much
standing behind the trainees
and they can
if the trainee complains about the
um
restaurant or wherever you're working at
to the
um i don't know what it's called work
association or whatever yeah
then
the trainee has the power to basically
destroy the whole
place
labor union i don't know i don't know
but there's like some higher power
so you would expect that if i told them
about that that they would take me
seriously i basically i told them about
the beer i told them about the other
thing and what did they make him do they
made him pay for one beer
did not suspend him or anything
did not even scold him properly i think
and i told him i never want to work with
him again and they said yeah okay and
for a while they actually listened to me
didn't put me into shifts with him
anymore but then eventually they did it
again i mean everything was fine still
but it was just really really
uncomfortable and awkward
they did put me into never shift with
him
yeah
sucked
i didn't like working there
but i got it over
with after three years of apprenticeship
but yeah he was really gross
really gross
sounds like he's been working there for
a while didn't want to lose him
they
they didn't i don't think they liked him
much either
but yeah i think it was hard to get
different um workers
for the job
at that time
but yeah so like
it's
not appropriate i feel like they should
have taken stronger action but oh well
[Music]
it just made me so mad i might be like
extra strict about these kind of things
because i don't drink
so
i was extra strict when i see
him drinking on the job it made me so
mad
cause like okay if maybe whatever if
it's a tiny sip and you don't drink in
front of me and you're not actually like
um
having any influence by it but he
dropped plates and he was like being
inappropriate so
that's like
you know influencing
your um
ability to work and that's going too far
[Music]
thanks guys for understanding when i
told the story someone else they were
like
oh is that such a big deal what
uh
that elves should have british accents
no not in particular what kind of elves
are we talking about
uh
yeah it's a fireball offense
i would say so too
especially because it wasn't only one
time i remember him being like
drunk a lot he always had this
strong
alcohol
breath
smell
stinky stinky stinky even if you didn't
stand so close to him so i would assume
that the
the customers would notice as well
[Music]
yeah what was hr doing i know
no
thanks thanks for understanding
[Music]
no thank you thank you
where was i oh yeah
jackson fp thanks for the pinky welcome
back yahwah i'm glad you got to finally
get hugs from the rest of the girls it
was cute to see i'm sure everyone's
asked about this but in case they
haven't what was your favorite moment of
the of collapse dreams
oh off the streams
we had the pop that stream we had the
um
super smash bros we had arm wrestling
and we had
karaoke and cocktails and an archive
called okay
so i would say my favorite one was the
arm wrestling one
a favorite moment from that stream
it wasn't captured well and i think it
came across as less fun
for the viewers than it was for me
but when i was um being carried by amen
i had the time of my life
oh it's so much fun
so that was the most fun part
now
i i looked at the vlog it looked really
funny
how we were moving
but i wish you could have seen it
accurately and like how it actually
looked like
then she dropped you yo i had problems
getting off of her i didn't want to hurt
her
and also i didn't want to like destroy
the suit but
i was kind of stuck
and then i just yeah then i just fell
down
she was like are you good i'm fine i'm
fine i'm fine i just didn't want to
destroy the silk
you saw me fall
[Music]
and jojo turned you down don't worry
that can't be get down then that can't
what did i just say that can't get me
down so easily yeah okay i'm good
english is hard
i know i'm a druid diagram one still
that's just a doodle i wish you could
have seen it properly but it already i
guess they tried their best
it looked funny
[Music]
i want to do more stuff in 3d i want us
all to be able to
um be in 3d at the same time
maybe once we all get to japan
and we can do a stream like the holo x
stream
holokusu
[Music]
school
yeah japan please
please
we could do so many fun things if we're
finally all together in 3d
yeah
yeah would be so nice
it doesn't have to be in japan but it
just makes the most sense because you
know that's where the studio is
open up
open up open up
i'm essential princess carrier next time
you know that might be safer that might
be easier
[Music]
miss you so much almost dropped into the
fryer oh no
[Music]
it was my birthday yesterday but i found
aya that's super chat
[Music]
um
i don't think he's here right now
but once again
happy
related
[Music]
hey that's christmas
it's 4am over there yeah
but
see there's still some of them here
thank you so much next time you should
probably write your birthday down
somewhere
even
who's kiowa
scratch cut me off
goldberg 619 dan kashan i am the senate
toilet paper retardation
thank you never wanted to donate and
such but i've been watching stereo thank
you so much
don question thank you
elvis thank you for the rest of the chat
10 days without you means 10 days
without janma welcome back takashi
was i gone for so long you forgot my
name
i am now takashi kiara
elvis
don't forget my name
no
i'm not takashi
remember please remember my name
[Music]
not forget no no
no no that would be takishi if i had a
castle
i have land now but not a castle
[Music]
elvis come back to me
will this kiss
revive your memories i hope
i hope so one can only hope
[Music]
when you visit usa don't go to la or san
francisco or new york they're all bad
and chaotic
i mean
one should at least see them once no
i need to see new york once hey
what a hater
i mean sure they're like busy places and
chaotic but at least seeing them once i
would say is
is necessary
ah
impressive places
[Music]
what you should do is go wherever the
you want
exactly i like your spirit
[Music]
nice movie you want to join chunky
uh nagio thank you for the rest of the
chat
welcome home hot wings hope america was
enjoyable also a quick quick follow-up
from my last super chat old viewers old
guards that i interact with are still
here just working working on cafe
projects we just don't talk on youtube
chat anymore why
but we're still supporting our attention
thank you
yeah you're also not around that much
anymore but glad to see you're not gone
thank you very much
also hot wings i was thinking you know
kiwawa and kiawah those nicknames have
really
um
found its place now
hot wings didn't quite
work so well did it i like it though i
like it
but it's not something that everybody
was using huh
yawa on kiwawa is good
very good i'm glad i finally have
a nickname that everybody wants to use
i still like hot wings me too
me too
it's fun
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
give me more nicknames i want all of
them
yeah
lady takanasi is a new nickname for a
bit long
yeah you can just send me lady me lady
[Music]
no
behind the monitor oh hello can i touch
yes touch
boy junkie pause
[Music]
i hold
thank you okay i'm holding her paw
while i'm reading super chat it's
beautiful nagal here's a kiss
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
welcome back
glad to see you're back with your cats
finals are ending me oh i thought you're
gonna say finals are ending
put all the off collapse cleansed my
soul so glad you met the girls and
hanged out with them i'm so happy for
you i hyped for your birthday stream
thank you me too it's so soon oh my god
finally
it felt like such a
long journey to get to
this moment
thank you for waiting dakuma and
everyone else and good luck with your
finals you can do it fighto
[Music]
or maybe i should read the korean part
of the name
said bubba who got no pets from
how long you gonna cry about that
cry about it
[Music]
squiggly mustache rings for the pinky
fiery chicken boss we have a problem we
tentacled have been laughing in the
bunks lately from mamaina now our heads
are smooth again
can you help me end the world so we can
get the ultimate head bunk in return
i'll return some of your chickens well
well well i understand now the whole
thing with the backs
you guys were just doing that
to
get a bunk from ina like a really big
one
and you got what you needed
all is good now
you've been satisfied right
and she didn't even bonk them
at least in the the fan made videos she
did that i saw
she didn't do it herself
she's
she needs to be more strict
more strict yes
you need to teach her how to be a boss
boss lady
[Music]
oh there we go the indonesian super
chats are coming in
back up hamster time
mr kyle brown
[Music]
of twilight zed
um
why black wolfgang kashung
interesting people telling me about the
coins
dominion
[Music]
not applicable
glad you had a good time where i grew up
oh you grew up in l.a or do you mean
america in general after the pandemic it
seems that payments are more often
electronic only
yeah i noticed that too yeah yeah
especially among young people even
cashiers depend on their registers to
tell them how to process payments yeah
american coins are weird you know i get
that and i think it's good
um less
um
uh coins in your pocket and
less chances that somebody up the
change and
uh yeah you always get the right amount
of money
hopefully
that's good
other than the crackling i can't fix it
[Music]
there we go that should be fixed where
is it
look at this brandon duncan oh wait i
forgot the kiss
guys
wow thank you very much
i think until next time when i go on a
trip like that
uh
i want to get a proper
credit card that works everywhere
because my debit card it only worked
sometimes and it was really unreliable
and made me worry a lot to like i don't
want to get into embarrassing situations
where
um my car doesn't work and i don't have
cash but i always i always had cash with
me just in case the card doesn't work
but then there were some places that
told me oh sorry we only take card and
that made me really nervous like what if
i can't pay
what if my card doesn't work now
like at the ticket counter
[Music]
potential after your uh performances in
the arm wrestling tournament we in the
usual room are no longer intimidated by
you so we are walking out of the usual
room
dot dot yeah you know um if you try to
walk out of that door
you're gonna get burnt
you can't just walk out there
you cannot it's impossible you're gonna
hurt yourself so better stay inside
until i let you out
[Music]
no you're not even getting a kiss for
this one
because you're being a rebel and i don't
support a rebellion
keep six three six thank you black
fortune duncan electric heart duncan
opportunity duncan s 17 b-42
oh
thank you
hey you did something similar to travis
g you also try to put all of the
all of the names into here super chat
good job
i see you used um inna and out as well
and amazing
very very simple one
patsy dankeshen wiki tunes dances
and spicy chicken
[Music]
maple leaf thank you for the red super
chat thank you fans for an engagement
ring for ami so you can have her forever
haha just kidding huh
are we
welcome back tanja just got here been
browsing twitter for minutes on today's
meeting glad to hear america treated you
mostly well
yeah
it wasn't too bad
had a good time
had fun
i mean i feel like you know for example
because i spent one day in like little
tokyo
like i didn't see that much of
the city itself
um next time i want to do more
sightseeing
yeah
are we are we kidding
[Music]
let me hold your hand
here's a kiss for you maybelline mwah
justin reinhardt
i'm not cool thank you for the red super
chat wow welcome back here i'm so happy
you finally got to meet all of me in
person hope overall your trip was fun
yes it was thank you
thank you i'm glad i could share this
experience with you guys too
yeah thank you soon everybody thank you
miako
boondock thanks for the pinky it was
noticeable that the bones of your
friendship between all of them is strong
i cannot wait to see all the hard work
you put in for the birthday recordings
you're so hardworking dedicated and
caring
thank you
yes
i did work really hard for it thank you
for noticing moon dog that means a lot
to me thank you
i believe that kishim kdhr
[Music]
with these ones
i
am hungry
so so
hungry
next one super chats reading super chats
yes super chats super deception super
chat super chat super chats more super
chats yeah yeah super chats oh no she
pulled her she pulled her paw away from
me
that's poof snack
no
no i'm good
i think
well maybe i want a snack
but then all my cats are gonna move too
[Music]
also i only have like like when we talk
about food that i can immediately eat
i guess i have a banana
i have a banana
[Music]
and chocolate no wait no i have some
snacks from from
some salty snacks
the japanese snacks
[Music]
there were some like there was like a
like a stick potato snack
that i really liked
[Music]
by the way jonker's is so sweet right
now
he didn't break weird they didn't bring
back white american food no i didn't
actually i didn't bring any snacks from
america
yeah
i did not sorry i'm out of reach for the
camera
[Music]
oh no i'm not gonna eat what bae give
gave me i want to keep it for
for the oh
oh she's
she's needing me
oh that was sweet
i don't know what you would bring anyway
yeah
okay let me go get the snack i'll be
fast hello kitty cats
unless the pretty cats get in my way
which they already are
hi
you look on the brand new
[Music]
did i hear it
okay i'm gonna get the nutella for my
bread loaf
[Music]
you lose so much hair you could be
chicago o'hare airport
[Music]
hey
i'm danny with the funny
[Music]
okay
i got a few ones
gotta say though gemma's choices
of snacks
are
for me a little bit questionable
like a lot of them are kind of snacks
that you would
i think eat with alcohol
[Music]
anyway this is this one i like this one
because it's like um fried potatoes but
they're like dry
[Music]
and um crunchy if you can't imagine
it's not jagadi cool it's kind of off
brand i think
it's called
[Music]
hmm
oh they didn't try the snacks while i
was there
yeah they're just basically chips yeah
[Music]
um
yum
i love the salt i just really like basic
salt taste
[Music]
oh my gosh
got more pictures
[Music]
hmm
m
[Music]
foreign
how much i like salt
[Music]
ah jen my snack box reveal
is a genma snack box yeah
[Music]
interesting
it's a really small package though i
wish it was bigger
[Music]
this one i really like i i don't know
about the others they look very much
like otsumami
like alcohol snacks
[Music]
like one even has a beer a full glass of
beer
on its packaging as like the image like
this is what you should drink with this
[Music]
so
i think my impression is kind of correct
[Music]
oh it says
it says people
ninety percent of people who drink beer
say that the beer goes down faster when
drinking this roughly translated
interesting
[Music]
hmm
yeah when eating that
[Music]
okay
that's it these packages are so small
um
[Music]
and one more that's kind of similar to
the one i just ate let me try it
it's called jagger pb cop
it's also a small package and it looks
like also just basically the same thing
but kind of in a different form and
some of them have different colors i
can't
i dropped it
[Music]
it was so close so don't worry
where did you get that the japanese
beers are saying that this these snacks
are very hokkaido-ish and aren't sold
normally
maybe at the airport
[Music]
i can't open it
sad
let me try to stab it with
something
[Music]
yeah
that worked
[Music]
okay
so this has
these these are like mixed with
something dark looks like like the same
kind of things but sweet sweet potato
maybe
and then there's the normal ones mixed
in
normal
dried potato
[Music]
oh
oh they taste a bit sweeter
and they're just cubes
[Music]
i know
not bad
[Music]
mm-hmm
okay
i think i can
go back to reading super chats
how do you rate them oh so far
i could give them a 9 out of 10.
better than pop tarts that's for sure
[Music]
do i need to turn on subscriber mode
oh well
they're just a fan
i gotta you know be open
to all kinds of people
we don't want to be discriminating
yeah
bots are just people too maybe
and where was i
[Music]
talking
ah i don't think i read any of this
right
all right patsy duncan
duncan thank you for
two pinkies
a kiss for you
ah greetings from indonesia thank you
greetings back
so it says my fellow chickens i have a
plan we're going to get on our camper
delivery scooters drive up to that valet
and say cotton burger for mr stinky bad
attitude dude fourteen dollars please
after he hands us the money we'll keep
the money and the kotori burger and say
sorry you're already in the system no
crispy cottage burger for you and then
we'll poke him in the bun repeatedly
with our knives for the empress
sounds good
that will teach him yeah
now it won't confuse him at all that he
didn't order anything to begin with
this plan sounds absolutely perfect
we'll work 10 out of 10.
cute thank you cute
thank you shane for trying to protect me
[Music]
and spicy chicken
is that a rainbow
oh yeah that's a rainbow i think
[Music]
welcome back boss missed your lunch how
a little happy we're back
hope you had a wonderful time in america
while you were gone i celebrated uh my
second birthday was kfb ah
do you make it sound like we've been
here for so long huh
that people are already you know
spending their second birthday here
on the 27th which i believe is also the
first time all of myth met each other
27.
[Music]
didn't we wait yeah that's true
so it's a nice birthday present
alongside with amitovi's stream also
wait does it cut off there correctly
it looks kind of cut off for the world
um your birthday will also be soon and
it's gonna be great seeing all the
effort you put in this month along with
the help of your gen mates coming to
fruition
creation
no it's okay don't worry
already uh no i'm gonna love it because
it's you and i know you work hard to
make
uh things the best they can be also
because we saw how cute your 3d model is
already how beautiful your voice is in
the karaoke especially those high notes
and harmonies and choreo always on point
though i can't believe they nerfed your
butt yeah what the
maybe if your skirt was long and they'd
buff you
no no i might i have to
investigate a little bit more about my
butt because you guys really made me
think about this one
really makes me wonder
i can investigate for you no thank you
i'll be doing the investigating i can
only trust myself with my butt
problems
[Laughter]
so thank you
you say korea always on point but
you've only really seen me dance
properly once so yeah you can't judge
much by that one time can you
but
there will be more soon
and i hope i can make you all proud so
thank you so much spicy chicken pablo
thank you for the support
thank you shane
all my love to you thank you
smokey while dancing frog dancing
but that's not really something you can
compare if anything maybe the vr dance
school
but even that was kind of stuff but yeah
it was
that was fine
[Applause]
[Music]
won't be around for long today but i
just want to say glad you're back with
us and also fight two for nail to get
your trash can destroyer back
demand it back and don't let them nerf
you ever again bye
also cute thank you i already got some
fixes done i wonder
if they're gonna you know do it if i if
i request a butt
improvement
you know i can't just you know say oh i
want this bigger i want this bigger and
this and that and this and that it has
to be accurate to the original reference
from hoka papa
yeah otherwise
you know everybody can be like hey give
me the boing boings
can be like that give me the boiling
blings
also that lavergaster replied to me did
you see it the english reply yesterday
last night
it sounded so polite that i'm wondering
if she
um asked somebody to
[Music]
translate her reply and it might have
been originally in japanese it may have
been super
like
you know intimidating and juniper but
then whoever translated it made it very
polite
maybe who knows
it was it was strangely
polite and
it didn't sound intimidating at all
i was really surprised when i saw the
reply i thought she was gonna
you know start a fight with me although
i started so
yeah maybe someone nerfed her reply
[Music]
i
um
i think i may have to
yeah collab with her sometime
oh well
you know
i'm i'm the adult here so i want to
be cool and all that but you know how
what happens when i try to be cool
in front of my kohais
so i'm worried i'll embarrass myself
um
[Music]
spicy
why you people call it a dump truck
and this legend is a whole life monument
and we won't stand for this cover kiana
love
thank you thank you
you guys should
tell them kill them go tell them we need
bigger kiara butt
it's not fair what you took from us
[Music]
[Laughter]
no the broken trash can you can't use
that as an argument
because
it wasn't a proper trash can it was
[Music]
it was just like four sticks
like it was bound to break
okay
do i need to get a clear statement from
subaru so that you will believe me
she will confirm this
yeah
i told him a million times
it's not me it was a trash can that was
yeah like a dollar store trash can
exactly
so cheap and like
like what
what's the right word when something can
he's fragile it was so fragile
[Music]
calm down i don't know what you are
burning about anymore but calm down it's
all good
jeff star thanks for the pinky you're
amazing
i'm sure you're amazing too
thank you for the support and the
love black christian duncan pudding
general duncan
um let me try to put that into papa go
have a girl
[Music]
uh
i always forget
the bees and the peas
uh
you were traveling central europe last
month for three weeks wow
you visited austria wow thank you i hope
you enjoyed it
what
is
[Music]
thank you for the pinky potential
attention welcome back i missed your
normal stream times oh thank you for
waiting
i've had a burning question these past
few days this whole talk on hiatus i'm
curious and i don't remember hearing you
say anything about on it uh it's been a
few months it was the last one yeah we
talked about it like i think maybe
during the memphis stream yesterday or
so
i already talked about it um it wasn't
purposefully put on hiatus but
yeah things kind of happened but it's
coming back i'm working on it and since
it's been so long i wanted to have
um
a really big revival so
it will get
some renovations and stuff
yeah
so look forward to that mm-hmm
[Music]
looney duncan wayne robert spalding
wayne robert spalding thank you thank
you
[Music]
soon
mister kel's big thunder
[Music]
just remember but uh
like a picture
for the rest of the channel
it's been a really busy week you did
great
thank you thank you
yes
thank you it was a busy week um i'm glad
that i'm back home with my kitty katos
back to normal seemingly
now we can have fun as per usual again
so thank you for waiting for me
thank you
for waiting for me
[Music]
to
is
[Music]
thank you
can i join the kfp i want to be kfb
employee of course please give me a cool
carefree fan name
yes i mean you already have savage
phoenix it's already related to me was
that on purpose or did you already use
that name before
and then there's something in korean
that apparently means tantra i always
love love you so much let's check if
you're lying to me or if it's real
[Music]
bad
i'm never a savage salt dispenser who
ran away you say you're not
but are you
maybe you are
i thought you were gone forever
what confused you
you're back
i thought you were leaving me for a long
time
welcome new egg hey
[Music]
thank you for joining for the twist
it's what same is it really well then
just
use your own name
yeah why are you trying to deceive me
i'm happy if you're back
don't deceive me
let me give you a warm welcome
welcome back welcome back
now stay don't go anymore
oh
employee number for birthday happy
birthday birthday
and uh yes okay how about 136.
well that seems to have been your
birthday
jack baker
and pepsi
[Music]
oh wait jack baker oh i don't know uh
did you do something bad
i can have it
uh
checked by manager's son later
[Music]
so maybe try again in the next stream
if you can use the account again if not
then i don't know i might even be banned
for a good reason or uh there is some
bug or something
yeah yeah i'll check it out okay
[Music]
i think i remember the reading for this
one
[Music]
cucumber milk
thank you
uh
australia hungary
thank you soon with a weird combination
jacob 47 al tank shane jim jersey duncan
fan service much duncan
[Music]
no i didn't see the cooling gate bridge
sorry maybe next time you need to chat
oh wait translator
[Music]
sienna
is there anyone in the chat right now
who's at ax right now
how's it going probably
uh if you're not staying standing online
that you probably don't have the time to
look at my stream huh
huh
[Music]
me really
thank you that you're still watching my
stream
was there the first two days ah
time zone is a killer that's okay hi
there
hyphen was there whoa i am it's awesome
oh
take photos
and show me i was looking for the tag
yesterday
yeah i didn't see too much though
[Music]
i have my stream what really right now
hello
really i know they're playing like music
videos there
am i
they probably don't hear me well though
right are you a kid
they should be playing my stream though
they should if someone's live they
should be playing it what do they have
the screens for huh
[Music]
i saw favorite night with audio
oh yeah yeah i also saw they were
playing my songs yeah yeah they were
playing like i guess everybody's songs
we have to hack into their system
and then play my stream on every
screen not only the booth screens
have you seen cool with conversation
yeah i listened to it yesterday
so cute
like she sounds
so perfect like oh my god
[Music]
i love her voice so much
oh my god
and then i saw some
i saw this super cute tick tock of a
kobo cosplayer not a tick-tock it was a
youtube short i think
of a
kobo cosplayer she was really cute and
she was doing like that opening from
koble which is like her song and then
her phrase i don't know it by heart
but
it was so cute
[Music]
so cute
and the cosplay looked so good it must
have been so much work because of the
wig and all that
wow
the wig looks like a pain in the ass to
make like that that's
every cosplayer's nightmare
[Music]
i didn't say black
book she's so cute
so cute
it's been a while yeah i need to forget
about her so that i'm not like
constantly thinking about her i need to
like
what's the word i need to think about
other things
distract myself
because otherwise i'm like
i i don't know how to keep myself from
adopting her
and looking for the time thank you
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat yay
erase
bro for myself yes thank you
[Music]
not applicable
thank you
[Music]
wait wasn't that something that i missed
wasn't that yeah i feel like i saw you
telling me that i missed it or something
i'm sorry if that's the case there's a
case for you if i really miss the
rainbow wow i'm sorry well thank you
just want to say again thanks for always
uh-huh
being our light this time i think i
might be able to catch up the birthday
stream hi thank you
[Music]
nice
i'm also happy to see you again i feel
like you might have been on a break or
something because i felt like i didn't
see you for a while but maybe that's
just just because i was
i was gone too i don't know
[Music]
what
area there sometimes is a paid service
for full body scrub it's done nude i
didn't try
it would probably be way more um
comfortable if the other person was not
nude
if they're just there
to do the service
why do they have to be naked
[Music]
just to like
not stand out and like have like not not
destroy the atmosphere or what
for the immersion
no but why
you know
it's not about disliking nudity it's
about like if i get a massage an oil
massage or soap
in a massage place i don't want my
massage person to be naked too
just to make me feel better or something
i guess
no
i don't need my massage person to be
naked
[Music]
see that's weird right that would be
weird
[Music]
[Laughter]
i would be weird yeah we're trying to
blend in maybe
[Music]
i guess they're enjoying the spa too i
guess
on their free time when they're not
scrubbing someone
what are they doing when they're not
are they just chilling in the bath like
for real i'm curious i want to know the
answer
what are they doing
[Music]
judging you intensely
scrubbing themselves
just endless scrubbing 20.7
[Music]
they probably are scheduled well if
they're really scheduled then they
really don't have to get naked though
don't see a reason unless they just
really like being naked like uh
like uh what do you call them
nudists
hi chunky wonky
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
oh man
i shall investigate maybe
cruz
at the air's hollow booth i wish there
was more merch of you
ah the whole booth doesn't it like only
have merch of the
free
ambassador is the
lisa
empire and
that's see that's the only merch right
yeah i guess you gotta go to fan booths
and
is there an omo campbell i think there
is but do they have stuff of us it's
probably sold out
well there's definitely fan booths that
have some i've seen i've seen some whole
live stuff in fan booths hmmm
[Music]
sitting behind the monitor again
i am done with the super chat rating of
the super chat rating
now animal didn't have super chat so we
move on to today
final stretch
yeah
let's catch up
ah it's already 10 p.m what the
actual
means i streamed
four five six hours
[Music]
oh my god
time passes so fast when i stream what
the hell
the day is always
like over
oh my god there's a lot of super chats
today
thank you very much
one second
[Music]
okay
thank you
thank you glad you like animals
of course i will
all right
she says dreading having to read them no
not at all
no i'm okay the snacks helped
[Music]
to celebrate my birthday with you
oh it's time is it today
and kfb and there's nothing i would love
to do more than spend it with watching
my one and only elsie playing my
favorite game series thank you for
always making me laugh and writing up my
brighten up my days we love you and
lady i can't talk anymore apparently
never change thank you well that's
perfect then originally i wanted to
stream wind waker on saturday but i
guess i
i don't know some
faithful hand has moved and guided me
towards today
because of you happy birthday
happy birthday fro fro
happy birthday profile
happy birthday from fro from
happy birthday from france
i hope you had a lovely day
and i wish you all the best i hope all
your dreams come true in the following
year all your goals
treat yourself to something nice okay
thanks for the love and support
[Music]
how far did you get for the letters oh
not too far i purposefully didn't read
too many
because
i wanted to you know take my time with
them
i did read yours for example space
waterfall
was so sweet
so sweet
so kind
[Music]
so lovely
i think i read lunchboxes
and i read
pudding
and
[Music]
i think there was another one that i
read
oh
not sure
which one it was
[Music]
someone
i remember the content of the letter but
i forgot
well to home to whom it belonged
[Music]
oh no when i saw her in america she
didn't have any new ones with me
[Music]
i already had like
i guess i was already up to date
no
not in german the other one no no anyway
with the rainbow
hi lady cat i'm gonna cheat a bit and
send this early in case i'm not able to
send it on the actual day oh smart
you're doing a smart thing here because
we all know that uh reading super chat's
after anniversary of birthday
can get very tiresome
uh happy birthday to our great phoenix
boss empress of kfc it's been amazing
watching you grow the past year
including all the fun streams and the
bang of music also thank you for
[Music]
um
now
there's korean
[Music]
oopsy
am going to make it so complicated huh
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
i know the german part is scuffed but
german is extremely rusty and i tried to
limit my use of dependence on
translations as much as possible
wow though i did use the dictionary wow
but
you tried to write that yourself huh
again i hope you have a wonderful
birthday i'll always be here to watch
and support you live on vlogs as long as
life allows me to do so also check it
out
you kind of made it so complicated also
you could have written one part in
japanese come on
thank you very much for your sweet and
kind words yeah i would hope that if i
put you in the into the usual room you'd
be a good chicken and stay where you are
until i let you out because
yeah i i'm too old for this when
you guys try to escape i can't take it
anymore
[Music]
she didn't notice oh what did you
recruit me or what
i don't see a rick roll in here
what what did i not notice
anyway thank you for your support and
your well wishes and your love thank you
for believing in me
oh that was supposed to be a rick roll
[Music]
ah
oh
it was so natural i didn't notice at all
yeah because the english translation now
that you say it and yeah i can see it
but it was so natural and smooth
lost in translation yeah
thank you
thanks for being with me for so long
[Music]
patsy duncan liver devoted
is that supposed to be something like i
am a you know what
[Music]
that name doesn't mean anything says the
next super chat
so
i don't believe
i don't
i don't believe this
what did you make me say
of course of course
of course
you little
whatever was that you
i think it was
[Music]
level
usual room
[Music]
huh
you confess
no that change is nothing why would you
do that
usual room one week go
you can watch my birthday stream from
the usual room was that worth it was
that worth it
you shall not risk
your freedom around my birthday
stupid little chicken
[Music]
no it's not a vip room
no
the hero what do you mean the hero we
all need
he didn't do anything for you guys
where's time to go to the usual room
exactly
[Music]
it's not front seats no you got a really
pixelated view because the wi-fi is
in the usual room
now we're fit now worth it
that could thank you for the pinky oh
yeah
[Music]
that's the wrong music that's not the
one that plays in the beginning was it
yeah it was the last one
it was the last one
sad
close enough
tacon dankeson
one two three four
thanks for
five pinkies
what
[Music]
okay uh okay i absolutely love your new
outfit it's probably my favorite so far
i've read this before haven't i
i love the two burps i've read this
before
your new gestures and especially your
hairstyle but my favorite part of your
outfit are the austrian mountains
[Music]
thank you for showing us more
germanic culture
you're strong-willed woman you want
wanted your birthday and freddie and you
didn't give up
oh you took
[Music]
it uploading
i'm proud of you you also got all of
live together by doing this and it
wasn't only me
it wasn't only me
many people are very thankful to you you
are awesome kiana a true blessing shout
out to the girls who helped you so much
yes
welcome intentional as always i didn't
miss you at all and was rather happy you
were gone
[Music]
almost broke out of the usual room too i
didn't worry about you or stayed up all
night and checked twitter all five
minutes to see if there are news
yeah if you do that
then
it was probably good that i left for a
while because that means you need to
break
welcome back i guess just kidding you're
a very
miserable almost red miserable
person and i'm glad you're here also
nice song cover and thank you two are
cute together and harmonize well i say
this all the time but i absolutely love
your singing voice it's incredible
thanks for ian lyrics as well
thank you you're welcome
thank you
yeah yeah with animal i wanted it to be
kind of you know special so i wanted it
to be translated
austrian mountains yeah that that's a
good one i'll give you that
[Music]
thank you very much
no need to resend anything though
uh i see it all i have my eyes
everywhere
so no worries thank you soon for the
support thank you very much
two kisses because it's two reds thank
you
[Music]
jim trying to sit down
bracelet nighttime
[Music]
you and the rest of myth meet other
worldly versions it's you again
[Music]
uh
meet other worldly versions of
yourselves they look just like you but
they're actually children who have been
aged to adults to battle a great evil
will you treat them as children or
adults
what
other worldly versions of ourselves they
look like us but they're children who
have an ancient adults
well isn't that just the same as we like
wouldn't they just look the same as we
look now
because they're
they're us
as you say they look just like us but
they're children who have an age to
adults
so they're just adults
who look like us
they have the mind of kids really okay
[Music]
to battle a great evil will you treat
them as children or adults
[Music]
i'll treat them
as a dream because it's not real
no but that kind of isn't that though
like um
that movie that we watched the one where
you go for the closet
[Music]
that was also children
fighting
the battle
yeah narnia
sounds like they're just dreaming or
we're just dreaming nah sounds like a
dream i would ask them to pinch
me
thank you
[Music]
for another weird ass question
thank you
[Music]
that's probably not how it's supposed to
be right because
[Music]
green wilder
here we go here's the rainbow
[Music]
howdy hot wings it's been a hot it's
been a minute since i've actually
watched anything live but today seems
like a good time to fix that hell yeah
i've been keeping up with just about
every stream though usually listening
while i'm at work and pausing if a
customer comes in since i never know
when you're gonna shout out profanity
that is a smart move
anyway i've got a lot a little catching
up to do first and foremost i know this
is a while ago now but i still need it
still needs to be said you were
incredible and link your wish ah
slowpoke
for each of the other myth girls it was
fun to see them in freddy for the first
time but then you came on and i was like
wow my aussie is a legit idol
you got me blushing there
it was really something special to
finally see you singing and dancing on
the stage everyone who performed was
fantastic but i thought you were one of
the special few that really stole the
show
while you were up there and then found
some proud in the van
related i'm excited to see what you have
in store for us on your birthday yeah it
will be way more it will be that but
like way longer
aside from that your new look with the
the endless gorgeous nobody is surprised
uh the first couple times i heard people
night i thought it wasn't really be it
wasn't really my sound but i kept going
back liking it more every time and now i
dig it i got put in a bucket the other
day too
so many people are being put into
buckets recently thank you
i asked the cooks to roast me on her
rotisserie instead of frying me for the
sake of customers who don't care for
fried food yeah that's good we need some
variety that's fine
your portland's down in parable streams
holy you're like
writing a diary to me
we're especially entertaining even in
the times when i was only listening
rather than fully is watching uh
oh
yeah you should re-watch them and fully
like properly watch yeah
speaking of watching though you've
ignited the desire
uh to replay wind waker in me and i've
been thinking of looking for the old
gamecube at my mom's house to see if it
still works oh
i wish we still had it i don't think we
have ours anymore and anywhere we also
moved too often so yeah i think it's
gone lost forever i hope you can find
yours made me so happy to hear that you
finally met all of myth in person that
must have been amazing we can only
imagine how much that meant to all of
you but probably a lot considering how
much it meant to us fans you're all just
so amazing and i'll never stop loving
myth oh i could probably go on but i
think that's sufficient catching up for
now just wanted to make sure you know
that as quiet as i normally am i still
love you
[Music]
[Applause]
you're the best and good luck with
ganondorf thank you
his his other forms his normal
form was okay
why is that one always the weakest huh
i hate him so much
but yeah thank you for all the sweet
words
[Music]
you know when i was on my way to america
it was so surreal
i was so nervous and it felt so surreal
that like i was on my way to america to
meet the girls
it was such a crazy thought
really crazy like a dream
[Music]
well thank you for everything wow
even if you're generally more quiet i'm
really really really happy to hear and
see a live sign
thank you for supporting me for out all
these times and yeah
i hope the customers will enjoy
your soft chicken meat
roasted chicken meat
i hope i can have a bite too
please
[Music]
thank you so much
look forward to the concert and that one
you better be paying full attention
even if you're working
well then it's better if you're going to
be working and it's better to keep it
as a vaude
to watch it
with 100 of your attention span
focused on it
rather than just half watching it during
the work
i think i think it will be better if you
just keep it for
a time when you need to watch it where
you can watch it properly i think
in my opinion and just pretend it's live
yeah
i gave myself a day off for that day
thank you
i'll take an hour off of work yeah you
can maybe take a lunch break a nice one
[Music]
i hope there won't be any delays like
with good ass stream but hopefully
everything will be ready in time
i'll try to
um
keep you guys updated though if there's
any changes
i requested the day off to wow
i'm taking the entire week off for this
to to like
[Music]
to um what's the word
why are you why are you taking the whole
week off now i think you just wanted a
week off didn't you
you just wanted to wake up for the sake
of having a week of
based
yeah you deserve it probably
mentally prepared no i was like because
this is happening on wednesday
afterwards you probably need some time
to process it that's what i wanted to
say
[Music]
ah july 4th national holiday oh
i guess you can get some extra days off
afterwards
we only had to work three days this week
[Music]
what what holiday was this week
does it just start that early for some
jobs you get some more days off
in preparation for july 4th
[Music]
i thought you would just get that one
day
ah the upcoming week oh
oh that's nice
i gotta leave for your birthday
i can't believe so many of you did that
thank you
that's so sweet even though it only
takes one hour in
that one day i mean maybe roughly enough
maybe one and a half i don't know i
don't know what the total will be yet
didn't have to take a whole day off
thank you
you're well prepared then
okay let's finish this oh my god miss
pistache and brandon ducation ponytail
duncan ultra noob duncan i don't know
but another one of the red super chat
thanks mate thank you hold the live
kfb oh yeah yeah yeah sorry about the
little travel today
thank you for waiting ultra noob
how's it going yeah i should ask for an
update how is it going
[Music]
let me ask
how is it going
[Music]
and thank you ultra new mum
wow it looks so weird to see idr there
so new so fresh
[Music]
yeah
i said to oteya because
i don't know
what
[Music]
i'm not sure if the meaning will come
across if i say idle meaning in japanese
you guys get it but i don't think
japanese members say idol meaning in
japanese so
i was just honest
quiet rioter dancing
oh are we sure canada's austrian that's
some texas style shooting partner howdy
thanks
like richard duncan doomsday 87
thanks guys oh everyone's praising my
cannonball shooting
mr cat's big stun cushion
dumpster dumb dunk
thank you
[Music]
probably pronounced wrong but thank you
the salsa artist friends of the pinky i
mentioned the forest water trick the
first time you beat the plant
[Music]
what i didn't mention is that method
wasn't found
until 14 years after the gamecube
release
wait what forest was a trick
ah
that one wait i'm still blushing
that you said that it's an instant kill
right
14 years after the gamecube released
that's even after the wii u version came
out who who who found out about it i
wonder that must have been legendary
must have immediately used it for a
speedrun or something
i wonder who found out about it because
that finding out about something new
like that something so big
after 14 years a streamer was it was it
accidental i kinda wanna watch that
moment is it like is there a footage of
it
is there footage of the person finding
out about it
i want the reaction of the chat and and
the dude
[Music]
there's a clip
show me
send me on twitter
let's see
has it been documented
i was here
there's a video documenting it really
oh
it was a streamer that destroyed their
reputation what
[Music]
let me look it up
wind
wind waker
forest water
[Music]
discovery
kylie demon's
forest water origins
oh yeah
that could be it forest water kills
colon demons
no wait
the origins right how the idea for the
first one
i was really gonna hit
that could be it
two minutes
25. can i look at it
okay
what
oh they're just joking about it in the
beginning
because
in the beginning it sounds like they
know
oh he's gonna pour it now
pour it pour it
pour it
it did
it didn't pour it
can you keep link yeah
maybe they push the button by accident
or something for the water
go go do it do it do it
linky
[Laughter]
you mean the link right you want the url
okay you're gonna do it now do it
do it
hey someone in the chat suggested it but
did they already know about it
then i guess the person in the
chat
already knew about it
what did i just guess
what
did you hit it with your swords
afterwards sword afterwards
i thought you didn't and the force would
have killed it they say they don't
believe it even
and they don't believe it
they don't realize what just happened
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i do wonder that the guy in the chat
if they
knew it
or if they were just like around
joking around because that seems like a
really
really accurate advice was a joke hmm
a bit someone in the comments says a bit
anti-climactic but sure
what a disappointing reaction
yeah i thought i thought they wouldn't
they're gonna be like wow what the
water to plant hmm
huh
is this really the first time it was
discovered
and some people saw it and we're like
investigating it
welcome back thank you
the stream enjoyed earlier about the
water change in the plants they're
coming suggested as a bit
and they
why did they bring the water with them
in the first place
maybe i guess because you needed it in
the dungeon did you did you need it in
the dungeon
huh i want to discover something so big
hey
i want to be the one
you didn't need it why did they have it
i guess maybe they just collected it
because you get it in the forest
and maybe they probably already knew
that you need it later when you're
outside
for the trees
oh maybe there's still some discoveries
to be made in wind waka
maybe there's still something that can
be found some secret thing
if there's a secret way to one hit kill
the plant maybe there's a secret way to
one hit kill
all of the mobs
all of the bosses i mean
time to investigate
put that tinfoil hat off of me it's true
[Music]
i'm i'm not i'm not conspiracy
theorizing
no
no it could be real
speedrunners would have tried probably
everything after that
[Music]
okay go ahead and destroy my dreams
go ahead
go ahead then
oh yeah vgm is back
i want food we need to rain faster thank
you for the info social artists that was
fun
disappointing but fun
nam
going down but every ganon is down bad
for kiwawa like you huh
thank you for playing my favorite legend
of zelda game i'm excited for the next
time you play one oh i'm so happy we
share the same favorite
zelda game
thank you very much i hope you enjoyed
the play through even though it was a
little bit scuffed here and there thank
you so much
teard tikki danke
happy birthday happy birthday
hope you're having a lovely day
soon chris hanson have a seat thank you
but i haven't uncle jones
gay movie and finishing another series
proud of you buzz hell yeah
once again
within dan kishan anthony webb kitchen
thank you chase walk with duncan
[Music]
congratulations on finishing my favorite
game of all time hope you had fun i
still stand by the gamecube version
being better even if others stay slower
well i did originally and just for the
sake of nostalgia and having the
gamecube again i did want to do that
gamecube version first
yeah
i don't know i mean
in my memory like i don't have
like
as a bad memory in my brain but
it's been so long and i guess i never
played it fully myself so who knows
it was probably an improvement
the
wii u version yeah that's probably good
but i did that one
would have molded in a good chunk of
parts probably two extra parts
[Music]
the old one
like
i mean i remember it but
in my memory
i don't have it much different than the
wii u version
like graphic wise as well everything old
in my brain looks so much better in my
memory than it probably actually was
yahoo
[Music]
there's subtle now when i saw the
comparison
i guess yeah it was pretty big
i guess
[Music]
what
i just saw
something in our discord that
confused me
uh anyway yeah uh huh
cow karatekash and celebrities beats
thanksgiving
thank you
it was such a woke journey when like i
might have ended but we always have
kiwama the chimpkin waker yay
not lu danke
dan kashan congratulations on breeding
windway cookie that was fun to watch you
play a pro game you had such fun
memories of from a youth yes
yes finally i can say i played it
properly until the end
on my own
with you guys
couldn't that have done it without you
that's another series under your belt it
was always very enjoyable and filled
with wonderful kimono voices i hope you
were able to enjoy playing your favorite
zelda game and it was as it was uh for
us to watch yes
except the end
everything else was fun
fox 70
[Music]
yucky bear thanks for the pinky comments
on clearing the windwaker again
though it was rushed in many ways it is
still an absolutely charming game that
will continue to stand the test of time
i fully agree with that yes the test of
time
just like the ocarina of time
thank you very much for watching
hopefully the whole thing thanks for
staying
throughout it
thank you
brandon
rump
congratulations on beating this charming
zelda game kiwawa i love seeing you
excited for playing this and enjoying it
with kfb everyone should play this game
at least once yes yes
soyu koto
it's awesome exploring and treasure
hunting viva la chiara thank you yeah i
still have
or had a bunch of treasure maps that i
didn't
um actually go through but yeah once i
knew that
they're pretty much all money
and at that point of the game you just
don't really need money anymore so it
didn't make sense but i liked the the
the thought of it and i did like the big
big wide ocean
a few more islands would have been nice
but i gotta say it's not as bad as like
skyward sword um
because like a big white ocean i don't
know it was fine like
um zooming through it but
in skyward stores i feel like they
needed way more
sky islands would have been nice bigger
ones and more space it was actually
pretty small
the whole space
yeah
yeah and fast travel would have been
good because i was really bad at landing
[Music]
more space yeah
not enough sky too much sword oh that is
actually a really good
explanation really good way to say it
too much sword motion controls him
hated it
worst worst
motion control game ever
inca rave and duncan i feel like my
maybe i'm remembering it worse than it
even was just because of that
ending
no
no i think it was just bad in general
inca raven dan kishan thank you i'm glad
you liked it
it is really nostalgic yeah
yeah finishing games like this also
makes me feel a little bit lonely
moving on to this to the next thing
it's like
i'm done with you i don't need you
anymore
dropping the game
so sad
but i'm not i finished them okay
i'm not dropping them before i'm
finished with them at least
at least okay that's something
like others who drop it just went after
like two episodes with free episodes
weaklings weaklings
they don't even think about how the game
must feel about never being touched ever
again and just replaced by another game
you didn't even
experience everything about them this
really sounds like a
like a
what's the word
mama metaphor for
for dating
oh man
sounds like something stanley parable
would say
or gladys even in her in her daily
moments
jw slate danke super snake barry duncan
gambit gamble dance
dance
[Music]
um yeah i'm interested in playing one of
the
wario's games i guess fire emblem if
anything because it's like the most
recent one
maybe for
but but not the whole playthrough and
i'm sorry i'm sorry
because i just had to talk about not
dropping games but at least i started
without the intention of playing it
until the end i'm i'm telling the game
that
this is not a long-term commitment
that this is a one-night stand
[Laughter]
if i tell them beforehand then you can't
blame me
you know
one stream stand
[Laughter]
[Music]
fn rank thanks for the ransom chant hi
introvert here just wanted to say thank
you for listening me up during my off
days oh
i assume that you're normally
lurking huh
thank you for saying hello
and yeah it's okay you can look if you
want but but but feel free to say hello
more often i'm happy to
hear some
voices some feedback and so on from
people who i don't see all the time yeah
so that i actually have a feeling that
there's more than just five people in my
audience
so thank you very much even thank you
internet weirdo dancing rise of freedom
kitchen for the pinky
it's my payday five days ago actually
oh
sorry for being late i got this evening
last week oh and the last few days
were a bit of a blur i don't know if you
are able to stream gamecube game but i
would recommend jrpg called skies of
acadia heard of it before
are you feeling better now was it really
bad
[Music]
eyes of arcadia
from 2000
from sega
wow looks so old
[Music]
i guess
i guess i never played it before
probably
[Music]
there's like a sky ship
ah
travel for the sky with a big sheep
[Music]
i mean that's something i might want to
try in my private time i think
looks nice
though
i like the the braid girl
she's cute
she's cute she seems like she could be
me she looks energetic has orange
braided uh hair
cute
has like yellow orange clothes
aika that's her name
yo that's a nice figure the figure looks
good
[Music]
statue launched last year
why did i launch a figure last year
she's literally me
aika
if you add an r and then turn the
letters around then she's kiana
you literally just need an r
she's me
she's literally me
[Music]
conspiracy very no
no she's mean the previous life believe
me
i don't know how i forgot
aika
micah
[Music]
it's the same same word
i'm remembering
i remember everything now
i
[Laughter]
[Music]
what the
oh that's a rainbow i did didn't even
notice that coming in
oh where was that ah pepsi duncan
entered the face of the pinky hi thank
you for the awesome cover of animal
reyna it immediately made it into my
everyday playlist i hope we'll be
hearing about tavanasi again soon he
will still be collaborating with her
won't you i think she really likes it of
course like
of course
i don't know why you're even questioning
it
yeah we're making plans for next week
thank you arigato thanks look forward to
the collab where we finished goose game
off inc
you're just cool thanks for the support
and i'm glad you like animal thank you
listen to it a lot please
dako madan kashan is baseball what a
space
are you done laying here
why are they so
i'm so amazed and emotionally touched by
them
being so clingy
downstairs says okay i gotta be real
with you it's been about five months
since i read super tattoos so sorry for
being a badass rebel also not that soon
you really couldn't go without that kiss
huh
so here's my carefree check all right
all right all right come here
come here come here come here
there you go i know you couldn't resist
now be a good chicken
be a good chicken
[Music]
and boo hoo seven two three donkey
chicken that side
didn't know when i would plan to do my
birthday stream well obviously on my
birthday
you mean
which time
wow
you guys are so dedicated because you
didn't know at what time it would be you
took the whole day off so far ahead
you guys are so cute
late johnny thank you for the pinky
before you fly again somewhere get
yourself with the money some spare
cables before you suddenly wonder after
your return where your cable is
yeah
but they must
they must learn to not take other
people's cables because i am not coming
home with any extra cables
could you go ask the girls if they came
somebody must have come home with extra
cables
and they must be punished for it we
cannot just you know
expect everyone to have a ton of
extra cables just because someone
is a kleptomaniac
just kidding
obviously they don't take it on purpose
but
yeah because we all you know have
similar equipment
kleptomaniac
myth
[Music]
cables will look like cables
i mean at least they could not
just take all of my cables because some
of them have the european plug and if
they would take that that would be
rather sus
and make no sense because they can't use
it
that would be very very obvious
like a shiny pokemon they're very exotic
er
earth ant or oozed and
kept skateboarder i have reached your uh
rainbow wonderful hello lady canada i'm
very excited to see the result of all
the effort you put into your birthday
i've been working on a video present for
you a short skateboarding video set to
the start of sparks oh you're really
like a skateboarder well
unfortunately it won't be ready by your
birthday oh so i'll have to pay a late
fee of at least one super chat for this
game until it's done to keep me
committed on the other hand this may
give me the chance to incorporate one of
your coil moves ah for sparks into the
longboard dance sections
ah wait i don't know what that means is
that like i've seen like videos of cute
girls
i think they were korean uh
skateboarding
just like kind of dancing skipping over
the skateboard while going through a
really long long long straight path is
that
is that that
what you mean
because that looks so cool that looks
fun
like in the mini skirt
it's so cute i kind of want to do that
[Music]
it's kind of cute it's kind of charming
scared the girl
skylar girl she said see you later boy
he wasn't good enough for her
that's the style oh that's so cool
that's that sounds more doable for
someone like me than doing like all
kinds of like flips and tricks
and grinding on fences and
or is it surprisingly difficult i wonder
i feel like it's it would be easier than
doing all those tricks
[Music]
i longboard a lot it's easy
but do you dance while you're doing it
i want to become scared of girl
used to be skateboarder and bmx rider i
got old
knees ache when i get out of bed it
really yeah does it have such a bad
effect on it or did that just happen
for other reasons
you need a good balance while you ride
in a straight line
i'm at balancing so it's at least
less scary than jumping downstairs and
stuff yeah
that would scare me like i wouldn't have
the courage to do it i think
maybe if i get bored someday i'll try to
learn it
and then do longboarding dancing with
miniskirt
mmm
yes
[Music]
titan
uh folded what do you call it
those folded skirts i forgot
that's cute
cute cute
pleated yes that's good yes yes so
anyway i'm looking forward to that
that's cool that's very original
but please be safe don't hurt yourself
and here's a kiss mwah for motivation
yay
zoom zoom zoom i can already imagine you
zooming for the streets
are you taking that with a gopro or so
i'm excited
code name senegal dan kitchen
re in chiaro nathan
rain don't you put reina in there
miss mr casper question
oh
oh you mean skies of something ah half
arcadia
all right i'm done
i'm gonna go now remind me next time
to give you some um stories about the
arcade because skies of arcadia just
reminded me and i didn't talk about the
arcade uh experience at all
so
goodbye guys i'm gonna put up the
countdown video and uh the schedule
and a reservation for tomorrow but first
i shall eat
wait for my food first and eat
so thank you for watching thank you for
watching the whole series and the ending
and for suffering with me for another
zelda game it's fun though i love it and
thank you for sharing an experience with
me
and we're entering the week of kiwamo
birthday let's go
yaya
[Music]
love you
i mean my neck is broken
it's done
what the
what do you mean
oh
[Music]
i guess no that's just a lump that needs
to be
massaged out
time to go to a massage
[Music]
thank you
boom
[Music]