hello
this is me again welcome back to another
cheering guide this time for my original
song
sparks yay
well let's see how that one's gonna be
like you will once again need light
sticks so get your light sticks ready
okay
sparks
clap
do
oh
[Music]
do we do it
let's get to it
way from side to side don't stop don't
stop just go your own way
wave to side to side
keep up keep up and never be afraid wait
wait keep on living
don't stop just go your own way
hey
[Music]
wait
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
keep up keep up and never be afraid
club club club
wave
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way
keep up keep up and never be afraid
[Music]
keep on waving
good job everybody so basically
throughout the whole course you're gonna
be waving you can't even you can take
down the the light sticks if you if you
don't have any that's also okay you can
in theory even take the towel but
basically you're just waving for the
whole chorus and then you stop every
time it's like don't stop don't stop you
know
okay
looking forward to seeing you vibing bye
bye