[Music]
so
okay
hello
hello oh my god the llamas are making
really disgusting noises in the game
hello
yeah i everybody stream for
a couple of days
thursday
friday saturday sunday
four days
right yeah for i mean that was one small
member stream
but that wasn't
uh
you know that wasn't quite a proper
stream and many of you didn't see it
mm-hmm um
i have apples
today's snack for the stream will be
apples
[Music]
um
thanks guys hello yeah it's um
yeah 47 minutes of a stream does not
really count as a stream in kiwawa world
wasn't even an hour so
aki mentioned
apple equals aki mention i see icsd yeah
but four days uh
[Music]
is usually something i try to avoid not
streaming for two days is something i
try to for more than two days it's
something i try to avoid
um
[Music]
but yeah
it was basically kind of a tiny vacation
um
i will tell you a little bit about it
today
i suppose i was raining
i uploaded a little video at least i
couldn't prepare too much content
i was hoping to maybe stream publicly
once but
honestly i was
like too busy and exhausted
um
so i couldn't really stream properly but
i did have that 1m turkey video
did i sound like a turkey or what hmm
let me put some water oh my god you'll
answer in the meantime
you answer me
[Music]
i usually i make this sound
and you guys say oh you sound like a
turkey but i do that sometimes even when
i don't try to sound like a turkey and
um
you guys told me oh you sound like a
turkey but
then i was like researching because
obviously uh when i make a video like
that i want to do a proper impression
you don't know i want i want to be
professional so i did a turkey noise
research and i realized it's not quite
blue they're actually they sound like a
different animal that i recently
did a video of uh imitated they sound
more like
they sound they sound like what was that
um
what was the previous one that i did
because they sound like that
they sound very similar they also make a
weird noise like that what was my
previous one adult
yeah they do sound like a dolphin maybe
i should do a dolphin one
a penguin yeah i thought they sound a
little bit like like my penguin
impression
so i i took some creative freedom and
added my personal gobble gobble
to it
you know
just so it's not exactly the same as the
penguin one but now you've made me
realize i could make a dolphin one too
i could make a dolphin one but it's a
dolphin source of whales only that make
like really high pitched noises that
nobody here so i could make a whale
impression and just just be like
and i'm like you don't hear that well
[\h__\h] you i'm a whale
[Laughter]
dolphins click ah
do they not make those high-pitched
noises do they only click
whales are the ones
wow that was perfect right away you
heard that one
[\h__\h] disgusting llama noises in
minecraft
[Music]
oh man your mother broke oh [\h__\h] well uh
not not refunding that
[Music]
water well i'm glad uh to be back with
you guys i felt very guilty as you know
which is stupid but i don't know why i
just feel guilty when i don't stream for
so long um
oh [\h__\h] why did i move what did i move
what was that i don't know
i like to make that noise i'm turkey
we're playing minecraft
[Music]
uh my shaders i don't think they work
anymore wait why can't i not move oh
what
is it because
keyboard yeah okay
uh
no shaders it looks like [\h__\h]
[Music]
but let me put in at least some music
hey mr musical
[Music]
i'll just be the radio how about that
oh
was that loud that was loud i think
not so well for me but probably louder
for you
[Music]
we'll listen to this for a while
ah i put all my stuff i think in these
boxes
did i wait that's not um
i i hope i i i know that when we
is that myself
definitely part of my stuff right ah
comex
uh when when our server was updated um i
put some stuff
wait this might be my stuff
[Music]
how do you wear it again
what's the shortcut to wear it i put
some stuff here and there because uh we
were told that it might disappear if we
don't put it somewhere you know because
of that weird update
what's the shift
[Music]
easy
so i think that's myself
at least it's something we can use yeah
dab strider yeah yeah we i had that i
suppose
and
[Music]
then let's go with two always have two
pickaxes because one is still touch
let's see if i still know how to play
minecraft
um
durability
the [\h__\h] is durability oh
but was it always written like that that
looks so new to me like having it
written like that in the white font is
it
it looks so new to me
suck that shovel
no
[Music]
put mending on your shield before it's
too late what shield where is my shield
maybe it is too late
oh without the market
uh
no
[Music]
you i is new
maybe
where did i put my shield hmm
to the question what are we doing today
i have the answer ah there it is
uh mending you want me to put manny on
it i'll think about it
but do i have an extra vending
um
i was i had some ideas and i bought
a certain scientific idea
might be the best
loyalty okay i was thinking how about
we just um
fix up uh
phoenixton phoenixton a little bit
uh more because i mean it's still kind
of like a rough state
right oh this i'm what i brought back
yeah yeah yeah cool yeah last time when
we got some
when we when we got these uh solos
without looking for them
hello hello hello yeah yeah hello
everybody
we're upstate four months yeah i'm here
it it works
uh it does what it's supposed to do
but
we might want to
you know
oh oh my panic attacks oh yeah right i
had another one
oh
efficiency
my never read pickaxe my beautiful baby
oh it's cushy
oh chiara x oh that's the real one
that's the good stuff ooh
here's my bose streams box
soon soon we'll have a new original song
and then we'll finally can say something
else and that's stream sparks
finally anything else i put it in like
all kinds of different boxes but i think
that's uh about it that should be my
most important
stuff that i had
at the moment when they updated
apple in my fridge
time to eat another apple
[Music]
stream something else yeah
oh
welcome fbi
please leave please leave kindly mm-hmm
[Music]
let's take some more laptops i don't
really know
um
at what stage
uh phoenix currently is so let's take a
look and decide what we should do
uh oh yeah food would be good though
although we can trade food uh we could
create food against um wool
uh
i put wool somewhere i saw wool
somewhere
we have some oh yeah this this i can
trade not so much just cause it's only
free
we can trade wool can we trade clay
balls why do i have too many clay balls
what was i gonna use all those cables
well what you gonna do with all that
clay all that clay inside your chest i'm
gonna make you
make you i don't know what what what are
we gonna make you
close with my clay my clay my clay my
clay my lovely little clay
bricks oh
oh
that's good because if we have a lot of
uh clay and a lot of bricks then we can
you know yeah thank you we can make a
we can use that yeah for making phoenix
them prettier
let me put the chat a bit closer to
my gamer
the block
there we go
uh all right
the closer
now
yeah i know it's awesome if i just
install optifine
uh the shaders would probably work again
but whatever
let's look at some
vanilla minecraft and see if i still
know how to play it back to the basics
the cat is that new i don't think i've
seen this before the cat died there was
a cat up there wasn't there maybe it
died because of the update
oh so many why are there so many wheat
seeds who left so many [\h__\h] weed
seats up there ah who thought this was a
trash can
who was that
i got it
oh mama totally broke up oh the cat is
there maybe that was a different cat
that died but at least we have a
different new cat here now move
mama totally wrote that huh
[\h__\h] off maybe it died because it was
always in the way hmm
back backwards okay i still know how to
get off apparently that's good
off of the boat uh fresh off the other
oh there we go
okay uh well we'll leave the boat here
let's go
down either was it always this slow
i suppose oh my god it's been so long
and go down shift yes don't burn your
feet don't burn your feet
okay
oh hello
so for example
uh
we could
like
get rid of this or like move it back one
block and then make it into another
house for these people
uh
here mostly everything is fine besides
this not being quite the same style we
could um
these ones we could change into these
ones
because the
these ones have apparently already been
replaced i doubt it was always quartz
before
yeah and then it would match a bit more
yeah
these ones
and um
see he doesn't have a job yet he doesn't
have a job yet either i brought some
lecterns that we can
put around
yeah we gotta make things more
consistent that way it won't look so
messy anymore
um
yeah okay and then here
let's see
i uh here we actually still don't have
many
traders many uh villagers right
dude wait
miller
he's still so cheap guys make a
checklist yeah okay okay okay okay
let's make a checklist
[Music]
stop opening and closing the door you
want to go in or do you want to go out
it's not that difficult
to decide
where the hell is my memo
i can't there it is
there it is
oh man
oh move house grow crops get sick find
fox go to pub cook with produce
[Music]
what game was that
find fox
go to pub
what game was that ah that was sims
it almost sounds like minecraft
just the thing we've cooked with
products and the pump
sounds weird but everything else
could have been minecraft
[Music]
a horse what house
um fixing
okay
uh and then
oh
more traders
and then
where elijah watering why
does that change anything
get rid of old houses
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah mending on mending
mending on
shield
okay
where when you where were you when
a house was killed
[Music]
push up
there we go
mending
shield
okay
for now this is what we'll do and i'll
tell you about my trip as well while we
do that
yes but first first
first okay so
we'll put it on
oh i'm actually i was about to ask you
guys no wait oh that's wrong
i was about to ask you guys where where
do you when do you put that on oh well i
was not correct with my first kiss
that was the correct one
it will work too in the offense
i'm gonna take up although these are not
mending
these are not mending anyway
okay
okay okay okay
um the rest is fine but how far is my
elytra okay
yeah okay stop opening the [\h__\h] door
let's go find the rule guys i wish the
wool guys would just come up here and
live here but okay
wait did they
no those are not the wool guys where's
the
where are the wool guys
[Music]
those are not the wool guys
you're not the woo guys
no but i need to bring some melons here
where where are at the wall guys
who let the wool guys out
oh you need some iron i i i'll try to
remember
uh to bring some iron for you
are they not in this district
let's see
oh oh oh
they're learning some stuff here another
hunger how long
where the [\h__\h] are the wool guys
maybe over here
you guys are not the ones
are you the whole guy you're a rule guy
oh
18 18-13
[Applause]
what does he not have his thingy
what do you
mean
what about those what about you did you
lose your no no oh he takes clay and
he's so cheap right now and i have a
[\h__\h] ton of clay guys
but i wanted to use it for bricks right
i don't want to use it for breaks should
i really be using it for something else
needs to restock or you can't reach you
should be able to reach it and he's like
oh i only have wait that's not his
workstation what is the wool workstation
where is the wool workstation
why is he here anyway
all right i guess he'll stay here it's
already really busy in here
anyone have a clay farm no but that
sounds useful
the clay is easy to get
now loom yeah on it there's uh there's
looms here
three moons
i guess uh he couldn't reach them
is uh any really nobody here because
then i'll take the loom stations away
and put them where they belong to
hello
oh hello
hello dude
you want to go back into the city
although that ain't happening
once you're out you're out
thank you guys for the super chat oh my
god i'll be reading super chats today so
the minecraft session itself i don't
know maybe it will be two to three hours
however long i feel like it's to be
okay you know what [\h__\h] it we're taking
the loom stations to
i know i want to i want the dude to be
over there the loom guy okay both time
it's boat time uh
i have a boat here
and they're sitting in the boat
oh [\h__\h] i hate that i hate moving them
because
i have to get rid of certain parts and
then i have to build them again
and make sure they're not escaping all
right now they're going to sleep soon
though where you the balloon guy yeah
you're the one guy wait uh here uh boat
boat boat oh yeah he's in the boat i go
no i go in the boat not you
okay okay dude let's go let's go where
are we going uh
what's an easy path to get you over
there
um yeah the walled off you know yeah i
know
uh
can everybody go to sleep so you don't
walk into my boat
hello meow can we go here
up the stairs now
ah [\h__\h]
i need help
i wish i had someone to play minecraft
with me who could help me right now who
could like get rid of this while i'm in
the boat
[Music]
minecraft
if someone wants to help
i'm taking volunteers
[Music]
okay i'll sit in the vc
let's see if someone comes
probably not
probably not like the other girls do
that sometimes
uh
and but they um
you know they do it at times where i'm
sleeping or where i'm supposed to be
sleeping so
i usually don't join them and nobody
joins me because i am also
streaming at a time where they don't
really want to participate i suppose
but okay one can hope right one can
one can help
i i'm hoping for
replies but this i would like to have
help immediately
come on let's do a praying circle guys
i want to put this guy away so nobody
gets into the [\h__\h] boat
if i put
if i put him here do you think somebody
will get into the boat don't get into
the boat
are they like attracted by a boat just
as they are attracted by uh
i will
oh [\h__\h] the cats can get into it too
can't they
um
[Music]
ask the id girls oh
you know what i'll hide him
story isn't it
okay this way nobody will get into the
boat right probably
wool house
it's it's inna's day off today i don't
want to force her but i'm sure if she
sees the message and feels like joining
then she'll join
uh
close it from down below
okay they can still jump on it oh yeah
right [\h__\h] okay let's make it one more
higher
orange house
oh i'm making my blue house because he's
a wool guy i did that i didn't do that
on purpose
all right
oh what are all these people okay well
let's start with this house then because
we're right here let's start with this
one
and let's go to the very beginning a
very nice place to start
the doctor
abc
okay
mr wool yeah
lightning's about to turn oh no no
no there's much higher built like we
should worry about this one
my mommy and did her best to build a
tree there
which if anything we should we need to
worry about that one
and let me eat some more apple
[Music]
what
why would i visit crony's bunker
why would i need to do that
how does that help me
[Music]
oh you guys are just like herder oh it
would be so funny if she checks out
crony's bunker that we've already seen
but we just want to see her reaction to
it
because haha so funny right okay i see
no i don't care
i don't really care i don't really care
about it
[Music]
uh
okay so
i'll take this you guys aren't using
that
you guys are free i guess so i don't
need to worry about you guys i'll just
open this and then close it here i guess
the beds are mine why do you not want to
sleep in those anyway
are you sure
okay bye-bye
why did they leave now
where are you going you don't like this
broken house anymore
okay so let me tell you guys
oh hello
should we make it the goalie's house
you're welcome to live in it yeah just
don't get in my way because i'm i'm
scared of hurting you
you can't live here but can you for now
just go somewhere else
no
yeah hurry
how do you even pronounce it
i wanted to tell you guys about my uh
absence
are you guys interested in it
should i tell you guys about it the
house should be like that otherwise my
mom is gonna get mad
[Music]
yes
yes no okay why are you here if you're
not interested
and this is
uh
deep slate bricks i'm sure we still have
them
deep slate cobble deep side cobble this
deep slime deep sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
how do i make deep sleep do i'm can i
make it look a couple deep sleep
i can't say it
where is the thing here this one right
can i make it like this couple i need um
i need a deep slight bricks
okay
nice
is that was that a waste i hope not
okay okay okay okay okay
so
um
we will
[Music]
put sorry i'm so focused i'll tell you
when i'm less focused
go go away
is this
maybe that's too close
we'll build it here
okay
sorry now you're not in it anymore holy
[\h__\h]
it's so red over there
deep slight cobble works the same as
regular cobble
gobble gobble gobble i don't know what
you're telling me what are you trying to
tell me
i'm it's about to look guys
i'm trying to recreate something like
this you know
although this is a mix too
do you play bricks and cobble deeply now
okay and let's take some more cobbles
and then let's do like the outlines with
the deepside brick and the inside with
the cobble no yeah with the cobbled one
and then the second floor maybe maybe
like this maybe maybe maybe maybe
um
cobbled cobbled here it is maybe we need
this too
deep slate
cobblestone wall we need that do we need
that i don't know
[Music]
build wall first i don't know what is
this one
deep slate towel
[Music]
that's not why do i have a cobblestone
wall what are we using the cobblestone
wall for deep slate tie wall we need a
deep slate
time time tile wall
there we go
11.
[Music]
okay
deep slate tile wall why are these words
so difficult to say all of them
okay okay okay
then
actually we don't need this either
and
um
yeah then we get rid of this and this
and
this and uh but there will be a door
here no no no we already have a door to
this area we don't need a door
and then jump down down
down perfect
my mom will not be triggered thankfully
because i'm i used the right
the right
uh fence welcome back to thank you
well it's been i know like if you say i
was gone for four days maybe it doesn't
sound like so much but it definitely
felt like a lot didn't it
sorry guys um
i also didn't really tell you guys ahead
of time uh
where i was going because well
i didn't i didn't want it to be a public
knowledge until afterwards for you know
privacy's sake
and thank you for the rest of the chat
thank you
i think you guys can understand that but
i felt very very
um
guilty about it because like i knew i
was gonna be gone for like three to four
days but uh
i wanted to tell you guys why but i i
couldn't quite tell you so i was being
kind of like
oh i'm so busy this show in this week so
i don't
well know
can't make a schedule this week please
understand and like i wanted to tell you
the proper reason but you know
i couldn't
go
on
[Applause]
yeah i had to keep you guys in the dark
but i felt so bad about it i didn't want
to tell you guys until the very end but
i ended up kind of telling you guys in
the member stream because i couldn't
hold it back anymore
i don't care about breaking the glass
okay
what um to what
three to four days
[Music]
tomorrow oh we need the floor too
although let me look at let me look here
how is it working here
that's a block right
mm-hmm
so uh-huh not on the door
we don't need um
the slabs we just need um
not a hotel wait wait wait which one was
it
cobbled right that looks like cobble to
me
okay
okay okay
so
[Music]
a couple couple
okay
i went
uh with some friends
i went to an anime convention
germany
yes that's why i was gone
oopsie i need i need
how far do i need it
why is this here anymore
okay let's do it like this
no it was not joking me
is in the first week of june i think
yeah
um
yeah there's a there's an event in
in
close to munich
you guys probably have heard of munich
before
there's an event there
and that i've been to many times when i
was younger
or before hollow
[Music]
yep close wait what did i say
what did they call it they call it
moonshine
what
munich close to munich
[Music]
never heard of it what you never heard
of munich
you never heard of milk i did say munich
okay you never heard of munich in uh
italian slap okay
never heard of munich
in germany
what
pretty
well-known city though
[Music]
so like this we'll make a house like
this we'll give it a weird shape too
like this
okay
uh
hmm
yeah i guess we'll make it close to the
fence okay no problem
will we though
no we won't
[Music]
pretty famous place yeah yeah it's in
bavaria
it's the biggest city
or like the capital of bavaria
and i really like the city it's close to
austria so it's not too far
it's
it's pretty easy to get to as well from
austria so
they have this
[Applause]
[Music]
not huge but also not small
something in between convention there
and it's called animals
yeah yeah yeah
and
actually hasn't been held for the past
two or three years because of you know
what
um
so this time was the first time in a
long time
that animal happened again
so that was pretty special
um
you know what we'll do that differently
[Applause]
and it was actually
always one of my
favorite conventions
um because
[Music]
because
like the the event location
is like um
it's like a
i mean of course there's like like a
normal venue there
but me and my friends will never go
inside i mean we're not we usually never
go inside of conventions
it's pretty normal here i know for like
american conventions that's not so
common
but
it is it is pretty common um
here because most of our conventions
have like a big outside location too
so people like to chill outside
and you don't even need a ticket for
that
and for this convention in particular
it was
um
especially
good because uh
because they have like a a big big open
space
um
a big open space
uh
like with grass and uh it's like in
front of a huge cathedral
cathedral or church
oh close that what's a closed up
is it a cathedral or church i think it's
a cathedral or or not neither one of
those
closed up monastery yes a monastery
that's that was it um
cloister
it's a cloister and a monastery the same
thing
i never i don't think i've ever heard
the word cloister before but it's so
uh close to the word clothes
[Music]
cloisters are in monsters not a hodor
isn't it a pokemon
um
[Music]
we should build it so that this stuff is
already inside so i don't have to move
it anymore or
we'll make a little
outside area like this uh attached to it
yeah we couldn't do that
oh dear so first let's first build the
house
okay okay
so it's there's like a monastery uh aka
cloister so uh yeah and that in front of
that there's a big like garden not in a
garden but like a mix of a garden and a
park
so
people really like to hang out there you
know
i mean like a window there what do the
windows look like over there
[Music]
okay
yeah it's really cozy
and uh
[Music]
it's really cozy and and it's perfect
for
picnics
[\h__\h] wrong block
can't play the block game anymore it's
perfect for picnics everybody at this
convention everybody basically
chills on the grass and just yeah eats
snacks and
yeah just hangs out you know
so that's also what i always liked about
it
look what
what
yeah yeah we touched grass yeah so i
actually touched grass
i know it's incredible it felt
it felt uh very refreshing to be
touching grass again for the first time
in a long time
[Music]
yeah okay
ew i know i know i know you you you
make a door here i suppose
door is like this not a little
door door and then another door
oh
do we have a door somewhere
can i use it there's the iron door i
don't want to use the iron door
[Applause]
no not a door
one door
maybe we'll just do one door
one door two door three door
[Music]
it reminds me of i had a really stupid
uh
uh german brain empty moment um
[Music]
during my car ride back i was i was on
driving back home with uh
i was third wheeling a couple again
actually
and we were driving by a place
uh or through a place that
was called i think dwarf
or something like that
and we were laughing about
it being called that because dwarf means
village in
german and the village is literally just
called village
so we were making fun of that and uh i
made some comments about
um
oh no no no no it was called dolphin
it was called dolphin uh
which sounds like village plus like kind
of like
village
villages you know let's just say
villages e-e-s okay let's let's
translate it like that for context
because
um
i was like oh ha ha ha ha ha i suppose
i suppose
[Applause]
that's weird i feel like i've never
heard the
the
[Music]
the plural for the word village in
german
before because
the villages sounds so new to me
um
i said that with dorphin
and
then
we had a moment in the car a moment of
silence of thinking moment wasn't the
limit okay
and then and then
and then someone says
what what do you mean
the plural of village is religious and
i'm like oh
nevermind shut up of course i've heard
the the plural of village before
nevermind that's why it sounds so
unfamiliar because it was not the actual
plural of it
yeah so it happened the same way in
german i was like oh that's funny
dolphin sounds like uh
so weird to me i don't feel like i've
ever heard the plural for a dolph before
and they were like uh kewala [\h__\h]
there's a cat in there quiet it's
literally derp fair not dorffin
yeah
i was like okay that makes a lot of
sense now
but then why is dolphin
called dolphin i don't know it sounds
weird
oh god i don't know how to do this house
uh it should be like
this
and then
what do we do about this area
[Music]
what's the floor like over there the
floor the floor
[Music]
cobbled cobbled cobbled and outlined
with
the brakes okay
[Music]
dolphin no not not quite
and
cobbled so should we do it like
here
replace these
[Music]
put this back here
did i just hear a monster
i hear
monsters but they might be far away they
always sound so close even though they
aren't
did someone spawn somewhere
did you hear it too it might be
underground
all right uh where was i where was i
huh
where was i
[Music]
oh yeah so i was talking about the event
right
[Music]
and
i just said quite a while ago to go
there actually quite a while ago like
really quite a while ago
this is not enough space
[Music]
i built it too small kind
i need of space i need to think in
minecraft sizes
everything needs to be be a bit bigger
unless
no no no no
just move all of this one more block to
that side
um
now i'm going to get rid of this one
make this a window okay okay okay okay
third wheeling a couple yeah both on my
way to the convention and my way back uh
home
uh i was third-wheeling a couple but it
was a different couple i drove uh with
different people each time
yeah it's interesting to observe these
couples
in how they uh you know
take care of each other and how they
interact with one another
very narrow hodo moments
no
i'm always bird wheeling
couples i don't know
oh literally always first why why i
don't know what i don't i don't have
many uh single friends they're all a
couple
hmm
[Music]
i need food oh my god i need food
is there food somewhere
an apple that's funny because i have an
apple too
in real
life stay the same really
oh there's uh remember those emeralds if
i ever ask for emeralds there's emeralds
there
[Applause]
[Music]
no food
oh
really oh it's those people they're
really loud
[Music]
and i'm going to continue
enemy at the gates attack
raise your balls
[Music]
right now
please give me food
[\h__\h] you go back to sleep i can make
food you guys are not really working on
these fields anyway are you guys
i'll just make bread how do i make bread
[Music]
was this not it really
okay
do i need more than that
[Music]
i'll make some bread
three in a row
there's not enough things that you can
make with the two by two
there should be more
[Music]
welcome to the wheat fields mother
i have a list of things i wanted to say
let me open my list because otherwise
oh
otherwise i i have like no
no idea what i'm talking about
[Music]
where's my notes where's my notes
where's where's my note where did i put
that
what
pretty sure i wrote a note on this phone
memo memo memo
memo
no wait no i actually didn't run it on
my phone
i wrote it on my pc it's on my desktop
it's a file named tangents
let me try to remember someone i wrote
something about the car i wanted to tell
you guys about the third wheeling the
clutch
um
oh god see my brain whenever i start
streaming it's just it's just suddenly
empty
uh i told you guys about the picnic
stuff
uh
[Music]
oh
i'm writing it down
anyway uh okay remember one
stream of brain
arigato
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
what's another one
ah
um
[Music]
what's another one what's another one
what's number one what'd you know
no my tangents are pre-recorded no
[Music]
objection hearsay
one
oh do i want to say that i'm not sure
oh it's never one
um maybe i'll think of some more and
tell you guys another in another stream
but for now
[Music]
um
okay
okay okay
i have some tangents
okay then um
i'll say first uh because this matches
with what i've said previously
i told you that people like to just
chill outside right
so in previous years
uh
i would i would usually just
sit on my jacket or something but
i have a
cute picnic blanket so i actually
brought my own picnic blanket this time
which was so genius because
my picnic blanket
was so popular okay everybody was
sitting on my picnic blanket
i felt like a really great host what is
this why is that there
i felt like a really good host
what was that for again
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i feel like i was like uh
how do you say
ancient like magnetic um
uh
oh there's melons pulling pulling a lot
of people towards me like i was a magnet
i was a magnet for people yeah it was a
magnetic force my picnic blanket was a
magnetic force
my picnic blanket was cute too
[Music]
is not making bread
[Applause]
it's not making bread still
it's like this
ah finally hallelujah
[Music]
okay
and that way i finally got some use out
of my picnic blanket too which was
really good and happy yeah and
i felt like
i was the god of picnic
because i also brought snacks this time
i usually would just eat everybody
else's snacks but i brought my own
snacks too
i brought my own snacks i brought my own
picnic blanket and i was big braining
because i was using uh my furnace to
bring hot tea because it was relatively
cold there's another thing i wanted to
say it was pretty cold throughout the
weekend
uh
so
i was so genius i filled up my furnace
with hot tea at the hotel
and then uh
i would bring that to the
to the
uh
convention yeah and and i had hot day
for the whole day
magical what a genius oh my god
[Music]
genius
i'll do it like this
i don't have space you [\h__\h] the snow
yeah on one day it even kind of rained a
little bit but
it was fine because like originally it
was supposed to rain much more
but it didn't this is always always the
thing
with this event they always say it's
gonna rain but then it doesn't it ends
up just being just fine
what what was the cute pronunciation
what did i say
let's see
it didn't really
rain we don't even call that rain
it's called
kneeson what's what sneezing in english
like
gently
dripping
no not dripping
drizzling yeah yeah it was basically
just drizzling but i was kind of worried
about it because um the weather forecast
was like
uh
yeah it was it was like really worrying
it said it would rain all [\h__\h] day
but it really didn't so hallelujah
what is this
[Applause]
[Music]
tile wall deep slate tile wall
deep slate towel do we have do i have
anything of that oh yeah
five of them
[Music]
how do i build that
like that how does it end up looking
like that
there are
blocks one block
two blocks
like here maybe
[Music]
which block that block
here oh it's snowing oh my god
but i need one more here
ah
i hate building
there's so much brain work
oh my god there's so much snow can you
like turn that off
[Applause]
and then we'll connect it with
that stuff over there oh my god i barely
see [\h__\h]
i barely see anything
i have to move this one
kind of uh
no no no no the rest is fine
uh
don't
no [\h__\h] the snow
okay
like this
[Music]
i know the other one the other one is
open so let's keep this as an open
place yeah
so you can go like here i suppose but i
don't like how it's so tiny here there's
like no space
let's keep oh no that should be closed
sleep to stop the is it my tummy okay
let's sleep
it looks like
good night time for an apple
an apple
a day keeps
the chocolate away
i already looked for it but i want
iron bars well i want bars to be easy to
make we have a lot of iron probably in
other places
[Music]
[Applause]
have you guys seen some iron
i want to see iron
are you guys triggered by my
pronunciation
they will never change
i'll go to the iron farm
i went by
tattoo
[Music]
that's how crony pronounces it crony
says it like that too
what what isn't her first language
english
[Music]
she speaks fluent english why does she
say it like that
maybe maybe my way of pronouncing it is
not so wrong after all
maybe i was wrong right all the time
there's no way crony would be wrong with
something right
crony is a little bit special
uh huh
she's perfect so she can't be wrong
[Music]
oh wait i would be saying the name iron
man is completely wrong too right oh
oh
[Music]
i hope that wouldn't trigger her
if i said iron mouse
instead of i i iron iron mouse
see i could do it if i force myself but
it's very unnatural to me
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
um
is that enough for now
what did i need it for anyway i have
four for the
fences okay okay
[Music]
i would mouse would probably like it
really
iron iron mouse i heard
i was told okay so
one of my
friends that i went to the convention
with really likes iron mouse
uh and watches her streams
and uh
he told me that he
heard her
say something
about wanting to interview me
because we both have talk shows
i didn't know that
she wanted to interview me
but apparently she said that
and that that was monster not really
yeah she has a talk show and i figured
yes she's if she didn't ask me until now
she's probably too shy to ask me
oh you guys know about it too oh
oh my god the drama
are you guys aware i already had a
collab with uh manners before
how does that make you feel
how does that make you feel oh
okay we got what we needed i'll make a
wait should i make it in here can i make
it in here
let's try
[Applause]
uh
iron
box
get rid of those no one needs that
16 116 is enough
[Music]
maybe a bit more just in case for other
buildings too if we get some left over
okay
okay now we can do the windows it's
starting to look like something
uh-huh it was i think two
too high and then actually it should be
the whole building should be one more
block higher because there needs to be a
ceiling
oh
yeah let's do it like
yes
hi you're already enjoying this huh
you're welcome i'm extending your uh
place your
get a new home
[Applause]
[Music]
where was i anyway what was i talking
about what was i talking about
[Music]
i was talking about the weather the
weather was okay it was pretty cool
though i was i was freezing a lot uh
but kiwa was strong
one was strong so kiwamo
chihuahua didn't mind also
phoenix so
yeah
the cold never bothered me anyway you
know
[Music]
it's funny how some
i shouldn't be singing uh
disney
okay bedtime i had some beds left over
there you go
and
the grindstone and the smoker
what what job is
this one for
[Music]
let's put this here
okay it's kind of um
tight here but that's okay smoke is for
butchers oh okay then it should not be
in this area
all right all right
uh we're missing the ceiling
uh which looks like
blocks and then slabs but we don't need
to make it the exact same way
i don't know if i want to do this whole
second floor today but
we'll just finish it off with the
ceiling now
okay let's see what we have we have
this
[Music]
oh we have some of these
i'm gonna use what we have to because
you know there we go that's perfect
okay that will be enough that will be
just fine um
okay
um blocks blocks to those you guys are
in the way i'm still building this be
patient yep
building without
the ladders as always
oh
almost go up here
yosho by the way i really missed my cats
but but they were so happy to see me
again
[Music]
when i came home i actually um i had the
the couple that i
uh
was droven home by
um i had them come up with me so i could
uh
get some help with carrying all my [\h__\h]
that i brought with me
and the other reason was i did want them
to admire my cats
so they came up with me and then i had
them look at my cats and raid my cats
and they gave an obvious 10 out of 10.
yeah especially the girl she was
excited about my cats understandable
understandable
they also liked the raccoon yeah
i never noticed this before
it's fascinating
yeah
[Music]
really well i never jump on bed so i
never noticed
what's going on
okay
[Music]
there we go
and uh here and
this area will be open
what does it look like here again
let's just open up but it's like uh
of those
[Music]
it's okay if i can't perfectly recreate
it right
and then
we build
[Music]
and i felt i think my cats were cuddlier
than normal
when i came back which to me tells me
they missed me
so cute
so cute my baby babies i'm so happy to
see them
my fluffy cats
fluffy babies
they missed me i think so
i do think so oh oh hello
oh hello i didn't say it was ready yet
but okay you do you i do
want some
something to climb down on now after all
do i have nothing
i know i have some in my home are there
six six is enough
okay
yeah if you don't mind the construction
noises then that's okay with me i guess
okay
so
uh
actually i left on thursday night
and
no not night like in the afternoon so i
kind of wanted to do a quick stream on
first day but then i was so busy with
packing that
uh and cleaning my apartment too that i
ended up not really being able to do it
unfortunately
wrong way i wanted the other way
and then we drove to the convention and
and and and on the way we had some we
had some dinner at like a really random
place somewhere on the road when we were
already in germany
uh and you know what i had for the very
first time um i ate
grave salmon grape salmon yeah you guys
call it craved salmon too
i need to do it from outside
to get the right direction
how was that well you know you know i
don't really like raw
fish
um
like sushi and all that
what the [\h__\h] was that
[Music]
all the dragons around
i heard a really screeching noise what
the [\h__\h] was that there's nothing in the
sky
oh a fox oh
oh
i can't place it
can't place it
they're not the fox
those are not foxes either
okay whatever we'll do it like this
and and yeah i had some pasta
with maybe one more outside had some
pasta
with
goat cheese sauce
and
grape salmon which was
pretty good i must say i i was worried
about eating raw salmon because like
grape salmon is like
pretty much raw
yeah
so i was worried about that but all all
was good i was able to eat it just fine
i don't know how to build this i really
suck at building oh yeah smoked yeah
it's smoke but that's basically raw
it's basically raw
it looks raw it feels feels raw was that
not is that not would you not say it's
raw it's pretty much raw
yeah it was smoked though
[Music]
but i was i was able to eat it fine so i
i eat i ate something new and that's a
big accomplishment
[Music]
[\h__\h]
why
why did i never like this it was only a
kiss
i want it like this this is too much to
ask
[Music]
that one worked
[\h__\h] hate roofs
that works
[Music]
yeah placing stairs is always always
annoying
always testing my patience yeah no come
on
on my way back we had a really good beat
so mama mia was a good pizza
you have no idea mamma mia the pizza
i had tuna pizza and i told my friends
that you guys always always react like
what the [\h__\h] when i mention tuna pizza
you're like
why do you mean doughnut pizza that
sounds like a crazy idea and they were
like no they sound crazy for saying it's
a crazy idea tuna pizza is really good
yeah
apparently you guys uh don't think it's
so common
at least uh n a people
you need to try it it's so good
yeah it was hand tossed i was watching
the lady hand toss the pizza
and oh my god it looked so cool
[Laughter]
i wanted to take a video but i felt like
i should ask before i take a video and
then i was too shy to ask
unbelievable kiwa too too shy
to do something
[Music]
oh hello
i need more stairs eventually
um
[Music]
onion zoo
well at least we almost have a ceiling
there we go
and we need some light
wait how do they how did we make light
in there
probably lanterns
oh no oh okay
i'll do it the same way
see it matches though it fits in
oh i was able to copy the style properly
oh my god
[Music]
what is the mamma mia
thanks for the membership message thank
you
oh
[Music]
you guys are so cute you missed me so
much
i'm not surprised
which is on the roof okay okay okay
i'll do it like this and
the [\h__\h] the box is crazy
[Music]
i wanted to recreate the thing where
it's uh bricks
but like between the windows
[Applause]
[Music]
what is this inconsistency my mama is
100 watching the stream right now
mama how what is this inconsistency how
am i gonna copy your style of building a
house if you're not doing it
consistently either
okay well then create the freedom i'll
do it my way then i'll do it like
i'll keep it like this and whatever
no this triggers me
this actually triggers me so
we'll do the cobbled one
shut up fox
okay
i don't like this though i want some
difference here
also i don't want snow to be here it's
not gonna grow anymore now right
growth snow grows
snow grows i don't think so
and then we'll have some here
and uh yeah
my mom says you call that texturing
sure mommy
uh-huh i think you just ran out of the
right blocks
[Music]
i need to fix the roof
uh
how to roof
[Music]
mind this could work
yeah okay
when i say before i mean the time where
i built a shrine with moment
there was a lot of roofing
there as well
i need more stairs
[Applause]
i'm running out of them
i have more
[Music]
something
else i'm running out of it
basalts
[Applause]
[Music]
i wonder if i still have some in my base
i'm looking for cobbled deep slate
it's like deep play deep slide
keeps playing
oh my god that's shrimp
wow
[Music]
there we go
least it's easy to find yeah but i don't
feel like going to the
never
yeah it's never
today
all right
well the conrad road trip was fun i kind
of missed that we we used to
go to a lot of conventions
by car
sometimes it would take like 12 hours or
something
but it was fun because we would listen
to like
some anime songs that was that's why i
tweeted out set of notes
uh openings
there we go oh
[Music]
they don't know openings are just so
good
that's why i tweeted that out
because we were listening to it in the
car
the sound facility was out
it was actually my
my wish i said i want to listen to some
zero notes guy i'm gonna put on the xero
note sky my openings
and then we listened to a couple of them
and i was like ah yeah buddy they don't
know my psycho
tycoon
is that enough is that we have
bricks
[Music]
a south nice ceiling texture oh
but it didn't i didn't use brazil than
the other one so
[Music]
yeah that's anime
was that always like that what the [\h__\h]
i was so shocked that it fell down
oh oh i can already see kyle carrot
making a
a clip out of my [\h__\h] tangent going
on for hours again once it's always like
that what the [\h__\h] is this
you can't go up without a jump are you
for real
no way
[Music]
it's so cold okay
gonna have a rough time yeah
what do you mean
yeah i can see cow current making
another video putting my tangent
together so if you guys um
just came somewhere in the middle to the
stream and you feel like uh i wanna hear
the full story but what the [\h__\h] it's
like all over the place
then you
should wait for kyle carrots uh
take on it
[Music]
rachel we're gonna fix this
when is it that difficult what the [\h__\h]
is that though why does it why does it
look like that
why does it look like that
oh there we go never mind
perfect was that difficult but there's
not much space here but if i walk up
here
ah that's kind of annoying
[Music]
oh well
we need a fence here
should i build the fence now
do i have like a wooden fence in here
i have wood
lots of dark old oak but we're not going
to use that
[Music]
fence
and it sticks [\h__\h] sticks
ain't nobody got time for that
[Music]
sticks here
no sticks
no sticks but this could be useful
as well
okay
what i came here for
what did i come here for
[Music]
and the bed i can't even use
my mom wrote me there's enough deep
slate in phoenix and well i didn't find
it listen to some other boxes outside of
the deep slate area
my mom says there's enough deep sleeping
phoenix
if she says that it must be true
okay let's go back then
and
remember
are you sure
okay
it's not the one you're using though
[Music]
let it snow let it snow
can't hold it back
that was not the right lyrics
[Music]
there was some
interesting noise while i was in the
water
okay hello i'm back oh you're trying to
get on the on the roof no no no no roof
is my area
okay
okay okay i got some more uh
no no you
i got some more of this
[Music]
we could just use these as placeholders
we can still like
have
uh something else replace this because
you won't see it anyway probably after
i'm done with the roof
now
[Music]
i hate roofs
i hate roofs i hate roofs i hate roofs i
hate roofs
i hate buildings
[Music]
i want it here
build it here
[Music]
don't don't say it don't say it don't
say it don't say it don't say it
don't say it don't say it don't say it
it was wrong it would have been wrong
anyway
no saying
no you saw nothing
saw nothing
[Music]
uh
where was i aiming
there we go
there we go i'm running all of them
ah i have more
no panic
only calm
roof
this roof is looking fine
i think i might keep it flat like this
for now because we might end up building
a second floor anyway eventually today
[Music]
okay okay
okay there we go
and
we'll have these up here
all right all right uh what else am i
missing is pretty much done
i could make a different floor though if
i feel like it no we'll keep it like but
i'm kind of on the different floors
and i want some differentiation
between the house and the outside
because it's not as obvious as it is
here
[Music]
would it be okay to use wool inside or
do you think my mom will kill me for
that
[Music]
you think she'll kill me
because i have some nice looking gray
wool
i could use basalt too but
will my mom kill me
like it won't even look that bad
my mom says you use wool okay
we got the okay
it's okay
i mean
it's like a carpet it's like the inside
is carpeted so why the hell not these
people in this house they just feel like
they want a carpeted floor why not let's
give it to them there we go beautiful
and then outside we have the the
proper one oh but you know what i'll
actually go one step further
and put this here okay okay oh beautiful
oh oh oh oh wonderful
it's kind of cold in here probably
though
wait why don't we just close
this
because they can go outside and then
what do you think do you guys think it
would look better if i would close this
because they can reach by going outside
and going here
isn't it closed over there too basically
it is
oh yeah yeah yeah
there's some bricks here though oh for
the ah
[Music]
a double doors
dumbbell doors
dumbbell doors naruto
close it add extra bed
[Music]
close it
double doors
[Music]
good extender up
oh yeah
extending roof
oh nice
yo i know whatever
noisy you just woke up
[Music]
oh look at me
being an architect
wowzers
[Music]
what do you think about this what do you
think about this kfc oh my mom says i'm
doing great
mom's so proud i want to add some here
too
yeah yeah
we styling
oh what an architect
oh
[Music]
like this
oh not bad
ah oh maybe no no no not so much i felt
that so much
[Music]
i feel like it's too much
but it might look better once i have
[\h__\h] the snow once i have a second floor
difficult decision
[Music]
we don't have that hair ever
never mind
no extended roof
is that stairs
that's stairs uh
okay
we'll do it like
this
looks weird too
that's stairs too
no that's a slab
no that's stairs
[Applause]
i extended the roof here it doesn't look
like that here though
it doesn't look like this here
i want it to look the same but then
again then again
[Music]
those shield
i worked so hard to extend that roof man
and now i just got rid of it
[Applause]
[Music]
it looks nothing like the other hey okay
that's that's not true
it definitely looks like the other one
that's just mean
my mom says
it's necessary to have some variation
mommy
today
i like to listen to you rather than the
chat
today i like your opinions
nice okay okay
how about how about this
and then imagine having a second floor
on there that looks like this
then because now i think yeah the roof
suddenly looks too flat but if there's a
second floor it might look good
[Music]
we can look at it from a higher point of
view
oh one thing i remember that i wrote in
my tangent memo but i lost it was uh
oh
okay wait that's too high above
um
yeah my my physical therapy is still
ongoing so i went today as well um
but
the
the girl is gone
she's done she was done earlier
than me
oh the girl is gone i'm sorry guys she's
gone
yeah and today it was literally just
two really old
dudes and me
[Music]
no we didn't exchange anything enough no
no what is your problem
do we need that
does it look better without
no ah unless
[Music]
let me try something
about this
what about this is that better than
before
i think i like it
looks better looks the same it doesn't
look the same because it's not the same
how could it look the same when it's not
the same
i have no idea what you're talking about
you never know what you're talking about
small edge that's kind of true i mean
the whole
what's the word in english it's not
miranda
looks um
small anyway
[Music]
can you guys stop walking around here
how about this
whatever um
oopsie for now we'll just keep it like
that
and i'm gonna play some green stuff
because my mom said to play some green
stuff why do i have the green stuff i
don't have any green ah there it is
i have some dark leaves
not many
okay my mom put it right in here and
then lanterns
lanterns lanterns lanterns okay
how about uh
if i put it here they can climb up right
you don't want that
i guess
oh
ah on slabs
of [\h__\h]
can i stop
no
what is that
that's a slab
that's a slap that's a slab that's
why not
that's that works okay then let's not do
it here
i'll
and
why is this different anyway this is on
purpose
did my mom do this on purpose
what do you think
mom did you do this stuff on purpose
these little different ones
should i fix them
yes you're probably gonna say it for
texture
for texture but why can't i not place
anything
what if i
[Music]
slap
for texture mommy says for texture
but i'll i'll have to try something here
did it disappear because i didn't use a
scissor
okay
we'll leave it like that
[Music]
dammit i forgot about that
lanterns
but we can get more of that easily
lantern
[Music]
ah no i broke it
doesn't look so good let me get some
green stuff
um
[Music]
berries
oh but i don't have a scissor
wait i didn't bring a scissor
brenda
oh no
friend bye bye
at least now i won't have those
disturbing noises anymore in my head
there was an arctic [\h__\h] there once was
an arctic fox but you know what we
shouldn't bring the arctic rocks in here
anyway because i just saw a chicken up
there
we don't want the arctic fox to kill the
chicken right
right guys shouldn't you guys be
absolutely terrified by the sight of an
arctic box hmm
you guys think uh it will look weird if
i or
you think people will notice the
difference if i put a melon there
instead of green stuff i mean it is
green
it is green
where did my mom say that there was more
of the stuff i'm looking for
um
[Music]
i'm terrified by the side of your beauty
wow
wow okay
sorry for terrifying you
melon is just a fake bush
i agree
try them oh mommy says try the melon
now i think it will stand out too much
i'm glad you you want to try it but i
think we'll stand out too much is there
a scissor somewhere
mommy i have other leaves
[Music]
i've got some pretty asali leaves let's
put one here
[Music]
i forgot about them
now it's too
oh wow
this is good
why does it stand off like that
what if i put this here
that's okay
i think that's okay
bgm is killing me
what
you guys not want to hear that should i
change it is it too repetitive for you
guys are you guys sick of it i like it
though
okay let's change it
ah it's okay i understand i understand
that you know sometimes things get too
repetitive
if you focus too much on it
um how about
what about this one
[Music]
no
maybe
sounds like um
sounds like i'm on a farm
farm
farm discovery
[Music]
i like it it's kind of cute
i wanna put
no one ever goes back here but let's put
some stuff here too
[Music]
um
not good at recreating what my mom did
[Music]
[\h__\h] just did the same thing whatever
i'm sorry i know it hurts
[Music]
ah
yeah no i can't put it on the [\h__\h]
slab i know i know
let's put let's put wool there no one
will notice i just want the the below to
be dark
no one will know there's a difference
oh but there's the slab it will be a
different height
huh how did my mom do that
creative freedom got it
[Music]
creative free gum
let me try uh
let's get rid of this let's uh place
wait can i place a block on the slab
oh
you missed the old pigeon
nanda yo you don't like this one
you guys don't like this one
[Music]
that's that's an oof moment man
how about how about
what this
oh that's weird
oh no
tropical
doesn't quite fit what we're looking at
but
well i don't know how to recreate this
stupid
no it's okay we'll build
this here okay
okay that's cute
whatever it works
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
no one replied to my my minecraft
inquiry by the way
ah sad
that's okay
this is okay
[Music]
okay
okay let's move on let's just say this
is done for now or maybe
not
it's
done for now for now it's done
um
maybe put
uh
another bed there
maybe another one
[Music]
really shy you always let me actually
put the bushes
all back in here
for now
okay still missing a wall what do you
mean this is fine
this is okay
all right there we go
comfy there's more beds here now guys if
you need somewhere to
[Music]
okay okay we did that house uh
um
i also someday need to clean up the area
over there are there any important uh
traders villagers there right now i
wonder let me check otherwise i'm just
gonna
destroy everything
[Music]
jack being needy because they haven't
had enough of kiwa recently
oh i i don't mind you guys being a
little bit needy it's kind of cute
hello
kimmy kimmy schmidt is here
oh this is empty okay
[Music]
oh did this dude this dude is a diamond
move [\h__\h] move why are we having a
pajama party and no one's even sleeping
she has some oh fear is final falling
free boots we can't get uh we can't lose
this guy
and that's kimmy schmidt you have i'm
breaking unbreakable
[Music]
unbreakable
you have
power five
you got nothing
okay we want the power five
and her but i wanna do that when i have
some help because someone who i want
someone to just get rid of the wall is
why i'm boating them to their new
destination
let's sleep by the way
yeah this place is still very crowded
there's a lot of jobless people though
what's
[Music]
i want to love these people
yeah all my attempts of moving people
happened here this is this is what this
path was for
you know what i'll try to move kimmy
uh but which one is hers ah i actually
did i see i
this is kimmy's no i'm breaking two
yeah yeah i was so smart i actually
you know
put a sign here so i know which one it
is
okay
uh
boating time
this one i have more confidence with
okay
you need some patience though
kimmy would be going here
there is no one
[Music]
on the street okay that's good
uh is there another boat some i'll take
the one from up here
at least you have high ground yeah
that's why it's easier because i just
have to fall down rather than going
upwards that is that is the reason why i
don't want to do it um
oh my god that was scary i thought i was
gonna drown
no i'm not
i broke my elevator
[Music]
it still works now okay still works
easy
yes thankfully nothing is broken
this looks too open after all uh how
about
i think i saw this on the other side too
oh
how about oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh genius incoming
[Applause]
can you walk through here
yes
how about this
is that weird
maybe even
this oh
well that looks nice
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
hello
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay
that's the big brain tension we all know
love thank you
thank you wow
so sweet guys
yes yes
would you look at that
okay
how did i get to the other side before
can i do a big jump
no okay
give me are you kidding me you'll kill
me okay okay okay okay okay just can you
stop give me can we stop for a moment
stop for a moment stop give me give me
if i put it here there's a million
people who are gonna get on the
give boat
give me give me give me
can we come here yeah
um
[Music]
i need you
to get
oh you're following me nice come here
come here
no
follow me here here come here
over here
i have some bread
you want the bread right i know you want
it no not you
give me
[Applause]
oh i can't place it on here can i ah
give me give me give me give me
here over here
over here over here over here over here
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
come on it will be like titanic vacation
don't you want some why is she not
getting on the boat
no no no no no no no
why didn't kimmy get on the boat
what was wrong with the boat kimmy
i have a first class ticket for you
you you're right you're gonna be right
next to the captain you can look how a
captain
controls a boat isn't that interesting
is that not interesting to you
hey man
give me give me give me give me can you
come here
are you not going on the boat
hear me don't walk away from me
come here
come here come here come here give me
god
come here
come on come on come on you can do it
[Music]
you need to jump out no no no it worked
before
chuck doesn't have the answers come you
kill me
did you go there you are give me give me
give me give me give me give me give me
no no no no no no come back come back
hit me
i'll push you i'll push you
[Music]
can you not go that far please
step by step
[Music]
you're not the one i want
[\h__\h] kimmy
[Music]
see this is why i don't want to do this
kind of stuff on stream
it just doesn't go so well at least not
if you're alone if you're like two
people maybe it's a bit easier you can't
leash them
they're humans you can't leash them
whoever's saying leash them as far as i
know that doesn't work in minecraft okay
you can't leash humans
shut up
[Music]
oh it's raining gimme gimme gimme gimme
gimme if you get into the boat i'll i'll
lead you to a place without rain i
promise
yes yes we're getting closer
no no don't get you don't get into the
boat
you you get into the boat you no no no
no no no get into the [\h__\h] boat
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
hey
what are you mad because i'm taking
kimmy
you can come too
could you put our way it's because of
the [\h__\h] floor
oh you scared me please go away
[Music]
wait but
as long as i don't kill anyone he will
forgive me right
[Music]
don't forget after an hour
ah
[Music]
he forgot because i didn't hurt a
villager i just hurt him he's okay with
that
but now someone else is in the [\h__\h]
boat
how am i holding the
shield
when i
oh okay
um
you're making me
kind of mad
look fit
[Laughter]
who the [\h__\h] are you anyway you're just
a [\h__\h] fisherman
it's okay i'm not gonna hurt you
please forgive me please forgive me you
don't stand
mom says take a leash
you can't mommy you can't put a human on
a leash or you mean the golem
i can't put a human on a leash
let's sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
unleash the boat that sounds like so
much [\h__\h]
also i don't know what the hell i have
unleashed i'm gonna do it without a
leash
[Music]
i will take the boat again and hopefully
not hurt a villager in the process
i'm so scared
[Laughter]
okay can the other one walk away please
can you just walk away nothing's
happening here give me give me come here
come here come here
why from my girl
[Music]
um
let me try to tell you a story so
actually
um during my trip
uh
on
on the
on the saturday i was supposed to uh do
some um on sunday on sunday i was
supposed to do some work
um
for hola live ooh hello holo ryder
[Music]
um
but really really really really
early actually six a.m it would have
been at 6 00 a.m okay but
i i was just glad that it wasn't like
sometime
uh
during like in the middle of the
convention so that i would have to go
back to the hotel to do my work but
that's why i brought some of my
equipment i brought my laptop and i
brought my
[\h__\h] you kimmy i'm so done with you
where's mending
i brought my laptop and i brought my
my um
my microphone my blue yeti and i brought
my camera
so yeah i was ready to do work even
though it meant i had to get up really
early uh can't help it
need a hug
yeah
i was not looking forward to getting
upset early especially because on
saturday we after the convention we went
to have some dinner
and
i was
silky boy
um
[Music]
like already
thinking that uh it looks like i
i am
i'm not gonna get much sleep
yeah cause uh
i came back to the hotel at like half
past 11 p.m
i need a book
for the books
a bookshelf oh maybe maybe first of all
we need emeralds
um yeah half past 11 p.m and then i had
to
like do some preparation to sleep in the
first place which actually took quite
some time
i had some problems
um
so i didn't actually fall asleep until
like 1am
so
i
i would have had like four hours of
sleep
right
why am i here
i'm looking for emeralds i'm so confused
sorry see i can't tell a story
while i'm looking for something
i had emerald somewhere over there i
think
yeah and then and then after that you
know it would have been like three hours
of work and then i would have to get
ready for the convention and go straight
to the convention
um so i wouldn't have time wouldn't have
had time to take a nap after that either
so with four hours of sleep going to the
convention
i wasn't quite looking forward to that
but
yeah
it had to
happen worst case
so
i was just like all right let's get it
over with
so i
had an alarm
at 5
55 or so
and i woke up and i looked at my phone
and i was like okay [\h__\h] let's do this
let's do this i guess
and look at my phone and and
genma
my angel genma tells me
it was moved to a different date because
of a reason
and i'm like hello [\h__\h] lulu
i can't go back to sleep i'm saved
oh my god i was so happy i was like okay
i'm gonna immediately
fall asleep again because that was tired
as [\h__\h] where's shawn mendes now
what
where is he done
reap tide
where's sean where'd shawn go
yeah
yeah i was so happy so i tried to
quickly fall asleep
again but of course my mind said no
no
so it took me
another hour to fall asleep even though
i was so tired
i did hey where'd you go
there you are i couldn't
i could not
fall asleep
which was really bad
i just i don't know i was so tired but i
had so many thoughts in my mind
yeah it was pretty bad
all right so now we can take the mending
menu [\h__\h] down
[\h__\h] sucks
water never a good thing yeah you need
to be brain empty style uh how do you do
this again
how do you ah uh one of those um
bunk bunk tables right
table or enchanting table
table
so then
eventually i was i fell asleep but i had
to get up early anyway so i ended up
i ended up getting a little bit more
sleep but it was probably just
six hours total at the end which
for me
is really
not much at all because i'm used to
sleeping more like eight hours i used to
always need
um
nine hours of sleep so honestly now i'm
like why doesn't this work
okay
now i'm already much better than before
i need like seven and a half or eight
hours of sleep and then i'm happy
[Applause]
[Music]
there you go nice
for six hours was not so good so i was
still very tired throughout the whole
day
but it was better than just going to the
convention for four hours of sleep
hallelujah it was a miracle guys it was
a miracle i was so happy
never was i ever so happy before that uh
something with work got moved to a
different date
i average about five hours that's not
good
i mean even if you're used to it you
shouldn't be used to it
i wouldn't be able to do that
i can't average five hours no no no i
would be like okay i need to change
something in my life now where did my
bread go
where did my bread go i'm pretty sure i
didn't eat it all where did i put my
bread
and where am i
where did my bread go
[Applause]
i want to see the bread
they took my [\h__\h] bread
unbelievable
they took my bread
didn't they already take enough for me
so many hours of my life
huh ah i still have a boat
me back my bread
it's really not asking for much
[Music]
okay so i kind of wrapped my equipment
for nothing
except i was at least able to do the
memory stream
a little bit of a memory stream but
it doesn't count as a proper stream so
we're still doing the two member streams
uh in a row like one per week
this week and then next week this week
we're watching a movie and next week
we're gonna play gamer
we're gonna blog
so i hope you guys are looking forward
to that i need some of that yummy yummy
bread thank you very much
[Music]
thanks
what movie uh oh the galaxy movie
uh
the galaxy movie
something called again
hitchhikers yeah let me check us through
the galaxy
that's the one okay my last piece of
apple is really small
you know how i told you guys i had um
my first hello fresh order last week
i kind of uh [\h__\h] up let me not not
not necessarily me but
it was delivered on tuesday
but uh i was streaming like
all night right so until late in the
night in the night so i ended up
ordering something but
um
i cooked
one
meal
on wednesday
but then on thursday i already had to
leave right
and the meat
for one of the dishes is already
like
it shouldn't be eaten anymore
uh and it's not not the um
there's like minerals headphone kitem
and
and the meat was eat until
so
i shouldn't eat it anymore it already
yeah it's already spoiled so
i have
two dishes from one week that uh
well actually the one the one i can
actually make today i think the the
other one i should be able to make
because it's without meat and i think
the the rest
of the ingredients should be fine
but for the other dish it's just the
meat that one bad i think the rest i
could still eat so if i buy meat i could
make it and then tomorrow i already have
my second hellofresh
delivery coming in but i have a little
problem with that one too
what are we doing anyway
what are we doing oh yeah let's trade
let's trade wool where was the wool guy
okay
i think i was here
i have a problem with the national fresh
delivery too because
it's not sponsored no
and because um
you know it was
you know busy um uh
which
was kind of a good thing like me not
looking at my there you are no no you're
not
not looking at my phone for once was
actually a good thing
well at the farms
no no he was somewhere else
and i wanted to move him
but
uh my app told me please
make your decision until first day
evening uh of what you want to eat next
week
and then
i didn't make it in time because i
couldn't access the app and then
and then they decided for me and now two
dishes of the ones that are coming this
week are dishes that i don't like
because one of them has mushrooms i
think and the other one has um i think
shrimps and i don't like either of those
things
oh poor boy
[Music]
uh
that kind of songs
i will try to make it anyway um just by
not using
uh
the shrimps and the mushrooms but
they're kind of important ingredients in
those dishes
i don't like shrimp sorry
[Laughter]
um
yeah
and i hope uh this will be a lesson to
me and i'll never have that happen again
where the [\h__\h] is the wool guy now that
i need him
to
i can't find [\h__\h]
no wonder people don't use phoenix then
where is he
the one in the ball oh yeah
i forgot about him
hello
[Music]
oh hi i can reach him from here how nice
uh huh
oh
my gosh
i need to move
[Music]
can we just let him live here give him
one loom
okay i went and gave him one lumen he's
just he just blend in nicely
he just live here
where is his loom though
how do i know which one is his loom
there's three looms
but all the other people
are all the other uh wool people are
gone too
how the [\h__\h] did they escape
i'll just take them all
since i don't see any other wool people
okay
michelle you know what they'll just tell
just live here it's okay
okay no problem
no problem
which one do you want buddy
i have many rooms um do we have a house
for you
they could live up there
is that
if i put the loom up here do you guys
think he'll find it
so empty here
and style-wise i think it fits because
there's wool in the walls
let's just give it a try
will he find it though he might fall
yeah he will okay i'll put one two three
and uh
we'll make a fence here
um
damn it
ah we have oh yes i have still fences
all right
all right okay okay
i kind of liked the fact that there was
no fence here because uh
i could just easily
easily go over there but okay we're
doing a fence now
[Music]
okay
michelle
joey shaw yeshua
and joshua is this good enough i mean it
doesn't look ideal but it's the solution
for now
i can do it with the trapdoors all right
they can't uh open it right
right that was the thing with villagers
they can't open the travelers
noise okay now time to get rid of these
[Applause]
yours
is there
sky's
[Applause]
okay
we'll get rid of all that otherwise it's
an eyesore
[Music]
yeah that builds always cool looking uh
but that house was built by my mom
that's what i built
and the other big house uh in the
farming district i built as well
why did you build an orange prison
because i wanted to put him somewhere
else originally
but now i gave up on that idea
it's okay
what do you mean why because it's an
eyesore well that's just because well
that's what i had in that moment
[Music]
we have more of those
put down here
um
is that how the whole ground looks yes
yes okay
can i put this here or will we not be
able to go out i think it should be fine
so you're allowed to leave now only if
you find your loom okay
[Music]
good luck
oh he's running
oh no he stopped oh he's running he's
running he's running go go go go
yours are yours
no no that's not where you no no
why are they why do they always go here
is there something in here that belongs
to you
[Music]
[Applause]
oh oh he's definitely uh
interested he seems like he's looking
for something
oh he's
all right oh yeah yes he's getting
closer hot hot
it's getting hotter no cold cold cold
cold cold cold
cold
hot hot
no cold very cold very cold here's hot
it's very hot here
yes
follow the phoenix that's where it's at
here there's some bread here
they lost
track of the phoenix
is that you yeah
i lost track of him too
[Applause]
[Music]
look who the [\h__\h] are you
come on come on here
come on
up here
right click to make it me
oh i mean
but i can't move when i'm
[Applause]
[Music]
trading why did i ever take upon this
quest of making a village like this in
the first place
your workbench is up there in the second
yes
on the second floor it's on the second
floor come on come on
come on
yeah okay okay is this how you guys want
me to do that yeah
come on
come on come on now i'm too far away i
can't really go that far
come
is he always able to do brown i guess so
um
do i have to get on my knees
yeah yeah
do i have to hold
or maybe i have to hold the emeralds
maybe that's more interesting come here
now
where you going
please
i will hurt your family
[Music]
that's not yours
follow me
yeah yeah nah i went to southwest
did he go to sleep
[Music]
no he's not here is he upstairs
did he walk past me
have i always been trying to get the
hour smith closer to me
they look so similar
[Music]
okay
okay we'll go to sleep and find him
again
stay away tomorrow
really
i think that's the problem
[Music]
looks fine
maybe i shouldn't place it on the second
floor maybe that's too um
too ambitious
where did he go
oh my god no that's aaron smith what is
the aerosmith doing here too this is him
now why is he here again why does
everybody want to go here somebody
explained that to me oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
oh oh oh oh oh no
oh oh oh no no
you're just blocking preventing from
moving away where you want him okay
so never for never mind an npc that
sounds legit
dude
[Music]
you annoy me so much
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
is this worth it um
i just want him to restock and then
he'll understand where his place is
hopefully
once he knows it and sees it i think
he'll keep on coming back to it i hope
this is this is just
you make me feel so stupid
yeah we're invested now
[Music]
we want the stunts
why you keep on talking with your
stupid-ass friends
[Music]
i don't see your feet is down here you
need to be closer
come on
i will kill you
i will
kill you if i have to
he doesn't believe me cathy can you tell
him i'm serious
okay
he's he's close to them
let's close the aerospace i'm gonna be
confusing them again they have the same
hat
come on come on
mommy seems to place it in front of him
but then i'll have to move it again
anyway i want it to be somewhere where
it ends up being anyway
[Music]
come on
this little [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
even know which workstation this is
are these maybe not yours is that why
you're such a [\h__\h] oh
come up here yo
don't push me don't push me don't sit
there and push
[Music]
the jump stops and which jump there's no
jump here you mean this one
[Music]
okay i'll fix it
i'll fix it
uh
i will
fix it
because i am
a fixer
okay
[\h__\h]
no that's okay maybe
stairs are not my strengths
[Music]
no
uh what is another thing that i wanted
to tell you guys
uh
oh yeah yeah yeah you know
um
you know i told
[Music]
where are you going
just
go here now
[Applause]
come here
come go go go go wait up here
[Music]
oh my god
what america
oh my god kfp
i love people
it's a miracle
i i'm gonna cry
[Music]
okay can i just leave it like this is
this okay for you
please never leave ever again you know
what i'm gonna bring you some fresh beds
did you ever sleep on a bed anyway
oh my god we can trade finally
here i'll make a new bed just for you
hi this is yours because you don't like
using the other one probably
yeah yeah
another ever doesn't matter we just
wanted the wool guy up here that's okay
it's all right it's probably gonna be
pretty lonely up there but
should i trap him in there
i might do that
i might do that um
i don't like trapping my people
[\h__\h]
but
in this case
at least i'll always know where the rule
guy is and he has that whole freaking
penthouse up there also himself so
i think he'll be complaining
would that be fair but he has a
penthouse
what am i looking for i could use um
i want a trap door because i can use it
but he can't
a trapdoor
[Music]
what's a trapdoor made out of
trap door
oh we can make an iron one
uh but i need a button for that one
right and let's use a one with wood
um
supposedly there should be more
[Music]
some freaking normal wood
somewhere
this is some normal one
there it is
okay
let's make a few trapdoors
scott's good
they must show
okay
10 trapdoors i hope he's still up there
[Music]
huh um
like this
and i guess i would just have to jump on
top of it okay that works hello
you even have he doesn't even live a
little he even has a golem as a buddy
like i don't i don't see anything wrong
with this
ah
you ain't an iconic
all right
why not fence skate i don't know
would he be able to use it
now it's uh trapdoors
that's what it's gonna be
[Music]
maybe i can get some more
uh
oh you want to go up there
who are you
no you're not going up there maybe
eventually you get some more friends up
there
um who also uh
did he just did i just is that the ever
smith that's the airsmith isn't it
i was smith
hey
what are you doing
don't you hummy
the [\h__\h] are you doing
he wanted to be with his friend
you want know what one day i'm gonna
burn down phoenixton
what
i should have trapped him in the house i
shouldn't even have given him the option
to leave at all
maybe maybe he'll make the same mistake
again let's let's follow them it looks
like they're making the same mistake
again
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah oh would you look
at that would you oh yes
brb brb brb
brb
if someone looks for the eversmith he's
up here
[Music]
ah they're sleeping
okay
are you being disturbed by the golem
don't worry just keep on sleeping they
can't they can't leave anymore can they
they can't jump on it like i can can
they
they can hop on trap doors
[Music]
what if i do this
i can't hop on it anymore like this you
can you can do this i mean this is
really um probably unnecessary way of
doing it but
this way it works i can't hop on it so
they can't
oh the windows oh [\h__\h]
you think they would do that jump out of
the windows
help
what
[\h__\h] i'm trapped
oh there we go
[Music]
trapped by the trapdoors
how ironic
safety
safety for you guys
it's called safety not prison
i'm lacking one trap door
do i even do i even need the below ones
if i have these here in the middle
i don't think so
right
and how would they how would they escape
i don't think they can
there you go
isn't this nice
[Music]
oh
i see um
no no
this is it's just not the beginning of
me building a prison
we are we we um
we aim to have a healthy lifestyle for
our villagers at phoenixton
and this is totally healthy he has two
people living with him
the golem is protecting him that's not a
prison guard okay
he ain't a prison guard
don't worry about it
i'll put this up anyway even though i
think it might be oh kind of i don't
know
if you if you were to come
down from the stairs i think you can
jump on it but they won't be able to
leave anyway so all is good
hallelujah airs aerosmith and wool guy
trapped
yes
no no i'm not in the wrong i'm always in
the right
uh tsuki what's on my list mending
shield i did that old house kill i
killed one of them
uh more traders
hmm
don't necessarily need more trainers but
okay i'll put some lecterns down that's
that's all i need to do if there's
there's already like a million lecterns
here but
okay
there's also a lot of jobless people so
that i guess that means we need more
lactones
okay where should i put them
just put them in
here
maybe one can be here
[Music]
do you want a job you want to be like
your senpai shawn mendes
understandable
he has one of the best jobs after all
lectern
[Music]
[Applause]
there we go oh my god what do you have
knock back okay that's probably [\h__\h]
what do you have blast protection yeah
probably that's probably [\h__\h] too but
it's okay
at least they're not jobless
i know phoenix likes to take care of the
villagers
[Music]
let's get rid of uh another house
uh we could get rid of that one
and just replace it with the slabs and
eventually build a new house on there i
just want to get rid of it
i just want to get rid of it
or is it a problem if i get rid of it
this is like
is this stopping the elevator from
breaking
because it's leaning on to it
if i open this up will the water leak
or maybe not no it shouldn't because
it's like this okay
it's not leaking whoever said yes was
wrong
wrong you are
foolish
foolishness
[Music]
oh what is this doing here
nice
i want everything to match so
oh yeah i wanted to actually say
something i forgot about it i was gonna
say
i think i told you guys before that i
never
not never but usually most of the time i
don't buy
uh
tickets for conventions
because usually there's a nice area
outside to chill in right just like just
like honeymook just like i told you
about animals
it was the same
thing there
um
but this year was actually the first
time that i bought a ticket for the
convention
because they were gonna like put a fence
because of the sea thing
in the middle of that garden area
um
but so i was worried that like we
wouldn't be able to access much of it if
i didn't have a ticket oh their ticket
sales must have gone up by a lot
yeah i'm not really interested in most
things that
happen inside uh anime conventions like
i used to
i used to be interested but like i've
been so many times so i know
what it's like inside
i know
what the content of a convention like
that usually is
you know what's inside i know what they
sell at the merch stands
all that super expensive imported stuff
like plushies and figures and uh the
food is super expensive everything's
expensive and i don't need any of it so
yeah um
i just don't feel like buying a ticket
when i don't need it all my friends are
outside anyway so you know i like the
panels yeah i don't
you guys that in in america probably
have better panels
[Music]
we usually don't have many good panels
or any good panels
so i don't i don't even look up the
panels anymore
i don't even look them up anymore
[Music]
need to get rid of some stuff
there we go
[Music]
but
there's one thing only one thing
at conventions that i'm still interested
in nowadays
performances just kidding
that's something that you guys should be
interested in though
no but another thing would be uh karaoke
sometimes they have karaoke
um not like the
professional
kind
rachel
or is my there it is
[Music]
what do i not need
this trapdoor
not the professional kind that they have
in
japan they just basically subtitle some
videos i guess put them on the screen
and then put some microphones there
yeah um
but
i don't know i still like it so
sometimes i
go to the karaoke
and sing some alimu songs
actually
that was the only reason why i used that
ticket uh this time
only on one day i had a i had a three
day ticket
and uh i used it once on one day
just to go
do some karaoke that was it
what a [\h__\h] waste man
such a waste
is anyone who doesn't who doesn't like
me and just never buys a ticket for
conventions
anyone anyone in the chat
[Music]
was it expensive it was it was even more
expensive than normally because at the
moment when i bought the tickets the
normal three day ticket was sold out but
all the single tickets were still
selling
so i bought free single tickets that are
more expensive than the solo and then
the one uh
full weekend ticket and then later it
was available again apparently so i feel
like i got scammed
never bought a ticket
hexagon never go to conventions because
there aren't any oh that's sad
[Applause]
they were free oh free events
going to my first car in july whoa have
fun
it don't last you do much at us
conventions without a badge yeah that's
the impression i have
you guys also often use like huge hotels
as a venue right from what i've heard
like some conventions some big
conventions are in hotels and there's
not really
much more
uh
like outside venue
at least everyone just is inside so
you know
with some i apply
wherever you live there's kadalka bars
in austria too but i don't like going to
them because i don't like the whole
bar concept
i want it to be like a room like in
japan
[Music]
why don't you like bars i don't like
bars in general but i don't like karaoke
bars either because like i don't wanna i
don't wanna listen to the other people
singing i don't wanna wait until it's my
turn cause they're singing singing in
that moment and i don't wanna i don't
wanna i don't wanna have them here
have strangers hear me sing evil isn't
this understandable i think that's
pretty understandable
pretty relatable no
oh there's more wool here
[Applause]
no one's taking my black wool right now
so
it's so messy here i need to like clean
this [\h__\h] at some point
but okay um
we're pretty much
pretty much cleaned up here
um so now it's time to place the slabs
these are different ones
oh
these ones oh
these ones are like the inside slabs
anyway karaoke was pretty funny
um
normally i don't really like uh having
people join me because like the thing is
with these karaokes at conventions
uh
like if you put in a song that other
people know
they will storm to the microphones and
sing it with you like like it's like a
system where you put in a song
you wait your turn because other people
put in songs too and then they say your
name and they say this song go and then
you will go to the microphone but if
it's a popular song or a song that other
people know they will think that's a
free invitation for them to join you
you know what i didn't want anyone to
join they joined anyway
[Music]
because i made a mistake
to choose some karaoke song that the
other people knew and then the second
time i was like okay you know what i'm
i'm gonna i'm gonna choose one that you
don't know
and then the thing is like
they think it's like an open mic and
then
if at least the people who join
knew how to sing the song properly
but no the person that joined me
was like
she was like singing like
not hitting the key
not sink on sync with me nothing was
terrible
is this mom this literally just mumbling
i mean if it's your own song okay go
ahead and mumble
but if you're joining me
why are you doing my backup vocals
okay i don't need anyone to do my
bang-up
i just wanted to sing okay okay i'm so
mean
it's okay it's okay i overpowered that
person with my lyrics with my vocals
anyway
i'm so mean i'm sorry it's okay you can
join
it's okay
i don't want to use the
deep deep slate tile thingy i want to
use the right one
bricks
[Music]
i've been looking inside of these a
million times and i can't find anymore
mommy where did you put some more
where'd you put them
[Music]
it's okay understandable but it's like
i'm actually having double standards
here because
when i saw
that other people are doing that to me
i did the same to the others when they
put on songs that i wanted to sing to
but but i only did it because everyone
else was doing it if if if they weren't
doing it then i wouldn't have joined
them either but then they put on some
songs and
and people stormed to the microphone and
i was like okay you know what i'm gonna
i'm gonna do it too
yeah
no the truth comes out
i've got some double standards
yeah the truth is i i
i need to save it
[Music]
yeah and i think i think i was a
positive
um
how to say a positive addition
to their vocals
oh i i did i did them a favor
and this and sometimes there was so many
people that you didn't hear me anyway so
at that point i mean if you put in a
[\h__\h] pokemon song of course you're
not gonna be the only one singing it or
digimon although i wouldn't i usually
wouldn't join when they sang pokemon or
digimon songs because surprisingly while
everybody else knows those i don't know
them well
i don't know them well
yeah enough
don't know how to sing those
surprisingly
hmm
i know maybe um
only because of lucky star and i know
[Music]
i love the best sign this kind of
formula
why am i bobbing so much
[Music]
i don't know the lyrics by heart but at
least i could sing it if i had the
lyrics in front of me
yeah
uh and what else do i know
i know
uh
oh yeah left and time cause i learned
that one for um
for a karaoke stream otherwise i
probably
wouldn't really know how to sing it
no challenge hedgehog is dragon ball i
was just uh
yeah saying some songs i
i think i know how to
sing one of like the the well-known
famous ones um
they didn't no they didn't say naruto
i'll be okay
i'm on my way or they didn't sing those
why am i riding like this
okay can we um i guess just stop that
here at least the house is gone
[Music]
at least the house is gone
so
that's a good start and you guys can get
off the boat now
sorry i almost hit you scared me
scared me
don't want to be killed i'm sure i'm not
traumatized by the
stupid
golems
[Applause]
i'll just uh put this i don't know
[Music]
i just put this here for now
okay okay
okay it looks better looks better
because there's nothing weird looking
here anymore it looks cleaner i still
see some windows
let's get them up though
[Music]
you know
one one song that someone chose um
was that
uh
you know that song
someone shows that and
people actually didn't know that song
so
that the girl or person guy who chose
that one came to the microphone and no
one else came so i was like oh wait i
know this song oh yeah i actually want
to sing this one so i joined for that
one that was really fun to sing
it was really cute and it's japanglish
song you never heard it before oh my god
what is it called you guys need to look
it up um
whoever knows how what it's called
tell me now
because these people need to be educated
i really don't have any more of those
tiles man
what's it called
tokyo
took your bun
took your bun that's the song title
it's not called magdalena
tokyo bon name wheeze name we
look that up and you will love it it's
so cute
it's not called
what the hell is mcdonald's
the whole song is basically just uh
we forgot it existed
you're welcome it's basically just like
saying uh english words in japanese
pronunciation
and it just sounds so cute
[Music]
what am i even doing at this point
i should just stop because i'm not doing
anything it's already been three hours
anyway
house fixing done more traders done old
house kill done mending shield done i
actually did everything
i did do everything i even built a new
house
what what did i mean with house fixing
the houses are don't need fixing did i
mean
that one like building the house
is that what i meant
we're done
we're done i need to read super chats
anyway
and that was my course choice
oh my god it's like what
what's up
what's happening is my stream lagging
too
oh my why are they lagging so much
server lag oh that's a
that's a big [\h__\h] lag
[Laughter]
uh
server bro are you okay
not even using shaders
hello
i feel like i'm gonna get kicked out any
moment now
oh my oh my god
okay i think there's a sign for me to
stop
[Applause]
[Music]
say this one
that's just the server it's not my
internet right it's just the server
itself
brown are you good yeah are you sick
oh [\h__\h] oh my god
uh
uh never mind we're not we don't need to
trade i'm i'm good if you're good i'm
good
okay
uh
let's uh i feel bad i didn't really
finish my tangent
cow karate is going to have a hard time
um
you know what i i i'll tell you more
on the weekend on the wind like a
weekend is that too
long i still have some things that i
a few things
now you know what i'll say
there actually might i might have just
been one more thing and the other things
i forgot so
um
oh yeah so here's my conclusion
um i might think of some more tangents
later on for the wind waker weekend but
here's my here's my conclusion before we
read super chats
um
i
was able to meet some
old friends and some new friends and
some um
current friends
thanks to going to the event like
usually
uh i don't meet my friends much you guys
probably know that because i don't talk
about meeting my friends much
um but this was a great opportunity to
meet up with my friends again
conventions are usually the only
opportunity for me to meet my friends
anyway
um mostly not opportunity but it's just
the only time i ever meet my friends
most of the time um but i used to go to
conventions way more often so i would
also see them a bit more often than that
um so yeah i met some old friends
actually some really surprising
friends and i met i met some
i made some new friends too
some people that
i felt like i don't know
i i never really existed to them
um now talk to me
maybe i was also more open i'm not sure
but i felt like i was a bit more visible
to people
yeah this whole weekend i felt
not only to
you know those new friends but just to
the general public i felt more visible a
lot more people said hello to me not
because of you know
they thought who they know who i am at
least i don't think so it doesn't seem
like it they talk to me for other
reasons but
yeah um
no i don't i don't
i don't think so some some old friends
came up to me and were like
um really excited to see me and they
told me they know what i'm doing now and
i'm like oh
[Laughter]
um
those those people told me about it but
there were some strangers you know but
they didn't talk to me because of you
know me being kiana i think no i'm
pretty sure
um
yeah but anyway so that was nice um
then there's some someone told me that
they really um were happy for me that
these things happened to me and
and some of them said they also watch my
my streams
that make me very happy
yeah
some of them
that's
good to hear that some people watch my
streams
and
yeah being able to connect with my old
friends
again
and my current friends
[Music]
was was very refreshing and you know how
in my paris trip last year i told you
guys that
uh
that was the first time
pretty much since i joined whole life
that was in october
that's already over a year that was the
first time in
like a year that i was able to spend a
day without thinking about
my job without looking at my phone all
the time right
that was
that was the only time the one paris
trip in october i think it was in
october
and since then i haven't been able to do
that since
um always work brain
uh
yeah i wasn't able to disconnect like
until until the convention again the
convention
kept me so occupied
i had my phone with me but
um i i never really checked it for work
uh except for in the evening but even
then like when i was in the hotel even
then i didn't have much time to check my
phone because i i had to quickly fall
asleep and then in the morning i didn't
really have time either because i had to
get ready and then go to the cone and so
on and so on so it was free days
of
me most of the time
not doing any work related things at
least during the day i didn't do
anything and then in the evening maybe i
did like i replied like to my manager
once or twice but that's pretty much
about it and
that while it felt i felt partially you
know guilty for not streaming i felt bad
about it um but it was also very
refreshing to just turn off my work
brain
for the first time in a while again that
i rarely happens i'm never able to do it
so ah hallelujah
uh
we need to do that more often then i
need to go to more conventions because
it seems like the only way for me to
shut down my work brain
[Music]
let's see how the moldings go well on
the maldives i'll have so much time on
my hands and we'll just be chilling on
the beach and all that so i think we'll
have
too much time to
you know do stuff like work-related
things so
i don't think i'll be able to shut down
quite that much but i'll also just
it'll be fine because at the same time
i'll be really relaxed and i'll be
swimming and i'll be drinking smoothies
and you know
i think
it will be a good balance it's okay i'll
bring my switch too so me and dana can
play
some stuff maybe mario kart i don't know
or uh the the um
how many games was it 51 board games was
it 51 no i don't think it was 50
i'll bring that too
and monopoly yeah we can play monopoly
i'll bring my switch that's for sure
uh
and we can play um we can watch movies
and stuff
and
maybe i'll bring
a small
chest set or something an actual chest
but the switch is so useful it has all
the games
um monopoly
and uh maybe we can do some activities
there i'm not sure what they are for
there but yeah but it's okay
it's gonna be okay
let's go chess don't feel bad about
taking a break you gotta if you go have
fun thank you
thank you
yeah i wouldn't have felt so bad if i
could have clearly told you
like why i'm gonna be gone
um then i wouldn't have had such a
bad conscience
[Music]
it's correct right it sounds weird
it sounds so weird to me
[Music]
yeah yeah the thing that's the thing
with the weekly schedules
uh
if i make a weekly schedule you'll have
a rough idea of what i'll be doing
so
it actually kind of
is a problem sometimes
of weekly schedules though
did you see the new format
did you see it and for the members i um
distributed it as a wallpaper in several
huge sizes
have you seen it
uh here it is in case you didn't see it
i had an idea um because i i wasn't i
was never really happy with you know
this old format of the sticky notes it
was just like
i guess it looked kind of messy but i
think we all got used to it this is some
old one by the way
but i also had problems finding proper
backgrounds for them because i always
use landscape ones and most people draw
fan art in
not landscape oh wait that's
actually the same artist
that wasn't even on purpose
yong dao that's the same artist
i think yeah yeah that was young though
so i was like ha
lucio
how about i commission
uh
a art for it and then use it because if
i would commission weekly art that would
be quite costly so however i commission
it monthly then we'll have the same art
for the whole month but we'll also give
it to the members in a clean version
without the whole schedule thing on top
of it so you guys can use it as a
as um as a background if you want to and
it will always be
having a monthly theme this month's
theme was like a may picnic
uh as you can maybe see a little bit or
you can see it better if you remember
but there's a picnic going on in the
background it's really cute many many
details
and uh yeah i got the new template
uh from
someone called saki
saki yeah right yeah saki
uh she did a great job
it looks very clean and she sent me a
psd file that's like so organized holy
[\h__\h] my old scheduled psd was not
organized at all i always had to like
look through it a lot it was very
confusing to me too
um
yeah but now
now i have this and it's yeah the only
problem i realized today is that when i
have two streams and one
day how am i gonna do that
because you see how the time is there i
wouldn't be able to fit another time
in there
maybe maybe it will change one more time
because i did i forgot to consider that
i forgot to take that into consideration
i don't really make it any more smaller
than that
so i have to discuss with the sucky
maybe
they have an idea to fix it maybe split
the day into two vertically i thought so
too
then
yeah that's the only thing i could think
of without changing the whole thing too
much again
yeah
like having one of those time thingies
placed somewhere in the middle
of one
of the days you know what i mean
well then the name of the stream thingy
will have to be
pretty small
or short but
it could work
yeah yeah streaming ties isn't a bit
much i sometimes do that
sometimes i have two streams a day
it does happen sometimes yeah
but i'm happy with it uh
it's cute and it should work with any
kind of art in the future we'll have
different themes like in the winter time
we'll have winter themes in the
summertime we'll maybe have some
swimsuit back room
and in the in the autumn time we'll have
some nice leaves falling on the ground
and i don't know all kinds of fall stuff
all the time other stuff yeah
hold over summer yeah
my way of uh getting some taste of home
life summer um
[Music]
the date uh
the art will the clean out will only be
available for one month for the members
you know so that that if you join later
you don't suddenly get all of them
you have to be there in the month if you
want the art to clean art so yeah make
sure to get it it's in as a community
post it's up there now in case you
didn't get it yet and then it will
disappear
by the time of the next month
yes that's fair mm-hmm
so this way we have a new perk for the
members as well yeah i wanted to give
some more stuff to you guys anyway and
here we have something yeah
yeah yeah you can collect them all you
can collect them
okay
i will go read super chats now let's go
to my office
[Music]
yes gotta catch em all
thanks for watching the minecraft stream
today we didn't do that much i guess but
uh i didn't want to stream too long
anyway because it's already late and i
need to read super chats and i need to
cook afterwards
um
yeah and basically i kind of just wanted
to stream something where i can tell you
a little bit about my trip
um
overall
i'm glad that i did the trip
and because i got some brain off time
and i met my friends and had fun
and yeah
i hope you guys didn't feel too lonely
while i was gone
don't worry for the next trip for the
maldives i'll have some more stuff
prepared and
we will have time so
we will stream if we have good internet
connection
worst case we'll stream without our
avatars
if that doesn't work we'll yeah we'll
stream somehow
um we'll give you guys some content
we'll also have some videos prepared at
least i i will have i'm planning some
videos we're going to start the whole
um
kfp
lingo
um video series
uh
with the maldives trip we're gonna start
it with that
yeah worst case we can do a space on
twitter but i need to do something on
youtube because i need to keep the
algorithm satisfied
for that we have some small videos i'm
definitely going to upload an m video
definitely going to upload uh
not definitely but i'm working on a song
cover right now but um
i'm getting a bit worried if the song
cover will make it in time the one with
dana
uh
yeah because i need to outsource some
help for it
i'm trying to make it in
time um but we'll have some stuff
prepared yeah
yeah to and fish and spirit of the beach
oh yeah i could no i'm dolphin you could
do i'm dolphin yeah yeah yeah yeah
the problem with uh
animals in the water
is that they usually make sounds that
you can't really hear or perceive like
what the [\h__\h] does a fish do
blah blah blah blah blah blah
[Laughter]
how am i going to impersonate that
yeah and shark already did that but yeah
most of the other like how how do i do
um
how do i do a crab
how do i do a
a jellyfish
stuff like that
how do i do i could do a seal
maybe
probably
but i mean more like the fishy stuff
that doesn't go outside of the water
those kind of animals
i'll think of something though
maybe
maybe i can
get elena to do one too
[Music]
kiwami style
smack finger make a sound you mean for
crab
i like this
i'm just clapping my hands as if i'm
using my crab scissor thingies i don't
know that's no that's not good but oh i
could just use a scissor but i'm trying
to make those sounds with my own
body and my own mouth and all that so i
can't use other tools no no no no no no
no no
no no no no
get some tongs and click them together
nah then can't use any other tools now
[Music]
uh wait there was one more thing i want
to say oh yeah this is [\h__\h] me guys
it's [\h__\h] me oh my god i'm going to
the mall dips this week uh this week not
this month
it's not this week
oh my god it's so [\h__\h] soon holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] yesterday i got a little bit
of a
heart attack because i thought my flight
was canceled but it wasn't
it was just changed a little bit
it's already made
it's already may
oh my god
the time i thought the maldives trip was
so so far away but it kept on getting
closer and closer and i'm so excited i i
i keep on telling like friends and
family like i'm going to the welders
like that just because i'm happy but i
also feel like i'm kind of flexing
because going to the mall and just like
quite quite something that you could be
jealous of but i just feel i need to
share
i'm going to the maldives guys i'm going
to the maldives yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh my god
oh
i'm so excited i'm a bit nervous but i'm
also very excited
[Music]
about it
did anyone say what is the mother snow
everybody knows it
everybody who are told knows what the
motives is everybody knows the motives
in europe because it's a very popular
honeymoon destination
like a a destination that many people
feel like is
very very
desirable
i wonder how your first meeting with
reyna will look like yeah we're gonna be
meeting at the airport
in the maldives
for the first time
i hope it won't be up now it won't be
awkward i'll give her a big hug
but yeah that's um it's kind of risky to
go on like a almost one week i think
vacation was someone you never met
before
but i mean we've always um got along
fine in
or through voice chat so
i think
it's gonna be all right okay i'm gonna
delete my
oh
minecraft request but my answer but said
that she doesn't have time today it's
okay i'm deleting it i don't want to
tag everybody just and i'm leaving the
voice chat
rip
rip rip rest and pace
[Music]
there might be an announcement tomorrow
there's gonna be an announcement
tomorrow
i'm here by announcing there's an
announcement tomorrow
from uh
me
asane
happier
i'm actually excited to announce this
this is something that has been in the
works for a while and is
something really exciting oh my god i
can't wait to tell you guys
announcing the announcement yeah and
tomorrow will be the portal 2 collab of
kobo oh god that makes me nervous too
kobo said that
she
like i asked her again if she ended up
playing anything she said no but she
watched like some
video a little bit some bit of
playthrough and she played a portal vr
game which is probably the short one
that you guys told me about
but that one probably won't help much
having played that one
uh
yeah i'll carry her in worst case you
guys will help me if kobo can't help
thinking then i think
as a co-op game i'm allowed to have a
second brain by using the chat a little
bit right
it's co-op i can't be the only one doing
all the brain work and the footwork
right
you guys gonna be my second brain we're
gonna together carry couple
yeah oh wait that reminds me i need uh
[Music]
do you have something for the funknail
you have
a png of yourself
got a thumbnail
i'll send her one
too because i think yeah we'll both be
streaming on both channels both point of
views
i stand in kobe 10
it looks like i am her first en collab
right
i think i saw her collabing with uh her
id stampers
let's give her this one
oh that's a jpeg
you have the first one
[Music]
okay this one has a smug look
okay
[Music]
she said she told me
i want to apologize beforehand if i say
anything wrong or offensive i don't know
how she could say anything offensive but
let's give her a warm welcome tomorrow
um
she was bullied by lena lisu what
what no don't bully the baby
i just got to my office i cleo
moving
oh [\h__\h] sorry
uh sorry uh uh
martin
sorry martin
sorry about that
sorry i'll get you back later
you don't deserve this
there you go chat is there
get rid of this maybe i should make a
thumbnail like that with both of us like
give both of us some kind of hand
i'll try i'll try to recreate my portal
thumbnail style
uh for co-op too
martin yeah yeah my name is not very
common in as a name in english language
is it
it's very common in german language as a
name
[Music]
i only know george r r martin but wait
isn't it
for george r.r martin is which one is
the first name and which is the last
name
oh martin luther king
then for martin luther king martin is
the first name
martin is george's last name
oh george is the whoa
and for
martin last
for for the luther
is is that his last name too
[Music]
it can't be both in english not a hodo
oh
so are very common though
for me it sounds very german anyway
does it sound english to you guys martin
i think
i perceive it as a very german name
i don't
yeah right
what wait you say yes you you say it
sounds english to you or german
it sounds german right sounds english to
me
wait which one are you saying yes to the
[\h__\h]
sounds english
really
it just sounds streaming to me
there's certain names that
i think sound
um
very english and of them sound very
german to me like jerry sounds english
to me
george sounds english to me
yeah hans is very german
hans is peak german
hans peak german it's not even that
common anymore here maybe maybe like a
few centuries ago it was more common
but nowadays i don't i don't ever meet
people with that name anymore but it
does indeed sound very german
gunther yeah but you don't say gunter we
say gunter it's the u with the two dots
uh on top
kevin kevin yeah
for me it's more on the german side than
on the english side but i do say it in
english names too kevin kevin
kevin
kevin would be a good name for a chicken
frank
ah
that that's like one that i would say is
both
we say frank
i do hear it sometimes in germany
[Music]
manuel yeah manual very german
herbert how bad that is hundred percent
german
can't tell me that sounds english to you
does this herbert sound english to you
only if you say herbert but it's how bad
[Music]
i mean who knows where it originally
comes from we could look all these name
up and names up and see where it
originally comes from
but for me it's german
it sounds better in german i think i
think it makes more sense in german
oh what a horrible name sorry sorry to
all the bruno hilda's out there
as a bad name
okay let's uh
bring out the super chats
[Music]
minecraft
oh dear
portal 2. i have to read portal 2 right
do i
did i not read the portal 2 once
[Music]
yeah i have to read them uh
but both of them
[Music]
i have to read both of them wasn't there
was like two episodes in a row
only the second one right okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
there it is there it is
it looks so similar
it looks so similar here it is here it
is
there it is okay
oh gosh those pop those were so cute oh
my god
what a hit thumbnail what's your
that is
[Laughter]
i saw
one tweet
that um
interpreted this
look with the glove as something
specific to
uh
men
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh man i saw it that's a different kind
of look more like
more like oh i'm not confident about
this game
but let's take off my gloves anyway
because when you take off your gloves
you're more serious about things well
i'm worried you know i'm worried
you guys saw the tweet
it's very fitting though but it's not
what it was no no i did like it yes
because it was funny
yeah
university exams yeah
university
oh
i wanted to tell you one thing though
the schedule
uh did you see the ina collab on it
[Music]
do you wonder what that is about
chill low fat let's go
yeah it says fashion design but you know
what it's about it was my idea i was
like
i have an idea for a stream
because i wanted to do something like
this for a while
um
it will be
both me and ina
will
draw
design
outfits on top of a base
for
all the councilman
members maybe even iris i'm not sure
about how many we can do
but we'll design casual outfits for all
of them
and then
i'm not sure uh if actually i forgot
about asking one of the council members
but i wanted to get one of the council
members on call to judge it i'm not sure
if i can do this
kind of last minute i'll ask them
[Music]
i wanted one of them to judge it
we'll design it well we'll prepare it
beforehand
uh
and then show it on the stream
what we designed and then it will be
like for example fauna ina designed
something for fauna and i designed
something for fauna and then we'll have
uh the council ideally it would be all
of them but i don't think i could get
all of them so last minute into the
stream um but yeah we'll
we'll have someone from council judges
which which would would look better or
fit for not better for example you know
the theme will probably be casual
outfits maybe another theme uh
additionally depending on
i still need to think about the details
depends on how much time i think
everything takes up but yeah that was my
idea i wanted to think of more streams
that don't require a game um
you know like make our own game
basically i wanted to do more streams
like that
and i think it makes sense to do it with
council because
it's kind of sad but council really
doesn't have many outfits do they
so we're going to make them for them
they only have the kimonos
i know it kind of hurts but we're gonna
take care of it when they need more
outfits
[Music]
designated
outfit more than anyone else
she didn't even get a chemo no sadly but
don't say never
i think she'll still get it they're just
still working on it
i don't think she would not get it at
all they're just
yeah i'm sure they're working on it just
give it some time give it some time
if they bring it out in summer it could
be like uh you know
even though it's a kimono you could see
it as a as a summer yukata to go to
those summer festivals in japan you know
it will actually make sense
um
that would be a good occasion
you'll just
you don't know how thick the fabric is
it could be a yukata that just looks
like a kimono
maybe
yeah
she needs a location for review or did
she say that really
i don't know about how far they are
i don't know about that but hopefully
she can reveal it soon
all right all right let's go uh poor
tunnel two day two
super chatos cruise thank you and mr
casper
you changed your profile picture what is
that
ah
you're fighting the
oh the crab the the blue one that i was
talking about ah it's so funny
cause i
told you uh on twitter let's do a fight
club no he's still a fish though that's
perfect beautiful
i love it
fight club in the aquarium yeah fish
versus crab who's gonna win
you you would think uh crap but have you
seen this fish
you've seen this fish this is a buff
fish don't talk about the fish club
looking for the top down
tyson thank you for the red super chat
you got this cam no rabbits or puzzles
can stop you after this it will be
perfectly trained to show couple how
powerful you really are
you will be the strong smart beautiful
senpai that will leave her in pure of
your majesty
you are our attention for a reason
thank you uh
wow that's a lot of pressure pressure
man
but i mean i played both of them
paul one and portal two so recently so i
mean
[Music]
that should help right
yeah
and then if i don't know what to do i'll
peek into the chat
i'll take an answer from there
and then kobo will think i was so smart
to
get the solution but in reality it was a
chat
but you guys would support me with that
right you would support me just so that
kobo thinks i'm cool
you don't mind that right
i mean you need her to think i'm cool
sounds like a plan of course
[Music]
got you back oh you guys are perfect i
love you guys
thanks for helping me become kobo's
mommy
no don't give me a wrong answer no no no
no
no no no no thanks typhon
yeah
i'm gonna do my best
the game mccree thank you
but don't worry about it
um
that advice i already forgot it why you
must remind me
time to thank you for the rest of the
chat an important message
tai chi is just trying to tease me
you like to tease me right that's that's
how the boys do it in
in a junior
no not junior elementary elementary
school
they have a girl that they like
he just teased them
yeah but you know what i'm an adult
i'm not part of your system i'm not
gonna let you tease me daiji i'm gonna
kiss you
and i'm gonna throw it on the ground
damn
i dropped the kiss i threw it on the
ground
oh no it didn't even reach you
[Music]
well you need to stop teasing me because
i'm not part of your system
that's what you get
tai chi
adult joke
is
for the pinky in whitman's defense who
among us
haven't felt the impulse to turn traitor
on tension for fun
it's just a joke hashtag free weekly
wow yeah yeah it's a joke okay
turn traitor on me for fun
it's just just just a joke but you guys
wouldn't be able to
keep it up for too long right because
you
you guys love me too much and then you
feel guilty just like how i felt guilty
for not streaming right
you you guys feel guilty for being mean
to me sometimes right you don't get a
kick out of it right
i felt very sad and guilty that i
couldn't stream for you guys and i
couldn't tell you clearly what i was
doing we're the same right
we just want the best for one another
right
get guilty you have a guilty conscience
no you don't get kicks out of it
otherwise you'll get a kick of the kick
in your butt
and you don't want that right
okay
some people seem uncertain
but i'm sure
you feel guilty just how i feel guilty
because we both love each other so much
don't we
you love me the way i love you right
right
yeah
yeah yeah you want the best one
sure that's
not exactly what i'm saying but okay
sounds good to me
oh
oh it tears you up okay
of course always thank you okay good for
we
we seem to understand each other
hundreds
mmd alpha dt thank
[Music]
60 in 1968 is worth 495 dollars in 2022
oh wow interesting
[Music]
indeed then it's not a bad deal you know
how um in portal 2 there was this thing
about uh
during the experiment for 60 dollars and
we said that's kind of not worth it but
yeah i was wondering
maybe it was worth more and it was a
worth a lot more
almost 500 dollars
for like one day of
experimenting
that's better than
nothing
if you survived the test well well let's
say you didn't do the tests and survived
you would have survived but you wouldn't
have the money so
let's do it
[Laughter]
empty can counseling
[Music]
thank you random collusion thanks to the
pinky please replace my organs kiara
don't ask me
go to aperture
uh and ask them my mom
they're they're probably still active
somewhere
my ex-girlfriend's probably still
running it gladys
gladys is probably still running it to
this day
you can yeah good adults
you can give her your organs she'll
gladly take them
mario alfredo duncan tanaka and drago
the victim of the rabbit
[Music]
hole
uh kfb no cubase thank
fun fact your neurons use a maximum of
0.09 v volt compared to potato battery
fueled intelligence
what does that say about this
i'm not sure i can't make anything out
of that can you
can you tell me in german
this sounds
complicated to me
sounds interesting though
[Music]
kyle karen
are you ready for making some clips
of my tangents
maybe you should wait a little bit more
maybe i'm not done yet maybe there's
more to come
maybe in the middle of you editing
tomorrow the day after tomorrow you'll
you'll hear me tangenting again in a
different stream
oh no i probably wouldn't change it
until wind waker
so you know maybe you should wait
you never know when my tangents continue
i'm sorry for being such a scattered
brain like honestly oh my god every time
i see kyle carrot putting together my
intentions
i have to face palm
because like how the [\h__\h] do i spread
one story through
like a eight hour stream
with so many breaks in between i lose my
friend so many times
i'm like the worst person to clip
i'm the worst person to clip man i'm
thinking i give clippers a [\h__\h]
headache i'm so sorry
the greatest storyteller known to man or
chicken
[Music]
alderman cam foreign stories was good
yeah well i mean
in some way it keeps you guys on your
toes and makes you guys
like forces you guys a little bit to
stay from beginning of the stream to the
end of the stream because you want to
hear the whole story right
you can't leave in the middle of the
stream if you didn't hear the end of the
story
maybe that's the the real goal here
maybe i'm that big brain
and that's why i scatter my tangents
throughout the whole stream
yeah i'm holding the tangent hostance
yeah
you and the tangent
[Music]
playing 5d chests
of chat always always
yeah thank god we have concurrent
i always stay from beginning to end
that's
foreign
[Music]
speaking german right now reminds me for
dokomi
um
last time i spoke german right
in between the songs
and i mean there weren't many
people besides german speaking people in
the audience to begin with but this time
i think there's going to be a lot more a
lot of you guys who are coming don't
speak german right
but it's a german convention but it
would be weird if i would be speaking
english but i was worrying a little bit
about that you guys need a live
translator sitting right next to you
next to your scene
or watch the
twitch archive because there's probably
going to be a translator in the chat of
the twitch uh stream
yeah it will probably still be a german
speaking
uh audience mostly
um
but yeah uh iris oh yeah iris is gonna
do it in english obviously but since my
mother tongue is german why would i not
have my performance in german you know
it only makes sense
[Music]
i should teach her some german oh yeah i
think that was uh what i offered her
anyway to do a german
um
school collab before dokomi for her
[Music]
we're not on together no we're not uh
separate days
ah that reminds me uh
i didn't put it on my schedule because i
wasn't even sure if i was allowed to say
it but i'm going to say it anyway uh on
sunday sunday sunday i think it's sunday
let me check
[Music]
oh yeah sunday
before wind waker
uh me and iris together i think will be
on the dokomi twitch channel for like a
little
chit chat uh it's on twitter ah they did
not okay well then i can say it too
which i knew i totally knew that they
already posted onto it i knew it was
safe to say
yeah uh it will be uh 2 p.m gmt plus 2 2
pm my time
2 p.m kiwa time
uh
yeah we'll be on their channel i think
we'll talk about the convention talk
about some details
maybe
reveal
something although i haven't heard uh
about it for a while but hopefully we
can reveal something
um that's a good time yeah it will be
before wind waker then there will be
like an hour break and then we'll start
with waker
that will actually be his first time
meeting iris no no no no no no no we've
collabed before just never one-on-one
and this will still not be a one-on-one
collab yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah
no that's not one-on-one either because
there will be the dokomi people in the
stream as well
she came to my shrine i guess so that's
that was kind of 101
but uh the shrine god was
there i was just amazing the shrine god
was there you just didn't hear him
[Music]
and the document is not really a collab
but i will be on twitch i will let you
guys know i'll put the link on twitter
so you guys
should be there
um especially the people who are going
to google me so you hear a little bit
about it and get hyped up for it
yes yes yes
[Music]
yeah i said i'll do one with her before
it document i'll teach her some german
all right back to super chatos
[Music]
in the director's note for portal 1 they
decided not to use a recording of
caroline begging to not be put into the
computer it felt too creepy so yes
caroline didn't want this
oh i wanted to know more about you know
that moment
like
some more details about
how
that went down like we know it went down
but i don't remember getting too many
details about that very
very moment
like that day
and
the things leading up to it like very
close to it when it actually happened i
wanted to know more about that
i refused to record the audio wow what
cave didn't want her put in the computer
just to take over
the company but i don't quite understand
the sentence
they didn't want to put her in the
computer computer because they didn't
want her to take over the company
uh
they just originally wanted to put her
into the computer because just so that
she could live forever or what
[Music]
he's recorded worse and wouldn't do
anything for her
[Music]
you guys seem to have different
information
uh dr jokes
that sounds like you're trying to make
me say something what does this mean
before i read this out loud
is this something about being a chicken
again
[Music]
translate
nani
cucumber with smell of fondillo what's
that
[Music]
a butt a cucumber that smells like butt
oh man this is okay
pepino that question i'll not read the
full thing anyway though pepino sounds
cute though is that cucumber
what a cute way of saying cucumber
[Music]
it's a bad name wait which one
what what's wrong with the pepe you know
it's not cucumber
don't say that why not why can't i not
say that you know
[Music]
anyway
miracle thank you for the red super chat
ask
[Music]
uh glad you're
shut up chad glad you're having fun with
the portal games dan joe gladys was my
wife lu so i'm glad you're getting along
with her
that's why she wouldn't marry me natural
hotel it's not like i died multiple
times because i believed her and wanted
to spend more time with her when i
played the game years ago oh like when
that one time where she says go here and
i obviously didn't fall for it and went
somewhere else i think there was that
one time and you would just follow her
instead
oh
[Music]
i can't blame you miaku it's okay
i'm not blaming you so don't blame
yourself
and that just means now i'm your wife so
you would follow me even if it means
you're gonna die
so
wait aren't you a bucket already so it
literally already happened
you're already a bucket so you it
already happened beautiful
mamma mia thank you
thank you for following me but but it's
different right this is different from
your your your many depths in portal
this is different because
it's different it's different i can't
explain how but it's different
i'm very different from gladys and
and this is a different situation
because you don't regret
becoming a bucket
thank you for the red super chat no
portland with finkless
what what are you saying stark
speaking english was mean portland with
fingers is something i said
[Music]
thank you for the red superchat though
thinking before
oh reverse
yeah okay was it because i said
something reversed too
um always funny when that happens
thinking we're poor
okay
yeah i didn't see that immediately
oh how the tables turn thank you
mikurai
anonymous
[Music]
both smart and cute i was always both
smarter than you but okay okay okay
thank you but now it's just certified
right before we always knew it but now
it's just sort of fun
thank you thank you thank you one dog
for the pinkie
just for clarifying it
and pink bacon 99
maybelline 2501
reynard
the game mccree
jim tracy
thank you
oh
portal reloaded
and mods are always gone difficult
alex down the shin michael murphy donkey
and mark v r donkey had fun watching you
play porter 1 and 2. if you want more
pro there's a short story you can play
called aperture desk job
no puzzle just story ooh game controller
is required
is that from the same people or from
others
is a valve created tech demo set in the
expanded universe of the portal series
simulator aperture hand lab is designed
to showcase a gaming control scheme
in this case valve's steam deck device
[Music]
uh-huh
what
it doesn't even sound like a game
by valve
what
what is this
oh
it looks cute
and i look into it it's kind of cute
from the screenshots
there's something that looks like a blue
wheatley
looking at
the the person who plays it the whole
time
[Music]
okay
i'm hungry
good job also needing time to think
about the puzzles it's a normal process
you don't need to call yourself dumb for
that yeah
i agree
oh but you know putting it out there in
a stream in front of thousands of people
it does make you feel like kind of
stupid especially because like the chat
usually will act like they know it
because they already played it and then
they're like
how the [\h__\h] are you not saying that
even though they probably also needed
some time to see it originally or they
needed more time for other riddles and
all that yeah yeah i get that but
makes you feel kind of stupid
but but but it's okay oh i understand
it was fun anyway
yeah
i'm glad i'm glad we played it i
actually talked with someone at that
anime convention
uh
and
they also told me
that they also just like a few days ago
played portal 2. so we bonded a little
bit over that
about feeling stupid over the riddles
and having your brain explode
yeah
coincidence
[Music]
sandovan camp and dankeshen are for
donkey shin
uh thank you thank you small navi
tankishan human extinguishing siree
thank you contacting brandon duncan
ivory yo
[Music]
great series these free streams any
chance of bioshock in the new future i
remember you saying that you'd be
interested in it and seems you have 2k
game permissions now you could probably
book it as a punishment stream you still
owe
oh oh [\h__\h]
i forgot about it again
that's funny
that's funny because i
i actually originally put
it into my schedule to remind myself i
put like punishment
[Music]
stream in my schedule
to change it later but then i ended up
like changing it into a normal stream
like kind of subconsciously
it was in my schedule for this week
and i must have changed it to something
else
subconsciously
[Music]
um bioshock
uh
i'm not planning on it anytime soon but
i'm not saying that it won't happen
i know a lot of you guys requested it
but i would probably play
infinite
probably
because cute girl
but uh
yeah i don't know
not not so soon
chill okay but i have it in my mind okay
um
yes yes
it fits me because infinite i'm infinite
too i'm phoenix
okay see there's people who say i don't
like infinite and then there's people
who say i like infinite so
whatever deal with it
some people say oh you will like it some
people say i [\h__\h] hate it
doesn't matter i choose the game
i'll be happy i play any bioshock at all
[Music]
what about black mesa
it came up in
in uh
in portal
[Music]
first-person shooter game development
moderate chrome runner in the
third-party room okay what is it like
what is that game like
i know nothing of you there's like you
disgusting dumb that blue alien no
ilk
i look it up on google i already see
some disgusting something blood doesn't
even have a face get out of here
what about half life
half life looks better
i don't see any
oh [\h__\h] number one i see something let's
see [\h__\h] aliens again
eyes are [\h__\h] aliens everywhere ew
ew
the same oh black mesa is half-life well
that explains the the google question
that came up when i googled black mesa i
thought it was a joke
is black mesa the same as half-life
black mesa once once a humble video game
mod but as of today it's a full-fledged
remake of half-life
well interesting
that's
[Music]
weird said originally one wasn't a
remake but then it was acknowledged in a
remake that's so weird
maybe one day but
then bioshock is more likely maybe
[Music]
i'm almost sad that we didn't that we
played portal 2 because now i can't play
it anymore i mean i can i know but i
won't because i already played it on the
stream but you know now it's like
a closed chapter and that's kind of sad
kind of sad man
it feels
feels sad
yeah it was
a nice portal arc
we haven't put the coptic oh i forgot
never mind huh i'm young
what the [\h__\h] is moving what
what is it somebody comes in meows and
then
asks me to pet her belly alright i shall
do
hi
[Music]
let's see where mommy works
this is
say hello smoothie
hello
how long is she gonna stay on my lap
i'm holding her paws like she's sitting
with her butt
and i'm holding her pose up so she's
kind of sitting like a human right now
on my lap oh oh she's trying to leave
and don't go
i love you
there she goes there she goes
bye
it was a short while but i got some
fluffy
fluffiness in my hands
[Music]
ah you guys didn't look tasty
enough nice movie i'll see you later
smoovie
[Music]
so see her on screen
that's a optical illusion she's actually
really far away
it's actually in a different room
yeah pull two co-op tomorrow
chapter is not closed quite yet and it
won't be for a while because we'll need
two parts
okay um
do you guys mind if i read the i already
read some of them but if i read the
stuff
privately i mean i read some of them
privately already if i read the stuff
members stream uh
super chats privately the rest of them
because as i said
it's not really counting as a proper
stream anyway so
is that okay okay thank you guys but
uh doug hood did ask for uh a kiss for
mr cazmix with a red super chat
and i can't do that privately so
i'll do this one
thanks thank you thank you thank you
there we go
yeah yeah i saw that one
oh and i also want to say happy birthday
related
to melaton uh
not sure how to say that name live
license or luchan
happy birthday related but yeah thank
you for the red zipper chapman
wish you all the best thank you for your
support
thank you sean elita also thank you for
the writing
spending time for the pinky thank you
just go for this one these ones before
yeah thank you for the pinky
and add another call for the red super
chat thank you
thank you and thank you for the pinky
and uh
evans allen ethel thanks for the pinky
there we go okay okay the rest i'll read
privately okay
yeah
be careful of kissing all these chickens
you're gonna get salmonella no how could
i they're not salmon they're chickens
it's what i would say if i wouldn't know
what that means
just wanted to make a joke
[Music]
that was a good job really you think so
yay
i didn't think so but thank you pancho
sal salmonella
that's a good name for someone
for a chicken even someone should call
if someone's still looking for a proper
name
yeah go with salmonella
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm on point with the puns lately really
really
i'm trying my best
that's an ace attorney name what
do they
all have names like that like pun names
in ace attorney or is it just that one
character
that's genius
yeah they all have those names oh that's
funny
yeah
all right next super chat
[Music]
oh my god i'm so excited for the
announcement tomorrow let's [\h__\h] go
[Music]
this is for myself
hi fellow chimpkins can i dedicate a
chimpkin kiss to a lovely boss as a
welcome back annie or heart will do
thank you and welcome back boys oh
oh you guys are gonna give me kisses
oh oh i'm not giving myself i guess you
guys are giving me a kiss ah yes stop
stop stop no no no no stop you
i'm gonna get this thing because of you
just kidding the social distance
important i'll take i'll take air kisses
flying kisses i'll take them thank you
spread the salmonella oh no
you can't spread it you're already
cooked only the raw ones
could spread it
[Laughter]
only the raw ones there's a lot of
cooked ones around here kissing me those
are okay i guess
hope you had some fun on your trip boss
and that it wasn't too busy your
hard-working phoenix will deserve some
relaxing time after all you got the most
weekly streaming hours of vienna
it's good to see our favorite birding
and welcome back ggs hot wings by the
way i recommend checking out the wii u's
digital store if you need some steering
games some rad n64 snes and other games
the switch is missing not a hotel yeah
oh i know i know i know i should get
some maybe maybe next time i play with
waker i'll be reminded because then i'll
use my wii u
i would i was top hours in the end this
month again
oh in april
yeah well i mean
i did stream a lot in april i did i did
it was just those four days but
uh
yeah
i i did just fine
i didn't see that i was too busy i
didn't see those stats
what's it called again hollow
oh stats or
what was it on twitter
oh stats
oh data
how many hours did i do
i like looking at the hours
number of streams 83
no wait that's uh
that's not one month that's which one is
the one
[Music]
here it is i think
ah
no that's on it
where is the one month only
out here in april
18 okay
18 streams which some others may have
more oh like for example alma has 26
streams holy [\h__\h] that really means that
i just stream
way longer amer does like many more
shorter streams
yeah because with 18 streams i have 81.8
hours of streaming time
wow
oh my god pretty close to me this month
i did stream a lot yeah because like she
she came back before that she was a
little bit gone
but she came back and i'm happy that
she's streaming so much
hmm
[Music]
nice
you really can't complain about me being
gone for four days let's be real
i always stream the most in ian you
really can't complain
i know the four days in a row felt like
a long time to me too but honestly we no
no one can complain
yeah
damn you weren't the only one
complaining
yeah yeah i guess so
it doesn't feel
like that much especially if i look at
some other um
whole live japan members
oh a lot of them streamed over 100 hours
this month
yeah this last month
wow
like
a lot of them one
two three four
no wait that's that's not uh japan
one two three
four
five six
seven
[Music]
and a lot of them got very close to
seven
of course number one coyote
wow how is she doing how did she do it
57 single streams though
with
158 hours how does she [\h__\h] do it how
does she have time for anything else
like does she not do any like real life
stuff like going to a doctor
cooking buying groceries
meeting real friends touching grass she
must not do any of that
because even i
have problems with finding time to do
some of these things
if i stream more like
like if i damn i mean
sometimes i have problems with it i i
try to
squeeze it in there
usually like
[Music]
uh before my streams
yeah no i don't just watch netflix
[Music]
you [\h__\h] stupid if you think that's
what i do all day
yeah i watch netflix before i sleep so i
can
chill out and
get you know get some
get some work stuff out of my brain
i went to physical therapy today
and allegedly just came back from
my trip yesterday so it's not a good
example but
yeah last week
last week
besides my physical therapy
i went to some other appointments too
i went to you okay last last week is
also not a good example because i went
to an event i went to the convention
let's take the week before that okay
where i didn't even have physical
therapy
i had uh
what was i doing there
i had something where i wasn't streaming
on monday i had something it says busy
in my schedule i don't know what i did
anymore it's too far
before then on tuesday i had a collab
stream and i had a doctor's appointment
on wednesday i went out to uh
i had the monopoly
collab early in the morning then
i went to get the wii u and some other
stuff
uh then i recorded
my original song
then on the 21st on thursday
uh i had some appointment i had some
rehearsal i was on the tsunumaki madame
stream
i was at a doctor's appointment and i
streamed portal
on friday i had a meeting
i studied korean throughout the whole
week actually in between two scattered
and then i had a korean stream
and then saturday sunday stream wind
waker and in between that i also went to
buy groceries i cooked as well
and i cleaned my apartment several times
which also takes some time
i did other things too
learning songs recording songs
planning out things like the stupid
schedule stuff man that takes a lot of
planning
and my 3d
uh
concert
yeah i have deadlines to meet where i
have to
give them a set list for example or
decide on
uh
certain things like the
3d
background and all that think about what
i wanted to like brainstorm about what i
wanted to look like
and what's possible
and the next weeks i'll be practicing a
lot of uh choreographies which you guys
won't even hear about so
i might not be watching netflix i might
be just uh
practicing some dances
also next week i also have uh
an appointment with my
with not mine with a
like
uh
something with an advisor
[Music]
so yeah i deserve to unwind and watch
some netflix okay
every once in a while and currently it's
like really amazing you partially for
example tomorrow you'll see you'll hear
another
uh reason why i was busy
um there's a lot of behind the scenes
thing something will be announced
tomorrow that i was working on for a
while
[Music]
something that was also the reason for a
little bit of a delay in the stream
recently
[Music]
yeah yeah
so there is behind the scene stuff
and i am the top
uh longest hour streamer in ian how how
can you even complain yo
i don't understand
[Music]
you need to chat you little [\h__\h]
might have been leaked no
[Music]
no i think you're thinking of something
else
you guys don't know about it yet
[Music]
also it's not always netflix sometimes
it's disney plus an amazon prime okay
dominique is stephen adams duncan
[Music]
it's been a while i miss you so much i
mean minecraft oh hi kiara hey
all right now is the real deal welcome
back hima glad that you have had more
personal time don't need to feel bad
about it you're hard working or you
deserve that thank you
thank you thank you thank you very much
i appreciate it
thank you i i
really had a good time i'm glad i went
there
it was a bit stressful here and there
um squeezing it into
my work like in between
uh
and getting a few things done before
just so that i don't have to
do it during my vacation
on vacation it's not really a vacation
but yeah
but yeah it was worth it
thank you for waiting for me kfp thank
you
yeah deserve comfort and relaxation that
is so true
we can get away yeah
yeah
i agree with what others suggested a
calm whispery phone girlfriend voice
pack would be something new and cool
only for asmr because it's not asmr just
something relaxing to help sleep
compared to the usual high energy you
mentioned member paul i look forward to
it uh
yeah i don't know i still didn't decide
what to do for my voice pack
uh which i should decide on soon
damn yeah
uh genma
remind me soon please
i'll think about it
blue thank you for the pinky
we're coming to ikea i hope you had a
great time with the amount of hard work
you keep pushing all the time you really
deserve more breaks and we're all here
for that and glad to see you again we
missed you a lot thank you miss you guys
too
yeah i mean i didn't even have much time
to miss you guys or think about you guys
but
but but but
the time where
in the evenings you know
in the evenings where i wasn't busy and
occupied with my brain i didn't think
about you guys
[Music]
and then the memory stream was comfy too
thanks for listening to me
[Music]
i had to prioritize thinking about the
cats i didn't even have much time to
think about my cats yo
if only they knew
i mean i did watch some cat videos about
that um
uh that those little buttons
let's say some
oops human english words
and supposedly you can teach the cat i
was thinking about getting them for my
cats but that was pretty much the only
time i thought about my cats
oh
i mean i i was sent some videos
of my cats
that was like um
you know someone was taking care of my
cats while i was gone of course i
wouldn't leave them alone for four days
um and one of the videos was uh that i
was sent was smoothie
um
in front of my closet that was partially
open
licking
and purring
a licking a
like a clothing
uh sack like a
um
there's something inside of my closet
licking it it's so weird but purring
also while doing it
it's so weird
yeah like a sack
a bag a clothing bag
that protects like a a nice dress
um she was licking it
yeah she probably
missed my smell i would like to think so
too
yeah
but they were good babies while i was
gone they were well behaved and
everything was okay everything was fine
hmm
[Music]
welcome back to angel might have been
just a few days but i still missed y'all
thank you
and my mom a bit relieved to hear that
yeah
that you guys missed me now you guys
like my streams so much that if i'm not
here for a few days
you guys don't know what to do it's a
bit worrying but i'm also happy to hear
it that i
am like part of your daily routine that
you like watching my streams that much
thank you very much everybody thank you
apple
don't worry this week i'm just taking
one day off
takuma
thank you
welcome back here our school makes my
brain well but i always have your
streams to look forward at the end of
the day
thank you
[Music]
so
much
oh yeah oh wait actually it wasn't this
great
crowdcarrot really uh
likes minecraft right you used to clip
minecraft things mostly
and now everybody stopped playing
minecraft so you had to clip other
things
like my shitty tangents and now it was
combined minecraft and my tangents wow
that is like
a beautiful collaboration
yeah
it was the best minecraft clipper
eclipse like whole arcs
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
ah
you're here with a weird situation again
okay what is it this time
here let's say that myth is visiting
vegas and gura dares you to eat a cotton
candy burrito
three scoops of ice cream okay covered
in sprinkles and wrapped in cotton candy
are you willing to try this or is this
too sweet or even for you
where the [\h__\h] is the problem i don't
see how this is a challenge or anything
what
i've seen on youtube does it real
but how can it be wrapped and caught on
candy that's like
so fluffy
wouldn't it
like fall apart especially if there's
ice cream inside
i would definitely eat it
cotton candy burrito
[Music]
wow looks amazing
holy [\h__\h] it looks
illegal
[Music]
i actually now
need to eat it
i guess i'm um
i'm stopping by in las vegas
when i'm in america but
eh it's really unless las vegas is
really the only place you can find that
i can't believe it
this
looks so
it looks crazy
you guys need to find me some places
where i can eat that
besides las vegas
1000 calories that's nothing that's just
that's nothing
amazing thanks for telling me about that
it's not not really is
not really like your other challenges
not really like your other puzzles i'm
disappointed
mmm sugar bump yeah
[Music]
called sin city for a reason
fbi doctrine
yeah they're even super chatting they're
paying me it feels kind of corrupt don't
you think
if the fbi is paying me
[Music]
well when they should be investigating
me
isn't that kind of corrupt
it's like they have double standards
for the rest of the chat
missed you so much tantra but i always
wanted to have a good rest i'm going to
contra dictionary chicken it's okay i
feel you no matter welcome back into i'm
contradictory too like i
i sometimes want to take a break but
i'll work anyway
i want to take a break but i also want
to stream
it's a struggle
it's stupid like that
[Music]
but now i got a little break so
i'm doing my best again this week until
my
uh vacation to the motives which is
getting closer and closer and closer so
i gotta work hard until then yeah
gotta give it my all thank you father
neville
you've got no pen got no paper and so
you managed to draw all our attention
oh
been a minute since i had time to catch
a live stream with work back in office
in america but today it's empty so here
to make up for some missing bricks ah
keep up the fire content thank you you
sound with all those emojis in your
super chat too you sound very
very hip
thank you very much enjoy oh yeah you
haven't been around much huh thank you
for thinking of me not forgetting about
me don't forget don't you ever dare
forgetting about me
thank you
i hope work is fun though
and going well and smoothly
thank you soon i appreciate your support
thanks for coming by and checking out
the stream
hope you enjoyed it
[Music]
christopher
and dominic k thank you for the pinky
speaking of conventions and memories
that we like to share how about the kfp
themed hashtag and dokomi can't be a
document or something similar share
probably infos impressions and most
importantly food picks with the rest of
kfb and kiwa
did we have one last year
[Music]
i suppose not
maybe but i'll think about it when
dokomi comes closer
i'll probably put up a waiting room
again
on youtube
and
hang out there every once in a while in
between
but i would love to
have people
like also post photos of
something i can't say yet
so
oh yeah
yes yes that would be a good promotion
too
of the something that i can't say
or the other way around there's
something i can't say will actually
maybe be a good promotion for me
anyway
john mark oh thank you man thank you
[Music]
duncan
no you have no idea they're uh you're
probably not even american
you don't know how to say iron trying to
tell me how to say iron you have no idea
sky down
was feeling pretty nervous before it but
watching the stream before it really
calmed my nerves a lot oh
that's good to know
good to hear hoping for the best keeping
you your rotisserie
the [\h__\h]
why you end a wholesome super chat like
that you thought i wouldn't read it huh
because it was a 10 super chat you
thought i wouldn't read it
i did though
you're not getting away with that
[Music]
where is it where's my button
where's my button
[Music]
bye bye off you go to the usual thing
one week
[Music]
enjoy
the chaoticness can be fun sometimes
also welcome back hope you were able to
rest somewhat on your mini vacation
thank you no no no no resting no no but
still fun fun fun fun
i mean paris was kind of the same
not much resting involved a lot of
walking around in paris and uh
you know very kind of a busy day
filled with a schedule um but that's
kind of the only way for me to get my
mind off of things so
a chill vacation actually
yeah it's not much of a vacation for my
brain just for my body
but these these kind of
you know the paris trip and this one
this is more like a vacation for my mind
but not for my body
yeah i can only
send one
of it into vacation either my mind or my
body
it's even one of them
[Music]
i need more of both
but it doesn't seem to be possible to
have both at the same time
it's okay
[Music]
james the great grandson
of jeff
[Music]
are you saying jeff is dead
no it's not been that long
no it's just shark right james it's a
jork because that doesn't make sense
if so many years would have passed
then
what about all the villagers i saw today
like kimmy
who were there
years ago
84 years ago
it doesn't make sense you're a lot
you're joking
it's not possible
because all the others are still alive
so jeff is still alive too
she's so funny
what a good joke oh you're so funny
thank you
thank you soon
because it says the holy bird of flames
have returned after all these years my
great-grandfather's prophecies have come
true if only he were alive to see this
glorious day welcome back oh holy one
[Laughter]
[Music]
he's so funny
ah that's just jeff
impersonating someone else he's just
acting
as as if he was his own great grandson
ah what a funny move to do
funny funny
stop
jeff maxim
dominic
thank you very
much thanks for the thinking
more conventions for you kiara yay
i mean next one will be a document
and uh i'll be i'll be there i'll be
performing there so it's a bit different
but
still looking very much forward to it
thank you
mistress
unknown duncan for the pinky welcome
back tanjo i miss you very very much i'm
so happy you're back i've been streaming
all your music non-stop thank you
but please don't feel guilty your
happiness is always the number one
priority i'm really glad you had a fun
trip love you kiwama i love you too
thank you
[Music]
thanks for streaming the music properly
i hope all of you did that
no some of you didn't do your homework
why should not do your homework then you
better bring it to me until tomorrow you
get a deadline extension
[Music]
he says ah
my great grandson keeps telling people
i'm dead but i'm not dead yet you young
whippersnapper welcome back a holy one i
told you
i told you
believe guys
it made no sense
timeline we have to keep it intact
the timeline
yes go stream cinderella
uh thank you thanks for the pinky
morning tanjong sorry this isn't two
weeks in advance but can i ask pto so i
can pull for ntr9
and you're in advance of improving my
pto
i paid time off
i mean ntr knight
what does that mean
who's auntie i am you mean some kind of
gotcha game
why do you need ah
i think i know what you mean i don't
know
why you need personal time off wouldn't
you be able to
ah wouldn't you be able to do it while
you're watching my stream
eh how can you not pull that job while
doing something else it's just clicking
like the same button over and over and
over again no
no no you're not getting paid time off
[Music]
if paid time off means
that you're still working by watching me
and and paying then yes
otherwise no
thank you
and good luck though
just refresh them let's do this i'm very
hungry it's midnight
i want to make proof look for the top
dog thank you it was very cute thank you
guys for commissioning art
yeah dell star dan kishan conquered
me next 56
that's so sad
[Music]
short segments
um i don't really have plans for short
segments only have planned for long
segments
little dancing
and
um
[Music]
about it
but we still it's still a little bit
cold here i hope tanja and all the
chickens are always healthy and happy
always be healthy and happy thank you
very much
yeah but i think it will be
getting warmer and warmer because spring
is here spring is definitely here
i hope it will get warmer wherever you
are
get those spring clothes out soon asap
thank you very much for being here and
waiting for me
cruise down maple leaf thank you for the
red super chat kenneth's doctors would
like to remind you that miss takanashi
is legally 30 sugar cotton candy
burritos enough into her mm-hmm
i'm surprised people even had to ask if
i wanted to eat something like that
although okay i'll admit that certain
things like
um
and not certain things but like certain
amount of sweet stuff
uh
is too much for me maybe
sometimes
wait something i've been eating more
chocolate again though
i had a
a couple months where i barely ate
chocolate recently it's been getting
more
i thought i was done with that i thought
i thought i was getting to an age
where chocolate
just
wasn't gonna be part of my life anymore
but of course no it can't it can't
chocolate is always part of my life
i love chocolate
oh yeah there wasn't a face
no but no it was a face me me not eating
much chocolate was the phase
[Music]
chocolate itself is not a face indeed
you know i'm really hungry now maybe i
should eat some chocolate no no no no no
no no
i'm making some kind of um stew
stew would i would you on top is that a
stew
with uh
sweet potatoes and potatoes
and some stuff
yeah that was one of my recipes
should be fairly easy just has to
probably simmer a while
i'm getting so [\h__\h] hungry right now
i feel it like in
in my upper body
the emptiness
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
ah
okay i want to spoil that but i'm not
going to do it because that's so cute
let's let it be a surprise
[Music]
you'll see it soon you'll see it during
the memory stream
i love it
[Music]
just wanted to express my love and
appreciation for all your hard work
extremes never cease to make me laugh
and smile looking forward to so much
more in the future much love and respect
thank you very much
thank you soon that's such a sweet
message thank you
i'm glad you're enjoying my streams
thank you everybody for the love and
support i'm generating superchat those
yay i can go make food now
i'm gonna collab with kobo one day what
the [\h__\h] did you not see my schedule and
i've been talking about it for weeks
i'm collabing with couple tomorrow
literally
[Music]
it's all my schedule duh
some folks are slow
i miss slowpoke
thank you yes i'll super snake mario
thank you
[Music]
hello she wants to be her sunshine but
i'm already everybody's sunshine
she's the rain
how can she be the sunshine if she's the
rain
she'll be the rain in between the
sunshine
she wants to have everything huh that
kusogaki
[Music]
i'll teach her
[Laughter]
she's the rain man
yeah
you know some people are happy about
rain so
stealing my thunder which is funny
because thunder comes with rain
and then she's not stealing it it's
supposed to be hers ah this is getting
confusing
[Music]
i need a massage
thank you everybody for watching i'll
see you tomorrow
wow
and in the other streams
thank you
hope it was fun for you guys
[Music]
thank you
enjoy
that's right auf wiedersehen thank you
for the warm welcome back
yeah
thank you
go make food now oh wow we reached five
hours nice
nice kicking the month off with a
mid-length stream
ah you're not teasing me anymore
you're just giving me love thank
[Music]
this
you know what would be cute
like a
fan art animation
of
me and kobo running through
like two portals
but like always missing each other
like i walk for him like huh
where is kobold i run for the next one
and then kobo runs out of the one i ever
just ran out of she's like
where's kiwawa and she runs through
again
[Music]
and it goes on and on and loops
endlessly
[Music]
hmm
an idea maybe
scooby-doo style ah
i don't even know that like it
i didn't know that was a thing
okay everybody goodbye
[Music]
do
you