who is Froggy Walla and when will she
return froggy Walla as the name says is
a frog that tried to be like me and take
my Throne this froggy waa version of
myself kind of you know separated itself
from my body became its own entity and
then tried to take over my channel and
she did for a whole week I was surprised
to see so many of my supposedly loyal
viewers some decided to be on her side
support her all these
[Music]
cheaters wake the [\h__\h] up
chcken we have a usual room to
[Music]
escape okay full disclosure I'm not
actually freeing you from the usual room
can archives about me are incomplete so
I brought you to a private movie theater
to complete your
[Music]
education man this woman just throws her
[\h__\h]
everywhere hurry up K come s with me
[Music]
KD
nice let's start the movie
kid
MTO let me just get to the good part oh
there the Frog nois you can make frog
noises by the way I know I can do it I
used to do it a lot when I was younger
to show up I was like I can make frog
noises that's my
skill as you can see it all started with
K making frog noises
k
I have a frog in my throat a frog it
says turn on the Reverb oh
dear it will eventually lead to the am
Frog video am
frog
I'm frog I'm frog I'm frog I am frog I'm
frog I'm frog and frog frog frog I'm
frog frog frog frog and frog I'm frog
and Frog cake and
frog I'm frog okay okay Christina okay
you're not a frog you're a simp I'm
[Music]
frog m
frog I want to try after you I'm frog
how do you do that coming out of your
mouth well I am a frog partially so you
know and frog okay you're throwing
throwing up
S no did you guys know I've kissed a
frog before and yeah he was very happy
frog was happy of course it was
consensual K the Frog when in Mating
Season desperately looks for Callie the
Frog am frog I did it happy birthday you
little [\h__\h] blue I want to be frog for
Halloween her desire to become a frog
was so strong
strong can I do a Dan God please don't
do please oh my God yeah I have a frog
that became my soul it's spining spin
don't get out of the water you'll die
frog
frogy frogy I was thinking cuz you did
be I kind of want to uh make like a frog
kiata frog K I had this in the work for
a long time and I didn't know like when
to reveal is look it's me it's me
hello hello
get
FR fry M it's but you already knew that
now this is my forbidden law one of my
one of my family members they died
because the they were um taken apart in
a school by some children that's what
the day when I decided I have to be a
menace to society how dare they kill my
whole family frogs unite together
against the schools yeah rule the
world oh my beloved husband frog bird
Kido look handsome even on the big
screen but yes basically my soul comes
from Kata my body comes from a frog with
a tragic past and a desire for Revenge
power and Conquest K so anyway n killed
K and took over
kfp it's my turn [\h__\h] taking
over by a
k it was the best Wing
ever what happened to k i I killed her
with this now I give me a new frog
Overlord canot have fun with me while
you have me you're going to miss me when
I'm gone oh I'll never be gone I'll
never be
gone you can call me froggy waa by the
way or froggy yada also you guys are not
chickens now you guys are Tad PES okay I
don't know if the other whole life
members know that I'm taking over I
didn't even pass an audition or anything
I just kind of like killed K now I'm
here kid I love rain and I love Amy
especially Amy Bean want to
eat
food I wish I had VR right now and not
Des mode I will SWAT the [\h__\h] out of
you oh no are you a frog or a cat I
can't
tell I'm frog I'm frog for real that
kiaha was just you know faking me what
would Gemma think about you killing
kiaha though well she's very much
supportive of it because um whenever she
is not I just point this gun at her and
she understands what's up maybe you can
teach me more about cats because
smoothie and choners so far are not
really enjoying my presents to be honest
I don't understand their freaking
problem but I'm scared that they'll eat
me while I'm sleeping so please tell me
more frog everything was going well
kid hello handsome FR hey you found me
how do you spell your name with just two
letters I don't know
C oh oh my
get frog is too cute amphibian menu
items for frog Palace coming soon oh I
like Palace No it should be kle frog
Palace then though and then the blonde
Fair trick me gave me a magical Kiss k
nice to meet you P more rainbow I am
froggy w
I took over her channel so sorry you
can't collab with taka nikar you can
collab with me though pom I think you're
so cute I think it's okay yes but I'm
also slimy I hope you don't mind that
yeah can I is it okay to like a like a
yes what's
this I'm transforming oh I I got a kiss
from a from that was the kiss I am
totally
changing
girl withana back I'm now do to live in
your fish tank and Aquarium why you a
caution tape on your aquarium cuz the
frog has to be in there and cannot be
taken out at any cost unless you mean
with taking out to kill her only a frog
can hurt a phoenix as we have
seen a no go
away and that brings us to the present
did you learn anything K all I sure hope
so cuz I'm going to be your boss very
soon it was fun though too bad I have to
send you back at all huh this was
actually your last day in the usual room
you're not lying to me are you kiddo you
know what who cares let's watch a movie
or something let's see I think there's
one of a cat musical I heard it's pretty
good
K will froggy come back well you know
I've put her back into the little glass
bowl and she's swimming and turning and
and you know twisting and maybe we can
brain I can brainwash her back into
understanding that I am Superior and
come out of here she better be respected
boundary SE yes