[Music]
do
hello oh god i'm still lagging a little
bit yeah
i know everyone five if it's
shut up
oh i hope it's really not that bad do
you
oh is this really that bad
come on hello 10 fps 5
fps 15 fps at best
uh well at least today
i'm connected uh to youtube from my main
pc
and not from my laptop from a wi-fi
so yeah it's a we have a little bit of
an
improvement today uh let me drink some
water
so we're back in freddie nevermind yeah
but i think it keeps on switching yeah
so now it's like lagging again and then
sometimes it gives me
30 fps again i would like it to be 60
fps
everyone how are you doing have you no i
haven't thank you for telling me
let me tweet
i almost have 500k twitter followers if
you haven't been following my twitter
account yet now's the time to do it you
might be the number 500 000
twitter follower starting now
[Music]
ew what is that thing gosh i i need some
kind of
fly trap or something just use all these
kind of like
mostly like really really tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny shitty flies here
and i don't even know why it's not like
there's any food here
in this room mary very suspicious
okay i have tweeted yeah y'all are
already welcome to retweet my tweet
thank you thank you kindly
and this feels so weird
this feels so weird i want to hear some
bgm but i've been having some weird
issues with like i suppose my go xlr
i don't know just i told you before
about this audio issue
and it's so weird i i don't even wanna
i'm gonna ask
am i later about because i'm gonna um
don't frax eat flies i'm frog
i have a collab with emma later uh from
from my time zone that's at midnight
gmt plus one midnight uh i'm gonna ask
her
because she knows the most about go xlr
it's so weird but this
like i didn't change anything about my
setup but something is really
weird i can hear my
my microphone feedback but i cannot hear
any
audio that i play from the pc and i
already tried a bunch of things
tried uh like changing the
audio output device to every single
option i tried updating the drivers but
apparently they were already
updated uh
and yeah i tried playing around with the
ghost but yeah
things are not really working but as
long as i
can hear my own voices feedback that's
at least not that lonely i would prefer
to have a
a bgm dough at least you guys hear bgm
a community post already done
an update on the bamboozle thing
there is a chance that maybe tomorrow
or so i would i would hope tomorrow
it would be fixed because uh
yeah some steps have been taken
today youtube has been
quite slow with helping us out
but we have our side has been reacting
in
lightning speed thank you janma
for um working so fast on that
i wish my i wish my cats would be able
to
hunt those flies um
jmt jmt jmt
also i've been blue clapper
also i've been uh looking at the
internet providers you know if i'm gonna
get a second internet provider
but like it seems like the
best option and this is absolutely
ridiculous that this is the best
option at least in the place where i
live right now
the best option for like 100 euro per
month
thousand embeds down
50 n bits up
400 in japan i was paying less than 100
i think
and i got like 500 600 on both sides or
even 800 sometimes
what the [\h__\h] is this you're kidding me
100 i mean what choice do i have but it
seems like
the prices here in australia
for reasonable internet
are ridiculous this is not even good
internet 50
m bit up that's the best you can give me
at least give me like 100 amp it up like
what
unbelievable do i have to move like but
i heard like in germany it's like also
shitty
so it's just all in europe i guess i
don't know
but i mean even that is i guess a bit
better than what i currently have so i'm
thinking of getting it but
hundred hundred no wait thousand
thousand embeds
up but i mean uh down
down thousand embeds down but that still
means like i'm not i'm definitely not
gonna get thousands of bits right i'm
gonna get like what
[Music]
500 at its best maybe i mean that's
that's okay that's cool
but upload 50.
what oh dear lord i mean i think that's
better though than what i have
fifty what is that and and that says uh
it says it's uh
uh uh the the the fiber
fiber thingy uh but
let's someone who i know from a
different internet provider he told me
that even if it says
um glass faza
uh what's it called
what's what's it called
glass fiber really it's just the same in
english
optic fiber even if it says that
it doesn't apparently doesn't mean that
it's actually that
i don't know it's ridiculous like
there's this this guy that i know from
from an internet provider and he told me
that even if it says it's a glass fiber
chances are it's not glass fiber and i'm
like what
what you you charge me for
glass fiber internet but apparently it's
not
clap what what and what
what
so and yeah then there's this this this
specific internet provider
has an option for 5g but this isn't
available
where i live in like in the street where
i live
so yeah i guess in the end the only
option for better internet
is moving and prior or to choosing an
actual apartment
um looking up if that specific apartment
has
that 5g option available so that will be
my main
my main reason to get an apartment like
oh do you have 5g
dough no okay and [\h__\h] this beautiful
apartment i need
i need some apartment that has 5g
but does this that's five to even work
in australia really
is that is that not just a legend is
that not just a myth
yeah i know i can look up the address
before i move yeah yeah yeah yeah i was
gonna do that
um but yeah let's see how long we can
stay in this apartment i don't want to
move too
soon you know i just moved here i don't
want to have the whole thing
happening again uh
um soundport i mean i don't think that
soundproof is really necessary because
uh i can at least get like a pretty huge
apartment
and then have like several rooms in an
apartment and then use like a room
for streaming that's like in between
other rooms
so i think and also walls are just much
thicker so i really don't think that the
sound will be a problem
um
is there anyone in australia who can
confirm that 5g
actually exists and it's not just a myth
uh because i don't believe it
if they already lied to me about glass
fiber and say that
it says glass fiber but it's not glass
fiber then what am i even supposed to
believe what that what
what what
5g work we don't know if 5g works for
streaming may not work without 5g is
mobile
[Music]
[Laughter]
what am i supposed to do what is what is
4g by the way
it's like what i don't understand what
what are those things like
what does that even mean does 5g mean
that i can get 5000 mbits
is that like like this one okay this one
says
class fiber thousand m bits uh download
speed but does 5g mean i could in theory
get 5000
emits download
no but what does it mean then
so everything with g is just mobile
so 4g 5g that's all just mobile what
what do i do if i want faster internet
for my for my pc though
[Applause]
damn
my internet provider dude told me to get
a business account
but even then like that what does that
actually do i get
i get better like support but speed wise
it doesn't really do much at least i
think that's what
he said uh
um
i usually have more upload ah
better upload speed um okay well
i'll discuss all of that sometimes i
mean i really i really have to see how
long i can go with the current
uh current internet speed like
it really bothers me that i'm lagging
just like
i don't you know what don't we have
minecraft this week
oof i wonder if minecraft like
surprisingly minecraft takes up quite a
lot of internet speed
as we have experienced before with bad
internet speed i wasn't really able to
play minecraft properly
so i'm gonna be interesting
if i can actually if i can't play
minecraft that's gonna be so sad like
minecraft is such a fun game that i can
play anytime and like collab with the
other girls so easily
yeah yeah
the thing is that in japan like there
was this time
where like during prime time my internet
would be like total [\h__\h]
but then after a while like it fixed
itself and then i didn't have any
internet problems anymore and everything
was fine like whenever i would play
it seemed to be fine
so
[Music]
go to
well well well have you changed the
latency setting back
after using your pocket wi-fi i can see
some wait you mean on youtube yeah i
i have uh changed it back but i have
uh i mean it's cool i want i don't wanna
i don't wanna
change it back to the pocket wi-fi
setting again because then the chat is
like so late i can't really have proper
conversations with you guys and i prefer
to have proper conversations with you
did you post your stream on reddit no i
didn't for this one i i did it on
purpose
because i thought like
like i don't know it's kind of weird
to be like hey this is my super chat
reading stream
please come like i don't know it's it's
a super chat reading stream
it feels weird advertising that on
reddit
i i don't know uh but hey
[Music]
um
it's a thousand four hundred people here
i'm actually surprised yeah
quite actually i'm surprised thank you
guys thank you
actually more than i thought there would
be here
that's that's about the same amount we
have for ryza most of the time
now that's just [\h__\h] sad oh
[\h__\h] this freaking shadow man i hate it
so much it's ridiculous
i could cry honestly oh my god okay
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] though um does anyone
like i know that we
we stopped reading super chats at a
mario kart stream
somewhere in the middle uh
with someone like the name was something
with donald
uh but
i looked through the super chats there's
one donald
irvi not sure if i really stopped but
also this donald already
sent more than one super jet so where
exactly did i stop
ah
some there's more was it donald irving
like i cannot hear any sound on my pc
right now so i can't even listen back to
it unless i use my phone or something
uh did it sound like donald irving when
i was reading that
really did it sound like that okay but
there's like
three free donald irvi super
in the mario kart stream does someone
know which one came
right before the donald irvi super chat
was it timothy burke
or was it will adolf or was it
candy pop 97 any idea
oh gosh i'm so hungry
you know what today i ordered my
roommate you know she's been
all through this to this whole situation
um
my roommate has been very active in
ordering i mean she's been doing that
since before already but
she has even more reason now to order
lots of food like she orders
food a lot and and she recommended me
this place to order food
because they got like really good like
waffles with
with fruit and all that and i ordered it
for for breakfast
oh those were so good and i ordered a
salad with it so i can eat it later
thanking for thinking to the future what
uh what a
um futuristic verb i am
yes rmt
and so yeah uh where did i stop reading
someone said the first one but how do
you know it was the first one
that was my hand blanking against the
table
uh
actually me and my roomie made a
breakfast that we're gonna a breakfast
what
promise i think i'm thinking too much of
food
me and my roommate made a promise that
we would order
uh ramen today but
she's doing this thing where she won't
eat food after a specific time i think
it's already over
let me i mean what's that hurt
is it too late uh
this one too strong
no my
[Music]
real common
and yeah into into that fast
inter intermittent fasting
i think it's already too late
mia
okay i think we'll eat ramen tomorrow
okay it's too late she can't eat food
anymore
i hope she ate something else though
[Music]
it actually works if i do it correctly
yeah i think like a bunch of my friends
have done that before
and apparently she actually lost a lot
of weight
yeah so damn
damn respect
all right oh well i'll eat my i'll eat
my salad eventually
i certainly don't even have that many
super chats to read i think
because i did a good job in like
reading the every super chat since i
arrived
so it shouldn't even be that many and
but where is this where's the mario kart
thumbnail
oh yeah wait
mario ah where is it
i don't have it okay whatever i'm
reading tomorrow and we're reading the
mario kart super jet but i still don't
know where exactly i'm supposed to
continue
is there any anyone here like is for
example
okay is uh timothy are you here
timothy burke are you here did i read
you super chat last time
where you said you're 12th place in
mario kart 8 but first place in mind
what
what a flirt oh man
uh or is that oh it's not a toaster i
hear an hour toaster did i read your
super chat
it's the one next to can
i see a and why
candy pop you mean candy pop
candy pop 97 did i read that one
[Music]
you stopped reading super chat on the
mario kart stream after two super chat
of general and two super chat of daisy
bald and no the last one was donald
wait there's another one from donald
azanai
was below him
not on the super chat reading from 20
now that the last super chat reading was
in the sliver dot io stream
i finished the takamoni concert
superchats i did i did
the last one was sliver.io and where i
read it
i read until my mario kart somewhere in
the middle
it's adam donald really
well i think i've seen that
i hear will adolf and then donald so i
must have
i must have read like slurpee about 9000
james will adolf donald irvi
irving was a pinky i think i remember
the last one being a pinky
i read there are over 8 000 of us here
right now coordination on
yeah i read this one before also did you
know your wife is a shotakon yeah was
that the last one
oh hey mel adolf is here then you
probably know what you're talking about
oh okay i got it i got it
[Music]
yeah unforgettable actually how come we
forgot about that
super chat from donald
okay okay continuing
[Music]
i think i was the one who stole your
item at the end of the rainbow road race
please don't send me to the usual room
daisy
at least you were honest enough to admit
your problem your your
your mistake danielle
thank you thanks for taking the time to
stream even though it's a busy week for
you can do what's best for you we'll
support you no matter what love your
attention thank you
thank you sarcastic light 476
here's some snack money for your trip
boss ah thank you actually at the
airport once i arrived
in germany i actually had a problem
with money i only had like yen with me
but i had my bank account card my
european
australian one so that usually works in
inside of europe with no problem but
it
wait what exactly happened
what no it did work
what was my problem ah
it didn't work out like a drink machine
i couldn't
baby two is trying to clean baby one
what is going on
will baby one tolerate it she didn't uh
usually she didn't tolerate it much
baby two is is licking baby one's head
oh my god this is too cute to be true
oh she's licking and looking when will
baby one slap
baby two when will she give her a [\h__\h]
lap huh
she's sleeping by the way maybe that's
why she's tolerating it normally she
doesn't ah
maybe two got distracted baby two is
looking outside of the room baby two
this is is it's dissenting herself and
stretching baby two is stretching like a
cute fat chunky baby
cute okay eh that's it
baby two has jumped down from the bed
and baby one is continuing to sleep
safe and sound
[Laughter]
commentator photon now this is good
television i wish i could show you guys
i wish i could just you know
do a cat stream and then you know you
know how i did the cooking stream
now i'll just not appear at all with my
hands i'll just be
having the camera to the cats on my bed
and then you know
i wish i could do that but i can't
probably not
this just in baby two is continuing to
sleep yeah baby one is continuously baby
two is like
i don't know i think she probably is
going to get some food or going to poop
yeah i wish i could do a cat cam
ah that would be fun that would be fun
um
you'll box them exactly that's the
problem i don't want to box my cats
i mean they don't go outside so that's
that but yeah
make the cats wear something oh like
black gloves
maybe maybe that maybe then i get
permission to yeah
show them on stream if i make them wear
black gloves maybe
maybe that would be acceptable
i don't think so though
reveal
i mean one would think that my cats are
already wearing socks
yeah they are
they are already wearing socks it's just
uh
fur socks
they need their own model that's gonna
be expensive
let's let's do a gofundme for youtube
remodels for my cats
i hear my cat eating front crunch crunch
crunch
they're done i'm a member now thank you
for joining welcome
aren't they wearing gloves and gloves i
i i i guess yeah they're already wearing
gloves
we'll donate oh yeah it's uh
ask ahmed how she got her [\h__\h]
oh my god oh you mean do you mean the
fruity dancing
one i'm talking about that one
thank you for the membership sneaky
waffle welcome
are you talking about that one oh my god
no oh my god imagine someone making
a 3d version of my cats in that cursed
style oh no please don't do it
no don't do it don't do it don't do it
no i don't want to say it no
no that's so cursed no
oh baby gonna jump into my closet and
sleep inside my closet because i left
the door open
i see you there i see you i see you and
come on jump you can go in junkie baby
oh and no oh she changed her mind
because she
the jump seems too difficult for her
oh no she's trying again oh oh
oh you can do it you can do it
oh good
i only have one door open uh of my
closet
and it was kind of hard for her to get
in there so she's
she had some issues with her chunkiness
to
fit in between that small small
space
gosh i'm so hungry i'm so hungry
maybe okay you know what i'll get my
salad brb
i got a nice summer salad
[Music]
you like that face i did it on purpose
so you wouldn't make fun of any funny
faces
oh baby sits on my chair now oh go away
okay
she's so nice that when i when i try to
sit on my chair she goes away
there's not enough space for the both of
us okay i got the salad let me explain
my salad to you
suddenly she's jumping around in my bed
playing with a with a toy
gosh cute yesterday they were playing
like with like a
small um
a piece of paper that's like
crumpled crinkle
balled up yeah a balled up piece of
paper like a really tiny one
they just like you know they they played
with that like they played soccer with
that for a whole apartment
they got really excited about it
honestly why even buying
pet toys when they play uh around with
like
crumbled up paper and like enjoy it and
have the
like a hell of a time like oh my god i
can't open this freaking salad
like they
they even they don't even need me to
have fun they just play with that piece
of paper
and shoot it around in in the apartment
and just have the time of their life
it's amazing
oh there we go so my salad has
you know the green stuff in it and it
has a
radissian what's radiation in english
and tomatoes and and uh
and i think
something like prosciutto and
uh and oranges and some melons
the orange yellow yeah a radish no no no
radish i think it's a different thing
how do you see this having something
else
radish no no no
green stuff is just the leaves okay
hello baby yeah this is a summer
like really refreshing summer salad i
think it's interesting that they put
oranges in here and the dressing is
apparently also something with
orange something something okay let's
pour that sexy
dressing all over them
[Music]
oh yeah this is going to be yummy oh
yummy
okay addition is radish
okay i give up
okay no let me let me eat one bite
is
hmm
that's a really good dressing
room let me get some of that
brush brussels doll
and with an orange yeah you give me that
orange hmm
m
salad with like fruit in it i think it's
just genius not many people do it
but it's genius
did you hear the crunch
[Music]
i'm definitely gonna order at this place
again
that's so yummy the waffles were already
so good
and like when i get like pancakes
or waffles with like fruit somewhere
they usually
barely add enough fruit and with every
bite
of the waffle or the pancake i want at
least one piece of
fruit with it
but so most places they don't give you
enough fruit so it's like always always
too much waffle or too much
pancake ratio compared to the fruit yeah
you know what i mean the struggle
but this one that i ordered today oh i
had to stick about
the right way he actually had too much
food so at the end i was eating like
a few pieces of strawberries like on the
side
unbelievable love it
yummy
let's get that tomato oh that's a big
bite
um
hmm no
that's so good i can't stop eating damn
my cats are so interested um
about the the window and the birds
outside
i don't even see any birds outside i
don't know what they're seeing
also when i look outside
everything in my room because i turned
on like outside is dark and everything
in the room
like is like mirroring itself on the
window
that's what i see i wonder
if they have a different sight
i guess if i try hard i can see kind of
what's going on outside
they seem to be seeing more than i do
[Music]
my cat just walked over my laptop and
turned on a youtube video that i was
watching
no youtube now no youtube now
my cats they someone asked if they make
those cute chirping noises when they see
a bird actually today for the first time
i think i've heard
uh one of my cats doing that sound but
only for a really really really really
really short time
it's interesting that uh when i lived
with them together in two years time
they never had a conversation with a
bird
or except for me obviously
but outside i never saw a bird before
but it seems like this is something that
they have um started
uh to do while i was gone and now
they're like really into looking outside
to see some birds
that's like their thing now so i'll
probably hear more
of that chirping sound in the future
i i i heard it today for the first time
like i used to hear it from
my old cat when i lived with my mom and
so on
we had a cat that did that a lot and
so i know i know it's like super cute
but my cats never do it
um
now the vinegar is really really strong
they can look at you every day full-time
bird
i think they look at me thinking i'm
a cat since i'm your mama
that's why they don't talk to me in
their
chattering language when they see me
even though i am a bird
food
um
we don't talk to you in chattering
language too yes because you are burps
too
yeah our chickens did you forget
a super cat stream
this is now a super cat stream we're not
super chatting we're super catting
that's all right with me
that's why the super chats are turned
off it was never about the super chats
bamboozle it's always been a super cat
stream
everything is only about the super cats
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay one more bite one more butt
one more big bite
with melon and with
and one secret orange
damn that's so good
ah 48 minutes of similar super chat i
didn't know i did already read some
i didn't already read them
yummy
one good thing about this
um
is that so many new places
that didn't didn't do delivery before
are now doing delivery
mark not only here i think everywhere
everywhere in every country have you
guys noticed
so many more people maybe in america
everything already does delivery because
of ubereats the thing is like we don't
have uber
eats
we have uber uber but we don't have
ubereats we have like different
um services
for that um and yeah anyway so now
way more uh places bring more
restaurants to delivery than before way
more
yeah it's pretty cool so okay
continuing to read the super chats where
did i stop now
zero deaths rtg donkey shin
feign 40k i've got that one
thank you for the red super chat just
want to say we'll navigate
no matter what this coming week spring
will re well you as you see it brought
me freaking shadow band
we will be here cheering you on i owe
you so much for being an inspiration to
me and making me smile when i didn't
feel like i could anymore
stay safe and spoil those cats like they
deserve thank you
thank you wow thank you tyson
thank you i'm really really happy to see
you know
even now that i'm shadow band the people
who are usually here
are still always here
it's it's very nice to see that you guys
are always here
and always supporting me
even even though the viewership is like
50 or even more down
i i feel like um
[Music]
super chats are just as always
yeah so thank you for the insane support
like at least i don't have to
uh give up too much financially
uh during this shadow ban because like
i've seen like this video
i talked about it before about this no
no no no no no
i'm sorry my cat about this uh person
who got shadow band but
like their whole income comes from that
channel and they make like a
a big uh like living out of that channel
and them being shadow banned for a week
was like a big
financial struggle for them and they
lost a lot of income
and i was like hey at least like you
know
at least i'm not like that's not
happening to me at least so
thank you guys so much really
it's amazing like wow thank you
that's that's quite impressive so thank
you for all of the support i definitely
see that
yeah it sucks for them definitely but at
least their channel got
reinstated by now
meanwhile i'm still waiting i'm still
waiting um
thank you guys for the support thank you
for all the hides you're so sweet
parents gt thank you shouldn't type it
out when i read that
bye-bye dancing space potato thank you
patrick
doodler full thank you thank you for the
pinky
this is my first stream of yours and are
commenting
i'm interested several others i watch
still haven't been restored but you'll
get it i know jenna is your angel
or you've seen more than mine my channel
being shadow badge just like recently
it's funny though because like that
channel that i've been talking about
seems like
we got shadow banned maybe even on the
same day but i don't think it has
anything
or maybe it does because because like
it seems to be an issue of me changing
location but the shadow band happened
before i changed location so
i don't know it's so weird um apparently
youtube thought uh my channel was being
hijacked but the only one
only person logging in was me it's it's
just so random
yeah they went on the binge
i did that with more people than me yeah
apparently with that channel is also no
one else logged in
then them youtube was glitching that day
damn why does it why does it have to
glitch for me
have i not suffered enough by youtube
like deleting my channel completely i
mean
yes i guess i have not suffered enough
because i had a blast
uh during that date
[Laughter]
maybe they were like okay she she had
too much fun when we deleted her channel
now let's give her some real trouble
let's make her suffer for real
then anything no no that didn't do
anything because she didn't
log into my youtube account um when she
streamed on my channel it was just like
obs connected
uh yeah but it's not like she logged in
she tried logging into my youtube
account and it didn't happen right after
that it happened
a few streams later
so i don't think it's because of the
nano hijacking thing
no that one oh man that was that would
that would have sucked if it was
because of nanette
[Music]
hope that all my viewers will be back
when i when it when it gets fixed
ah what i was i wrote this in the
pre-check um
i would i wrote this in the pre-chat
today and
i'll decide tomorrow though
if by tomorrow when i wake up
and my
channel is not back to normal then
instead of taking friday off i will take
first day off and stream i think i was
planning
near for no wait was i planning
no i think i planned minecraft for
tomorrow
was it minecraft
wasn't minecraft
uh there was sunday okay okay and
i guess it was minecraft yeah okay and
so tomorrow when i wake up
and my channel is not back to normal yet
and i will move minecraft to friday and
then
take first day off because normally it
will be thursday minecraft
friday off and it would be done at the
same time by the way
then i would have first day off and
friday minecraft
okay sounds good i think yes
yeah ah yeah i will inform you guys on
twitter of course
of course of course yep
okay so uh doula full wrote in his pinky
this is my first dream of yours that
i've gotten to catch life thank you for
being you
we love you a lot here elsa i love that
you cuss it reminds me of my home and
makes me loved
cried during the last stream alongside
you
wait why did you cry wait because it was
so funny or ever
did what what what what thank you
doodlefool
if that was your first stream that you
were able to catch live i wouldn't if
you're catching this one live probably
not but thank you for the support thank
you
glad to have you around hopefully for
many many streams in the future too
oh interesting it reminds you of your
home though is everyone cussing in your
home
emmy ziggy
thank you for the pinky take a deep
breath teeth to a hot one yeah this was
i think when i was like uh
starting to panic because of all the pc
advice
thank you brian that's very sweet of you
yeah this is still a mario kart stream
yep yep thank you brian
gd danke thank you all so gg so sweet do
super chat reading some other time it's
stressing you out very much
some of you guys are just so sweet like
um
telling me to you know take a break and
and not stress out too much you guys are
so sweet i love people
you are all so sweet but [\h__\h] what your
name is brian but she's not talking to
you
i mean you can you might you can act
as if i'm talking to you if you wanna
try for that makes you happy
why not
donovan's thank you for pinky you're
stressed and i don't like it have some
money
daniels thank you that's very sweet but
i think thank you i mean it's not like
uh
money can i guess
indirectly money can relieve stress um
i like the directness of that super chat
thank you very much i appreciate it your
concern
and your kindness thank you your
generosity
thank you very much hello cat welcome to
the bed
hello baby
hello i'm back i'm back i'm back
oh yeah hardware unblocks that that's
the one i watched i know about that
that's the one that i've been uh
referencing too
free too i will snatch them no they're
from my cats
you do not just simply take away the
shoes that are for my cats
i will let them hunt you and destroy you
hi back you guys suck
stupid stupid
hope
don't worry it's just stuff and we got
you back everything will turn out okay
and even in the worst case it's not
really that bad thank you
donald early dancing
thank you for the virtual hug jackpot
thank you
thank you and
derek just do what you can do
if you feel like you need to just do a
super chat only stream later we're here
for you if you need it
thank you so sweet of you guys
thank you deal of 67. thank you i'm fine
now thankfully
that day was very stressful but i'm fine
now thank you
it's it's always reassuring to see
everyone's
kind-hearted comments thank you thank
you
abstract beard thank you
we love you that's all i want to say we
love you kihara it will be okay we love
the stream and we love you take care of
yourself
wait could it be that
what so what i got from this message is
maybe i could be wrong but do you maybe
love me is
is that what you're trying to say typhon
i could be wrong but i think that's what
it is
thank you love you too
we'll always be here we'll always be
here when you are not super busy
and stressed until take care of yourself
first and good luck with everything safe
travels thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you i
appreciate that
thank you very much thankfully the
travel was safe everything was good
why black wolf thank you pinkerton
please don't apologize canada everyone
has stressful times just do what you
need to
one step at a time have a safe trip and
don't force yourself to stream for us
take care of yourself first thank you oh
rower for side accounts uh hatching
congratulations
oh you're no
thank you
cat hair everywhere oh my god
oh my god
and night 360
and that's it for the mario kart zip
chats that's
it and now we have the members only
streams and sliver.ios
members only super chats and sliver.i
are super cats
mixed together and
let me see if i got it from now
number one
don't know why the members only found
this though
imagine it don't know where it is
so we're reading uh this one and members
only
again
sometimes my kitty cat brain goes a bit
haywire i had a bad day at work so your
exposing actually cheered me up even if
it was embarrassing
wait what did i do if there's anything i
can do to make it up to you let me know
also you're a big dog
wow big dork you're a big dork
no what did i what did i do
ah ah because you wrote a love
challenger
i remember
you also all remember that's funny
step by kitten then continues to write
also just for the record uh
love and heart are totally the same in
the felling language
you really should be more sensitive to
cat cultural customs tangiel
what will your fluff balls think
well yeah i mean everything sounds
similar in the filling language it's all
just meow meow meow meow
what set by a kitten we're speaking
english here okay so get used to it
adjust yourself
just kidding it's okay thank you for the
membership welcome
thanks for the pinky too thank you thank
you jeff i kitten
dean love 67 thank you shane also for
the pinky so many pinkies
and sapphire kitten is clearly lying
danger everyone knows that the philly
language does not have a word for love
it does have 81 words for feed me
however
[Laughter]
he might be right
but sapphire kitten follows up with
don't listen to him he doesn't know the
first thing about love
but he's dealing 67. trust me tensile i
majored in feeling literature also it's
only about 80 words for feed me
hey but i think he knows some things
about love he's called dean of 67.
i think the one thing that he knows
something about must be love
so i i believe you
saying that there's only 80 words and
not 81 words
that's very specific for um
feed me but
haven't you you two gonna sort that out
yourselves
there's not much i can do it's true what
can i say
well is the fire kitten here to
defend themselves
this one only d stands for dinner did it
i know exactly what d stands for and i'm
proud of myself for guessing it
absolute genius big brain boob
[Music]
tantra since you talked about community
i want you to i want to recommend some
single camera comedy have you watched
malcolm in the middle yes brooklyn
nine-nine no silicon valley no an
american housewife no
surprisingly there's a lot of ones that
i've didn't watch
hmm i started i started re-watching
parks and rec yesterday unfortunately
it's not anywhere anymore not even on
amazon
i mean amazon prime so i had to buy
the digital version up there's like
mostly only dvts but there's a digital
version
but
the thing is on my amazon
the only digital version of parks and
rec that i can buy
is german and i don't want to watch it
in german but i
what choice do i have so i have because
it's nowhere else to get
so i had to it's on canadian netflix it
it would be on peacock yeah i read that
but like how the [\h__\h] would i get
peacock
[Music]
so yeah for now i'm watching it in
germans kind of lame i don't want to
watch it in german
you i used to watch it in english now i
have to watch it in german
is it really on it's on american netflix
eh
when i googled it said uh parks and rec
has disappeared from
every streaming um provider thingy
and is now on peacock
i'll check it america and canada korean
zones
for realtors
it's right it's lightest um i'm in pain
that was a nice crap thanks dude thanks
i'm proud of my cracks
that was a good one
and pain
uh just check we have in canada
oh canada oh canada
best country in the world
never been there but damn canada sounds
nice
canada sounds hella nice
baby's fighting oh baby
yes go baby go no oh
my yes kick her kicker
baby two is attacking baby one who is
just lying on
on the ground but baby two is very
chunky so she can wrestle her to death i
think oh my god oh no they still have
both they're like wrestling while
standing up
oh now they're just looking at each
other oh that they go for it again oh my
god
oh i love it so cute
now they're just lying down together and
like
just thinking about what's the next oh
next action to take baby one
stood up and it's probably giving up
oh
yeah it's over that was a short fight
seems to have one
yeah okay and they just they're just
taking some
distance now are you guys okay
you love each other don't you you're
sisters yeah right
maybe make me so cute
damn it five bucks down the train
i support baby two because they are
chunky every kind of you
very kind her chunkiness is the charm
another win for maybe two but the
interesting thing is like in other
situations it seems like
baby one is the one the
alpha alpha alpha tia
wait how do you say that in english
the one who seems to dominate the room
like when i play when i try to play with
them
like for example if baby two first uh
like
attacks the the thing that i i'm playing
with them
the alpha cat ah
alpha predator yeah yeah so
and then when uh when baby one jumps in
though
baby two is like oh okay she's like
you you you take it i i'm fine i'm fine
like she always stops playing
thank you for the membership she only
stops playing
as soon as baby one jumps in
she's like she feels like probably that
i don't know it was interesting
it's kind of sad because i want baby one
baby two to move more because she's so
chunky but
baby one loves to play so whenever
something's moving baby one would jump
in and play together
and then baby two would stop moving and
baby two is just too chunky she needs to
move
but when it comes to wrestling then baby
two is the strong one
i i think she feels inferior maybe
when it comes to playing
interesting observations
yeah chunky chunky baby
tucker and muy
lost the bet here payment wait what
is that a sub account oh you're paying
with a membership because the super
chats are turned off
got anything planned for a six-month
anniversary coming up me
personally for me alone actually
no i it's coming up so soon right
isn't it like next week or so
actually i didn't yeah
yeah maybe i'll do uh is it next week
i think it's in 10 days
yeah it might be at the end of next week
um
maybe i'll do just like uh because i'm
doing karaoke this week so i don't want
to do it again next week
um maybe i'll do a
q a i don't know
me personally i didn't really have
the time to plan anything special
[Music]
next we'll talk man oh next week i
suppose
gotta talk with the guest about it
though
german read w i guess i could maybe do
that
um or we could do some
we could do some kind of contest maybe
like
uh make like a like
like some kind of healthier
something fan content like for example
clippers could do a half year
compilation
or artists could do just a general
like celebration fan art and
people who are neither of that could do
i don't know a letter or poem yeah maybe
a half year poem or something like that
any kind of fan content contest i guess
i could do something like that yeah
maybe yeah
and then review it have the deadline
before the streams died and i review it
on stream
oh i'll see ya that might work
you
okay let's do it let's do it
let's do it yeah eat
cat's design conscious no no no no no
cats showing contest with a cat reveal
as a grand finale
and i can't show my cats and i don't
think everyone has cats unfortunately i
wish everyone have cats
motion dankeshin looking for the top
down
account names depth collector dan
kitchen p1234a
and p1234 m thank you
[Music]
no matter where you are you'll belong
with us no matter the time that passes
you'll belong with us
no matter the things that this new
chapter has in store you'll be along
with us no matter what
you're loved and you belong what
jonathan what's going on
here's being so so dramatic and poetic
what's happening thank you that's so
sweet
that's so romantic
nice to have a little romance in my life
[Laughter]
the the only romance i'm getting is
these super chats
ah thank you thank
philosopher
i don't want anything but my cats
let me drink my dr pepper
wow that that air exploded in my fist
dr pepe
that's so good
um actually yeah kelly i haven't
haven't actually spoken with
or two cali ever since i
arrived back home
i think she's busy probably
rule number four read it
i just magic dancing chris dubs
thank you for the red super chat i
suppose it's a red one
is that is that actually two
i have been in the past i've been in the
past six years with no goals and no
dreams because my mother is in very poor
health
she has a very serious cancer there is
no possibility of
cure oh my god the doctor said this is a
rare case
for the past six years it's been like
that
finally my mother received hospice care
in the hospital at that time i can only
wait for my mother
to pass away and i can't change anything
but my boyfriend let me know how alive
and i know potential you cheered me up
again i will learn to drive and find a
job again
live earnestly and actively oh
applause good job
wow i'm proud of you i'm happy
that that happened i mean that i could
help like that
good job wow wow wow
yes you know you're gonna you gotta get
back on track gotta get
back up on your feet again and you know
live life and enjoy life
yeah good job so proud of you
all the respect for me and my chat
you're amazing
thank you thank you keep on continuing
what you're doing now you're on the
right path um really sorry about your
mother but
i think she's she would be i don't know
if she's still alive or not but i guess
she still is
says she's in hospital so i think she's
also very very proud of you for doing
that and taking that step
nice nice
keep doing what you're doing
[Music]
thanks for asking i'm good how are you
thank you i am very good thank you very
much
you know um
[Music]
you you you're cute
you are cute thank you soon
a coffee is not members no it's okay
[Laughter]
thank you i meant to kill yourself for
the red super chat
i'm fine and i hope you're fine too how
are you
how are you thank you
are you here even you're here
ah i love how people are actually here
for the super chat readings like live
and actually are able to
you know have a conversation with me it
makes me happy
i go man your story in the supermarket
i kind of picked it up while i was
reading the chat nice one
thank you for the membership welcome i'm
fine
you should be more than fine you should
be good
why are you not why are you not
perfectly fine
oh my god my cat looks so cute can i
just
can i just give her a hug please
i have a problem she always looks cute
so
can i can i
do it okay
next
[Music]
hello
no
and back
[Music]
never ending cat break
baby you're so cute you're so cute
oh enough another sub account thank you
for the membership
[Music]
mode
baby
cute okay
back on track
i love my cat so much i love my cat so
much i love them
i love them i love them so much
no i love my cats
i love them
here is your money tree
well since i couldn't simp uh for you
and my wallet is getting kind of heavy
here's 50 and more till you return don't
stress the uploads and just focus on
getting yourself back home safe back
home thank you
soon i appreciate it thank you
uh very kind of you very generous thank
you for the support
thank you dominic thank you
is a new experience i'm glad to watch
that
i'll have a right
thank you for the pinky hi kara thank
you for all your hard work and i hope
you're doing good today you give me
smiles every day and when i'm sad you
make me feel better quite often
i'm so happy to be here and i wouldn't
trade it for anything i love you
i love you too so happy to hear that
thank you
thank you very much that's that's very
sweet
i'm glad to be able to have that kind of
power to make someone happy
thank you very wholesome very wholesome
indeed
thank you hope you stay happy
[Music]
it says uh he doesn't only thank me for
my streams but also you guys for being
so
so open and welcoming to you know
um japanese viewers and me streaming at
the japanese
uh times yeah yeah
very wholesome isn't it nice to see
everyone so sweet to each other
everyone's so caring
[Music]
though i'm shadow banded even though
it's pretty late in japan
[Music]
japanese viewers so sorry that i'm not
really
you know doing much a japanese content
or japanese talking
this um super chatter is having an eye
surgery today so
wish him luck coming good luck good luck
what about us see
i like how you're picking up on the way
i say
s-e-a it's um
thank you
[Music]
but yeah um it's it's very difficult
it's impossible to
stream at good times for everyone
but i've realized that being in
europe it's it is it is not impossible
to stream for every other content
in a good time it is definitely easier
than
in japan and so
even though i will maintain
uh a mainstreaming time of european
prime
time uh i think every now and then i'll
do some
streams that are good for uh you know
japan
and australia and so on as well i will
do that but please do not expect me and
please
please don't cry and whine when you see
a schedule
that is not cut out for you because
there's nothing it's never gonna be
perfect for everyone
and i'm sorry and i wish it could be i'm
sorry
but it's just not always gonna be
perfect for everyone and you're gonna
consider the fact that i live in europe
now
and i will mix it up every now and then
but stop stop crying about when
a schedule is not very good for you
please it makes me feel stressed out
like i want to make everyone happy but
then there's these people that are like
oh i can't watch any streams this week
oh this sucks
what am i supposed to do whatever i try
i try i really try
try to make all of you happy because i
don't want you guys to miss out on me
and i want you guys to be here i love
you guys every one of you
every single one of you is my my my
viewers from
the the west side of the globe
my viewers from the east side of the
globe everywhere
i love them
i know
[Music]
um
m
thank you guys thank you and it's really
not
i i personally think it's not a big deal
to just watch
the archive if you can't if you can't
watch something live i know
it's not as good as watching it and not
live
eh as wasted in life i know watching it
live is always more exciting but
i mean i personally like watching
archives because
then i at least can decide when to stop
and when to start
yo archive gang whoever is watching this
in the archive you
which reminds me of something uh it's
totally random but if you guys see
that after my stream is uh uploaded
on youtube uh recently what youtube has
been doing
for some reason is every time pretty
much every time recently
they turn off the comments like not
exactly they
you can comment but it always reserves
them for checking
and i always have to manually turn them
back on
it's so weird but sometimes i forget
about it that that happens and i don't
realize it because i don't check up on
my
already over already ended streams if
that happens you guys are welcome to
spam me on twitter and tell me that
uh i should turn back on the comments so
we can do it quicker
yeah it's kind of weird youtube is so
buggy
so buggy
it happened so often recently so
annoying
he would remind
so annoying
anyway
santa thank you
gd thank you for the pinky
congratulations 500k views on heart
challenger viva lakia and shout out to
the pro gang thank you
heart challenger currently doesn't show
up when you look for it
and so it kind of sucks
um card challenger
when when will will hard challenger ever
get to
um a million views i will i will wait
for that day
patiently you mean love challenger
no i mean hi challenger uh maybe i've
been just looking for the wrong title
maybe i should have looked up
love challenger no i think it's height
challenge i'm pretty sure it's hard
challenger
gonna loop it all day thank you
people really been missing on my own
honestly mamaloni artwork for that music
video
i want more people to watch the music
video just because the music video is so
great the combination of navidu
and mamaloni my mama only drew so much
art
for it so much in such a short time too
and it's just so perfect she drew so
much art for it she's like
a pure angel and a nebula with does the
3d stuff
he did a great job the music video is so
good i love it so much
mv doko you serious now if you go to my
channel page it's
there playing automatically i think if
you are
subscribed and that's what plays and if
you're not subscribed and i think it
plays
no wait i think it also plays hard
challenger right now
possibly well yeah just check my channel
for god's sake
also there's the hack playlist watch the
hack playlist i i shared it before
ring-a-ding-ding monochromic uh
thank you
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
and has been a viewer since a long time
and he recently got a new job and he
told us before that he got like
bullied at his previous job so that's
why he didn't want to go back working
and he quit his job because of that and
he was like a neat for a long time
because of that
according to his super chat but he
finally got a job again and he's like
he was like um worried about getting
bullied there again
i was apparently really bad before
so i tried to give him some advice like
uh
like i mean i i totally believe that
he was bullied before like that's i
don't wanna i don't wanna say that
that's not happening but in his new
workplace
like maybe this maybe this will um
help anyone else what i'm gonna say now
uh but i had like a similar thing like
when i started working somewhere
i was really worried about what people
would think about me and i would think
like that these people are like
only nice to me in front of me and
behind my back when i'm not on the shift
or whatever when i'm not at work
that they probably like talk bad about
me or make fun about me
and in some way i still think that that
might be might have been the case
but but you
in many cases when people think they're
disliked by the people around them it's
in many cases not true it's just like
you you're not
having any confidence in yourself puts
this little bug inside your brain and
makes you think that everyone hates you
often that's just in most cases that's
not the case in most cases people
really don't mind you
but you make yourself believe
that everyone around you hates you
so gotta gotta think about that
do you actually have any proof that they
don't like you or is it all just inside
your head
hmm difficult difficult
yeah but i'm not saying that that what
tyso has experiences in his head but for
for the future now that he got a new
workplace and
whenever he thinks like they dislike him
maybe maybe that's
if you don't have any actual proof of it
yet
maybe that's just maybe that in that
case is actually
really just you having no no confidence
and
thinking they just like you but they
might actually like you hmm
you can always find a new job i mean
generally i guess so
but i think at the moment it's
everywhere hard to get a new job
so being like ah if they bully you at
that job just get a new job that's
i think not that easy right now and
especially in japan
like where i'm from it's different where
i live it's different but in japan it's
like
if you quit your job too early
then it's gonna look really really
really bad in your
um thingy
in your work history thing um that's
i've heard that that's quite a problem
in japan that's why many people
stay at their job even though they are
not
feeling happy there for whatever reason
um
and and about like
that's not about like one year is not
enough two years is not enough three
users
if you quit like it seems like if you
quit at after three years that's still
not enough
it seems that already is
too short for japanese standards
that still makes them feel like oh this
this person doesn't stay in a job for a
very long time so let's not hire that
person
it's very interesting because like where
i'm from it feels like this like
job hopping or like um at least
i guess it depends on the industry but
job hopping like maybe once per year
isn't that big of a deal and it's kind
of like hey at least this person is like
gathering experience in a lot of
different places
that's how we see it i suppose
at least in the in the industry where i
worked in
so
[Music]
different cultures loyalty thing yeah
yeah
yeah that's sad
i never i never stayed at a job more
than
two years i think ah not maybe four
years i guess the longest was
three years which wasn't really
i didn't really have any choice for that
one though
i had to stay for years i think that's
the longest i
ever had one specific job
so yeah
you could not take
will you stay in her live in the next
five years i wish i could stay forever
let's see how it goes
black friction
will add
[Music]
thank you um i'll play around with the
bitrate if i need to thank you
baby dominic
and downstairs see thank you for the
pinky thank you
i wish safe travels tangent please be
safe we love you p.s transporting
chicken to the never has not been easy
the locals make it a bit difficult
hashtag busy gang
oh we got a we got another employee
never kfb
employee here uh
please uh consult that with someone else
i'm i'm not in charge
please consult that with the never um
with the head of the never branch
thank you thank you good luck with that
unknown thank you for the first ever
super chat thank you
pudding thank you soon kfb
[Music]
hope this is enough for you to get
something nice to eat at home that
you've been missing
joel oh it definitely is thank you
be sure to let yourself have a decent
break after returning home again miss
you already
actually yeah i didn't i didn't really
take a break because
i felt like i already had like too many
days where i didn't stream like while i
was
still still in japan and preparing to
move so
i wanted to get back to usual i
asap but it's okay i don't feel like
exhausted or anything anymore
i'm really well rested and happy
yeah it's all good but one thing that
i've been um slacking
uh unknown was a red subject oh i think
i actually reacted to it
uh during the stream but okay uh i'll
give him another
kiss in a moment um what was i saying
one thing that i've been slacking is
that um
you know unpacking all those boxes that
i sent myself
from japan yeah it's a lot
it's a lot but if i take the day off
tomorrow then i'll
i'll get to it tomorrow i promise yes
yes yes yes
so much like um i unpacked a lot of
boxes that were
in the in the cellar already from when i
left
australia so mother what tonight
so i i had a lot of boxes here already
previously
from before and my suitcases which were
huge so i already did all of that i
already did a lot but
yeah yesterday i got like seven boxes
that i have to
uh yeah put away everywhere take your
time gentle thank you
that's i don't want to take too much
time though because i don't want to
bother my roommate with having too many
boxes
in the in the hallway i i
i don't wanna you know i don't wanna
annoy her
you can stream unboxing nah
nah i don't i think again it's gonna be
too distracting
are you and i'm gonna play chess today
no we're playing super bunny man
we thought a lot about actually i
thought a lot about what to play
because i kind of wanted to play a game
that i don't have to stream on my
channel
only on her channel because still shadow
band and i got to the conclusion
we could play super bunny man because i
never played that it's kind of funny
it's kind of funny no chats yes yes
i saw the thumbnail eh did she did she
already
did you make did you use it did she
already make the streaming reservation
oh yeah then you should have known
ah yeah it's there it's up oh she used
my thumbnail i made it
i made uh the fondant because uh i
didn't i
i didn't want to put too much trouble on
her
there it is yeah it's there
hey hey hey hey it's up yeah
we're gonna be bunnies and bunny
i should put it up for 30 minutes ago
[Music]
yay
actually dad that um sorry why did you
wake up
baby actually that that those bunny
uh hats remind me i used to have like a
really cute phone case
and that looked like that like it it
gave my phone
really cute bunny ears and it was really
cute
noticeable that i made the thumbnail
i wanted to use there was this uh like
me and ahmed don't get much fan arts
together like ame and kiara is not a
really otp pairing for some reason
so we don't get much uh fan art but
there was this one fan art that
um
someone made of us i think just
yesterday or so with us
in uh like
how do you say
what the [\h__\h]
my one of my babies oh my gosh gave me a
heart attack
she just fell i don't know out of my
closet i think i'm not sure what
happened
uh yeah the prisoner yeah the prisoner
um i'm a tory fanart
and from
ellie made this really uh adorable
prisoner i wanted to use that one but it
didn't really fit the
theme of the stream but i don't need
i do have a a need for more
more amitovi fan art i need more
someone fix anyone fix this lack of
amazon yes
very often and there is often fan arts
of the trio
of uh uh
and sometimes there is even gura and
cali because i guess people like that
small and big uh sorry
small and big combination
but there's like besides
these are interestingly like besides me
and kelly
people don't combine me much with anyone
else
even though i would say i'm pretty much
i'm on pretty good terms and
i'm pretty good uh harmony
with other girls when i collab with them
i thought that
uh amatoni and and and
uh wait what's
what's my thing with summit wait what
what was my thing with summit oh my god
hello
amitori and summit tony
i think are pretty good combinations and
also takotori
hello baby hello baby
you know i think they're pretty good
combinations
but there's like people think if they
want to draw
like a like a fan art of more than one
person
that includes me then they always draw
takamuri
hello baby
[Music]
remember
so overwhelming yeah i guess so need
more tacoma islam's desk
but there's already so much takamuri
i didn't you know yeah that's also
something that just doesn't exist
it seems takamoni supremacy
yeah i get it i get it but i want to see
more combinations
why did i read those oh yeah i read
those okay so anyway unknown
unknown thank you for the red super chat
once again wow
i think i reacted to it before uh when
you actually sent it during the stream
thank you one more time thank you so
much for the red super chat
thank you thank you for the support i
appreciate it
sorry fun question thai fan thank you
for red super chat
mwah last super chat read motivated me
to move beyond
a mindless drone and obtain the ability
to fly oh yeah
typhoon kfb legal eagle now oh baby baby
two is attacking baby one
baby one is making weird point oh baby
slapped baby one in
in the face and now she jumped off the
bat and and
disappeared and baby one is just like
what the [\h__\h] just happened
everyone's like what what was that why
did you attack me
why won't you attack me anyway back on
topic
typhon gave me legal eagle i like i like
the upgrade
even though the drone thingy
wasn't what i thought it was supposed to
mean
at all but now you made yourself into a
flying object
i love it
legally oh alright that's still like
you're still included on the legal stuff
somehow
uh i figure i've done a good enough job
to earn a promotion now hopefully this
new title has your blessing boss yes it
does
good luck on a trip home give those cats
some love for us oh believe me i'm doing
more than
giving them some love but that sounds
weird
[Music]
big red super chat five five fifty
thousand
uh japanese thank you thank you guys
for
[Music]
okay
for all
[Music]
super chats are done chet is dead
on my stream no it's moving
activity jack everyone are you awake are
you here
everyone say hello
[Music]
hello hello hello hello hello i'm
actually like really surprised that
there's so many people
here right now
for super chat reading even though i'm
shadow band thank you guys
hello hello hello hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello everyone
say hello to my cats in cat language now
just say meow
everyone say meow maybe they'll hear you
meow meow everyone say meow you gotta
say not only hello to me but also to my
cats okay that's just that's just
matters that's just having good manners
meow
i think yeah i think baby two hurts you
she looked up from cleaning herself she
was like
and then she was like oh
and now she's back to cleaning
meow and baby one is just you know
meditating she's just meditating thank
you
actually uh someone wear a woof woof in
the chat which is
german dog noise i'm actually pretty
good at um
making dark noises but it's pretty loud
so i don't want to do it right now
but there might be an m dog in the
future
i have i have quite the uh
confidence in my dog
first
[Music]
impersonation
cannot speak english isn't both the same
in english yeah but it's written
differently it's w-u-f-f
impersonation okay thank you
do it no i don't wanna impression ah
impression i don't wanna
i wanna struggle with my cats
they're just chilling now
savoring through michael tyson's
what could that be it's cut off there
but i suppose it's his ass right
it's probably his ass
and the name is too long so it cuts off
but i think i know what it says
zero
[Music]
have you had a chance to listen to the
full kfb album yet do you mean the one
with
uh um like all the chickens saluting
in the picture yes i've heard it i
wanted to make sure kfc members heard it
but especially
of course i heard i heard it the first
time you tweeted it
and it represents the love and pride we
have for you plus it would mean the
world to me if you played
oh you want me to play it oh if you if i
have the permission wait um
how do i find it again um
what's your twitter account miracle too
oh yeah
all right
oh there it is
ah but wait um i haven't i have these uh
audio problems right now i'm not sure
if it will play it probably not
on it
yeah no it doesn't
like i can't hear it right now i got
some audio issues but if i
download it
[Music]
one second
okay uh this might be loud
let me put it in here this should work
uh close your
ears for a second that'd be loud three
two one
i don't hear it but i don't hear it but
hey
you guys hear it
[Music]
salute
i don't hear it but i'm imagining it i
heard it before but i don't hear it
right now i got some audio problems here
for everyone who wants the youtube link
thank you guys for the memberships thank
you
youtube link is here
it's really well done i remember it
being really well
done yeah it's the kfb album
orchestral version yeah pretty cool
[Music]
i like it i mean i don't i don't hear it
right now but i like it
it's awesome right it's pretty damn good
[Music]
um damn i wish i heard it right now
um
[Music]
oh my chat is like acting really weird
so ok
[Music]
ok
it's beautiful
[Music]
imagine me just sitting in the room
shouting
viva yaquiana
hello and my cats are just chilling on
my bed next to me looking
so unimpressed like
difficult audience different difficult
crowd
anyway there we go i think the anthem is
over now
whoa beautiful thank you for creating
that
i might if i figure out my audio [\h__\h]
here again that i might
uh play it on stream more often if you
allow me
thank you thank you
i like it when people make like tracks
like these because then i
have something to use for a change
something different
and it's not always the same
[Music]
let's oh yeah continue
thank you for the ram super chat too
once again thank you wow
free account name donkey shane
what
oh we have a confession or something
dear purple snake
near bj rank all my life my only dream
was to feed my flesh to kiara yet 6 000
points later
you took my dream and dashed it against
the rocks
no that's today you made a very petty
enemy what
ah a couple name was like wanted to feed
himself to me but
he got like killed by a purple snake
oh no you made a very very strong enemy
purple snake whoever you are be aware
next time we play sliver.io account name
might be after you
dark rose donkey kamiyah
this time you can do it yourself if you
try you don't need to be carried i mean
i was carried
um i guess in those runs yeah there were
some runs where i wasn't really cared
but i think if it wasn't for
you know having all these kfp snacks in
there
if it was only me and only randos
then yeah we might have not it might
have not gone that well
yeah but yeah
there were some times where i was on the
leaderboard and it wasn't even because i
was protected it was because of
me being strong
mister otter danke thank you for the
pink for the red super chat i think
mwah hi ken i'm very new to the
beautiful thing but
your love with cali moved me and now i
ship takamori like it's my full-time job
i really love your passion and kindness
and everything so here's my first ever
super chat i wish this little dollar
dollar can help you improve your
internet a bit in
australia thank you dan you
yes uh their into that situation is
gonna be
quite expensive because if i can if i'm
gonna get that extra provider
the one that i currently have is already
freaking expensive
and i can't get out of it but having two
is fine
it's probably the best way to go anyway
but both of them are gonna be expensive
and still shitty internet this doesn't
make sense to me
oh my god how come we have such shitty
internet here
i don't get it but thank you i will do
my best to
yeah make the best out of it that i can
with my with the with the opportunities
that are being given to me
thank you for the support it's an island
kia the internet is hard
[Music]
yeah makes sense
yeah i think you're talking about the
wrong australia
arigato
actually your internet is pretty good
today there's basically no stream
latency yeah but i'm lagging the whole
time am i not
um
[Music]
let's see how it works with the i hope
that i hope the collab will be fun
thank you for the pinky thank you
it's manageable not too laggy
low frame rate yeah oh well
i hope the collab will be fine but you
gotta test it out you know
thank you for the pinky strawberry with
no text to it so anyway thank you for
the support thank you soon
listen every now and then
you may not see this until after your
home but i hope you have a safe and
uneventful trip i hope your cats don't
take too long to warm up to you again oh
yeah
they didn't thankfully was very happy
about that
you can start streaming once you're good
and settled and stay calm and farewell
for now thank you very much yagadu
although yagadu you and me we're having
some
issues right now but
you think thank you i suppose
thank you
no i appreciate it thank you for your
kindness thank you soon
they know who your mom is i'm so glad i
do they really seem to
have recognized me again quite fast
don't throw your children into the ocean
what do you mean what are you talking
about
wait what what what what what reference
what is that referencing to what did i
say
oh because of goura well shut up
she is a freaking shark
oh my god you make me so crazy that i
have to take my medicine yaga
she can't swim of course she can she has
to
survive this is what i learned today
sharks
um can only survive in the water like
not only by being in the water like
other fishes
sharks have to move forward in the water
so that the water is constantly going
through their body
otherwise like they can't just be still
in one spot
so in order for gouda to survive she has
to be constantly moving in the water
forward so yeah
she has to do it i have to throw her
into the
into the ocean is for her own sake so
that she doesn't die here's a shark fact
she has to move in the water
she needs floaties yeah whatever she can
use those floaties that's okay
could i name some up lunch is not a
discussion that you
and you and me are gonna have this is no
no discussion
shut up shut up shut up she's my child
okay you know nothing about my child you
have
no say in this you are not her father
are you callius so shut up
[Music]
i got to watch a couple minutes of the
stream and what i saw was a snippet of
you finally getting a taste of how
painful it is when we tried to find you
in the game
yeah it wasn't that easy to find my mama
um
yeah it was hard
best of luck with the move bus we
definitely want to turn your japanese
branch into a club while you're out of
town
absolutely not those uh those security
cameras are just decorative right asking
for a friend
you are not going
to turn the thing that i worked on so
hard
into a club no scout chicken lives no
matter how much money you give me i
cannot accept that
[Music]
i hope you were just joking
thank you for the support
thank you thank you a viewer from
english speaking viewer from japan i
hope you can still
watch my streams every once in a while
please thank you
thank you would make me very happy
[Music]
and yeah security cameras are actually
working so
[Music]
motion thank you
is
this this is not dice right it's this
right this logoria
did i finally say it ryan this logaria
danke shin is that correct i wonder
thank you for the pinky no excuses live
to the cat rigs when
they would actually i don't want to
break the fourth wall but
um
that's it would have to it would have to
be able to
actually um react to a cat's face
uh but i've seen like there's like
instagram filters and stuff that
actually work on pets
yeah so i guess it's not
what was that noise eh what noise
i don't know what you're talking about
yeah anyway yeah there's uh filters like
that so maybe
maybe maybe it's possible
eh chicken noise
what happened that was a chicken yeah
that was a scary noise
what did you hear
weird noise earlier and maybe it was my
chair when i
uh scooched over to my cat
sounded really weird yeah weird noise
wait in one way
sounds like an uttara matoon on the otto
matone
robotic voice it probably was my chair
sounded like a speech oh that's
mysterious
anyway it's crown thank you and
starbucks thank you so much thank you
for the
red super chat good luck with the move
tango wish you the best and all of cafe
will be waiting for you patiently to
return thank you stevens
are you here now are you here are you
here waiting for me
thank you thank you for the support
thank you for the good luck
thanks to the good luck that you wished
me it went well
mary pippin sang i won't be able to
catch your european
prime time stream sadly but i'll watch
shark ups and catch everything else
thank you
thanks for always being so fun have a
safe trip also
cali is a treasure i'm glad that you are
making an effort to watch them all thank
you that means a lot to me
ace crown danke shin pudding pudding
that's not a red super chat
that's a as betrayal
putting sending a two dollar super chat
and writing in there that it's a red
super chat
lies you can't fool me
gask thank you sebastian thank you and
spawn flyer thank you
since this is not going to be read soon
hope the flight on pickup wasn't too bad
and that you're safe and sound in
australia
it was worth the wait for the stream
just to see you thank you
very much
oh sebastian wrote the letter
i want i don't think it arrived yet but
i hope i'll
i hope i'll get it sometime soon
[Music]
88 kelly what are you saying i don't
understand
hey hey calorie
what do you understand the
how will that get you now actually um so
basically
i have the choice of either um asking
them to send them to me
from japan or pick them up eventually
when i come to japan
oh yeah i don't know how often they're
gonna
send them to me though
i trying to make you say i hate kelly
i ah could be
it's written a i g h e
space e-i-g-h-t
space k-e-l-l-y
i-a yeah
seems like they wanted you said it no i
didn't really say it that way i said
more like a8
yeah a i said a not i
anyway that's ridiculous no one would
ever believe that anyway
thank you for the pink subject though kb
channel thank you for the rest of the
chat
thank you joint got close lagged and
died to mama
still i had fun thank you for uh the
streams today tendrill try to catch the
live streams on the new stream times
because cats and of course you
have a safe trip and i'll be waiting for
your return thank you very much i think
for
american viewers my my new time
times are not bad at all so
i mean some might be a little bit early
in the morning but mostly they should be
actually always fine for um
n a viewers um so hoping to have a lot
of you always around thank you guys
yeah thank you shadow looking forward to
having you
in my streams forever and ever and ever
and ever and ever and ever and ever
and ever and ever
fodr also with a red super chat wow
thank you
thanks for the streams that you have
saved your thank you apple for hanging
out even though there were some scuff
streams
you're always here thank you
i'm so grateful thank you
so grateful
thank you soon
stream time should be better for you too
i hope
i think sliver was the last stream right
before
i i moved and ah no waiting room super
test okay
i think we're almost done with the
sliver super chats
snow crab thank you ellis thank you for
the pinkies
i wish you're safe and good flight
attention finally you're coming to the
eu branch kf yay we waited for this time
oh yeah
you're from hungary aren't you thank you
hello hello hello thank you very much
for welcoming me back to europe no okay
europe is really europe doesn't need the
wink but australia
thank you oh yeah a few ones i guess
um
[Music]
thank you strong sad donkey shin raven
home thank you
thank you next
time thank you for the pinky
might be one of the last times i'll see
you live i have watched you since your
debut and have seen you grow so much as
a streamer
as well as entertain and help so many
people so remember remember that no
matter what i think i've read this one
before
it's been fun and good luck yeah you're
still staying close
oh alberto showing his soft side here
thank you thank you
i hope you can come more often though
yeah i read that live didn't i
gd thank you for the red super chat
hi kiana safe travels to you thanks for
the streams really appreciate her your
hard work and striving
to give out fun and amazing content
again and again tangents roll
i'll try to see your stream as much as i
can oh yeah australian buddy judy you're
here right now
anyway godspeed viva like yeah glory to
kfp what time is it in
australia right now isn't it like in the
middle of the night
it's like isn't it like 5 a.m or
something
how fast 5 am
gd you mean baby 2. ah jd is here
isn't it like half past 5 a.m oh my god
six out wait did you did my australian
viewers
pull an all-nighter for me guys i'm so
sorry don't you guys have to go to work
or something i'm so sorry
oh man i don't want to lose my
australian viewers
i don't want to lose them
hmm yes no
i don't have jobs i think they do
[Music]
i love my australian viewers
if you guys can't come
to watch me and then
just come to the archive i'm always
there
oh i will not disappear
if you can't come live just just watch
my archive
okay don't force yourself to watch my
stream and
wait weird times
although i'm always happy to have you
guys starts at 9am
oh my god it didn't sleep
oh my god
okay final
real real fight the power you know
i hope it won't be too rough thank you
for the red super chat
damn so does that mean you cannot watch
the amelia collab
read the real question is does that mean
you cannot watch the collab
misfits thank you venison
one
yep unfortunately oh man
yeah i think for pst i had quite decent
times before i left
in japan
i forgot i super chatted well there you
go
see love67 thank you shin covers
nighttime cameras night
red super shot with no text in it oh man
thank you very much next time write
something meaningful please
thank you thank you thank you very much
for the support canvas nine thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you have a good and uneventful
flight i hope you get
a calm seat neighbors oh actually i had
no neighbors they were
as i told you guys they were um ah
actually the flight from germany to
germany to australia was
quite packed but the other one the
longer one wasn't packed at all
um
no no there's a city in germany that's
called hamburg and
uh this person superchatted from hamburg
that's
i wasn't talking about hamburgers no no
and that you stay calm we will wait
patiently
for you also don't worry about us we big
birds can take care
of ourselves you should arrive and
settle back in before doing anything
else
thank you thank you and thank you for
the support cyrux thank you
everything was all right the flight was
uh quite
i was really glad and relieved that i
was able to
like sleep properly in the flight
because normally i always had issues but
that was because probably mostly because
i always fly with
economy but this time i fly with premium
economy so it wasn't that uncomfortable
it was quite comfortable actually oh
thank you thank you i'm both happy and
sad that i can't super chat happy for
wallet set for new super chat
please don't worry about it it's really
not necessary i'm so sorry then i made
you feel that way
please don't feel like it's like
anything you need to do
i just want to properly thank everyone
who did uh send super chats but it's
really not necessary
thank you sarik thank you
hoping that now that we seem to be in
the same time zone
then you're gonna watch my streams
ah i think i read that one before
thank you for the red super chat
broke say something heartfelt about safe
travels woke
more bizarre recoil chiada content
i don't remember what happened there i
remember there was something with
rickroll going on but i don't remember
what exactly was going on
still streaming yes always streaming
swan flyer thank you er one one
affordable
thank you for the red super chat gosh
when are these
sliver super chat's done
almost almost almost done
mama
hope you have had a comfortable flight
back home thanks for all the fun streams
and good times might be a little bit
harder to catch your life when you get
back to
australia or another or australian rio
no
but even if i have to join the archive
gang i will be cheering you on investing
the best thank you very much thank you
thank you i appreciate the effort very
much
[Music]
right sorry i don't know it's i've been
reading super chats for too long that i
um go over these maybe too quickly now
sorry sorry hello baby though
baby
the minikians are multiplying again
jeffrey kitten are you using that
are you using that um someone posted
this on twitter today
some like desktop application where
a lot of mini cheaters show up on your
desktop and do stuff with your desktop
is that what you're having issues with
right now that's so funny
uh sorry i can't help you with that
so funny that people are actually using
that kia
shimaji
i want to try that out maybe what do
they do do they actually like move like
windows
in your on your desktop like do they do
[Music]
something
to your children
yeah they throw them i love it
they attack oh my god i love it i love
that
they eat it oh my god they eat the
windows
[Laughter]
oh that's hilarious
you
no keep them that's pretty funny where
can i find this i think i'll retweet it
after my stream
thank you for the pinky i'm gonna miss
you mama hope the move goes well i'll be
blasting your songs as many times as i
can especially when working out oh thank
you
gotta lift those those weight weights
good luck with that baby baby
no no oh
[Music]
oh baby so cute
no don't go away
she always runs away
always runs away from me even though she
loves me
[Music]
thank you moto sand for another red
super chat thank you
thank you
for listening partially
see you again we'll see you soon thank
you ryan p
very sweet of you um i hope i can see
everyone again goodbyes are so painful
aren't they
thank you ryan he stole my balloons also
thank you for the pinkie
i was gonna save this for you one
million but figured you'd wanna hear it
now no matter what happens from here
remember that
of all the western otaku with teenage
dreams of becoming
an anime girl slash boy in japan you're
one of the few who succeed and love you
what do you mean teen's dream of
becoming one i always was one
no idea what you're talking about he
stole my balloons
no idea if you're talking about tina's
dream of becoming
a member of hilarious yes i'm one of the
few who succeeded
now that's something i can be proud of
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you for the support
ty rex thank you soon thank you also for
rent
uh for rent supported yeah trevor t
hoot kia i hope you are able to relax
and have a safe flight i wish you a
wonderfully
sappy reunion with your fluff balls you
have gone for a lot recently
but continue to do your best to stream
and you deserve nothing but to
but the perfect return home safe travels
thank you
it's funny how i've been for a lot
before i came here now i've been i'm
going for
these stupid shadow bands for a week
already
give me a freaking break fair enough oh
you're here yeah thank you
besides besides some streaming youtube
problems and stuff
everything has gone pretty well it's so
weird though
after one year coming back it's it feels
feels very weird to be back it's like
what what what happened where am i why
am i here
i feel very weird thank you
for the support i'll do my best from
that one too
arigatou gozaimasu
stop making cute noises
don't distract me baby you're too cute i
have to read super chats
is
[Music]
that's the the super chat that had uh
33 343 yen for
good luck
[Music]
finally we're done with the snake super
chats
okay my freaking nose is started
maybe i should get some like wet tissues
for my face
always ready for me to use
because it's just so
lovely
i keep on rubbing it
okay
okay next super chats are a mix of i
guess mostly m
sheep first yeah one from the waiting
room but mostly i'm cheap
uh okay i'm sheep super chat
[Music]
what are you attacking no baby
yes she's so cute
babies are attacking me
babies are attacking me maybe
[Music]
one of you has to come here now and help
me
who's gonna be do i have to get you
myself
all right one second
no don't go away
[Music]
are you gonna stream now are you gonna
stream
okay i got one cat
cute
oh it's so soft oh
no okay bye-bye
[Music]
okay
they're fighting again only for one
second
flambe so thank you for the red super
chat welcome back yeah
thank you
uh yeah
what the [\h__\h] was that
what was that
what are you playing with let me see
you want to play with that okay come
here
yo no no oh they want to play guys i
can't stream right now they want to play
uh
[Music]
hey
eh
[Music]
oh
ah this is what it feels like to be
replaced
tangents are not replaced by cat rings
reject stream return to kettles
gotta give them attention when they want
it
and they're in playful mood right now
you
now
oh
okay it's all the girls
okay
okay i apologize deeply for
all the cat breaks
very sorry
baby no
no
okay anyway plunder once again
thank you for a red super chat
while i see super chats are back on yeah
you got uh you sent me a red super chat
right away after this super chat got
back turned on thank you very much for
the support
thank you
baby okay okay i have to stop touching
my cats
[Applause]
there's no one who can ignore a cute cat
right in front of you
laser guide 67 thank you for read super
chat
ah sweet super chat relief wait do you
love
i think you're using super chat strong
is super chatting
a way for you to relax and relieve
yourself
i don't think this is how you should be
using the super chats
but i mean i'm not complaining
thank you very much for the support
thank you
and foreign
stop laughing chat stop it
uh platinum knight danke sun
elsie laban thank you soon randall dan
kishan
sakba
oh i see some i think i see some
puns i may
be lamb blasted for this
but never gonna give it
it yeah what's that supposed to mean
like how did i read that
e-w-e i put that in like a million times
is that supposed to be like a like a
sheep sound
if it even
evie you
why is it is it i don't get it
how is ewe you
how is that it's a young sheep
yvette is a female what
i've never heard that one before
how do you pronounce it though never
gonna give ava up never gonna get
let eva down never gonna run around and
dessert even
never gonna make even cry never going to
say goodbye and i'm going to tell a lion
her david
stupid screen save jealous
[Music]
eva is pronounced you
what
what what the [\h__\h]
english language
what
how ha
that's just [\h__\h] stupid
that's the weirdest thing that i've ever
heard about
english language up until now
ever
what
that's just that's just stupid
okay i for now for from now on i will
reject the english language and just
speak german because
german makes sense to me english doesn't
i suspected
[Music]
to my decent english in super chat john
outdoor train
at listen hello
glad to hear that you that
your home
[Music]
your cuts over
over your head
when you come home
i really missed your
[Laughter]
i'm allowed to hear
the sweet soft
beautiful
foil of
my favorite
[Music]
phoenix again
here
sorry i'm very distracted
where bear okay
oh my god my cat is like so crazy right
now
oh my god you okay
no she's hunting air right now
oh baby one is coming you can you can
attack here now instead of attacking the
air
the air didn't do anything bad
baby one is attacking my sock
one second
ah
come on mom okay um
sorry guys
sorry guys hi cat sorry i'm late for
work when nice you finally came
it's okay though people are easily
missing out on my streams right now
elizabeth thank you for the pinky
outcast 777 thank you also for the pinky
thank you thank you thank you welcome
back yellow we miss you thank you well
you wrote that at the time where i think
i didn't
oh no this is ah ah oh yeah they got
turned on when i came ah
these are all welcome back super chats
yay
the landing super chats thank you
no one danke shin dominique duncan is
for stopping thank you for the pinky the
phoenix had landed welcome home tension
hope you had a good flight now get some
rest and give your cats lots and lots of
love thank you thank you
cats get such a cute
i missed the landing after being there
for days um now yeah the waiting room
was open for a long time wasn't it
um sorry for everyone who didn't make it
patrick and duncan
ah so that's why i woke up so early and
couldn't get back to sleep must have
been my body's way of telling me
attention was back in australia
voice you had a good feeling about that
i see good job good job
i was betting on friday evening but i
don't even remember when i wrote
when did i i think yeah arrived saturday
morning
in my time
i feel lucky for witnessing it oh that
was very lucky yes
i was scrambling between sets to walk in
your back
thank you who was actually there who in
the chat right now was there for the
landing
raise your hands
oh oh
quite a lot of you whoa super chat was
proof true
true yeah you were there
nice good job guys
good job you gotta you got a special
badge for that everyone who is there for
the phoenix landing gets a special badge
will be sent to you will arrive soon
jacqueline napoleon madrid
thank you for the red super chat
thank you for two pinkies in a row that
makes you one red one
went and post some crappy photoshops on
reddit as well good job
phoenix has led it i repeat the phoenix
has landed
thank you sorry my my my i'm getting
weird
[Music]
good to know you had a safe trip welcome
back our queen thank you for welcoming
me back so
so warmly so so
so is that even the word you actually
say
like that gosh i'm getting crazy after
all these hours reading super chats
thank you
what up bro gang
uh
it's because you don't take enough cat
breaks dental must be
true you're right you should take more
cat breaks
kiana i'm drunk please enable the super
chats
as you wish sir
wait i'm having an issue
there we go can't open it right now
maybe in a moment please wait for me
i'll open it at the end again
shrimp for you
yeah you're as beautiful as the day as
we lost your wednesday
yeah it shouldn't have been much changes
thank you danceable function unknown
decibel duncation gloves
kiana's gloves has a proper picture with
black gloves oh my
god i cannot [\h__\h] believe it
i love you guys trevor g thank you for a
red super chat
and and another one following up that
dear kiana my little turtle dove how are
you i'm not a turtle i'm turtle it
didn't happen yet
but okay how are you how was your flight
i hope it was pleasant and you were able
to crest peacefully
it hasn't been too long but i wanted you
to know i've
i visit you i pray
oh oh wait oh wait oh wait there's a
bunch of puns in here
oh baby baby you want to read the
trebuchet super chat
i pray you landed and returned to your
nest safe and sound with love georgie ps
recently
benny in kfp did you guys hear that
did you guys hear that meow recently
money and give me have taken
to calling me a monster it's a little
hard to swallow
i can't possibly geeze as to why it's
not like i've committed murder i hope if
your return they won't quail at the side
of me anymore
holy [\h__\h] travertine you're on fire
you're on fire with the bird puns oh my
god don't worry
um i don't think you're a monster
i mean it was pretty scary you having
that chicken
in your hand and killing it and eating
it
that was that's pretty terrifying oh but
i think we all love you
baby second meow debbie
[Music]
yay that was that was uh
that was baby uh chunky baby by the way
that was terrifying it really was
oh why are you dropping my things baby
don't do that
it's all good i know it's too to tell
but i know it's i know i know turtledove
i was making a joke god damn it
no don't call her bad baby she's a good
baby even when she does bad things
[Music]
you heard the gum so loud
stupid so let's keep like thank you for
a red super chat
um mwah what's drinking i was drinking
water
hi phoenix london congrats tanjo you're
back with us back with halloween
but most importantly you're back home go
hug your cats thank your roommate tell
your family how much you miss them and
enjoy life as much as i know you do
then you can come back and tell us
oh i swallowed keyblade really
has his priorities straight
that baby
you you um yeah i think that's
that shows that you are a good person
said
finally
uh so yeah so let's keep it thank you
for the support
i think um i've done all the things that
you
said i should do thank you very much
and i will try my best to enjoy the
situation i'm in right now
with my cutie cat
danny scope thank you cat
baby cat passing through in between my
my legs on the ground
oh oh baby cute baby so soft
thank you for blessing me with your
softness
they're so active right now oh my god
i'm gonna drop that too oh my god i have
like this shelf with like a [\h__\h] ton of
random things
on there right now because i didn't like
sorted yet and she just
laid baby too chunky baby she probably
doesn't feel it because she's so chunky
she's just laid down on top of like a
[\h__\h] ton of like random things like
like i don't know she cannot that
literally cannot be comfortable it's
like
a lot of small things and she just lays
it
on top of it just right on top of it
chunky she's probably like
her own pillow so it doesn't hurt
are you are you comfortable
yeah she's comfortable
fluff absorbs all it really does
oh she's not happy anymore she's moving
oh she's gone
yep she's now on the bed again
oh no okay i think they're calming down
now
danny scope thank you for two pinkies in
a row which makes a red super chat
thank you mwah telescope at long last
after taking flight over thousands of
kilometers the great
theory fiery majestic phoenix has
finally landed on the land down under
is that what you call australia everyone
is grateful for your safe journey
and may the remaining stages of your
moving go buttery smooth
your pc arrive unscratched and your cats
bless you with warm cuddles welcome home
takana
thank you that's actually uh pretty much
what happened yeah
everything went fine thank you for the
support thank you for welcoming me with
a
red carpet thank you that is australia
uh we don't really say that in german
but yeah i've heard that before that
saying
jk monkey also thank you for red super
chat also red carpet
nah thank you i'm getting exhausted now
hope you had a wonderful flight and
welcome back take all the time you need
to enjoy all the clubbing with your cats
greeting and family family
and friends and traveling back in your
loyal employees will be standing on
guides to report for duty for your
glorious return
thank you i'm happy to hear that
thank you that's a big relief to have
you guys always there
thank you so much for waiting for me
thank you thank you thank you it's all
back to normal now
back to normal streaming times streaming
almost every day
so i hope you'll you and me will have
lots of lots of fun together exhausted
after three hours who is this imposter
it's been three and a half hours i don't
know i'm kind of exhausted
it's a lot of super chats holy macaroni
flander also for red superchat thank you
very much thank you for the red carpet
adding my brick to the red carpet you
shouldn't add a brick that
no that's not very comfortable you let
you reset it in the same sentence
red carpet supposed to be a carpet not a
brick
that doesn't make it a carpet
welcome back yeah glad you had a safe
trip miss your streams
and but hope you get some well deserved
bread first
arrest first after a taxing type of
moving countries
thank you gosh i'm so
weird right now and
uh
who am i
where am i
shut up i'm not always weird
shut up shut up you know nothing
no i did not morse code wink at you
thank you the red carpet flanders thank
you very much
and also thank you for red super chat
thank you welcome back home thank you
gaga
thank you i appreciate it thank you for
your generosity
and contributing to the red carpet cyric
also read super chat oh dear lord
welcome back hope you had a good journey
and
i'll settle in and rest up a bit the
care if we will wait patiently for you
hopefully have much fun cuddling with
your cats as well of course
thank you very much thank you
thank you you know i you know i
appreciate it right you know you know i
do right
right thank you i love you
thank you
[Music]
he really glad to hear you made it i
miss you i panicked a little bit but
deep down
under no he didn't ride under it deep
down i knew our feelings was laughing
there's so many wonderful things i've
been looking forward to thank you for
joining whole life and being part of my
life wow thank you
thank you thank you too i'm i'm really
happy to be
in this situation now being in whole
life is
such a blessing and such an honor
and honestly such a lucky thing to
happen to me in my life
and it's really hard to grasp but
it's the best thing ever to happen to me
in life so
thank you for supporting me in that
package
black friday
[Music]
rainbow carpet like from which
am i supposed to reach from the top or
from the bottom
because the first one has no words in it
but i guess it's just you know
i guess from the bottom probably makes
sense
and rainbow dreaming about rainbows
signal positive and colorful adventures
it's a symbol of renewal happiness and
dreams coming true
i think i've never dreamed jammed about
from the top
but do you realize that
you want me to start from the hundred
dollars okay
everybody
no that's okay okay the top for me would
be
starting from the hundred dollars but
i'm starting from the lowest one okay
okay
okay panic panic panic okay yeah yeah
okay okay
i got you i got you fan and
yeah i never dreamt about a rainbow did
you guys ever dream about a rainbow
before
i can't give you sweet dreams or make
your dreams come true but have this
rainbow to welcome you back home at
least
you're in the name of all your fans good
luck and a lot of success in your
australian
adventure majestic idol
your fans are staying with you for
freaking finn never quitting
i hope that like a rainbow glowing
through rainy days reagan bougain
why did you write why did you add the
the german there
meeting us fills your life of color
sorry color and mixer remember that
there's a horizon
to look forward to even during cloudy
and gray days
that's some deep stuff that's very deep
to sound cool oh wow
well i'm glad you think that adding some
german and makes you sound cool
just don't forget that rainbows need the
sun shining in the sky just as much
yeah that's you yeah i'm son
i'm son i'm sunburned i'm feeks i'm son
p.s i can't believe how much i missed
you oh well that's so sweet i was just
gone for a little bit
but i'm glad you guys missed me or you
missed me specifically i don't know if
the others missed me but
i'm glad to hear that muslim makes me
happy makes me feel
needed thank you
thank you for the big big rainbow
looks beautiful even though i don't see
the color right now
i can imagine it thank you so much thank
you for the sweet and kind words they're
very very very sweet
i'll cherish them in my heart
thank you for all the support you give
me
i hope i can dream of a rainbow sometime
or see one again whenever i leave this
apartment ever again and go outside
which will be in a million years because
i don't go outside
thank you
big kisu a rainbow case for you
armored goal and vacation del star city
vancouca
[Music]
oh what happened there
oh god were you pooped out
is that did he get
pooped out what happened
followed up by jasper by the way
okay calm down
casper
oh okay casper is just drunk oh girl
he drank too much
oh he's fine he's fine casper is fine oh
my god casper and jasper's so cute
freaking love those two
i love casper i love the casper super
chats i want to give him like an
award or something oh my god casper is
the cutest
cutest super chatter that's out there
you guys all lose to casper sorry guys
casper is the winner
yes love those super chats
best thing ever absolutely best thing
ever i mean jasper is pretty good too
they're like a good team
pretty damn good team there
sorry guys sorry can't win against
casper
y'all y'all are getting pretty close
though not trying to win that's okay
that's good
it's not it's not a competition yeah
but if it was then casper won
imagine losing to a dead mouse he is not
dead okay
he's not dead he's alive he's very much
alive
grass gross rat extra lie excuse me can
you not
call him a gross rat he's not a rat
my babies are just being too cute oh my
god
he's not bad no
no no no
he's not dead he isn't
no
reincarnation by digestion shut up
he didn't get eaten he's alive okay
uh yuki baskerville thank you for a red
super chat
my first super chat to commemorate that
the phoenix has landed we miss you a lot
boss but i'm glad that you are
safe and back in australia with your
cats
sorry that you could have to look at
them for a moment
[Laughter]
it has been a long travel so please take
care and rest well see you soon
thank you thank you very much
oh my god cute oh my god
oh [\h__\h] she started kneading oh my god
baby one is needing my blanket
she stopped oh my god that was so cute
she made she made um fast food biscuits
speed biscuits
[Music]
anyway it has been a long
travel so please take care and rest well
see you soon thank you yuki thank you so
much i'm glad to be
here thank you for waiting for me and
for welcoming me back
thank you so much mwah i can't name
stepped collection
thank you so you got kamiyah thank you
for red super chat
tanja i'm sorry i went to tease we're
almost done oh my god we're done
i went to cheese neda before you landed
i asked her to demonstrate hiccup i
promise i'll be good in the future
please don't put me in the usual room
i want to i want to understand the super
chat send me a clip or something
[Music]
thank you sweetheart tell me more about
that
bird
thank you thank you thank you thank you
bird god
is domestically thank you for the pinky
as they definitely say in australia
how does a canadian come up with that
phrase where did you get that from
thank you
nice thank you shin yazid lazy guy danke
shin
pyrrha homura dan kishan and the last
one oh how
fitting the last one is from homo
airlines
i loved the the all the messages that
hubble airlines was sending during the
um arrival lobby
i hope you had a good flight and had a
good rest chad thank you for being here
with me this chat will go
down in kfb history books love you all
thank you
holo airlines thank you soon thank you
for being there
pretty much most of the time i've seen
you there always every time i checked in
thank you guys that's the end of the
super chat that i had to read
sorry guys it took so long and
we are done i can go back to my cats and
then in two hours
we'll have a collab on amelia's channel
it's been a while since the last collab
with amer
same with gwyra that's why i asked both
of them this week if they want to do
collabs
so i'll see you in two hours maybe and
some of you not
maybe
thank you guys for watching the the
super chat reading stream honestly i'm
i'm really
every time i'm always so confused as to
why so many people want to watch the
super chat reading streams
but if it weren't for you guys it would
be a very sad
couple of hours if i would just be
reading this to what 20 people then i
would probably be
thinking why am i doing this but since
you guys are all here listening
and having fun together with me and just
hanging out with me
i really enjoy these super chat reading
streams i
it makes me definitely realize that
everyone's everyone who is here for the
super chat reading streams
really love me for who i am and are
just here for me as a person even though
there is not even much
interaction with the chat just more
interaction between the super chat than
me
you guys are here anyway and i really
really really appreciate it thank you
guys
also the ones who didn't even super chat
but still are here for the super chat
readings like
wow thank you you're just here to listen
to my voice i guess thank you so much
it's it's quite interesting to me and
i'm very happy
to have so many of you here i'm very
laggy too i am very laggy yes lag
and lag
oh it's prime time right now so maybe
that's why
anyway fixed
oh
so yeah thank you guys cool
see you again um maybe tomorrow
depending on if the
shadow band gets fixed tomorrow if not
as i said
there will be a day off on first day
instead of friday
and then we will have minecraft
hopefully on friday but for now
we will we will wait i know hasta i turn
on oh yeah i said i'll turn on superchat
okay
i will turn on super chats but i will
not read them how about that
thank you for the membership i'll just
look at them
i just look at them and say and i'll
acknowledge them
but i'll not force myself to read them
is that okay
that's even better
how come you don't want to be read by me
but i always feel so guilty though when
i say that and the super chats come in
and i feel so bad about not reading them
and then i end up reading them anyway
[Music]
okay i'll just i'll just look at them
while i eat my salad okay
that's a good idea okay
[Music]
um
okay here they come
here they come
thank you
what
british accent he
you know toray i don't i don't know i
don't know how
what
thank you
um
hmm
i love your gay mom oh my god
thank you thank you flanders thank you
apple
thank you happy happy thank you
cutie cats hmm
alec that is a very very um
that statement makes a lot of sense
but you know
i know you gotta talk about that with my
with my papa better next time
i have to read that one as cute comrades
these words are for you alone
chimpkin gays is distracted but you must
not know of our plot our next current
one and so following
i will never not read your super dads
you cannot
escape my case
hmm
okay
yes king mufasa you deserve it
i'll send you some over
i'll send you some on my salad
there's like almost nothing left over
but yeah
ah
[Music]
oh
hmm
there are no koalas in kangaroos
kangaroos
unfortunately i mean in the zoo maybe
that was yummy
thank you as you guys for the pinky
well what's what's trap oh what do you
mean you don't hear an australian accent
from canada what do you mean
this is my australian accent i don't
know what you're talking about
boot a boot i don't know what you're
talking boots
okay i gotta really go to my cats now so
bye bye
they're getting impatient waiting for
their mama
they have left the bed now yuppie
can we get a wardrobe okay i'll try
that was the water bouncing back into
the glass i don't know if you heard that
did you hear that
what
[Laughter]
and in german we say
affilazin thank you
see you in two hours
thank you for all the super chats at the
end i i have
staring at every single one of them i
just haven't read them out loud but i
have acknowledged
them all thank you
for all the support you guys give me
i love you thank you thank you for being
here today
it was it was really i'm very
honest honestly you guys just without
you guys i would be
i would be i don't know freaking
devastated thank you for being here
thank you for watching bye bye
[Music]
cat cat cat cut
you