[Music]
w
K everybody
Welcome excitement in the in the in the
contestant side
please we love hearing the the rumbling
sounds of many people in Discord at once
hello welcome to this real Family Feud
stream this time not rigged at all Al I
mean if the game is riged then it's not
my fault I am your host takanasi kiaha
and these are my contestants let's start
here from the very left this this person
I wonder who this one is who Could It
Be I'm not a chaha I am
fuaa and today I am not Fu I am you're
on your
own yeah you can't even do your
introduction together because you're
here all
alone p
p but yeah you you you will you will
show your sister right that you have
more knowledge than her right yes I'm
the oldest sister I could do this does
it matter it matters this is serious
differ Chang anything does it doesn't
you know I said we can change the teams
the only thing I want to keep the same
is Fu moku separated that was my
goal I'm excited for some family feud
between
them next to F we have
G
hello day
to I know you excited for Family Feud
because you were like immediately like
I'm in in my reaction
meow yum yum I I'm very excited I think
it's such a GAA game
right game the contrast of her voice in
the face
of hey
don't hey I mean you are they all have
like pretty much the same face okay
granny not of their retirement home
they'll take care of me and they'll will
me to my bed where I can take a nap my
children I'm not good luck than you
Darlings me
kiss well I'll be I'll be looking
forward to all the very very special
knowledge you will share with us that
will surely match the opinions of the
American crowd American wisdom yes share
it with us I'm looking forward to it
next to you we have another blue member
this is this is narissa I don't know if
you guys noce but it should be
nerissa hi Darlings this is hollow life
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only nerissa Raven coft and I'm uh let's
let's trivia yeah
yeah we have some random trivia for us
right now uh uh uh did did you know that
Ravens can actually uh imitate uh human
noises so for example they'll make uh
like uh construction noises cuz they
think it's greting cuz I hear it so much
there thank you that's so cute lasers
too that's so cute yeah I think I heard
of that thank you for sharing that with
us I love W surely this this is looking
like a smart team so far and we have
crony who makes his team even smarter
right
crony yes
siron CH it's Ora crony from Hol live
English promise a promise now yep yep
everybody remember promise and we are
blue
blue down with
the down with winning let's go let's
go
te no team winning I just I was making a
thumbnail and I was like putting you
girls in random places but then I
noticed we have a lot of blue members so
just for the Aesthetics I put you on
that side you know it just
happened yeah it looks gorgeous you
girls look gorgeous oh my gosh thank you
and then then we have the somewhat I
guess you could
say reddish colors team maybe we're the
cute team
cute so we're starting with
moo I know I'm Mo yes and this isn't the
blue team we are the rage team the rage
team
yeah M go is her own person she has her
own introduction and she will show her
sister who's the boss even if I'm
smaller it doesn't mean that my brain is
smaller it means it's
bigger what what definitely got it a
body
ratio
yes no unfortunately I couldn't uh give
them dog ears you know but I feel like
this is pretty close you know they have
matching cat ears so you girls are cats
now meow me we
like I'll eat them no oh my God
terrifying I don't okay the next we have
be boo and this is the like for me I'm
sorry bi doesn't quite look like bi boo
but this is the best I could
do it's okay it looks um cute yeah
so introduction please oh yes uh
bomu I'm
k um oh sparkling J of H life English
Advent and today my goal is to get angry
and rock sick like the rest of my team I
will hopefully be as mad as everyone
else
yeah yeah I'm excited to to hear the
rock rage
rage give me a give me an angry angry
girl I've been
pring it's
cute want to pet it I'll P The Rock
might have to work I'm going to bite you
oh oh I'm so scared oh no better go to
am
vibrating am please you look I think you
look so cool didn't I nail you yeah like
yeah you're pretty cool yeah
Waton number one detective and I
uh yeah the rage team you
know
yeah it's looking pretty pretty angry
right now do you like your glasses I
think they're so cool super cool thank
you I love this Amelia Watson and if
only there was a like a like a a a skirt
with the the famous Amelia Watson
pattern I forgot what's called tarton
yes that but no there's no not even I
was I was even buying uh clothing items
and there's not a single skirt I'm so
sad why not what's the hate of
skirts maybe we'll we'll have to call
Family Feud after this and make them fix
this problem which is obviously a big
issue but yeah I me is a detective so
she'll surely be leading her team to
Victory oh yeah
yeah alongside the the the library of
knowledge right M oh yes it is me Nim oh
hi I'm from Hollow live English promise
I've shed shed my plaid today you shed
your what um I plaid I pla my flannel ah
mhh I'm yes posing now yes I'm a
different woman today she even has a
mustache she requested a mustache
personally I kept the mustache I I still
have that yes ah you had it in the in
the promise cab too ah I see okay so
also I just want to note that in this
team there's uh like in both teams
there's one person each AK the promise
members who played this game recently so
maybe they know some answers but that's
like evenly spread out so perfect I
would say perfect know I have memories
of this game yeah okay well then are you
girls ready for a little bit of Family
Feud let's
go fight fight fight fight fight fight
fight fight oh wow
family
em em
we have
Mo it automatically became dad I guess
you're already split families damn wow
look at our
litter I said by wa how does that
work goodbye abis Guard
Family
there's when you on the family f
oh thisy wow nice wow nice
moves I am taka thank you so much for
coming here to the
fi oh yeah
strike we've got two families ready for
to Feud it out for a load of cash oh I
don't have money for you so is there no
monary
prize it's not entirely clear I think we
get a car
[Applause]
they look primed against the team yeah
team to find best to our questions
whoever gets the highest score will go
to the final round and then get to play
first to be first you want to be first
because it will give you the best chance
to bring home the big
bucks which are imaginary here we go
here we
go wow
wait this this means
oh nice
timing oh no okay okay that's
fine I love that that was a comedic
effect here love
that no it might have been maybe because
I had the game open the whole night
maybe let's give it another
chance round two
what happened
to I hopefully all the everything's
saved uh in terms of looks I hope so
Same by by the way uh for for the
audience uh we can't hear the game so if
we talk over lucky McCoy um I don't feel
bad at all nobody would feel like you
know angry about that don't
worry why it's not loading come on come
back to me a there it is right before
playing
[Music]
how can I read that how do they me to
finish just
epilepsy this looks like a horror
game W family fute D how many people
worked on this okay a lot of people and
we will see that effort that went
into oh yeah okay thank you thank you
we're we're almost there there we go we
go
back Family Feud let's get quickly back
into it party
battle single and my characters are here
yeah okay uh yeah
[Music]
yeah we we can in between the rounds
still change it but you know think this
is a beautiful lineup right
now uh
[Music]
color that's it okay right back into it
does this look correct yes yes okay and
this team can you confirm this is your
family
M my family
but is now someone
else I'm sorry I'm just messing with you
the the or is reversed oh we SL places
that's okay that's okay it's a nice um
order you know pink brown my Senai
okay we'll have to hear the introduction
again or I'll read it to you
[Music]
again how are you girls doing on this
lovely evening by the
way me
teated she made you what she made me tea
I
did how many bags how many bags had it
was H's tea it was not Rat King tea so
it only had three bags oh no why do I
feel so hot
[Laughter]
now I really want to see how you store
the bags I'm really
curious I'll take a photo
sometime I want to I want to understand
this blue team
team lose Rivals the rage
team American let's go let go okay
you'll both be answering questions
trying to guess what our series have
said do your best because the team with
the most points at the end of the game
gets to play Fe fast money not Feast
money with huge Advantage whoever comes
out on top goes home with a lot of
cash
imaginary yeah I love
imaginary
round
okay now this will happen please don't
hate me if I I
go already starting strong here we
go
I okay shake your hand nice
handshake okay scream out your name when
you think you know the answer in as fast
he'll be in prob find the top answer
first gets to decide if they want to
play or pass yeah surve of 100 people
for name something you wear that starts
with the letter s
oh hi what do you got a skirt oh skirt
okay can I still answer a smart well not
not yet here there's the skirt
understood that's surely up there I'm
sure it is how can it be no skirts in
this game oh
what oh my God
H with shorts shorts yeah okay please
hold on I'm going get some points for
sure what
shorts that everybody is wearing are
cute though
mhms for play or
pass oh what is that me oh do you want
to bring it play it play play play I
don't know why we were pushing it over
to play it I don't know why you would
pass it maybe it's because if you run
out if like if you can't answer the
whole board then it will go over to the
other group and they can steal the
points I'd also like to discuss a
possible baby swap that occurred those S
very uh scarf scar oh nice okay can I
change my never mind no I think
lock I think that could be up there good
answer I
[Applause]
don't it's not on this SC should
definitely not be there I'm
angry why oh so
disappointed Why did no one say shirt
shirt right maybe it's too simple too
obvious but let's lock it in hey the
shirt we have to Simply the classic
shirts of course number one right yeah
yeah nice
good for you team rage M up
next all right lucky fella I'm going to
say socks
socks I forgot about the socks should I
do
sock socks plural
plural good choice sock good choice good
choice otherwi it sounds like you're
saying I want to like or
something come on
okay nice damn they did
it back
to do you have one more shoes
oh the big bra think of those shoes and
I just said s i first thought was
spats spats I don't I don't doubt that's
up
there that's the almost full only one
left gets tricky I'm I'm get another
chance do you guys have any I can ask
them for answers
right you guys have any ideas
shoes we already
saiding
teamut yeah I could see that being a one
of
the I just come on come
on you guys sh no it's what I
[Music]
do a slippers slippers
slippers H
[Music]
okay I don't think that's going to work
I'm I'm locking it in maybe wait
nope nope yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what
else is there
skin skin Oh there's not much time to
type that
in oh skin I wonder well it count
sandals
sandals I
mean aren't real so blue team gets a
chance to steal all the points if they
can guess the last
answer what this is not
fair so as a group you can discuss
quickly
um it be suits also or suits oh which is
more popular swimsuits or suits I I
would think of
swims anything think simple is the only
thing I remember being told should I
right
simple
I try how many Dam chances do we get
hey you get one one yeah
one that's too much pressure I don't
know
yeah come suit suit has less letters in
it than
swimsuits skin why do you get so much
time
that's only one think about swimsuits
during summer though for the most part
unless you're like a vacationer I feel
like suits are a pretty Universal thing
yeah I think it's suit true yeah you
agreeing with that suit if suit suit or
suit suit suit suit if skirt isn't on
there then why is
Suites or something I pray for you oh
no ra ra do not rage just
rage little baby little baby 89 it's
okay oh is 89 not very strong see this
is maybe why you might want to pass
because then you can get the chance to
steal later if you don't think you can
fill the whole board with answers wow
yeah that's okay I've I've been I've
been around I know how this works okay
save your rage save your rage it might
be time
for
ohm
yes get your ass up here watch changing
the order was good granny oh don't break
your back careful gentle now all
right shout your name if you want to
answer I got to sit up for
this often be described as sharp
sharp I'm going cut off that's why I
didn't hear
her
KNE knife knife knife KN KNE KNE yes
knife knife knife knif why was there
Star Wars
involved I let's
go that is
sharp not as sharp as our sensus but
oh 77 77 simple people player pass wow
do you guys want to try blue wait how
does this work yeah yeah do you want to
do you think you can f fill out the
whole board on your
own wait if I pass it doesn't go to the
team behind me uh you stay in the face
off uh I think for one one more
answer
hello me what do I do if she says
no play Let's play it play I'm confident
I'm more fluffy than
Shar you can do it you can do it it's
only how many answers while they suffer
I'm going to idle meeting I'll be super
fast oh okay okay oh God meeting you
know I was so confident but I suddenly
can't think of anything sharp does
anyone have any
ideas I have scissor yeah no
scissors yeah I should have thought
about I I'll I'll give you one too next
time lucky
see scissors
scissors oh is it
nice what are the other ones got you
knives I thought of something
I uh uh needle why you ice cream okay
need or is a needle pointy
ah are you sure about
needle it's sure yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay needle it is I I could
see it being sharp yeah did our survey
say
it
needle oh that's too bad I thought it
was
Goodell back to was
turn do your best I was sticking pencil
oh pencils are kind of sharp well not
always you would want a sharp pencil you
could stab someone with a pencil you
want you don't want your pencil to be
soft you want it to be sharp generally
see if that's a good answer that's an
optimistic
answer see there oh my God it
is but needle is no good
huh a pencil is basically a needle you
know do you have another one for us
granny wants to put down a sword sword
arm that was
mine now it's her sword swallowing sword
well you want try sword swallowing
swallowing no no no no no okay
sword Granny says sword hopefully it's
just a bigger knife so it's got to
be no
way I did not I'm happy to return to
offering welcome back welcome back
welcome back thank you you already have
two you know
[Music]
failures I'm so lost how could it not be
a sworded that's so weird oh right that
is so weird quick quick razor razor that
sounds pretty good razor or razor blade
razor just razor who calls it a razor
blade in this year of
2023 okay I that will be up there I can
imagine razor blade sharp you talk about
yeah it's
blade let's go clean shaven
men surve crony another a
chance kill
meor oh wait woman shave too claws
claw yeah right as to my cat claws are
pretty sharp yeah claws are sharp okay
unlock it
[Music]
in answer accepted you just buy a hor
let's see if it's there let's see oh we
have three more answers is it up there
no
what R team gets a chance to
steal okay steal a
bag what else you guys have anything so
I have I have a couple thoughts have IDE
too is teeth and tongue yeah cuz like
having a sharp tongue yeah
but I don't know cuz it's just name
something that we often described as
sharp so I feel like a tongue is often
described as sharp so I feel like the
logic works but didn't didn't we say to
think simply yeah what would
the could be one
person Tong
you got to think of the mouth okay any
any other ideas from the rage I have
glass and Nails Nails Nails that'd be a
good one I think Sharp As Nails two for
nails would guess tough as Nails
guess I'm I'm might lock in nails for
you guys I have 19 seconds go okay nail
nails or Nails Nails probably Nails
Nails Nails nail nails nails have nail
it be accept both
basic
the the razor blade was the
same
what
noing tongue or te okay if tongue is
there I'm so sorry they the point I'm so
sorry for calling you too
smart okay I'm curious maybe there's
paper up there sharp
paper make me
oh oh yes not a sword what sword is it
what Wht
my
dress man old people wrote this a sharp
dresser a sharp but what does that mean
what is a Sharp
Dress dressed sharp today that is
stupid the only one who understands it
how dare old p
how dare they not on the
[Music]
swich
okay face off oh I like this lineup man
hey baby girl hey baby girl how's it
going hey baby
girl
today only three answers oh wow oh dear
but double points so very important
shout your name if you think you know
people
answer name something you shake the sand
out of after a day at the
beach which one was first I heard Nissa
say
ah forgot my name said first said her
name
first but yeah well sorry there's some
people who said her name properly and uh
doesn't sound so
confident uh and they need points
swimsuit okay B the The Comeback of the
swimsuit that we didn't use in the
previous one this time for sure
swimsuit yeah I I shake it out of my
swimsuit now our survey says
swimsuit come
on okay not the best answer I think we
got it oh oh wait unless unless they got
it right a
chance answer come on towel nice
nice how dare you how dare you use
me
howw team blue seems happy with that
answer oh oh oh let's use
M for the
towel please please who do you think you
are you just need one more answer so are
you going to play or pass uh we're going
to play hell yeah that's what I like to
hear theme Let's Go Blue Team sweep so
faroni it's right now this is starting
to matter yes shoes or sandals I mean
shoes are kind of Broad
and sandals to be included so that could
be
okay even if this is is wrong I think
you still get another chance another
[Applause]
one
yeah oh my God
points oh my God they're just getting
the easy ones cuz they have an old
lady and don't you forget
it oh team surprisingly but not
surprisingly it's blue team
sorry R Team guys come on you'll get
another chance
feeling it's not over yet there's the
fast money
round fast money fast
money buckle up for buckle up for some
big bugs it's time to play F money just
the captain will play this round oh just
the captains okay we can change the
captain later about team let's laugh at
some
W you got
this your competitor will get a chance
afterwards for now you have to give five
answers
fast name a sport that has the wildest
fans soccer soccer she says soccer just
like
me oh my God y a Family Expense that
increases with each Child O uh uh uh
school school oh okay ha she said
School NE food that some people snack on
while grocery shopping what people do
that uh chips chips chips you think
someone opens a bag of chips while
they're uh shopping people do
it name a popular color for a sports car
r red oh R
red okay there it is something squee
there name something you squeeze to get
more out of it
orange I love oranges oh yeah there it
is that's it you got it all very
confidently good job now the other
family love you and now it's my turn
well go go get up here you have to
answer again the same questions but
different ANS I'm going to ask you the
wait the same ones answers you have to
answer that's hard for us yeah going up
second so name a sport that has the wild
fans hockey
hockey hockey like ice hockey you
mean okay name a Family Expense that
increases with each child
food food oh nice good one good one very
logical good answer yeah snack the
snacking while grocery
shopping gummies
gummies is that just what you want to
eat
gummies they popular color for sports
color blue
blue opposite yeah you were using the
opposite colors that's cute uh there you
go sque something you squeeze to get
more out of it
shampoo oh
okay that's the first thing I
saw that's the best you got I would have
said toothpaste maybe yeah I know that's
what I was thinking oh no no what are
you doing I was just thinking about
shampoo that's fine it's maybe it's up
there we we'll never know until we know
let's find out first up drum
roll the said drum roll but they drum
roll dare
Talking Football which one was it
football football was the top
answer Family Expense Family Expense
increases with each child
hey but doesn't Hawker have more points
28 is this game not American wait is
this game not
americ oh it has more but that doesn't
mean it's the the the like a top answer
even I see I see ANW the snack was chips
versus gummies
[Music]
gummies are good okay grapes oh grapes
the top
answer you can just pick it off the
bag's open
already want to that
rude red versus
blue
yeah I can't choose the same color then
one more one more
final interesting well I think orange is
kind of weird
too I
[Applause]
my multiply by 10 multiply by
10 I'm going to get extra oatmeal now
that's a lot that's not happening you're
not getting the money I'm sorry LEL up
give us the money we'll see you next
hand it over is that it do we win yeah
you did EAS awesome you won every
round blue
te look at them don't they look like
winners with her
money nothing cuz it's fake
motorized motorized hoodies I like
what we want to we want to see a Revenge
right
you want to see a come I I may have I we
may need to approach this in a different
way this may have taken surveys from
Canada I repeat this may not be a this
may Canadian depending on where you are
in America uh hockey is pretty big and I
definitely think in in America soccer no
one cares about soccer in America I've
never met an American who cares about
soccer but my Google research has
brought me to this um possible
conclusion wait but they said but the
top answer was football football so
isn't that that doesn't that that's
American football American yeah that is
a good point but it could also fall
under soccer
iird
but soccer at all I said I said soccer
for yeah but football was still so it
might be America yeah it might be
America cuz they don't have we shall
approach this with more cautions
discussions let's go for a rematch renge
team don't have remebrance
day reveng now will the pink team be
able to show us a good comeback wo one
can only guess what's going to happen on
this second game of Family
Feud woo wooo W wo
oh wait is it the same wait oh you might
have wanted to mix it up sorry because
then the last round will just be full m
again well we can we can swap we can
just have a
I oh
no crony okay let's quit this what yeah
I'm going to I'm going to rearrange the
teams I mean just by just a leader we
care about Aesthetics here yeah I think
would be a good leader let's
go they are the most Senai after
all please Senpai carry us yeah yeah
carry Senpai their experience will carry
each team to success hey my my team and
totally not the other team remember
Canada right right remember is it
Canadian yes it is Canadian you should
think like a Canadian because you most
American American ever I've looked it up
and I telling the truth
no Canadian
national no way how do you think like a
Canadian though I don't
know oh bio it's you you can just think
like an American it's okay but
other I think that's not true okay
just continue to
sign cuz why is there no Remembrance Day
in the last time we played this game
what is that oh that's because um
Canadians just didn't remember it
existed forgot oh you can't say that
bro
Rememberance I don't I don't even
remember like Austria's like you know
National Country Day thingy so like
maybe yeah some people just don't
remember their special days bro it's a
national Hol
bro if they told the Canadians to think
like Americans and it just that's why
it's just so difficult to play this game
hey hey hey hey wao okay whoa who oh
nice okay girl a leader nice let's go
grandma Yeah okay wait let me match this
up I want Advent to match up again or do
you girls not want to go against each
other for the the face off
Watson
what yes or no yeah that's good yeah
okay yeah we're good yeah the others
too facing off I think it's it's just uh
you know perfect uh the face off will
still be I'm in yeah the first one yeah
oh I see what you're saying I see what
you say okay that looks good here we go
family fi goas family round two
[Music]
family they put your name in like
that
right I mean your your Discord does cut
off uh quite a bit but maybe if you say
your name call Yell your name really
loud no that will make it cut
off does cut
off that that was fine that was fine
okay Back Where I Belong
y almost looks like the whole talk
Studio yeah fing families they switch
their leader um to switch it up a little
bit this family wants to win it all
again again yeah Frey blue family I will
complain you're complaining I will take
my
complaint hopefully hopefully we'll be
translated to good answers
okay get go to the final round and then
get to play
first exercise your
brain
yeah well gaura I think has done many
brain exercises in the course of her
career I have 2 a.m. dementia let's go
te
isn't 2: a.m. the time where you are the
most active anyway absolutely not
no all right girls come
to oh handshake friendly
handshake shut up six
answers six nice
Beret it a we asked 100 people all right
all right I'm on the right we asked 100
Canadians something you don't want to
see a dog aiming at when he lift his oh
was
that she said it before the question was
done said it first before that after
that she seems confident
oh face wait your shoes your shoes mouth
shoes did you shout out face and not
your
name what I'm still not sure what I
heard you say all right in the beginning
I said face first but I decided to
change it
ah shoes oh yeah oh yes all right take
it away team let's go let's
go oh oh you take it away cuz you don't
have the top answer yet is a
chance uh mouth c i that CR shut up a
couch or sofa okay okay they they're
probably putting those words together
into one I would think yeah right I'm
hoping oh it's on
furniture I'm so
sorry that's not fair you could have
said they're asking Family Play Play
This is rigged wait what do I don't
understand this still what do I do guys
team wait play play I
play okay this is a rude
question it is it is a rude
question should pass oh oh yeah I do
want to hear the doggo's answers but
first is
Nissa uh um leg leg oh yeah I think that
could be the number one answer that's
like the obviously the most unfortunate
aim
spawn yeah exception surve this will be
a great guideline for f
what that should be number one if you go
to dog
parks the experience is me seeing other
people have it happened to them it
didn't happen to me I should
clarify I'm a demon gu dog okay yeah so
it's different uh but those regular dogs
yeah no manners h no manners
mouth
face I
mean I don't know B sleeping on the
carpet and what you're going
with it it would be really
unfortunate technically
MTH does it have to be mouth oh my God
cuz that's the worst
save your
team your
te it feels so bad when you Brea
like oh
appliances yeah you know should I write
appliances to get
appliances okay short
cting I don't know these are such broad
answers I'm so mad oh it doesn't have it
just phone just phone just pH then no
time oh it does okay okay okay let's go
Appliance what a word such a smart
sounding word h maybe not the top answer
but oh
no we can do this we can do this we can
do this group group meeting group me
what do you guys what do you guys think
of carpet just
ipet IET you don't think it counts as
Furniture rug rug or no carpet does
count carpet isn't Furniture either rug
or carpet
carpet carpet if it's
R okay we can do
thats is a
carpet what yeah but but this game's
stupid my cat's up on the carpet
yesterday oh
no there's no way that is actually
what's going on the
even what what is wrong with people
yeah find out let me see let me see this
number six was a car car yeah yeah
lifting their leg onto the car
okay
computer electric things yeah yeah and
Grandma
that's so
stupid M first yeah but you you meant
yourself with all these body part
answers but it didn't take it like that
God damn
it
only only a the rage team could still
get it back of course I want to I want
to stick this man behind a
tiger what does that mean he can
experience a different type of I guess
tail lifting that's worse wow
agression not
again go I love
you okay your names please not no
s everybody
Cal Calm before the storm people us an
answer
to name another famous bear that Yogi
Bear might get into a fight with what
that was Nissa who's that um smokey
Smokey the Bear nice this seems to be
something
American Smokey cuz I have no idea what
this is
about don't Smokey Bear you don't want
to is it written correctly yeah I think
I think yeah the the the r R's R is fine
I think R is fine
R so I'm blind those
seems okay now that that sounds like
it's a there Smokey Bear what is this
who's y wild
prevention oh good job Nissa oh my
God uh what do y'all want to do of
course what
pass let's do it okay let's do it play
y'all better know some famous Bears cuz
I don't know
anymore I have one answer I'm not going
to share
okay
my Freddy
F hul What hulk what's a bear what's a
bear with a name Faz bear wait what
noog quick the the the bead the bear
that's really
strong not Godzilla I can't talk
that he's a monkey are
youing I don't know it's okay you can
have one
one that's okay crony what the big okay
come on cron thinking of a monkey uh
Paddington
Paddington so I do not like how quickly
it was recommended that is a bear right
answer that do be a bear what
bear a bear in stare let's go oh oh nice
one
Grizzly oh that was my answer give me
some
huh go p a p
p p h p with h oh yeah I was going to
stop there wait po
what Winnie with a W try start with a w
Winnie w i
n Winnie is
winning yes can win in the Poo make you
win this one again let's
[Applause]
see
nice just a bear cartoon cartoon Bears
any um Bob
b a l that from the
jungle Balo like this yeah yeah L yeah
okay you think that's a name I haven't
heard in a while let's run with it let's
see if these Canadians thought of it
when they were nope
no no Canadians aren't allowed to watch
those movies so sorry
redeem
yourself okay I remember what I wanted
to say so I'm going to say it grizzly
okay that is really scary a type of bear
is that a actual bear
famous we we had a Grizzy Bear Run at us
before we almost we almost P him and
then that's an interesting story what
you yeah we were excited okay exced we
thought that we might oh God wait what
we what we do bear there's bear and
steam Bears what do you guys want be Ste
but doesn't no one remember how to
remember it because of like the Mandela
effect so we think that's spell
differently no
it's what happens if you look at
bar you sp yeah I thought it was bar can
you look
B
Bean e see what it
recommends Bean Bear wait is it not
going to recommend it bear bear what it
doesn't recomend it this is a good sign
wait wait what about like the what is it
the Red Riding Hood bears do they have a
name Red Riding Hood were Bears those
were wolves the Bears with the for the
Bears with little bears bears Papa Bear
papa bear bear wait okay baby
bear I'm indecisive you guys pick
dude I don't know I don't know
doar
bear
papaa
sorry maybe it'll take
it there's too many bears bears bears
come up
and what what are the answers what is
that care
bearers
okay I for oh my gosh Boo Boo from Yogi
I don't think he they wouldn't
fight he's too chill but he would if you
wanted your honey true no he would you
can still get it 9 points is still
doable team rage especially CU I think
the double points are coming up people
to
Jo
okay show down baby
okay s
s there are seven answers for this
question seven seven a all right let's
sweeten the pot a bit dou double or
nothing we got 100 people to answer the
following
question name us name usate with two
words
name well I me that was for
wa right um new yor yeah
[Music]
amazing I could even agree with Dad I
think that's
there
y oh wait there's even a lot of other
ones New
[Laughter]
Jersey in New York
1920 a grandma
guys guys we
got are you yeah play you think you can
get all seven answers oh God yeah I know
all 50 states in alphabetical order I
could do this by
myself
Nifty um Las Vegas oh yeah wait US state
North
Dakota
chaotic North
Dakota North
Carolina it's all there damn I I don't
know I'm Canadian man what am I supposed
to
know
God damn this is
this time for your guest which one would
you like there's so many
[Music]
uh New Mexico oo New
Mexico uh there it is oh New Hampshire
enough oh wow let's see if
the New
[Music]
Mexico nice one nice one Nisa we just
need one I know you have all but we need
one um what one is no one else going to
know who is not American in our tee um
thinking uh let's do West Virginia West
Virginia Misty
[Music]
Mountains so
[Applause]
mad there's easy one
foroni so miserable right
now come on CR Dr in that misery crony
no let it let it take
you nor Carina Carolina yeah just pick
one of
these just got to start
answer West what
yeah wait what else is there what else
is there n what El is there New Jersey
New Jersey and now New
Jers
okay that's one that came up also before
yeah new if you just type in new then it
comes with tons of stuff right new yeah
let's try newspaper now New Jersey uzo
New Jersey where you're going with
this do we have New Hampshire already
enough New Hampshire is not okay New
Jersey no one cares about New Hampshire
nice the second biggest
answer okay
KO have one so this has to be like the
third state that people thought of yeah
yeah um famous
One do we think like Rhode Island or
like South
Dakota both are good guesses I could do
whatever one you don't do I'll okay I'll
uh I'll try Road Island okay RH I think
is it RH o it's not there it's not
there what it's not like this it's not
like that
[Laughter]
okay one more time
R wait what what if it's not there oh it
is there okay okay r with the yes thank
you sorry I'm
European it sounds the
same the island of many roads it's not
there okay oh God we can do it we can do
itth Carolina
South Carolina
put New Hampshire we did we do Hamshire
yet West if the answer is there you'll
Ste the think South Carolina is a good
bet South Carolina okay sure it sounds
familiar to even me so it must be a
famous
One North one wasn't then it's probably
South South Carolina South
Carolina here we go okay let's go let's
go let's go get our survey sa what if
it's North
[Music]
Carolina big one we're missing we can do
it it could
be no you don't even you don't need the
last
there do
you he just tells you it could be
okay hire wait you guys didn't do New
Hampshire yeah nobody always there in
the
suggestions I'd like to call out chat on
their horrible geography skills those
You' seen Las Vegas and Los
Angeles W you're winning now rage team
yeah trip point triple
point
trip can do
this the
promise
promise was
naked good to see
youbody I could say the same your names
name is m okay name something you get
every Valentine's
Day
that said
oh did you say chocolate
chocolate
chocolate I
remember I'm so sorry everyone I failed
you all I failed all
[Music]
good I um flowers yeah I thought so
flowers she said
it flowers couldn't say it had to be
crony who said flowers yes feeling luy
flowers I agree crony please beautiful
flow so satisfying
[Applause]
what at least a
tire time or what's the top answer a
kiss you think
we are you playing play it play Let's
Play Let's
Play how are these not the the I never
noticed you had such beautiful green
eyes
crony I know thank you it changes in the
light yeah okay host a card c
yeah I don't
have I
[Music]
know of course it's
there of course it is
yeah wo I think that's a stupid
answer do I get chocolate because it's
on sale and I get
choc yeah what so I get some chocolate
Nara what do you want for Valentine's
Day is it I I mean I always I always buy
myself chocolates but that's what we
exactly yeah want kiss um uh I would
like to kiss I buy myself I want to see
if that's up there they care about the
trees
kiss most interference host interference
no no no what the last round host
interference
yeah Island yeah okay sometimes forces
just happen if Kisses one then maybe
hugs
oh that's cute a hug hugs or
hug hug hugs hugs okay not just one
multiple hugs multiple yes one is not
enough we want many please and we want
many points
too what if you don't want kisses he
just want hugs the Americans just don't
want hugs no wow hey there
okay
and what would you want
dinner I don't know dinner din dinner
not pretty WAOW big brain dinner
dinner blue buff understood I wouldn't
have even been able to think of that
same
damn
shes actually good
choice um two more
answers I have two ideas I'm thinking
either like a teddy bear like a toy you
always see the toys or like or jewelry
oh yeah
I okay I think I'll try toy then okay a
stuff animal or stuff like that I can
see that yeah toy
hope Toyota Ted Toyota I would love a
Toyota for
my a
Toyota to got a problem of a Toyota
no
no I wonder if they would have
differentiated between they might have
jewelry jewelry let's go let's go safe
rout
yeah cuz we don't know if they
differentiate jewy or
[Laughter]
Jeweller yeah is it jewellery a place
that makes Je
I don't I don't
know free wait I have a theory what if
it's like go sadness you know because
the other side of it like depression I
was going to say
lingerie what
what I was going to say teddy bear like
be more specific but we have to get this
so what do you guys think I I I guess
lingerie to be honest don't look at me I
don't
know I could see it we can go with
lingerie okay I don't think that's wait
wait wait wait wait is that to let's go
with that let's go with that Heart Break
oh wait really 40
seconds I don't know you get every
Valentine's like is is sadness
overthinking it 30 seconds I think it's
is it overthinking it a let's go with
underwe under underwear lingerie
lingerer okay I person think it's a
really good one cuz I think it's quite
common
it's Ted be teddy bear teddy bear teddy
Teddy Teddy Tedd Teddy Teddy
Bear was already tell you that love to
get Linguini yeah
[Music]
is it's sadness I'm going to be so mad
if it's sadness It's s be mad for you so
that you don't have to get mad at me
forness I'll be sad no
way that's
like guys grandpa oh
shoot wouldn't have got it
anyways stupid SC
it feels bad though when it's something
we didn't think of so perfume seems kind
of stupid
rude fast money round clone depending on
who it
is yeah I think
good he is that to make like the other
person smell how you want them to smell
yeah May or it like oh I know you like
this smell so I'll get I'll get it for
you hope you like this yeah cuz good
perfume can be really expensive so I
don't know good gift I
guess your
per answers because when you're done
your opponent get buddy scor points
round I'm glad you also hate him your
time
begin okay okay face what food do you
think should be chosen as the national
food of America hamburger yeah hand a
hamburger
okay hamburger a cheeseburger impair uh
name something you don't like to see on
your spouse's face what my bsh a
frown okay I would have said many
different things but that could work
frown that's a nice major decision major
decision the whole family should
participate in
making child
vacation
vacation where are we going let's go
somewhere where's the seat there
vacation
vacation should we move Grandma into a
home name something nose nose
no she got the genius answers damn
okaying my nose name something some
people cheat at test test
oh speaking from
experience test test no no maybe it's
who would ever cheat a test not us no
never cheated a test I totally didn't
have cheats under my skirt um right at
the line where the skirt ends no no way
no no way you
did let go what think should be national
food of America well she said hamburger
so I think pizza maybe pizza that's more
like a natur food of Italy but sure if
you want to steal
it name you don't like to see on your
spouse American Pizza is different
anyway what what do you guys think for
this like Kiss like lipstick or
something right because that be like
yeah else are should lipstick or or kiss
Mark or something like that okay
lipstick okay lipstick
okay major decision the whole family
should make together a
move especially if it's a really should
moving or move just move I
think there something you pick flowers
flowers again the flowers I feel like
parents would disagree with name
something some people cheat some people
cheat at games games games a a good one
that's ding ding ding ding maybe moving
would have been better that's all the
answers you can
give this is almost the same word let's
see top answers would be
preferred can we let the rage team win
for once or will this be another win for
the blue team
Burger we a couple
good next is the what you don't want to
see on your spouse's face here's what
you said yeah B their face I think we
might be their face yeah the whole
face
close hair hair
hair was the top
answer like beard okay maybe they were
like mostly men partip
in or maybe woman who didn't like facial
hair I'm not realizing vacation may not
be a major
decision for a second I would be wrong
you are right name something you pick
okay no versus uh
Powers come on
where good
good final thing was name something
people cheat at games and
test we can totally get no this is our
zomie won but still the total adds up
for the blue team again
this game doesn't Define us it's okay
I'm so mad
yeah we did a the will
the change anything we can still rage
they did it again
yeah well now what I'm thinking is we do
one more game but should we completely
mix the teams randomize them no blue no
pink just random random
team yes cuz at the moment it seems
surprisingly
one-sided no this is just bad
RNG no it it's all luck this game isck
oh how about we do Adent versus
sunai oh okay so that would be
wait there oh oh that could work wait
yeah there's four of you here this works
perfectly cuz if we win we're good and
if we lose we're just really
nice I'll the leader who wants to lead
the other
team but maybe one of the pr on cuz you
didn't uh I mean got to do it yet wait
why am I the
Le crony
CR you have like the the the hat for
it you do have a large beautiful hat I a
very beautiful I gave you that hat cuz I
fought you just sad stylish you an
umbrella yeah thank you you such
aitar all right this is the team you can
already see who are going to be facing
off against each other wait can I not be
last you don't want to be last okay no
problem um
who who is
this where where do you want to
be
uh I don't know do you want to do the
fast round
crony do you want to do the fast round
won't everybody ah the fat ah the f one
is only for the leader yeah oh do do you
want to do it if you want to do it only
if you don't want to do
it I'm okay
with I would like you to make a decision
because you are the leader
I would I would like it if you make the
decision because I care about you I'm
going to make decision give
it thank you so much okay she seems
really I really just don't like making
decisions so thank you okay that's fine
got you H and fire are going out where
are we going to go have food
so this is nissa's
family
cute like
[Music]
that let's go one more last round let's
see if the mix up teams will show us
very surprise result our bger and power
as the
young yeah they're
old damn right
what what is that
P I am Kwa and I'm in the mood for
[Music]
fi hopefully we got new questions nice
questions logical
questions these are the teams family are
look to home
the
basically and the
oh Senai let's go
Senai as a senpai myself I want the
Senpai team to win or else
wow
us I will sabotage you I might I might I
might you want the co High to you know
have an easy time you know they end up
winning no yeah well if like first like
it's just it's a win-win so we're going
to win because it's time for off time
for the first face off here
I my girl emo I will kill
you me friendly put down sword friend
please I dropped the
flannel remember I want your names to be
shouted out
survey we asked 100 people 100 people
were name something people get on and
off
ofaa yes that seems
like something everybody would think
of nice top answer maybe she's laughing
you already know this one
I don't even know what I'm doing
honestly it's okay like how could you
ignore that um we're going to play it
sorry
family
the maybe she doesn't remember
everything there plane or train or
roller coaster oh uh a
bus I
instead a
taxi oh okay another
bus she's
sleeping it's
[Laughter]
okay she's trying to not use her
existing knowledge
okay go
a horse a
horse thank you for saying it a horse
you got
it okay did M suggest that one that
horse no oh there it
is
damn I mean I'm not suggesting anything
what about a camel even though I really
want I said it so many times yeah
I do be getting on and off planes a lot
oh airplane yeah did the Boomers who
made this game get on and off the plan
ride plane this
is it is a relatively new version of the
game it came out I think
[Music]
shocking people are scared of
airplanes
apparently but more people die in car
crash bike bike
bike saving the
team else am I supposed to
say all things that
move
okayy do you remember one at
all uh train I'm going to need a GU from
you train okay that that sounds like a
good good answer
this is not now a game not of guessing
but of memory train or
train train train train train I was
going to say bike but then she took it
so I was like oh
no oh no
train train is yes it's
there we just need one more
girl I I beg you to look down at your
the ground deep with in
my heart what happens when you look down
and you're standing what do you
see my
heart I say feet
feet let's go oh M you kept that one
for I was just
wonderings you calculated what why feed
why is there not an elevator what that's
actual answer the she's played this one
before
up your feet I just like when G does the
the the meme you
know you knew that was the answer which
is why you suggested it no I just like I
like I like the memes sure M play
sure it
now well hopefully there will not be
many any more
repats see for another face face off
number two
and crony we both you got this
CR
it I my
FL okay I need your Nam to be shouted
out get
ready the the question is 100 people um
name a word instead use inste of friend
that was she was very fast that was fast
buddy buddy good one good one good one
oh there's so many good answer
budy look right is it the top answer
though probably cuz that guy wrote
ited I agree this isn't fair you're
going to play around you want to beat
him up
let's go I would love to beat them
up hold your arms so that you can
punch
your uh what do you think dud
maybe help help help help help help is
an insult okay is
it is
it
dude's dude are you sure yes I don't I
guess it is
offici but
nowadays people say all the time yeah
it's
rude H what we said buddy pal uh
brother brother brother oops brother are
you sure brother or sister the BR the
BR that's what
what's up bro surve says I don't think
isn't this done by old people I don't
think we forgot have
brothers I
mean nesa you can do
ITA we believe in you amig where other F
together bestie bestie no that's that's
that's that's too young Amigo it's not
even English Amigo but okay it's
that wow lucky one it's up to you
now oh yeah Spanish is the language of
Canada uh then um Canada is the the
French French language
right I'm me I'm me I'm me what AM me in
French is friends how do you spell
seriously a m i right like amig it's not
there what um um
um no
time
me I can't believe you still bring up
this one particular one that I think of
we will mate m
m there are many kinds of
mates that's good A friend is also a
mate hey
[Applause]
mate
M oh God you guys do you guys have
friends what do you you guys
you are friends each other's friends
what do you call each other a
hie say
anything no why get that wait we can
collaborate you
guys go um let's see a friend
buddy not fella um oh there buddy pal
let me go
hey
there
homie
myosi bro I already did bro yeah
yeah dude okay you want to go for
it to have at
least I can't Ty so fast fast fast show
dude dude Wow Let's go if it's dude I
told you
by is not rude it's not but it's okay
there's so many answers it have to be
one of
them don't say that word okay it's rude
are you serious it's not rude in
America in the Northwest Passage it
is okay I'll remember that if I ever go
to the Northwest Passage could it be
could it be
comade
acquaint how you doing acquaintance
homie
asso let me introduce to my
associates stupid an acquaintance and a
friend is very very
friend yeah is not a friend like our
answers everybody's answers were was
more like how you would actually like
call someone in a conversation but the
others these were more stiff like when
you talk indirectly about someone no I
could look at kby like yo that's my dude
right
there no I think like the way we were
thinking was just very different from
them
sadly hi Grandma Grandma hell hello
great
hello it's the small people small girls
against each other to the LEL with
double points double double
points Focus if cats backpack
back my heart was
that I heard gura louder I guess I I
heard gura too actually wait what what I
heard people I heard me first I heard me
as well I heard me first
wow wait guys what do we think I didn't
think of an answer I was just right cats
love treats I don't know treat or
catnip May C also think
orat wait we had this one too you had
it promise is not allowed to give their
answers to
it was for dogs it was dogs it was dogs
no okay okay it was dogs wow dog wearing
backpacks it was dogs wearing backpack
why help help catnip catnip catnip does
that count as food no Okay C cat cat cat
cat
L surve I think they would just pee
wherever they want if they could decide
it oh there it is
she we're playing we're playing play
play play play play play play play okay
all are cat lovers we got this yeah
they're
motivated toys toys yeah toys toys is
good
okay
toys like a nice cat oh wait should it
be more specific like yarn or it was F
but it said food right so okay
yeah yarn would be cute
[Applause]
though hey what else could they bring
I'm I'm a cat lover but this isn't
realistic so I just you have to think if
you're going camping what would you take
with you now then you think of yourself
as a cat guys what do you think litter
or kittens K oh I think litter I think
litter I think
L okay let's try litter yeah uh L ah
litter well I hope it's also of cat
litter together we sure about that well
it's too late even if you change your
mind oh
yes one more just one
more
stupid car litter I have an idea but I
will not chair how do you put milk in a
backpack I me that's what I meant it's
not milk
I think it's going to be like my heart
or something it has to be
somethingit's
go 10 seconds 10 seconds I would
say
whatow because M wasn't there I put in
Mouse quickly don't worry don't worry
this sabotage no no I was saging you but
I think it's milk honestly yeah let's
see I mean a stri I want to say milk for
the meme it's not good for a tummy but
they do like to drink it man I love
milk what milk milk yes why is it a meme
I think it's legit a good answer that
people would think of man I love koseki
it's a b me
answer I
[Music]
I understand now
what cat lover Mo you got this oh gosh
this is pressure think like a cat you
have cat ear CL cats have tails yeah
they have ears
yeah they do
heart my heart my heart what no wait no
don't do it don't do it love love love
that's not wait in a backpack wait no no
why are foral throwing
that's I'm going to put it in cuz you
deserve it but it's
[Applause]
it's for being
so what could they have in there okay
kittens M what
what it was the tummy kittens M you
think Kitt good
idea we leave the kittens at home yeah
kittens but she okay G really wants
kittens okay Kitt K I mean it would be a
faster way than carrying one by one in
their mouth so normally they carry them
what else could be cat name let's see if
yeah yeah
would be good
for no way I'm sorry coming close D you
I underestimated
you I'm never making extra suggestions
again for my team that they don't
take no more kittens left because they
would be ours now stolen for real
if the Senai win it just means that they
think older than us
true
us
older you got to Revenge that
statement avenge avenge you can do it
okay you better you better do
it you better make sure your answers
count yeah it's important we asked 100
people thist dominance name a food that
name of food that people hate when
it's oh I'm
sorry so
slow fries oh yeah that's a good one
right that
is
fries we oh man what the Sur you still
get this on yeah
maybe no
to I believe in
you uh is it what do you guys think
about cereal right everybody hates soy
cereal I was thinking cereal cereal not
everyone hates when it's
soggy good it depends on the cereal I
would say I feel like a family member
family member who would let the cereal
sit
[Applause]
so is the The Higher One flakes you
never
see let's play right guys let's do it oh
gosh soggy food okay that's a yes right
yeah
y let's the rest of don't worry Advent
you could still steal it if they don't
get all of them so you know we couldn't
do it we couldn't steal it you can't
give up on us have hope don't give up I
think I've given
up or do you think bread or do you think
something better when does bread get
soggy sandwich Sanda fish okay so bread
May I'll say bread let's get it over
with it could be there yeah maybe not
the top one but one of them where's your
skin
color back I'm so good at this oh my
gosh
you got anything for us damn nice dear
CR
um chips chips oh do they get soy I
guess if you spill water over them or if
you leave or if you keep the they get
STP they get soggy or stale should I do
crisps no but chips chips oh
um w
if this game is British but why is
Carrot
chips sounds good oh wait true
no that's weird maybe it was Chris but
isn't that the British way of saying it
it's British
crisis
Cris yes what can get
soggy Pizza P yeah pizza pizza pizza
gets soggy I say sag
Pizza Spell correctly
please it was a one time only
thing I'm on your side goba
understandable the RH Islands that's
understandable name of food that people
hate when
it's uh did they want you to say like
potato chip maybe maybe we can try it if
it's oh
it's up the but why do they get soggy
I'm sorry I don't understand I feel like
if it was potato chips it would have
taken chips usually okay okay quick um
shoot what do you guys
think um I guess we'll try it anyways
potato chip potato chip we don't have
anything else chip right there it's
right there
yeah I think I think there's a chance
whatever come
on yes
it was worth trying worth trying we got
one more one more fill the board or or
are they going to steal it oh wait it's
me oh god oh no oh no oh no oh no salad
is also disgusting all the lettu sogy
salad but this is
America
salad salad you want to do do you want
to do that's a Sal it does suck when it
gets too soggy
[Music]
yeah day you should even eat day salad I
love salad
Greenery oh my
God high five high five good answer
done get so I don't know about oh
no
pressure you can still get your score a
little bit higher but why you guys happy
your Senai are
winning aren you happy your
sen no no a no happiness wait we you
just we you just don't uh relate to this
Boomer energy
ask advice ask him Senpai
advice you guys should be more positive
they were pretty positive with their
heart exle
postivity okay let's you see us winning
oh sh hold on hold on hold on name
something that
develops what children your
brain children I was thinking of a
really it answer but name something a
husband ask his wife to carry in her
purse for
him wallet I'm so sorry I guess so cuz
they offer wait Pockets right well
wallet you had like a kangaroo wall name
something you
might the second children CH children or
child work with the first one too child
child yeah I normally it would be just
one cou po name St going good couch
potatoes um is chips wait no no no a
couch a couch remote control remote s
snacks REM TV TV a TV TV TV TV TV is
this fair I don't know if this is fair
TV yeah yeah animal with long ears
animal with long ears
elephant long those are just big
okay questioning
me the B is losing
it slamming her hand on the keyboard oh
why did I say
El
elephant don't any answers because if
you you can show us how much better
answers you have than everybody else Nam
develops film oh nice oh nice see my
first thought was always software but
okay name something a HB name something
a husband ask his wife to carry her
purse for him um what did what did they
say I forget don't worry about it I
don't remember uh then I guess um phone
okay oh that's good old people have
phones what about Maps use maps right
if you had a kangaroo name something you
might carry it
waby no
wallet purse don't listen to them don't
listen to
them's having a
purse remote rem remote yeah they're
stealing my answer no I got
[Music]
it I think they might be getting the top
answer is here that's
all oh my God okay you've done Nissa has
learned how to drown out noise of
Advent it's my
talent I guess it makes sense The Sound
Don't worry don't worry guys we got this
don't
worrying out the sounds noise name
develops did we get top answer at all
children or
[Music]
fil coming
back well we can still wi s of if you're
not B how do you know what film is uh
I'm like
10,000 oh this one goes
the okay next one was the kangaroo
question you might carry mine mine makes
sense you answered
yes babies just a baby
but yeah
yeah you're asking a human you have to
think more humanlike not kangaroo like
name something it already carries a baby
it already carries like this is how you
answer those answers look yeah Co potato
question
a big answer W I need to talk to this
guy without anyone
looking without any Witnesses I need to
talk to this guy definitely not elephant
I mean he probably got some
points many points for that did we win
we win no he didn't but it's still
pretty awesome of a comeback
damn I'm just being nice we
win multiply by 10 back there we can't
we can't
C my game
[Music]
crashed sorry what is this okay I really
nice and I wanted all of you to win so I
hope that you guys have a more positive
I hope that this teaches you a lesson
about positivity stay positive
and will come your way I'll winth isn't
adding up and totally let us
win the f I got the fastest answer I got
the most on
board
cheating I have no regrets damn
another fastest
Sink s
wow the real winner is
M the fast is at the slowest oh my God
what a title to
[Music]
claim
damn
I I cannot get over that fastest and
slowest [\h__\h] there's something cracking
in my boob cuz I'm
laughing don't you have muscle yeah
something in there I'm get me thank you
wow be super nice if you could keep
stuff in there I'm sorry I can't I can't
believe they they turn it
[Music]
around the I think it's a bug yeah no
what no I think it's because they get
Triple they get like triple or
quadruple like at the end he says that
they yeah it's um multiplied by what was
it 10,000 or th000 or 100 like a big
number I thought that was a joke oh it's
times 10 oh so the fast round is times
10 oh so that's basically if you do win
you win you win the game yeah I have I
have another lesson from for the kohai
nothing
matters that life is
pointless what happened to the
positivity this is NE this is not
positive or negative this is just what
it is it it is tless when when win the
whole game until the fast money round
and then whole point the fast money
round we can do whatever we want you
can't take you can't take the points or
the money you got from this G to death
so
yeah well my body has stopped
functioning and this is great because
we're ending anyway here yeah um I I
would just like to hear at the
end how how you feel uh now let's hear
more yeah I think from M we heard how
she
feels how do you feel after this
experience yeah it was pretty good I'm
not really too good at this type of game
but it was fun yeah got some good
answers I think so you were great yeah
you were a good um addition to your team
whichever team it was don't
worry I'm a smart GAA also I'm so sorry
about Rhode
Island it's fine I'll remember it's fine
don't worry about it I remember I am
personally offended though that people
are calling you
old so why baby what the hell I still
got this SP I'm I'm Jessie F 300
a.m. she's a spice spice can tuna it's I
didn't even know old people could live
like past 3:00 a.m. I know I don't know
how I'm still
here she is I got second wind at 2: a.m.
here we are but now
I'm yeah I'm ready I'm ready to go GG's
GG B how how did it feel to rage for
real today I feel like I've unlocked my
inner uh Rock sick Rock I think I had a
lot of good uh insults to the to the
Senpai today I feel I feel like I'm only
insult was prob old that's only bad
that's a bad insult though so I will
take it I will take it yeah you need to
learn more insults oh okay you'll be old
too
people Advent one day okay well uh I'll
ask uh M first how how did it feel
today against sister I helped so much
and I really carried the team and I got
so many answers right did you guys think
love did she yes I don't know did she
that
was the last game just didn't have it
game's broken the game is broken we all
know that I had the answers it didn't
have him I I don't think that any of you
two really uh particularly asserted
dominance over one one of each
other
I yeah I think your memory is broken no
no so f are you seem quite happy with
your performance today yeah I thought
you know I didn't have much confidence
um but after this I feel like maybe I am
smart maybe maybe did you die this
before you doubted it I don't know I I I
didn't know if I was smart enough like
my
Senpai but it shows the maybe they're a
little bit silly you know maybe that
their brains have gotten a little bit
older so I take back what I
said we may be growing older but we're
also growing Bolder so better be nice to
us respected
[Music]
mhm okay M we we're just getting do use
any more words of wisdom to share with
us no no oh oh wait you Baler thanks
Chad you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] I'm not listening to you anymore
you had to work on my insults there you
go you st cat can't even come up with
your own huh uh-huh so true oh yeah
leave people alone
you you have to look at chat
oh Wen you looking at chat earlier no I
was making fun of them oh we're kind of
forced to look at them right now yes oh
Nissa uh I think you you you're very
very pleased by uh your team's
performance and all that right yeah I
mean to be honest uh I don't like like
um games like this because I actually
can get kind of
um I'm bad but but more than anything uh
I'm just happy that I got to play with a
some Senai I hadn't got to hang out with
before so thank you guys so much for
having
me I think you absolutely you're the
reason why your team won in the end so
let's go there is
a excuse me excuse me it's true it's
true did you see what happened were you
watching okay last but not least we have
crony who's maybe falling asleep by
now oh no I'm good I'm just kind of
tired but uh thank you so much for
having me thank you for coming yeah it
was uh it was
definitely a new experience with
everyone a new yeah very new you didn't
just played recently oh yeah no of
course not but you know it's different
with new people and yeah it's not really
um Family Feud really isn't my thing but
I did my best and yeah I think that's
what even though it's not your thing
thank you for signing up for it D that's
sweet of you I'm glad you
guys number one most of all you all are
number one in my
heart that's a fura Moko kind of thing
to say but um
[Music]
to though so sweet if we had fun then we
all won yes oh yeah the magic of
friendship and stuff like that
wo now I will I will now go and shavee
off my hairy hairy caterpillars on my
face so thank you so much thank you for
hosting
by problem I was like for to this like
since I signed up for the perms yeah so
I'm glad thank you for being part of it
I I'm sorry some awkward timing also I
thought this would be a good time for na
but maybe it
wasn't but yeah now it's great I feel
full of
energy this is what
you're okay then I wish you all a lovely
night um Halloween is still upcoming so
everybody has like exciting streams
upcoming look forward to all of that
I'll be playing chicken feet later today
let's go and in German we say Al in
right
girls happy Halloween happy Halloween
happy halloweeen byebye hallowe
[Music]