[Music]
hello
sorry for the delay i was waiting for
kelly's music video
uh let me put on some pgmo
btm hmm
we need i think we need a bunch of
different tracks today because it's
gonna
be a long
stream
hello
isn't this cute
[Music]
hello everybody
thank you
thank you thank you
um
today we'll look back a little bit on
the
performance i did at the um birdfest
link you wish concert
and
[Music]
uh read a [\h__\h] ton of super chats
i have to go for them
um and i'll do it together with you guys
you were so hot in day two
thank you
congrats on your 3dw i will not call it
a 3d debut
many of you probably call it a 3dw but i
don't call it a 3dw maybe a 3d sneak
peek
um performance
because i want to do a proper 3d w
well sorry for you guys
when it becomes possible
i know
[Music]
it was a prequel
also a word for it perhaps yes
you were on fire
yes yes yes everything was on fire i set
everything on fire
yes
you freaking nailed the other day how
good that did that feel ah
it felt good but yeah uh i already
talked a little bit about it on my
members only stream yesterday
uh
so there will be some
repetitive remarks on my side probably
if you watched my member stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know if we should just i don't
know start uh
talking about it right away or first
read some super chats because i got so
many and if i if i start talking
it will take me like two hours to
actually start reading super chats did
you hear the meow yes there was a meow
in the distance
my cats my kitty cats
[Music]
dance i i i
[Laughter]
i am
sleeping over it uh one night um
makes me feel today it feels like
that didn't i don't know it almost feels
like it was a dream it didn't didn't
happen
uh
i hope we can
repeat something like that um as soon as
possible
um
i'll i'll i'll say some things now and i
might say some things later
but um
for me i i currently in order to do
something like that again i need to go
to
a studio and it's not as i said before
it's not just walking in there saying
hello and then and then doing 3d bam
it's a bit more complicated like that
and quite quite a bit more complicated
um so preparation is necessary for
whenever i want to do something like
that because i just don't have the
necessary equipment close by or at home
yet but
um
i slash we are working on getting that
done and making that happen
um
so that even even when i can't go to
japan uh like whole life japan to make
use of
the studio and all that so that i can
still
um
yeah do stuff like that
somehow
in a similar
quality hopefully uh from home yes
uh without going to a far away studio
within europe as well
uh cause like that's that's possible um
but as i said it takes lots of
preparation and it's just not that easy
just wanted to
let you guys know that i'm working on it
but i probably won't be able to provide
any
3d content anytime
soon
which i'm
sad about as well but i also want to
keep the proper order that i always was
so
excited for and um looking up
to
the prep order i mean you know having a
proper 3d w and then doing all the kind
of stuff that comes with that
um
yeah i don't want to like put out like
like little itsy bitsy's of content here
and there
without doing that first and that's
maybe that's maybe
maybe that's not necessary thinking like
that but that's just how i think because
i i
all this time when i joined home alive i
i gave myself the goal of doing a 3dw
after watching so many of my senpai's as
a whole of life fan
um
doing the same thing like working hard
until the 3dw then having this magical
review where everyone uh
watches and is like wow she's pretty now
yeah yeah
and
yeah i want that too you know
[Music]
and ideally of course it would have
happened before the concert but things
just didn't line up that way and
um
that has to be something
that we accept
um
[Music]
we're trying to make it work from home
at the moment like that that sooner or
later we can put out content like that
from home
um
[Music]
but
you know
originally we all just wanted and we
still kind of want to we still kind of
want to go to japan and make it happen
there but but we're kind of i guess
trying to do
uh both and see what happens first
[Laughter]
if japan suddenly says okay
you can come now for real then that will
happen first but if that still takes
like another 10 [\h__\h] months or so
then within that time we will do our
best to
um
have a similar quality
of debut
from either home or a close
or far right somewhat far studio
working on both at the same time
so
um as much as i would like to show
more of my 3d to you guys now i have
this
i'm i'm torn apart you know i
i want to do a 3d music video too but i
don't want to do it before my 3dw and i
want to put out 3d
i don't know streams or whatever i don't
know i want to do all that but i don't
want to do it before my free nephew
it's just good
it is a really difficult
situation
um
yeah
yeah that's my way of thinking
because if i put out stuff like that
then the 3dw won't be special anymore
you know
i want it to be something special that
that i've always waited for and and
always dreamt of
always planned for been planning for it
for ages
yeah so
please wait um there are screenshots out
there of my 3d
so you can take a look at that or watch
the concert if you if you're eager to
watch it it was an awesome performance
so
it's worth watching
it if you really want to watch my 3d
um but besides that i guess for a while
longer we'll have to act as if
i don't have a fridge
um
incredible performance thank you
starting performance thank you
thank you thank you well yeah i still
have my like the vr chat opportunities
but i also don't want to use my 3d model
for a debut in a vr chat stream
i think you guys can understand why
because that's just not the quality that
i'm hoping for
i
i want it to be perfect yes
you know it's like a like i don't know
like a wedding want your wedding to be
perfect don't want to have like i don't
know
a half-assed wedding do you um
yeah
rent a studio i already said
it's not like something i can do like
tomorrow it's
it needs more preparation time it needs
to be like you know all kinds of i can't
talk about it uh
just because
it and i don't know how much details i'm
even allowed to say
uh about what uh
is necessary what steps are necessary to
be taken in order to do such things so i
prefer to be careful and not get bunked
by genma
but don't worry i have
both things on the radar i have doing it
from home
when the necessary equipment arrives
uh on my radar and i have doing it uh
going to a studio
on a radar too just not the japan studio
but yeah i mean i have that on the radar
too but i just
i kind of gave up on that thought
i have a feeling that you know it won't
happen in japan
if it will you know i'll be excited to
have a 3dw
properly in the japan studio
um but at this point i've waited so long
for it
and waited and waited and waited and
waited and waited
kept on
waiting for those delays
and then the news saying oh japan is
opening its borders oh not really
psych
wait it's so long for that yeah so i
wanna i'm just i just
i wanna have three different plans at
the same time so that whichever happens
first we can just do it as asap
so that's what's
happening
[Music]
well i can see them in 3d
they aren't pretty on my side
yeah my supertest is able because you
know exactly why because i have to read
like a million
brilliant trillion
chats first
[Laughter]
well yeah what else what did i want to
say i wanted to say
i wanted to say oh yeah i said this
before but uh on my member stream
but
i i performed hinotori my first
uh let me put up a screenshot
my first
first
uh original
song
that i put out
wait which screenshot do i put up
here
[Music]
in chihuahua in 3d in
not the best quality
waiting for some high definition
versions
um special i'll put up one more
[Music]
yellow pixels
pixels
[Music]
everything was on fire
it was a huge stage
a huge audience
you saw some screenshots on my twitter
perhaps yes i'm waiting for the blu-ray
there's gonna be a blu-ray released uh
sooner or later and
uh
we all need to get that because you know
did you see those pixels did you just
see those pixels
we need to watch it in hd
the bitrate destroyer
mode
yeah um so i said i chose hinotorii
because first of all there there are i
think three reasons
three reasons why i chose hinotonii
number one is my debut song so it's
special to me and
because i'm saying this because i think
some people um expected me to perform
sparks because my most recent one and
because it was fairly successful
probably the most successful out of my
free singles
um
and it's english and i represent whole
live english but here comes reason
number two
um
this is a japanese venue in japan with
mostly japanese people watching in the
real life audience
and because of that i wanted to perform
something in japanese um
yeah
and
yeah then the third reason
was
um
right there might be four reasons third
reason was i already had a choreo for
hinototi like ages ago uh
way way way way before i even
had a 3d debut in sight which i still
don't seem to have but
yeah a long time ago i had a
choreography specifically commissioned
privately um because i want it to be
ready whenever it happens whenever i can
perform it
and i wanted it to have a specific
look and taste to it
so i wanted to commission someone
specific for it uh and someone where i
know what i'll get from it rather than
um leaving it to
kind of leaving it to the company um to
get a choreographer on their side to
make a choreography i wanted it to be my
thing um
yeah
so and the fourth reason
was
ah yeah because because as much
uh fun as sparks is as a song and heart
challenge as well i think um hirotori
has the right elements that i wanted um
for this performance um i wanted it to
be cool rather than cute so heart
challenger is out of the window there i
wanted to leave a cool impression and uh
i wanted um
you know
heart challenger and hinotori are um
written by
a japanese producer who um
japanese producer parents and
these kind of j-pop songs they tend to
have the same kind of like pattern and
beat and rhythm where you can easily
like uh especially i think for japanese
audience easily vibe to it
you know with those utah
um it's just something that is so so so
so common in japanese j-pop song
japanese pop songs uh and
anime
songs
um
that makes it so easy to vibe to and
therefore is so much more fun because
you can interact with the song even if
you hear it for the first time if you're
used to these kind of
um
songs then you will automatically
recognize the pattern and know where to
do what kind of chants or
um claps and all that
yeah
and i i went to
so many concerts in japan um
from hello project uh my favorite idol
agency which i don't follow as actively
anymore today but i was a huge fan back
then i went to so many concerts i went
to uh first row second row third row and
all that um
he
spent a lot of money on tickets um and
merchandise and all that and and and and
i just [\h__\h] love
these kind of concerts because even as
like an awkward
person like me and
perhaps some of you guys who don't go to
the disco and go like
you know
[Laughter]
um
you know like i don't know about you
guys but i i just don't want to go to
normal like i don't know festivals and
concerts of like western
style artists or discos or whatever
parties because like i i don't know how
to
i don't know how to vibe to that kind of
music and even if i have it in my head
if i
um acted out with my body in reality it
just looks cringe and stupid and like a
five-year-old
i just don't have that kind of charisma
um
that the cool people do out there if you
know what i mean
but when it comes to idol songs and
j-pop songs it's so easy because i can
copy their choreography and then i can
do those chants
was my favorite idol um
it's just so much fun because you know
what to do and ah and you feel like
you're one with everyone in the audience
because they all do the same
it's an amazing feeling
it's just the best feeling ever in those
concerts man so i [\h__\h] love it
so that's kind of what i was hoping for
with my uh performance um i mean the
audience was not allowed because of
restrictions c c thing restrictions um
to cheer with their voices but i still
saw them jumping up and down in rhythm
and going like
this without saying
and um
it's so solid and and i felt it and i
mean it would have been even more insane
if they could have cheered with their
voice
but still i'll just
imagine the sounds yeah
um but they they looked really really
hyped and that's when i fought them yeah
it was a great choice
great choice to uh go with hinotori and
also they had a live band there which
meant hinotoni
in this concert venue
even more
impressive
yeah
yeah if you don't follow my twitter then
[Music]
uh you probably
and if you don't if you don't follow my
twitter if you didn't see the concert
then you probably don't realize but it's
a [\h__\h] huge venue all right [\h__\h]
huge menu it's makuhari mesa i've been
there for
various occasions
uh
but look at that oh this was during my
concert
yeah
yeah and this is still i would say half
the capacity of this venue because they
had to keep i think they still had to
keep
one seat open between
each person i saw it in some shots
that's crazy right it looks pretty damn
filled it looks like
like filled to the brim but if you look
in some uh audience shots you definitely
saw that there's like uh one seat in
between each person open
social distance
[Music]
because of that yeah they could have
sold even more tickets if it wasn't for
that man
yeah
but but
a few a few kfp uh fans japanese kfp
fans made it into the audience anyway a
few a very few others tried but failed
because it was a raffle
it was not like buying the ticket and
then uh like first come first serve no
it was a raffle
um so you had to be lucky which i think
i like this system uh
better than first come first serve cause
that's so stressful
and yeah
just when the sight is down even when
you're one of the first then you get
kicked out of it that just [\h__\h] sucks
doesn't it
yeah it's more fair this way i like this
way um
[Music]
yes yes yes some well-known japanese kfp
fans have been there
which i'm happy about that they made it
yeah
i'm having someone i'm happy that at
least one person out of all these people
made it because you gotta think about it
this is a venue in japan so obviously
most fans will be mostly like having
japanese members as their oshi
um i totally get that but considering
that
that i'm not even the aussie of let's
say 99
of the audience they still
jumped so hard and hyped so hard when i
was on stage and performing my song
and i'm so glad
my goal was to leave an impression um
yes
i i wrote this um
this is also why i wrote that message uh
did you see that message um
that's also why i wrote that in japan
japanese because it's a japanese
audience but i wanted to leave an
impression there um and i wrote that i
wrote i want to appeal
to the audience here there it is there
it is wait
i wrote the translation in my tweets
though attached to it but i wrote until
now i watched my senpai's on many
different concerts and supported them in
the audience this time i get to join
them on the same stage i will not let
this chance go to waste
i'll show off my full power um
but the last sentence was kind of hard
to translate because if i say it says
gel but i feel like even though it's an
english word it doesn't work that well
in english but i wanted to basically say
i want to leave an impression with the
people there and the people watching the
stream as well of course
and i think i think i did
but but
uh
kfp was shocked when i said this
yesterday
um
i
did honestly not
expect such a
positive
reaction
um
first of all i was worried about how you
guys would react to my 3d i mean
i don't know
you guys said it looked great maybe i
just looked at it for too long but i
don't know i don't know
it looks good um
but i felt like so something was off a
little bit looked a bit different but i
mean it's pretty good
and and then the other thing was i was
just really worried about um
performing when
you know everyone else is so great there
everyone else
has such a great performance
and
also following up on cali who is like
performs a [\h__\h] banger and and it's
just such an icon
everybody everybody knows callie
everybody knows kelly for her music and
and for being a freaking dope cool
person
um
so that put some pressure on me i i i
don't know i'm not very well known for
my music after all even though
um i i work hard on it as well um
yeah so
i was really nervous about it i don't
know i also um i have i have experience
with dancing and performing um in the
past so
um
i don't know i
i i wanted to do my best but i i felt
like um
really nervous about what you guys would
think about it
um
i was just i don't know word i mean you
gotta be nervous because it's the first
time performing in 3d
and and yeah showing it off to you guys
and
uh
yeah but
um immediately afterwards
i realized
i worried about nothing because it was
great
[Laughter]
um and
yeah you guys were um crazy
yeah and i left an impression
so much that my
legs
became a meme
[Music]
i made that kicking kick come true
we we coined that word a while ago
and who would have known that it comes
in handy
like
this [\h__\h] kick at a kick
yokata you got down
need a fighting game
yeah
a fighting game tekken kiana
is a new character in tekken
the chances are over for super smash
brothers invitations so i guess we gotta
go look somewhere else
let's go check in
here comes a new challenger
it's not really a cake doll
it's not it's not really a cake it's a
swoosh
but okay you guys can call it a cake i
guess there's a screenshot it looks like
a kick but if you see it in motion it's
not a cake
it's a swoosh
circle roundhouse oh yeah roundhouse
maybe it's a roundhouse what does a
roundhouse kick look like maybe it's a
roundhouse cake
i mean i wasn't i wasn't i was dancing
okay i wasn't trying to fight someone
but maybe maybe i was maybe i was
maybe i was
even fubuki senpai made memes out of it
that was funny oh it's funny yeah
um
so that was that was that and um
yeah
it was [\h__\h] amazing to see the crowd
cheer like that so much fun but it was
so short it was just four minutes and i
want
more i wanted that moment to last longer
so that motivated me definitely to
make something like this happen more
often and sooner rather than later
um
one thing i can say i will not
accept
a birthday
without 3d this year
i do not care what i need to do to make
it happen
it will happen and therefore the 3d
debut must happen
before that
so
yes that is my plan
have a 3d debut
or maybe a
couple i don't know however it's
possible however soon it's possible
and then a 3d birthday
live
on youtube for free of course
[Music]
there won't be an audience like that a
real audience that i can see and feel
cheering
yeah that's that's unfortunate but
because of that um
i also
am even more motivated to
work on an album and then
have a proper live concert in a proper
venue
um
maybe
maybe by the end of the year maybe
december or january if need be
yes i want to do a solo concert
but wanting a thing
is uh just the very very very very first
step
yeah
an album yeah i mean um i currently have
i've been talking about this for a long
time now i have a song in the works at
the moment it should come come out
somewhat soon
maybe within
the next
[Music]
one
for one and a half months i don't know
what maybe two months i don't know i'll
have to see
um
we will see
[Laughter]
and then i wanna release
maybe one more single
before i release an album
in wintertime
that's currently my vision but i cannot
guarantee anything
[Music]
i'll do my um i'll do my best
and now
yeah i'll have to work hard for it but
i'll do my best
[Music]
foreign
i mean i always had that um as one of
the things i wanted to do in the future
um
but now it's definitely
very high on my list of priorities
and of course
of course
eventually
whole live english only concert would be
[\h__\h] dope you know i want that you
know that whole what whole life japan
did with you know singing together on
stage
and then doing units and all that and
solos and all that i want that for us
and
we will we will
i think cali really wants i think we all
want it no there's no way that we no
someone doesn't want it in the whole
life english
yeah
oh let's let's make it happen let's make
it happen
[Music]
let's do it let's do it let's make it
happen
country roads
no
i do not want to perform that on stage
[Laughter]
no let's put out some more um exciting
originals until then shall we
all of these are just visions
from that that will happen in the far
far future all of these kind of things
or maybe will happen
all these things are just currently
wishes and dreams and
take a lot of work to
put into reality
but but i hope that this
um concert with whole life english
uh whole myth in it got you
motivated as well
and
makes you want to stay longer and
and look forward to what we're doing
[Music]
in the future yes
journey of a thousand years yes imagine
that's one that we we would have to
perform yes
and and now the halloween song
myth or treat
me if i treat doesn't matter if it's not
halloween doesn't matter i wasn't
leaving yet yeah i hope so we're not
leaving i hope so
you guys are
in for
cool things i think you need to witness
them
i think many of you are here since
the beginning or sometime in the
beginning and wouldn't it be amazing to
witness
how far
we
come how far we can go
um
collapsing with nana um well as as
announced previously we have
a song cover
in the works actually nancy just sent me
um the finished
product video
and song
uh
yesterday
and it was so good
i didn't tell you guys
yeah it's so lovely and
we're just waiting for it to be approved
by management
um and then it will go up on nancy's
channel and
yeah that's just a cover song but
i
me and then it's yesterday i showed up
in her in her stream
it's been 40 minutes okay let's talk
maximum 10 more minutes and then read
super chat i showed up yesterday in her
stream and
uh um because she also she also messaged
me after the concert she was like
you were amazing
and i was like yo yo yo thank you love
you let's do some [\h__\h] together we
talked about it in dms and then we
talked about it on stream as well but
um
i think that me and energy are
similar uh in some ways and
[Music]
i think when it comes to
how serious
uh
someone
takes the whole idol aspect
i think within whole live english we can
all say it's me
and we've been all alive japan
nenechi is 100
an idol
and i think together we could just do
really really cool things and and we're
both so motivated we want to perform and
dance and sing and and and we're both
orange so you know odenzu orenzo has to
become
something bigger um i always dreamed
about it man i always dreamed about it
being like on a concert like this
uh the link your wish concert and then
having
us being one of those units one of those
sub units
yeah
the greek key
so uh i want orenzu to maybe even become
like uh officially acknowledged by
cover slash hololive
maybe get their backing
and then do some stuff together
yeah i feel like ah
i feel i feel like we could do some
really cool stuff and and and
it might be difficult because i'm
overseas and she's in japan um
but i think you know we can never
overcome that and um
yeah
we can overcome that and and and and and
and
how do i say this
i think
because it's a combination of two
different branches
we can
[Music]
show
we can unite the two branches yeah
you know what i mean
unite the branches show off titty and
wholesomeness
[Music]
and strengthen the bonds
between the branches
[Laughter]
[Music]
orenzo
we already have a logo so i already did
some some groundwork i got us a we have
a logo okay we have a logo
and and we have a cover coming out
there is some groundwork there
[Laughter]
so let's uh you do
you saw the orange logo there's a
japanese and an english one
yeah so let's make more out of it
um
i of course also want to do some stuff
with horotodi or at least with uh subaru
and elena i feel like us us free us free
uh have a special bond as well
terry duckin yes but can we not call the
group turducken officially because
it just doesn't sound cute
[Laughter]
odenzu lorenz has a cute ring to it but
turd duncan is just food
i mean orange orange is our food too but
that sounds cute and i don't know turd
duncan is just not a cute unit named
there are so many possible names but i
feel like
as a unit name as a like real serious if
it's just a joke like one time
performance okay
but if it's like a
serious name
then
i don't know needs to be something cuter
huh
what
[Music]
i feel like
package delivery person tried to call me
can i try to wait
what is it
[Music]
there no
that's just too
basic
[Music]
maybe now
reply to my message
trinity
i know it's a great name
it's one of the names we came up with
uh back in the early days
three twenty two three
[Music]
trinity three people and it's 20 boobs
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
generic that could be everybody
well we'll think about it and see
and see what else can be done in the
future but yeah if
i er
if i have like a birthday stream or
whatever any kind of 3d stream i want i
want my friends to be there i want to
tony to be there i want nancy to be
there i want ian to be there
um
so
yeah looking forward to
the future um
yeah and one more thing i want to say is
um
my spats
my black shorts under the skirt are too
long management could you please shorten
them they are too long
even if i just stand there you can see
them they're too long that's my uh
official complaint
um they're too long you could have
shortened them at least like you know
one
width of a thumb
uh-huh
yeah they nerfed my crotch
[Music]
please
i for for ina for example
i don't really her spats didn't stand
out
at all to me
and she has like a really [\h__\h] short
dress as well i mean it's maybe even
shorter than mine
if you think about it it just doesn't
leave quite that impression but her legs
holy [\h__\h] ina's legs
[Music]
unfair show my legs too
i want to show my legs too
free mouth eyes
she didn't do any high kicks
oh yeah what would happen if she would
do a high kick
if she would try to do a high kick
[Laughter]
equal rights equal size
justice for the wise
[Laughter]
with the power of the ancient ones she
could do it
[Music]
um anyway okay um
need to read
super chats oh what the [\h__\h] that was
like i just noticed
that was uh hours ago that was a
different
yes definitely
i was supposed to receive a delivery
today and i was awake i'm telling you
that but
they didn't bring my [\h__\h] belt and
then just brought it somewhere else
don't you hate when that happens
when they don't even ring the bell
yakuza
[\h__\h] i have to read yakuza super chats
[Music]
only the end
ah
i cut it up somewhere
oh [\h__\h] yeah where i was supposed to
refresh ah
how will i know oh god will it even be
on the list
oh god okay let's let's uh start
scrolling um
let's see
ah youtube's gonna be so
youtube studio gonna be so heavy when i
go for it ah
it's gonna load endlessly
[Music]
ah
oh
i didn't i didn't read it
ah
i only read the rainbow a little
[\h__\h]
i'm never i'm definitely not getting
done today
i can tell you that oh
how do you use that
[Music]
looks complicated
wait where to go
this one
no that's my stream how do i get to
here maybe
okay i got it cool
uh and which order is this ah i think
it's from top to bottom
[Music]
okay
yeah so from here on out i'll be doing
super chats readings
probably gonna take me about a year to
finish them
yeah probably won't finish them
but we gotta get started somewhere holy
[\h__\h]
so we start
at
the yakuza stream
i'll just put it here okay uh
screen is really busy but i want to keep
up the
wait let's put this here and this here
i wanna keep those screenshots up there
okay
okay what a mess my screen is such a
mess right now oh [\h__\h] what did that
just move
[Music]
why should i put it here
this is this
if you come into the stream do you know
where to look how about here or here
maybe here here
i'll put it here
pretty kiwah was so cool thank you
thank you thank you thank you i'm really
really really really happy for all the
uh um positive feedback i i really
didn't expect it thank you guys for
spring so sweet
man
thank you
okay let's get started
mr casper's duncan have
the rainbow i've already read so
let's not go for that again uh
cartoon thank you for the
red super chat
kick was amazing thank you you deserve
the prince thank you
you're so sweet
[Music]
and my wonders is super talented why are
you writing in german again in dynam
homemade vr biscuits from spitzen
cluster and that's the water ultra nerf
beast
guy with us
with poor equipment
i don't want to read german
[Laughter]
[Music]
chat i acknowledge your super chat
stop writing in german
makes me embarrassed
to read it out loud
ah
yeah well you did see my full power
level full power
unleashed you just see it didn't you
so
you're welcome
duncan
why why because it's embarrassing
i feel awkward
talking german in the middle of speaking
english
at least at the moment sometimes i do it
but right now i don't i don't wanna
[Music]
i refuse
like my german
thank you
[Music]
i think that adds up to
wait 20 40
17.
it doesn't add up to all right no no it
doesn't it doesn't but it's like a pinky
thank you trevor team
yeah
how low again i'm a bit of a turd owl
but i have to say seeing myth together
never fails to bring a smile to my face
they're talking about the vr stream by
the way
it's already failed like ages ago
and no matter how much of my soul has
been destroyed by work oh man what
why is your work so destroying
why you need to get a job that makes you
feel happy
my mom's still ignoring me by the way
sorry i was looking at my phone one more
second yeah i'm not looking at my phone
anymore um
uh where was that
i love dance instructing uh kiwama and
her dorky students
seeing you girls bond and feel like
you're in the same room together having
fun revitalizes me so thank you for the
fantastic collab oh and when you said
before that long distance here okay with
the other girls maybe possible i
remembered an idea and was curious what
you might think about it have you ever
thought about doing a cutout okay
roulette
randomize a list of songs like cool
originals and take turns singing oh that
sounds fun
[Music]
yes
good idea
hmm
maybe maybe uh uh mix in some songs you
know that someone maybe doesn't even
know that well like you know some
uh
cali rap songs
and then have them try their best
struggling
okay
i like that idea
um
[Music]
let me throw that
into our group chat
idea
uh
vr chat karaoke
roulette
uh
um have
a bunch of songs from home
[Music]
randomly
and have
one or two of us sing
okay
keep on going
[Music]
okay
disappearance of hats
isn't that the one that goes like
[Music]
i uh
already watched the video thank you once
again thank you
uh
[Music]
korean
chat i'm looking forward to food fest
starting tomorrow i'm glad to see your
first performance i'm happy that one of
your dreams has come true and i'll be
rooting for you with
rooting for you with you in that happy
moment
thank you
yes by now it's already over did you
enjoy it did you enjoy did you have fun
are you here right now i wonder
are you here
thank you for supporting us and thank
you for watching day one together with
me i think you were probably watching it
together as you said here um
yeah yeah it was a great concert wasn't
it i wonder if you saw the previous
concerts that whole life did but they
improved so much i think
um it was so
so so dope
yeah
lots of great performances lots of great
songs
really great visuals
[Music]
this was my first concert oh
you should watch the old ones too if you
if you're into some of the
maybe in japanese girls then um you
should watch the old ones too
and violet evergarden
[Music]
right did you change your profile
picture again why is it why is it torah
now
it's fine i've never got him right
i'm reading this correctly right
what it
is
[Music]
yeah it is
change your profile picture again
um
[Music]
written in japanese oh i can write that
asa
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
are you here too
are you here
maybe not
why not
attendance check
write it down
they're not here during their shift
check the toilets maybe
[Music]
he will regret it for the rest of his
life
[Music]
big rig ready spaghetti
i always check if you guys are here in
the chat usually often you guys are here
when i read your super chat which is
really impressive because like i read it
for hours and hours and then weird times
and you guys are still here
which really just means that the people
who send super jets are addicted to me
and love me i love you too
press everett thank you yeah
miniature pincher
come sign it up for the rainbow what's
rainbow in korean
to the white
rainbow
oh
lame boo uh-huh huh really that's you
don't have a
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ah there's a proper word but papaku
translated rainbow to rainbow
[Music]
moon it's d-day
which i think means it's the day of the
concert
[Music]
rainbow
thank you so much i've seen you around a
lot recently thank you thank you thank
you also cute dog
not really my type of dog
but cute anyway
cats are better though i hope you know
that
[Laughter]
thank you so much for the beautiful
rainbow not much text with it why why
why why just wanted to show me a
beautiful rainbow i guess thank you
thank you
[Music]
it's okay to be wrong
guards get him
he's saying that your attention is wrong
oh oh oh your attention is never wrong
no no attention always in the ride
[Music]
cats are the best although although
although although i will give you that
uh there are cute dogs out there and i
do want to get a dog one day
in addition to my cats so it's not like
dogs are bad
dogs are good
good very good dogs are gods because if
you turn dog around then it's good
and cats and
are
even better gods
mapping ate thanksgiving for the pinky
tomorrow we finally get to see in 3d i
wonder how different you look congratula
i can't wait to see it
[Music]
it's not it wasn't tomorrow though it
was the day after tomorrow right comment
center i can't wait to see it and i'll
still wait for oren's 3d live one day
yes yes
i
i yesterday i really felt that energy
really really um was passionate about it
too so
i'm so happy i'm so happy that she was
really really really wants to do it we
both said we'll pressure our managers um
here i don't know if manager stand is
watching denmark you're watching
pressure
i'm just
i wrote her the japanese kanji for
pressure
to put some pressure on her
but honestly
actually i feel sorry genma has been so
[\h__\h] busy i think and hasn't had a
time to breathe in the past
millions of months
i i want to take back the pressure
lightning lighter danger
thank you for the pinky
oh chunker is sleeping
yes that's it said that chocolate is so
cute man
okay it's my baby thank you tai tea
thank you and sarah
i think we're almost done roma there
thank you for the red super chat finally
back had some problems with credit debit
card and couldn't use for a month i feel
like i read this already just got a new
one and the first thing in my to-do list
was renewing my membership yay with my
favorite phoenix love you and i'll keep
supporting you as always thank you then
you renewed your membership just in time
for
uh my members stream yesterday
welcome back
thank you
thank you for not forgetting about me oh
you put on your uniform again noise
good that you get back to your original
status as a member if you uh
pause it
[Music]
gotta flex that uniform after all um
thank you roman
jim tracy duncan conduction mr big
duncan duck joseph duncan
jacob 47
i'm investigating the disappearance of
the rogue takadashi known as squiggly
mustache
last scene on your stream with you
saying i shall have your head care to
elaborate or this is a declaration of
war for hurting an innocent takodachi
takodachi investigator
you think you can
fool me
i see you wearing glasses let me take
them off
oh
it's you squiggly mustache it's you i
thought i took your head i took off his
glasses and i see who you truly are and
you're asking about the missing squiggly
monsters it's you it's you take him
guards take him and send him back to
where he came from
right this way write this no don't be so
kind don't be so kind to them
no you know what don't put oh
[Music]
he's there see he's there
he's a squiggly mustache just typed in
the chat huh
well then
well well then
maybe the takodachi investigators just
see a twin
um
but in the end
he's there so um
i don't think
any measures need to be taken
you're happy now
thomas the gintama guy duncan skye thank
you so much
[Music]
one second i need to get my hyper chat
out because youtube chat is just being
useless again
[Music]
need to chat says oh i see that you got
a new uh weapon today it's really
intimidating especially the plushy bits
ah my
my handcuffs yeah yeah but then i missed
so much story and i will need to catch
up but finally it's weekend now so i
will have time and i'm so excited for
the fest ah yay
thank you thank you yes yes i hope you
were able to catch up just in case you
didn't yet tomorrow is a day off i
forgot to make the schedule before the
stream sorry i'm really going to make it
after the stream but tomorrow is my day
off just so you know
[Music]
um
how's it going it's going okay so far
not very far with super chats as you see
i'm here
[Music]
but we'll get there we'll get there
so yeah
thank you
more yakuza soon so make sure you're uh
caught up um
elemental colors duncan
yeah people mentioned to me there is a
bowling mini game that i
need to do
i'll keep it in mind maybe next episode
because we didn't do um any side quests
or not many side quests so far so maybe
next episode could be a mini game and
side quest
stream
but we would be
ah that's good we would be we would be
um
majima next time it's majima time and
people
told me that at the point where i am
there's going to be like a like a majima
mini game or so like a way of money
making introduced that i will really
like apparently
yeah
so if i really really like it i guess
we'll get busy with that as
well everyone for bowling only for
kirito ah okay and we'll have to wait
with that
um
guess we'll have to wait but majima has
something fun to offer as well
apparently
[Music]
your name is no no it says i want to go
home no no no no no no no outrun the
wind danish and seth please thank you
for the pinky glad to see you're doing
all right i turned 20 today my wish for
my birthday is to give you good luck
love you thank you it's so sweet of you
already a couple days ago about 20 the
20th birthday huh
special birthday i hope you celebrated
it because that's a special
one how do you feel huh
how are you feeling about it
you feel old yet
because you're not
you're not
but make the best out of your twenties
people say
the 20s are
the time
to
live life to the fullest
don't um
i think i think you should not waste too
much time
on a job you don't like
uh
spend more time
finding a job you love
and enjoying life with traveling if you
can and
and yeah having fun just have [\h__\h]
fun
[Music]
i say this as if i'm like 50 or
something
i am eternal phoenix
joseph duncan reverend three five seven
donkeys
and dog
oh my god we cleared one
and now
now i feel a little bit less pressured
now we're gonna read the super chat
scram oh no not this one
uh wrong thumbnail this one
yay day one watch long
so happy so many of you tuned in i think
it might be because it was a very
special concert with en an id appearing
by the way i have a donut here
i ordered a donut
and i'm so excited to eat it i'm getting
hungry already because i only had um
some fruit for breakfast so can i snack
on my donut now that we have one stream
done
oh it's by the way they had a lot of
crazy donuts but i just went for a
simple sugar glazed donut
isn't that awesome as well
donuts donuts donuts donuts donuts
let me try it
oh
oh my
[Music]
really chad really
you're trying so hard chad
and you
[Music]
that's a donut in japan
the donut
chain
uh mr donuts
they have this simple donut that's also
basically kind of just like a sugar
glazed
donut
but um
it's like oh it's so muchy mochi
it's so mochi mochi
such a good mochi mulchiness
no i don't have mr donors here
but i want to go to mr donuts again
[Music]
while i'm eating i have a question for
you guys
[Music]
um
within jackpots party games is there any
any game that you think would be easy to
play for a japanese person if if one
were to explain the rules to them
beforehand
in japanese but just like throughout the
game once you're in you don't really
need to know english
the fighting game probably right
[Music]
the dragon fighting one
drawful
uh hulu x played jackpots games before
really
[Music]
hmm
drawful has english prompts oh
and that's difficult
oh
they did
which one did they play
[Music]
tico which one was that
which one did they play though
because they aren't they all english
only i thought there was no japanese
version of jack box party games
that's a t-shirt designing one uh-huh
okay
oh then i already know it huh
because um i was talking with coyotes
and by about
um
about the collab
and i suggested
um that we could play maybe one of the
jackpots party games senpai
i always say the senpai to them [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
yeah but i thought that maybe
because she wanted to somehow implement
english
she called it herself krusodzako english
into the stream and i was like okay
maybe we can do uh jackpots party games
then maybe one of the simple ones
um
[Music]
well even when i was writing to her i
first typed out coyote senpai and then i
deleted it and i wrote coyote
[Laughter]
canon
[Music]
what are you talking about
that's not true
it's not true
what are you talking about someone
at least i saw at least two comments
saying that piccolo played jackpots
party games i was like what no she
didn't
and then someone said oh of course she
did because she played it even with
bales how do you not know about it
you're talking about uh
the switch game
51 party games
yeah that was clubhouse games we're
talking about something else some people
are confused is that what you're
thinking of when you say whole explain
it wait
hollow x
uh
jackpot's party fan i really had to look
it up now like when the [\h__\h] did i miss
pick without playing jackpots party
games what
holo x
[Music]
are you sure home explain
jack's party games
[Laughter]
are you sure
when i look it up i find nothing
council played chat books party games
yeah what is it with these these fake
informations in my chat
i was legit like about to believe you
that x played jack box party games but i
was really wondering like how did they
like what
i don't remember anyone in whole life
japan playing jackpot's party games yet
because it's only english
maybe you thought i was talking about uh
clubhouse games huh
it was mix it up in your head maybe i'll
give i'll forgive you i'll i'll give you
that you could have mixed it up in your
head
confused everybody's just confused now
man
big confusion
no i was talking about jack box party
games which is not clubhouse games but i
like clubhouse games too it's just like
um it was so overused for collab uh
streams in the past
that i don't mind playing it again but i
feel like the audience wants to see
other things
anyway okay
now that we cleared that up
that we cleared that up yeah
[Music]
yeah
i was thinking about you know
teaching her how to play jackpots party
games
maybe i i'll look for them again and
try to find one that works uh even if
you like without english prompts because
like trying to translate those
when i don't even see them sometimes
would be difficult i think
[Music]
okay super chats from day one watch
along uh starting now
but let me switch the
music so that we don't get [\h__\h]
brainwashed today
what was this one
hmm it's not bad
[Music]
it's my calm cute story time audio stalk
track
okay emotion thank you for the pinky is
this where i buy my tick i get tackled
by the joke police for making the same
unfunny joke i make every concert for
all year
yeah i wonder if i'll see a lot of those
today again in the super chats
people trying to buy a ticket
in the super chats
[Music]
thank you though thank you motion this
is not where you buy the ticket
but least you bought kind of a ticket
for hearing my voice i guess
read out your name
by my voice
that's something that's one one good
thing
you it didn't go to waste it did it
for the pinky kiara even if i can't
watch it the concert evo day one or two
because of life stuff work time zones
and having to take care of my cat who
just had surgery oh no let it be known
that i'm really happy do your best i
know you will i'm so proud of you
are you planning on catching up on it
or did you already do it man i hope your
cat feels
better though
that breaks my heart man i had to
um when trump did i ever tell you the
story guys
about jonkers
when she was really really really really
itsy bitsy small
and she was a little wonkers
is that a
right word
because she was walking wonky because
she was so small
i did i'll tell you like i'll tell it
again yes
[Music]
um so when john chris was just a baby in
the first week after i got here
[Music]
she was really really baby
and actually not the first week but the
first night i brought her home
and
both chunkers and smoothie they were
really small and shy
and they were really scared i tried to
introduce them to my room only first
because i i heard that if you bring a um
baby cats home kittens home then you
should not show them not let them go for
the whole apartment uh right away you
should like um make them get used to
room bathroom can i speak english hello
and um
so i did that um
i was i was in a like a
roommate thingy like i i lived with
a roommate a different roommate than
afterwards and the roommate that you
guys know
but anyway so i had my room and i put
like the cat toilet and the food put it
all there and and and oh this is going
to take a long time until i get to the
point
[Music]
um but yeah so so so they were like
wobbling out of their um transportation
walks
and they were hiding
they they really were super extremely
shy i saw some kittens who get out of
the transportation box and immediately
are like zoom zoom zoom zoom
but mine were really really scared
i was i was so worried about them i it
was evening time i couldn't sleep
because i wanted to make sure that
they're okay and that they know where
the toilet is i want to show them uh so
that they don't pee like on the floor in
the middle of the night um but i i
couldn't get them because they were
hiding under like a table sort of thing
but yeah eventually it was just so late
and they would not come out so i just
had to sleep eventually and i was just
hoping for them to find the toilet it
was not far away from them
but yeah anyway
um
in the morning i wake up and i look at
the toilet
and i see they used it without me
telling them and without even using um
uh cat sand that was familiar to them
just random cats and they found it and
they peed in it successfully
my babies have always been so good like
they never pee somewhere where they're
not supposed to pee
except when they were paralyzed after um
taking the possibility from them to have
babies
um but anyway yeah so smart yeah that's
not the story though um
i woke up to
uh
what was it really the first time it was
definitely at least in the first week um
i woke up to
a loudly meowing
endlessly meowing chunkers
like without a break like she kept on
going and going and going like
wow wow
wow
but more
tiny meows because she was a kitten so
it was more like wow
literally 24 hours i swear at first i
wasn't sure which what she what was the
problem because she looked fine
visually and i gave her food i i i tried
to make her go to the toilet i i was
then worried that maybe she misses her
mommy
maybe maybe she was homesick i don't
know but um after 24 hours i was going
insane as well because she just really
would not stop meowing and she would not
be able to sleep either so i took her to
the emergency
um
vet
hospital and not just a small bed the
big one because the others were closed i
think it was probably a sunday or
something
so the normal vet clinics were closed
and i had to go to like an emergency one
which is already the first problem
because i was really broke back then and
i literally just spent
um the money on the kitty cats and then
now
emergency hospital
[\h__\h]
um yeah um
so i brought her there and i was i was
i was crying
you
i i was i was uh i was so
i was falling apart because
i i also had to go to work after that so
i was like really stressed out
and i was worried about my cat i just
got there she was my baby
i didn't know what i did wrong and then
before work it was a really [\h__\h] hot
summer day i i do not have a car or
anything i did not have the money for
taxes so i had to go with uh public
transport uh buses and i was like kind
of uh lost somewhere in nowhere at some
point and the cat was meowing and crying
and i was like
[\h__\h] i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
it was terrible
uh
yeah
um yeah i was a cat hair in my mouth
eventually i finally got her to the
clinic um
after being uh absolutely drenched and
sweat myself and drenched in tears as
well
because i felt guilty and worried and
all of that
and i was stressed out because i had to
get this done before work uh and yeah
they
kept her at the clinic for like a whole
night which you can imagine that will be
expensive
[Laughter]
and they let me know uh they were like
okay we'll take your cat we'll do some
scans and all that we'll call you later
and let you know what's wrong um so i
went to work and then at work they
called me and they told me
that
[Music]
she
had something they did an endoscopy or
something like that where you would go
in for her butt i think they saw that
she had um
like a string
a weird string in her stomach stuck not
stuck but
you wouldn't know if like
like if she would be able to poop it out
or if it would get stuck there because
when the kitten is that small it could
endanger her and kill her
so you can't just wait for her to poop
it out you have to
um do something
but i was like they were asking me on
the phone like do you
what do you think that is like do you
know what it is i'm like no no i can't
imagine
because i didn't see a picture i only
saw a picture afterwards
and when i got to pick her up on the
next day my baby
and i went there and picked her up and
they showed me a photograph basically of
what was inside and it was a like a
a bitten of a string of one of those cat
toys that have like a long string
attached to a
stick yeah
in
the first or one of her first nights
at my home
she chewed through
a cat's toy it was actually a pretty
thick uh
string he chewed through it and then
decided to eat it
[Music]
and it almost killed her
stupid chunks
but i felt so bad like oh my god yeah
maybe she did that because she was
stressed i don't know i felt so bad
about it i felt so guilty because i
didn't put away the toys i didn't think
she would eat for the whole thing man i
didn't think so
and um
yeah they took it out she was fine but
that little little wobbly tiny tiny baby
kitten
i looked at her and i was like baby i'm
so sorry
and then i was also devastated looking
at the
the bill from the holy [\h__\h]
for me
i think it was like not 800 900 bucks
which for me at the time
was almost
uh one
month of uh my income
a little a little bit less than that but
no it was no it was it was one month of
my income
it was one month for my income indeed
yeah yeah yeah
i was working part time
so
yeah but
obviously that's just [\h__\h] but i was
just happy that my cat was fine now and
sad at the same time that i you know
that that it happened and then
yeah i still had to go to work i was so
stressed out so i got my my best friend
to um
look at my cat uh
re rehabilitating
after the
she would have probably been fine but i
was just so worried about her on the
first day after getting home from the
clinic
um so i had my best friend look at her
and send me videos while i was at work
but yeah
ever since then
um they were mostly fine the only thing
that
sometimes that one one time i had to get
them
um
what's the word
castr
castle
take take the baby
machine out of them
um
spade yes spade
castrated yeah oh catherine
[Music]
get them fixed yes that was also uh
interesting
it was it was obviously harmless but
seeing them um in a slumber
looking really dead like it didn't look
like they were just sleeping it really
looked like they were dead because their
eyes were open
but they were not moving
they looked so dead
and that made me
feel
so
shook
it broke my heart looking at them it's
really scary yeah
and then
okay i'll tell you more about my guests
so then
at least on that day i had a day off
so um i i was like um i brought them to
my bed uh and just i i tucked them into
sheets normally they wouldn't like it
but i felt like
wouldn't they like it to be comfy if
there is
unconscious so i've tucked them into my
sheets on my bed and i was watching
netflix until they would wake up i was
waiting waiting waiting waiting waiting
waiting hours later still not woken up
and then i i woke up i walk over to the
living room to talk to rmt
for one second and i walk back
to my room
and i see on the floor in front of my
door
smoothie
in a puddle
lying on the floor not moving in a
puddle of her own pee
and i was like girl i was gone for one
minute and that's when you decide to
wake up and pee yourself i would have
carried you over to the toilet
and then i look on my bed and it's a
smoothie no none of my bed i think but
just one meter away from this movie was
jonker's also
uh lying on the ground in a puddle of
pee
[Music]
both of them
yeah so i washed them up a little bit
and
well they obviously didn't need to go to
the toilet anymore anytime soon but um
i waited for them to wake up properly
and then
and then and then at some point they
were um awake enough but still drowsy to
walk around and they wobbled
was funny they wobbled to the toilet and
then pete uh successfully into the
toilet my good girls they tried i could
not be mad at them peeing somewhere else
because they tried they tried their best
yeah
they must have been aware panicked when
you left no i don't think they panicked
then
i don't know they just felt like this is
the moment to pee apparently
oh man they made an effort yes
they did
[Music]
i never i never want to see them like
that again
this is scary it's so spooky
my mustache
[Music]
experience similar thing when my dad got
new
i guess pet owners
dog and cat owners can understand this
one
they did their best what are we talking
about my cats
[Music]
my cats obviously
usually that's wait for them to wake up
but that takes hours
they they had them
at their office for like one or two
hours until i picked them up
but yeah it still takes like a few hours
for them to properly wake up hmm
okay okay back to super chats back to
super chats
[Music]
and i i didn't want them
to be at the vet too long anyway i
wanted them to be
in my care
yeah and i wanted them to be cozy
because at the vets they were lying in
this like cold ass
cage looking cold
i'm wanting them to be comfy in blankets
even though they don't give a [\h__\h] about
blankets
anyway where was i oh yeah uh here i
literally only read one super chat
no i read a few okay okay
[Music]
my greeting signature at home office
you mean
the signature the written signature
is so cute
you mean the one on the board
the drawing
i did i did a few things um i wonder if
you saw
uh
i did like a drawing for
the pamphlet i think
did you guys see that too somewhere
not only the signature at the booth i
wonder if you somewhere the panic was
yeah i didn't even see
it anywhere how did that how did that
turn out
you see that eventually because you
bought the template ah
[Music]
my mind looks particularly celebrity
like yeah i i tried to make it look cute
thank you thank you thank you for
looking at that um
a nathan cotton thank you for the pinky
i cried the other day it was announced i
cried after the other video teasing it
yeah
i feel a bit sorry um that maybe ami's
video was overlooked a little bit even
though it's so so great i hope you all
watched it but you know there was so
much hype going on because of the
concert so
but i think i think a lot of people
watched it anyway so
yeah the video was so good on this video
hmm
did you watch it
[Music]
is here too
and whoa
it's like an ian hologram
yeah i guess it got a lot of views so
i'm just worried that it got
overshadowed too much and that the hard
work was overlooked
but 525k okay seems seems like maybe i i
don't need to worry
thank god okay
um
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
you watched it with me oh yeah we
watched it together on my stream
[Music]
not enough tears of pride and joy can't
wait for the debut it will be too
special to handle thank you how many
people do i have to correct today about
calling it a debut don't call in and
dump you
no no no no no
no no sneak peek sneak peek
thank you nathan though thank you that
was a a day of
many many many emotions definitely
thank you very much
skye thank you for the right super chat
beforehand super chat for sunday
thank you
and finally it's time that you are on
stage wednesday months my aussie channel
you're the star thank you i hope i made
you proud skye thank you so much for
supporting me um hope you like my
performance
yeah
i'm so happy when i think about
that you guys okay of people
enjoyed me and and and are proud of
what i did
that makes me happy i'm glad i left an
impression on other people too
but i'm just happy to see that k of
people
i enjoyed it so much
thank you
skye a kiss for you a trevor g sent
free ride super chats thank you
is it because fruit festival
it's kia razi how time flies only a
little around a year and three months
ago we were watching second fest
dreaming about you joining your senpai
on stage
now here we are finally watching the
first fest where you are about to
fulfill that dream it has been a
blessing to witness you on your journey
here
a journey of a thousand years right
you've helped brighten even my darkest
day like the shining starling you are
and i know when you step on stage your
radiance will be greater than the sun
thank you my beloved songbird for all
your hard work and the joy you spread
for me and for being you
cute
also thanks for the concert watch alongs
these are one of my favorite kiwawa
experiences simply as you make them feel
as i'm not alone it's even more special
today since i'm lucky enough to spend
another birthday
with my or she phoenix you said oyshee
or she now i'm hyped and so proud of you
what is your it was your birthday
it was your birthday
birthday
oh
happy birthday to you
happy birthday travertine
yay oh
exciting
what a special day to have your birthday
on
congratulations
[Music]
well that's a birthday you will not
forget because it was the special day
when kiwawa had the concert
i know i guess it was day one so it
wasn't not exactly almost close enough
close enough
um
[Music]
uh
there was no choice about outfit first
freddy was always in the main outfit
and usually
uh
extra outfits that come after that in
life to z are not usually not made into
3d no
[Music]
usually
not it's not
not tradition at least i don't know
maybe it's possible if i pay for it
myself maybe but
um
sounds difficult
because then probably everyone would
want it
my whole life i don't know i don't know
man
[Music]
listening
that message was 14 minutes ago
[Music]
pomeranian pomeranian my beloved
she was watching because she reacted to
my cat story
[Music]
i think i think pomeranian my beloved is
gone
[Music]
i think she's gone
i need to read super chat anyway thank
you trevor g thank you
happy belated birthday and
i wanted to say wait there was something
i wanted to say that i forgot
let me read it again uh oh yeah oh yeah
cause um you said you liked the concert
watch along so much
[Music]
i'm glad i was doing them for so long
because people
um kept on saying both
you guys and japanese fans as well they
kept on saying that they
uh
you know during times where a lot of
people can't go to the concerts in
person or when concerts are just kind of
quiet because there's no cheering
allowed um
you guys still can watch it together
with me and uh i'm so cheerful during my
watch lungs that you know you kind of
get hyped more than just watching it
alone in quietness in silence which
feels kind of lonely
[Music]
thank you so much travertine i love your
puns don't apologize for them
thank you so
much zero thank you for the pinky let's
go sorry i haven't been in a lot of
streams for a while attention but i
won't miss this i'm so excited to see
you with other myth members in 3d no
sleep for two days
i hope you guys get together in japan so
not just beyonce i hope so too yeah
don't worry about it are you busy or am
i too boring now
i hope you're just busy
yeah you're always welcome in my stream
so
oh you're here today
yo yo yo busy okay
busy with kfp work obviously
[Music]
yeah i hope so too i mean vr chat is fun
and all but it's about [\h__\h] time that
we meet up in real life
oh but
um
i i recently recently just right now um
one of my acquaintances
uh
a person i know
went from austria to
america traveled from austria to america
um and it's just having fun there right
now being a tourist and all
and
yeah that made me realize oh yeah
i could i guess
probably
[Music]
if i wanted to
hope they see lots oh they went there to
party it looks like
it looks like they just went there to
party because all i see is a
party
party party party party pony party not
really my thing but yeah
apparently america is the place to be
for clubbing yeah it's a party in the
usa
as miley cyrus tells us
[Music]
oh is it spring break right now
wouldn't that be a bit too early
it's not spring break
it was
[Music]
for some it was last week
it's time for me to go now
wherever spring break is still happening
and take part in a wet t-shirt contest
let's go
[Music]
home a wet t-shirt contest
do you want to join
girl messaged me again
[Music]
yes
what what do you mean mind is in the
gutter why
why
when i was watching mtv when i was
younger mtv was telling me part of
a
part of what americans do
is um
have spring break and and
um do wet t-shirt contests
[Music]
so now now i just you know what the full
tourist experience just kidding
[Music]
just kidding but uh
we don't have that i said that just a
while ago we don't really have that here
yeah
yeah mtv is bad bad bad bad bad bad i
know it was just a joke it's not an
educational channel obviously
[Music]
uh
no summer break oh we do have summer
break but i don't know it just doesn't
look like the spring bank look spring
break looks like in america
voldo's university student made you know
what maybe it does exist and i just
don't know about it because i didn't go
to university and i don't i'm not one of
those
party people
maybe it does exist
maybe it does
cranes are tasty duncan yoshi pudding
duncan
two oranges
oranges and a yellow one
let me read out thank you for the thank
you for the reds uh
in japanese
[Music]
thank you so much for your support thank
you
hey yo you started a little bit of the
fire but
i set the whole stage on fire
nice fire
thank you very much
very impressive cruise down this and
lily s thank you for the rest of the
chad hey yeah red
it's finally here i'm so so happy and
excited for you and the rest of the myth
girls to be able to perform on such a
grand stage finally definitely that was
very grand you're true you all truly
deserve it and day two is on my birthday
oh got cake and some tissues ready there
will be tears
what's your birthday
on the day of my performance yo
what a coincidence quincy donk i think
not
[Music]
a little bit late happy birthday just
one day late but congratulations
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear lily ass happy
birthday to you
okay
hope you had a wonderful birthday
listening to the concert watching the
concert
while eating cake mmm that sounds
like the best experience ever
thank you so much for your support
doug joseph duncan saturday
um
[Music]
and jeff starr dance psycho oh wait
sorry jeff star was a pinky thanks for
waking up early for the concert you're
thanking me
you're thanking me for waking up for the
concert it's a it's uh
it's
how to say
it's i have to how could i not be awake
for the live concert
[Music]
and you
looking at your uh currency you probably
uh were awake for it all night
pulled an all-nighter for it so respect
to you too
oh i was very asleep i was thinking i
realized that later maybe i was extra
sleepy because i took uh melatonin
uh the night before
but then
didn't sleep long enough
and maybe it was still
in effect could that be does it not wear
off relatively fast
because i slept like what four or five
i don't know maybe i don't even remember
maybe five hours
all or nothing if you use it oh
yeah maybe it was still
i don't know maybe it was still making
me drowsy
i felt really really really tired man
[Music]
much love from bulgaria thank y'all love
back to you
[Music]
it does wear off really fast usually
hmm
and maybe it was just me being tired
because i didn't get enough sleep
maybe it was just that and nothing more
a cycle
joseph thank you
thank
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
thanks for listening another watch long
tantrum also awesome voice acting work
from everyone
ah for the small adventures
was so cute was already hoping for ian
hologram after the 3dws this was orders
of magnitude better than holograh and i
love holograph
[Music]
yeah i mean holy crap it's funny and all
um but
yeah it was it was better
that do be true
[Music]
the script right she wrote it herself
she's good
she should write more
[Music]
just how they should put me into the
production team of the concert
they should put ame into the production
team of whole life english horogooda
[Music]
yeah she did the script and the sound
yeah yeah
and she also uh
pre-spoke all of the lines i think
i think
what i think i remember it listening to
it
um
what's dankishu ah it's german for kamsa
nida
german
i say it because i am from austria
[Music]
welcome you egg welcome
i need to see the kiana dubbed by amen
well everyone would be dubbed by amen
yeah it's it's um
it would be funny to see but she didn't
put that much passion into her lines it
was just to kind of i guess get a
structure going
hmm
[Music]
anyway uh thank you thank you hopefully
we can see more like that um if vomit
feels like it or if management feels
like it
yeah hoping for the best and moon dog
thank you for the pinky the days are
finally here you're all finally getting
3d and having a stage to perform on like
the idols you're all we were all meant
to be i'm so happy to pro and proud to
call you my oshi ikuza thank you
yes finally finally finally
we all waited so long for it and then
even now it's still not quite there
because it was just a one-time thing for
now at least for most of us
um
but
yeah
you saying like the idols you're all
meant to be to be honest
um as much as whole life likes to call
them
themselves or like whole life likes to
say we are idols um
during the whole streaming aspect of it
i don't think any of us are an idol and
as an idol fan
myself
this is not what an idol is
but i mean you could redefine it i
suppose but it's not really what what it
is but um the concert
once once we're in a concert
then yes it felt very much like an idol
concert
that is true
and
i
[Music]
did not think
that i could experience something so
great
[Music]
i was hoping for it but
yeah
honey
but as much as it was a sneak peek for
you guys i guess it was also a sneak
peek for me
maybe the future will be even greater
[Music]
but i don't want to claim that we are
idols or something
during our normal activities because
that's just no
i don't like it when people call us that
because
it's not
really what we are
um i guess it's a joke okay as a joke
okay but
i think some people really like
especially the ones who don't know as
well
when they talk about whole life they're
like oh yeah but they're idols
[Music]
sometimes maybe
something like an idol
but
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're and we're entertainers if anything
part-time idol yeah
sometimes i don't every once in a while
idle every once in a while
shut up
dragon's fire thank you for the red
super chat can't wait for kiana 3d
oh
but you had to wait one more day after
that
thank you dragons fire
the wait is finally over
it's just about four minutes but you can
rewatch it endlessly so you'll have
endless kiwa 3d isn't that great
isn't that great
please watch it as much as you want
i hope you don't get sick of it but it's
really a [\h__\h] dope performance
i think i'm proud of it
i'm proud of it
yeah thank you dragons fire um didn't
need you because i had the phoenix fire
didn't need you on stage but i did need
yours and everybody else's support until
now and in the future as well
need my fans support to continue putting
out great content yoda school dragons
fire
[Music]
wish the bit rate was better i wish the
same thing man
let's wait for wait for the blu-ray
internet debate goddamn
sandy echo duncan joe b duncan big and
anime duncan stark stark stark
for the pink sticker thank you you're
amazing you're amazing too
thank you so much
[Music]
87 thank you for the rest of the chat
it's 2 am drink
you mean drunk
love you tk i better see you at
coachella next mo coachella's next month
oh dear
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] my pc just lagged
for a second
and he uses korean
[Music]
um
i was at
uh edm concert in japan before but
coachella is like
a scary place i don't think i would want
to be there
just from what i've heard and what i've
seen
no
not not my cup of tea
[Music]
that's quite a jump yes
i mean they sometimes have cool
performance right i think uh perfume uh
performed at coachella before
and maybe baby medal
maybe
i'm mixing something up i think they
performed them before like that's cool
um but everything besides that
would intimidate me
very intimidating
[Music]
yeah they had a japanese artists
ah california your palm
not baby metal
i have a bare metal is also
here and there nowadays overseas
that's let me go too maybe maybe yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
it's uh coachella mixing in
some interesting performers yeah
i mean i think it's cool but
it fits in
weirdly
hatsune miku at coachella
it's two completely different
worlds colliding
and crashing yeah i wonder how they
reacted to
[Music]
wow
i have baby metal performed at vacant
which is like a
german
heavy metal metal concert thingy
festival
i have heard about it
[Music]
why is everyone talking about eurovision
right now
yeah maybe we'll try to enter next year
for austria let's go
make some more word worlds collide
[Music]
don't tell people my plan
thank you i'm sorry
[Music]
wait does that mean you were gonna go to
coachella because you say i better see
you at coachella
oh you mean i thought you meant as a as
like a visitor but you meant maybe as a
performer oh you know what with kyani
palm yup
and perfume and all that being a
coachella i can see a 2023
with retubers performing at coachella
but oh dear lord have mercy on us
have mercy on us
imagine
oh
[\h__\h] i don't know if i want to support
that
what a crazy timeline oh my god
um i'd go really
isn't that scary i don't want to go
[Music]
yeah i meant to i thought they meant the
audience
[Music]
mr caspancian tanaka dan kashan for the
pinky my whole fest wishlist for next
year oran's do it holy burps group song
and luna x mikko x kiana baby group song
oh yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
those are some good ideas um
i'm not really generally not really
considered a baby living whole life but
i do have my pacifier and i think i'm
the only one
who had a pacifier in her life
[Music]
i'm more of a baby than you guys would
think i am
[Music]
just a big baby
baby
[Music]
but i'm definitely in for the arrest to
it and hollow braves group song what
else would i want to do
um
i would like to
perform as uh
as and i would i would like to do a
takamori do it that would be hype that
would send mamaloni to grave
she would die at the spot
and
[Music]
i would like to form
a duet or unit
well
[Music]
i have so much
so much choice
i could be selfish and say pecora senpai
but
i i don't feel worthy
[Music]
now we already said oren so that's an
energy but besides that
[Music]
and the [\h__\h] senpai
ah
and mine is for the amazon for everybody
everybody i just want to perform with
everybody
i'll just do a solo concert where
um
it's as many songs as we have whole life
members
and
i perform a duet with each member or
maybe some units but i just bring every
person in as a guest
and i'll be in every song because it's
my solo concert but i'll just have a
guest performance for every song
[Music]
sounds like a mission
i will be in every song
songs ah manageable manageable
um
thank you for the pinky
thank you for just watching on attention
it really feels like we're there and
enthusiastically cheering along maybe a
bit jet lag but it is worth it oh you
were jet lagged
thank you yes yes i am glad i can
provide some cheering background noises
for you i i saw someone writing on
twitter that if you put on kiara and oli
in the background it really feels like
you're in some kind of audience
[Laughter]
maybe add the vaude of fugue senpai's
watch along to it because she
[\h__\h] said by goes hard she's like
from beginning to end continuously like
enthusiastically going hey
[Music]
i respect fubuki senpai
she was so into it
justin reinhard thank you
thank you
thank you for another red super chat
thank you very much
fanatas x-rays free perry junior
dankeshen the game mccree duncan
miniature pincher chang thank you for
the pinky jesus my jaw dropped like
summit
is that a
joke about that a
shark movie that's called jaws or
something
is that a
joke
[Music]
it's a joke
but am i getting the reference
correctly
i didn't see that movie
[Music]
it's called jazz right and it's a movie
about sharks
oh
i think
a joke
huh
i did get a reference in school
a killer shark
is it a good movie
jaws
very big shark
[Music]
good a small shark
jaws big shark
it's a classic movie oh
watch long we already have so many
movies on the list of what we want to
watch i feel like
david's tr thank you for the pinky she
got bottom teeth yes she does kuda has
bottom somewhat visible bottom teeth
in her 3d yeah yeah
that was very cute
very small very cute
i thought the performance was so hype
because i just [\h__\h] love reflect so
much reflect is so [\h__\h] hype
ah
i can't
counting chickens thank you for the
pinkie i've cried so many times now how
am i going to survive tomorrow ah
well you survived didn't ya everything
was all right right you're good right
i looked so hard for those teeth
and you found them
um
good i nailed it yeah banger of the
century yes it's so much fun
the different personalities
and different verses like so so much
variety in that song
[\h__\h] genius
farhan is a genius
cotton chickens anyway
[Music]
sorry i had to get a cat
how do they keep on getting into my
mouth i don't get it
[Music]
uh thank you counting chickens i hope
you didn't lose
all of the hydration in your body make
sure to drink some water to make up for
all the tears you cried okay
[Music]
the fire kittens
um
thank you for the pinky today's my
birthday what
as my final semester has started i
couldn't spend as much time with you as
before but i'm still trying to catch up
on your streams please keep shining as
always love you my only oshikiana i miss
your clips buddy
the korean people need you
they need your clips buddy
happy birthday birthday though
thank you to kahamnida
[Music]
we need you
i will come back soon really
okay
i'm excited you're just cool
edwin or lana thank you for the pinky i
can't stop crying over ian and idea's
showing in this festival i can't wait to
see you live tomorrow kiara you got this
thank you i really gotta say the first
day also made me so nervous because they
did so great and yeah
yeah
but i'm so glad it went well
on my part
thank you thank you for supporting all
of us edwin
and watching the concert together with
me
thank you very much i hope you enjoyed
it
thank you thank you thank you
a korean name i've seen this name before
come
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
thanks for watching it made the whole
experience so great it seems like we're
getting to the end of this
sometime soon we're like at least um
past fifty percent
made the whole experience so great thank
you i'm glad i could provide another
watch along
i don't know if in the future i'll
also um i'll probably won't be doing
them anymore for the big concerts
because i'll hopefully be part of it
but but but we'll see we'll see if
there's something that i want to watch
together with you guys
um then i'll still do it
if i'm not part of it myself
yeah it feels like a fun
um
a fun tradition at this point we've done
so many
um
and maybe uh
maybe we could also just watch the vods
if if i'm part of something we can
always watch the vods together
[Music]
chill hop music
oh
you're live right now what are you doing
here you have two streams live running
right now
what are you doing here getting go go go
go go handle your viewers over there
just kidding
just kidding you have two streams
running low-fi hip-hop radio beats to
study and relax too and chill hop radio
jazzy low-fi hip-hop beats man good
stuff what the [\h__\h] multitasker yeah
hey can i use your music on my stream
are they uh copyright free
[Music]
are they copyright free
not
probably not because this is like well
you can submit music it's probably not
copyright free
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
i cannot risk such a thing
[Music]
always gotta use copyright free stuff
very cool don't lie to me really
oh stop
they claim they're copyright free
[Music]
do you have a business email i need that
in writing
[Laughter]
i would need that in writing
[Music]
i don't see a business email on your
channel
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's probably a lie
line live
but if you have a business email ah
you should you should add it to your you
should add it to your
uh youtube uh
uh this description
are you from the netherlands this
childhood music from the netherlands
i yo
yo
neville yo
close close to me i'm from austria
yeah
netherlands is nice even though i say
that and i never
i never really have been there i've been
to the airport
but but i've only heard good things
about the netherlands and i have friends
in the netherlands and uh yeah
beautiful beautiful country yeah
time to visit
best ever
you do have a good airport and i love uh
i love klm
wait klm is your island right i'm not
saying anything wrong i [\h__\h] love klm
one of my favorite airlines to fly to
japan too because they are so nice
their uh flight attendants are the best
the food is really yummy
i love klm i've
why did i hit the table so hard i've
flown flown fluent into japan so many
times with different airlines because
every time i was looking for the
cheapest one then sometimes it was like
this airline sometimes it was that
airline and out of those airlines klm
was
one of my favorite ones yeah
and and and in shippong airport in my
stopover
um um i ate really really good food at
the airport as well
klm sponsorship
get get kiwawa to japan please yes yes
yeah
so
judging by the the kindness of the
flight attendants i am assuming that the
[Music]
people in the netherlands are just
really really dope
[Music]
yes okay continuing
oh it really sounds like it's uh coming
to an end
karna thank you
sticky thank you for the pinky thanks
again for the watch long boss and i hope
you have a great time for your own
performance tomorrow i definitely will
try not to cry when you show up on stage
well maybe a couple of tears
i feel like
i feel like it was still on fire there
was there was no time to cry
[Music]
but oh i did see some of you guys react
some of you guys recorded your reactions
and some of you guys got a little bit
teary-eyed and made me go like oh
don't cry for
me oh
come on
and somewhere like
you [\h__\h] nailed it
oh my god
that was that was general
he was like
he couldn't believe his eyes
[Music]
oh my god
you don't know what you don't even know
what you're watching
you're watching me too but i'm from
whole live english but i'm just reading
super chats right now so you kind of um
zapped into a bad stream
just reading super chats from the
previous streams because i have too many
to read yeah but i have funnier streams
so please subscribe subscribe subscribe
subscribe subscribe
[Music]
back i mean you gotta admit there's
better streams to get to know someone
like me
there's better streams than a super chat
rating
yeah
yes
[Music]
i know you guys like it but it's just
not the best content to jump into
scribble yata
we got em we got the netherlands
in our
grasp
yeah
[Music]
got him
where was i
oh yeah thank you everything
how much did you cry how many bottles
did you fill how many pet bottles
um one liter two liters
three
liters feel free to um bathe in them
it's a good uh salt peeling salt is good
for your skin i think yeah
[Music]
mr blue blur danke
german
why you must do this i want to read it
quietly
[Music]
i managed to catch you and kelly live in
the next morning nicer
oh yeah
yeah
i read that um you uh your alarm
made you miss the first two hours
goddamit at least you got to watch the
vlog yeah yeah
there's always a vod
[Music]
okay cocoon
i read your super chat
stop branding in german
[Music]
i mean you can continue writing in
german but i'll just read it quietly
[Music]
thank you for the pinky boo hoo seven
two three down
okay
oh the t-shirts yeah they they have some
interesting effect i thought so too
because it reminded me of the idol
concerts stratified akashin
miniature
[Music]
i think there is no streaming from
tensho tomorrow jst also ksc so i will
respond in advance i mean there was a
member stream we've been waiting for
this time fantastic thank you
where are my korean viewers
[Music]
did you watch my concert
say yes yes yes
say yes
oh so many so many
thank you
[Music]
don't say it really no it was just maybe
maybe maybe i'm just saying maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe
yeah
i want to
um
do a concert but i think like the first
concert
of kiwawa
overseas would be uh
somewhere in europe or in america
probably realistically speaking
maybe
but
looking at
all the fans in korea maybe what we
could do
is
[Music]
very possible
if a korean anime convention decides to
invite her life
as a guest
then it's very possible
[Music]
do you guys have anime conventions in
korea
i think they're all over the world agf i
think i've heard about that
agf
korea
is this
anime
anime game festival oh
yes yes please yes please
yes please
wait asuki was a guest before
i just went on their instagram asuki was
a guest in 2019
[Music]
asuki
in a korean anime convention called agf
korea 2019
[Music]
so they are aware of whole life
at least
[Music]
and then my dear korean friends you know
what to do you need to tell them
to invite hololive again invite
takanashikiwawa tell them
tell them
is popular in korea you need to bring
her to korea
please and then then i'll fly to korea
and i'll do some sightseeing and i'll
eat some korean food and buy
clothes in korea i want to go shopping
want to buy clothes and makeup
[Laughter]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah please okay
okay okay it's a deal
it's a deal
[Music]
i'm counting on you these kind of things
they they don't work unless you let the
convention know that you uh want this
person at the convention this is how we
got kiwawa me to perform at dokomi in
germany last year
because
german fans wrote to the convention and
told them please invite takana
[Music]
yeah you need to let them know otherwise
there's that just like so much choice
and the the
organizers will just invite whoever
whatever looks interesting for them
but that doesn't necessarily reflect
what the the people who go there want to
see the visitors
[Music]
we can we can go with um
bails bales as well maybe kiwawa and
bales
go to
agf
[Music]
sounds good
where was i
uh
oh yeah miniature pins your jungle you
get another kiss
[Music]
i
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
for the watch alone translation cat i
can't wait to see you up there tomorrow
thank you
thank you did you guys survive without
my translation at least there was not
that much um
talking anyway on day two so
yeah hopefully
hopefully you survive without my
translation but of course it's more fun
with my translation right right right
but this time you watched it from a
different point of view hopefully with a
different feeling like this time this
time the girl that i always watched
those uh
streams together with
this time
she's up there oh i'm so proud
kind of like that
oh he was helping
good good good good
until she cried
[Music]
uh only i wrote her a message because ah
she's so
so sweet for always being so so so
openly
fully supportive of everything in her
life
so i wrote her thank you for being such
a sweet supportive cutie pie
um
yeah
yeah it's really sweet over here
she really really loves being part of
her life and
um
yeah
i think that's really nice that's that's
the kind of person i want
to be i want to see in the whole life
i mean if
if it were all like only then i would
probably
[Music]
go [\h__\h] insane if every whole life
member were like only or if we had more
than five
people like only
i would probably go insane
uh but having one person like only is
perfect
my ears would retire yeah not only that
but yeah it would it would be a very
very busy
um
whole life
because everyone everywhere everywhere
there would be someone fangirling over
another and would be like i love you i
love you
[Laughter]
i don't have the energy for that but one
only is totally fine one only is exactly
what i need
[Music]
thankfully
thank you simpion
jenny
and brandon duncan talked to ricks thank
you
thank you for watching i can't wait to
see you tomorrow on stage hatchima's
song infinity is very emotional um she
put a lot of herself in it even though
she isn't my oshie i have a lot of
respect and love for her oh
yeah
yeah yeah
it was really really
a great performance of her doing
infinity i think it's um a good
opportunity to
show people that
you have a different side as well i mean
people like to joke about ha ha so crazy
and all that but she's definitely more
than that and she has a lot of chill
streams as well
um
works really hard too
and i think a big big concert like that
with so many eyes on her was a good uh
opportunity to show
that she's not always like
crazy blah blah blah
which is a good side to her as well
a funny side entertaining side but
there's more to her than that right
[Music]
yeah her emcee was great it was
definitely my favorite emcee in the
concert
[Music]
i think we're going through this pretty
well paced i'm almost done with the ones
from the watch along
[Music]
a drowsy cat thank you soon wait i think
i didn't give you a kiss miaku now kiss
did you catch it
yeah i'm trying to um
only read the pinks and the red ones uh
out loud because uh there's just so many
there is just so many
but i do read um
some of the others
quietly in my brain
while i zoom through them
[Music]
i know
and where was i drown drowsy cat
no no
need that for the pink super chat
and it's in korean so let me translate
it
[Music]
um
thank you so much for your sweet super
chat for your sweet supportive message
it says uh basically it's finally
tomorrow i'm really looking forward to
it i'm very happy to be with you at this
moment i'm always rooting for you kiara
fighting thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you for
supporting me in the past couple of
weeks months
up to this moment thank you very much
for being part of kfb donkey soon
sam says thank you for the rest of the
chat thanks for watching i'm so hyped
for tomorrow
yeah watch long was fun but being on
stage is even more fun
thank you for watching me and supporting
me from afar thank you very much hope
you enjoyed it hope you liked my
performance sam says a kiss for you
thank you
and justin
flaming pants down
[Music]
for 10 just 3d life tomorrow ah less
than 24 hours left yes uh now it's uh
more than 24 hours ago
i wish i could go back to that moment
but
it's over it's over so isn't that sad
so sad
it was so short it was so short i wanted
it to last longer i should have i should
have
chosen
you know what the the redshift remix was
it this one or was it the astrophysics
remix of hinotori one of them was really
long
i should have performed one of the
remixes because they were longer
right
i think it was the
astrophysics one
that had like a long intro
yeah but
even though the astrophysics one is
really really cool it probably wouldn't
have been so fire as this one was
i should have just added
a few
choruses of the original song to the
original song just add a few more and
hope people won't notice
keep on dancing
[Music]
yeah
one day maybe i can um perform the one
of the remixes and kind of adjust the
choreography to the remix
yeah
it would be cool i think
thank you fred's fred squirrel
for your support hope you enjoyed the
concert moon
[Music]
for the pink super chat attention please
put down your light stick now please go
up to the stage tomorrow and be the
light of the clerk potential oh
[Music]
yes it was time for me to put down the
light sticks
and be on the other side yeah
[Music]
but i like my light sticks they're fun
they're fun to
wave around
[Music]
both sides are fun both watching and
performing both is fun
[Music]
thank you kamzan nida
salubrious
[Music]
did you guys see the art to do she sent
me a hd version because i asked her for
it
wow
[Applause]
hey
let me put that here
she was so fast
like she was she must have been drawing
right after my performance like well the
concert was still ongoing
man the screen is so busy
[Music]
it's perfect
perfect
it's better than the screenshots because
the screenshots are so pixelated
yeah
now she's just a little bit shy
don't worry about it
and
[Music]
a
thank you
[Music]
is
i love that
bishop johnson
jones duncan i can't say your name
probably i'm probably
saying it really badly i'm sorry
[Music]
translate
yeah y'all you sound very motivated i
like the spirit cs poli thank you
you got attention really
oh i'm relieved
i'm glad i didn't butcher your name
thank you for supporting me and cheering
for me
i got a lot of motivation from you guys
thank you man
thank you also for a red super chat
[Music]
yesterday yesterday at this point
yesterday yesterday yesterday
thank you tai chi
you must have been
really really hyped up thank you so much
[Music]
thank you
let me drink some water
[Music]
our hero translator eh
what do you mean translator was tied to
translating
it
[Music]
translated tai chi tai chi said more
than one word
you must have confused someone with him
thank you for the membership thank you
wrong guiding
wrong tai chi yes
that doesn't sound like this tai chi
[Music]
tai chi ha
mistakes have been made thank you tai
chi
[Music]
thank you
glad my translations helped skye duncan
christina manzanita
[Music]
but the biggest one is yet to come
ah
wow
damn i thought i would be here for 12
hours today
[Music]
okay but the next one is longer um or
more than
the
two super chat streams that we just read
together combined
[Music]
but i didn't expect finishing them
anyway so i don't need to force myself
to finish them i can still read more
after the ellen ring stream too
how's your throat it's okay we can take
a little break maybe i also need to go
because i've been drinking so much water
i need to go into an idol meeting
[Music]
of a break
oh yeah fauna fona's birthday stream
starts at what 11 p.m my time
i think
[Music]
um
so i'm awake for that this time
hallelujah have fun are doing a birthday
stream at a somewhat decent time for me
recently there's been so many birthdays
and most of them were like at bad times
for me
[Music]
but this one actually works
a few hours from now yeah and i'm gonna
call in
she did give me some time that um
i should call in
[Music]
i'll be the
oh wait a second uh
what time is dad
i'll be the third caller
spoiler alert i'll be the third caller
so
uh that's
[Music]
11 pm is 7
00.
oh i think i have to call
right before midnight i think perfect
perfect
[Music]
call
somewhere somewhere here probably
spoilies
[Music]
foreign
i'm excited to see her like birthday
merchandise and stuff
excited oh i need to send her a png
i should stop talking for a little bit
um
but then it's so awkward
here here is my png
okay you know what time it is it is idol
meeting time
or his name she likes to say
toilet time but no i don't go to the
toilet
i go to an idol meeting
i don't mean time
[Music]
sneeze sneeze
ah
[Music]
do
hey
i brought junkers
what she's making weird noises
[Music]
no
huh
[Music]
i cuddled with smoothie and chunkers
and went to an island meeting perfect
i am recharged
if you
[Music]
inhale the chunkers
yes
no
reading
two but
i can't type
can i type that correctly yes
okay
[Music]
everybody was impressed by a high kick
yes yes yes yes
i am
i've done it
i became
i became a meme
let's go
my legs are meme
[Music]
great performance thank you kiki kick
yes
she hurt herself for the memes i don't
don't tell them they'll think i'm less
cool
oh what is this
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my
god i got the
oh [\h__\h]
i want to listen to something
i can just mute it so you guys don't
hear it um um
my um
my soon-coming
uh new original song
um has been ready for a while um
as in like the instrumental was ready
for a while
and um
i got someone to write lyrics for it and
i've been like checking over them for
the past couple days and now my lyricist
recorded a demo
and her voice is so great can i listen
to it
because uh i know i don't think i've ha
um
properly listened to it yet and she also
added harmonies
perfect i love her
she added harmonies to it as well
can i listen to it
i'll mute it's muted everything's muted
don't worry
you
you didn't hear that did you
just checking i know you didn't hear it
[Music]
what a beggar
now
okay let's go
don't hum kiwawa don't hum to it
just vibe yeah
don't hum oh god don't hum ki mama
[Music]
oh yeah girl
oh harmonies
oh god i need to hold back
[Laughter]
oh
nice
[Laughter]
now you guys want to listen to it
sounds good
verse two
okay sounding good
oh
there's a second verse oh my god
like every other song
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah
can i just release it like that her
voice is better than mine
yeah
oh
oh yeah
mm-hmm
it's not picking up
you don't
you don't get any
any image from that no no no
all right
oh
it's too much good good
[Music]
one thing i can tell you it will be a
very different
uh different genre i've been telling you
before but it's a different genre from
my
um i didn't hum the whole song what the
[\h__\h] no i helped move for one second
um
i vibed for the whole song yeah but it's
a very different genre from my other
songs yeah
and i'm really nervous about that
because i don't know how you guys will
like it really like makes me really
really really nervous about it
um
no there's no yodeling no no no no no
no no
there is something else
cool
um it's definitely a different genre no
it's not metal
no
majority will eat it up well i hope so
i think it's uh
hmm
very
cool
uh
nice to vibe to
it might not be like super like
something that will blow
everyone away and make headlines
everywhere
um but i think
for kfp it will be great um
because you'll you'll hear a different
style
of music
but i am nervous let's pick a different
medium
i want this one
probably not for too long though
[Music]
looking forward to it thank you
please do i i hope it won't um flop
i really hope so
yeah that's my biggest fear
cupid's i'm right it's my papa papa papa
big jam
isn't it cute
[Music]
it's not on here okay okay then i gotta
go to youtube studio for this one
[Music]
but i really want the lyric kids to
release
her version of it
her voice is so nice i really i really
really really love my lyricist voice i
hired someone else for the first time
ever this time but i know her
um for a long time
um and her work is amazing and yeah she
was really excited to
write the lyrics for a song for me
oh no it's an english song
yeah i thought about implementing
some japanese words into the lyrics
but
currently currently it has basically no
little to no
no japanese in it just like some
like maybe
five words or something
just as a
as an accent
yeah yeah
cause this production is taking so long
i've been talking so openly about it
usually how i like to do it
but this is comfortable i don't have to
keep everything a secret this way
and can talk with you guys about my
worries about it as well
what is it called it has no title yet i
don't know what to title it
and i also i'm still
i've been wrecking my brain i'm still
not sure i guess
about whether i'll do a 3d music video
or not no i don't think so because like
this will come out rather soon and i
don't know if i'll have a 3dw by the
time then this is coming out
[Music]
but then i'm looking for
an artist who has a fitting style for
the song because i don't want it just to
be some
random anime cutesy style because it i
don't think it fits the song
and i've been looking around for
um
artists on twitter
looking keeping an eye out on
someone
who can
who has an art style that looks suitable
but it's
really hard
[Music]
but i can't talk about
what style i need because then it kind
of reveals
too much about the song
anyway
i'm gonna read the super chats from this
stream
they should be
not mixed up
should be fine the order should be fine
i might ask ina
um for advice she probably knows
like she can probably think at the top
of her head think about more artists
than i can
maybe she can think about
an artist that would fits the song
[Music]
oh god
she's got a heart attack footwork
because i thought it was helping my
original song but no i'm just coming
along to
the vgm
[Music]
oh my god
just pgm it's just pgm
it's my new song
[Music]
yo
um
[Music]
i'm sorry that was just windows being
annoying
tanto bought the ticket for both days
but sadly cannot catch the concert live
oh no
damn
wish all the best you rose like a
phoenix twice and you are one now it's
time to ignite the sparks always support
you from afar
did you think i was gonna
um
do you think i was gonna perform sparks
huh junky chunk when you trying to
be smart here and then and have people
tell you oh my god you can look into the
future because you knew ahead of time
what i was gonna perform
bamboozle i did not perform spikes
i would love to see
how the crowd would react to sparks as
well
so let's make it through one day
[Music]
no i was not really really
there was way more than sparks on that
stage there was literal fire
sparks ignites the flame
and start a fire today
i started a fire yesterday
thank you donkey
[Music]
thank you thank you cotton
oh you like mine and enos uh duet thank
you
the sound cover
thank you it's a good one yeah
[Music]
no
no you can't call a phoenix an arsonist
no all right
just
me being mean
yeah i don't have any bad intentions or
something
the game recreation
studio ralph duncan
fleming fantasy duncan miniature pincher
again thank you for another red super
chat
wow
oh
this one
oh these super chats are when i was
performing
already yes oh that was that was fast oh
ooh yes
thank you
were you surprised when you were
expecting
[Music]
while i was performing what the hell
focus focus on the screen
[Music]
another one another one who's sending
super chats while why was helping
happening
i had to
you couldn't hold back huh
[Music]
no problem yeah cause they're from this
stream basically
[Music]
it was too hyped
yeah because of that i don't know how
you managed to send a super chat in that
time
it was needed to be done okay okay okay
okay i will not complain
thank you cotton
rick salanti dancing miller thank you
tai chi thank you for the triple rhine
thank you tai chi
i forgive tai chi because tai chi didn't
write anything any text so it was just
like
a few clicks and that's it
thank you
pepsi
and internet debate god dang memory card
dankeshen alexander gary garza thank you
for the red super chat this is a dream
come true for all of us thank you so
much for being awesome dan joe
thank you too
you guys are awesome too for being here
for choosing me to support out of all
the people in an ocean of youtubers
yeah
thank you thank you
when will we see the 3d model on stream
available for everyone as i said in the
beginning of the stream i currently
don't know because i don't really have
the the
[Music]
technical equipment at home that i need
to
deliver good quality
content i would have to go to a studio
and that's not so easy
because it takes planning and
certain other preparations
but i want to do a 3dw as soon as
possible so be sure that i'm working on
it
and i'm also working on getting the
right equipment
asap with the support of the company
[Music]
i want to put out more content like that
too i don't want a lag behind or
anything of course so please please be a
little bit patient and
[Music]
i will try to
um put out content that satisfies
everyone as soon as possible thank you
for your understanding
[Music]
thank you gary garza
matching eight thousand stratospherician
reynard thank you for the pinky
getting shivers from your performance
you're amazing
even though you're shivering
you had no typos in your text so i doubt
that you were shivering
you wrote it perfectly
that super chat is perfectly spelled out
with no typos i don't see any signs of
shivering reynard you're lying to me
eggs both
now maybe maybe autocorrect helped
in correcting the shivering typos maybe
maybe
i'll give you the benefit of the doubt
but next time you better shiver more
shiver
shiver at the sight of 3d takanashikiya
could have been speech to text maybe
i need an explanation
thank you reynard mr kyle brown thank
you so much
long thank you
thank you for the red super chat
thank you i love you i love you too
thank you
you're so sweet
thank you so much for your support mwah
you're too generous thank you so much
crazy crazy crazy
jenny l dankester and jonathan dubray
thank you and mrs sticky thank you for
the pinky it's too beautiful congrats
thank you you made it thank you i made
it indeed it was really really beautiful
as in i think the effects and everything
yeah they did a great job
the only thing that i missed was the
fire
there was some
red clouds or something like that
fire would have been even better but
besides that it looked really cool
um
stage visuals
were intimidatingly
red and on fire
[Music]
it was magical yeah
smoke smoke yes smoke
fire budget ran out
maybe it was that
[Music]
why why so many people expected a skirt
skirt north
[Music]
um
don't you worry about that
but i need to get shorter
pants safety pants underneath
t.k danke and mr vick thank you
[Music]
my ceiling doesn't stop leaking what do
i do
um um um
move into an apartment that doesn't have
a ceiling
uh so move outside live outside i guess
i don't know
it's maybe it's not a bad thing that's
leaking maybe it's a good thing
thank you cotton yeah
thank you for the membership welcome
okay
okay cotton is moving
maybe you guys can help cotton with the
moving process
help packing and carrying the
the
the stuff
[Music]
you can get up now if you're still
kneeling
you're welcome to get up now
thank you so much you guys are so
supportive so enthusiastic it's so sweet
um thank you
[Music]
finally you became a real idol
i always was i just couldn't really show
you properly
but thank you for waiting for me thank
you for waiting for this moment being so
patient always with me thank you so much
dr joseph thank you and to pete thank
you for the pinky you were amazing
tension can't stop crying love you thank
you love you too
stop crying
do i need to sing
kitty
[Music]
oh the second one something kitty little
ball of fur
happy kitty sleepy kitty purple
one kitty yeah
[Music]
chicken worms again little ball of
feathers
happy chicken sleepy chicken purr bulk
book book
[Music]
you guys don't purr i suppose
or do you
have i missed something
yeah you don't purr
bug bug
but but wait why would chickens not be
able to perk because like uh doves make
these purring sounds as well
not really purring but they go like
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe chickens can do that too
you can pray if you want to i want you
to yes
that's cooling well it sounds like my
cat sometimes
[Music]
maybe chickens can yeah you can do
anything anything
like the video chicken spur oh my god
oh no
chicken's purr
[Music]
thank you
i'll risk it i'll risk it and play this
not human voice only chicken voice
please
[Laughter]
[Music]
so
it's just a fluffy
ball with legs and a beak
look at this ball
oh my god
[Music]
so cute
it's so cute
oh man chickens can be really cute
[Music]
mama
you cute yeah
i have a pet chicken can confirm very
cute you have a pet chicken how old when
when is it starting to work for me
[Music]
power
there's so many reds ahead
oh man
oh man uh did i read this one
ntp i think i did read that one quiet
thank you for the red super chat no text
but thank you mwah what a chat thank you
very very much
for supporting me
counting chicken thank you and also for
red super chat
crying and it's all your fault that was
amazing my potential
should i say you're welcome could you
say it's my fault but it's is it a good
thing
sometimes you need to let out your
emotions
maybe a lot of you were stressed out
and you you didn't have something to let
out your emotions in the past few weeks
and months
and then and then kiwawa
comes on stage
and you absolutely lose it
it's a good good thing to cry
[Music]
actually a good thing
you let all your emotions every day
funny aren't ya
it's a good thing
oh i stressed out it was worth it it is
okay to crack yes okay
i did cry a lot like the whole day and
all you guys
don't cry
i mean do cry i guess but i don't only
only happy tears don't cry so much but
do cry and release the stress but then i
feel bad if i see you cry
i don't know i'm torn again
[Music]
i don't know what i want
tell me what i want what i really really
want tell me what you what i want what i
really really want i wanna i wanna i
wanna i wanna i wanna really really
really just don't wanna see you cry
um
[Music]
thank you counting chickens
and brandon thank you for a red super
chat stop crying chad stop crying
super cry chats today
crying stop
crying about it
stupid gift chip
i've now experienced scattered hundred
percent power and i'm blown away and
those kicks you are the stuff of legends
viva la quiara thank you
thank you yes legendary phoenix
[Music]
i made history i made history
thank you brandon very much
so so so sweet of you
i'm glad you enjoyed my performance and
liked it so much thank you very much
i don't know how to say thank you
anymore
i don't know how how
how
[Music]
i need to say
in other ways
need to find more vocabularies
gracias
yes
[Music]
i'm stuck
uh
i said that a lot when i was in brazil
[Music]
[Laughter]
polish
[Music]
okay i'll stop here because i don't know
maybe some of you guys are trolling me
[Music]
guys let's do my homework i need to read
the pictures
right now thank you for the rest of the
chat it says i'm crying kiara
[Music]
we're sorry
crying about it
thank you though rangana
and you must like me very much
if if that means you cry
i'm thinking about that makes me happy
i like you very much too
i really really really really really
really like you
thank you
[Music]
right now mary janke
never read super chat thank you
congratulations on stage you really made
us so proud
thank you
oh man
really
dad dad that girl that girl there and
that girl
really
[Music]
um
you guys make me proud to you know why
because i have the best
fandom the best
the sweetest
people
i'm proud of you
i'm proud having you guys
oh stop no you stop no stop stop you
guys stop
[Laughter]
why ochi danges
thank you for the red super chat
snapchat i need to turn you off if you
don't stop being so
cute
so cute that was amazing tension you
truly are an amazing idol dad absolutely
owned the steaks
yeah
thank
you thank you
i'm having a moment ready to yawn
[Music]
so much again [\h__\h]
can't stop
yawning
thank you eric newstrom
also
you also got up early for it huh
thank you for
supporting me
by watching my performance
[Music]
i hope it won't be the last time and i
hope you get to see the other times as
well thank you so much
[Music]
how annoyed android thank you soon katie
duncan right now thanks for the pinky
[Music]
it says it was so good right ghana going
crazy again
thank you
you guys
[Music]
info thank you for the triple insane red
super chat
crazy ethel thank
you absolutely amazing the singing
dancing especially yukiya amazing oh
thank you
you're pretty amazing yourself you know
that
thank you
based
yes based and biased but i love you
no you
no
i don't know what to say anyway you guys
are so kind
[Music]
i don't i don't know
thank you
[Music]
i want to give you all a big hug
hug i can do that
i can't do that where is my
where is my chimpkin
it's not here
i gotta go here
[Music]
okay
i decide when it's winter time
i decide when it's summertime
you're like my little puppets my
marionettes
i have you on strings on several strings
and i'll make you dance around the
seasons
and i make australia feel extra special
or stupid
for having it turned around and having
to celebrate
christmas in [\h__\h] summer time
psych
so that you guys feel like left out
because when all of the world people are
selling summer fashion in their super
awesome fashion brands it doesn't fit
your season
it doesn't fit your season man
you can buy it but you can't wear it in
your current situation
stuff like that you know i know i'm a
monster yes yes sometimes i like being a
monster
[Music]
so cruel
but whenever a certain fruit is in
season
in the rest of the [\h__\h] world you and
australia sit there and you're like [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i have to eat frozen fruit or so i
don't know if that's really true
[Laughter]
[Music]
suffer australia suffer for making me
and those austrian
feel like um
something that doesn't exist because
everyone always asks are you from
australia and i say no
this is my payback [\h__\h]
[Music]
no it's okay we're cool i like
australians in australia
we're cool we're cool
we cool
[Music]
we cool though
what's up
accepted me as one of their own did they
really don't they were just scared that
i would destroy them if they wouldn't
accept me
[Music]
you do miss the wings oh i'm from
australia
[Music]
yeah
i think um
it was funny while it lasted
[Music]
because it was an insider and i thought
it would be more of an outsider but it
ended up being quite the insider
it was too much of an insider so that
eventually people really thought i was
australian
how could i have made it any more
obvious
i am from australia
doesn't that sound sus to you
i always have something in my eye every
time i mention australia
australia if i were from australia
wouldn't my
english be a little bit better
i don't know man
i feel like it would but okay
[Music]
better or like at least i would maybe
have an australian accent which i told
her i do
uh here's my australian accent
this is just my generic whatever english
accent
you can hardly understand bae sana or
amelia amelia
what
really
[Music]
yeah sana has some moments where her
english is very very
funny
but i like it i like
the different
flavors of english
[Music]
are you guys sick of the song yet
isn't my body hot in 3d
you can see
that
that tiny cute waist
[Music]
yeah
good waist
then that's one of the things i like um
we talked about it in the member stream
but the fact that my outfit is so tight
makes the dance moves look really sharp
rather than having all kinds of like
accessories and ribbons and fluffy
dresses and petticoats and whatever
it just shows what's necessary and that
is the
silhouette of a sexy hot flaming ass
body
anyway
i
love you too
thank you thank you thank you mwah
right ghana
i love you kiara love you tom
thank you skye too generous thank you so
much
[Music]
thank you
will we ever see your freebie again yes
of course
[Music]
i will
do my best to make it happen soon
but please wait please wait a little bit
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you for the uh red super chat not
pinky kiana thank you for being amazing
you showed everything we hope to see in
no time at all we are going to get to
have a full concert with you and we'll
cry our hearts for you even if we can't
be there in person you killed the
audience thank you for being my oshi
[\h__\h] i just wanted to burn down the
stage i didn't want to kill everybody
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] i'm gonna get cancelled
oh no
goodbye everybody this was a nice time
with you
[Music]
i'm gonna get cancelled it's over
it's over my dream is over everything is
over
hello
thank you girlfriend
thank you so much thank you all for
letting me be your aussie i'm always so
happy to hear those words
mai oshi
my favorite words
my favorite combination of words
my oshi
[Music]
it feels
magical
that's me
thank you
[Music]
guys
i need to close the chat
too
i can't i can't i can't buy my chat
[Music]
no
no no no there's too much love here calm
down
you are too down bad
in an innocent cessal way you love me
too much
you love me too much kiana
yeah
as a class empire would say
you guys
like me too much
okay come back
come back come back
i'll come back
[Music]
soon
why are onions so beloved
maybe it's the thing with onions
aqua sempai is onion i am onion we are
onion
you guys love onions you like onion
rings
onions
[Music]
five onion rings
onion
[Music]
no we're not saying union we're saying
onion
[\h__\h] unions
[Music]
for the pinky i've never been more proud
to call you my let's see really
what about what about the time
with the rose bump huh
you're seriously amazing out there
oh thank you
what about the time
with the rose bomb and stuff and when i
killed those bosses and atelier
[Music]
let's not get ahead of ourselves why was
that more amazing what are you trying to
say
was that was that did you when you're
more proud then because i know you were
really proud of me back then
did this top how proud you were back
then it was more amazing what
this which one this one this performance
more amazing than
what i did in
italian
you use that bugged item really good why
did you have to phrase it like that that
sounds as if i cheated
there was still some amount of skill
necessary okay
and understanding how to craft it to its
maximum potential in the first place
yeah and if you don't
believe in that then you should go talk
to motion because motion is on my side
when it comes to that
[Music]
okay my performance is stopped okay
uh-huh
creative usage of game mechanics
okay for people who don't know this is
our old story i played um
ryzen's atelier
on stream
over a year ago
or so
and you gotta be an alchemist there you
gotta
make items
to fight and you can also fight without
items but
um those items are really strong and
it took me a long time to really
get good
at the game even though it's a fairly
easy game
but
but then i [\h__\h] rocked it okay
where did the time go good question man
it's been so long
i'm just assuming it's over a year yeah
i'm assuming
i love the btm2
[Music]
need to check out the streams if you if
you like atelier games and you haven't
watched those streams yet then yeah go
ahead they're really um chill and i
think i introduced a lot of new people
to the atelier series
and we had some really comfy
wholesome
times
while i was streaming that i think
[Music]
it was a really cute game it was also
the game that made me stop saying
ties did i say ties
i can't believe i was saying ties back
then instead of pies i always said thick
ties
what the [\h__\h] now that seems incredible
to me
my english always was really good but
how come i always said ties
i fixed that other things i will not fix
like biome i will always i will always
say biome
because it's
the better pronunciation
i just can't change the way i say iron
even if i wanted to
i don't even know anymore what it's
supposed to sound like iron
iron iron
onion
you don't really say the art do you
yeah but no i will continue to say iron
i earn i earn i earn that sounds [\h__\h]
stupid
no it's iron you guys don't know english
what the [\h__\h]
ah you guys just don't know english
aluminum
no aluminium aluminum aluminium
one of them is true
[Music]
i say lyric is weird
oh [\h__\h] off
[Music]
lyricist
lyricist lyricist lyricist shut up
[Laughter]
[Music]
you don't know
anything about the english language i am
from whole life english wouldn't i know
how to pronounce english words i mean
they wouldn't hire me if i didn't know
that i don't deserve that thank you
lyric is shut up shut up
oh man
[Music]
i have a point right
they're both correct oh
it's
oh
aluminium there's a german italian dude
saying it or aluminium
aluminum as a computer
[Music]
aluminium coated
aluminium
containing aluminium
okay americans
aluminium acetate
aluminium airframe oh you're the uk
person
aluminium airframe
aluminium airframe aluminium
aluminum oh they say it differently
so you guys just can't always assume
that the way you say it is the correct
way
there is also chiara english which is
just as legitimate
as
any other english pronunciation
legitimate
legitimate okay
[Laughter]
anyway
[Music]
hello
how many more am i gonna read today huh
um it's been four hours i'm getting more
simultaneous
war sister shire
uh
that's probably worse
which worship [\h__\h]
something like that
war sister sure
[Laughter]
auditorium these are all correct you
can't tell me that's wrong cartographer
cartographer
i only have about 150 left oh but a lot
of them are a big one so i had to take
more time laces sliced
debris
some of these i can't be fooled with
anymore
doing great oh thank you really
uh indubitably
i
i always struggle with that one cute
chiropractic probably
lester yeah
okay i i say that japanesey because
just because because it sounds stupid in
english and it's originally a japanese
word uh
i would say
career okay or what's what
how do you want me to say it carray okay
[Laughter]
cantelope maury
carrie okay
no no no no no no it's cut out okay it's
a japanese word
yes i am proud of my pronunciations
because the only right way to pronounce
things
the only right way
yes
[Music]
give us some difficult german words
uh every german word is difficult for
you guys to pronounce
um
[Music]
even austria is difficult for you guys
to say
first
because people really seem to have a
hard time to pronounce
the ones of the dots above
him no not ostrich
[Music]
i would like to order a
levaka semba and with cocaine
please
a
maybe even a castle customer but i don't
really like it with i like the normal
basic ass because uh libertas not the
castle because
[Music]
how do you say mcdonald's uh
we say
meki
i mean the the we we like to say
i mean if we say the whole thing that we
would say mcdonald's probably but
we like to shorten it to maki
in japanese i like to shorten it to maku
makudo
mak
but who cares about that we're at a
[\h__\h] kfp yo
don't advertise other
other
fashion franchises
anyway
where was i sunday comics duncan not
applicable thank you for the pinky my
aussie was on stage let's go yes that
was finally part of it finally thank you
god applicable
thank you very much
uh rp wn kt
thank you oh thank you for letting me be
your aussie right now
anthony webb thank you for the pinky
you're amazing you're an emperor chicken
thank you
thank you very much
i appreciate that
i did my best
seventh
i can't stop crying my ocean is a real
idol those moves and oh my god the 3d is
so cute
sorry i want to say something more
meaningful but i'm shaking in my brain
ah
understandable relatable
yeah
that's okay i think i understand what
you're trying to say you're trying to
say you love me i love you too
you thank you
you get to the more emotional part oh no
my [\h__\h] ht thank you hd
thanks for the membership welcome
empty bottle of monsters thank you for
the red super chat
yeah you burnt the stage up kia joe yes
i did thank you for sharing your work
your love and your dream with your
chickens we love you and we'll always
support you i'm proud to call you my
aussie
ah
can we do a counter of how many times
chimpkins say
that i'm there or she
and that they're proud of me and that
they love me
you're making me blush
making me blush man
stop i need to censor it
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
i'll give you one of those grandma
kisses or aunt kisses that
the kids never like they're like no
don't you uh don't kiss me
[Music]
congratulations on accomplishing one of
your dreams kiara you were amazing
you're chewing mine
[Music]
failed
thank you jim tracy
[Laughter]
oh man
yeah i i know a lot of you guys said
that i can take off that my list like
everything i take off everything off my
list
um
which i guess is true but
i'm definitely not done
like
i'm not satisfied so we're gonna keep on
going we're gonna keep on working hard
and keep on doing my best
keep on trying to make more dreams come
true a new list yes concert solo concert
whole live english concert uh official
unit with nancy
first album yeah there's so many things
time to make a new list exactly
true maybe i should maybe i should
true
i mean i already have new goals in my
mind we just need to write it down i
guess
thank you jim tracy
dominique k thank you for the pinky
thank you
how did it feel for you kf is
collectively dead we won't stop happy
crying i won't stop crying
stop
it
[Music]
how can i go for able to use super chats
it's it's so
so too much love
oh
man
what are you flexing about not crying
huh
you feel cool now
stop you're exaggerating guys
[Music]
i like sandwich the performance with
crying bread what
i survived and i could not stop smiling
good to know
it's been a year and a half you mean
since we've been waiting for this
yeah
opening super chat now
over my dead body
no
i don't want to read super chats
anymore
i feel bad about not being able to say
anything besides thank you
i feel bad about it
i can't say anything besides thank you
pretty please are you really asking for
me to open up super chips are you guys
insane you guys want to go bankrupt or
something
oh my god
no
keep it no no no
maybe if i finish these today
which i don't plan on finishing them
do it
nina
one minute
[\h__\h] no you you take it as a challenge
then i'll be [\h__\h] overwhelmed
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no
oh
i can't stop yawning
tomorrow
tomorrow night i could be
[Music]
okay come on let's do this fruitful
thank you for the rest of the chat mwah
my aussie you're amazing we got to see
your dance moves i had the peepee in the
now
you
can't be so proud of you raymond kiana
glory to kfc we love you tanjo love you
too thank you for all
thank you so much
[Music]
it's it's a german
way of saying
uh
that you're crying um by saying you know
you know how you say uh
in japanese you say
that you sweat from your eyes this is
kind of like it but you say you're
peeing from your eyes it's kind of weird
it sounds weird when i try to explain it
like that but it's a it's a way of
saying i'm crying
so i said you
thank you fro from
[Music]
er
only fire chicken should i translate the
first part of your name as well
a korean part
it's the same in korean
thank you for the red super chats
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you
after all this time we can finally see
you on the big stage never thought i
would feel so proud for someone i've
only seen from the other side of the
screen
yeah it is kind of
it's crazy right it's crazy i think that
i i think i understand how you guys feel
um
yeah because i used to be an idol fan
and and i was very proud of them for the
things they did
yeah i think i get it thanks for the
membership welcome
thank you tonya
meliton listen thank you soon for the
red super chat it's raining
congratulations tanjo finally i can't
find words to describe how happy i feel
right now you're amazing on stage you
really killed it boss i'm so happy to be
alive right now and i've witnessed your
great 3d w love your kiana love people
you guys are praising me so much
[Music]
you guys surprising me too much
no
[Music]
you praised me too much
no
i don't know what to say
who may not be
it's like no
no understand by his song about praising
was even more than that
[Music]
it's not alive
and i can't stop yawning
why is there no oxygen in this [\h__\h]
room
i'm gonna put on pajama pants
feeling
cold issues
okay cozy
um
yeah
anyway
joe knight thank you for the red super
chat um
your love for others was so infectious
that in maine we purchased concert
tickets so i could feel what you poured
your heart and soul into oh
now i've been enlightened and i hope to
see more of your amazing performances
than you thank you for everything oh
and that makes me think that a lot of
you guys probably
probably don't listen to
this kind of music in your free time and
you don't really follow like any other
idols
um and a lot of you guys are probably
really new to this kind of culture and
all that so
yeah i'm glad i could capture
your interest and your attention
so much
maybe you understand now even more than
before why i was an idol otaku
um
i would have never bought my ticket
thank you
it was more on the k-pop side oh that's
somewhere there similar
hmm i appreciate the idol concerts but i
wouldn't really call myself idol fan a
year ago
i knew violence but i didn't really get
involved until i found you
never listen to j-pop before you
when you stand mamamoo when you were
listening to k-pop huh
close enough
i'm still a metal head mostly
see it's it's unbelievable that people
who usually like listen i don't know too
heavy metal or something like that now
look at my performance with a j-pop song
and are like wow let's go girl let's go
yes
isn't that fantastic fascinating
yeah
hinotorii
maybe maybe some metal elements with
really really strong
guitar and
drums maybe
maybe maybe maybe
maybe
maybe with a lot of fantasy
not man okay
i said elements not that it's a metal
song
[Music]
i've been sitting for too long
not even a particle of metal oh you [\h__\h]
i got the metal fans angry
kiwana don't call that kind of bubbly
tape of [\h__\h]
metal ewe
and say that and say it was metal
thank you joe knight thank you thank you
thank you i'm glad you found an interest
in all of that thanks to me and and i
hope you will continue supporting my
activities
[Music]
australian mate
sorry for flipping your seasons around
so bad if you chiara your singing was
perfect and your choreo was amazing you
made me cry so hard
congratulations
[Music]
i think you feel like you have a lot of
tsuntu moments but you seemed to have
been very dead
when you sent that
super chat
thank you
you sweetie
sweet potato cutie pie
i'm glad
i could make you proud and make you cry
i guess in a good way
oy i'm not so lol that's what it soon
would say
[Laughter]
thank you thank you
hmm
now stop crying i'll i'll i'll go there
and i'll poke your eyes
sorry i'm that's scary and i i'm having
a hard time dealing with all this
kindness um
i i'll give you a hug
yes
i'll give you a hug
cruella
those moves were fire
big congrats on the first of many great
concerts thank you
yes hopefully many many more
but
i'm very very very happy with how things
went thank you thank you very much i'm
glad you liked my moves yeah as i said
yesterday during my members only stream
this
this is only
a small small part
i can do
even more
busy
detailed
choreos
um
but then again um
i'm not quite sure i haven't uh
tested the limits quite yet with 3d i'm
not quite sure how
um but it did capture
very well but i mean like with more
intricate hand movements
and all that
i would like to experiment a bit more
yeah
it's a front wall frontal walkover front
walkover
yeah yeah yeah yeah more trackers more
finger trackers you need to need the
fingers to be captured really really
well
with the kind of
choreos that i want to do
[Music]
anyway
it looks pretty good though i think
yeah pretty accurate
and
cool
you killed it boss loved the
choreography i was wondering how you
were going to dance to inhibitory but
you pulled it off hey
i wonder how much it's going to cost to
fix the roof on that building what
because i i raised the roof is that what
it is
thank you
yeah
um
i did say yesterday also in members only
stream but i'll say it again um for
hinotoni i asked for a somewhat simple
choreography to have a focus on the
singing parts at least for the verse
uh and the bridge
um
yeah and then
some parts like the intro and the dance
break that you guys didn't really see
much of because i was going
um those are maybe a bit more detailed
um because like i wanted it to fit the
instrumental
um but mostly it's still fairly simple
so heart challenger for example has
a way more
um
bouncy and energetic and exhausting
choreo
oh
yeah
um but yes that is yes yes yes
you guys are just not used to seeing
choreos like this huh
[Music]
maybe eventually i'll be able to show
you guys a good difference where where
the difference is
you bet
you did bet that i would sing heart
challenger
oh
i think heart challenge would have been
really hyped too but it wouldn't have
stood out so much because there were so
many cutesy songs throughout the concert
um
and a cool song
i think makes more impact in that
situation
maybe
[Music]
or at least it's the the way i want to
represent myself
for the first time in 3d because like
that's also why i made hinotoni
um in the first place
um
i remember saying back then
i don't know how you guys actually felt
but i felt like you guys would have
expected me to have my first single be a
cute one like heart challenger for
example but i wanted the first song that
i put out there
um to be a cool one to show a cool side
of me
and the same thing goes for 3d if my
first 3d performance
um is a
singing one then i want it to be a cool
song
i used to
i used to always want to be perceived as
cute and i still want to be perceived as
cute but i also wanna be perceived as
cool i wanna be perceived as everything
uh i just wanna i guess i just wanna
show that i
have many different sides to myself
maybe
um
[Music]
that sounds weird
uh that sounds weird
multi-fuck it yeah
fast
faceted faceted
multifaceted
that sounded good that sounded like
proper english to me
nice
nice i didn't even listen to a reference
[Applause]
thank you for the rent
performance
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you very much can you dance like
that
i i think um
i think i could teach you a lot of the
moves just
just uh
a few moves like the the kick
and the turn
are
a bit more advanced
i have terrible rhythm i have rhythm is
a minimum requirement
in
the kfb dance school minimum requirement
a feeling for rhythm
stanky lick
oh
body rolls oh yeah well
um so hirotoni is a cool choreo heart
challenger is a
a fun cute one
sparks i don't know yet but i do want to
have
eventually a song where a somewhat sexy
choreo fits
nicely too
i will not twerk though
[Laughter]
i will not twerk unless they give my
butt
jiggle physics
actually yeah why the butts
in in 3d and all that never have jiggle
physics that
boobies always do even here and live to
the
what about the butts man where are my
jiggle wiggles on my butt
uh
i'll i'll request it
oh
speaking of did you guys see um this was
kind of overshadowed but did you guys
see that uh live 2d
uh 2.0 is where we're currently at in
whole life it's turning into 3.0 did you
see
there was um during the concert there
was a kind of like advertisement
however
um
i don't want you guys to get excited
about it yet because
until it's our turn
it will
take a long time you'll probably forget
about it
until we actually get it
yeah
it's um
it's gonna be you know it's gonna take
some time until everyone
um
gets it and it's yeah
uh
um prioritized by senpai
generations
but there's a lot of cool things
um to look forward to like finally
uh you know um
we're not um um we're gonna be able to
like
uh have like tracking on like for
example uh you know how um ina has like
a
uh
a little animation of a drawing tablet
uh with her hand moving
okay she kind of made that herself but
we'll be able to do stuff like that and
with controllers and and keyboard and
mouse
and
implement it into our model
like it doesn't have to be like stuff
that the fans made for us or whatever
you can already see some samples
from matsuri senpai hatama and so on
because they were
showcased in the
3.0
showcase yeah
yeah keyboards and stuff i think it will
track the input of what buttons we push
and all that and how we move the mouse
and all that yeah
and and yeah official controller hands
yeah
oh i was i didn't expect that but that's
really cool
yeah
um
[Music]
and i don't know what else yeah
expressions more expressions like crying
and pouting and sticking out your tongue
and all that and moving a little bit
forward and backwards i gotta be honest
though
um
there's like
it's hard to explain it maybe it depends
on the record but i've seen some live 2d
models that
um like move so much back and forth and
all that
that it just like
i don't know i didn't really like
it
i feel like it was too much at some
point i feel like it felt like too much
but maybe it depends on the rigor maybe
a certain rigor can make it look
perfect
[Music]
bit distracting visually
maybe yeah i think it was just too much
over over animated yeah
and and i a lot of the
those over animated ones are also like
too too wobbly i think yeah i trust cafe
papa definitely i trust our our reikers
i trust them
because like i have a lot of movement
but i think my movements are really
sharp i see a lot of different riggers
who implement a lot of movement but it's
like it always feels like it's kind of
like lagging behind like so soft
and like really smoothed out and that
makes it look so blue like slow motion i
don't know it's hard to describe do you
guys know what i mean
like jelly yeah like jelly exactly
so i just hope it won't look like that
but i'm excited for the expressions
um
there will be more expressions
yes the pouting one i'm looking forward
to a pouting one but as i said
actually you guys and me we shouldn't
get excited about it yet because it's
gonna take a long time
[Music]
i'll be excited about it anyways you
can't stop
me well you know they gotta do it for
all of us and obviously they're gonna
start with the seniors and then go down
to the juniors it's just gonna take a
long long time
a janky movement can be a bit
distracting i think so too yeah but so
far from what i've seen
from them
from the preview it looked really good
yeah
so let's hope for the best
[Music]
ah i cannot answer that question
so i will not read it out loud
um
no no no fast track no no no no
wish
[Music]
and he made a cat
i think that will be something that i
have to take care of myself
better lip sync
i think the
mouth movements are fine i mean
you know
i've been i've been feeling like mine
could
use some improvements
after looking at them for a long time
because it's always like ah
oh it doesn't happen very often until um
unless i force force it
force it
force it you know what i mean
i'm happy with my
with my raking
i have i have the best
best papa cafe papa
yeah i'm just very
[Music]
i'm getting tired
oh
it's nap time for me
it's nap time
it's not time can we lay down i have a
bed behind me so
can we take a nap
we don't know
i'm almost halfway through wow
that's pretty impressive
didn't even take that much time to go
you mean halfway through for that
specific stream super chat so for all of
them
super chat rating twitter space hmm that
would be comfortable but
difficult to get to reach all the people
that need to hear it
oh it's already 8 p.m
damn
wait what it felt like it was just i
don't know
1 p.m why is it 8 p.m what the [\h__\h]
it feels like it's 1 p.m
spaces are not archived but i guess you
could like
manually archive it by recording it
oh my face is getting tired from smiling
so much why you guys make me smile so
much
i mean that's one reason why these
super jack readings make me so tired
because like i read them
enthusiastically and smile so much
[Music]
imagine smiling for
for
almost five
hours smiling and laughing
is actually pretty exhausting
[Music]
they have an archive option oh i didn't
realize that
i haven't used it much yet
i'll read a few more
big sweet thank you soon silly fellow
thank you for the red super chat thank
you you were amazing thank you
so kind someone uh told me
thank you in polish just a few minutes
ago and i already forgot sorry otherwise
i would say it i'm polish right now
uh
i wanted to write one but my brain was
fried couldn't put sentences together
to be honest i felt similar after
um after the concert when i was trying
to write uh a tweet i was thinking
pretty long about it i wanted to say a
lot but i
i it was difficult
[Music]
hopefully
like in german okay
i'm too lazy now
anyway thank you very much
we have a korean super chat next
with no text for the korean name
oh
you can hear
[Music]
thank you
thank you very much
for supporting me thank you
i'm so proud of you boss just so
overwhelmed you did it you shared the
stage with your senpais and your aussie
everything was worth all the ups and
downs for this one moment you killed it
i love you so much
your moves you dance divine
exquisite
could it even be
thank you so much keyblade you seem you
seem very much
in love
thank you
thank you so much
for the kind words
yeah um
[Music]
to be honest it doesn't feel so much
like i shared the stage because i was
alone out there and
i wasn't in japan for it so
it still feels kind of like lonely um
so it looks it looks like we shared a
stage but it didn't quite feel like it
i hope i hope i hope next time i can be
there
yeah
and not do it from europe
but go to japan and then have some duets
together
not be
performing alone only
because what am i for what am i in the
in the in the company like this for if i
wanted to do things all alone i could i
could go windy
but i'm here
to have a good time
with other whole life members to create
something together and all that yeah
so
yeah but this time obviously time was
limited
um everyone got a solo song and to be
honest i'm really really really thankful
and grateful that we got that
opportunity to begin with to get a whole
solo song solo time in that concert
instead of just i don't know doing one
one song together which would have been
fun too because we would have been
together
but i don't know if that would have even
worked out but
um yeah this this way we all got our
time to shine and make an impression got
some special time
so i'm really happy that we got to do
that no country wrote no thank you no no
ah
[Music]
the light sticks are beautiful yeah
it's so
beautiful and they go up and down and up
and down and up and down and up and down
yeah country world sorry serious kiara
hates country votes
thank you swarovski plate
right now
nene diesel duncation forward super chat
my heartbeats cannot stop you singing
dancing everything is perfect amazing
job buzz congrats on your first 3d stage
oh wait i saw your video i think
your reaction video was so cute
[Music]
you're so into it i loved it
i loved it
i'm not mixing up people now right i
think i'm pretty sure it was you
i think it was a it was a private video
or something like that or it was only on
twitter
not mixing things up right nene diesel
are you here now i'm pretty sure pretty
sure it was you
thank you for the membership thank you
soon
thank you nene diesel i'm glad you
enjoyed it thank you so much
yeah i did my best i'm glad it paid off
thank you thank you
[Music]
yeah um fauna stream starting in two
two and a half hours i think um
we're fine the koala universe thank you
so much sodom thank you for the rest of
attack
thank you thank you thank you no text
with it but thank you for your support
very generous thank you soon
plan of lots of fancy thank you for the
pinky
for fleeting instead i was spirited away
to a place bathed in the warm radiant
thing was it for approximately uh four
minutes and a few seconds
bearing witness to that beautiful light
is the moment i'll never forget thank
you for everything you do tanto thank
you for never giving up no matter what
thank you
[Music]
in some way
i already did give up before
before her life
you guys know that because i talked
about it before
but there was like
in one one tiny tiny tiny flame
still
left
flickering
and waiting to be ignited
into a bonfire
yeah it's it's understandable after you
try
for such a long time
in so many different ways
eventually feeling like
it's it's over and giving up
is
it might be sad but in some ways it's
also realistic and
at some point like maybe you need to
accept that
something is just not happening
maybe
if it's something unrealistic i don't
know
um
if you really tried for like 10 or so
years then maybe maybe it's time to move
on but then then again i mean
look at me
i
i mean i'm not doing exactly what
exactly hundred percent what i
wanted to do
but i'm doing something that's
just as amazing and fulfilling and makes
me happy
and is somewhat similar to
what i originally wanted to do it's
close enough yeah
and
yeah i'm not
not uh
i'm like actually maybe it's even better
in some ways it's even better
so
i want to tell people to never give up
but i understand that at some point it
might be the
good thing to give up and move on to
something else
if you've just spent so much time on it
i don't know it's hard to
say cause like you can't you can't put
like just hang on to something for your
whole [\h__\h] life
if it's just not happening but you
should at least
give it everything you got
for as long as you feel like you can
and if you'll get to a point where you
personally feel like you're you've tried
everything you could
really 100 and you would be
fine with
uh moving on to something new because
that's a that's
even though i was really really down
um i was
i was
ready i think to move on
so at least do it until you're
until you feel like you're at a place
where
you think it's better to
find a new goal or new dream that maybe
is more in your reach
yeah there are limits as much as we like
to say you can do anything
i'm sorry this is maybe out of character
me saying this is maybe out of character
but
as much as i am really really always
like fight oh my god
i am also a very realistic person i like
to
look at things very realistic
and it's yeah i think it's also
dangerous to
um
like
waste too much time when i say too much
time i'm really speaking of like
like 10 20 years
yeah because because like
you only live once you know you only
live once and you gotta make the best
out of the time that you're on this
earth
[Music]
and
even if you
if you try hard sometimes
things are just locked like a dlc
but you can't even pay for it
what you need is luck okay sometimes you
even need money for certain kind of
success but
um yeah there's sometimes there's just
barriers that you cannot
overcome with
what you currently have what the methods
and
yeah
the material that you're working with
like
sometimes it's not your fault it's just
luck and and for example
if you try to do something that's like
a business that
a business or a career or something that
only works in certain requirements like
let's say you can only do it until a
certain age i don't know become
i mean
[Music]
you would say that for example modeling
you can do at any age because they
always need models for any age but but
but if you want to be like a supermodel
that walks on um victoria's secret
catwalk then let's be real
you're probably not gonna
start doing that with 40.
you know and that that's the point where
you should probably
start being realistic
and oh yeah athletes for example yeah
athletes
you gotta start early with that
but hey
feel free to still do uh some kind of
um sport if you if you think it's fun
for you and and it's good for your body
so just do it
yeah you might you may not end up in the
olympics but
yeah
and certain goals are maybe a little bit
too crazy um
yeah for actors stuff like that
if you want to be a hollywood actor
it's
easier at least it's easier to do if
you're like
in your 20s or teens or something like
that
to to really reach that
unfortunate unfortunately that's just
how it is like these kind of
careers they want to see young people
and and yeah that's
that's when you got to be realistic
they want to see young people
unfortunately
you gotta be fresh
out of the oven it's not always like
that obviously there's people who reach
success like that as a singer as an
actor or as a whatever later on but
that's
that's being lucky i don't know maybe
they won in some kind of america's
next superstar show or something like
that
yeah
where's my point my point my point
my point is
i don't know how did we even get to this
i don't know how we got to this
about not giving up i think that was the
point yeah that i never give up but i as
i said i have a point where where i
fought okay
it's
i have to be realistic realistic i have
to move on
but then i got really lucky
then i got really really lucky without
that luck
i would have been lost at sea
[Music]
certain people
they're not that lucky and all their
talent and skills
unfortunately go unnoticed which is not
fair it's just not fair
but i recommend you guys to
work hard towards your dreams and goals
and if you don't have a dream or goal
that's okay too
i don't know how old you are but maybe
you're too young to really have a really
clear image if you're in your head
or maybe you're at an age where
you think you're done but
there's still other things you can do
maybe you need to
find new hobbies and interests to also
connect that to a new goal and dream
yeah
but also it's okay i think to be honest
it's also okay to just not have a huge
dream or something just live your life
comfortably
yeah
i think that's fine too like when i
worked in a normal job
i did not try or like aspired to be
like the the
big next ceo in that job or whatever i
just wanted to keep the position i was
in because it was comfortable
and then on the side well well that job
was going so comfortably i was having a
great time with my hobbies like going to
anime conventions or whatever
i was having fun elsewhere doing my best
elsewhere
[Music]
what would you do if you knew that you
can't reach your goal well that is
something that can you really can you
really
judge that because normally you
personally are more
more negative about
what you think you can do
you gotta look at it objectively if you
think that you can objectively say
realistically
that you can't do what you want to do
then perhaps it's
okay to find something else
but
yeah
usually usually you judge yourself to
the heart and you're like i can't do
that i can't do that but are you even
trying are you even trying
what maybe it's me what do you mean
what do you mean sounds familiar what do
you mean
what did i do
i'm content with my life but everybody
around me always tells me to aspire for
more i'm perfectly comfortable and can
take care of myself that sounds really
healthy the way you say that sounds
really healthy
sounds good to me
you sound happy
break it down into milestones that is
good advice too yeah if you have a goal
that you think that it's like
unreachable
then go baby steps
don't
don't expect that from one day to
another you're gonna reach the top of
those stairs
um you gotta go floor above floor step
by step
eventually you'll end up at the top of
the skyscraper
[Music]
no the building doesn't have an elevator
the building doesn't have an elevator
no
you're too spoiled
[Music]
all right
all right all right all right let's do
this um
where was i
the gamer cream donkey shoe black
fortune duncan for the red super chat
it says you've made it i'm proud and
privileged to be one of your friends oh
i cried and got out of my chair while my
friends were watching
shouted hard too
jesus you were so incredible
jesus wasn't the whole life fruitfest
kimono can't wait for more in the future
love you never give up thank you
when was jesus on which day
got you i got you
i got you
[Laughter]
jesus is the original idol somehow yes
for some people yes
oh man
i can't keep on getting away with it
ah yeah god was there matsuri senpai
true
she's not jesus
jesus
whoo
thank you for the membership welcome
thank you black person thank you so much
love you too
[Music]
ricky tones thank you for the pinky i
may not have been here from the very
start but i'm happy to be here now and
see you live on stage you are so
beautiful up there and [\h__\h] amazing
and i'm proud to call you my aussie i
look forward to seeing you after more of
some people like you
once again calling me there we'll see
you again
thank you winky toons
viva la wikitunes
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
thank you
sweetheart
and it's okay not being there from the
start otherwise there would be no growth
navidad made it for the red super chat
oh god i'm crying that was beautiful my
aussie is an idol you're surprised
you wrapped that stage boss your full
power was on display those moves for
fire you've waited for this day for so
long i'm so proud of how far you've come
kiana
thank you
[Music]
yeah i'm proud to
i'm proud to
thank you guys for following me
for this whole whole journey and
experience or at least this part of my
journey
in your picture it does look like i am
jesus
thank you fried squirrel for a red super
chat viva
those moves those poses pancho you
deserve the world and more i'm shaking
right now you're the best tend to kill
our love thank you
i don't
no
i can't i can't i can't i love you too
thank you fried squirrel
[Music]
thank you for the reservation i thought
i was ready i wasn't trying not to break
down at work oh
yeah that was amazing live hino tony is
a whole other beast too bad they nerfed
your skirt they didn't nerf my skirt
they nerfed what's underneath the skirt
but yeah live pinot tony was really
really cool
um it really like blasted out there it
got like a lot extra power it was
already a strong one i would say
but i think it got a lot of extra power
too
um i i asked uh gojo the producer of the
song i asked did you sing it did you see
it and he was like yeah it was really
cool life band was awesome
yeah i'm glad i'm glad
yeah
thank you soon every another cult
elf on dance thank you and simply cinco
danke
foreign
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat amazing
performance thank you attention
thank you for watching
without an audience that would be
nothing thank you very much
[Music]
yeah i was thinking so too maybe i could
do a hike with some some hand poses oh
yeah waving waving was possible they did
show that waving was possible
maybe there's some other extra options
yeah
let's see what they'll do blowing kiss
ah was that a thing too
eating chicken
do a flip
thank you brian
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah who might choose it could be
useful
[Music]
no
i wouldn't flip you off
i really don't want to play for you off
no
i i feel um
this is interesting
i
carelessly say [\h__\h] all the time
while
apparently in america and so on you guys
are more careful about that but when it
comes to flipping someone off
i
i can't
not not as a joke if i'm really [\h__\h]
mad at someone
okay
but
no
that's that's where i draw the line
i don't know why your fingers shut up
looking for the top get out of here
[Music]
i don't know i feel like the gesture
is
very insulting
it has more of an impact to me than
saying
swear words
hmm
[Music]
yeah it's supposed to be insulting
they should meet us americans well yeah
i mean of course there's like a lot of
people who just swear whatever but but
but but then like
how do i explain this
my gold is under streamers
english-speaking streamers
they seem to have like a good control
over it because
yeah they have a filter
and they feel like a filter is necessary
apparently
while
i
would like a filter but i can't hold
myself back
oh but yeah a gesture like that and
that's that's at least something i can
control
and i will not do that
[Music]
i don't think we'll get anywhere talking
about this
um make penguins duncan merry pippins
thank you for the words of a chad you
you did okay not like i cried or felt
proud or anything
not like i thought your voice or
choreography was amazing or that i was
screaming my head off i totally wasn't
thinking about how much this meant to
you while you were out there or how much
i love you congratulations
no you're a
but [\h__\h] so obvious
so obviously what do you think
help me
potential dies
thank you mary pippins i think i
understand the secret message that
you're trying to convey to me
thank you
er
what was that again
[Music]
oh it says i'm happy to be alive you're
the best that was great thank you
thank you
i'm glad that some korean bros were
watching as well
thank you very much
[Music]
please continue following my journey and
supporting me okay
santa maria thank you for the pinky you
set that stage on fire yes i did
thank you
dominique is an extra light thank you so
much
thank you for the red super chat you put
it on and
an unforgettable and legendary
performance i'm happy that so many
people saw just how incredible and
multi-talented you are i respect and
admire you so much thank you for
existing your beautiful phoenix
congratulations love you so much proud
of you thank you
yeah guys it felt really good to finally
be recognized
and and praised by so many
for my performance um
for me
an idol
not only for me this is really just what
an idol is in japan
is
not a perfect singer or a perfect dancer
if they are both then holy [\h__\h] top idol
but
is basically someone who can do
dancing
singing
and entertaining all
together
um professionally
um
yeah have like a decent level of all of
that um they're just great performance
and
and and a multi-talented people who
spread
happiness and energy and all that make
other people smile and make other people
happy it's a good package yeah it's not
like a super insane singer super insane
dancer
it's it's a package of everything
and
and yeah they're they're basically
there to make other people happy
that's an idol
and
um
i hope
i
i hope i hope people
see that when they see me
hmm
that's why for me personally i don't
need to be
the
next celine dion or ariana grande and i
don't need to be a professional
dancer who learned ballet or whatever
i
always aspired my whole life to be an
idol
like hello project like my favorite
idols
[Music]
i want to be
what they are because there's a reason
why i loved them so much
i enjoyed going to their concert so much
and got so much happiness from them
yeah i forgot what my point was
thank you
[Music]
i think i'm gonna end it soon i can read
the rest during
alden ring because we won't be
um
taking super chats then either
you know what i'll give you a minute of
super chat
time afterwards but one sec
if you really really need to get a
message across
the village and demon ah
no go gentlemen
come samnita
for the red super chat thank you let me
translate
it
yes
yes that's me it says the phoenix idol
who did not give up despite numerous
setbacks exists and her name is
thank you
how did you know
thank you very much
thank you that is very very very sweet
of you ah you're here hello i love i
love your profile picture
i mean it's a bit scary but it is a it
is a tanooki
it's really cute i love tanookies
oh
thank you for your kinder it's no no
come sanita oh now i can sleep oh you
were waiting i'm sorry i'm sorry
sleep kiss
thank you and good night uh wait wait
[Music]
hello my neighbors
hello my neighbors hello
raccoon
gentlemen
cute
very very cute
[Music]
good night good night korean bros i'm
gonna end it soon anyway
and lars kristensen christensen thank
you spaghetti and blankets
thank you
to see you set the stage on fire with
vino to your performance was
indescribable
i'm so glad you became my aussie it may
be almost 3 a.m for me when i ride this
but my energy level is for the roof
thousand percent energy level
thank you afriam's nothing byra
week
mate every week
but thank you thank you thank you yes
i think my hinotory performance was
really strong i'm glad i i gave it
everything i had
not everyone has a bad sleep schedule
i thought everyone who watches kiwawa
has a [\h__\h] sleep schedule
wake up at six by six or seven okay if
yeah i mean
if you watch my streams normally
then you gotta get up at six seven to
watch me
yeah
yeah yeah let me know the concept was at
the time
that i usually am in dream wonderland
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
okay continue
thank you for the red super chat oh my
god i can't stop crying my oh she's
shining on the stage tension cycle thank
you
kfp
cycle mwah and your father love you
lord evil thank you for the pinky sorry
for the late super chat
while still sobbing and talking with
other kfp seeing all the screen shoots
shoot i was supposed to take a lot of
screenshots myself but i got distracted
by your performance well done buzz you
killed it
i'm surprised that you guys even got to
take a screenshot the first time
like i i would first want to focus
and then watch it again later for
screenshots
[Music]
yeah but some of you got good shots
anyway thank you
for all the nice shots thank you soon
[Music]
today's life was the best of all you
shined the best
you're biased
obviously i think all the hard work
tantra has done has been rewarded it's
hard to express all of this emotion even
with a super chat please continue to be
our brightest phoenix in the future
[Music]
thank you
lunchbox thank you soon
gee thank you for the red super chat yay
that was absolutely amazing seeing you
on that stage is a dream come true
please keep on dancing and singing i'm
so proud to call you my aussie
i will continue now that i've been given
this body that i can use
i want to make more out of it
can't let that sexy hot flaming body go
to waste yeah yeah yeah you agree don't
you thank you
thank you
i don't know what to say i was
overwhelmed the moment you popped up on
stage i didn't have a moment to think
you took my breath away and the tears
just stopped oh i was engulfed in the
flames of our shining idol you owned
that stage and kicked it he killed it
[\h__\h] don't tell the police blazer
don't tell them don't say it out loud
they might be watching
please shh
thank you
thank you trevor to thank you soon
[Music]
i'm glad i could make you proud and
enjoy the show you've been around for so
long and finally finally you get to see
me moving like that
fluently
in 3d must have been beautiful
thank you
for watching and supporting
trevor g dankester lunchbox down kitchen
blue duncan alvaro duncan
[Music]
there's not much okay i mean there's a
little bit much left
ah
a bit more come on kiwamo
and do
[Music]
that was amazing i'm so proud of you on
being part of kfb from the beginning
yes
yes that must feel good doesn't it
you're growing up so much i'm still
crying from the happiness that i was
able to see it live holy [\h__\h] that cake
was godlike and black hole bigger than
your skirt
so i love where we go
oh yeah i don't know i don't know when
we'll get an idol outfit but um
yeah i agree um black hole too big too
much black underneath my spats
spots
underneath those shorts
those shorts are too long
we all agree on that
thank you doll thank you for being here
since the very beginning and probably
also until the end
thank you for the pinky yeah your
performance was jaw-dropping you had me
out of my chair in excitement for your
dancing and singing i had to get up and
cheer i'm so proud to be on this journey
with you and kfb
viva lucky allah
thank you
thank you for getting up yeah
i think it's it's
when people watch it at home and still
get like excited
about it and not just to sit there
quietly
i think that that really shows
how passionate you guys are about it and
and how good the performance was
thank you
thank you thank you
yeah
i hope i can see you guys vibe at a
concert
at some point yeah
[Music]
it's hyperventilating that's not good
where's your inhaler
drowsy can't thank you for the ransom
chant
oh in korean wait
wait
this voice is so kind man
thank you i feel like mommy is praising
me
thank you
[Music]
you're so sweet
so sweet
[Music]
watermelon i got you in my fridge
have you love fridge i love you
watermelon
you say so well today thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you you have sung hirotori so many times
at this point
um
it goes
it it's as smooth as butter
at this point
but i still
i still sometimes don't know the lyrics
to my own songs
but but but sound wise like
singing wise
very smooth
ignore the fact that i don't know my own
lyrics
yeah
oops
it's just because um even though i've
sang it so often i don't sing it
regularly so
your performance was incredible danger
literally kicked out of my chair i
couldn't stop the shaking of my legs
you were the most i think your legs
wanted to dance you were the most
beautiful girl on stage for me
i can't express how proud of you i am
thank you for this wonderful journey
let's make even more memories
yes that's what i was about to say
thank you
yes thanks for the memories even though
they were so great yes
thank you
the most beautiful girls dates
[Music]
no
you have those
pink
tainted rose tinted
glasses on don't you that's the word
you though keep those glasses on don't
take them off
so that hopefully you will continue to
only love me
love me love me say that you love me
fool me fool me
really is that the lyrics
why would you fool me
[Music]
would you want to fool me
follow me for me
say that you fool me
why we fool them
i can't care about
anything but you
it's a nice song though
guys i love food here i am
yeah
that's just how it goes
thank you
and this is the last one i'll read
miniature pins and john with a rainbow
thank you
er once again something like
[Music]
or something like that
wait wait
green ah it doesn't translate it here
was it
something
[Music]
there's
a miniature pincha chang
thank you
for sending the mujike
[Music]
[Laughter]
it says i'm afraid to stand this shock
but the impact of this stage crashed my
mind in a good sense
i want to say a lot about this beginning
of legends but super chat is short
you say that and yet you make no use
of all the other super chats you sent
they are completely empty
i hope tanza will always be happy and
wish every chicken all the best
you could have just used the rest of the
super jet but you chose not to
and the ending says
thank you
i
[Music]
am you very much
thank you for the music
can't believe i actually remember it
then
it's not enough super chat is short
look the rest is empty
oh you could write me a letter though if
you think that even the rainbow is not
long enough then you could write me a
letter guys you can send me letters they
will probably arrive um
eight months eight to 12 months later so
keep that in mind
um but if you go to the home live
website there's like a i think an
address where you can send fan mail too
no presents just letters but it's about
time that you guys write it so that it
arrives for christmas how about how
about writing them now for christmas
today
um
[Music]
get right on it let's go
write me those christmas letters
okay
then
about the concert that or the album
let's talk you can mention an album that
i put out at the end of the year you can
be like yo how will you put out with
such a banger girl
[Music]
so many different songs of so many
different words
and melodies
um
yeah and you sang
them so that was great
the album art was beautiful and
yeah
glad that you got to work with
those producers
good job piana
i'm happy for you
track five was a banger my favorite
track is the second one though
because all your feelings are in that
song yeah and i can so hashtag relate to
it
and triple backflip now don't pressure
me like that man
wow
okay
ah
wait i'll there's a few more another
mixed freezy warrior thank you so much
okay so this is where i'll stop after
the after the rainbow
um before the next red after the rainbow
at pet c
okay remember that
please
now do you want me to open them up again
how many more are these
still quite a bit
i could open them
but would you still want me to open them
if i said that i would read them
quietly in my private time after the
stream
right away
and not read them out loud
to save my soul and my voice
really
oh it's actually perfect because the
last super chat here on that list that i
have is from pat c
as well as the last one that i read
today is also from patsy so everything
after that patsy
it's a good it's a good border good
border
okay
okay if you want to do that under the
guarantee that there is no guarantee
that i will read it
yeah i would think that would stop some
of you
i mean i would no guarantee that i would
read it aloud i mean in a super chat
reading
yes
so only if you don't mind maybe if i if
i um have
if i still have energy
after the
elden reading super chat reading then
maybe i'll add them to my bunch
of the ones that i'll read but but the
chances are low
what about this week's schedule i'm
still streaming man i'm still streaming
i'll make it out of my screen okay
[Music]
give me a break okay turning them on
everything after pat c is
uncertain
okay
i'm gonna have this problem again where
i want to react right now
i need to ignore it
for now
yeah they're open
[Music]
um but yeah i will go make my schedule
now i'll call in and phone as stream
later and also have some food now
hopefully
yesterday to be honest i didn't make
dinner i made um
one piece of toast with some salami on
it
and
um
i ate ice cream
yeah the garlic bucket filled me up
decently so
i didn't eat anything proper yesterday i
basically ate yesterday i ate
uh two muffins
one garlic baguette
and one piece of toast of salami
wow
none of that is
the the muffins were supposed to be
breakfast but that's not proper
breakfast the growling baguette is
supposed to be a snack i guess but it's
never a lunch or a snack
oh my god and um
and
the piece of toast
is really not dinner either
recently i've been getting really really
lazy with my food
intake again
i have barely been
cooking
are you good guys
thank you guys
oh
you write that letter really nice
thank you oh man
oh my god
oh you want to get to know that lady
there
you you have it right in front of you
[Music]
thank you
i'll read them i'll read them after the
stream okay
i promise
i'm already reading them now
what
grenade launcher oh cause that's what
you like
wow
oh on the live website somewhere there
ah this takes a lot of pressure off of
me
oh
it's too sensitive
the word aussie is too sensitive
thank
you thank you
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
you guys are crazy
[Music]
hello
no no namaste
oh that is so funny
[Music]
okay okay
okay i'm gonna go now
um
remember pepsi
had to see
rainbow
oh from
[Music]
thank you
ah my first super chattering swim
oh
nostalgic man
that was really a long one
i've gotten so weak
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you guys
hey write so free you've been stopped
by
ancient powers
thank you guys thank you
okay i will go now okay
and
thank you
oh my god oh my god the people who are
writing paragraphs
are sending their super chats now
they were like girl give me a moment i'm
still writing i'm still writing
okay
are you done
[Laughter]
thank you very much
thank you thank
you i think your pencils down
yes time is over
[Music]
because they use honeycombs
that one's not that funny
[Music]
you know
proper play
yeah
okay pass the papers forward yes yes
leave the classroom now and in german we
say auf wiedersehen and goodbye goodbye
goodbye
bye bye love you guys thank you for
being so kind
i
don't know what to do with all this love
uh
it's
so much
[Laughter]
i gotta store it somewhere
need some cardboard boxes
my cats will join as well
bye bye i'm hungry i'm gonna eat some of
you guys now mmm chicken
oh thank you
for myself
[Music]
yonder
farewell
goodbye
oh if he doesn't know it
ah
what
what was it
[Music]
um i need to eat
some food and call for now
[Music]
so long very well auf wiedersehen
goodbye
i will
take
the day off
tomorrow
so goodbye
[Music]
goodbye
thank you for watching
my performance
in
the concert
what
don't take one too serious
[Music]
thank you
stop spoiling me you guys are just
too nice
i'll get like a big big big head
and uh
i'll end up being like really really
really
um
stuck up
[Music]
and i'll be like
i'm amazing and i know it
yes well head
big big head joe
big head joe
[Music]
oh
good idea turn them off yes i will