e
[Music]
good good good
morning
afternoon or is it evening
[Music]
what is going
on where is this
place what what am I doing
here the light it burns my
[Laughter]
eyes what
what's going
on oh my eyes it
burns it
burns where I
don't
what I can I can move
I can
move
oh who are these
people I've never seen them in my
[Music]
life what what's going
on in ntic
recollection oh what could this be oh
no oh no oh my God you can read those
symol I think so I don't know what's
going on but I think I think I can read
this W oh they have something over their
heads love
forever Mor
cop e
n is this what they call a status screen
I've seen I'm kind of remembering this
it's
like when you
get
isite and you can get
a status
screen is that what it is am I the
protagonist in this
world what but I also feel like I've
seen this before
[Music]
where uh it's coming back to me when
when you usually wake up in a closed
room with many people it usually ends up
with with it being
a some sort
of death game but it can't be right
everyone looks so
friendly it can't
be
right also happy
birthday oh oh no I don't know what came
over me so so a voice that wished
someone a happy
birthday what a what a weird weird
situation
we're I mean I kind of woke up in this
world without memories so I could say
I'm kind of reborn into this world
right it must
be oh someone new has
joined it's everyone's birthday
today our birthday in the new world
Happy Birthday what's my superpower I
don't know maybe maybe if I think hard
enough I can open up the status status
window that's what happens in these
kinds of things right you got a cheat
skill
and
then I become
OB
status um what do I do I have to shout
status status
window oh it's not
working menu
oh maybe say it in say it in
Japanese
uh
status it open my
inventory wow
wow it can't be wait I have
a I have a inventory in a different
dimension no way that's
op that's not stat yeah but it opened my
inventory you think my pronounce the was
bad
I'm breaking Dimensions to open a
dimensional
pocket wow is that my cheat
skill oh everyone seems like they're
communicating maybe I
can what do I usually
say to communicate or or have that
automatic translation skill when you
do unsilent unmute all
right
un to do wow want a coin I my head you
hit your head too I I hit I just hit my
head that's crazy crack are you sure I'm
very dur durable but it was trauma Dam
very durable you look familiar hello are
you guys also heroes from another
world anyone see the lights I wonder if
you can people here did you see the
lights I don't
remember am what's going I want to go
back there so many voices I'm scared
oh I don't have a BL button you guys are
talking to each other did you see where
you
who
[Music]
oh oh no I guess I'm dead
gu I
died I got e kind again oh no
[Music]
my God am I am I
dead me so I was turning
around you
watch are you are you a
human yes I think so at least I feel
like what about you you look pretty
human I don't I don't no I'm a rat I
don't know why you're very quiet you
have you don't have rat
ears what's going on it's too
loud is this a mental Asylum I don't
know but I'm hearing
voices in the last 24 hours as well I
think I don't remember be L of
recollection why
is can't stay as a blank forever is that
a typo talking I'm not talking to a typo
all right that was
the excuse
me I didn't realize what's your name
actually you good with
languages I I'm really not
what about you I thought I thought that
was spelled
correctly no no no the N the N I don't
think that should be C is that your
super power you can recognize grammar
mistakes yeah it is my super it must be
that must be my power
ninoa is that my name I think so it's
what status status menu tells me wait
you also see names too above people's
yeah it's insane I've never had
something like this happen before wow I
think we all got superpowers when we
were sented this weird room yeah this
weird box yeah does it mean we're crazy
is that why we're
here I don't know but I hope it's
okay yeah me
[Music]
too well good luck to you on your uh I
don't know Adventures good luck to you
as well on getting out of this box okay
hello hello hi hearing voices is normal
[Music]
I don't have fish what do I do I want
fish have you adjust oh did you
adjust have me take
me you
are yeah
are do you remember how you got here
langage I I I think that's a dream maybe
maybe I drunk too much yesterday and
drink
maybe I actually don't drink so that's
weird that's very weird do you know why
we here it's all a conspiracy I tell
you it's a conspiracy it's a
[Music]
conspiracy how how do we get
out that's the thing we don't what do
you mean you don't I don't want to die
here it's a conspiracy I'm
having I think we can do that maybe
maybe uh maybe there is like a puzle we
have to solve or maybe we have to kill
everyone until
we Echoes of Forgotten
memories
what who am
I the world I live
in and more than
anything the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel empty
relieved perhaps
distraught
what uh
there we
go I just want to WR music track okay I
do not
know so much I don't know and
yet at the sneak point
so much I don't know that bright light
it calls to me so much I don't know I
didn't I just say that toward the
light which one there's a
lot who's in my head hello huh
oh
hello hi we have to go towards the light
is it this thing the light the light
hello H what is your
name it's G it says on her head
oh my name is Jonathan spelled with a G
cool Jonathan Jonathan saw light light
where shall we head towards that the
fastest readers yes I think so I read
fast oh it wasn't reading it was there's
people here oh they're they're even
faster at
thinking
hello that like
what is is this a hole but what came
first it looks like a hole oh it's not a
hole okay it's not a
hole which light though wa it looks like
an
egg jump
jum jump jump jump jump jump
[Applause]
H the best little
[Music]
castle you there what are you doing
here you have the look of Outsiders
about
you quick send word to his magesty the
the heroes have arrived at the
sanctuary right away
oh the
king the Royal audience
chamber welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of liestal and I am its
king the guards who brought you here
have informed me that you remembered not
but your own
names a side effect of travel between
worlds No Doubt
this must all come as a surprise to you
but hering well was I who summoned you
here King
please speak slower you see an unpre
precedented Calamity now threatens our
world it has soon the Earth with
corruption and d h driven us from our
homes
this blighted land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known known as
stain this Kingdom of liestal and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left for us
Lees but should the Calamity be left
unchecked there's only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world kind of short
faced with this Prospect I scoured the
ancient texts for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found
one the ritual of hero summoning I'm a
hero you who Hil from another world have
been summoned here by me to become the
savior of
lesto oh only you have the power to save
our
world Nani
and so I ask Will
[Music]
you it's for it's green you your majesty
what is it a great host of Stains have
broken through our defensive line no we
are rushing to mount the defense but the
situation is tired Your Majesty we must
get you somewhere safe
who are these
strangers what say you Heroes will you
accept this
Destiny there is great power within you
will you use it to save us to save this
world oh my God
there's wait what there's bread W what
is this place yeah what a big Kingdom
there
Rubi what's going
on we going to fight my is something
tells me I should I Fe The King The King
did you guys meet the king I met the
king you met the king the king is most
mistaken if he thinks that I can become
aware
be of
this we have the same sword though I
don't think he's very smart thank you I
think we can do hero from another world
I think the king made a mistake with me
to be to be honest a great mistake I I
guess I'm somewhat of a hero
myself I don't belong
here can we
to R
yes I do a mysterious
power the ancestors blessings upon you
my name is Cel do not hesitate to call
upon me did you need my Aid let your
heart be your compass and I have faith
we will
prail I thank you for Lending your a
brave
Heroes supposed to
uh I guess Elizabeth all is
L this situation is so funny to host of
stain is upon us flee while you can
what's
this it
isn't I shall fight the last oh you're
so
brave it's okay I'll protect
you I will beat a hero the kingdom needs
it is my
call I shall protect this
Kingdom my own what's above my head I
don't know if I want to find out I have
to ask one
they will know
me
the am I just want to find a cabin in
the wood live a quiet life for the rest
of my ready bring it on N oh you call my
name oh no no no is that I just thought
that was your name cuz that's what is
written above your head well are you
more C big I guess I guess so that's
what I've been told my name is well can
I call
you Callie for sure yeah it is a long
and tedious name a pretty long name I
got to
say
cool there's a damel in
distress what there's a damsel in
distress we got to go see her I regret
that you must face such danger so soon
after you arrive danger no face such
dang soon as his majesty no that explain
to you our kingdom faces an
unprecedented
crisis kind of miss the Calamity beils
the land leaving it B of life and
infested with the monsters known his
stains not even the mighty theal Castle
can be set to be safe
anymore maybe it is too late to save
this world from destruction nevertheless
uh-huh our duty to defend our and our
countrymen
to no I was listening to your narration
there a
boss king
[Music]
the get him
the I'm not doing any
damage oh there's an Archer get the rang
first that SW is really guy I don't feel
like this very
though oh perhaps this wooden sword
could to be useful let's go
oh might be a thing I hurt I
Hur did I get AR I mean
this give give don't give
up we got to we got to protect the
castle this is on me this is on
me believe
believe in the me who believes in you
I'm very confused oh no a big heart I'm
a let's go I'm oh the range get the r
get the archers
yeah that's the there's no
way oh there's
Doles stay Doles
oh God
goodness
get why are those like
guys shout
Revelation revelation
nothing's
happened
[Music]
Revelation re
Revelation re revelation
R
Asian oh no I died
it can't
[Music]
be
Revelation
Revelation Revelation I can't believe
the world ended
already revelation
[Music]
Revelation well it seems
like uh
oh I am the voice of Raisin known as n
from Hall of English myth I have taken
over this mortal's body for a second to
tell you that there may be some
technical difficulties and we'll require
a couple of
minutes for it to come
[Music]
back so uh how you guys doing
all
[Music]
right pretty
good pretty good watching a cute
YouTuber oh who are you
watching share with the class
[Music]
Nino Ena oh Adventures of Nino in who's
Nino
en Ena the hero you must defeat the Ian
curse for too long it has haunted this
otherwise joyous lands go forth we're
counting on you I shall
defeat the evil that is the e and the
course it has taken root so deep that
its name changed to the e in
law oh very quiet very
interesting very time for a
snack oh
so I got these uh
chips they're apparently habanero
chips potato
[Music]
snack it doesn't smell very spicy though
hrow isn't that spicy is it
no no no no I'm not Nino ninoa who has
been is right now I'm the voice of
reason called n my of H of
Englishman it's not that spicy I mean
there's a little a bit of a tingle
but I think to a normal Japanese person
it would be very
spicy it's like a good tingle of
spice you know anything about
Revelations or stains
well I happen to be in the intro um
stream that talked about it if you guys
haven't watched it
yet stains are
stains my spice tolerance is scary I
think my taste buds are broken
unfortunately I've been told that many
times but people
you're like I think your taste spts are
broken this is supposed to taste
spicy you tried level 10 COC and it was
way too much I mean level 10 is okay to
me now I got used to it I think the very
first time I tried l 10 was pretty hot
very very hot
but I haven't tried 15 yet I haven't
really had kokichi this time or this
trip
rather spice is a feel of pain
maybe other things in my life is just
more more painful than spicy food
that's really funny
cuz I think my mom when she makes soup
she just naturally puts in like hot
peppers to a point where normally we're
just like oh it's not that spicy but to
a normal person they're just like what
in the world
she's been training
[Laughter]
me I think just my family in general
likees spicy food
but I probably like it the most out of
everyone and then probably next is Papa
and then
mama like the black screen uh we were
hit by the stains a little too
hard and the uh server or the world
ended and now the almighty powers are
trying to restore the balance and
rewrite the world to put it in a
way this is the uh branch of
the of the reality the timelines that
the stain took over the
world
no seems
like zombie named Ollie I feel like I'd
remember what is a I say my
farewells oh wait I've been in this
place before this is so Deja Vu oh my
God God we're back guys did you know we
we failed to save the world once that
was that was the that was the world
ending oh my
God so is this like a different timeline
I think the almighty forces have turned
back the time and now we
just going to save the world for you can
go back and his we finish the proposal
and you can get me out of here
to
do the
reset this is our second chance to save
the
world I'm going to call off my we're
going to call off
this thank you how much do you have you
have a nice sword too thank
you we have
returned oh no this place
too oh my
go I offer
you piece of
bread I gave you my
[Music]
bread wow trade
box I got
a that was a pretty fair tray although I
can't really hear
[Music]
youz your name
is you
hius I
will and your title is
passant to the B oh ba you are so my b
no my bread Tak weapon yourness my bread
how am I going to how am I going to feed
the
cat my bread where's my bread where is
the bread where's my bread where is my
bread where's my bread two kissing in
the
corner that's the cat and the N want to
join you want what are we doing here I'm
looking for my bread you I heard you
stole my item pink
cat no
hitting I protect the
weak Echoes of Forgotten
memories sker sker
Deja
Vu skiper
[Music]
skiper the bright light it comes to me
sure sure skiper skiper it was all in
our head yeah it was all in our heads
I'm going to be firsted let's go let's
go to the light let's
[Music]
go nothing
happened ooh what's what's all the way
over there yes if we go to the end of
the world what is there oh I can't go
there's invisible walls who placed this
invisible wall oh there has to be an
open open block somewhere there has to
be exp these lands and claim them for my
own own I'm going to start my own
country you're going to what I'm going
to start my own country Blasphemous what
you're going to take over the kingdom
that we were in can I have a piece of
land no don't don't tell the king
that oh
okay I I I misread re I I misread it as
Revolution I thought we were
going you're going to overthrow the king
I'm going to tell everyone of your Deeds
no stop stop her your
first I'm going to assassinate please
the hero can you explain what's going on
you said you were the hero yeah so uh we
kind of failed to save the world ones
but the the almighty forces have turned
back
time well I can't say I didn't warn the
king I said from the very beginning that
it was a mistake
in me who believes in you I find you
very attractive too let's go I feel
tingling in my senses when
you yeah there it is
again say you're with
me what is that word it's a magical
phrase top in my family throughout the
generations your family yes the family
of Heroes I think they might be right I
am I am believe in
yourself believe it save
[Music]
you do you believe no
[Laughter]
oh no she was thinking too
[Music]
hard oh Skipper
skipper skiper skiper
oh oh
ohc hello
I didn't but I was thinking about it I
forgot your name sound like a crazy
person so I don't think took any of it
we're back to the
Divergence F sh decide her harness was
going to if this world lives or
dies you know what happens yeah
we'll be fine please don't help me did
did her Royal Highness fail at the at
the marriage proposal
again what marriage proposal oh so
actually if this is just a secret
because I don't think she wants her her
identity to been known to the rest of
you know the peasants um I'm I'm peasant
by the way peasant the bay nice to meet
you hi um hero I know you're a hero but
I'm just I am just one of the Lonely
masses her Royal Highness is actually
among one of
us I see so apparently his Royal
Highness was in the middle of proposing
to her Royal Highness when suddenly you
know we got all thrown in here so you
know in the second time Loop her Royal
Highness said that you know she was
going to continue on with the marriage
get the king to to finish off you know
the uh to finish off the proposal and
then she will she will give she said she
will give me she'll make me a duess and
then I can I can just live out my days
in peace but we're back here with the
weapon I don't know what's happening we
don't know
oh
Heroes
[Music]
heroo hero oh
no I thought maybe hear the voice a hero
oh
espe I hurt myself oh who say that what
a big hat you have
thank you my dad gave it to
me you kind of remind me of a different
mushroom of a different world I see
don't like the mushroom you sound just
like
them Heroes you must defeat the stains
or my family will be
gone don't worry we'll save your family
powerful but F pleas sa
hero you got a z in your back shut up I
bre hey oh your hair is
yellow I report you you have hair you're
unlike the other what your great great
great
Grandad
will you do send me to The Gallows if I
I have cattle on
you tell the captain captain I'm calling
him right now hold up Captain can't hear
you from all the way down should be
remember said me correctly just call me
Shakira just call me
Shakira blood
flame accept
your own how have you faed through
that do you mean I am
the you are one you have fused I am
rubius right you are
yes rubius it seems you have eaten a
fair
Maiden twoes oh no the
dialog great
power a
little I came here to tell you that you
are The Lost Child of our of our
family what I mean I don't know who I am
you are my my father you mother
or the daughter of my great great great
grandmother's second cousin I need to
my uh daughters
[Music]
Sons yeah I I I I all I know is that my
name and and now I have found family
this is glorious I know how they move
you must protect the kingdom defeat the
St I will
father I got
B the
[Music]
queen protect
them maybe we should okay we got him
nice swo let's go guys defeat them
oh well done there's
someo get get
[Music]
him in a circle
okay
time H run ow really big
range get you nice
nice okay I'm King him I'm King him wor
not we got him we oh there's small ones
too be careful I'll protect you oh it
explodes no you don't there's more over
there look get
him thank yout my are we winning
my on a mission to save the
ladies he's like a
thingy be careful
[Music]
in they seem stronger than the last time
are they going to get
stronger lose this Loop
then oh no we lost the hero
R oh no the dog
died ow oh there's a wall okay fine look
at the
hero but we did no damage to the king
whoa re Revelation oh no
wow
Revelation the stain host has been
routed wait I got a
book you fought Brave kind Heroes I pray
you were not
injured that Mighty armored one must be
their leader the stain King fascinating
Most
Fascinating well I see why they call you
here Boos we been right to pickle with
with your
health we sustained minimal damage
thanks to your Valor our kingdom is in
your death thank you I must hasten to
inform His Majesty of our Victory will
you accompany me oh
okay we did it we helped them I heard
the news though we called upon you
suddenly you Rose to the occasion you
have my deepest
gratitude what interests me most however
is the strange power you manifested
during the battle with which you were
able to defeat the
stand the power May well be the king to
saving our world from inhilation anal
an according to the heroes the power
came to them like a forgotten memory
when they spoke the world Revelation
yeah it totally did but once they used
it to Route the stain host it seems the
power vanished Without a
Trace well that's blood brilliant Ed
it so what are we supposed to do next
time the St will talk revelation we must
uncover The Secret of this phenomenon if
we are to Prevail against the
Calamity many questions remain but one
thing is certain the kingdom of liestal
still stands today thanks to you we did
it here here so Heroes I ask you once
more will you lend us your strength to
save liestal from
ruin I didn't have a choice I just
nodded marvelous on behalf of all the
bestin I thank you we are blessed to
have your Aid of kind Heroes allow me to
introduce the four Great guilds which
are responsible for ensuring the
Kingdom's peace and
prosperity The Haven for the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet wand the
home of the glory Seekers with ambition
and vision where closest allies become
fiercest Rivals the Amber coin the
sanctum of healing where the spirit of
empathy and devotion thrives the thuan
cup and the beacon of the righteous and
Royal with the great threads were uh
arra with even greater courage that stay
sword
money one of these skills will become
your home during your time
here Beyond this door lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestor
shall decide your guild fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to Enlightenment excels your as I
always say even higher time the road
that eh we seen some of you D down at
the amb coin
gillo let us save this world
together the room of Truth awaits go
forth with
[Music]
Valor
wow the room of Truth step on the
platform and receive the will of the
ancestor Revelation oh
oh
wow all right I'll receive the will of
the
ancestors oh ad miss the endless flu of
time seek the power that Amber
Grant
Amber Cerulean
up Dawn the cloak there's a
cloak
oh armed with an un neighboring will sck
to defend the soul of
jadee wow
[Music]
G you
again my name is Jonathan G with a G
spilled with a G hiy
Jonathan no it's Jonathan was a g g
Jonathan with a g a t h o n hello
Jonathan with g g thank you Jonathan G
your name um
ninoa ninoa it's nice to meet you ninoa
it seems that this is our Guild leader
Celeste
Celeste oh
Tam oh hello oh
Jonathan what Ste summoning egg what
what are all these things raino Wast
spin what what is a map there's a map
there's a
map W wasin I have a cool cloak magical
tone M let me just St put on my
cloak what happened to my Ste summoning
it
this is so fast wow oh my
God okay that's so cool what horses so
quick need you
oh Jonathan do I have my j j you're here
Jonathan G it's Jonathan g g g for short
uh I think there's uh something a
little different about
okay really oh yes you're oh are you
by are you in W what do you mean you're
going ah I cannot bear look at you what
she's evil you're evil your black cape
where is that where did you get that
from the The Voice St what I'm one of
you you're you want to wait so are we
all s and was that we are all ceran it
seems like
so talk to the Guild
Master Okay Master Guild Master I am on
my
horse daners is busting upon you hero
welcome to the Guild Hall of the Cilan
cup I didn't read the first
part where's the even so soon after your
summoning speaks volumes about your
selflessness oh oh as a member of this
Guild you'll be joining the effort to
cleanse this land of stains and brings
salvation to the
world but one must walk before one can
run first you should learn about the
town we strive to protect as well as how
to accept and perform quests Quest
within this town there is a location
known as the quest board where is it is
there you will find the quest master who
will import his knowledge upon you you
may also use this time to familiarize
yourself with the
town oh it's a quest all right follow d
okay where did she go where'd she go
where'd she
go
she she is really fast yeah well we just
keep going this way okay I believe you
guys I guess we can ride horses let's
go oh this is really
fast Quest master
oh the quest board Quest board Quest
board beautiful seeds everyone you too
thank you thank you he you must be one
of the heroes then the kill Master told
me to expect you I thank you for risting
your lives to protect our fign kingdom
uh gilm how do I get off my H uh shift
sneak sneak sneak or yeah yeah sneak
sneak than than you than I understand
you're man d is r g the STS but I hope
you'll take the time to help some
citizens in
need he must be tired of my battle by
now so how about we get you started with
the quest right away I see looks like
perfect job for you well best of luck oh
here go now which which Quest should we
take what what what are the options what
are the
C okay we can I can read these right oh
I think so materials need at the Smithy
I'm The Apprentice at the Smithy and my
master says we're running low on raw
materials if you can help us gather some
please stop by the Smith can we only
take that Quest it looks like this the
only Quest I think so everything's the
same okay Quest
accepted I will get on my horse too okay
accepted accepted where is the
smiy uh
smiy where is
SM well there is a there is a map so we
can maybe look around and uh it shows up
like the name of the
NPC oh Apprentice of the blacksmith I
see
it is this where a blacksmith would be
is this a smithie
no yeah oh it's
smiy smiy
materials
needed what do you need what you
need oh great you saw my quest I posted
well to start with could you bring over
10 oak logs there are a bunch of trees
not far outside the town you can
jop okay 10: trees this person over
here all the
appes we'll get 100 coins upon
completion 100 coins can buy food with
that I'm kind of
hungry okay I guess we can get out of
the town what's the name of your horse
of your speed
GG oh mine is ninoa
oh what is your let's go
GG I think it's
a a co wait are you are you guys all in
the same party together not yet should
we join a party shall we party up I I
how do I leave my party you joined the
party already in a party I got K Out by
a random party I don't know how I did it
you're just in a party yeah without
us
huh I got kidnapped oh well by who by
I'm green someone named I'm green I'm
purple I'm green stole you yeah she
stole me I'm in her party for some
reason can't believe this
strange kind of scary I'm trying I'm I'm
calling upon the scriptures to see how
to leave a party yes I I I do not know
how to leave this I've been
kidnapped okay
well let's let's see maybe did you get
that party invite
oh I did uh I did
not hold on how do I
accept let me let me look at the
scriptures the scriptures the scriptures
on how to free ourselves from someone's
party
yeah uhhuh ah
uh the voices in my head are very help
it said I have to find the person who
invited me but I don't know who invited
me oh there's I'm
green so she wasn't just made up see
she's probably very far away cuz we
don't see her
return Our member to
us oh maybe the magic Tob can help try
your magic toone a magic toone there was
something really sparkly over there for
a second did you guys see
that where in front of the quest board
ooh the magical to wait so magic I'm not
a member of a party but I'm I'm in a
party huh what what I did not mean to
trade you oh I failed to invite
you maybe
mayhaps oh might I think that if you go
to page four of the magical toone you
may be able to
leave wow such magical to I I I think I
pressed that magical to and it says that
I am not a member of a party but on the
my screen it says I am a part of a party
so perhaps you might need to
uh unconscious yourself AKA oh oh yeah
perhaps eyes I will come close my eyes
and um go to sleep and
then I will give you some privacy I will
look away from you look away doing
this where she go this world where did
she go she left this world wa she just
welome back oh she just W come
back are you still in a party oh I'm I'm
good now I have the grass of the random
people yes what an wait why do they fail
to invite
player we
good why why can't I can someone else
try to invite her to our party I think
only party leaders
can so strange that is difficult is
still in a party how about we remake the
party how do we remake a party let us
you click on your magical to the magical
toone
yes I've justed my party I will invite
you no fail to invite oh
[Music]
oh it's okay I
will I will
be the lone the Lone Wolf I I guess it
is my destiny to work
alone I suppose free
her free her member
who is
eating it's
Gigi
you I was hungry in Minecraft I was oh
oh yes what is Minecraft I mean I
mean I was hungry an enigmatic
recollection yes recollection we are in
know I don't
remember back to the Quest board oh yes
yes I don't think they're in the we're
in oh wait they are there oh
oh W everyone's here I thought it was
only us there she is oh my God okay okay
okay okay okay okay free her stand still
do not move I shall free you I will kick
you from my
party free goodbye it was a wonderful
moment thank you
yeah okay
[Music]
okay yeah it
[Applause]
worked party now okay everyone let's go
get wood and beat the other teams we
have all right world first let's
go of them we so so ahead where do we
get wait that's not the
exit uh uh where is the exit oh it is
the exit yes yes
oh okay all right kill the chicken get
the get the that's not part of our Quest
that's not part of our Quest you're part
of a future Quest she has a point but
we're getting the logs before anyone
else can let's go
log empathetic
healers oh wait is that a
stain there's a
stain I don't know
if wait we can get coins from defeating
stains
guys guys we can get coins from
defeating stains
oh there's a
rabbit time to
grind oh okay I'm helping I got to do I
do have a better weapon but it has a
cool down it
seems I mean I can use it revelation
nice okay I have nine I need one more
there's a lot of stains are you guys
okay okay I guess I just got to keep
going
ow just a double check check your
pockets check your pockets I you're your
NB your bag the bag on your hip
mayhaps this is they're sleeping kill
them while they sleep they
cute these are kind of cute I want one
as a pen kill them while they
[Music]
sleep seems like there's no uh Critical
Hits so
nine okay I need one
oh oh that was very cool we got 20 coins
yeah let me see your
Revelations it's on I'm tired now oh I
am tired yeah I have a cool down yes I
have a refractor W yeah these are some
magical trees yeah they they come back
to life
trees wow the spawn rate on this is
insane crazy yeah crazy stained slime
ball can be thrown why would it spawn on
top of me all right I need
to be efficient
okay
ow hey wake up wake
up hey wake up wake up
[Music]
oh a
headbutt
ooh oh the range is pretty big oh did
they go
back w I want to keep
pting can I use the
walkie-talkie here we
go
end oh private call
I
exactly completed
sneak easy my
friends ooh all sorts of tools
easy interesting I have an
axe we need 20 coins Oak planks and
stick I
complete the quest speak to the
m Quest Master did he say what we needed
collect 10
cobblestones all
right so I guess we have to get ah okay
okay somehow I had the wood and gave it
to him I'm I think I'm confused
we need Old Plank and
stick can we craft that here
okay is that
it wa can
I surely not
right oh we can make Oak plank okay
three or
PL maybe I have to go to the quest
Master again
yeah where' my team
go oh
craft the wood and fix it
the wa already
did have to make it again surely not
right not the only one who's
late with all of this uh I talk to him
or what hello how does this
work oh it says completed
ah
okay Julian pick up the
phone thank you H very much
app where did you guys
go where did you guys go I'm just doing
the
quest I see I I finished the uh where
are you I'm at the quest Master now oh
okay we will return to you post taste
okaye post taste was with haste with the
utmost haste I am on the way collect 10
cobblestones and speak to the blacksmith
ptis
okay I must go my people need
me oh farewell oh I wasn't talking I
think we can leave the radio now oh yes
now that we are together we can hang up
the phone call as goodbye my fellow
party members good day sir wait I mean
we can just stay in in here it's fine
right Cobblestone
though ah that must be
[Music]
it I should have gotten this
earlier wait
there's
oh
wow
oh I seem to be being
attacked finding MMA
[Music]
just need 10
right it's okay I'll go I'll
go find my teammates again
I just passed them was it was
them there's no way people oh teammate
oh joyous day oh teammate let us make
haste to the I
will ow I B my
[Music]
head H complete the side quest and then
speak to the question oh whoopsies I'm
sorry about the horse why some stone
tools great you brought the logs your
master you bring the raw materials to
him through tools and items for
you you can craft logs into planks and
planks into sticks from your inventory
[Music]
in sticks seem
useful
like Quest Master party
Member
One Miss party member ah yes should we
just stay in the
call yes perhaps I think we should
[Music]
okay ah okay should we call the others
yes call the others yes this is the way
the
seruan members hey we call a upon the
upon
upon upon
the
a deliver a wood
shovel okay that's easy oh hello hello
hello hello we have can they hear us in
the I don't think so oh I can hear you I
can we can hear you guys yeah even if
you're in a call we can still
hear because we have ears and you are
next to
us all right are we ready to complete
more quests I would love to complete
more I just finished the the
cobblestones one I'm not sure what to do
we can we finish to the quest crafting a
stone pickaxe and a wooden shovel oh I
need to collect a cobblestone I have not
done that yet yes yes
yes okay where where where would one
goire said Stone you go out where we got
the got the wood go a little further and
there should be a mound of
stone let us make oh
escort let us make haste I'm being
escorted wow the
adventures Adventure
we create a party uh no there's a party
leader right now she would have to
invite you oh can you invite me to the
party please I invite tree as well there
you go inv
reason this makes me feel a little
sick I go back I feel some sort of we
can't hear anybody else to these
solid of them oh wait she can hear me
mind
um CH says they become
Bedrock maybe we can collect some of
this I don't want to I don't want to
hurt them though it feels like against
my nature to hurt them here I will give
you I will engage in trade oh trade yes
and then I will give
you 10 of these things oh thank and you
are not hurting them oh I don't have to
hurt them yes you do not have to hurt
them you
so kind you're so kind of course it's
part of the ceran way of
emption oh wow so strong I prect so
strong thank you I owe you my life
Wow should we uh perhaps ask the uh ask
the to join the the group group call as
they call it yes maybe maybe we should
on the group call so that way we do not
get it perhaps when we get separated we
can still oh we should probably run
after us I may have brought a joyous
crew okay okay yes
yes this doesn't work by my friend
woohoo Let Us return return oh crap I'm
ring ring ring yes this is protect you
Fair ma ring ring
stay on the phone call just in case we
leave each other's it's not
range joyous
day oh we have
returned we're good I am running out of
bread though
maybe I should ride my horse so I don't
get
hungry perhaps my my
group it
must against The
Rock You must do it yourself I must
do what what we have to do
now great
we completed the L thank you so much my
over there if you bring
theong Cobblestone
Cobblestone we did
it there are there are so
many oh God damn it there are more
quests we have so many quest to do
huzzah I love the quest Lo so that's why
we need that's why we need the
pickax you can repeat the quest you can
repeat the
quest
soy W talk to the
shopkeeper I'm not I'm not you're not
done the
shop
hies to go we're going to go get
cobblestone not yet what happened did
you have a pick po salad they have some
bread I have to speak to the child in
the gardens child in the gardens there's
a child I must I so sorry my bartender
friends what's going on do you need
assistance no I killed them all okay oh
no it must have been very hard my
friends where did all of you go I'm at
the uh sh find the child okay I will
meet with you cuz I do not know where
the child
is oh I see you my fellow Maiden the P
hello don't PBS usually have
food did you speak to the child in the
gardens already
mayhaps where is the child in the
gardens I know not I was hoping you
would know where the child in the
garden's rest H maybe this is the child
in the
garden is this the child in the garden
the child where are you oh I see it's
the child in the garden oh it's about a
few many Ys
away Ys away I I have a feel be
dangerous let us make haste I am making
haste to the child in the gardens the
child in the gardens is this a garden
my horse cannot jump can it it can't
jump never mind moving on my horse can
n yes there is a leeston child right
here I have found oh Lees
child let us speak with
you everyone's doing what they can just
like
you the child does absolutely nothing we
are spreading joy and
heroism to this town oh that's where the
shop Endeavor yes yes ah no we are
inspiring him you too can be a hero when
you grow up if you just look to the sky
and Shout
Revelation re you will die an epic death
because you are too small and puny no no
our devotion the Cerulean leaders would
like us to spread empathy all right
empathy yes you up to become a
shopkeeper one day or a quest master or
a hero or a great
NPC what is an
NPC what's an NPC what an NPC these are
just people I know it just popped into
my
head oh a lot of things seem to pop in
your head wonder what the Calamity
tastes like it's like tip of my
tongue I wonder if it tastes like
cookies I cookies the tip of her tongue
cookies cookies something about cookies
the tip of her tongue ah tip of her
tongue the tip of your tongue tastes
like cookies is this the only thing you
can buy the
potions potions they're very
helpful
so I have 693 coins what do I do we must
things I forgot what the quest told me
to do we have to speak to pitch dman
pitch D why do I have so
much who are you why are there so many
cute
girls oh you can build oh Beyond The
Garden you can build
freely I just realize why is my horse in
an egg why not horses come from eggs did
you not know oh this must be the place
not know Mason I found Mason they come
from eggs well you seem to know very
well about this realm you are very well
acquainted how do you know build a house
a store room are you does TH an PL where
the shopkeepers are across the way from
the Smithy the smiy thank you my trusty
companion I appreciate it problem why do
we all talk like this I have no idea
like
what like what wow it is how we speak we
can build our own Guild House BR dear
friends Guild House let us build our own
Guild House yes oh how joyous day let us
Jo day H let us make our humble abode
yes our humble abode we have our little
plot on the uh near the
wall let us Build Together miss this
time lady yes
Rock I shop I I have seemed to have lost
my way shop is this way oh thank
you yes no problem well
your iron
me anytime
rock thank you
blck oh nice nice potions 100 points
what is this
place a
Coliseum oh I like the way it looks
what
please accept our call for the
shop sneak sneak sneak sneak why are you
sneaking so much I'm sorry I'm sorry
sneaking sneaking oh reminds me of a
sneaking I don't know I think I'm
starting to remember a certain song
about sneaking like a sneaky NY oh oh
like a sneaking how do you all know that
that song have you grown up in the same
area
perhaps these memories they a me the
guild
Halls it must have been a song you all
grew up with like a nursery rhyme mayh
have it could
be
mayhaps mayhaps I was taught as a
child excuse me excuse me uh you you you
seem to have a blue aura around you oh
yes yes our our other our I'm I'm I I
found her I found on the way where
teammates to the do not let her be taken
us they trying to I don't know how to
get out of
here they're trying to take where I on
the way what I am I am making haste guys
I'm getting very hungry
she's she needed you Qui come with
me join our even know
where late now
so okay
yous what what youur my friend honestly
if you want to be with us you can be
with
us help you
come here come here come here come here
let's go Iris super come hereis
you you
are walking
away theying her they're taking her away
not stop taking her she's our I know you
have two halves one dark and and a
lighter one you must listen to the
darker us give her back oh my go she's
suddenly hitting me she's suddenly
hitting me she
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm I'm
I'm sorry
[Applause]
I'm hey reation
re
reation
Revelation
reation Revelation
Revelation done oh nice
fist God cool
moves they look like from a retro game
Revelation is a retro game a retro game
yeah yes I know not of what you speak
who are you you beautiful beautiful
violin lady oh at least you know I am to
be the next Queen of the kingdom of
lesto what I did not know of your
intention that's how you say it this is
not an intent this is meant to be your
destiny it was meant to
be are you are you related to them are
You The King and I we
have yeah yeah yeah what no we have bled
eyes and we knew that we were Des
to oh that was
cool he was to propose to I think she's
disconnected to
shop I wanted to to inherit the power
holy crap that's a lot to scar I see oh
my gosh then just select what you want
to buy yes
yes I'm glad you know fellow
peasants my my quean I'm sorry for
speaking to you with such
disrespect respect oh my goodness no
that's why you're in a different
Guild
oh gg gg gg yes yes G
help stay away from her she is our new
Queen she is to be our Queen it is the
will of the
king the P where is she looking where
are you going off to
yes return
wait what is what is your name
okay oh nice to meet you Iris yeah the
bgm is great my name is Jonathan G
spelled with the G Jonathan G GG for
short
horse GG for short Jonathan J G oh
jonath Jonathan Jonathan with the
G bread now yes he's Jonathan oh I'll
call you Jonathan Jonathan oh oh okay
yes I would like that so okay Queen
Jonathan um who are you hello I have a
name I not
Queen you don't like it you can call
me for
sure so sounds very cute and then who is
this rock that was trying to kidnap me
I'm
K Ki beu yes oh wow your name is
beu I don't know why that sounds but
slightly different from what I remember
different I don't know I don't know I've
always been beu yeah why am I being
surrounded by so many people you're one
of us team you are one of us you are one
of cup but yes but I but I joined
another team no you can leave no no you
did not join another team you are one of
us you you've always been one of us we
are tting for each other really what
what makes this what what what what why
why am I one of you eyes I see it in
your eyes because you have empathy yes
you have I feel your
tion my te kind of
being she's one of you guys don't you I
don't know especially you you don't seem
like you would have empathy excuse
me I am made of empathy you are I am I
am liquid empathy I've seen it in her
eyes in Tam's eyes the way she spoke to
that child she's full of empathy m i see
yes I will I would have to discuss with
my current uh my current team members
will you return to us it
is Jonah Watson she wants to kill the
king wats wants
told she wants to kill oh it's oh no she
thought she thought Revelation was
Revolution and she was planning to
overthrow The King The King
I mean I can understand that that
misunderstanding but what arrow is the
set in you I have no the what era what
what is even an era I have noidea
[Applause]
[Music]
what she wants to kill the king Jonathan
would never kill the king Jonathan is I
heard it with
M are we talking about
the
things stay away from my guild
member excuse me excuse me excuse me EXC
me m like that these
tracks friend
to hurt the king my would never want to
hurt the king we are parts of the J
sword and we are
loyal Loy empathetic yes we are empathe
your father's hamster and your mother
smells of
elderberries excuse me I bmed my mother
to
be I've never known my mothering the
know I'm so sorry don't listen to
whatever hey hey hey guys I'm don't cry
don't you you want to kill the king am I
right to
Bean thank
[Applause]
you is that which Guild is that I know
interested let's find out let's let's
find out bam I
watch smash you what Guild are you from
okay we'll meet up where you
hail I don't know you are too evil
Amber Scarlet wand wait Amber oh
disgusting disgusting
my disgust
us we don't interact with we don't
interact with those supposed to be like
this we were supposed to be don't talk
to us don't talk to us I will be
submitting a formal complaint don't talk
to I can't he you I can't hear
you excuse me the air is very loud today
I I you are a king killer you are the
king okay thanks now I can report you
guys
no report what I'm going to report you
guys hey hey hey that's not a good idea
hey hey hey hey that's not a he has
absolutely no power
where is she she's running that's not
even the right place where are you
running where are you headed to she's
going to report us where is she
reporting us to I have no idea it's a
thing Master oh my
goodness
hey Our member
hello what the heck just happened oh
that's
pretty w
what is Naruto what is Naruto what do
you speak
of what does I don't know what it sounds
like did you just make a fart is
Naruto oh passage the bay it is so good
to see
me your Revelation is a fart it's it's
been so
good do you know John Jonathan
hey Jonathan
yes who joh John Cena John CA can you
see him is he around here I can't see
him who is John
Cena John Cena John do you guys hear a
familiar jingle whenever you hear that
name oh it it it goes like
Jonathan is it is Jonathan with a G you
know right I know that how do I know
that I don't know I'm Jonathan with a
G the memories they're coming back
slowly no it's no it's Jonathan a
amberin it's
eil yeah oh you would be
gathan
yes you are of Amber you on the Amber
team are you of Amber are you he's of
Amber you of Amber
coin you're on the Amber
[Music]
team what no you are on our team
freaking you're on our team no you
shut I mean you you shut your humble
mouth know it's quite interesting
hearing only one side of the
conversation no I did not say anything
where are you I'm a I'm Sol L leveling
you too
do not
defective
okay I I see well you're supposed to
refuse it man you're in Cilan
Cup oh sorry I you are one of us come to
our party join our
party I said join our party Please join
our party Please join our party do you
have empathy or not if you have empathy
join if you don't have empathy you are
you are a
traitor you are a
traitor let's let's be nice here okay
we're we're all
about caring not nobody wants you except
us nobody wants you except us
the wow we are so compassionate
empathetic we go taking joins you must
in your magical tomb do you see this the
iCal book open your magical book and
locate page four locate page four of
your magical book yes and and dissolve
your
party oh my
goodness try try leaving try to leave
yeah
yes no no no no no just
leave get out you you belong with us
yeah they ditched
you mhm yeah yeah they ditch did yeah
you only have us now it's not a
misunderstanding yeah you were just a
decoy uh-huh you were meant to be with
us you are one of ours one of us one of
us we accept you for who you are traitor
or not you can make a new Legacy with us
we we we have been tied by the strings
of debate
yes
yes this is the right answer nobody
loves you except us yes only we can
accept you for your true S no no we
are we are we are we are we are the
empathy group we are the group that is
full of empathy and did you
leave okay okay
that's recycling on page four of your
magical
tomb yes yes yes yes yes yes oh I guess
the sword doesn't have
Whatchamacallit now now we will now join
our team join us join our party you are
one of
us try try
clicking yes we fullness
love take our
love love right
now
radio and now open your magic radio yes
yes yes Magic
radio
mag and join our call us ring our radio
call on our
Radio stere Chat there
go yay
feel like I belong yes you
belong she's
[Music]
[Applause]
here I'm not getting done let's go I
thought we were supposed to be the calm
ones we Cal we are Cal we are calm we
are very calm we're full of empathy
we're kind yes we're so ni kind we know
love we know peace we know does our
ancestors actually know us I don't think
they know us maybe they were like us and
they rewrote history they were like we
are the calm ones Think About by the way
your quest sorry my beautiful te yes my
beautiful teammates uh uh how do I check
what side quest I'm on oh you done your
magic book one more time and you you
flip page
two oh pick oh okay okay yes it says I
do not have any active side quest
what you to you talk to the board okay
okay the board he the quest board okay
okay are you guys are you guys you know
fully
already much farther ahead
words you guys just ahead of me we are
three quests ahead if I were to
guess I see they have
yes I I came I came a little bit you
know a little bit after you guys
probably because I'm just that important
you know uh-huh you are we are just so
full of empathy we understand we know
why the board not the dud empath okay
okay oh there's so many quests accept
all of them there's all of them because
we are a helpful every Quest I think
there's only one yeah I think there is
only one okay
there is only one it looks like a lot
okay and then I do you want the fast
pass through some of the quest oh
there's a fast pass is this is this gizy
what is gizy I have no idea what I'm
talking about called the U
special oh the enoa special please me at
the Smithy where's the
Smithy the Smithy the SM is this way yes
I would like a horse where do I where do
you get a where do I get a horse your
egg you
crack oh my God horses are are born from
eggs yeah the best that they are yes
oh well that's new knowledge is it over
here and how do I get off of it oh there
we go do I just abandon the horse or
just you you shift the button you sneak
and then you get off yeah
gotcha oh sorry there you are hold on
okay hello
hello fast pass hello here is your fast
pass you are drenched you are soaked I
am drenched yes I just saw you in the
water wait I can't I can't give items I
think you have to trade you have to
trade no you you have to trade get a
cold okay no I'm I shall trade you you
cannot you cannot
Fastpass the actions on her own you're
drowning help
[Music]
drowning I cck the red
block
am thank you fast
pass I amly little
clown matal needed at
the you drowning right click
to what's going on you're
oh my God what the hell's going
on was was someone
tortur are you guys torturing somebody
no we are having a nice
bath I did not man this is such a
peaceful team I'm so I a handful of
under the water though was it you no
someone was holding me down very te I
couldn't get I could the Amber team must
have done it the Amber coin used their
telepathy on you is is the ambercoin our
like our our main enemy yes they are
enemy mhm are oh they are so they're
like they're the ones that we should go
out to kill kind enemies yes yeah in the
name of empathy we must kill them yes in
the of empathy guys I don't think that's
how violence to show how empathy Works
yes I see I didn't know empathy was so
but it makes sense one of them what do
you mean it makes sense so sometimes
violence is the only answer to to have
empathy show up we have to restore
balance we have to restore balance I'm
starting to understand a lot of things
thank you this is what empathy means um
empathy is to kill empathy is to kill
the bad in this world empathy means to
kill unfortunately my loyal companion I
have a a pull somewhere from the unknown
and I must are you being summoned by the
forces beyond your knowledge the the
darkness is and I must Shar can drown of
course um but I believe in you guys you
guys will you come back to us come back
to us will back I will I will come back
to you come back to this world as soon
as possible please don't forget about me
okay don't forget I I do not wish we
never we'll never forget we will never
forget you please we will never forget
you in your wise
words beu and I will return to you my
companion we will we won't forget you we
will never forget please wait for me I
will I will see you again I will see you
again goodbye
goodbye uh uh uh
uh oh she is gone the
her she has disappeared the greatly
forces have claimed the soul oh no but
she'll be back will that happen to all
of us eventually perhaps eventually all
of us will will be will die why do you
have to be so dark like that because
empathy is sometimes dark I see that
makes so much sense there is Darkness M
wise words Queen wise words slay Queen
words slay
slay the queen
no slay the stain like Slay Slay
Slay I I do not understand but I will
try I I will try I will
try good good
good now can someone tell me where the
leeston child is once
again he is in the garden after you've
spoken to him oneon-one
uh yeah about that
oh Ena how do I open this box that you
traded me with like items oh you just
right click after you have it in your
hand I think what is right clicking oh
okay right click TR placing on the
ground oh yeah place it on the ground
with your right hand yes with your with
your maybe try interacting okay I got it
I got it on the ground thank you thank
you man my throat is dead I I don't even
know why it's dead it must be the
multi-dimensional transference that
caused it ah that makes so much
sense what what wait wait side quest
side quest sure where is the Jade sword
Guild Master does anyone mayhaps
know if you um perhaps find something
green go to will attempt the
arena maybe you will find them
[Music]
inside the arena I'm not sure but
Apprentice pitch
dor huh yeah I need to talk pit dor D
you saw the quest I posted what the pit
Dorman is he a Dorman or is he a Pitman
I think he's a Dorman a Pitman M no idea
oh there we go you mean like a Pikman
what's a Pikmin I have no idea what do
you mean
something something something I remember
it's
like Dand I am all to be here I'm kind
of remembering the the art of D allowed
to be here I'm remembering something
about Pikmin and the only thing I can
remember is that you throw you throw
them at people but the art of dund tell
me where your leader
is is there any other Quest I can do
tell me Le is
it's all going back to me of thank you
Jah Watson even though you wish to kill
the
king excuse me do you know where are you
guys I am faced with an Amber coin
member and you need to kill the king you
need
assistance an Amber coin member yes how
will you save
him where where are you guys one second
I almost where is everyone be right back
I need oh
oh
huh what
happened they're
gone oh I have enough stick
[Music]
it's so
quiet without
everyone what happened
so why was I
just delusional in imagining I had
friends in this unknown
world
people the Amber coin I am Amber coins
money they're not I love money you got
some money I can't get enough of the
gold I love so much child does not have
any
money oh this is not the G well as I am
part of Amber coin I would hate to give
them my
money where is P yes that is
Henry
Henry pit door for me check the
map you know they said don't walk with
your your map in front of your
face I feel like kind of need
to oh pit
Dorman there you are
wait they're so
far for oh that's why they Jade sword is
a passenger a messenger whatever
abuki auki pit
Dorman oh you're back I have I am
returned yes hello I just had to have a
conversation with someone did I get
disconnected from the grp friend
conversation welcome back cuz the why
did I get
disconnected cuz cuz G had to go talk to
someone I had to speak to someone um yes
oneon-one
to spread some empathy she seemed to
have fallen on hard times and it was a
private call a oh I see you yeah ah pit
Dorman there you are talking about
[Music]
hello oh where's pad Dorman where I am
hello by the door cuz he's a doorman
hello hi who who are you talking about
the one that required empathy oh um I I
spoke to jna Watson a little bit and I
saw her side of things she seems like a
pretty good person a good fellow
sheeded she she's Ed she just she told
me that she doesn't plan on
no she told me she told me I heard her
sign a story that she doesn't plan on
killing the King she promised she
promised she promised she wouldn't kill
the king it was only had to do with her
backstory her childhood her
history what what happened during her
time
stains killed her Village and they
stains killed her Village The Village
was sentient yes the
time the wandering Village was sentient
and the stains killed her Village and
all the villagers and uh they left a
note and it was a note from the king so
she thought the king had done it the
entire time and she it was cleared up
with the meeting with the king oh I see
mhm
she had a oneon-one
yes we all had one-on ones remember when
you met eyes with him and he proposed oh
yes right okay yes he had proposed to
our Queen our highness in here yes yes I
remember a clar as day it's almost like
it happened like an hour
ago he proposed to you an hour ago it's
almost as if I can recall you know like
I can recall so well that it's almost as
if proposed to me an hour ago uh of
course our our Majesty our highness our
lady in waiting
yes I'm glad you are aware I am aware I
am fully aware well worry not Jonna
Watson does not plan on killing your
husband not my husband yet your husband
to be yes you're be be hello
where is Calamity understands it has
born where did Iris go she has lost the
call lament what has regain the powers
of
[Music]
Revelation possible
Lane sh a mysterious ancient ruin we're
not really shaking to find ourselves in
another world come to think of
it Ray you will Aid us in our fight oh
then then your Aid go forth with
Valor head to the Plains and speak to
Hess of the Jade
sword is this a call for
adventure
mayhaps why are we speaking to
disgusting Jade sword when we should be
talking with
her cup leader is Valor and why do we
have to go with him
[Music]
exactly W the
Coliseum you're in
another why does she keep leaving us
again she keeps leaving us no she she's
in the party she's just not in the car
H if you see on the right our party
still has her in it
okay you trolled
us refer to page four once again
yes wait where did she
go it seems the
party is a little
bugged should we just remake the party
cuz we have to let us make at the blue
the quest board okay all me to the quest
board if I that sounds like a splendid
idea if I can find it oh
hello
hello yes mayhaps Wow We Gather our
party members
too at something bug oh we have I don't
know I don't know why I left please I
don't think there's a limit to how many
people party we shall we shall remake
of
five we have a party of four so you two
must fight each other to the death in
order to join our
party I mean I mean well our rock is
gone so we have four yes oh
true that's true we do have
four please good
night are you in a party you're should
we should disband the party you can join
the call again by the way nothing how
with using the green uh radio item yeah
but I'm not in the party so I
can't really it says I'm not in a party
oh maybe that's why yeah can can can you
okay we shall we shall get rid of this
party it's not it's it's weird I don't
know why I like they suddenly shoved me
in a party with with some Amber coin
members it seems disgusting we must
leave this
world
for a
second to
resolve this
issue
okay it's all right you will leave this
world for a slight second and you can
return to the blue house probably I see
I I need to leave this world yes is that
what I need to do I think so I'll also
do that I'll be right back okay I'll
leave the world and be back wait a
second
[Music]
wa will refer to my tombs to spam this
party
okay what went to miss
okay okay here here is an invite to the
party where did my there we go there we
go oh there we
go and now we can join there we go the
wonderful
radio stere real y the way you move a
fair where' you where did those words
come from I don't know I don't want to
get involved I don't know it's just a
Poe
memory hello who are you new people
beautiful pink lady wa beautiful um oh
gosh these two are exhibiting an aura
that I've never quite before are you
what is your name I'm feel I feel like
your legs are calling to me your thigh I
feel like she's the M call to me and I
don't know why your thighs are calling
to me I have a scythe I want to sit your
thigh I don't know why I want to sit on
your
thigh
now now
watch your Scythe is so sharp but you
know I also have some sharp shuriken
like this amberin WOW sword I a poy
Amber ambercoin are you I am Jade sword
okay then you're okay Amin sucks but you
oh no she's been praying
your are I have no idea that's what my
gu told me to say it is focused on
dexterity as long as I can join you for
your adventure guess bronze
but my fair Maiden can you open your
magic tombs and go to page four weaps
sure and leave your party whatever party
you may be in we are better than that so
no worries I'm going to
you swine you did you to do that say my
brain is Tiny I know this place like the
back of my hand I am very smart welcome
I've joined your party well Welcome to
our party welcome how do you know this
place like the back I'm not abandoning
Elizabeth she seems to have made
friends what huh you we are not friends
we are not we are not to each other what
is going on butt about to hush her gums
a traitor she is a traitor you can hush
gums is supposedly Amber coin how do you
hush gums J like
this what was that I just I just
contacted
someone harl too what what happened I
have no idea what happened but what's a
harlot you do not need to something wet
what
wet I don't know it sounded a little wet
don't you
think wait oh well you know let's let's
let's let's forget about you know oh
recollection recollection Revelation I
forgot everything that happened your
sword upgrade must be
flustered the fluster the fluster sword
or
am the beautiful pink lady beautiful
pink lady is Jord
okay what will you do there they're
going to make more money that's what
they're going to
do I want to go
[Laughter]
dungon what does she lie
about
oh no we're we're the we're the best
team in the world and you should join
you should join our our our call our
call on the magic
radio yeah you're not in the magic R you
don't you don't need to you don't need
to possibly
join this this this thing that's in our
hand right here and then you you click
on it you right click on it and then you
ring ring with the diamond thingy or I
don't know if it's a diamond thingy but
the thing what is the diamond thingy oh
actually I don't know it looks like a
pile of dust to me where where I'm
trying to I'm trying to recruit the pink
th the beautiful pink thighs to join our
call oh I'm in it
[Applause]
yay the castle Gates everyone the cast
Gates wait did everyone do the quest up
until the follow
me follow me up until the uh the ruins
the ruins yes no no I'm still at the
Smithy Quest wait wait let me let me
finish that real quick yeah okay
definitely is there something we wanted
to do after that I'm assuming we speak
to well like you got to get to the quest
first cuz our quests are not synced so
oh okay okay wait wait wait wait sorry
let me let me do this real quick
uh uh could you bring us 10 Cobblestone
okay okay okay okay yeah yeah it's so
hard talking to these um these leest
that you have to like you have to like
Crouch like crazy to make the sticky
keys the force of the sticky keys comes
on and makes it very difficult everyone
falling I think they turned off sticky
keys actually cly people maybe I'm the
only one that gets this sticky keys we
were advised to turn off the sticky keys
in a long time but if you press shift
six times
though the greater Powers have advised
to turn off those sticky keys before
start how do I how do I give it to them
wait true I want to give it to them help
I am being swarmed at the castle Gates
there are so
many eight hey how do you not can
someone tell me how to get cobblestone
follow me follow me yes it Hur my queen
what KY Mory K they
hurt what what
happened what is your quest my quest is
to exit the Town Gate head to the Plains
and seek to hastas of the Jade sword
okay we're on the same Quest okay great
Iris wait is your name Iris your name is
Iris yes my name is Iris what yes follow
me here this is the castle gate special
okay they're all very special let us go
we are full of empathy mind you empathy
is our middle name oh my God this world
is so large what all of our middle names
is empy Cobblestone is this
way see over there oh it's Minecraft I
mean it's it's Stone what is
Minecraft Minecraft what is I have no
idea what I just said what how do you
craft the mines yes
yeah bully that puppy bully that puppy
it's making puppy noises we not bullying
him we are freeing him of his they're
quite aortal V why are you trying to
kill the rabbit yeah it's a dark
one what's wrong with the dark one I
don't
know alone what the rabbits are F The
Blue
Team no no it's not what about the cows
a normal rabbit can we can we can we
make meat out of the cows sorry
instincts I want to get off the horse oh
there we go wait let me
Revelation Revelation Revelation G
stories Revelation the cow didn't die
from the Revelation wow this cow is
strong wait that is a strong cow that is
a strong cow die
reation
Revelation oh my God I didn't mean to
kill those oh God why did I go it didn't
drop anything didn't even drop any meat
I will help you
coins there we go hey the monsters Dro
coins they do we are rich we are rich
I'm going to
[Music]
be no we are not to be full of greed
that is not us we are full of
empathy I have no idea what empathy
means anymore what does empathy mean
could someone give me a definition of
empathy passion compassion yeah
compassion peace empathy
that's what it means are you Cerulean
cup yes we are all ceran cup we are all
ceran cup yes nice to meet you this very
what what is Jade all about huh what is
Jade all about hey heyy so aggressive no
t St we are courageous fighters who
fight for what's right oh wow oh okay
you guys seem like the actual good guys
okay yeah why so good guys we are good
too the actual oh yeah oh yeah you're
right right you're right we're full of
empathy and we force empathy on people
by killing them right no no okay well
everybody's got
their taking things into their own hands
I
guess is that oh excuse me sorry my
horse is a it's quite a um you know
Rowdy fella you see I I don't know how
to control it oh what a Rowdy of course
I'm I'm talking to I'm talking to a
ambercoin member right now and who is
the ambercoin member this ambercoin
member is the same member that adopted
many children and um and is oh loves
money I wonder why Liz said
that Co she must love money cuz that's
what she says Liz who is Liz you know
the theed money for breakfast does does
it taste good you seem to dislike a lot
of people on my team she was very oh wow
what kind of um money do you eat every
single for breakfast lunch dinner is it
different every single time Iris Iris
where are you are you in the place at
the Smithy you're at the Smithy I'll
come save
you copper flakes oh I will return what
about silver when do you eat
silver hey hey hey stop talking with
that fake Amber
coin hey get out of here get don't leave
alone get
out hey us cups are here get out of here
I was just I was just asking what her
what her nutrition D diet was she's
really not bad don't don't talk to don't
talk to her she's like a fake Amber coin
oh she's I mean that's not a good that's
not a bad thing right I thought we hated
Amber quein yeah she's Jade sword
apparently oh she's not is she actually
not Amber
quein
Jade oh I actually thought she was amorn
yeah yeah I thought she was amorn too
yeah wait D you lied to me I thought you
were I thought you were ambercoin you
kept saying you loved money that was
just like a full-on
sign how dare you how dare you I could
was really confused why you were saying
Amber coin wait where did your teammates
go I have to apologize I was also lying
on her behalf saying that she was a
member of Jade sword she is not no she
wants to keep her her identity she not
even J
sword oh she's a compulsive liar oh my
God she Li don't know where she is from
oh she's
dangerous so it's that mean she's in the
red team uhhuh I mean it makes sense hey
hey you don't talk to hey you don't talk
to my killed member like that yes yeah
stop stop it you shush your mouth hey do
not raise your voice at me I am the next
Queen in line you will have you will
respect me leave the queen alone
leave isone she
puts on the ground PVP I can show you
where there's PVP there is would you
like to follow
me I will take you to the Jade I will
take you to the Jade sword Guild what
your at the G Jade sword Guild it's
right this way follow me she is Jade
sword is she Jade sword is she I don't
know what's going on she Jade sword or
is she not Jade sword I should just
remember this stuff welcome to the Jade
sword guys are we are we going to
dungeon I the
dungeon yeah you're right we should go
to the dungeon like to fight later on
sword Arena whenever it's waiting for
[Laughter]
you only I do have courage is on the ble
Battlefield I need to do my quest you
guys can I need to do my quest wait uh
what was the next Quest I need to go
back to the quest Master Miss ninoa
where is hastus at the plains you can
check the map where left sh oh is he
onwards I need to check the map and I
should show you the NPC you need to go
to next I know we've got grave Duty by
Quest time I do not see him on my see
him he's very far south oh you are here
get your started yeah money speak to the
shopkeeper I think it's just straight
where is the
shopkeeper the shopkeeper is right
across the the Smithy okay thank you
yeah I am here he has been expecting
me is it just straight AC the oh no what
is this Jade sword you I think I see
shopkeeper shopkeeper shopkeeper
shopkeeper or South huh am I just
supposed to talk to the shop maybe
across the plains I see
oh hello we must kill all of these ooh
gold do not be so easily
distracted I'm sorry my my empathy I
must return to kill them all you have to
do is talk to me and I'll show you when
I've got in stock then s what do you
want to buy isn't that easy empath I
must put the stains down do stop by if
you ever need anything okay hero you
expecting us have a break and do
something okay you could try visiting
the Gil Halls of the four Great guilds
for instance each of them have an
activity okay oh the great ruins do I
have a lot of quests I need to do which
one are you at not many I'm at the
shopkeeper well these are all side
quests
like you're almost there I think have to
go talk to the the kid in the
park you got some time you why not visit
the gardens the children are tending to
them I'm sure okay the children children
let's St some children stains I oh wow
wait wait while we wait for friends I'm
going to go ahead and pin my my jade
sword out emblem to my where's the
children where's the children lead me to
the CH where's the
children in the garden there's a child
in the the is it the place with the
Amber coin is it where um Liz was trying
to take us or is that a different place
no if you if you check your map you'll
see a red marker for the next NPC you
need to talk to do you want me to help
you
wait let me see if I can figure this out
why does it say I don't have any side
quests huh I thought I
did did I like where should I pin it I'm
coming to find you where are you I'm in
front of the shopkeeper and I'm just
like wait I thought wait do I so I
talked to him he was like go find the
children but then like now I don't have
a quest and I'm just like where's the
children uh so like just follow me mhm I
I think yeah so it should be I think it
should be around here maybe was this
one yeah I think are these the children
uh there there's a child like in the
middle of the
garden sword yeah there's a garden
garden wait maybe this isn't it oops
speak to child yeah it's the leeston
child and it's in must be one important
child to be called the Lees child I know
right he the child of the country got
anpad where where did crony
go I thought I was following you and
very cool thank you isn't that a pin
where's the sharp part going into my
eyeball the bestle child oh found it I
found I think I see the Leal child wait
oh really okay I think it's it showed up
on my map now it wasn't there before
cool okay good thank you I can't find it
I will now make Jade sword a part of me
Leal
child let me talk to you I just want to
say hi Leal
child Leal child yes the it's the best
child ever is the Leal child if we end
up perishing in battle in this ruin oh
wait is that theal child it looks like
any other kid what makes this one so
special the ruin oh some have reported
hearing a strange voice but we know not
what to make of it let's see Souls of
stains open the
way okay looks like our team members
already figured out the the riddle
there's a
riddle I mean yeah it says oh slay 10
stains and then you want to do some
building or gardening got it leave it to
me I'm
ready cannot proceed yet oh yeah you'll
we'll see about
that I've been slaying stains this whole
time dang
it speak to the
okay speak to the pit Dorman okay now
I'm at the pit Dorman okay pit Dorman
okay you found the pit Dorman where was
the pit Dorman again was like in it was
in the yellow area right no it was in
the green wait was it yellow what the
heck is
this I remember crony saying she wanted
to see the pit dorant 20 minutes ago so
yeah who cron I can't climb I mean I
mean the queen I mean Tam Tam Tam oh oh
okay wait what is your name
Tam Tam Tam your name is Tam yes oh
where' that come from oh I mean jonath
Jonathan named me Tam Tam dance for the
Azure Maiden Tam for short I see now
hold on it makes so much sense what yes
yes
yes I'm so soaking in all this
information maybe I didn't use it right
oh oh no not the
map rich I know you
make who is Tam that's strange that's
me you we all have been in the same
party for tens of minutes and you do not
know her name your name isn't that a bit
odd huh I was told that the
faker are you talking about Liz yes and
you lied to us about her affiliations
why did she yell at me then why would
she lie then she just doesn't want
anyone we can gamble here apparently
she's in the arena but I can't find her
The Guild Master wishes to speak with
you please meet him at the J
confused speak to the Jade sword Guild
Master Okay Jade sword Guild Master oh
sound maybe after our
Quest None Shall
breach wait oh never mind you're not
master you look like har hold on I got
to I got to drop out of this call for a
second excuse me excuse
uh I guess the call
ended hi
guys how's it
going I guess if someone leaves the call
the entire call ends
[Music]
I don't
know I don't think I think I was the
first one in the call so who
knows this is bringing me bringing back
some nice oh hello
memories of the
past that I think I might have lost
oh there's so many
[Music]
stains time to become the bleach of this
world get rid of all the
STS just bringing me back to the old
days
that you enjoy hello
hello there's so many around you I will
help wow
power oh my gosh
so
no
hey yes and then you Ki and then you
lead me to the
loud what see you're so mean to me
and there they
go I do have quite a lot of
copper I don't think levels really do
much ah peace and
quiet it's a sucer
tree what is this
place
[Music]
W oh I cannot proceed
yet I was getting flashbacks of a of
another lifetime where
where you know there was a there was a
gate of some kind of a fog gate a foggy
gate oh I don't have the
right I apolog iiz that you are
sad investigate the underworld dungeon
then speak to the apologize that you
were a lesser
being here have some of my melons we all
share the same goal where I don't know
I'm trying to F to you supposed to
protect the land I should leave some
stuff here I have a lot it seems I
cannot give you my melons oh no it's
just a radio what are we talking about
the Harlot is talking about melons now
have so much stuff
I
tried these melons are stuck to my hand
what oh never mind I can't leave Stu
here melons I apologize for not giving
you my melons can I have your melons too
actually I would try but I cannot give
it to me that should be F how can you
try and and fail at giving
melons I I am using the uh the mus the
muscle the Q muscle is not ow oh my
God someone's making IR hear that and
just go oh is this a Shar chest arrived
we have been expecting do you have do
you see my stuff our initial for
portal yeah everyone I guess everyone
can use it same with the barrels if you
have extra stuff
on oh good you have to slay 10 stains
too exit the town G head to the
plan slay 10 SLS and speak to H it's
okay okay I think I'm almost at the the
dungeon
Quest this corner will be mine yeah I do
have more ah yes I will slay them I will
take this corner Barrel from
me okay I'm going to go I guess they did
get rid of the
recipe this corner Barrel is mine
St okay I guess I can Jo come
they must have entered the dungeon
already hey hey hey no crits damn it
there's no point
in guess I can check the thing magic if
they have shields Shields would be nice
I I made a trade
Quest
nice how many more how many more do I
need to do
[Music]
okay okay okay is my skill a
revelation Revelation I can't tell how
far it goes oh my God it barely does
anything you killed my prey well I mean
I Revelation it what are you talking
about I didn't kill it I Revelation it
seems
like I'm dying don't mind
if okay where is uh I forgive you
dearest what is your name red thing
don't mind I am Jonathan with a
G oh ow it's actually Jonathan
G
gathan oh
that's a
Jonathan gathan no no noan I think there
is it's in the other
shop it's like a potion of regeneration
yay I killed 10 of
them yes they're one step closer to
Extinction to accept oh why are you e
your of fashion surprise Box portable
Lantern why are you eating your melons
in front of you oh maybe this will be
useful okay now what do I do um talk to
the Dude Where's the dude okay through
the power of my empathy I forgive you I
know it must have been very rough to
have fallen in hard
times ow oh did you guys make up I'm
I've made up with her okay that's good I
got the key I got the underworld key
thing I don't forgive you I I'm I'm
working through it get one to
see I can go to the dungeon now
anyone does everyone have the map s not
map does everyone have their
key
yes oh give me a second I'm I'm shopping
last minute but I'll be right there
okay is this instant heal is this the
dungeon where am I has this ke where is
the dungeon anyway oh I can hear you
guys now oh my gosh or you guys can hear
me sorry about that oh this way it's
right there at the end yeah I got the
key um already enter no I'm back at the
town just chopping a bit I see it you
have to use the warp and then you go all
the way to the
end what wooden swords is enough you
guys didn't get fre you think that would
be good H should we do should we buy
stuff should we buy
upgrades well we don't really have iron
you know what let's Let Me Mine a bit I
see gold right here maybe they want to
stay with their
group oh that's mine no what are you
talking about what do you mean that's
mine actually I was almost done I was
almost done that's mine actually no get
out of my way get out of my way was
almost done I was almost done that's
what you did to me you will never you
will never successfully dig that one out
you will never no no no no I I will not
allow
you
you're you know what it's probably
faster if I start it appears there are
people in a cut scene in front of us or
they're seeing visions in their head and
they are reacting to it well they must
be crazy then they must be crazy then
wait oh I think they must have cleared
the uh clear the dungeon then okay do
two other people want to enter the
dungeon together maybe let's enter the
dungeon let's enter the if five of us go
then one person will probably be left
behind really only four can go only
five yeah we have five yeah but I feel
like we should also what about Liz she's
not in our party ah we can go into teams
of three we can swi yeah we can split
yeah I that will be the best way
everyone meet
inside are we really going to go are we
going to go in with um with wooden
swords I I think I should probably upgr
stone sword can I can can you possibly
be kind so oh so kind to um throw me a
stone
sword gathan
beloved to town get you a stone sword
I'll
come let me come with I think we have to
split the party before going into the
dungeon there's a area in there that we
must make ready checks I think we are
allowed to oh split the party before we
do our ready checks okay if you say
so who there they
go all Thunders are repeatable I think
yeah oh
okay solo I am here Fair Maiden
Iris oh
gathan my lovely handsome gathan yes yes
your comc maybe after we clear it the
first
time it is pronounced John I am here I
mispronounce many words no that's
comically large please accept this trade
this is how a normal sword looks looks
like yes I have a stone sword you may
have some raw beef thank you I will eat
it in front of you to show how
appreciative I am please eat the raw eat
a raw the call
hold
oh
arise tacos why did they come to me so
naturally
tacos what are
tacos I guess I'll just
wait for
everyone
perhaps
yeah yeah we made it
the video did they give us a better way
to play
it no spoilers
[Music]
all
right I'll be patient and wait
okay let be good
enough what we doing team love
what sound
right show some
empathy
oh what we doing
team we we are trying to
get Liz her Quest completion so she
caner I think she needs to kill a few
more stains
outside
wait there's one over here I'm going to
go dig for some more stuff while
I got to hoard all the all the materials
you
see that's what I'm here for hoarding
yes okay I'll be right
back hey what are you doing what are you
doing here huh you
hoarder you hoarder yes you hoarded you
hoarded my gold you're a hoarder who are
you speaking
to I'm speaking to a one lady that is
not in our group call for some reason
even though she is a part of the
team how could they do such a thing man
she she really likes hanging up on us so
you know I don't know I don't know
what's her
problem maybe it's the person who
creates the phone call hangs up and it
hangs up for everyone perhaps
[Music]
oh I'm going to test
it what watch this what my fellow
[Music]
friends did it
work I see I see I see
[Music]
muted in
stream I was about to say what's going
on guys
hello I am
back what's going on think we can get in
the dungeon before Sun oh the sunset I
was about to say Before Sunset but
hello ah
finally
oh hero hello who are you the he
hello hello pleasure to see everyone are
you leaving or are you incoming we are
incoming
oh I wish you to this isn't the right
way it's not the right way you have to
turn back off this Cliff yes death Waits
you otherwise you have to pay your
taxes down there pay your taxes yeah
promise just down here down here promise
[Music]
let me in
No Cap pleas please do not bother me
have isone inside the
dungeon oh okay are we going in the
dungeon now first and then we split
weird yeah no we yeah go inside past the
bridge and then we can split our party
yeah okay okay pass the bridge around
here this area where we're waiting in
front of the
dungeon farewell I passed by something
farewell maidens yes t t Tanashi K kiari
kir Tanashi this
Tanashi Tanashi
kiari Tanashi Kar goodbye Tanashi
Kiara name was
Kar I don't know what they're talking
about they're making me really
uncomfortable maybe it was k
k karia sounds familiar can you please
leave me
alone where's everyone I have issues
with people right in front of this the
Ed at the edge of the bridge group chat
okay may we should get out of the group
chat h Hello group chat group chat my
God hey assemble assemble CH assemble
alone I just want to go in the dungeon
with my
friends I don't know what you're talking
about please leave me
alone no I don't know what you're
talking about I just want to go I just
want to go into the dungeon with my
friends
is someone stopping you from entering
the dungeon big up
SZ yeah I should get out of here who is
preting hey what are you guys doing to
my
honorary guild member hold on there's a
CIA person that's being very rude let me
get rid of
them uh me put them in time out for 24
hours there we go that's right I'm in
the toilet so
white should we go in should we go
inside what no no no just come come um
that's not the dungeon yet you it's the
it's the path going toward the dungeon
so you can go inside yes I get it thank
you appreciate that what is crony doing
in a toilet hey like I said group chat
assemble stop hanging around in the
toilet wherever you are yes I'm not in
the
toilet how what what what what are you
letting out that you're taking so long
in the toilet just wait where are you h
we're we're we're in front of the
dungeon I'm in front of the dungeon what
do you mean you're not in front of a
dungeon You're the only one that's not
here what we aren we at the canyon no
click the thing to go in after you get
the key oh
okay
henceforth known to all we must enter
the dungeon okay God we must split and
enter the dungeon yeah we got to split
up I don't know
Liz knows the does Liz
know okay okay let me go let me go see
if I can pick her up Liz don't know if
she can read let let us go to the
dungeon towards the dungeon if we're in
a private call can she not hear us I
wonder let us go in Dungeon no she can
hear us if we are in our radio call okay
yes yes all right let us I am going to
go to page four of my magical Tob okay
we can make a new group and disband this
party yes party
disbanded I'll make a new one then
um who would like to claim your three
two claim your two my two claim your two
was it my one to claim your who wants to
join claim your to
yeah oh you guys yeah oh my gosh they're
very frightening but I'll invite them
you mean
tring I have let me grab Miss
ninoa okay and let me grab Liz who I
have forgiven I mean aren't you also the
aren't you also perhaps like something
that might be connected to this dungeon
we have a cheat code yeah huh I mean I
do get a familiar
feeling competition
now invite Miss Liz he we should
probably drop out of the radio then I
suppose so a new radio call then
yeah is everyone ready standing by to
enter the dungeon oh there we go stand
by we're going to do amazing I have
stand by to enter the dunge faster than
the other teams yeah yeah we will enter
the dungeon no players standing by you
got to stand we got to ready up we have
to ready first yes there we go ready
check oh underworld d D let's go it'll
be so
easy D the dead where are those who live
in call home I see Naro
do finding the final resting
place
ah got
GG I'm entering radio call yes enter
radio call so we're not lost pull your
your radio out and join the party call
dear Liz okay we're
good okay does not look like it is this
way okay we must go forth this way
wow I've seen a lot of people die today
or i' sensed it IED run let's go we are
not going to die wait is that is that
one of those transport teleportation
things we got to go to then these egg
looking things maybe we reach it over
here let's see yeah someone can
Photoshop underworld dungeon bracket
Savage
yeah everyone rank whoever did the best
oh it's a checko
[Music]
oh okay
ouch they're going to they're going to
be they're going to be monsters I think
so
like this place seems like a good place
to fight a very wide open space I guess
we should go on and
open oh she was behind
us go towards the oh you are up there no
I I am down in the
lava I perishing jump off oh if you're
on the lava block you can sneak and you
won't take damage unless you're in the
liquid one then pray
and then you can get this
checkpoint this wonderful beautiful
checkpoint and then it seems that we are
going to engage in
parkour I am now going to engage in the
art of
Parkour oh maybe I I can't click this I
think it's just activated um by team
bases
probably it activates in your brain
waves
portable Lantern very
nice got a portable Lantern yeah I
bought it at the shop oh what a good
purchase I will have to check the shop
next
time are you okay the draw fine of
course I'm fine I am a a hero are you
frightened mayhaps are you I'm never
frightened you can make this jump I'm
hungry hi
hungry hello hungry I thought your name
was
Liz all
right let's
go this way and
up and
H and
H you're doing very well I do not need
to hear that from you loud one no what I
thought that we have made up we've made
amends no you are to
fall you are doing so well we're almost
there yes we're almost there wait if we
got the next checkpoint does she revive
at the next checkpoint I am at the
checkpoint I wonder if has to unlock it
her does if I get this does it pop up on
your screen too new checkpoint
unlocked try try dying dear dear Liz a
okay if you say soy try dying and see
what
happens oh hiy hey this is a strat y
magic we don't need this as a strat I
was just testing your your heroicness
yeah that is all your
strength it was due to our strength that
this was possible yes I was seeing if I
could trust
you worry not I see it I see the
checkpoint Over
Yonder that was almost
dangerous
dangerous my middle name is it maybe I
don't know what my middle name is
which way is it this way I'm trying to
make ey contact with our next I think
we're supposed to go towards the
thingy so this way this way
yes a job
no it hurts it's like you never left yes
I was just right behind suspicious
castle looking thing
this Castle won't know what hit it once
I'm done with this
Castle it's going to regret standing
here in the name of
empathy oh we got to climb from this
side up this
way this
way where is is it where's the entry
point I see it I see her see it for
empathy oh that was almost y
okay it is safe up here there is nothing
to be scared
of okay we good oh wait we get the
checkpoint yeah yeah checkpoint obtained
so worry not okay we're good you do not
need it though you are so good at
climbing take a mountain goat I learned
Channel your mountain goat Channel your
mountain
goat oh make sure you're not
hungry I'm eating
bread
oh bread ready let's Venture Yes W
checkpoint do you think something will
kill us in here possibly which way shall
go
mostely oh here a
zombie oh my be gone foul Beast what is
this very dark room they are red zombies
this a maze wait we lost a knife what is
that no we lost
Li where did you go I'm behind you okay
okay I am discovering the secret to
attack the zombies
oh I found it I think I lost you
guys uh no you are closer I'll go back
to
you don't worry I'll make sure these
zombies don't hurt
you this
way oh my God they're holding
like same way oh they have different
star
key oh are you okay wait they have keys
maybe I have to collect them I'm
hurt are you okay I'm getting surrounded
by zombies there there's I got
you it
hurts wait I think we're supposed to
collect the shaped Keys which one how
many should we collect
um so far I have star triangle and
circle okay
and where do we put
them it
burns I also have a start two triangles
in a circle okay I don't know how many
we'll need so maybe we
can I'll throw this
stuff wait okay all right you guys
good um uh I'm
okay I do not know where you
are what does this say
is is
nothing oh there's a
keyhole okay okay
okay wait I can't put any oh oh I just
got to click the thing wait we got to
find Liz though I'm here I see her name
she's right behind us okay let's go to
the next
area oh the recycling bu TR ah what a
joyous day W do great
what is your
name me um
Nino Nino yeah can call me Nino Ena
whichever one n
n Nina Nina Nina it is a beautiful name
thank
you we just call you
Liz you may okay do you prefer something
else
um H oh oh is this a puzzle as you are
offering
[Music]
H
oh nah just Liz this time no just Liz
okay yes just I don't know why but your
majesty oh are we supposed to light up
everything what every single one if we
click frantically this is what I learned
in my my past is that a puzzle can
always be solved through the bruest of
forces
[Music]
umm you
know
yeah you know what I
mean this is going to take a while huh
my tummy is shook oh I did not mean to
kick you from the party you stood in
front of my face rejoin come back
please I can't believe you the party I
did not mean to I did not mean to do
that I was so please please
GG well gin for the first time and then
I can't seem to click any of the blocks
is it only you can click it I'll accept
oh maybe it is only me that can click it
well I I hope you can click it I see I
see I used to be able to but now I can't
oh why Exile so you were clicking
them yeah I can click it oh maybe maybe
it's a party thing maybe cuz I accident
did the thing no do I do we even know
what they're supposed to do
here apparently other part of words are
being beamed into my head other parties
had the same thing happen
oh why would they who would put a puzzle
inside of a no dungeon it's just a
bug who would dare do such a
thing well it's all up to you let's just
see oh
no oh
no
wa you know we need your we need your
Superior brain
power should I maybe get out of this
world and then
return maybe that'll work I don't know
if it'll kick me out to your world of
this world or dungeon hopefully it does
not okay well hopefully it does not I'll
be right back fingers crossed
welcome back I am here can you click it
hold on it's still
loading I believe
okay oh I can click it now yay
huzzah huz
thank
goodness hold on should we just have one
person do it at a at a time so that I
entrust this to you you can do it I
entrust this to I don't know if I trust
myself to do
this not smart
enough you are so
wise wise beyond your years I think you
do better than I did the first
time I don't know what happened so much
was
happening so close I see it in my mind's
eye I see youing this yes ah you are
getting so close to soling it
I am going to find fitting music because
right now the music in my my brain waves
are sending to be quite Jolly but this
is a tense situation this is very tense
my brain is being tested
H my brain
hurts oops
it's so close so much of it is lit up my
brain hurts you know you are of the
bigest brains you are so wise I believe
in thee believe in me who believes in
thee you are this
moment
oh oh oh my gosh you're did you work CL
lady this is hard I don't know what I'm
doing what did you what did you work out
oh I don't know oh you don't know okay I
thought you worked it out I did
not I thought I
did I feel like you did it
better I don't
know is this the part where people took
the longest
probably this must have been what caused
people to falter for so
[Music]
long you got this
what is going on in your head
nothing it is so full of thought that
you only think that way but I'm sure
that you are thinking many things I
am yeah you you are thinking so much
ah it seems I cannot help with the
puzzle you may have to disconnect your
Consciousness and come back just as Ena
did oh what
completely yes well you will have to
return to to your
conscious your default state of mind and
then return to this
body okay I'll try as
in
um
in appar according to my scriptures that
it reads this connect from game and and
return Hol life what is Hol life I'm
starting to
remember
wa what how does that a stand
for oh my
goodness I did
it you did it I'll day cuz you starting
to remember I'm starting to
remember
Hol H what is Hol live what is hollow
life where I don't know but I think
that's back she solved it while you
g I'm starting to remember we're
starting to remember things yeah but did
you work out how you how you solved
it we saw Hollow live and then it was
solved what I think Hollow live is a big
clue yeah it made the letter H and then
she solved it immediately after yeah
because of hollow line well I guess we
can go ahead yeah now we can
continue all right what's ahead of us is
it telling us we are Hol but we are
alive maybe maybe we are alive the maybe
we'll find the answer at the end of this
place
yes there must be something here please
rejoin my telepathic radio channel oh
yeah oh we're here
[Music]
okay I am inside your brain hello you're
in my brain we are I'm in your
brain
w What does that
skull what does that mean I don't know I
feel looking feel
danger oh no whatever is ahead of us W
what the what run what's
happening we must run run run run run oh
there's no Rock oh no oh no what's
happening we're full
fell what was
that I thought I could do that to us I
thought I could just that St attack us
oh there's a mushroom this there's a
mushroom dud a skeleton are these oh
that's your skill okay I thought it
exploded do we have to survive this is
this uh waves of
enemy and you survive of the waves of
skeletons are they're really hurting
us make sure you keep yourself well
fed oh I am very hungry thank you wait
does it come back alive stomach is
growling do we have to do something with
this
mushroom how do we oh we let it have the
mushroom beautiful now I did something
is there another
mushroom we just keep killing it I don't
know
what the
oh oh well done I feel like it comes
back alive we need to bone meal this oh
it drops an
item so we got to grab
closer oh I
[Music]
see so we got to kill it here and then
the tree will grow cuz it drops Bor meal
when it dies and it doesn't like us
picking it up die on the
platform oh it is growing she's growing
nice one and soon we can parkour
yeah all
right
nice okay we're getting closer come here
skeleton do not come here
skeleton come closer skeleton come to
this middle platform with the tree I
need you to take root I think we can
already go maybe there's like buttons
here what do the buttons do buttons yeah
I've grown it a little more okay I think
we're ready to go
okay
maybe the
decorations oh yeah we can totally jump
from this let's go okay okay okay on my
way up but make sure we're well fed
there's more more
trees to kill with the skelet
I'll wait for
everyone I
can't you guys can climb the vines too
at the
start oh so it's easier yeah
yeah oh gosh there's two trees
next
no skeleton is too powerful that's the
thing we we it's hard to go up like on
your own with the skeleton
attacking all right maybe I can shoot
down from
above I wonder if it
reaches
oops okay go go go wao climb the Vine
how does one
climb oh there we go nice oh I see
everyone's head good job
Nino all
right all right keep going
guys I'm a bit
stuck you
good yeah I'm always good I I am of the
Jade sword I
am
yeah uh uh anyway uh are you
good well I was almost not good but I'm
good oh I'm glad you are
good I
guess it's not I like you or
anything oh you good okay yes let's
go there's another
there should be another skeleton y there
is oh no there's
two all right draw it here get rid of it
with this first no more
trees oh it was a little far
sorry it's okay I'll come back alive
here
hello nice okay there's another one here
should we grow one first do we only need
one
seems like I might need two if there's
two here only spawns one at a
time
ow unhand me foul skeleton
Beast maybe where is
it oh it still has knock back
huh oh if only I can push the item it's
fine if found
uh do they do they both have to do both
of the trees have to be I mean let's
start with one maybe and see where it
goes maybe it's like a mechanic we need
but
not okay got one
here oh there's another spawn
bring it
here push it against the
tree get on there
buddy over
there come here you want to hit me on
this tree trunk so
bad mayhap you are obsessed with
me I think we can just jump
let's see where this goes okay
[Music]
ow leave me
alone all
right okay up up up
up and then over
here what
why does it look like
this think we got to grow it one more
or maybe maybe we have to grow it or we
go over this way potentially over here
and up down oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
maybe I don't think I can make this y y
y y yum
yum y y y yum y yum yum
oh from that way okay
okay
nice
okay oh
goodness this this tree is in my
way oh this is a little rough we have to
grab one
more maybe we do have to kill one more
or we go up fall from a high
space Oh no you're good I'm okay I will
kill the skeleton ah
okay skeleton will kill me did it grow
did I make it grow no I think this is
the maximum
then I wonder if we do have to grow both
of them and then it leads to the other
side oh yeah maybe oh
yeah that
could unless unless I'm killing it worry
not stay up
there let me know if you see a
pathway okay I've grown it
more oh you have is there a new
pathway
yeah ah I am block oh yes good job ah is
it nearly I've made it you may die I
will die I will die I will I will die
but I don't want to
die but if you die you may live
Nock I refuse to
die a momento I want to just look at
this
to the Denis of the Underworld the light
emanated by Souls one moment teammates I
just want to look at this tree and
Ponder it's just so amazing what are you
pondering I just need to have the tree
some thoughts to myself for a sec yes
yes
oh if you see over here this oh no how
do I make this come
back there's a book in this portal
light emulated by Soul was vital needed
it to survive in this ever cold and dark
environment yet among them there was a
her a heretic who called their customes
into question do we really need to take
others lives to sustain our own no there
has to be another way and so she stepped
into the plane above who is she got on a
plane she got on a plane I think
so what is a plan what is a plane the
astral plane plane
above the world oh the the plane in the
world above the plane above
all the plane of Life the plane we call
Life yes fun I saw the meaning of life
in this tree oh what did you see what
did it say
42 42
42 yeah I counted 42 blocks I mean tree
leaves tree leaves she counted only she
can count a lot my
eyes mine eyes power of Revelation has
grown stronger oh
wow you recovered a portion of your
memories what did I remember Hollow
Hol live is this the timing to Hol
live play the thing oh it's the
time it's time to play the
[Music]
thing a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their s
[Music]
Testament but I keep
wondering
so is this the right thing to do no it's
not
[Applause]
[Music]
what's going
[Applause]
on look at
that turns out we can also use people's
emotion we don't need their souls at
all Reaper should help the
living that take away their future if
the others can't accept that go get them
that's their
loss I'll do things my
way this is the woman who joined our
party that's what is she
doing that's
her oh
my God her memories wow was that was
that from the dungeon the
memory these are her memories it was
kind of
like she did say she was a Reaper yeah
and we met with her maybe she remembers
more now
wow so cool the
Underworld the
underworld she so does that mean if
we if we go ahead and clear more of
these dungeons we'll have more of these
memories coming back I wonder I wonder
who whose memory will we unlock next
oh
wow that seems so
cool my
goodness that's my guildmate that's your
guild mate it's true that was your gu
mate
wow that's so cool it seems there's a
lot more to her than meets the eye yeah
well maybe maybe the Jade sword Guild
Master knows more yes we must we must
ask Let Us return to Gilda Master more
of our own
memories it's time to play the happy
adventuring oh yeah happy music once
more wow
okay yay now it's no longer ambient
noise pece of the world wow great job
guys hey we saw your memories yeah yeah
do do you remember now you remember how
interesting I do but did you guys just
clean or did you guys did something else
after it's a little embarrassing cleared
no clear we cleared and we were just
like waiting and uh we're just having
you know just having fun in that last
did we take that long we did we take
that long yeah you did oh yes we we oh
yeah we we finished Way 3 hours ago even
yeah 3 hours yeah 3 hours
ago let's go turn into Quest you know
let's go huz
they
are oh my God they are sparkling what is
are Revelations SP yeah oh they are
they're so shiny guess it's time to test
them
out I am on my
horse look at my horse it seems
just like Raaz how do you know that song
I don't have any memories what maybe our
our parents very strange you're
young maybe maybe it is it maybe it
might have been your lullaby oh maybe
maybe it was my lullabi maybe a damage
but but maybe we'll
see wait is it the Guild Master outside
or in the place he's like underneath the
thing jigy
oh so the one in the
arena uh I think there's like an
entrance and then you go in the little
cave looking thing yeah there he
is brave hero your quest I am heartened
to see that you have returned unharmed
pre tell what transpired at the
ruins a flashback I see to think the
ruins held such secrets
a crystal deep within that when touched
returned a fragment of your memories to
you oh my goodness memories which in
turn reawaken the power of Revelation
AIT at only a fraction of its
potential that your summoning and the
discovery of these ruins should con
coincide so
closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation oh I see I see Brave hero
seek rubius The Guild Master of the SC I
don't have to read any of this anymore
this Guild has also been searching for
strange ruins in the lands of lesto
mayhaps they have discovered something
she is transcribing for him yes thank
you thank you my throat is dead today
from all that
stuff Scarlet wand Guild
Master be located follow me I know the
map I
think uh there's a the a bridge here
okay okay follow the
bridge oh
my onwards to room my radio
disconnected wait where did oh rubius is
down here
okay here
I found him no I lost the big hat oh
wait that's the G keeper where is
he he's
outside we need to make these he needs
to show himself more
clearly
oh nothing less nothing more I now they
have B power I love those I love these
hats they remind me of a certain Moon
Queen from oh where am I remembering
this from oh from from a certain Elden
game yeah with with lots of rings good I
I think yeah I know what you're talking
about lots of my preciouses
oh trace the power of Revelation
fascinating Most Fascinating one might
hypothesize that those ruins are the key
to unlocking your powers we of the
Scarlet one have also been investigating
near the Plains and wanted to know it
just off the coast we
speak to Corin spine it's spine a light
with a striking resemblance to
Revelation Corin good hero would you be
willing to travel to the coast and Aid
in our efforts there members of our
Guild are already there hard at work I'm
quite sure they will appreciate your
assistance good luck and
exelo exelo go to the coast and speak to
Corin of the Scarlet
wand all right Corin Show Yourself ah my
horse ooh they're like
purple they must be pretty far I guess
they're outside
huh it's Ki
beu she has wandered off she did not see
me but it seems she has returned we
Pizza we're talking about my name hello
we talking about her name can I
introduce
you her name is t
Tam Gander so your last name is Gander
your first name is Tam she kept she kept
saying taner peon see even she thinks
that we're talking about pizza no I
don't talk about pizza all the
time oh I love that
pizza pizza I love pizza I love the
pizza you guys remember this language
why do you see the
language oh my gosh it's KIU she is back
hours later then I'll be doing if you
want to enter a dungeon with other
people that's fine and we could do a
different I Jonathan
yeah yeah let's do
it the coast is by the Sea and the sea
is near the coast where is the coast and
where's the
sea uh who house South uh yes east west
east west southwest follow the
South West we got into a fight with some
people and then we cleared a
dungeon we did indeed yes we indeed
cleared the dungeon only you can hear
me oh I have found the ocean the coast
there are some dangers but trust your
heart and your empathy and it will guide
you to the the
end yes so inspiring your empathy will
guide you she's telling seash Shell by
the SE your empathy will well for joh
Words
kosu see here rising from the Ws locals
are quite a steer with curiosity yes
thank you I will go
onwards farewell where is Nino Ena by
the sea I am by the
Sea where is the sea it is is to the
West after you get out oh okay so I must
leave the kingdom walls you
must gathering
information object known as the rainbow
Coral
cluster we can breathe
underwater I am
lost I am just going in a a
[Music]
circle rainbow Coral shards and refined
magical
energy need not concern yourself with
the lad good hero okay in search for the
coral shards iridescent as a rainbow
once you have found enough please return
to the guild and present to the Guild
Master I I see I am making
haste this kingdom is a very large yes
indeed large Kingdom oh
oh that was
[Music]
quick where have they
gone where yeah where are they Where Art
Thou oh hello
a really un good old
[Music]
days Civility and
tears the real empathy our empathy will
keep us together
together all thanks to our empath
see I am headed
west west this just follow the road West
Southwest
westish Southwest Fair
Maiden do feel like it's East please let
me in your empathy oh I am not the
leader I think oh who is you see I see
the fair maiden of dark pink dark pink
of the super hot pink she says super hot
pink super hot pink she says I am hot
pink I am let me just let me just you
know emphasize the hot yes hot pink hot
hot super pink hot pink yes hot pink yes
mhm okay we wait right here oh the hot
pink Maiden has is waiting for you
please the hot pink Maiden you must join
our party once more thank you I know
Hots to popular yes a stain I will
protect you
thank you thank you my oh my God it yes
yes
no weon actually looks kind of
cool this just a
book you're actually doing spells you're
like a
magician I'm just doing ninja stuff
she's a
ninja where's C I guess crony crony is
too busy doing her her crony I mean her
T stuff
yeah who's gron yeah I know mean the
Queen the Queen the que the queen Tam
yeah Tam
T
Tam Tam oh how could you are under
attack I'll save you yes back off
they cry like a dog to make us feel
guilty she's looking for the Scarlet
leader isn't it somewhere around here
that's why I'm the Scarlet leader is
back in town this is the he is back in
town wait it's actually sparkling in my
hand shiny it's sparkling and in the
inventory too oh my God you actually
have knuckles I need to see your
Revelation can you re revelate for me
can you
revelate
Revelation
W yo she's a punching quite cool
punching girl how about you show us how
about you reveling for us yeah are you
talking are you telling me yeah yes okay
yes hot pink one okay wait wait wait a
sec let me let me just get the
Revelation um thing wait wait here wa uh
go let me get my goex I mean not my goex
I mean one what ex what what what no no
no no sorry no nothing nothing okay I'm
ready now I'm ready to revelate okay
revelate okay
Revelation that is crazy wo where did
that go where dides that go I can't tell
where it went to the ground I think
whatever you're aiming your curse or
your uh
Vision wherever I I imagine yes her yes
where her aim is true where her eyes aim
exactly I aim at my targets
yes hopefully into the
end revelate for me enaa I mean Nina
okay
Revelation ooh so cool oh my god oh it's
like a gun I
mean is what I have no idea what a gun
is but it must be something like that
yeah
if I knew what a gun was I would say
would it's kind of similar yeah
something like that like a
gun man I love holding on to these two
stars you look like you can assassinate
some people with those I can I can
someone called me Naruto what's a Naruto
Naruto I don't know I have what do you
mean who's a Naruto so what's Naruto
what is Naruto crony
who's crownie who's join our party T Oh
yay
yes back we're back imagine having a
girl named Tam in our party right
now man it stands for the almighty right
Tam is great Tam is even actually named
me so oh yes yes I thought I stood for
the almighty the Azure Maiden oh and
then Tam said it was too long so I said
Tam is
okay
yeah it's a good name your last name is
Gander right yeah Gander yeah when you
become que is your is your last name
going to change I'm going to assume I
kind of want to keep my last name though
I don't know but you're going to get
married to the king T
bestl yeah well I don't want to be
called like you know
T
beand Gander laal how would you
hyphenate
uh you know I I want to I want to keep
my name you're you're going to keep it
yeah I'm just going to keep it I'm just
going to tell the king like you know I
see stole my
kill your exp whatever that is is mine
it's mine mine yeah I'm level 10 now
yeah but you you do you do hold
affection for him
right yeah yeah no sure yeah of course
oh okay okay I I see it's because of
your
empathy yes the
Revelation okay she's level 10 let her
hover I'm going
[Music]
Revelation
Revelation hey your kill
stealing oh I'm sorry I'm sorry it's
fine we're on the same team the EMP
you know I keep getting scared whenever
these
dieom yeah it's for the kingdom for the
kingdom your kingdom we're getting side
again be Tam isn't in the voice chat
either yeah Tam is too slow oh now I'm
in okay it does sound like a very
dangerous dangerous monster from another
life are we going out on an
adventure wow the water is so beautiful
it is swim take a
swim how do you get
up
drown we got it we got it this is just a
little it's a it's it's just a little
splash splash in the water we're fine
hello hello we are dipping we are
dipping the water's cool feel I remember
your horse's name but it slips my mind
oh do you maybe from
another your another
time what letter does it start with an a
yeah I think so I think I feel like
there was a strong connection between
you and the horse sad yeah I just can't
remember the name Adam
oh from all the stains she's remembering
she she is all
theing she did see her
memories I should get more all right are
you guys ready to go to the coast this
is where it is the co to go to the coast
yes yes we do so yeah hold on how do I
remove someone Beach episode it's the
magical my mag tomb mag
tomb I would like to get rid of I cannot
get rid of our offline our I mean our
disconnected um I mean our sleeping
member let's see our sleeping member you
mean our our banished member right yes
our banished member she seems to have
disappeared I know not
where let me reform odd yes we must
reform I must reform okay okay sounds
good take shaped to a new
form yes I will accept
curiosity mumbling I'm just reading yeah
you got to open your mouth when you
speak crony what are you reading sorry
sorry okay no need for the sex spicy no
it's okay I get spicy when I make
friends spicy spicy yeah the spice must
flow yeah oh I left all my stuff in a
different Barrel well maybe I'll put put
it in this corner Barrel too if I'm
[Laughter]
allowed yeah I almost take the corner
Barrel breathe underwater we believe
this is no me rumor as the Guild Master
was able to find what does it mean I
don't know it just we're going to be
able to breathe under water just came
into my mind yeah I think we're going to
be able to breathe under water I think
oh next is
Atlantis what what what's
atis I have no
thatly what
tantis does have something to do with t
it starts with t chantis chantis where
you come from Tam oh were you originally
from were you originally a mermaid Tam
maybe that's that's why she's marrying
the king it's like a marriage of
different
countries different species you mean
species different species and countries
lest and mermaids they are joining
together she a mermaid can they
reproduce I'm sure they all right let's
go back to town guys if you talk to I
want to think about that if you talk to
the uh the thing we got to go back to
town okay okay Coral shards huh is what
we need where do we get the coral shards
it says to gather them and then speak to
the Guild Master do you think back where
do we yeah we need 10 yeah where do we
get perhaps there there is some Corals
in the water nearby by I don't know
should we go look wait why why' we try
to go to are you are you leading us to
them are you mayhaps leading us to the
coral the coral
flying okay I was just thinking that you
guys didn't see where it was oh I
see I see Coral rainbow you see are we
collecting it uh oh yeah I got four oh
oh yeah these are oh I'm returning I'm
returning
yo I can't tell if I have how many I
have I need Coral in the water easy yes
so
delicious uh-oh yikes yummy at least
it's not dead coral it's not like the
coral is still alive and fresh which
means that the sea is very clean we got
to go back to
Ruby us there's no more I need
moreal so you can always go back oh
speak to thear Guild
Master I make haste back towards the
kingdom me too let's us
ride I don't know if it's just me but
rubius reminds me of another another
person who has thank you T who was joess
in another
world what's your name Pink
hot pink hot pink yeah wa what's your
name though you could call me hot I have
been expecting you good hero I take it
you have found the rainbow Coral
sh upon receiving word from my
colleagues on the coast I immedately
said about making the necessary
preparations for
crafting with these shards you have
brought the preparations are complet the
Scarlet one is he not the scar the
Scarlet we have to go see he in good
maybe Iris will end finished I do say
I guide my way so this is a rainbow
Coral cluster an object I had only read
of now brought into existence by my very
end not alone but I should not bore you
with my exaltations you need this for
your
quest here you go this will allow you to
uh freely explore the Debs of the sea
use it well and think nothing of payment
or reward as far as I concerned C
is I'm going to in a minute but there is
one thing I would ask of you and that is
your safe return from this Quest I can
think of No Greater way right there's a
path need me you I expect good news upon
your ex it's a a Sandy path right okay
let's see and then rubius is right over
there okay there's rubius yeah yeah yeah
we got it don't worry about
it you guys don't have to worry about me
I'll find my way I have a map right
she'll find her way are you guys
digging you have dig in a tunnel dig in
a
grave they're digging a
grave could be I think they're digging a
grave heck yeah yeah I
think grave
diggers seem our next task would be to
explore but I think our path is blocked
you're digging me yeah it feels like
maybe I don't know I am I am perhaps
give enough time the path will open on
its own the path will open on its own
eventually maybe tomorrow hot pink yes
what Fair the well yes Fair the well
goodbye goodbye goodbye lovely lovely
gorgeous ladies oh I guess this means I
will do a magic trick and disappear oh
it's disappearing oh wait I didn't
disappear right away oh shoot I was I
was planning on disappearing okay EX
he's really silly Exel
Exel okay where's
[Music]
the there we go all right maybe I shall
do something that calls my
name it calls to me call your name it
calls to me a small blue
box a small blue box a small blue
box we're not talking about the manga
right oh wait no no no what's a manga
what
a what what is a
manga is that how you pronounce it I
don't think that's true I not no I've
never seen one before you're right we
wouldn't to pronounce it small I have no
room I guess I I can get fin oh what did
he
do rainbow Coral cluster an object only
red how do I use this waste band oh I
know we become
mermaids just like
Tam just like
Tam just like Tam she didn't need this
item to begin with wait can we
form
Farm we can farm farm I think that's
what the shovel is for right like
growing things
yeah cuz we can build at our Guild base
oh yeah can build a small gu
house and then have some some some weat
so we can not have to pay gold to make
bread right can we can we make bread we
should that we should make our own e
g now we can have like a guil chest
someone is calling me GG I am Jonathan G
she's gathan I thought you were good
game gathan what is good game one I must
drop the telepath
call it's going to drop
it oh I know how to use it now
okay she's in her own world oh hello oh
sorry I was trying to use use the waist
bin I couldn't no problem I don't fit in
it unfortunately uh neither do I it's
kind of unfortunate yeah I was I was
going to you know recycle myself but
yeah you know that's okay you I think
we'd like to keep you for a long time so
please don't resent yourself oh oh
okay fair fair Maiden you are quite
beautiful I just thought I should tell
you you
too thank you your deep Scarlet
eyes like the dear
Scarlet I just I just wanted to say
hello oh hello how how's it going are
you enjoying your life in this in this
realm yeah yes in this realm yeah I I'm
I'm looking for some puppies because I'm
going to run a dungeon with them oh the
puppies
yes did you try try some bone meal bone
bone I I haven't and I haven't located
their position
yet um I don't know maybe I feel like
these magical
words just came up in my head oh what
magical words have come up in your head
bow oh I must show
you may I see what yours
do oh sorry don't worry don't worry it
doesn't hurt incredible incredible I
love it thank you for sharing with me
your magic what a what an interesting
little book Christmas trees yeah it's
a it's a it's pretty pretty normal book
but then you know kind of kind of has
some Powers I think I like it yeah thank
you I like your I like your tuning fork
thank you it's very cool I Bonk people
with it and it makes a loud noise so I
love it oh you think you can uh make a
barbecue
that you know probably I think it would
be really good for roasting marshmallows
yeah I was just thinking you know
totally not hungry
but I am I won't lie I'm hungry yeah I'm
quite actually I'm kind of hungry
too then we should eat together okay I
shall summon the Doos
again oh hello hello hello ladies hello
ladies we got horses you don't we got
horses you don't oh I guess you're just
horsing around then huh yeah Oh no
you're making the same joke I did an
hour ago
nay I disagree n my horse my horse is is
a very onx onxx colored Steed look at
how Majestic my my Steed looks mine's a
normal horse but I like it is it just me
is it just me or is ena's horse like
like a pony sure yeah try moving
Ena why are you making fun of my horse
why is D to you you're just short oh
there we go never mind never mind never
mind I was only pretending to be a pony
yeah wow that was rude don't don't
listen to them don't listen to them G
you're not short at all oh is that the
name of you're a wonderful horse yeah
that's GG I will find my gem it was nice
to see you fair maidens all right take
care survive do
Exel all right well we're going to go to
the coast the coast the coast The Sea
Calls to us yes the ocean the ocean wait
where did where did Fair what was their
name Jonathan with the Cho I'm looking
for you oh hello hello hello you have
returned to us our precious Rock I
finally talking to so many people at the
same time wa you know someone was
looking for you yeah yes I am I am
looking for them she had a fork out
they're in the town you should go look
for that okay I will I will go it's a
tuning fork but you can use it as a
fork oh that's your name oh yeah that's
her name Fair Mor kop I didn't know that
hello Fair n n we're about to head
over to the coast again oh can we do
that dungeon I think I don't
think maybe get ready to do it at Le
ready sure sounds good to me I'll go all
right let us ride let us ride okay let's
the
[Music]
wind
oh we're so fast we are fast and
furious oh I could use some carbonated
drinks right
now love some
carbonated carbonated love do you love
your carbonated
I do indeed
o i I don't know what that means but it
must be something amazing oh wait oh and
we can cook I mean I can cook
investigate speak to the I can stain
meat actually yummy where is this ocean
Temple I think the Ocean Temple is
somewhere far out in the ocean and you
know we have this rainbow Coral cluster
so I think we can bring wa where where's
my rainbow chloral cluster oh yeah we
can yo I can breathe under water let's
swim that's awesome hey me too did you
find your Rainbow Coral
cluster it should be in your inventory
it's not was my inventory
full if you cleared the quest like the
they the rudus gives you one yeah but I
think maybe my inventory was full this
is a rainbow Coral Shard which was used
to make the thing hello Cerulean members
what is happening uh's a coral rainbow
Coral uh cluster is missing oh check my
check my magical
book ah there it is where where was it
in your was it in it was in the magical
to of greatness oh okay thank God for
that thank god oh I can breathe
underwater now brilliant Under the Sea
Under the Sea Under the Sea Under the
Sea Under the Sea Under the Sea Under
the Sea something tell
me I have to watch out for something
called a dmca under the sea I don't know
but it tells me to be careful that
sounds scary DMC sounds absolutely scary
I think I'm going the wrong way oh is
this it I don't know this looks
suspicious where are you guys where have
you wandered
I'm wanding I'm trying to wander off to
the did you find it to the to the thing
on the map what's that that looks like
numbers which thing on the
map like there's a thing on the map that
we're aiming for that's the dungeon I
think the Red Dot on the map that's on
the look like D no not rubius not ruus
um hold
on right side I think I left side left
side left side inside the ocean I'm on
my way yeah I think we're all kind of
split so no
worries don't tell me I can't get these
no I can't you no it looks so beautiful
wow so
deep can I dig can I dig let's try
dig
[Music]
wow
wow oh she's finally joined I will find
what do you mean finally joined welcome
back Tam Tam doesn't want to join the
calls I spoken with someone named Mario
Jonathan keeps dropping the call so I
had I had to speak with Mario Mario said
that she's the queen and that you're a
liar who's Mario I to do this um she is
pink and she looks like a
cat no wonder okay I get it why she's
called Mario okay okay yes that is what
she called herself not Luigi but Mario
okay her name is Mario okay she was the
one making fun of my
name she makes fun of your name she be
able to get into the mysterious place
she kept calling me Tam tenders for no
reason Tam tenders that's not tenders
tenders Tam tenders Tam
tenders why would
she what an EV she said that she wanted
to kill everyone so oh wow that is
yeah that is pretty evil I bet part of
Amber coin yeah not the Amber coin I bet
I bet she's part of Amber coin are the
water we can't get to the dungeon
there's an invisible wall oh I see I
feel like time will solve the problem
wao look there's something called time
this is Diamond did I just go the wrong
way strong enough pickaxe for
this I'm going be rich oh no I'm at the
edge of the map I'm going to be so rich
is hi sorry
I'm oh I knew you going to say that
dungeon is still
dormant oh is that what it says when you
try to enter yes it is
dormant seems that we Cann enter just
yet Perhaps tomorrow maybe we need some
sleep yeah yeah I think it's about time
I need to I need to get some sleep yeah
I sleep get some Shi let's meet again
let us meet R Vu when time opens up a
new gate towards the next when the gate
opens let us meet again I will be
waiting the ceran The ceran Guild
Masters will make us assemble right this
Cerulean assemble right I will find a
carrier pigeon and letting you guys know
with my pigeon
you're a love you you have a lovely
carrier pigeon by the way thank you
thank you that's really cool yes I will
send a pigeon to your inboxes and they
will leave a note to you let we have
inboxes you mean you mean our mailboxes
right yes yes your your mail boxes I
will our carrier
pigeon yes yes
mhm I will send note I'm
getting thank you well have a great one
everyone take care guys take care
everyone farewell fwell meet again
tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow I love you love
you tomorrow how do we all know this
song very weird I don't know only do we
come from the same world maybe that's
crazy I hope not maybe oh why
not why do you hope not I don't I don't
I
good has her problems has her
problems tomorrow yes her name is C I
named
her don't put it like
that I don't like I don't like the sound
of that I
her allowed me to a suggestion farewell
farewell
and th ends the
coal you think we can make
diamond tools at the blacksmith maybe
it's one of the side quests
later what do you mean guys the day is
only starting
[Music]
yeah I'm going to get a whole bunch and
I'll will try it out maybe like a
[Music]
stack it's a side quest Grind
Time oh yeah I was going to buy the the
blue box
huh it seems The Rock has drown I mean
understand
[Music]
probably very hard to
swim unless she's like a volcanic what's
it
called that rock with a lot of holes in
pish then she can kind of FL
ous
Rock oh I didn't mean to get
that I broke something I didn't want to
there we go oh right the waste
bin all right how many we have 53 got a
little I mean we can buy another uh
pickaxe when we get back it's not a
problem look at all this
free free real estate
brilliant maybe I'll also make a little
bit like get some grass and stuff and
then we can start our little little farm
I don't know if we can make bread but
it'd be
nice we got to get to it before the
competition starts you
[Music]
know oh the lantern you're right
although I'll be honest with you I'm
more of a Darkness
person if you know me I don't really
turn on the lights in my
house or I think I used to not
all right 64 oh 65 okay can go
back oh don't mind if I
do oh don't mind if I
do I mean getting extras is good right
can help the
others pick a pikach St
it's so beautiful here though it's quite
amazing I mean we can clear more more uh
side quest maybe we can get more gold
and we'll be decked out a new new
clothes
oh I can't do
[Music]
the I wanted to do the the flying fish
thing ah the ocean at night is so calm
look at how beautiful it
is so
beautiful all right Let's Go
Gigi back
home wait maybe I can grab some grass
blocks while I'm here
anyways I should be able to do that
right oh I can
okay
okay we can make a small farm I don't
know what the ground is in the guild
space
so might as well grab some you
know I can just walk doing
this it's grass well you know you can
never have enough wait I think the Box
had a whole bunch of construction blocks
maybe I didn't need
this you never know
oh it's the
toos bow
bow all
right let's check the side quest first
actually
Help Wanted at the cavern
oh I'll let you use the cook I can
cook help one to the the
[Music]
tower
oh I can
cook Shi
came at the perfect time the customer
has just ordered the delivery cuz she
delivered this cake to Celesta the cing
oh
oh hey hello are you also I told was all
H huh what did you got did you got the
memory back do you remember now I only
remember something about Ki Mor oh
oh I see yeah perhaps we'll get more
stuff down the line more memories oh
wait I have a phone call one second mush
mus I am I am walking
around all
right got to go back to celum
moim Mo
to my guild leader who
ordered a sandwich I
think Meer doco
ah ah yes this is the cake oh it was a
cake cake I ordered thank you kind hero
May the ancestor nourish you as this
conection will nourish
me let's go
now we go back to the
Shi I didn't understand I
think hello
[Music]
stf update carrot and
potato oh that's at the
shop carrot and
potato I have no inventory
I don't need
this I
mean h wooden sword oh
[Music]
yeah
okay yeah the swords don't break I think
you asked the blacksmith to make one for
you
okay I'm so hungry I need to make
[Music]
food
blacksmith I'm
back Ariel are in Game
both oh the cooking pot
[Music]
I'll put this potato salad back where it
belongs
okay get rid of the stone tools I guess
so they're good backup but I guess the
sword doesn't really run out
so it should be
okay okay hello
[Music]
Chef take this egg and beetroot combine
them with the ingredients to brought to
make potato
salad
oh so
[Music]
how do
I
potato inside the
pot it's not going
anywhere yeah it's not
the middle oh oh that's the lid I see
what else do I need to eat oh
egg right oh there's a recipe book
[Music]
need the
beetroot oh beetroot is in the
Tob oh oh there's a cake oh oh my
goodness there's so many items can I put
I can't put
items all right this is my secret
chest all right
[Music]
okay let's try that
again carrot
egg you did
it a nice cut of stained meat salt salt
and pepper put it on a
grill oh okay let's see some recipe
[Music]
books potato salad nourishing soup sweet
berries and water bucket butter milk
bucket slime
Jam raw
noodles there's a lot of recipes
[Music]
I feel like we do need to start uh
farming stuff it's quite interesting
quite interesting
indeed okay let me retrieve
these okay so my side quest is done
let's see if there's any other
Quest cuz we didn't see any diamond uh
things oh looking for five gold ingots
okay so I feel like if we keep doing the
side quest there will
be one for Diamond that's what I'm
guessing you do have some raw
gold oh I can turn the side oh there's
[Music]
pages and then there's going to be
probably like enchantments too oh five
[Music]
Diamonds the Smithy make a backpack
oh lapis lo oh I should have gotten some
lapis
too
[Music]
milkshake arm
wrestling oh 10
stains okay let's let's start with these
there's a lot I think backpack is really
important
okay um oh I didn't mean to do
that while I
have
a gold going I go and give
diamond
oh backpack 200 coins
coins oh wait diamond tools already
th000
coins stain
bone I only have hide where do we get
the
bone maybe it's a different type of
stain we got the back pack which is
pretty important
okay it's not that much stuff
but you know
useful
uh okay where would we get stain B maybe
it's further away can I buy multiple
backpacks I think
so buy two backpacks oh you got to
Smart okay this one's going to be
food well have this bread maybe
everything else I cook I'll put in here
potions can go in here
too can I name my
[Music]
backpack I can't
Can I stack backpacks what if I break
the server it's like n there's a forbid
move then put this
[Music]
here okay got the gold ingot
nice lapis lazuli okay we got golden
ones too there's there's something else
we can buy here it seems like
it's uh backed
by I guess side
quests
interesting it's a mysterious tool of
some kind
okay now that's more like
it
okay wonder if they're doing it
again okay there's
that guess I can go out to get some
lapis oh this is so
[Music]
fun where do we find
lapis no there was some by the oh no no
I think there was some by this
place maybe
or is this it just copper and
gold oh invisible
walls I think we have to go underwater
yeah it's okay quick detour very
fun nice
Moon get this
way wow
I mean the
underwater dungeon Place had a lot of
other stuff too
so it's worth the worth a
visit it's the map available
[Music]
yeah except I think uh
we can't go in the dungeon yet got to
wait till
tomorrow maybe we'll grab some Redstone
and Lapis I think lapis will help us
enchant stuff or allow us to start
enchanting stuff which is
good this is so much
[Music]
fun oh yeah I was going to buy new uh
pickaxe to carry around totally
forgot yeah these ones are hard to mine
cuz
they're
um they're
underwater we'll find one that's and you
know we might as well grab some some of
these where there's one up there
[Music]
is there like a easily accessible one I
mean there's a redstone over
there oh there's one over there okay
just grab these real quick you know you
know what I'm
saying I think I'll grab have some extra
cuz I feel like you will need them to
enchant
stuff o more
[Music]
time never know what you'll need in this
world
diamonds and stuff respawn really quick
so I'll just I'll just mine stuff until
41 wow it's a
lot yeah I need to get more money
too I mean I can do the good old
grind I'll mind until this pickaxe
breaks and then I'll go
oh yeah I should get redstone
oh there's a easy red
stone I meant to
eat oops
stain archers with archers I
mean who would drop a
bone yeah I do need the bones to make
the diamond tools as well
so I don't think the stained skeletons
maybe there's a skeleton
but the dungeon ones didn't really drop
anything other than the items needed for
the dungeon itself
so I don't know if they'll necessarily o
[Music]
already maybe a new area cuz I feel like
if they introduced you know diamond
tools this early they'll at least have
something
to not let us do get it as
quickly okay I think that's good
enough I will bring more lapis just in
[Music]
case Shop sell stain hide so maybe I'll
have some stain bones after side quest
possible possible they never intended
for people to grind but this
is this
is Hol
[Music]
life but I guess I will uh perhaps
not overdo it so that I don't
accidentally break the balance and
anything is what the voice in my head is
[Music]
telling okay time to go
back but he I wonder I feel like the
side quests are there for to be done
like throughout the
entire to totally
right it's time to I don't think I lose
levels when I die let's see how much I
can get to by the
end show up to the uh to the dungeon
tomorrow hey
guys level
99 allthough levels in in in this world
doesn't really give you startat or
anything
so you know it's pretty fun
I mean I'm like almost a third of the
way there
right ah this is bringing me back to the
good old days I mean I'm starting to
remember the joy of the grind
the joy of the
grind the good old
days
[Music]
oh 200 coins let's go
can't forget that milkshake they say
huh milkshake that brings all the stains
to the
yard and they're
like the
bartender Okay so with the
ingredients apple melon slice and Sweet
Berry Apple mil melon
slice
Apple I think Apple I might be able to
get but Sweet
Berry I don't know if I can take from
the garden Kell
or is it in the shop is it in the shop
oh I don't think I've seen it in the
[Music]
shop
ah of course oh melons oh we have to
grow
them and a hint of
what it's farming time
[Music]
melon Apple melon SC and Sweet
Berry I think Apple we can get from the
tree
outside can break the leaves
[Music]
I thought that was an apple but it
wasn't the fallen leaves tell a
story do
they it's it is this type of tree right
from what I'm
remembering my memory fails
[Music]
me wonder if it drops here too
ah got an apple okay we're
[Music]
done okay maybe I'll stop after this
Quest wait I have to stay some stains
anyways okay slay stains and then
milkshake and then we'll we'll start the
farm and then we'll end it
it's fun but I don't want to be too
ahead or maybe I can go go go run the
first dungeon try solo it I think I can
solo it maybe
[Music]
how many do we have to kill probably
have a couple more
left yeah but I don't have the uh
Whatchamacallit
stain bones maybe maybe I don't I need
to empty out my pocket
hold on let me go inside and end out my
pocket maybe it's a rare
drop that I'm missing out
[Music]
on
uh cuz we have the slime ball meat and
hide that's a lot of diamonds
[Music]
okay that was
10 okay
the soldier guys if you find them in the
over I guess so those are like kind of
supposed to be
stronger stronger stains
[Music]
right wonder why I'm supposed to go for
the oh Quest Master prob
[Music]
okay got that milkshake okay we got to
go
to our
guilded wait don't we also need to get
[Music]
a I guess melons you don't need
the whatchamacallit
uh the thing for
farming got to go back to the
gardens this the C is no the other
way the rake
I wonder if I can just plant It On The
Ground wouldn't that be
funny now we need the thing with Jiggy
[Music]
there were melons in the garden oh there
were maybe we can Farm
afterwards ohoh there is you're right
oh
brilliant you guys say wait I didn't
need to buy berries they're right
here
unbelievable
[Music]
unbelievable I just wasn't sure if these
were breakable I
guess I'm
bub all right
bartender where you at
che
[Music]
oh oh wait bartender not
Chef
[Music]
apple melon
slice and Sweet Berry
[Music]
this
guy and
milk how do we get
milk does the shop have like a
[Music]
can I make
bucket there are cows
but I mean there are crafting tables I
wonder if we can just make
a I mean technically we could make a
crafting table but Bucket from Smithy
that's the thing like I feel like there
must be a way to get a bucket right
[Music]
I mean only one way to find out I
guess well there's the water
[Music]
cauldron r b b
see there is a crafting
table what bucket again I need to I need
more
IR oh yeah it's in the
[Music]
backpack it's a v right okay I
remembering I'm starting to remember
okay oh oh I
Can Wait so technically if you remember
the recipe
if we have somehow regained our memories
for the
recipe okay uh
this
cow oh okay now it does that okay
okay ahuh aha
[Music]
aha oh it keeps
happening not quite what I remember
milkshake I have was thicker and richer
one slime jam and speak to the
bartender slime
[Music]
Jam Sweet Berry slime ball
sugar
[Music]
sh uh you have a berry slime ball so I
guess we
cook I'll just put put
one slime
Jam I'm cooking guys I'm
cooking oh no they keep
falling are they okay mix that in it's
getting closer but the milk sh I
remember tasted fancier more
expensive eat a different type of apple
it was yellow very shiny
what one golden apple and speak to the I
need another Apple this bartender is
really
[Music]
pecky oh we can already do
that I thought we already like used up
the the Apple but I guess
not I'm good
oh not the horse
again all
right surely this
[Music]
time I yes that looks like the Apple I
remember them
using this is it this is the taste I
remember goodness I can't thank you
enough 500
[Music]
coins
wow I'm rich I'm
rich I think we have enough to maybe buy
something and still have
money
[Music]
yeah wait I still have the apple and
stuff all right what are we going to
get oh I can choose which one guys the
very
center top left middle
left top left very first one a middle
one follow my
heart okay I'll
go first Row 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 construction supply
box Amber coin baller no slime
stain ran camp
[Music]
I can take
this no I didn't get it
no
[Music]
okay all right guys which
one I only got a construction supply
box one 2 3
[Music]
5 12 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 Jade sword
ham what
but it's not my
house can I not wear
[Music]
it oh now get it
off I have a helmet
get it off doesn't
belong uh let's
see I'll put it in here for
[Music]
now huh
unbelievable okay now
what I guess guess I could go check out
what the other
uh what the other quests are I guess we
can go to dungeon afterward haunted
[Music]
house have too much stuff to carry all
by myself moving house enchantment
research
[Music]
oh what
I didn't
even arm wrestling slay some oh slay
some oh go back to the report your
findings oh I was going to do that
anyways good thing we
checked food deliver a potato salad to
the quest Master okay I can do that
too there's 12 of
them Bor in fried stain
special stained
stew oh the l a wooded shovel oh I
should have thrown it
out I guess I can just go buy it from
the
thing stone pickaxe to the quest okay so
we
need one stone
pickaxe and then one one wooden
shovel oh these are just for cold I
think I heard someone they're
[Music]
gone okay enchantment research what do
we got to
do oh hello
who a good
kitty who's a good
kitty yes you
are what what you up
to I am helping some some people making
quests and
dungeons okay yeah what are you up to uh
doing some side quests it's pretty
fun that sounds cool okay well have fun
have have fun bye good luck with your
side quest you too
byebye Can it can it pat your head as
well I guess this time maybe you
[Laughter]
can okay
bye why oh why sounds so familiar
[Music]
wow I think there's a quest here golden
shovel enchanted with efficiency three
or
higher golden
shovel and I need
my okay efficiency three or higher
how do
I it's efficiency
[Music]
too oh
napit Unbreaking efficiency
2 enchant something else to reset it
enchant my
sword
Unbreaking wait why did this come out
[Music]
here should I use level
one sharpness two
oh Unbreaking
three I just need two more levels where
do I have two more levels I mean I have
to go take stains out anyway just might
as well do
[Music]
that efficiency not oh efficiency not
Unbreaking right that's
[Music]
unfortunate oh
uh
oh I can't do that while I'm on the
horse
unbelievable oh wait we can deliver the
potato
salad
right it's the other
one there's a wait
it's oh I can what
[Music]
huh maybe the magical tomb
[Laughter]
[Music]
no wait hold on
let me just report this to the uh
authorities you find a missing
bag huh you did you find a lost bag no
it's my own bag but it's uh it's
glitched so oh no it copied the exact
same object as my other bag when it was
opened oh wow and uh it happened to be
the back that has a lot of
uh good things in
it oh no so I'm I'm reporting it to the
authorities well I hope they'll get back
to you yeah Gamba okay
Gamba items in the first pack
amazing hello hello you have a LP I do
you I like your L what have you learned
today I have learned that this world is
full of mysteries and wonders full of
mysteries I would like to uncover these
Mysteries yeah this m my
horse can I see your revelation oh oh of
course of
course
[Music]
Revelation yeah
Revelation it's shiny that's
right oh yours is K
[Music]
too wow can I see yours oh yeah okay
Revelation
wow ring
hello let's try at the same time oh yeah
are they
stin that's so
cute it's so cute and fluffy and fuzzy
like you guys
bow oh B bow we need to find the co the
up here but it doesn't really look like
a CO um you guys need the way yes please
show us the way yeah follow me okay
okay oh yeah I have a horse
[Laughter]
too oh this is the way
like all right follow me
okay and then you go this
[Music]
way you go through here what
no this the co this is the coast oh
the all right my job here is
done thank you what's your name goodbye
mysterious hero I mysterious hero I
farewell friends
farewell oh I can't I can't leave okay
farewell my
exit it was supposed to be
epic all right it's time to defeat some
stain oh Another
Hero I wonder if
there's
W have we been here are we allowed to go
here oh of course there's not time yet I
do not have to
right cuz I took her
left okay let's defeat some stains I'm
guessing yeah the bones probably Dro
from a new area of
stain okay this area is pretty good for
uh
it seems the Overworld Powers have
answered and asked not to use the
backpack for the rest of the day if
possible I shall
[Music]
comply it seems the the powers have
agreed that there are slight errors in
the
message okay just a couple
more okay
[Music]
wonder if there's a way to dodge their
charges yeah there is to kill them
before before they hit me
[Music]
ow best defense is a great
offense I guess I might as well just
make another potato salad what did I
need I need a potato
beetroot oh but oh wait but I know where
there's another potato salad
[Music]
did I finish the
quest for
stains I don't think
so did I even accept
it I know where there's a salad the
stale one but they wouldn't notice
right I forgot the stain
one okay it's fine we can do it again I
mean we need the experience anyways
ah there we
go and I believe it was in here
[Music]
get rid of the sticks maybe just I can
make more so should be
okay
okay objective
completed now where
does who wanted to potato Sal the quest
master I should make a a a chest and put
some stuff
in yes 100
coins
nice is there always just I guess some
of them I didn't complete some of them
are repeatable probably
oh yeah this one is
repeatable just make a whole bunch of
potato salad and repeat the
quest okay 10
uh uh okay let's make a
chest oh but my wood I think
is oh okay I I do have it okay
I mean I guess I could make
a yeah I'll make a one in the kild think
kild this this
way yeah I mean I don't want to empty
out both oh someone already made some
chests and stuff nice
put ours
[Music]
here wait why don't why don't the quests
get rid of the
items that we made
over can I eat this
Jam I can't
[Music]
oh I could place cake on the ground
nope
okay you know what let me throw out the
stain meat cuz I'm going to get more
anyways okay now oh we
[Music]
can okay it's just that I can't place
the cake on the ground of course that
will ruin the
cake
uh oh the recipes are gone oh I'm
starting to remember how to
make a
chest you a chest
starting I'm starting to
remember oh I remember it's an O
right how could I
forget oh I
remember all
right um
okay this is the real
bag I'll leave this other
bag in here I I I wish oh I can't leave
it in here
okay I'll leave these stuff in here
maybe oh finally some
space what happens if I have both in my
bar still it over writes or overr one of
the bags
so
H I'll just do
that maybe I'll put oh I didn't mean to
that sugar in here
[Music]
cake uh this stuff I probably still
need uh can't really move that there I
can't put the cake in the can't be
traed what can I place
it I can't it's bugged it just can't be
traded or
anything oh well oh yeah I should go get
an
iron
um
Whatchamacallit I should maybe get the
stuff out of the
backpack
uh and place it in the chest so that I
know
[Music]
which is the real
deal I already told stuff about it yes I
mean the the overw worldly
[Music]
beings I don't know how the resets going
to change things so I'll just leave
things in here
[Music]
how do you make a sign again was it
like don't
[Music]
remember six planks
oh this
is I made
SLS I don't think I have any more
wood my
bad 9 in moment you know what we're
going to go to the dungeon
oh my
brain construction box oh you are
correct
indeed ooh
oh so you it trades for
[Music]
oh
oh hello Fair Maiden I have a a question
yes I have I have heard that there is
something called gaj uh yes in these
parts do you know what it could mean uh
I believe there talking about the
possibility of getting lovely hats from
the shop hat they hat
hats where in the shop yes yes at the
shop there is a blue box you can get I
think for 300 gold each and you can get
some
hats thank you for this information
Fair no is
fine yes no yeah thank you so much for
this information no worries good luck
Fair Maiden good luck thank you thank
you fair Maiden empathy let's go let's
[Music]
go okay I think I'm ready for the
dungeon you think I think after I return
from the dungeon I probably have enough
experience points Maybe
[Music]
all
right it's time to Solo solo
leveling it's time to
arise if I can find the way out of here
that
is I remember the way oh it's this way
okay
do I have enough food I
do oh I was going to oh oh hello Fair
Maid I found the I found the house thank
are you going to do the
do I've heard that there is a pit where
you can gamble your money as well there
is oh you do not know I do not
know
oh there's it in the pit oh the pit I
see oh what the pit door
man the pit door man yeah the gamble you
like to investigate it together I guess
we could do that I could take a slight
detour oh what what are you currently
working on I was going to go solo the
dungeon oh do we have twin
horses I think we
do wow wait actually we don't mine has
the mine has the
marshmallows it's they're from the same
family yes yes yes well I don't want to
interrupt you on your quest but I would
I would like to see where it is just you
know in case the sun is rising okay
let's
go the
pit we're in the pit this is the
Coliseum
no the p P what is what is the pig
uh
uh the white building is the is this
the the white
building opposite way they say follow me
follow me Fair Maiden okay
ah I think I see
it the home of the Ember coin of
course where else would it
be the
[Music]
pit make a bet the rules select the
color you want the bet on decide on how
many coins to bet Canon will start
firing taking up four color squar with
each slot after six shots only one
square will remain player who bets on
that color wins winning player will
receive a payout based on the
multiplayer list on the color they bet
on oh o what do I bet at the
bookie oh I want to bet
on uh oh there's chances I'll try I'll
try yellow
[Music]
okay surely this oh I see the cannon now
it's on the wall over
[Music]
there I made a bed on
yellow maybe you'll get
it oh they're firing the cannon
[Music]
oh
again
H
[Music]
oh I get it I get it now I
get oh no the chances
oh there's one yellow
left no you
won won the
chances so lucky I got 50 coins wow wow
wow that's that's
pretty
wow all right I should have more you
should have I should have but I was like
this my first my first I want to see how
it works but I see how it works it's
okay next
time thank
youting take care good luck I might be
here a bit
uh have fun at your dungeon all let's go
let's go let's
go wow she's a very lucky Maiden unlike
me I'm just a
I'm just a you know wait where am I
going I think this is towards the castle
I want to go this way I'm just a
normal normal person with normal
luck wait I do have the quest right I
think so let me double check that after
I think I accepted the quest
get stains and dungeon Revisited okay
let's
go it's okay I'll just slowly and and
safely Rock up my coins to buy all the I
need to survive in this
world oh maybe I'll finish this the
stain Quest here first
cuz I think I can get quite a few
here there's a lot of animals here
though I feel
like there's a need for uh thinning down
the crow
perhaps wake up wake up wake up wake up
wake
up wake up wake up wake up wake up it's
time to
die can I use this on the horse maybe I
can oh I
can that makes things a lot
easier oh never
mind oh wait I I got the quest what
I can't aim though that is
true need to wait for the cool down
Teresa just kite them
around make them into a very cute little
group easy to aim
nice all right to the dungeon
I think after 30 I should have like
enough
for enough for like
[Music]
one extra
enchantment so I can reset to get
efficiency 3 was
it oh yeah to leave the party
[Music]
okay oh I can check all my side quest
here too magical
book one wooden shovel I should have
done that too oh
[Music]
well okay
well ooh raw chicken where did I get
that I wonder
all
right can we need some intense
music
oh okay that's pretty intense let's go
ha ha ha ha
ha and H
[Music]
grab
checkpoint to battle
[Music]
nice time to eat
nice
okay oh almost fell
ho
[Music]
that'll be funny if I fell the last
one all right this is going to be kind
of maybe the hard part cuz there might
be a lot of mobs
right got I got the three
shapes we did enchant our sword though
so it's slightly stronger they do die in
one
hit I need the shapes need to go deeper
ah okay got one need a star in a
circle okay found the door
star circle circle
too Circle
C there
triangle can't believe I have to
actually go searching for them
[Music]
ah give me that give me that all right
we're
good
nice oh is this
the can I read
this think
so is this the right oh maybe I didn't
is this the right thing to
do no I don't think dungeon mobs give
exp never mind I guess we got just get
rid of the
STS we got the
checkpoint ah it's you again we'll be
here a
[Music]
while uh how did I do the first time
oh
[Music]
easy I think I got the concept
oh now this is the
part where it's scripted
right
goes then I
fall
[Music]
oh
okay come on
going aim myself
here pretty
easy I think this dungeon is
easy like solo cuz
it doesn't have the
argro jumping around
[Music]
wait I think it would have been harder
if these had the bows but
[Music]
yeah they I mean with with the bow
enemies right you got
to make use of line of sight that's the
that's the big brain
play okay one's done
[Music]
da
wa I think one more was
it
nice don't know which one we have to
climb first I guess either is fine oh
probably the
othere I remember I fell last time
[Music]
wa is this the
way don't think so this
one wait
wait
and ah oh
gravity oh I almost
fell okay this wasn't the
way is here
then
[Music]
so wait wait is this start
way I can't
tell wait
follow the
buttons oh I guess the buttons show you
the way
huh you know what close it up as long as
I'm going up it's
fine
ah ow
nice that was
it we did it that was pretty good I
think that was pretty good thank you
thank
you zero death let's go
now I just got to go back to the wait
did
F do horses change every time you summon
them did I just realize
that they change every
time I just
realized okay thank you friends I'm done
here my job here is
done it's like a random Force
generator the technology of lesto is is
astounding all right I think what was it
was it a
wooden wooden
shovel should I buy it should I make it
can I make it
I want to spend my spend my
money I have the wood
oh meano
Rock
oh how do you make a
shovel I'm starting to remember how to
make a a
shovel I'm I'm
starting people lost coins
in oh I'm I'm starting to
remember I'm starting to remember
I guess we
can't I have to buy it darn they
knew they knew what what was going to
happen fine I'll live by the rules when
in
leesta
leesta do as leesta
wooden shovel
okay then iron pickaxe for myself oh I
don't have the iron I'll do it
later okay to the quest
Master Okay wooden shovel dungeons okay
350 honestly you know what let's go
check the uh
enchantment
right I have the lapis I think I left
left the lapis at
home
uh efficiency two still
efficiency
one I guess I could try go
for I should have just I should just
leave lapis
here if you combine two golden shovels
with efficiency two you can get
efficiency three that is true
[Music]
no I don't want to use the dupe ones cuz
that's that's not the proper way you
know it cost way more yeah you know what
I'll worry about that later this this I
think these side quests are
probably some them are repeatable and or
some of them are you know not a whole
rush
so you
know we
uh we'll do them
later all right where should we end it
wrap it up for the day maybe at the
guild base near my near my
supply all
right well
oh that was
long but we did it we played for a long
time tomorrow I
believe um I might join later in the day
because I do have you know a convention
appearance I have to be
at or at least wait this is this is n
inanis i have taken over Nino Ina's
body so uh there's that
um yeah but uh I technically have to
go
uh stay near the studio I have to
actually pack and
go uh cuz there's a Typhoon Warning and
I need to be at the studio very early in
the morning tomorrow
so hopefully it works out hopefully I
don't you
know lose my umbrella
but anyways thank you very much everyone
coming to watch this stream today I hope
you guys enjoyed it thank you take
care until next
time bye-bye