hey do I have your attention well done
takas fre year anniversary celebration
merchandise is ready for pre-order now
we got a lot of cute stuff so please
consider it we have small W not and Pen
a backpack a luggage tag and uh this one
comes with a limited edition version uh
Polo ride yeah look it's so cute oh it
comes with a little calendar inside and
a pen wow so so oh and the backpack yes
in turquoise a really really nice color
it comes with rubber charm and a rubber
patch and inside of course it's some
orange kfp design let's go and the
luggage tag oh my God it even comes with
a paper where you can write your address
and your name and everything on top and
then you put it on your suitcase I
recommend this and if you are able to
now now if you watch this at like the
moment it comes out then you have a
chance for a limited merch yes well I
will sign with my own hands otherwise uh
full set comes with the Polaroid that is
signed by a machine or so I guess yay
thank you for your attention and free
the
w