keeping me captive ESC my way you say
I'm way to fragile I'm just Idol
[Music]
bre you I don't even know what to do
with this
[Music]
you don't even know what to do this
you make me fall in
[Music]
don't even know do
this good play my Mir
[Music]
the on and and
reflection going
underused Obsession I still wonder if I
was made for you if I could only see oh
[Music]
pleaseing you never see what I want what
I need oh do
[Music]
you you I don't even know what do
this good
play with the don't do
anything left F I did a king and queen
of
you you see you all
[Music]
meag I need do you
do follow through let
you
now me I you
[Music]
yeah there reflection going under
confused Obsession I still wonder if I
was made for you if I could I only
see oh please oh make me up a new
persona calculated perfectly for you
pretending like it's all just for me
don't think so live life in C
why got and yet I'm asking why you never
see what I want what I need oh do you no
no now I follow through like you pursue
by
now you me on a mirage I you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this tell me to C be good playing part
my
[Music]
Mir told you I do
anything I'll be the king and queen of
new Fise
you see I'm you you're all of me it
seems like everyone wants it all run
around running run around on and on the
cycle keeping me captive Escape my way
you say I'm way too fragile I'm just
your perfect Idol break me shap me
high you never see what I want what I
need oh do you no no now I follow
through like you pursue but now
oh you saw me on a mirage I tow you up
into shred I don't even know what to do
with
this Play Your Part by
[Music]
Mir SP disgu on and on and on dis I'm
lost me me me me me me r
you make me fall
in you make
me oh
[Music]
no do it this tell me to it be good Play
Your Part my Mir
me me me spinning the light disgu on and
on and on and on this Mir I'm
[Music]
lost yeah
ah
[\h__\h] I had some problems right before
the stream and then apparently it
reset something with the mouth it was
too wide open
again I'm going to
fix I've learned to fix many things on
my
own uh lip sync setting
yeah it reset itself it wasn't supposed
to be that big I know that's a bit weird
and it's that big because I I'm using a
combination a hybrid
combination of
like face tracking and like reacting to
the sound when I sing then it reacts a
lot also what the hell like H I'm still
new to this but the mic was why is it so
it I keep them I'm drifting away
wait I'm basically in the wild I started
all the way over there I swear I
adjusted it it was so
close bro I'm
drifting like Michael
Jackson oh yeah oh well why did I set
that up and I'm going to just drift away
from
[Music]
it but yeah see I set up some cameras
we're already improving from the
Halloween stream I
oh I was wondering when I'm switching
camera like what this wasn't how I set
it up oh there was there once was a mic
there I but I think I'm I'm Drifting in
My yeah I'm drifting in my motion
capture uh xense program let me try to
bring myself
back uh using this as
reference um
[Music]
Wait no that's the wrong axis I I always
have to guess I'm never
sure
uh
bro have you tried walking no that
doesn't work like that I probably just
move further back
[Music]
I I I've arrived but we'll probably move
back again and there's no point in
this well the mic the mic can go
honestly
hi but do I look
[Music]
cute come on can I not zoom in anymore
that's not that can't be
true maybe I maybe I should make myself
bigger I don't know
oh hey what's up is my butt toggle
on let me double check that too probably
turn itself
off ah here magic is going to happen 3
two one okay it's just a tiny
buff but that's good that satisfies me a
little bit here let me move this a
little bit too yay
welcome to the one Mirage 1 million
views Milestone celebratory
commemoratory
stream
yay
yooo in which I show to you this
model and maybe sing again with better
with the less open
mouth look it's so pretty it has this
like irid
desend chromat I don't know I don't know
how to describe this but this wasn't in
the MV to start off with as you may
notice the
color it was just white there but this
was like the original
[Music]
intention yay
beautiful
wow M I really like it and that's
um maybe one or two small things added
to it that improve it even
more H I will show you I will show you
but first of all let's take a closer ooh
not like
that a closer look at my face
oh oh oh oh shapes ah shapes e
shapes and I can
do this cat
mouth
cute cute
[Music]
right of course blowing up the cheeks as
as always is necessary
nowadays holding holding my breath until
Mirage reaches 1 million oh there's no
need anymore yay
yeah and I think my teeth are really
pretty now in this in this
model ah cuz normally Waba doesn't have
very visible teeth as you may
know but now I
[Music]
do tongue is there as well
tongue before my life Tod gets a tongue
I get a tongue in 3D of
course by the way reminded this is not
an official
model this is just my Mirage model that
I'm allowed to use uh for special
circumstances only not like every
day um but yeah I want to start with
like some credits this will be a short
stream by the way I I I don't really
have that much to
do um where should
we m
oh it's
fun wow I feel so I feel so wow
professional it's like I'm like doing uh
showing you the new Apple
iPhone that's what I feel I'm doing so
as you may
[Music]
remember the original design was from
Mii who drew like a lot of different
designs for me and um they're really
pretty we I went like chose like the
more simple style one because I thought
o for dancing and for modeling it with
small amount of time in the first place
is probably good to go for a simple one
I talked about all of this in the Mirage
song and live recap live stream a while
ago mhm oh by the way I didn't see I
didn't see Kik
ke let me say Kik ke Kik ke
[Applause]
[Music]
yay have I moved further back again I
wonder I'll have to recalibrate myself
maybe later cuz it's it's at some point
I'll probably fall for the world that's
why I I couldn't start on time I fell
for the world right the
beginning okay yay where was I here on
this camera wow nice this looks like a
TV
commercial m
H okay okay where was I
here yay thank you so much and I think I
then requested like a Black Version too
which is how the Black Version came to
life cuz I thought you know it's nice to
have a little bit of a variety but ain't
nobody got the budget to have a second
completely different design 3d model in
the music video so just use the same
model and do a recaller you know I like
to do that like with my default outfit
as well yeah yeah the tips and tricks on
how to save money just by yours trly
takanashi
Kiana yes and so in the
MV actually a different model was used
if you look closely you will notice
differences in for example how these
Jewels are modeled and the hair the
ponytail is quite different actually uh
what else
yeah this effect of the shininess is not
there here and there there's some
differences because different people
modeled it and I talked I talked all
about this before as well how it came to
all of this but basically now there's
like two or three or four Mirage models
um and versions of it there's like a
there's the MV version which is made by
chainon um but then the ones with the
YouTube shorts are the chaintown model
with like like added on beautiful like
Colors by chy that's like the YouTube
short version and then there's the Sean
version the old version before chainon
came in and then seon dropped out but
then Sean came back after the MV was
done and see was like I want to finish
this model and this is the result of the
uh post and be finished model by Sean
basically made for me to use like this
for a stream to show it off because I
think the other model the MV model would
not have been like properly set up for
me to use in this
program so
this okay and then yeah so as I was just
talking about it the 3D modeler for this
model is Sean who has done a few models
for me like fan on on a fan-made basis
so far thank you so much I really really
love how it turned
out I really really like it see is uh of
course one of us a
kfp thank you so much for your help yeah
Sean has also like been trying to figure
out and help other things like how to do
the the lip sync how to improve the lip
sync and
stuff oh we got a ring by the way have
you seen that ring
if you like it then you should put a
ring on
[Music]
it you want to see that don't you I
don't think it'll look that
good I'm so far I wasn't so far when I
adjusted this did I was
I oh man I should just stay in a
close-up then you won't notice that I'm
drifting actually no I could
um I could whoa
Mama
Mia I don't get it I need to
recalibrate so but I don't want to do
that so I'll
just I'll just add this camera is fine
for now how long I wonder yeah this this
world is kind of like based on the
virtual take the not the VIR the first
T I just wanted a simple place
so so so so
so where's my
mouse yes now I want to show you a
little special edition that wasn't there
in the MV but if you
recall here in the back don't look at my
butt so much look at those wings right
oh actually yeah those they don't
look much like the ones in the MV you
got to compare them guys I don't know if
I can get around me but you see
that aren't they pretty oh they're so
pretty they're like a little bit more
defined now and um what I can do let me
show you it's like my favorite
feature let me show you my favorite
feature what's it going to be
what's it going to be a feature that I
don't know since this is a model that
I'm not going to be using every day who
knows when I'll be using it but it's
cute so whatever
taada oh my
god I'm an
angel they come
out and I can add a Halo to it I'm a
legitimate angel
[Music]
I'm an
angel I could be your angle or I could
be your oh
wait let me say that again but be ready
for it I could be your angle or I could
be
your
devil de
de wo
oh
nice so this is like the leather Vibe
but I was thinking like this looks a
little bit like lat
latex but if I move around you see how
the reflections like make the black
leather little bit more like purplish
it's
pretty and here instead of like the
green we have the
red and the wings oh I I didn't try them
out in Black yet I wonder they probably
work
too don't
they Let's test it out well the Halo oh
the Halo wait no the the wing the wings
are just going to be normal Wings right
oh yeah
[Music]
sick I'm your
de evil Halo oh two w on your show ERS
which one will you listen to
H
cute very cute this
n
shoes nice shoes nice legs nice
boots yeah now can I redeem myself and
sing Mirage again with better with
reduced mouth
opening and maybe we'll bring the mic
back should I should I bring the mic
back I'll bring the mic
back let's
[Music]
see wait a yeah I turned it
off okay come here come to
me come microphone come we can do it in
in Black Version this time
mhm how's that
looking
uh yeah
[Music]
yeah
uh
uh help it's inside of
me that looks
okay let's see how far will how far we
will drift away all right right now it's
[Music]
fine nice okay let's try it again let's
try it again First Take
waa I'll try to not clip into it it's
going to break the break the immersion
my microphone is actually here isn't
that perfect wow it's so
immersive okay
ah
[Music]
oh
yeah Mir reflection going under confused
obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could only
see oh please oh make me up a first all
not culated perfectly for you pretending
like it's all just for me don't
[Music]
think and yet I'm asking why you never
see what I want what I need oh do you no
no I'm drifting again
follow through like you pursue but
[Music]
now me on a mirage IW you up into shreds
I don't even know what to do with this m
tell me to Cross good Play Your Part my
Mir my
Mir told you i' do
anything but i' be a king and queen of
you
from I'm you you're all of me it seems
like everyone wants it all run around
running around on and on the cyle
keeping me captive Escape my way you say
I'm way too fragile and just your
perfect it don't break me shave
me you'll never see what I want what I
need oh do you no no no follow through
like you
[Music]
pursue you Me On A Mir I you up stress I
don't even know what to do with this
mess good Play You by
Mir
SP on and on
and
me me me me me me me me me
[Music]
me you make me fall
in you make me
feel
no you s me on a mirage I to you up into
Tre I don't even know what to do with
this tell me the C it be good say your
part my
Mir I sping little on and on and
[Music]
on o
ah I reached the
wall
no I wasn't
there don't [\h__\h] with
me oh
man I need to figure out how to I mean I
don't really think there's a good fix
for it but I need to figure out how to
stop drifting away let me may I
recalculate please a Rec
recalibrate H you may now listen to my
recalibration
process uh yeah go to a starting
position where you can safely perform
the calibration
yeah so it's kind of
loud stand and in pose relaxed and look
straight ahead for 3
seconds now move around to move and
rotate all the sensors avoid rapid
movements I'm moving around you just
don't see it trust
me please be good please be good
processing please
wait okay now is is it acceptable or is
it good I want the calibration to be
accept uh good good not
acceptable now stand still to apply and
finalize the calibration the calibration
process is now complete you can move
freely now okay where am I
though
ah where am I don't know where am I
here
hello hello
hello
H
interesting oh
whoa oh oh I'm way too ah I think I know
why position zero
zero there we
go ah all back to
normal to where I'm supposed to be
yippee let me turn on some bgm did you
enjoy that lady's voice did you like
her sorry that's very loud I found this
cute bgm
[Music]
it's could be a loading screen now you
really look like vernus
Vernis vernus Vernis
vernus Vernis Vernis Vernis
Vernis Vernis Vernis Vernis
vernus
uh vernus verus verus I guess
so verus verus verus
verus and at the very
end
verus I can't do that that's a Vogue
move I'll hurt
myself burnus burnus
burnus dead de dead always on my
schedule always has been always has been
right de that has been on my schedule
for a long time people always like she's
play that a dead but I've had it my
schedule before it even existed how do
you explain
[Music]
that so uh besides singing Mirage twice
for you and drifting away and
introducing no credits and showing up
off the cute
LS there's actually something else I had
on my agenda actually one of two
things
um
I uh I okay so hash Mir challenge has
been a thing for a while now and hope
you guys have been enjoying all the
YouTube
shorts have you have you which one's
your favorite tell me why I'm drinking
Dead or Alive W what
[Music]
what icy
yummy Iris Iris Ollie crony phone I love
green it's yeah the green is so
beautiful the one with vaa I just
cracked my
back uh Iris crony m s Iris F crony
crony lots of crony
lovers but I'm the number
one I
see did you hear the crack it was my my
spine when I go like
this but now it only did one but you
probably didn't hear that only if the
spank was
hilarious spank that that
ass well there's still more coming
there's still more coming and even after
the like list is worked off I'm still
planning to release
more
because I don't know it's
fun and I still found some willing
victims yeah but can we appreciate like
the light Reflections on those
stones o and Jen
oh man oh look at the
back can we see that back from
[Music]
here oh
I'm just like looking at myself
man can we make this model
[Music]
official yes
please never felt so cute before in
pretty twerk well I I I okay just to
clarify I know I can't twerk on
that actually my Fredy model can twerk
better than me because the 3D model's
ass is shaking actually I think my ass
would shake a little bit too but I know
I don't really know how to do it but on
that Halloween stream I want to clarify
the only reason why I was doing like
this was because I had a huge sheet over
me and so my usual method wasn't working
and when I did
this I noticed it looked a little bit
more like twerking than and the usual
motion
[Music]
here isn't that how you do
it I don't know something like
that I really don't know I I admit it I
admit I know I don't I know that I am
the white as
girl in the neighborhood I don't know
how to do stuff like that but I only
know how to dance according to
choreography and speaking of
choreography I shall Now teach
you let's switch back to the White
Version though just for
fun have a little bit of
variety the first time was not bad
really
really how do you like my camera system
isn't this nice I took a uh some time
today to set it up and then and then I
drift
away I there's also like I can turn on
the wind but my hair is so flowy already
on its own so there's no need for
[Music]
wind where was I oh yeah so I want to
teach you guys the # 1
million h no # Mirage challenge Dance
Challenge the dance movs for that just a
little bit more in detail even if you're
not planning on Dancing it and putting
it up online that's
okay yeah yeah yeah I'll teach you I'll
teach you so let me teach
you first I'll try to I will say that
like the tracking like this is life
Tracking not process tracking so it's
like less accurate and stuff and my
hands go into my body and
stuff yeah so it won't look perfect but
I'll try to I'll try to make it look
decent adjusting to it as I
go so there's the Coors it starts like
this you sold me on a mirage I told you
off into shreds I no you sold me on a
mirage I
you shreds I don't even know to do with
this
mess and starting from the second course
there's the part that I've been doing in
the YouTube
shorts me me me me rise you spinning
that part that part I will teach you
properly so let's look at it
once
okay talking while dancing is
[Music]
difficult oh
yeah so one
example you sh don't even know what to
do this
[Music]
yeah okay now we're going to turn that
into super slow motion
and I'll teach you slowly and then you
can learn it it's it's going to be good
but you don't have to dance it okay
don't worry but I just thought it would
be nice to give you a little little bit
of a tutorial so maybe if I perform this
on stage someday you'll be able to do
me okay so I can uh how does it work
again
uh uh
uh slower slower slow slower very much
[Music]
slower are you ready
here it
[Music]
begins my
Mir
[Applause]
[Music]
and
okay I'm not a dance teacher so probably
that wasn't the right order to do it but
okay I'll I'll explain it step by step
now you have a little bit of an example
that you can go back to but step by step
it's like this you um left leg uh you if
you want to learn this you probably have
to like horizontally flip the screen but
actually I can do that for
you I
shall I know I can flip the the
motion
uh um I'm probably have
to
wait ignore that I I'm going to reset it
so I can flip the motion for
you I always have to set it up with the
face
tracking so it takes a
moment
okay mirror tracking yeah let's mirror
it okay there we go my emotions are not
mirror so even though I'm doing it on my
right hip it looks like I'm doing
it well on the left but of course so
it's mirror so you can look at
this right wait does that make sense or
is it should I no wait should it be the
other way
around oh yeah it should oh no then it
was fine the way it
was sorry my logic didn't make
sense it was fine
cute pose cute wa pose so good how does
she stand like that there's so much
grace so
much what's the word po po po
Poise there it is thank you guys for
helping me
out okay mirror checking so okay it was
it was always mirror to begin with so
that so that it doesn't confuse me I
raised my right hand and actually there
it's raising its left hand okay so here
it goes
sorry and left hip kind of angled like
this and you start on the first meat by
shaping coming a little closer shaping
your two piece fingers downwards into an
M that's supposed to be an M have you
noticed before it's going to be on your
side sorry my boot is in the
way look at the peace signs that's the
important part
[Music]
[Laughter]
mhm don't look there look here it has to
be connected ideally okay and then this
is the first me me me me this was
already here but you're going to put it
a little bit more to the side so me and
the first me me me me me me so you
separate the Miis one two first the left
hand then the right hand and then you
bring them up to your eyes ideally like
these mhm and then I find this a little
bit difficult but you're going
[Music]
to curl them in okay
so me me me me R do happens on miru miru
me me
me oh wait the right hand might have
been
first ah the right one the right hand
was
first oh whatever hand is fine but I
think the right hand was
okay me me me me R you and then this
twister I had really lots of issues to
understand myself just just do it like a
little bit of okay it doesn't have to be
too proper because it happens so fast
miru spinning spinning little eyes is
happening here so just spin it actually
to be uh exact I think they taught me
like like this like you put the palms of
your hands together and then and then it
ends up after you do one twist it ends
up with a like a sh sign behind an O
open Pal Palm
get it but really it's so fast you can
just and
then you pull it down while the left
hand still stays up but you bring it
down through the middle of your your the
center of your
body so this is a
uh you spinning little lies on Li I will
bring it down and then it switches
position uh after after we curl the left
hand inwards okay yeah and but you curl
it in into a fist but then you open it
up again because we want to pass them
and and cover them cover the one hand
when we're passing you know what I
mean I'm so bad at explaining
this H it's so it's really difficult so
don't get like like stressed out when
you don't know how to do it it's really
difficult so
me me me me R you spinning little lies
then switch it cover it and then you're
basically already done because then you
go like in opposite directions the right
hand goes down the left hand goes
up eyes you spinning little eyes KN
thisg on and on and on for the second on
you kind of like jump out of your St
into a wider stance and put your hands
to the
front and then um bring them towards
your body while you're
also pulling your butt back and on yeah
do I sound like a dance
teacher
so and and while I do this I also kind
of like move my hips a little bit
H I lost you no worries for step by step
I also get lost when I get like taught a
choreography and we just have to like
redo it again and
again so me me me me rise you curl them
in spin the hands spinning little
lies new
disguise on and on on and
and and and on wa let me can I Just
Dance it to the music once we'll do it
slow motion you kind of already know it
now well we're already kind of pass
uh I'm forgetting it
[Music]
too what to do with
this acoss it
could okay here we go m shape m shape
separate me me
spinning on and on and
[Music]
on
okay you got it you got it you totally
got
it so after we the uh uh on and on and
on there's this uh confusing thing here
we first uh kind of
like this the right hand and the right
knee the right knee goes inside the
right arm goes outside and then we do
the same thing on the opposite side this
me and we keep the the other hand up
still so this me and then we cross them
while also see my hands first they're
like uh angled inwards and then
outwards so this me rash and then you
bring it back again I'm lost and then we
do this famous me me you ass shake yeah
we love that favorite part why is the
chicken lady 140p 140 I mean it's just
because like I'm kind of far
away so the Raju part is really easy you
just put your your whole body kind of to
the
side raise your uh right leg on your
tippy
toes and then when you shake that
ass it's like uh you really only shake
the right leg here
looks like this from the
front like this from the
side yeah this
me you uh if you want to know really
exactly uh where we first shaking it uh
this miror as I'm lost on Lost I'm
already going into
position which is the right arm straight
to the front to the center to to that
front in that case and the other hand on
top of it and then we do a little
twinkle
twinkle yeah and then we shake it h on
me me me me Mir the first me is when the
hip goes up and then just keep on doing
that and when the me miru ends then we
turn around for another miru this one's
a bit difficult cuz you got to twirl
really fast but you can you don't have
to do that if you're watching me live
then you don't have like if you watch
this in a concert hall then you will
have space to do this anyway but I don't
know you can just be
like
okay
soize you then turn to your left your
left and while you're turning already
prepare to put your left hand on your
hip and your right hand
like this pretty next to your eyes and
then still kind of like
Shake uh right yeah your right
leg you can like kind of tilt your head
a little bit and then Sparkle Sparkle
Sparkle Sparkle and then it's just sorry
cable on my
leg this is just like
whatever just bring one arm push it out
push the other one out and then sway
sway Like a
Bird yeah whatever is
fine you need coefficient to dance this
oh yeah have have good luck learning
this feel free to use this as a video
reference oh actually that be so
exciting to see someone like really
watch this and learn it
live I could troll him and and pretend
that in the choreography there's like
Parts like
this
included okay now my listen class room
Focus I've probably drifted away a lot
again before I disappear in the wall
let's do the slow motion with with uh
audio again okay this is 50% slow down
so I know you can do it remember a
little bit of a walk through again
before we go with the
music okay H left leg up M sign separate
okay me me bring it up to the eyes me
Raju curl it inside spin twist bring the
the secret sign down and then swap
places and
[Music]
then and then this part this me r I'm
lost and
but sorry there's a cable
here really need different headphones
for
this that's how it goes easy right hell
yeah let's
go let's go you're so ready just do it
don't let your dreams be
dreams
just do it yeah okay here we
go somewhere
[Music]
here here we go
dis and and
on
[Music]
this okay I forgot one part that I just
noticed I do subconsciously but uh at
this part this me Raj at this part I
kind of Look Away towards that side you
don't have to do it but it adds a little
bit of an extra spark I didn't trip I I
gracefully kicked away my
cable cut it off no then I can't hear
the
music and let me drink a little bit more
W I'm teaching You choreography I'm so
[Music]
proud okay
now we shall do not 50% slow down but
25% slow down
okay uh
here okay you can do it chickens you can
do
[Music]
it wait have to
recalibrate I'm already in the
wall I'm in the
wall please hold or can I like move this
in this
app I don't know if I can move it in
here I got to figure it out another time
maybe
uh can I re
reenter I don't know calibration
[Music]
time go to a starting position where you
can safely perform the calibration
yeah I
shall stand and in pose relaxed and look
straight ahead for 3 seconds 1 2 3 Move
move around to move and rotate all the
sensors avoid rapid
movements moving
around processing please wait please
hold the
line
okay
okay come on now stand still to apply
and finalize the calibration ction
cration process is now complete you can
move freely now calibration process was
poor I got to do it again
guys was really poor there's good
acceptable and then there's
poor I guess my heart wasn't really in
it okay I I I I apologize lady
calibration lady go to a starting
position where you can safely perform
the
calibration
yeah St an end pose relaxed and look
straight ahead for 3 seconds for
seconds bam now now move around rotate
all the sensors avoid rapid movement
movements
yaho processing processing please wait
okay I'm
[Music]
waiting calibration lady I'm sure she's
single but she's like AI now stand still
to apply and finalize the calibration
the calibration process is now complete
can move freely now
yippe it was good she says it was good
she likes me she likes me
again hello
hi
yay oh
oh I love that triangle
mouth oh
that's so cute I think it reset my
my my my my thing
again you saw me on a
[Music]
mirage yeah it did can you just like
stay like that
oh that's so cute shall we look at it
closely oh oh
oh I want to bring my wings
back want to bring my
wings t
[Music]
yeah they get me so excited I love them
so much best thing
ever
[Music]
whoa
sreenshot okay where were we I'm not
done with you yet we were going to do
25% slow slow version
huh where's the camera I don't know
where the where to look to get the
camera but
okay
go here we go was somewhere
here remember me me me me me you
spinning little eyes this gu on and
on
okay stting position
[Music]
my you spending the
Liv a and on this
[Music]
me I taught it wrong it's it's different
when I'm trying to like teach it without
music then it's not in my body sorry you
weren't supposed to do this you're
supposed to do this of course of course
so you then just turn and lift the left
leg and then me me you okay evil way's
fine anyway but actually do it like this
I'm throwing you off to confuse you and
see see if you can adjust adjust adapt
overcome okay understand I want to see
you do it correctly do you remember now
do you [\h__\h] remember I want to see
you do it right now with me
[Music]
okay he
he here we [\h__\h]
go be ready or
[Music]
die so sorry one more
time not my mistake no no your mistake
[Music]
spinning
Li
me
cable okay get it get
[Music]
it did you do it right
hm did you do it right did you do it
right huh
you you did you did you do it
[Music]
right uh-huh you think you did well
let's see if you can do it with 100%
yeah let's see if you can do it with
100% speed or like zero I mean normal
speed
okay
okay this is like Tak Mir boot camp boot
camp I'm innocent I'm
angle okay here we
go noral speed
My
[Music]
Mirage
yeah woo
did you do it did you do it you really
think you did it huh are you just saying
that because you think I can't see that
you were just sitting down and watching
this while
sitting why the [\h__\h] don't you stand up
huh
huh why don't you and if you're standing
and if you are doing it with me good job
good for you good for you hm
I'm eating I'm eating lunch I'm in bed
you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] I'm working my ass
off here what are you doing you in the
car um well stop the car dance on the
side of the
street I did it
yay I'm grooving
yay well you know you guys could watch
the vaud and then watch it at home and
learn it at home that's what you were
planning on doing anyway
right say yes say
yes you didn't sign up for the booty
Camp wait wait are you trying to say you
signed up for the you didn't sign up for
the boot camp you signed up for the
booty
camp
or for the booty
cam here's the booty cam but you only
get the booty cam if you do the boot
camp
okay uhhuh I don't think you're
understanding what I'm trying to say now
you made me mess up my camera angle I
don't know where it
was okay that's
fine all right then we shall do it once
again once again for good measure and
then you you're able you're allowed to
leave okay here we go
go and for you I I shall dance it from
the beginning of the course
[Music]
[Applause]
y we did it
yay yeah
yay clapping clapping see my hands don't
match up that's why it's difficult to do
this yeah yeah
y yeah you did it y good for
you that was
fun that fun that was
fun that's fun h
tiny arm robot no no no no long
arm okay now I have one more mission to
do
today just not going to do the speed up
version I wanted to teach you guys a
chant Mirage chant it's not completely
finished
but let's switch to let's switch to
Black Version again
[Music]
um uh okay sorry talking while dancing
it's really not my
forte
wow w
[Music]
oh god let's not do
that okay so my mouse is up here by the
way I put it on like a elevated space so
that I can do this while standing up
um so I want to do chant learn chant
with
kfp okay so that in the future when
Maybe this will get performed somewhere
one
day yeah we're gonna do we're gonna do
chant uh now we're going to do like
K-pop style chant
okay yes yes uh I never made the cap of
cell chant before but it's actually kind
of easier Maybe
then Japanese style chance because you
just um have to learn the lyrics of the
song that's all you got to
do yeah sounds
easy is
easy trust
me
okay I prepared the ly
sheet kfp you can
then
uh I I I I'll try to I'll try to uh make
it into a PDF and then put it up on the
community board how about that on the
YouTube community
board um there it is
yeah shall we zoom
in maybe a bit
more so um I'm open for adjustments
for now we
shall go through it once discuss
it m looks great K thank you I think so
too
okay so you know the the song Start
o yeah often for K-pop intros they do
like
a like a chant in that Rhythm but but in
the intro but I think better without
just like chill like
relax you can do the ketchup that's the
one like Japanese style thing that will
be here to um maybe not the only one but
the ketchup remember is
like if you have light sticks in your
hand then just hold the light sticks and
you go
like towards the stage yeah there's also
a variation of that where you
clap while doing it clap
clap yeah so any of those is okay you
can do that in the beginning
ooh o
yeah okay and then basically everything
that is blue you're going to scream out
loud with me or I sing it and you're
going to scream
it okay actually I'll just uh I think
I'll just play the
song um um but any notable things for
example the p p p high is this PCH PCH P
hi clap clap clap hi clap clap clap hi
but I don't know if it will really fit
well maybe without the high just like
clap clap
clap you don't have to do the Hy that's
optional
maybe and then the other notable thing
here I see this a lot in K-pop too uh
like at a highlighted moment like the
chorus when there's a little bit of a
gap they go
like that's it that's all you got to do
easy
right and uh this one is better if I
give you an example while we're playing
the
song
and yeah here's ketchup at the calm part
always at the calm part to do
ketchup okay then let's listen to this
from the beginning I'll try to I'll be
you and you can follow along you can
clip this part and then follow along to
practice before a
concert
um
P woo
[Music]
going
under I still
[Music]
wonder we should add
that be
[Music]
ready yeah okay okay okay we do
twice do with that's the this
[Music]
part and then my Mir r
keep that empty and
[Music]
then yeah in the
gaps Escape my
way
[Music]
per oh you
oh do
you yeah got
[Music]
it I don't know where exactly we should
start live this
mess
yeah my
[Music]
Mir an
kch no way
this my
uh my
[Music]
Mir and on and
on
yeah
[Music]
kch with the maybe with the clap
cl
[Music]
cl yeah that works pretty well I added a
few more in the middle so let's let's do
a proper version where I'm not
completely lost in my own
song
uh let's put the catcher here as well so
that applies to everything below and
then do we have it in the beginning no
okay then the ples here too okay nice
this Mirage and lost don't be lost come
on it's so easy is it not easy I think
it's really easy come on you got to
learn it there's like way a complicated
uh chance out there trust
me okay here we go this is the uh
hopefully correct version so if it's got
to be clipped in this part please let's
go and Tak Mir chant version let's
[Music]
go going
under still wonder
[Music]
I forgot
that okay to one more time this is the
the clippable version here we go takana
M concert chant version
[Music]
going
under I still wonder
[Music]
oh do
you okay okay
[Music]
okay do with this mess
my
[Music]
mirush Escape my
way perfect I know
okay okay I'm ready I'm
ready oh you
[Music]
[Applause]
oh don't live this
my
[Music]
Mir here we go
don't with
[Music]
this My Mirage
yay thank
you nailed it
nailed it yes yes yeah that's I think
the first first no not the first we've
done this kind of before but I don't
know if we did it this proper if I did
such a
proper I think I did I think I did a
proper video like this before for like
heart Challenger and so on but was it
with 3D I don't know not in this proper
3D
yeah yay y y y y huh
okay this can go I will save a PDF and
I'll upload it on the community board
for you guys y
yay eggy wa oh yeah it was an egg
great H good times I also I guess was
once an egg even though I wouldn't I
want you to think that I never
was no no no I don't hatch from an egg
even though my first debut lore says so
and I actually wrote that myself
but adapt
adjust adjust adapt adapt adjust
overcome in any in case overcome and
adapt and
adjust you should know by
now impr
improvise
improvise what's the
order help me out here come
on whatever you say B bro
improvise improvise oh wait I have an
idea
improvise
adapt where is the
[Music]
camera
bro what
happy accidents
improvise
adap
overcome I don't know
man switching the camera it's difficult
okay I know oh I know that was weird
that was weird stop delet it delet
[Music]
man I need a camera team so that
somebody who switches the camera so that
I don't have to have these awkward
[Music]
moments
okay sulking in the back
oh it's so quiet you're not even
enjoying it properly it's so
[Music]
quiet IRL wa Tong doesn't come out like
that how does she do it I want to learn
from my Fredy
[Music]
this model is too powerful that's
true let's bring out my wings one more
time cuz they're so
[Music]
cute which version do you prefer the the
uh white one or the
dark
[Music]
one white white white oh wow I think in
the maybe for the MV I had more people
saying
dark is it the white because of the
pretty
effects you don't like me being your
devil you don't like me being your devil
should I be your
angle the Sparkle is not yeah this it
has
Sparkle see
a I'm just trying to show off the
sparkle though like wow it's the
universe
a showing off the model man what's wrong
POG
okay now one more time White Version cuz
we just can't get enough of looking at
this oh I think every time ah does it
reset the mouth every time I switch
model Maybe
[Music]
he so
bright I'm going to get to the wall
again I'm just trying to be
cute I guess that's the sign
the wall wants me I'll give the wall a
hug maybe now it will leave me
alone it's Ena
[Music]
Ena no
okay so uh yeah
um that's it do you remember do you
remember the
dance me me me me me me R you spinning
the this on and on and on this me
[Music]
okay all right waiting for that video
coefficient oh oh
no okay um I'm I don't know this so cute
I can't
stop but I shall end it there
um wow I hope
that this
pretty
beautiful version of
takana blessed your day and made it a
little bit
better
oh heart
[Music]
I am
old
um every once in a while I'll bring it
back maybe for my next 3D unarchived
[Music]
K I got to bring this
back screenshot time
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay before my batteries die how my
battery batteries how my hand batteries
let's
see
oh
uh 50 uh 40 40 45ish on my hands
okay thank you oh my God I got nothing
to do anymore I just want to sorry I'm
I'm I'm not trying to do this here I'm
just this embarrassing
[Music]
sad other tacos well I mean I have some
like angry sad expressions and so on but
um I think they look a little bit
extreme actually sorry Sean the angle
the
angle but at least you know I can do cat
mouth without like pressing a tle but
yeah I I don't know about that
that one's
cute what do you mean you didn't want to
dance with
[Music]
me
why
why why okay will you at least do the
chat with
me when I perform someday
by the way no guarantee that is anytime
soon but just you know be
prepared what's just smug
[Music]
ha
sheu shaft angle
how how much
more
okay let's do more like like
angle dramatic
[Music]
pose JoJo pose just Dynamic I'm just
being Dynamic looking at and not
everything is Jojo This is
JoJo
uh I
[Music]
know I don't know I I never watched JoJo
I'm just imagining what JoJo would be
like how about this is this
JoJo is this Jojo
I'm in the wall again it's time to end
it
man is this
Joo where am
I I was trying to look through my
legs is this
JoJo is this
JoJo that's that's getting you I don't
even know what that
is is this a muscle car is this
[Music]
JoJo is this a muscle wait what what
kind of
expression
happens it's this a normally it's
butterfly right is this a butterfly
ah ah I see let's recreate that before I
[Music]
go
perfectionist at work I maybe you want
to be able to properly clip my my I
don't know do you want to have it full
in the picture here
is this a muscle
car is this a
butterfly is this
a is this a pigeon right he doesn't say
butterfly says say a
pigeon is this a
pigeon is this a chicken is is this a
chicken wait maybe got the sound
is this a
chicken use it well do you want you
probably want green screen guys right
but I don't know like I'm I'm green and
then blue and then I'm all these things
so I mean here how about how
about we can try we can try with like I
don't
know Maga but my eyes are magenta I have
this problem nothing works for me
I'm
suffering where is the
here the
hell
H transparent background
yes oh
oopsie okay uh we'll try we can try with
several colors
is is uh uh is this a
pigeon is this a pigeon
okay and then we can try
green maybe maybe darkish green no
probably not but we'll try is this a
liis why
so it says a
chicken is this a
chicken how about black like sometimes
black kind of works for me at least
within
OBS is this a
chicken is this a
pigeon okay one of those hopefully
works okay and with that today's stream
comes to an end I while I still have
batteries I got to record something for
the next Milestone reward probably we'll
have that Acappella video out
before uh before I'll have more shorts
out I don't know uh everybody thank you
so much for supporting me right as you
made this
possible I mean
I I don't know you you you made this
reveal possible but the model was made
possible by Mei and and c and
me yeah thank you so much for supporting
my music and supporting my little things
that I
do than I hope you enjoyed the stream a
little bit of a well I don't know what I
was
doing
but I don't know I'm awkward I'm going
to go I'm so
awkward I'm just I'm just going to go in
German we said we doesn't Al in the
beginning I was playing a uh a really
nice remix so look up Mirage remix on
YouTube there's a couple ones now I'm
going to play a different one while when
we
go when we go
out oh yeah oh
yeah bye
bye
byebye
byebye in the void in the void in the
void I can't
clip yay
byebye I don't know when am I streaming
tomorrow I don't remember byebye also
this week
taka let's go let's
[Music]
go
byebye see you in Jakarta or tomorrow
for my stream I think I'm I'm I what day
wait wait is it is it
Wednesday why I not I don't know am I
streaming tomorrow am I streaming
tomorrow who knows oh you an eternal
okay yeah I think Shi will join us see
you tomorrow for the
[Music]
hey
wait oh
[Music]
refused I was
what I need
[Music]
every
keep you up I don't even know what you
do when
this
[Music]
good me fall in
me
[Music]
the