[Music]
n
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
a e
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry I was feeling a little bit stiff
for a moment
um hi
yeah ah not free arms no no no no no no
no no no no no no no stop spreading lies
you liar you a liar liar liar pants on
fire come back to me switch come back to
me wake up wakey
wakey apparently there's a Peppa Pig
game on the switch what the [\h__\h]
anyway apparently I have
charged so all is good all is
well we are going to waste no time today
K
KY how are you
guys I'm already in the game I'm already
in
[Music]
there tangents I don't even have really
many tangents I'll tell
you I'll tell you about my Korean
lessons a little bit later but besid
said I don't even know so I'm going to
disconnect this
[Applause]
now I hear
nothing ah now I hear but it's pretty
quiet
oh a you don't hear anyway did you oh
wait you
did oh is this loud quiet tell me tell
me
rare focused gaming
stream uh seems
normal sounds fine
okay
okay yes of course I'm already
fluent well uh
today uh we're going to finish
this we're going to try our best to
finish just uh we have
10 the game Modio low for real for real
we have 10 artifacts together I think
and make it a bit
higher uhuh uh yeah
and free bosses I
think you just completed 100% for last
night oh damn then you got good memory
now to help me
no
no it's not low it wasn't
low like an in
between um ideally you know what I
should like I know you guys would help
me but I feel like communication is
rough um
artifacts Metroid
Prime Remer maybe I can see oh yeah this
is exactly what I need just so I see it
on the map where I need to
go and then I don't have to ask you left
or right the whole time where do I go
where are we going audio is crackling
you for real are you
sure I don't hear a
crackling but you for real crackling
like last time when I had to like
restart
the the capture card
[Music]
what do you good you hear it crackling a
little what about now like normally the
small crackling that I also sometimes
hear I know how to get rid of it and I
just did that you still hear
it I don't really hear
anything Snap Crackle
Pop
uhhuh I don't I can't okay whatever 12
guide
yeah maybe the crackling comes from
being in next to a volcano or so you can
hear it what what do you
mean I'll I'll restart the capture okay
close oh the audio still goes through
interesting very
interesting all right and here it is
again a very low
crackle that might be the game B
GM it's probably just a game B GM
guys whatever okay so we already got the
artifact of truth right and what's the
other one we have let me see I want I
need to let's put this to the
left
uh should we start just by focusing on
the
artifacts if there's something I can do
like on the
like what is our main goal now besides
the
artifacts that is also the
question oh I need one more boss boss
first yeah but on the way to that boss I
want to get all the artifacts that are
on the
way [\h__\h] um
uh I never really like properly looked
at this
stuff
H you heard the
crap what the
[\h__\h] what about now
huh how did I fix it last time just by
restarting the
the the program I did that already I'll
do it
again but
okay how about
now ah the a port oh maybe how about
now or I mean it's still in the same
port the the the capture card is still
in the same
port well I'll go to the other
port how
about how
about
wait how about
now of course it was gone because
nothing was happening how about
now oh wait now there's no sound at all
is
there and there is no sound of course
it's
[Laughter]
gone uh
what there we go okay sound is back how
about
now gone okay funny because I just
switched it back to the one that was
apparently the problem last
time okay
[Music]
um who
knows where I have to go ah the boss
right where is the
boss where is that boss where do kiaha
go B it to the
ride the
ride that way
workstation tunnel Face mind white door
okay I'm guessing this workstation
[Music]
tunnel okay so if I pass for a
room that has uh a artifact that I
didn't get yet cuz I only have two
please let me know and I will stop and
look for
it there are two here at
magore
um well if they
are in the magore workstation is there
one in the marmore
[Music]
workstation there's one in the lava lake
did I get the one in the lava lake that
one looks so obvious I probably
did no no she too far okay okay let's
just uh if it's too far then now let's
skip this one for
now we'll probably have to go
back to
magore area again
anyway also we have to warm up but I
think I'll be mostly
fine where am I okay and now I have to
go up we're going to do this today I'm
motivated are you guys motivated
H oh hi you guys are here
[Music]
uh this is this is a good warm
up I wish my ice cream was faster man
sometimes it takes so much time
we good we
good but do I have to go up
there go kiaha go
believe yeah she
believes oh plasma oh yeah right I got
to test this out on
everybody like you um this kind of
structure break wave ball oopsie
break with balls
n
sick I watched a little bit of a
speedrun the the world record speedrun
right now but that one uses glitches
I've watched it without spoilering
myself like until not until the end just
until a certain
point wasn't really helpful at all
though cuz so many glitches I was like
what the
[\h__\h] there glitches to I want to watch
the glitchless one but that one probably
takes much longer because even with
glitches this dude took 1 hour 50 or
so that's still very long considering he
uses glitches and does the world record
for real for real but that's for the
remastered version maybe there like even
shorter ones
on um non
remas ah I'm not
here
oh why you know Dead Yet now dead
[Music]
okay what is this
room another very tall room with a red
door and uh a white like elevator
door plasma
op it's all right what the [\h__\h] oh is
that a yellow
[Music]
one oh he fell down down oh it's she
still
alive now he's dead bye-bye ah yeah
that's a a bad place to pick a fight
with me
buddy 2 hours we even with no glitch oh
that's not even that much longer than
the one with the
glitches okay we can I guess take that
floating
platform I have The High
[Music]
Ground reload the
safe well I fell into the [\h__\h] pH
and um
this room will kill you fall fast do not
fall
um well I'm in a shitty spot now
[Music]
everybody no I want to reload the save I
want to reload the save
[Applause]
[Music]
that was just that was a great
start great
start no time to
waste more
why why why fall downa why we get it we
get it thank
you I have The High
[Music]
Ground that one didn't
count oh was a
preview of how the whole stream will
feel for us
[Music]
and I was making fun of him for picking
a fight with me in that place because
it's a bad place to pick a
fight also a bad place to take a
fight
[Music]
man trying a little bit uh to sometimes
use
M to
sometimes use she she's even skipping
it uh the motion
controls you now I'm like that kind of
stuff like just skipping the enemies in
the room that's like speed run the
stress guyses learn from
me thanks for the membership
[Music]
welcome we're already we're already like
back oop see what am I
doing I mean you don't even
get uh uh experience points in this game
so what the hell I'm not even wor
wasting my time with
that
right
yeah I I do not see there are no enemies
but yeah that
sounds beep I've improved much from day
one thank you
wonderful bye-bye now
kiaha not fall down go
he really does not see
me no not that
one oh
s being close for the edge makes your
nervous and me too is he going
to attempt to come up well now they all
shooting at me where's the purple one
though
ah it's not good now they're paying
attention to
me that one's a red one I see a yellow
one to the yeah yeah let's Sho the
yellow did that hit
him I don't know did it
wait wait wait
wait feel like I made it more difficult
is hitting you think so well three of
those he must be dead by now oh yeah he
did okay let's do the red one
next sniper
strats ah but this one this one
he Dodges and I
can't oh no this one hit him and he has
burning damage on him too thank you for
the red super chat
L now now he's kind of not coming
back
ah what so cool did I possibly get that
hit I thought it like just hit the floor
that I'm standing on
think we're
good
ni giving me a ideas again
huh there's still someone there but we I
will go
now
rainbow
okay where are we
going go there
oh they're growling at
me
oh which color oh red still
alive red space
pirates aka the pole of the
Teletubbies give me
those and they won't reach okay well now
I think they're all dead do I just go
down
what's the white door white door white
door is
like there
okay color oh red
again all right pick a fight with
me
ah [\h__\h] I can't get my camera uh any
lower than
that okay no more playing around kiaha
white
door
hi I'm
in ball I don't know where this leads
but a
ball why it's so dark
yeah The High Ground
H it's it's supposed to be an advantage
what is this room sus oh apparently I've
been here
before where am I going
though what's the
room that kiaha go
to or is this the head to the safe
point uhhuh okay that
one means right first right
up there
moners oh these are normal ones
oh are they ghosties cuz they look like
he disappeared for a little
bit that's it that's
it oh coming down coming
down
okay where is the safe Point okay
FAL Vis let you see we invisible all
it's
okay they make themselves quite visible
to
me most of the time oh wait that was the
scanning that is that is different oh
hi did that just one hit him
okay uh through this room
straight and then
left
uh this is that poison
room it's not poisonous anymore
that's not gun
[Music]
op it doesn't work ah I to
go go W go go go go go
go taking too much
damage go white girl go go Tano
to like rainfall
[Music]
yeah what it in the uh non- remastered
version also like that you shoot three
times four you can
[Music]
charge no cuz like that
often has
uh nice like showed them where I am and
kind of messed up everything
nice
yeah kind of ratting me
out like look look kiaha is here and
then they like even if they don't see me
if they see my shot somewhere then they
find out oh she's there even though I
just want to prepare and charge and then
make them see me and
you
know so hard to get used to and I didn't
even think of it yeah but well I I I
started the game with that so I'm fine
but you know there would be some sneaky
strategies if it wouldn't do the pew pew
pew and then big
Pew there's a map room here
what what I mean map
room go here right
again tell me if uh I'm like running
into a room with an
artifact what the [\h__\h] what what the
[\h__\h] why sh why is it
shaking uh how do I find this one again
I'll just I'll just do
my
oh sh
oh he's doing hand
[Music]
okay
easy wait wait wait wait jump and nice
kiaha
nice wow kiaha I'm so proud of you you
have they grow so fast you have improved
so much kiaba I'm so proud of you
probably could have just run past him
and just moved onto this room though if
I was a
speedrunner
[Music]
hi want to
fight oh there's so
many oh oh oh no they they oh
[Music]
ah it's white it's white
shut the [\h__\h] B Hy it works right
it's supposed to
work when it's frozen or maybe
not miss don't even when they're
frozen all right
was just waiting for you
friend was just giving your
chance okay safe
[Music]
Point super ice missiles will work but
you have never found
[Music]
them okay saving now and then maybe now
boss
time boss go I've been looking for you
for ages
forever since you guys told me to go to
Safe Point here I'm guessing I have to
now move on to here more like
platforming
time oh I know I can shut these off
right but it's okay
ah what the hell why are they still so
[Music]
sturdy again wait on this side too
not
this he you mean the
ball but I didn't want to do
that I'm taking so much damage because
it's stupid
idea so stupid should go the wa
way W way best way
yeah I didn't see the the problem is I
don't see the ball path right
away that's why I just want to kill them
normally where am
I oh oh white
door oh wait well I didn't
[Music]
some
missiles
missiles tdge blast missiles mess up tur
it's
[Music]
good
ah y
very SS nothing no enemies here oh no
he's dark ah We're
Here auto aim no more kiaha aim is the
way to
go is it
oh wait I got
one yo you
amop
okay uh I have to go up there it's so
hard to see
wasn't that kind of brighter last time I
was
here
xray oh x-ray oh I see the
platforms can
i
o oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh nice back jump good job
kaha I can do this jump
no I can't no no no no I can't K
cannot jum from the
mushrooms
oh one would think that those would be
really infected as
well
okay spooky ghost
platforms nice landing safe and
soft
okay uh
no stop jump straight you mean
guys this looks kind of far at least in
the
X-ray
okay I don't
believe h
[Music]
oh those you can barely see in the X-ray
cuz you just see fruit or a little
jelly
okay as long as I can uh hear them what
the
[\h__\h] where was
that is it the darker
[Music]
parts think so Panic
ball M Jelly
wait a
[Music]
mushroom can I see
no
nothing
F okay
uh I this
one okay where are we going where you
taking me huh
up
here oh it's very close basically just
straight ahead maybe platform here
too
no
what there must
be oh wait is that a ball
track hi
and fall and
attach
spider spider
ball ow you're still super chatting
thank
you what's
that what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] yo the moment I enter that
area something funky happens
it's like a c
cold this little
[\h__\h] hey I can't get
them they make me so
mad I hate
them recording to log how beam
what uh similar to
the attack it has enough cunning to
realize when something is too large for
it to handle and beyond that is fairly
ignorant what it lacks in brains it
makes up for with
aggression [\h__\h] all of
y'all
yeah come on
I need to use this one because this
one's
faster I needed those HP so I'll take
it there's something up there
can I reach that
no it's not meant to be reached
maybe okay elevator
Chan elevator Chan my belov
it have you guys eaten breakfast or so
lunch or dinner yet I've had uh Gila for
snack but for breakfast I had pancakes
with blueberries and chocolate cream
yeah I have some stuff for dinner so I
don't have to cook I am
prepared all is
good yog good for
breakfast yog good for
breakfast M very very rarely I eat that
piz
yummy just woke up for a stream oh good
morning huh what was that
oh what color is
that no
color oh so easy this beam is so
powerful always extra careful k
careful but I also want to be fast today
that's my
problem that one was sturdier
than the Pirates
damn okay wow speed walk
challenge this the floor FL not all of
it is dangerous right only some of the
floor I think only the shiny stuff
yeah floor floor okay the floor is lava
basically but worse than
lava what that sign to grapple hook is
that uh okay I thought it was on the
tentacle on the floating
tentacles no no no no please
[Music]
stop recommend Ice Beam for this H okay
thank
you maybe ice beam and then switch to
power a
PL ah there we
go I don't even need that grapple hook
is it like a
shortcut I can just jump over these
mushrooms I
think
[Music]
me when now now I kind of need it
maybe a
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] come back
please okay okay
okay next
I think this needs some ball explosion
action is this like a camera reset when
I'm
ball no it's just telling me nope kiaha
you cannot do that here what isn't
that is that a bug
or is it on purpose
sometimes it's there sometimes it's
not hold cuz I think I'm supposed to be
on top of
it go
fast is it part of the game wait they
all kind of like disappear and oh oh
when you like tou them once or shall
they disappear boost ball
okay oh wait I don't know how to use
that
really
okay
wait
[Music]
oh
n first time like properly using that
ever except for the you
know when I was
doing this theop the thing for that
upgrade
[Music]
oh nice same
kiaha and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop
coming a that other buddy of
them doesn't even try
almost to the hardest boss for most
First Time
Players
o well whenever you guys say next area
is the hardest and so on I feel like it
was like mostly like
manageable let me see where are we one
big room two
doors which door first left or or or
straight he's manageable
left first left missile refill
okay
okay up there how do I get
there what
how not not from
[Music]
here that's hard to see with this stupid
visor I just want to look
normally grapple beam the
creature that's the jelly
ride I don't see any more creatures
should I not have killed the the jellies
I recommend fmal
ER yeah but
then it's kind of like I feel I don't
even see how to get there looks like
there's something there but I can't
reach it yet maybe I'll just I'm just
supposed
to oh oh wait wa wa why am I doing
that stay on the
mushrooms and now I see the creature
yeah
and jump and
jump get faster what on Earth
girl fter why you take so long my God
this is a matter of life and death
kiaha Bring me um not
there we here yeah oh now I know how to
reposition it Ice Beam why so slow it's
like a shotgun
yeah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] where am I where am
I this ground is safe oh my
god oh there's a whole
like no no no no no how do I get back
up please pick me up pick me up I'm
scared pick me
up pick pick me up
please pick me
up no come on maybe if I
jump and I get closer yeah yeah it does
work this needs to be the right
[Music]
timing she let
go she lets go
I can freeze it oh no no she got it she
got it she got
it okay now come on that is totally
manageable
see m what does m ah safe
safe save point no no
upgrade
missile missile full oh that's what that
was it looks like a safe Point don't
make me don't tease
me hey
yo is that worth
it okay my little
friend wait we are going to move on to
the next Red
Door there will be a safe station soon
oh God oh God oh God I thought I was
falling
off what is
that oh I can actually see a little bit
what is that what's shooting that it's
just coming from the
ceiling oh
are ah now I see
you
that where we at I got
you now kiaha has been granted safe
passing uh is this ground safe nope nope
nope
nope oh wait can I see oh my God ah
[Music]
yes yes good
job show much the
G
beautiful okay
that yeah I just want to get that out of
the way I think I'll prefer that over
being greeted by them
when I arrive
there
yeah B baby burn oh nice okay now
there's a little rail here another with
another door here that I could already
reach now what is this
room no right that's where I came from
of course I can reach it
now so I'll go I'll go this way
I love the chicken on fire
emote do not burn babies oh sorry
that's little uh language
misunderstanding I do not mean to burn
babies of
[Music]
course huh
grapple not reach only burn chickens
yeah exactly but also chickens I I will
wait until they're fully grown of
[Music]
course sorry sorry sorry spaghetti
got the spaghetti
syndrome can you please say B you is my
favorite V why do I have to say that you
should be saying
that would be weird if kiaha says kiaha
is her favorite feature because that's
not true
[Music]
although I recommend kiaha to
anyone game is telling me
again that I am apparently too
slow but I appreciate it you should only
honestly tell me that
earlier oh okay seems like I'm very
close to that room probably through that
one red door but should I go try the
other Red Door first maybe that's the
safe
Point yeah
okay I see you guys I see
you
p p
why why must you always Panic
Kaa hope run
away I want the missile attack for the
red
beam when will I get that
it's actually pretty bad what a missile
attack for the pl what but I just want
it because it will it will follow the
enemy but if you guys say it's really
not good or right
then there are optional so you have to
look
well did I not drop anything
ideally I will
skip things that are optional if you
guys say that they're not really
necessary for me to
really finish today it's pretty mid
wow that's been really good you can just
start go enemies in one
shot no not not those that have a color
themes but hey we got a safe safe Point
nice let's read this recording to log
book as we continue to observe the
development of project helix's Elite
Pirates it becomes increasingly
obviously obvious that these Warriors
will usher in a new era of space pirate
dominance they are incredibly resistant
to damage and their ability to transport
and wield so many weapons and at once
makes them the ideal main stat of our
Ground Forces though they are not as
quick as typical Pirates it makes little
difference with the platoon of elite
pirates in the Vanguard of an army of
normal and flying Pirates we will have a
near indestructible backbone that should
turn the tide in any
engagement they are very
very uh confident aren't
they good for them confidence is
important I wish I could cut myself a
slice off of that
confidence only got a scan the red stuff
guys
sorry this is also another way of saving
time I need a
[\h__\h] expect it expect it
confidence and then Samos happened
exactly this one I'm guessing I can
explode as
ball
no I thought so because the door is
behind it
scanning to fre
shoot
up what you want
game missile
maybe I already saved
you I wa you this
is n with which one though this
one oh a Charged red one or any charged
one maybe oh wait this is boss fight oh
yeah this is boss
fight well I have 100 missiles I have
almost full health
I saved I saved I saved so easy easy
safe Point very close for
[Laughter]
[Music]
once first phasing boss record what does
that mean
[Music]
Omega pirate can become invisible to
normal sight oh it is vulnerable when
cloaked as all energy is drawn from
defense
systems by exposing itself to phas and
it can regenerate damage we already like
fought one of those though didn't we
like a small version
maybe should be hand with Extreme
Caution maximum
Firepower yeah yeah cool
um so
this is leak's worse so I don't remember
how did I fight the smaller
one when he's invisible I can hurt him
when he's not invisible I I
can't should win invisible
with any
weapons [\h__\h] I need to learn how to
jump break his armor didn't shoot one
invisible
oh he's traing now right like the other
guy oh oh oh
oh
ouchie to keep track of hey I F the I
who's getting those jumps relatively
well down I guess
not I got a mid mid mid uh uh what's
happening what's happen that
ow okay okay
ouch I feel like I'm already losing too
much health
here
I'll oh what is that he dropped some fun
friends no just
bombs I'm actually really grateful so
far it feels like there were no
bosses that like spawn extra minions can
you
not oh wait f is able to do that even
though he was wait I can do that even
when he lifts up his hand at least it
like turns red
social distancing all right all
right
uh
oh
n n
n okay he's
invisible oh he got his friends but what
what works on
them what works on them this this
reflex oh wait I should
just I thought I had to use X-Ray when
he goes
invisible okay okay
okay but this is not even challenging
him just having minions out when he's
gone he should throw those at me when
he's still
around okay
fre energy check his left
oh
what wait what what
what wait I'm going to die like oh my
God oh my God can I restart why is he
back to full I missed my
window
oh I do not understand like you guys
said something about x-ray but I didn't
didn't see him I only saw his
minions when you fell down when he fell
down you
attacked I feeling the whole time you
were fighting them Al so do I just have
to be really fast
or I'm going to die
anyway and I keep on stepping into the
phasin you have to be fast just kill me
kill me just kill
me break armor then he
goes He spawns on the farthest pH and
puzzle from
you oh
fun break armor yeah yeah yeah I know
that I didn't see
[Music]
him power BM
I can break his armor instantly with a
power bump you mean this
one that
one where am I
[Music]
where am I where am I
here where am
I where am
I
ah I'm going
backwards okay
uh come on K what don't K dot dot dot me
I'm trying okay this was my first try I
just need to understand the system and
then I'll I'll do the thing don't start
ruining my mood already
okay let's try to
be PR and Dy
the [\h__\h] not working
[Music]
why do I not remember this at
all I don't even remember this what
okay
so uh if I want to break his armor I
should become
ball and make super ball
explosion cuz all these words they like
super beam super missile BL blah blah
they all sound so similar and I never
know what you guys mean
that's hard to carry
out you get you will get hit too much
you
don't I feel like it might even itself
out the thir is away from
me so he will like spawn either here or
there we can try it
[Music]
can I start to SP as a
ball I'm going to
try that that's the TR
though okay wait ah pacle pacle wait
wait wait wa wait wait wait so now just
as fast as possible I kill the ones and
then he comes back right I just have to
be
fast look for him now in x-ray but even
if I find him doesn't that
really xray ignore small
ones invisible
I don't see him I don't see
him I don't see
him I don't see him I don't see him I
don't see
him no I see
him that's just how long he
takes oh
will he continue
to is he is he going to do his thing is
he back to wait so charge ah is he
charging
again no it's he back to
[Music]
normal [\h__\h]
hell are they
gone I just go what the [\h__\h]
little
[\h__\h] okay okay okay okay now they're
gone now they're
gone sorry I'm like panic panic cooking
everything
one
again I don't care I don't care no
no oh he takes quite some time until he
appears anyway doesn't
he oh I even used the purple one h
would have been a bit faster with the
other ones
maybe
okay did that oh that one didn't work I
think and now I'm out
of I'm out of the
my bomb soone now I'm kind of on my own
ow
okay that's the wh spawn purple
on you spawn
free I feel like that's not working
that's not purple that's not purple I
don't care I don't
care I'll just look for him there he
is random
[Music]
yeah I'm not I'm not winning this time
either although he is halfway
down [\h__\h] hell I don't know where I
am
[Music]
yeah how many times do I have to do
that was I already in the last
um Loop
five
times until he's dead I hate that
answer that's like when when do we
arrive we arrive when we
arrive that was close
y' I guess
[Music]
so I left
okay
um where is
[Music]
it I am
blind I don't see anything
this
is what am I looking
at I'm so blind guys I'm so sorry but I
just don't see
[\h__\h] wasn't
this huh
why is it so dark
man I'm scared
[Music]
mommy I hate everything
today today is just not fun
it's already not fun guys
because people are
mean game is
mean everything's mean
[Music]
set me
back okay well it worked
did he not spawn
yet oh there he is
okay come I'm going to keep I don't know
I don't know if I should uh do it I'll
try I'll
try
okay get as far as possible with this um
strategy see what color he spawns one
yellow two
yellow nice
did I waste it feel like I wasted
it I wasted
it I wasted it I wasted my charge
not
wasted
okay and I guess there's going to be
some yellow yeah
look uh you guys say if I fast I can get
him another time is that true
oh I did I did
need them to [\h__\h] off because
otherwise no
why ah
the jump is so hard to get right oh my
God I'm going die again
I'm taking too much
D I don't see it
help
[Music]
me he's always charging with a stupid
hand
[Music]
I don't know how I'm going to do this
yby yeah Bo
can they can they just [\h__\h] off I just
want to find him really no I'm dying
this is not it this is not
it not this
[Music]
I got another Power
it's not
okay I'm not upset there was so
[Music]
many there were so many
minions and they were all I was already
so low on HP so I wanted to make sure
they don't they're not going to be the
reason why I'm
dying you
know purple super missile fast kill the
boss in two faces purple super missile
you mean you mean the the ultra wave
beam
thingy Super
Wave I'm I might um try it then because
I have so many missiles anyway that I'm
not using in this
fight wave Buster yeah
not the
way
fine I don't like switching between
the hold the colors so much cuz I
already have to do that for the
[Music]
minions I'm shaking
I fight the minions I have to fight the
minions otherwise they're going to be
millions of them and then and then I'm
all going to
like PE at me while I'm trying my best
already to dodge the damage that he's
already doing to
me the boss kill minions I feel like
they stayed uh last in in my first
try even
though he was already back on his feet
again
what trying to hit him when when he's
already the shields
what Shields I don't know what that
[Music]
means right away from the B you I've
been trying to stay away from him but
then I always step into this [\h__\h] and
one question is there any way
to have him have his arm up less because
when I when he has his arm up I know I
can't do damage but he's got it like all
the freaking
time no oh
man
okay one more H he would have died
yeah and I know I got really
close third third or fourth try or so
let's go he looks like
me this don't get
sucked oh this time it didn't
immediately down him is it because it
was like too
lopsided y nice shots
though I mean in this moment I I feel
like I can still play with the minions
because he's kind of like still thinking
where he should go
anyway now now now he's like going
somewhere
kind is she going to kill him oh what
[\h__\h] I had better um hits before with my
bombs
[Music]
[\h__\h] you a [\h__\h]
you [\h__\h] you kiding
it sorry this terrible terrible
run little bastard [\h__\h]
he
he always Dan spawns in the opposite uh
place right or no oh
no they're still alive look got will
kill
them now they're
gone this is not the Run E look at my
health
nice that a good
one nice get Kiwa
where is he where is
he them them them
a can someone tell them to [\h__\h] up
already set up to help come
on took you long enough
that's a charge isn't
it where is he
[\h__\h] no I got
a got
a now it's t really find him okay I'll
I'll ignor him completely I'll ignor him
completely
jump around just jump around jum Jump
Around jump jump jump jump
jump I did it but at what
cost don't fall on me what the [\h__\h]
squished
salus e e
is he mounting on top of me thank you
Doug Hood ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew
oh but it makes me even stronger I'm
like a Powerpuff
girl I feel like that's how Powerpuff
Girls work in the creation
process fa and suit oh does that mean
that now I can step on all that
[\h__\h] has been infused with pure phasin
this corruption prevents damage from
phasin radiation y
thank you
Game I'm so salty this suit isn't in
Smash to me it looked like I just have
some I don't know some
weird uh low opacity layer around
me yeah well I mean it was obvious that
I'm not going to do it first
try I don't know why some of you guys
expected me to do super well on the
first try
of course I need some time to learn it
come
on of course I
do safe should I go back to
Safe yeah I'll go backwards cuz I don't
know when to save B
this I wonder if failing a few times
that the boss is calculated into
the estimated
time okay finishing the
[Music]
game
yes I would hope so otherwise it's
unrealistic and I need some health
please
ow might have been counter wait I get
health in my I'm saving sorry
I know I know I
know I know I know ooh wow wow wow wow
wow actually now I see some differences
I wish I could just like sometimes just
look at myself let me look at myself
again I mean in this view it's kind of
hard to
see cuz it's so
dark what the real color is now am I
like brown now
H which one this one why am I I'm black
red oo
[Music]
oopsie
oh wait
camera
camera uh oh there we go
wow here there we
go
wow yeah that one looks really cool but
I already missed my normal orange suit
because orange is my my image color it's
supposed to be my
color
man okay so we move on after this is
just the artifact
hunt then Final Bosses you can finish
this in maybe two to 4 hours depending
on your pace and how many times you die
Final Bosses are the Final Bosses more
difficult than this
one this one was like I mean the whole
like
tactics that's manageable to figure out
but like the problem was my health I
didn't have enough
Health a bit somewhat okay but not
like these are Next Level what what's
with them
they don't get
Frozen Wait do they have
colors this is why I don't scan
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
you just trying to get to know
you this is what you do to me just
trying to read your
profile uh my turn split into two forms
mut capable of splitting into this split
endows the new creatures with
invulnerability to most weaponary this
effect is unstable resulting in weakness
to a type of weapon fire the
vulnerability appears to be random due
to the chaotic nature of the phase in
mutation again I mean judging by the
color is already guessed
well the purple one
probably doesn't
like [\h__\h] you guys how about you eat my
[\h__\h]
bombs yeah I can see it but the white
one doesn't seem to react to the ice one
I mean it doesn't get iced at
least [\h__\h] these [\h__\h] I hate them
what they're so annoying
[Music]
no can I just say no just just
no no no no no
[Music]
I'm getting
bullied I'm getting
bullied come
here oh why don't you come now
[Music]
what on
Earth I never want to pass this stupid
room ever
again no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no
no I'm going to race quit because of
these [\h__\h]
[Music]
there's not many things that make
me
like yell in
German this is one of the very rare
things
that make me rage in German and that
means a
lot oh my
God why why did they have to follow
Evolution theology
H why is that really fair
all right let's figure out how to get
out of this [\h__\h] hell
[Laughter]
hole power
bump what the [\h__\h] is a power bump it's
not this thing right cuz I don't even
have a charge in
them that's what you meant I read that
comment already before and I tried but I
saw I have no charge
so that's not going to help me now is
it you are dealing with a very very
salty
kiaha how do I get up
there can I
even there is a path here
too wait
uh this I saw before and I wanted to
enter it but if not if it wasn't for the
stupid
metroids that kept stalking the [\h__\h] out
of
me let's talk about something nice shall
we what is this I had Korean lesson
today let's
go yeah Sim came again Sim means teacher
I
[Music]
am or something like that but
she's hello
yeah today we repeated in the beginning
we repeated oh 50% we repeated a little
bit of what I learned
previously and
then which was uh Pim I think they're
called CH
Pim the endings that I tweeted about
last time and then she was like oh TR
because I did so well and I remember it
so well wow w wow W well a this is so
pretty
yeah so that was no problem so we could
quickly move on don't tell me it's
no no more floors lava
y oh Cam ra that sounds like a cam
ra oh
hi yeah and then uh we M I think we
started uh some more
reading
practice and
then I think then we moved on to like
already learning how to build
sentences and she told me that in Korean
you always ends the sentence with a verb
so no matter what it always ends with a
verb so subject and then
verb and that well I think on the
language I've learned it's very similar
so that's not too difficult to remember
that that's not a problem and actually
quite easy to remember it just always
follows that
[Music]
one that one theory that one same
pattern m
and then she told me that uh there's
like uh markers after a subject and
after verb and
after what was the other thing that I
wrote down I forgot I forgot but you
always have to uh end something with uh
like a for example subject marker so
kiar or or like eggy eggy baby uh it
will end Ed K and eggy ends in a
vowel so that he would end with
depending on if it ends in a vowel or
the other thing what a consonant I don't
know all these fancy words you have
different ways to add things so for
example un and n and uh she I think I
need to repeat I just learned this so I
need to repeat that that stuff to learn
it uh and remember
it yeah but I've heard it many times it
seems pretty pretty reasonable so I I
learned the same thing
for for the verbs as well you have to
add something after the verb as
well but even for verbs like coming from
a German language where we have like a
million forms of uh verbs uh of yeah
time time and
persons
Etc I'm glad because Korean doesn't seem
so overly complicated to
[Music]
me ping about is generally a good way to
make sure their information rains your
brain I agree that's really true yeah so
far even when I haven't been practicing
between the Le lessons much besides 15
minutes right before the lesson I still
feel like I kind of like remember it
very well I thought I would have to
practice in between more but that wasn't
really the
case just talking about it a little bit
here helps
though so yeah um yeah and then we
started making some
sentences uh like she told me some
simple verbs for now like eating and
drinking and watching and hearing eating
is Mo so for for example
Ki
[Music]
K I don't know uh pop pup is rice
pop well that was probably partially
incorrect but uh that should mean kiaha
eats rice or is eating
rice and then the other on M
M now the other ones I already forgot I
think I think sleeping
is CH something like that I'm un sure
CH something something with true and I
think what a good sentence in a day yeah
jum was it jum
J yeah okay that was right okay I
remember yeah so we wrote down a couple
of uh
sentences where do I
go and then also she told me some
greetings like
hello but like more more polite than
that where do I
go more polite and then thank you and
goodbye and all that all that kind of
stuff yeah
spider track behind
me is that a spider
track oh there that's hard to
see
okay yeah so I feel like I made good
progress again
today feeling very
satisfied uh uh uh
yeah yeah fall
down good better this way why are they
so stunned why are they not moving
around
Buck the
N you
okay drop me something
no learning at a really nice Pace yeah
for real I feel like
oh I feel like I'm learning really fast
and really efficiently so I really
appreciate it must have been a deep
fault maybe yeah it this
[Music]
room shall I go
in there where some more tracks outside
though where's this
having a teacher to guide you to learn
is pretty good yeah I'm really grateful
that was the right choice I think I
already made more progress than I did
last year throughout the year learning
alone this a shortcut or so oh I don't
think I have to go there do I
got the
artifact check my guide for artifacts oh
okay well well what is this area
anyway which is there anything in here
that I C at which which area is
this maybe something
uh green burp ain't it not definitely
not
pH and mindset
too and
minds are those the closest ones
now
ones
oh face mines oh yeah artifact of War
artifact of
newborn one is an elite in an elite
research room
I don't see that up here that's not the
right that's not the same map and one is
in the phas and Mining tunnel
oh but that might be that might be
somewhere where I am he in mining
tunnel
T is that the is that what I'm
saying there's a
little maybe not not maybe not
here there are two in this
area
um
wait I just saw
something phasing processing set oh wait
this this one facing
my there's one
here and
one in a big
round room which I don't see oh wait
it's this one Elite
research okay but I'm in the middle of
these
Maps so
maybe when I took this where did I come
out where so where does this bring me
wait that brings me to I have to take
this like elevator I suppose to go
down which one was it the
um this
one um yeah yeah all right I'll
take I'll find an El elevator this this
uh Brown Arrow downwards should do the
trick no I'd go up first because going
down is always easy
up just go
backwards well I'm here now so
I'll what
oh that wa that where I just came from
s are you
friend and now
down oh no there's more of the metr
[Music]
now oh hi
he's
down I hate you I hate
you now it's purple that little [\h__\h] is
now purple and now it has a purple and a
white
one I hate them I hate them I hate them
I hate
them I'm going to rage quit this game
because of these
[Music]
[\h__\h] are they for real like they
can't
even decide who's going to jump on me
next next are they gone are they
gone
unbelievable where is this
door I need to take this down otherwise
I'm going to go absolutely
mad okay I needed to be quiet and calm
the door is above
me I just ignore enemies from this point
I would like other enemies yes but these
stupid metroids they jump on me and I
have to become a ball in order to fix it
and then they just don't stab so
honestly I have to kill them I would
love to just opt out for that as
well but they won't let
me I know they died to one Power Bomb
but did you see if I had any no I didn't
have any
I need to recharge my power box
but I
can't salty CH yes today is a day to be
extra
salty
yes they started good but now they they
not my day
not every day can be your day some days
are just not as nice and that's just how
it is that's
okay but then you got to force it to be
your kind of day I don't understand this
isn't this where I came from this is
exactly where I came from but then I
don't I don't understand
huh red but I thought I had to go
through this ow
thingy maybe we should not play
this maybe we should just leave this
game
onto I'm on the level I want to be on
all
right uh faing mining tunnel so I just
go
straight you're so close yes I
am so I also don't want to just end
it no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no wait what
[Music]
I no no no no no no no no no
what no no no
[Music]
I should just I should
just I hate this thing this is
so not good for
me it's not fun today
[Music]
no this is not even so annoying that's
not
it not even so bad
at least I can walk down here
now I don't know it's just not fun being
like constantly
like getting these I don't know how to
describe them comments that make me feel
like I'm the stupidest [\h__\h] piece of
[\h__\h] ever hi artifact I see
you no I don't see you
anymore Which
Way h
oh wow we're doing nothing we're
collecting
artifacts number
three uh
uhuh thank you mental
Jett you sweet you're really a mental
Jetty you know you know how how
to cheer me
up why do I not just jump normally oh oh
I see I feel it already I feel it Ki wow
why don't you just [\h__\h]
jump we're at the bottom now back to the
top could I go for the purple
one and
then I guess I got to go for the green
one after
that but the purple one is
close no
no no no it will get better now surely
surely
Temple
um okay so I take this path
again
down we're going to up this time I
assume
yeah surely Temple pretty good oh yeah
right oh wa this isn't even an issue
until it becomes an
issue
right this really does give pinball
Vibes after
all Metroid invol
form basically after reti gets used as a
pinball machine
ball want a life to
live I'm just going to take the bottom
[Music]
path they did make a
Metroid pinball what the [\h__\h] okay okay
now now now now you're taking a fight
with
me ah
absolute
chaos my
friends my best days let's
go that one stuck
are they're going to kill
me I wanted to leave the room okay now
up to the b b the
top I'm really trying guys I'm I'm
trying to you
know oh always look on the Bri side of
life thank you thank you
Panic ball is literally the exact
strategy for fighting
metroids all
right at least I have you know my guide
and I don't have to ask you guys all the
time left or right which
one so I'm a little bit independent
today and that way I think maybe we're
saving a little bit of time as
well going my own way
now I move on
to Green
Place Green place kind of
far not going to
lie but after this we can leave this
area that has all the stupid metroids
right they won't be there any the other
places hopefully
[Music]
wait did they upgrade the Metros
everywhere
now feel like they upgraded them
everywhere cuz normally the ones that
spawned
here pretty
harmless about that
what you're telling me they're like
everywhere
this like this now oh my God they are
they are aren't they what if I [\h__\h]
die on
[Music]
them the problem with the lock on AIM is
that when there's so many enemies where
it matters which one I lock on to oh my
God what what am I looking
at I don't really have control over
which one to pick
and now there's so many I can power on
them oh I got one I might have to use it
just now
anyway
okay okay everybody gather
here and be eliminated forever rest in
Rest In Hell
[Music]
please okay okay okay that's beautiful
gone it's silent now which way do I
go be gone
Monsters uh kind
of right and then
up
right and then up and then
left purple door
ah this is the room again where you can
turn them off
[Music]
huh well I don't
care unless I can do from
here I still took a lot of
damage yumy I need is there a saving
point on the way oh yeah there is okay
we can we can heal back up there all
good all good
yeah these are the kind of enemies I
prefer but maybe I shouldn't
even maybe I just
go
okay
saving these ones at least are easier to
run away from
and then have to get up
[Music]
there I'll I'll kill them CU otherwise I
can't look
around I'm not a coward
I'm a part-time
Warrior remember I don't only make
burgers I'm a
Survivor I would have to lose my
title if I were to run away from them
all the
time can't do
that how do I get up there hello Raiders
thank you chat for telling me that
there's
Raiders I think Kento is now working on
the hyper chat upgrade so that I can see
the
raids platform
platform
platform I only remember I only remember
jumping
down not jumping back up what there it
is there is the path the golden path
[Music]
I never forgot about your part time
where status thank you really sometimes
I
forget I have to
admit
okay
no not good for people with really bad
iight ah this happened before I have a
dja Vu
now an outfit based on your Warrior Lord
would be super
badass but when you think of an outfit
based on on Warrior lore what kind of
outfit are you guys
imagining what my jump button didn't
work I swear are you thinking about
something that looks like Senti like my
sword like inspired by my sword or my or
my full plate
armor I don't think that's the type of
war that I am full plate more fantasy
more medieval fantasy inspired leather
armor and I'm trying to fix the audio
right
now okay it's crackling
Fire Emblem style night lady I
[Music]
mean yeah I would surely look good in
that but I don't think that would be my
choice if you mean like I don't know
like Jade what I'm busy I'm getting
artifacts return AR to gain access to
impact y yeah yeah give me some time
give me some
time oh go there I'll I'll go there
after collecting some
artifacts let her cook game exactly oh
my thank God there's no metroids here
Bey
b you are now my
property oh
hi but yeah I also think like
something that shows the fierce fighter
side would be nice what the [\h__\h] why am
I
so wait wait for it no no no don't don't
well I only got one of them
[Music]
which door am I going to go
through give me a moment to look at the
map full power Phoenix
form oh wait that that door actually
never entered that white
door should I go
now linkless outfit link this outfit
cute if I'm thinking of the same thing
that you thinking
about
yeah oh yeah have to break that with
a power
bump only got
one only not
what's behind oh a map I already have
like the whole map
though I already have it
all I only get here with a
PP ah but I guess it's it wouldn't be
only of the middle level that I am on
but like of all three but I kind of
already right this map room is weird why
did I hide it behind a rock
pillar I feel like I already saw all of
it nothing was added thanks
thanks just maybe one room at Max and
that was the room where I got the map
from great all right no complaining
for completion sake where am I
going uh green one almost
there almost
there there still a room I
[Music]
missed
what oh
well exena Warrior type princess type oh
wo whoo wait I feel oh I don't have my
phone of me I feel like I know I feel
like I must have seen it
before
wa have a SE seen I think I
have I vaguely remember
it let me look it
up Cena war ah Warrior
Princess no no no no that's not what I
would go for no no
no
nah
no n nah
[Music]
I am
uncultured too much skin no that's not
the
issue it's kind of lame it's kind of
lame well well just leave it to me I am
cultured I will prove
you oopsie
wrong I know you guys say I can skip
them now but I feel like it stresses me
out when they're just like running
around me and the music also stresses me
out and then I can't really think about
where I am
especially if it's like a small room if
it's a big
room where everything is clear
maybe are we going down or up up right
with the green one
okay letting me cook thank you thank you
out herself or a legendary B oh sure
sure she is a character yeah
[Music]
yeah I need to rewatch the
movie all
right I got it yay
second artifact is in our grasp
reach I'm going to the top and then
we're getting out of
here out of the phas and
mines this is this all the ph and mines
is what do you call this place
this big Elite research room oh we're
really close to it just got to
get up there and then up there
okay this room I
remember ey yay you speak hongo
oh and by the way I also learned in
Korean they only have
two
honorific um
titles you know how in Japanese there's
sun and Chan and S and
Kun and even more fun ones in Korean
there's only two she and Nim so you can
say kiar she and kiar
Nim and because Nim is one of them
that's why like for example in some some
Nim see it's how it's already there so
you don't have to add another one and
jum Jang n it's also already there so
you don't have to add another one to
that either it's already included in the
word you can't really say it without it
though my teacher said it's just like
part of the
word oh this one's
noral H but I am very familiar with
the whole you know honorific titles
thingy so oh there's a room
there so that is not difficult for me to
grasp either especially if there's only
two that's really
helpful but basically the same as in
Japanese if
you call someone without a title at all
which you
can only same as Japanese if you like
really really close like if your couple
with your BFFs for
life and those oh oh got the timing
down only in those cases so again
another thing that I didn't have to
learn because I already knew it isn't
that
amazing so I've been really appreciating
having this knowledge already
yeah
s dead
mean like bordering on
family terms yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
like for real for real for
real for real for real for real okay so
there's a there's an artifact here let
me see this one's pretty you you'll
notice a capsule here containing a na
rather nasty beast called the
phasin
capsule faing elad simply use a power
bomb to release the Beast oh oh is it
down
there oh
hi
okay shoot yeah is that I I just saw
it we release that we'll kill it and
then we get the the reward for it get
ready for a fight mm be aggressive here
but avoid shooting the pirate and hand
is raised yeah plasma beam all righty
all righty all righty I have to release
the
monster
oopsie no
problem wake
up
kaha oo I just already fought a really
big version of you
[Music]
so this is like small baby
version I killed your dad
basically sorry maybe I shouldn't have
said that maybe it's nicer to die not
knowing that I I mean you can meet in
heaven that's what you believe
in yay artifact artifact give me give me
give me give
me
easy oh thanks for the Super Chat I
might be a while until I read that
properly well I I'll get to it
eventually maybe in two
weeks the six of 12 1 two three four
five four we have four now okay okay
okay all
right
uh is it worth checking out this room
does it have something interesting it's
pretty
close Leo thank you thank you thank you
check it all
right where am
I oh
oh oh I got hit even though I wasn't
aiming I'm going at a good Pace am I
thank you thank
you thank
you I appreciate positive vibe
than um down here and
then more
down yeah I'm mean from here just the
artifact collection I feel like there
shouldn't be anything big hindering
me except for
metroids metroids currently my biggest
enemy
scan thing to the
left
what other left other other left is
right don't that
this
thing does that
[Music]
mean you want me to blow it up with a
super
bumb super missile Power
Bomb does it have to be a
power
okay force field
inactive
ah n Nar Nar
Nar R room
wouldn't be a kiaha Metroid stream
without a couple of jump
scares steal their
weapons this is not that kind of game as
far as I know where such a thing as
[Music]
possible oh how could you miss kiaba you
were right in front of it
feeling kind of bad at them seeing them
like having a stroke like that
I'm
sorry let
her they deserve
it from our point of view they're the
evil but from their point of view we are
the
evil you
know what he
this it was worth coming
here is that the the red
missile
[Music]
thingy flamethrower you say it's me in
what game is a flamethrower ever
me it's one of the last weapon things
you get can't be
M okay I won't use it now I one the
waste missiles
next next go next go next
uh what what is like the
closest
area this is
what we're in the in these blue ones
right the phas and
mines where is easily accessible for me
go to elevator okay
will take me to town
for
down where's the white
door oh there's more
[Music]
leave
me at least they can't walk through with
me um what yeah I'm going the right way
okay we have to go up but maybe I could
save too should I save I should save too
right I will
at this point you can pick any route
okay I'll just see where the elevator
brings
me what's this this big
place
okay do you
remember how to get to the safe point oh
yeah kill me
recently I reminded myself of a or I was
reminded of a really cool is it is it
Punk or rock pop run Rock what punk rock
pop punk rock rock Punk is that a thing
really cool song from back in the day
that I'm going to sing in my
next in my next cut you guys are going
to be like kiaha Bas so Bas oh my
God can't believe she's saying the
song I was also surprised that I knew
the
song guys are going to love it I think
everybody knows it unless there's a lot
of tumors in my chat are there many
zumos in my
chat who here is
under
22 who in the chat is under
22 I think it's better to ask who's
under 22 then asking who's overt to me
me
what okay don't say not me I'll just
make should I make a
poll make a
poll under 22 or 22
over
okay I mean I feel like if you go
through a lot of like music and maybe
you even know these songs these old
songs 21 one month old I round up how
the [\h__\h] are you guys so
young help
of of course I'm I'm just as young but
um
anyway okay let's see the result have to
disable hyperchat for that okay well
most are over 22 hallelujah thank
God it's 40 over
22 that's quite oh qu a I mean 15%
Zoomer in my chat
kitty
kitties no I mean you know of course the
the ones that are young you know you
have to understand I'm I'm we are all we
are all also very jealous at you for
your youth share it with me but just
want to understand like who is z Zumer
who is
not hold on I do have like statistics so
AG
statistics so I I don't have to do it
like too closely if I want to get more
info I can just look at my YouTube
statistics we are now here is there
um an artifact in
this Talon
Overworld Talon
Overworld there's two but don't I
already have them
probably artifact of Truth artifact of
choal I feel like I have those both of
them the truth one I'm sure I
have life Pro one I probably have that
one
too I mean it looks kind of familiar to
me I got them
okay okay
so where am
I should I just enter the next best
elevator that one chos a ruin
South Cho
ruins there's three artifacts in the
choso ruins and I don't think I have a
single one of
them so let's go chose the ruins
a
elevator go to the top I
guess platforming kiaha wow wow wow
[Music]
the artifacts I needed yeah of
course I need all the
artifacts to prove that I am the chosen
one the right
one all
right here we are there's free let's see
where we land to see where where the
closest one is there's one in the
meditation chamber one in the sun
chamber oh I think I saw that in the
speedrun and one in the Elder
chamber Elder chamber Sun chamber
meditation oh so many
chambers which is the
closest antichamber that's not
it all of
Elders
Crossway Fus
energy
core
buring Hall Sun
chamber sun
tower I found one Hall of Elders has an
energy tank too oh there's some uh extra
rooms that I haven't seen yet
h ah hall of Hall of ERS oh yeah you say
there's an energy tank there are you
sure I didn't got that one
yet you have to go for sun
tower what meditation
chamber meditation
[Music]
chamber Sun
chamber Elder
chamber El chamber is
like maybe
here
s am I blind what is this one Plaza
access
ruin have no
idea just's go Hall of ell oh okay
okay
[Music]
straight save point H I just saved
recently I think you I'm good I'm good I
this one would have been Maybe easierly
easily
[Music]
accessible nope Hall of the
elders yeah this
room where is this
uh this energy tank that you speak
of so fondly
n we have you fight this
again I mean I see them mostly purple
purple a gole purple purple works right
purple purple always
works yeah purpple always
[Music]
works me me
no power
beam My Pal beam was
[\h__\h] was that red
[Music]
yellow that's what I
thought but with the
missile
no okay one more
tanky yeah I'm also very
dodgy damn hadoken
[Music]
spammers so these are always going to
show
up annoying okay where was
so
tank morph ball in hand ah yeah I saw
that in the speed run I
think yeah
yeah no never
mind no mind kind of different from what
I
expected uh
what how how does it work
again shoot red circle and bomb
it oh I can do all colors now did I ever
do that
before probably
it's so nice being held is this how it
feels like for you guys when I hold you
Simpkins and
no only one of
them oh can I undo it
jump up and bomb
it
uh not sure how to get
there I don't remember anymore oh hey
safe
point I'll
save just
jump oh maybe I can
H jump from the
chair platforming speedrun
strats oh oh what's
[Music]
up
um um
[Music]
what do you mean just
jump oh wait I feel like I managed to
jump from
here over there before I maybe not oh
I'm not here
okay okay okay
so is it okay that I have all three of
them activated
seems fine
oh
[Music]
W this is where the that huh I thought
that's where the energy thing is
[Music]
wait because the Elder chamber is not
called elder chamber on the map it's
called Hall of the elders and that's why
I got said to come here and I thought
what cuz it's called oh wait
underneath ah but you don't know about
this until we
[Music]
open that is
confusing I should have maybe yeah maybe
if I read all of this then I would have
understood what about the other one that
I couldn't find then there must be an
explanation for that in the tower of
light oh yeah okay Tower of light leads
you to a wave beam door right at the
bottom of the room it's underwat so need
gravity
suit and okay
okay it's like a secret
yeah very
secret not very nice though cuz I need
all of those
all right uh go
next Tower of light I think it's pretty
far so give
up go through here go through Tower of
light this this one or I guess I could
first go to the sun
chamber that probably makes
sense I'll aim for the sun
chamber so
[Music]
wait there's another white door that I
haven't opened yet
here but I thought
no it's a shortcut middle slot for the
energy tank middle
slot ah middle door you mean
[Music]
which one is the middle this
one a middle slop ah you mean the bomb
slot what have I never like done that
before
really I guess I'll take
[Music]
the wait what do I have to leave the
room
[Music]
once maybe I have to leave the
room but I already did reset by going on
the S reset
please hey
please a
and do I have to leave free
rooms so I reset two rooms is this two
rooms
goodbye does the door have to close
[Music]
ah yeah
and what are you waiting
for thought that was
it no that's
it okay next this is the middle one you
guys say for the energy tank or what
all
right activate
[Music]
it thanks for the
pinky thank you left something matur in
your art tag oh thank
you looking forward to it thank you for
watching
are you going to
work CH can going to second job what
about this
job it's
okay yeah I love my energy tanks
D go next now we go to the sun chamber I
think need money for merchant super
chats true true true true what a
motivation to
have
[Music]
motivation what about this one
why does it why did that did I never use
that
door well
nice for now just follow the course what
is this is too
dark it's so
dark but this place meant to be
dark these are shortcuts for completion
is not
needed okay in the furnace okay at the
pizza
chamber tomorrow Pizza it's going to be
a little bit uh giddy gidy
because my pizza
chamber has been having a little bit of
a delay in delivery and has yet to be
delivered but it should be delivered
tomorrow if not then we'll have to delay
the stream to another date
but hopefully it will come
tomorrow I hope so my pizza chamber
friend is also very excited
we're all very excited just
way
e sorry pizza fun no no no no I'm not
going to use a normal oven no who do you
think I am I take pizza making seriously
as one half has to one must
always when making pizza be very very
serious about it as if your life depends
on
it if that's not your attitude while
making pizza then that's why your pizza
doesn't turn out the way they
should
mhm that's why you will never get the
real Italian flavor I mean you never
will never will if you don't put a lot
of work into
it got to put your whole
body's forc into
it I'm going I'm going here
now energy core access basically I'm
looking at
it oh
yeah does this one also want hit them
now yeah is
it let it at least makes them go to
sleep piz isn't tomorrow yeah yeah yeah
but I forgot does Amazon deliver on
Saturdays
here but the thing is if I if I'm like
still waiting for it on Saturday I can't
be sure if the stream is happening so
and I also can't practice my pizza
making making the pizza have to practice
making the pizza so I'll take a safe
point it should have wrapped tomorrow it
has
to Amazon does every day in America yeah
and then Japan too in Austria it
definitely doesn't do Sunday I'm not
sure if they do
Saturday it happens too rarely for me to
remember maybe they do but they
definitely don't do
Sundays we austrians or maybe Europeans
take
our weekend days very seriously which I
would say is pretty like nice as a
worker I don't remember
either I thought Amazon was every day
know whatever no no no no no we have
more human
laws but still I mean even then I'm I'm
sure that Amazon delivery people they're
really on under constant stress
nonetheless probably
the Tower of light is
closer as you have to go the long way
around the Sun chamber due to flag or
blocking off the shortest way in Oh you
mean that this way is not possible to
enter oh that's the
case then all right I will go to the
Tower of light
first okay okay
then I'll go straight first I think and
there are
oh maybe I can
keep there are shut up shut up shut
up okay what was I going to say there
are some rooms there that I haven't seen
yet either so that's going to be
interesting these guys are always near
artifacts yeah but now they were pretty
far but I saw I think I saw in the
speedrun that the S chamber one is also
protected by them
yeah two rooms near
count I prefer them as I said over the
Metroid so all is good oh I'm in the new
room now
what's it called magma
pool wait I don't have a suit yet for
the magma
right is that even there's no magma suit
in this game right we just take like
less damage now
but what's down
there oh more this looks like in
Minecraft this looks like just
ah where's it where's I don't see I
don't see it's okay I don't take that
much damage Don't Panic don't wait I
really I really don't see I really can't
see I really can't see I really cannot
see it shouldn't be like shouldn't it be
like one step back like oh yeah there it
is
what
the wait I wait that's what that is for
isn't it oh my God oh my God
oh if this was Minecraft I would be dead
I
think
oh how the [\h__\h] did that
happen I was going to be careful I was
not going to fall in and yet I
did the moments where you're extra
careful that's when you you fall in
oh oh okay this room this room I know
and then the next room is unknown again
I'll take that one is that basically
like a shortcut
too
straight also look at
that a
[Music]
oh
no [\h__\h]
at least it's only
two I want to get those uh that energy
tank that I saw the other side of the
room it's an energy tank R give me give
me can I blow that up with uh
ball it's kind of
low
or or is it for
here got to do a puzzle
okay it's a
puzzle wait no no no no no no
Cal calm
C wait
what
perfect oh why is it a puzzle why is it
a puzzle there's only two of these
things that already looks
perfect oh time time is up the essence
[Music]
what even though I
fumbled on the
millisecond clutch does the other side
also have something useful or is the
other side bamboozle what is
this what does this mean again
I how you cut
out opens the way
forward Oh you mean the other the door
that I want to
take
okay uh
come on come on waah come on
waah oh wait oh this one is not oh this
one's not a Time
challenge oh through the bird
[Music]
mouth H there was a power P expansion in
the lava room
m not
[Music]
a should have told me earlier we're
missing it now it's
okay I'm hoping that it's not that
necessary which where where am
I I'm so close to the Tower of Lights uh
basically
straight down here okay
missile Straight
Ahead look up for
grapple oh I see
it uh what doesn't react to
me too late now
huh before I jum down why why would I
want that
there I'd have to go back to reach it oh
[Music]
no do I need
it do I need
that yeah chat delay you guys have to
write those things 3 minutes ahead of
time a missile upgrade ah have a million
missiles now I feel like I'm
good careful about the gum
[Music]
Pizza
Pizza a
pizza yes
what all right how do we get there
again think oh wait H don't worry guys
don't worry I got it I got
it there's one correct side which I
think is this one oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I missed I miss in this room to
left side no no I feel like that one I
got left side from
here wait this was actually the the that
path to the door
on side
what you got the one on the bottom oh
there's another
one ball too
small all right if it is easily
accessible I shall get
it oh yeah okay
okay if it's on the way I'm fine I'm
fine if it's on the
[Music]
way thank you for telling
me just in
time
uh wait what wasn't it de
way [\h__\h]
no gaslighting
myself camera changes
confusing her brain
no next is light of
tower to light of tower what tower of
Lights Tower of
Lights light of tower kiaha come on
English light of toas
toas light W yeah
yep let me
see uh ah right at the bottom of the
room it's on the water okay oh bottom of
the
room
here yo easy that one was nice
[Music]
fifth of 12 it's filling up it's filling
up we got the six now I
think all right and then we go back and
then we have to go through here
maybe to reach it
okay uh where am I oh there
okay how is your tailes game two years
in the future come on not that much in
the future or in in
advance you jokey person so funny
haha room of the ruins PL yeah yeah I
know I know
and all right all right I think I have
to
[Music]
go yeah up
there
what oh the
bees the bees are still alive after all
that destruction the bees are still
alive what does that tell us maybe we
don't need to worry that much about the
bees after
all think got
there unless unless Kiama gets
Angy that's that's how it
look go somewhere
else well actually the
[Music]
was well actually they're Birds okay
they have
wings they fly means they are
[Music]
bird how does w Ki waa get to that
door how does she get access to the
plaza I would don't
remember maybe
jump but they bug you oh are bugs called
oh bugs because they bug you
Now give me
missile I should be able to get missile
too
no I have like everything you could get
in the game pretty
much there's a grapple
hook
no how do I
oh is that the one uh is that the one
where it was like oh too late now it's
too late
again or no I don't even think that was
access accessible this
time okay okay so I give up on that one
all right
um can you guys tell me how to get over
there I don't remember I don't remember
I don't
there's the door like this thing is that
can I even open that it's like dead
don't I have to like activate
it wait it can only be opened from the
other
side
M M M M all right I do have to take this
path
wait look at my health I only have one
more energy tank to collect
apparently so thank you guys for telling
me all the time where they are because
otherwise I I would have no idea
and I would be
lost Lost in
Translation I never watched that movie
by the way I know everybody says oh it's
so good it's legendary you have to watch
it it's also on a lot of like two Japan
plight often in their
repertoire they have Lost in
Translation
ironically never seen it either pretty
Man movie
what I've
totem
it oh wow a lot of people much don't
even know it what that's actually
surprising it's legendary and from 1979
believe it or not changed horror
horror okay good that I never watched it
I understand now why I
didn't it's a horror
movie it doesn't sound like a horror
movie Just judging by the title it's not
no it's not
elevator CH maybe I'll come to you
later oh we're so
[Music]
close red cockroach just pool what the
[\h__\h]
what okay okay cockroaches are gone
too there's lore in here oh this
one the cordite while hanging appears no
that's not lore that's just a hit app
appears to be slightly cracked are you
telling me to make it go boom a this one
wait I never read this
one the cries of this dying land echo in
our ears as we chose to watch the great
poisons seep ever further into the
living poles of the planet the dark
energy sinks into the trees and Waters
devouring all life peaceful beasts die
by the thousands some creatures survive
but their forms grow as twisted and EV
as the force that fell from the sky many
of these mutated monstrosities remain
small small enough to do little harm but
others grow enormous and threaten our
very existence one such Beast defiles
our sacred Fountain this gorging gorging
gorging joring gorging maybe poison from
its fou form replacing pure fly flowing
water with Cascades of creeping death
even in the face of such horror we CH do
not turn in
here I had to ride the first time
okay we are all that stands in the way
of this great poison and it is our duty
to contain it hi hi hi hi I'm working on
it so what is
this what is
this super missile the weak
wall weak
wall this
one what's super missile
again that
works that's like the sign
that's the other
sign scan
puzzle this runic symbol has been
activated four runic symbols in this
room must be activated
H has been activated
[Laughter]
okay okay two
more maybe over
here no
check the
pillars do I break them
too oh wait ah ah there you are what a
good hiding
spot ah
okay okay
okay
oh all
right B
[Music]
time
uh
y i okay I just normal ch
maybe if I let go of the button I'm
scared oh
okay
uh that that's tough especially cuz you
can't change the camera
I didn't trying to tell me
something he slide out he do a slide a
slide he do the
slide was he supposed to be
here I'm
in I'm
in hey bring it on
baby I cut the coil
[Applause]
Miss oh
no give me Miss
but that did the trick very
easily I playing with switch Pro
Controller I'm using yeah switch Pro
Controller remember this this was our
first big
boss and I
struggled and then I
won why did they want want me to go
through this specific door and close the
other ways
why why why why but this now is all of
the artifacts
in the chos of
ruins and look 1 2 3 4 5 6 seven out of
12 we have four more totally doable
so you couldn't retrieve the artifact
before spider ball
oh okay now you say magore how does this
one lead to magore oh yeah it does
okay I'll go that
way does that way
recently maybe I don't have to take
Korean lessons but uh math
lessons no I don't want to though I
don't need that anymore I don't need
math
lessons or even counting
lessons do not patronize me
bees go
like wa two 2 * 5 is
[Music]
10 don't num is in Korean yeah yeah yeah
yeah then we have to do that anyway
yeah okay we are in the beautiful
beautiful
magore oh is it wasn't really that
small so
Magmar there's two here in the Magmar
Caverns there's one in the lava
lake and one in the
oh in the mod station that I'm pointing
at right
now that leads to the warrior shrine set
the closest one then I one is the Lava
Lake Lava
Lake lava lake is first okay just go
straight going
smoothly oh wait maybe I need the
it they're
gone need the missile
please when you reach the warrior Shrine
use a power bomb on the
Statue uh uh-huh
[Music]
okay I'm going for a glass shaft power
bombed 3 minutes early when going for a
glass shaft Power Bomb is that the same
information than the that what the other
person was trying to tell
me another I don't remember how the
fight this
those are two different things but the
ice super missile ooh okay okay yeah I
would like to have
that wait does that make them stop
forever
better wait what isn't that where am I
like tunnel Okay lava lake is
next
okay um
first damn obliterated I feel
bad x-ray visor all right all right all
right all right to tomato
[Music]
oh well it's in there
okay will my weight destroy it
no yeah blow it up can
I Power Bomb It From a Distance or maybe
just uh just missiles normal
missiles a big
missile big
missile big yellow
missile
hi wowow wow
wowow to
artifact the nature one and now it's
four left
uh next moving on just through
this
room to the monitor
station off we go oh look at
that secret
door
uh oh there's another one really making
me waste all this
bombs
just is
it I'm
confused Overkill normal bomb would have
worked Mama
Mia I have no understanding of where I
am and what I am right now
Overkill Mama
M
oh I'm really confused what that just
did did I always St that path
[Music]
H thank
you
no I out balled
them triops sorry I keep on checking
just because I need to understand
understand in what direction I have to
go thanks for the membership
gift have to
[Music]
go
hi uhhuh
oh
missiles more
missiles missile expansion you use x-ray
if you want to get
[Music]
it it's in there isn't
it she was M he get
missiles no hold thanks for telling
me o
how do I get there did I just mess
up ah so close
what
what maybe from
here oh there an invisible platform
is it above me is it above me
head
yeah you sneaky little
[\h__\h] okay okay there more let's try the
other one first
maybe they really sound like merlocks
those things down there
a
[\h__\h] they're different ones too only
these
two only these two
[Music]
huh start from the beginning of the room
okay
okay wait this one's not
[Music]
invisible fall heart thank you fart is
the chat that Drew the F
art yo I hope you just came to the
stream and didn't see the beginning of
my salty so helpy play through until
now that is so pretty I love it so much
thank you so much for drawing me like
that perfect thumbnail material
absolutely gorgeous FL ah now I say
it when I still reging I know I can't I
know I can't what
no don't don't don't don't watch no no
no
okay is this moving it's
moving wait I want to go to the
top absolutely great art so true so true
can you get any
slower does it only go down when you on
it oh it's a
jump oh to
[Music]
jump am I getting
higher yeah I
am how can we get much higher I'm so
sorry but how high can we get I think
this is the
limit yo okay
a little bit too much effort for this
missile so
[Music]
high
okay
oh spontaneous Bal
[Music]
moment so now now now we take this route
rout where are
we what is telling me again to go
I'm busy getting the
artifacts
[Music]
girl is it the rway
yeah ow
return the monkey reject
humans that's just mean
chihuahua all right
I man ice is really really
powerful really do be powerful okay so I
am in the monitor
station you'll need to reach the very
top with the help of the space jump
boots and boost ball
ability double jump on top of the monit
station until you see a mechanism to
raise a metallic Bridge okay wait first
let's just let's just get to the
top let's just get to the top first
Ice Beam is the most powerful beam in
most my
[Music]
games no what I like about it is that it
freezes things so I have time to
panic don't have to deal with all the
[\h__\h] they give
me is this the top or should we go even
higher what top of the Mone so on top
like the
roof up
[Music]
there oh okay re
reachable w
[Music]
until you see a mechanism to raise a
metallic
bridge probably
this
mhm I need become
[Music]
ball ah what do you want
does it happy
now power rest St wow I'm a battery
suspension bridge
operational yay yay how to move
suspension
bridge record to oh great thank
you become battery again okay
[Music]
what although I just jump but I have to
move
this
jump oh but I have to move this
somewhere this might be one of my
favorite bgms in the
[Music]
game some of the instruments they use
the sounds they use kind of give me
breath of the wild
um what are they called
again the the go go go go go go go
go Goron yeah Goron
Vibes what is that that you hold in your
hand it is shiny it is fancy I need to
have B instinct
[Music]
yeah feel like
gorons are there also gorens in English
they have like similar
music in
Zelda thank you tazzy you're doing a
really good job at being
sweet it's gorin in English too in
German it's
gonin like I mean that's the the plural
deun and theun
all
right did I get them already all of them
I already got all of them
oh yeah the two from the M
Caverns now there's an elevator close
here fend oh thank God that's
like close
[Music]
by how about the
Statue NY
why would I break such a beautiful thing
huh
why here I
here as if I did it on purpose
Arthur that was close right
there what a
waste is that the
ice bubble bubble ah it's a power B EXP
it better fill up my power bombs though
didn't only byy
[Music]
one you sent me
back you set me back you little beach
okay calm down kiaha let's not be so
mean
uh turn
around ice in the Next
[Music]
Room next wait this
somebody once told me that this I think
is the room where I need to do something
or do I also have to make a big
explosion
here the room
oh ah it's the ice missile thingy oh my
God I'm getting too much
power oh ice
spreader sounds fun can I make all this
floor
ice I don't want to waste my missiles
I'm just still loading them up best
weapon in the game
that's F okay I'll give you
one oh how long does it
stay not a a little bit on lava well who
knows how well it works on enemies
[Laughter]
okay don't know in what times to use
this thing you going to say it's
powerful don't know I don't know when to
use it you tell
me I be back again oh my
God can't be bothered now why is this
there it
[Music]
is I know I was going to become ball
elevator feel so good to make progress
man thank
God thank God okay next we uh what was
it whatever F there's free in
here free am I missing free I thought I
was missing four
Ice Area I like it
icy let me see we have one in the
control
tower one in the choso ice
temple and one in the storage cave which
is on top of the circular fana's Edge
room where you will find an expansion to
your power bomb they say what's the
closest one
La
Canyon Ice Ruins Ice Ruins
Courtyard quantin
cave
Observatory storage cave Ed room choal
ice temple control tower ah control
tower okay maybe that's the
closest what's the next series that you
planning on starting after Metroid and
fire blem well first we'll play a couple
of like filler games I think and take it
easy ice
temple okay and then we okay will where
is that ice temple Play Breath of the
wild no chose the temple cles where the
[\h__\h] is that I don't say it
from starting position to the
right ah this one okay thank
you the wild is massive we're going to
start with the second one yeah cuz I
already like watched the like full 100%
playthroughs including the
Crocs a million times I've watched it a
million times like everything so I I
don't I'm not going to I'm not going to
play it
but looking forward
to I feel like I could make that looking
forward to playing the new one yeah
tears of the Kingdom saved
already um I don't know when the last
time I saved but I guess I could go save
Prime two will break you oh well I'm
currently not planning on playing
it if there are qus in the new game will
you collect them all please no no no no
no no especially not after seeing what
the reward was after getting all of them
poop it was
pop nothing useful
can you believe
it up
there oh before I could not make this
jump can I now no still
not eyes this
way leave me alone
and I think that will take us a while
right how many hours was breath of the
wild in terms of gam playay
length a lot
50 so I'm guessing tears of the Kingdom
will be like
close there's a missile up there
below me too
what below
me below
me c in nice
don't make me use
power ah normal this one
works okay
yay oh thank you I didn't see that one
at
all oh
oh my
God
[Music]
brutal he
don't
that's I'm sorry
[Music]
okay what about uh that one up
there this looks very familiar doesn't
it was this
one this one
mhm oh only
one somewh by the wall seems to have
been
activated people
people oh that is how you get the mile I
think
[Music]
h no I did that that that was my
decision to do
that so I mean it's late in the game but
I would say
finally
huahua got a little bit
of
scanny strategy tactics in her brain
now I mean it wasn't hard to get yes
though of course anyway artifact
y I am
here choso ice temple once again you
need a plasma beam here uh at the top of
this room resides a chos statue it h
it's handheld in a perf ball first the
ice the Nestle into the s's hands in
your Mo ball this will cause an opening
the real cell
okay oh
[Music]
what I think I didn't understand the
task what
[Music]
higher HP statue oh not this one yeah
that was another one even higher
right okay
okay it was an attempt
H the statues are pretty I don't mind
them think it's good they have so many
more bird statues would do the same for
kfp chicken statues all over the world
M drinking water Min water again today
trying to be
healthy I'm so
healthy pick me up pick me
up oh Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy feed me
too mommy present thank you
[Music]
two more I yo
yo yo yo yo yo thank you
Mommy sorry
[Music]
Mommy Le you need to go back for the
pirate
base pirate base
P base P
basey what do you mean I
understand what is the next
room go the control center you go
through the dark areas no no
no
no no no no
no no okay now I will be not so scared
anymore no which room is that we did the
chos ice temple we no maybe control
tower control
[Music]
tower this
one xray makes it easier to see in
oh yeah maybe it
does cuz the other one was pretty like
fuzzy over
time
um can I go for the ruins entryway
um Maybe not maybe I'll go the other way
this
way I'm back hi welcome
[Music]
back
sorry already got the missile expansions
here this swim at
least thanks Uncle
Stone that's your favorite
thing oh yeah we they already told me
yesterday about her switching the
fingers just your favorite thing because
of the finger
detail I don't like the visor to begin
with
[Music]
oh peekaboo look at
you darkness my old
friend do you
also react the same
way to fire no no this one disappears
differently just
[Music]
normally I can flame for whatever thing
ooh I don't
[Music]
know no need to
Overkill ah I haven't seen you in a
while
[Laughter]
either another
one oh oh one
charged uh
hit kills them
instantly
noise what cool back then because they
weren't publicized thousand web articles
oh yeah yeah yeah times were different
back then weren't
they yeah I feel like we talked about
this before but
yeah you don't get spoilered so easily
back then and you didn't you weren't
able to look up everything so easily
back then
back then buying like a physical copy of
like a full game walk through was still
a
[Music]
thing they would sell those do they sell
sell
those yeah loading game
facts I did that to for Tales of
Symphonia not so much though cuz most of
the time my brother was playing they
still
do a little bit but not very often huu
hu what
what did I go in a circle no I just went
back because I came from what or did I
go in a
circle I lost track oh
don't I want to go this
way took a small look how did that
happen I went for the wrong door here
probably
no no no you know what's going to happen
you know
exactly
oh wait
what I remember this like really really
slightly is this something I can like
activate now that I couldn't before
no
okay huh
what
what there's something here right that I
am not seeing because blind
Joel no
empty wasn't there like this room
Ah that's that's the
[Music]
room that's the room I was thinking
of s looks like I could blow it
[Music]
up I'm still bouncing
am I on the ride track now
yeah all right don't mess it
up cute no you
cute you cute oh my they get Miss
too for some reason I thought they only
gave
help thanks for the
[Music]
missiles more more more more more
more
power almost missed that they fill up
everything I guess huh
[Music]
uh
ah you know how to dodge unlike your
friends amazing
incredible must be one of the smarter
ones
a this room we had a lot of fun in this
room as well didn't
we uh this room right control tower so
purple door up to my
left here do I have to do this stupid
thing
[Music]
again
nah nah
[Music]
ah maybe
yes ah there's ball
tracks does it can I just use this
one I don't know speed dou
[Music]
shortcut yeah wow y
oh
here guess we didn't have spider ball
yet last time we came here oh no h it's
spooky
time oh
wait not any
ah I can still I can still see
oh we are scared don't worry Mommy's
going to protect you kih mommy going to
protect
you that's not being faster yeah it's
all right
Okie doie and now purple door I
can't I save things so weirdly recently
on
purpose
purposefully in shitty English
[Applause]
do not touch me or my cute chicken Sons
and Daughters ever
again language called switching no no
no it's on compose thanks for the
membership than
[Music]
welcome you like my esms thank
you thank
you that makes me feel special
oh I feel like for
me someone is too ESL like some certain
certain ways of speaking I don't
really like listening to and others are
nice to listen to so I'm
glad I'm glad I'm maybe the one that's
nicer to listen
to
let something that
way I mean just because it's easier to
understand at listen to anyone of course
but some are just I know a bit more
difficult to understand
so can barely tell your
ESL thank you English is magnificent
just quirky at times that's
fine sounds good to me all right we have
to go
up
so to my left no how
do I have to jump up
here that's
the shortest way which is to
my oh where basically where I'm looking
at no no yeah yeah
yeah up here ah up there
no I get there I
[Music]
love is that is that
something I don't know what that is use
heat I know I need to go
there wait oh no that was just I think
there was like a monster in there
before beat me up Scotty oh
hang I will just ignore them
now for the sake of my sanity and
everybody's time
schedule purple purple y was it the red
Place yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah is it is it
dead
explosion what am I what is
that what is that eyes is it grass on
the ground
it must have been like that red grass
Stu these [\h__\h] visors I don't see
[\h__\h] what is this ah now the door is
[Music]
unlocked ah if it isn't the
observatory we need to get much higher
egg
nay
yeah they're basically invisible of XR
which makes sense cuz they're like you
know ghosty enemies should I
[Music]
safe oh okay did I forget I forgot to
bring my glass oh well maybe I'll fill
the bottle with
water who wants to fight me
it's already quiet
guys
oh that actually looks pretty cool when
it's completely
dark oh all righty I have to go
up great great
why is it going doky doie does the Earth
have a
pulse or is that
me thinking up
guys a my dad
this room no wait wrong no yeah yes yes
safe station forgot we were going
here doie doie how many artifacts uh I'm
missing one or
two and now the other
[Music]
side do not
fall okay well
W hunting almost over yeah it
is I love it
h where am I what where am
I control
tower elevator
huh I was confused because it didn't
show on the map as an e was like a
different kind of
elevator ah you guys I'm so happy to say
you again remember me you
nightmare kind of thing to
say oh
oh more more more
more wait I can see
here
artifact wait let me
read control this one's a little easy to
miss if you're not sure exactly what to
do first of all head to the control
tower the exterior room with the
research based INF fandr drifts take out
the flying p Pirates and jump onto the
East Tower
wait it's the things that I already like
saw
before destroy a stack of crates of v
and you'll see a window covered
y
y I discovered this like a million years
ago and I was like what to do with this
and you guys said oh this is important
later [\h__\h]
[Music]
wait a
know use a plasma beam here fire a
missile through the window into the base
of the tower
[Music]
Beyond a
missile through the window into the base
of the tower
Beyond oh I can
enter ball
time my true form my final form
[Music]
destruction of
property oh one more last one
is in the storage cave simple looking
[Music]
one it's only been 4 and a half hours
guys what
mommy
what
[Music]
what how do I get back
oh that's it game over I'm stuck here
forever
oh that's
how why could I go in but not go out
oh I guess it's too too tall ah okay
okay um f
f i feel I need to go in is meeting but
I'll continue
um storage C near top of the circular
fana's Edge room so I still don't know
which one is
that this one
this
one I'm pretty far
uh
uhhuh
okay go go go
go I mean it always looks far but
sometimes it turns out it wasn't that
far after all
ow now this is just getting
[Music]
silly here right or here or here yeah
here and dras in I don't remember what
room that was was that like a boss fight
room in any case we got to
bottom no no no no no
no no no no no no
no and there a oh she
gone I have to okay in this room you
really have to kill these monsters
otherwise the door doesn't open
up this room is hated by all F
Runners op
down to white
door starting to think like a
speedrunner really
do o Funky Music again where am I going
wrong way right this way this way
down
and there's two that seem to lead to the
goal should I take the bottom path or
the top
path maybe one of the doors over here
are closed off
again tunic T pu
work I'll try to on it's hard to see if
I take the bottom one I just have to
drop myself that's kind of
M I'll take the bottom
one oh I'm in water oh I
mom wait I can actually see in here
okay ooh the underwater
path and
fish bloop bloop
bloop this also nice
track what is it about these fishes that
uh upsets my vision so
much strange great oh that was
fast
electricity my oh my oh my
[Music]
platforming what did that one die by
going into the
water I'm here uh but it says near the
top of the circular F's Edge room where
you find an expansion for your power
bomb use the xer visor and you'll notice
the door is hidden behind a vol okay
another I
wall
okay blow up with a power bump
okay uh can I not just melt it
okay um I'll find an expansion up there
too go all the way up I will
try who's shooting me oh
okay
okay after I'm done with the artifacts
I'm going to take a
little idle meeting break so you guys
get one too yesterday I did eight hours
without taking an idle meeting break
kiaha got idle meeting bladder of
Steel incredible
right skills in life that you don't need
but they will come in handy at certain
times bladder of a Titan
[Music]
what my jump button didn't
work my jump button didn't I
SAR why would I not press the jump
button there
huh I need a new joycon time to buy that
tears of the Kingdom fancy new
controller right I was interested in
that one anyway like also like
my this one oh well that was actually
doing pretty well but that's uh uh uh
what do you call that pad
d-pad also gets stuck
sometimes I don't know if there's some
bread
crumbs in there or
what if it just needs to be
oiled but you
know violence is not
always the solution you want
yeah I'm using the Pro Controller that's
what I
mean yeah but they have a new Pro
Controller for tears of the
kingdom it looks pretty nice I like
it gamer girl controller G what why is
it gamer oh cuz game girl bath water and
all
that
[Music]
sure near the top they said not at the
top where is my
expansion where's my expans
[Music]
maybe
there
x-ray what am I supposed to
see I say
anything if you were standing on the
artifact room okay
[Music]
thank you for helping me
out oh there it is the power B expansion
[Music]
and now here I use the
X-ray
what
what notice that the door is hidden
behind the vulnerable icy
one I see I
see not here right am I done here
[Music]
oh go
okay don't roll too
much maybe over
there the right
[Music]
oh no I'll go I'll go check every
platform
[Applause]
again it must be
like even this one or that one
what
the and then one of
those that's icy how's that not
icy getting closer a d maybe
no
here is it the floor what an IC see wall
I feel like it should be this
floor behind
me
well what was it
plasma
beam never getting the last artifact
next I now I see
it was that
there was that there before I was
looking around how did how did I how did
how did I not what I was looking around
[Music]
and I would watch the VOD I will check
the VOD and we will
see maybe I only St because first I melt
to this or
so and then no way that was there before
no
way don't say I look fast no way I did
no no no no
no
[Music]
impossible okay
yay s we got them
all wow you saw a frame of it I mean if
I didn't see it that means that you guys
didn't see it you only knew where it was
because you know where it
is yep true true all right it is Idle
meeting break time and then we will kill
two more bosses and finish this game
easily in under 8 hours B
unless it takes me for some reason 10
hours to kill two
bosses all right I me in time BRB I'll
bring my glass too
L I'm
BL
I'm
I'm I'm
[Music]
I'm
BL
[Music]
I gave some pets to Smoothie because she
was being really cute she was sleeping
and when she heard me she went
like and immediately jumped off of her
sleeping sofa on the ground fell on the
ground purposefully
and then stretch and roll and offer me
her belly for really warm belly
rubs so cute so
cute everybody tap back Kaa back tap
back into the stream and say hello to
you WWA are you all back check
attendance
check Are You Here My Dear lurkers too
are you
back is everybody ready to move on with
me hello hello tea in hand
hi nice
tea hello
hello study lurking oh what are you
studying acknowledging W thank you we're
back with
chat was saying there is an energy tank
or is it the last energy
tank please tell me how to get it thanks
for the memberships yay no I like
lurking okay as long as you're here I'm
happy but it's good to know you're
here nice keep final e tank oh
background listening while napping am I
making you so
sleepy tank in the transport access from
thank you okay I will check the
map a wall of ice okay thank you thank
you thank you guys everybody is like so
into
this everybody's so what's the
word what's the
word you want to help us thank you I
already forgot what it was
Transportation room
or what's it
called invested
yeah what was it
called last bles are easier than the
Omega pirate hell yeah I mean some other
people said it's a little bit more
difficult but all
right the room with the
banana shape banana
broom
banana
[Music]
banaana kaha eats the
banana yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
banaana in
pajama okay what banana Where's banana
room there's the banana
room healthy potassium room let's go
grab some
potassium should I go for ah thank you
for making the decision for me I
guess no I I still have the
choice which room I I have to take the
top one I have to take the top one oh no
actually I could take the bottom one
again I'll take the top
one no I'll take the bottom one sorry
that was what I I wanted didn't not say
clearly I'll take the
bottom that's what I
wanted I just
misspoke like I wanted to take the pop
room was was just I was just
[Music]
joking I was going to take the the
bottom one anyway
no way you dodg
it all right all right all right can I
reach this
no maybe mid jump but that's kind of
dangerous
[Music]
J I can't believe it it
worked oh for another
swim ice cold swim
nice
nice oh yeah somebody on Twitter was
like wondering oh did you write it down
in English for us and I'm like no no for
the studying Korean when the teacher
came for the first time she asked me if
it's okay if she teaches me in like
English to
Korean because she actually speaks like
decent German but she said English is
easier for her and I said no problem I'm
fluent so she teaches me from English to
uh Korean which I want some more credit
for that because English and Korean both
is not
my my first
language why that jumped down they're
not worth
it that explains why the notes are
English yeah I've been writing down
everything in English too because when
we're already in that language actually
like I often write my notes down you
know my tangent notes in English as well
just because my
brain a lot of the time it just defaults
to English which is like I don't know
why not trying to
be super cool or something but I
am can't help it
I guess I can make that jump oh I
can
okay yeah and I haven't really
had any issues like understanding it
properly the contents to
learn no more one you no more than one
Lang going to using one or the other for
different
[Music]
things I know some
things seems like I feel a bit more
comfortable uh using English
for
interestingly where am I going
wait wait wrong wrong wrong wrong re
don't worry I
noticed that is not the banana
room banana room is up up higher oh you
guys are back
[Music]
again nice
okay uh so even
higher oh sure
[Music]
really that
jump oh
no ah I got it I got it I have it under
control thank you
[Music]
the last
one
Yahoo and
now where is the book
can't believe we we hun 100% at the
energy tanks
damn nice
one nice one
really bring me the bus return to your
ship how M more Caverns elevator is like
right there with that be a close
one yeah
why did I do
that let's go kill bus
wo I will tweet actually about
[Music]
that on my way to kill the last two
bosses now
it's
time
okay
M I'm not a I'm not several
crows I am just one single phoenix bird
let me save over there
do you feel motivated
yes feeling pretty good right now I
think I'll feel even better if I eat the
chocolate Bist purple of course purple
what else would it
be just
one just
[Music]
one my free crows in a trench code
confirmed I will never know how to
pronounce that word man
[Music]
never um
um what [\h__\h] what am I
doing uh where are we going next this
one no that's SP
ones this
one Talon Overworld I think
[Music]
the enemies are also like
e is it all already goodbye kiaha time
[Music]
no oh no don't finish the game play more
play more of us
[Music]
I refuse no don't want
to this chocolate is
incredible Al I wouldn't say I really
rush for the game maybe today A little
but not even even today I feel like I
was just determined but I wouldn't say I
was
rushing and me not scanning every little
thing is not me rushing it's just me not
wanting to scan every little
thing I'm
sorry oh yeah chocolate bu
you're meant to Rush the game keeps
track of you faster
times so what the hell do I get out of
it for being fast I think only a
speedrun that really get something out
of
it is tyly expensive now that the Wii
was yeah yeah yeah well
I decided against getting it before this
store
closed better ending ah
oh wait it's not only about 100 pering
it's also about how fast you
were
what it's not time best in this game all
right there you go it's only
on aut were based on speed
mommy I'm
home
dark always that
part always confused
[Music]
me hello darkness my old
friend h
[Music]
what you tweeted a screenshot about that
corner what
corner dark oh oh yeah yeah I saw that I
saw
that it's all right
though it's just a thing I have to deal
with
[Music]
fine you can't do
that wait what where am I going
what
um is this where I was
Play No I want to go to the other
side actually a that's fine there is a
bridge wait this one's also
ah this one definitely grew back you
can't fool me
now that wasn't there before what is
that can't
see what is
that I'm more more
okay are we home
yet Ma
[Music]
hello okay and
now what do we do
now do I go to that artifact Temple
thingy we made it yeah it's still
raining is it always raining here so
sad s for rain now to the temple okay
oh thanks game yeah now I actually got
the artifact so I'll go to you don't
worry let just
check uh turn around
right game game and its
impatience
grows
steadily Ste
[Music]
dad
boy daddy boy
[Music]
does someone know this song does nobody
know this
[Music]
song Enough
they were all automatically placed there
anyway why did why did she want me to go
back there in between in the middle of
me still collecting
them oh my God most people don't know or
everybody doesn't
know
wow
Zoomers oh hello I wasn't mentally
prepared is it happening here are we
doing this here or you picking me up and
you're bringing me somewhere my Uber
Dragon
huh why do you have such a human name
anyway
rley no what the
[\h__\h] hey fix it you have to fix what you
[Music]
destroyed de
scan scan
okay I'm scan go ah let me scan you you
little
[\h__\h] wait meta rley Genetically
Enhanced rley metal form re born and
evolved through pirate technology meta
rley is a fome enforcer his armored
height is extremely resilient safe for
the chest
which has finner plating the Pirates
have fused a number of potent weapons to
the creature including a multi missile
system a kinetic breath weapon oh dear
what does that mean a meon bomb launcher
great and an ultra thermal flame strike
projector
cool shoot the
chest meta rley is also a formidable
melee competent making any sort of
engagement a risky
proposition well okay is there a
a recommended weapon or should I just
use the red
one
w
Qui he's p
stuff he's go getting he's he's gone
getting some more
upgrades oh he's cleaning up the area so
we can fight
better win
[Music]
win he B I brought all the energy tags
and I got 120 missiles I haven't used a
single one of
them Al I haven't taken damage so far I
think CA no maybe a little
bit oh okay now I have wow that does a
lot of damage half of my
health oh
oh oh you're coming down here now all
right face me face me it's
person he's out of here again that was a
short live
visit he's
cute oh he's really short
tempered but I think I'm rocking it so
far he's half
down nice music
it's coming it's
coming nice DOD so once for
that I thought it was already behind
me still got all my energy
tanks you
suck you
suuck you weak
you don't even have any Dragon Friends
where's your fire spit some fire at me
eh Spyro is better than you fire is a
better Dragon than
you and
cuter come on don't waste my
time wasting my time you're about to
break
through emotional damage
M absolutely rocking
it it's my
confidence the confidence that I have
right now
my left uh finger is really starting to
hurt though just getting a cramp
from the
[Music]
focusing someone
dead he never gets me with the first
one wo Ridley has learned
Dodge why is he so easy oh
oh he's he's down here for real his
wings are broken oh
no it doesn't I don't think it's doing
damage did I scan
again it's the same
[Music]
stuff no oh now it's
working showing me his C but he's so br
[Music]
huh now he's immune again there's
certain times where he's just is he
looking for
me what why are you so cute I take it
back you're just as cute as spy oh no
he's playing with me maybe he wasn't
like looking for
me I don't know
what are you
doing what are you
doing oh I keep on dodging
it no I didn't dodge
it there A lot of times where he doesn't
take damage
is there a weak point
on oh wait
no couldn't charge
it oh that's
fun do the stom the stom we do the rley
rley Stomp rley
finally he's getting a little bit
challenging though but only because he's
got so many immunity
Windows
otherwise weak
jump into
help stop repeating
that lame
a
[Music]
yo
yo what and he's totally fine
but what a little piece of
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh repeating the same
move oh
am I doing something wrong I'm I'm
aiming for when he has his mouth open
but besides
that in this space like it's really hard
to get in
damage [\h__\h]
sorry I was looking at a comment trying
to get advice
yeah oh
oh oh [\h__\h] why is he taking no
[Music]
damage like barely
any I see when I do damage so but like
damn even when I do damage I do so
little damage now in this phase
sters when
I can I use wait super missiles are the
yellow ones though
right I switch that but even that will
be difficult to get the timing even more
I think
oh what perfect timing I I was just like
trying but now I didn't get his heart
so no no no ah wait Fu I'm going to lose
no you're was so easy
no up
there that's not fair
no
no [\h__\h] no
no no
w
I'm so
tense I'm so
tense you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
way what the
[\h__\h] of course you get overconfident
with that if until that last point where
it's he seemingly has only 10% of Health
left until that point it's like he takes
5,000% more damage then until that point
where he suddenly is like oh I'm immune
against everything now and I will only
open my mouth every once in a little
while and even then when you do hit me
with the most powerful attacks that you
you can possibly pull out even then I
will only take like the smallest amount
of damage ever incredible incredible
what a [\h__\h] rigged
game you little [\h__\h] rly you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] that is just not
fair that is why am I silver now wasn't
I darker before no you little [\h__\h] no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
no that little
sh
what I am smiling though while saying
all of these things I am tilted but I am
smiling am I going the right
way what the [\h__\h] is the matter with uh
face two huh or face three it's not like
face
500 don't say don't say that guys how
can you not get cocky when up until that
point is so easy until the last like
five
percent
H how can you not get cocky he's
absolutely teasing
you no I know that he only has like
certain time Windows which are by the
way way too little where he gets damaged
but I'm I'm saying that even when I hit
him suddenly he takes so much less
damage than he did before that's what
I'm saying you get what I'm saying
and of course I must fail
again so
close
to finishing him
off every first my Prime play his first
time fighting it
right smart giving you that false sense
of security for
real all right
well can we just skip all of the forl
really
H skip it it's really
necessary that's a poser such a
flexer hurry up can I skip the scene
[Applause]
nothing
[Music]
second time to charm guys cross pleas
oh oh yeah oh yeah Dr something
[Music]
there oh it's nice in the beginning the
pillar still like Drop upu
but later on there will be no
more come on come on come on
W
camera oh
wow
oh he hit me
good come on Ry readle whatever your
name
is my name my name
stop playing
[Music]
G
C my name my name
got a massage from my
fingers rley
C oo Health back up one last
time oh my God oh my God oh my God I
think that was the last pillar there's
no more no wait there's one more
[Music]
there I want to go into this little game
replay afterwards with as much HP as
possible so far we're looking
good okay is are we playing our game no
not yet not
quite still has to burn his
wings yeah I'm I'm always trying to like
Dodge
everything much as I can wait oh no
we're already playing the game no [\h__\h]
that one I always do
wrong so should I switch this
[Music]
now that is really difficult because
oh um there's not much time to recharge
but right before he does that he opens
his mouth for a little bit and I feel
like maybe that's the moment to do
it oh wait if I just stand still I go
under the ler
okay when he opens his mouth for that it
doesn't work I think unless I'm just
wrong with
positions come on take some
damage yo okay okay okay easy I still
got full
HP o and yeah you you stand
still no okay never mind what
it trying to
dodge yeah no in this in this position
cuz I definitely hit him now when he has
his mouth open
maybe just don't do anything
all yeah it's easier to dodge when I
don't do
anything I could give up on trying to
hit him in this
timing it's
impossible ah he does that
ride ride after I don't
know
[\h__\h] me out
Punk it Tri to
St
stuck and he's
still barely barely
keep rapid
[Music]
firing I only have 40 missiles left I
don't want to waste my plasma now cuz
that one eats it up really way too
fast sure what if I run out I'm kind of
[\h__\h] why don't you switch it when I
tell you to switch
it Miss low Miss slow I don't know if
any of that
works [\h__\h] that
[Music]
the red
one somehow I connect
a red with plasma or a plasma with red
I don't think I can make it this time
either oh [\h__\h]
you I'm not going to make it because
he's such a piece of [\h__\h]
[Music]
give me a [\h__\h] break
I saw it coming though
oh
lucky I didn't
jump oh
it earlier is
good a that's going to be the end of
me oh [\h__\h]
thought
[\h__\h] w
I thre in a missile for
fun that was
important oh my hands hurt so
much so
tense what do you want why do you look
so friendly
now CH the
ghost why you so nice
now thanking
me m Mia what is
that does it heal me or does it kill
me does it support like bring me to the
next place I probably shouldn't go right
I should saay first and heal
yeah I'm just going to completely ignore
that thank you
yeah I was thinking so too it looks like
it brings me to the last last boss but
this was just the last boss this is
like save files
final PSD final final P final final
final Final
P final final Final imagine dying here
do
PSD oh yeah wait even if I say if it
doesn't try bring me back my missiles
huh it's too late that but he's weak
against Ice Beam nah no way no way you
telling me that
now n nah she reloads ammo did it
really oh okay the ship does but other
save points don't is that how it is
ah well then wonderful
okay so does the portal bring me
straight to a boss or are we still going
to do like some Metroid Vania
Shenanigans no for small
area little bit more of
Metroid
no he it's only been 5 and a half hours
so how much more can it be from now on
for real if you have the answer tell
[Music]
me 1 hour 10 minutes it's not going to
be 10 minutes not much wow wow yesterday
we some people were still doubting that
I could make it in one
stream never doubt kiala ever
again I was ready for like an 8 Hour
stream then if not nine even
sorry I doubted
you the guide SP up the process well if
it wouldn't have been a guide you guys
would have told me but it was good to
have it like visually and you know in a
timely not so delayed
manner but I love it when you guys help
me too though you
know impact
crater where is this
safe Point here for maybe the only
one people people don't be scared wa
it's all going to be easy but does he I
fight him again don't
I he's
either just as difficult what the [\h__\h]
is this or I
kill or are even more difficult
save
okay the budget clearly ran
out that makes you think
doad what is this floor
I don't trust
it limited data on unknown material
available material is highly
radioactive
radioactive you will take damage from
direct
contact phenic qualiity is at least 86%
great than phasin unshielded BS below
index level P will suffer fatality
within moment
so no
T but
how
jum oh wait supposed to be my
friends no touy under any circumstances
right
okay
no
no sit
no no
and
go what do you mean I spend endlessly
spawn how can I ignore them I can't
ignore
them okay
uh
what I can't them they're going to like
suck on me
this look like to
teeth anyway I'll just try my best to
platform shut
up maybe he's showing me where to go
actually maybe he
friend yeah
well now he's kind of like a
companion sometimes he just he means
well he just sometimes Bonks against me
because he's kind of blind and he's just
following my
scent but he means well
right Next Level platforming all right
all right all right
of course I'm going to fall down when I
become bald there but what choice do I
have but to become
ball oh my
God oh my God I was giving you a chance
to be friends with me
don't just Glo
me oh no there's
two they're
multiplying little
[\h__\h] no no no no
no how can I ignore them how can I I'm
trying to ignore them this ignoring
strategy guys it doesn't work
okay is this how you treat all things
that are annoying to
you fing
out this this is it this is why
absolutely
Los do I spawn more only when they're
all dead or do they
um even
continuously great great great great
great great
[Music]
sorry I need to go to my happy place
don't you even think about it don't you
[Applause]
I'm going to rage quit this [\h__\h]
game oh
[Music]
now you tell me to not ignored him sure
[Laughter]
no I just restarted because of my
HP okay you don't it's okay you don't
have to tell me about the Power Bomb but
I'm
aware but I thought I should keep one
alive and that's what I was
doing cuz you want say keep one alive
otherwise it spawns
more or so
[Music]
all right next time they grab me my
power bomb the [\h__\h] out of them problem
is I only have
four it's got to got to work
smoothly oh [\h__\h] is there like a safe
point though before the boss or do I
just have
to hope
for as
much no no no no no Health as
possible no
not
great what do you want H if you glump me
glump me somewhere where I can safely
destroy
you want to do it
those are like the most annoying
things I've
ever
witness in my whole life of
streaming ever
ever right here safe what do you mean is
safe do I have come up this
High what that's the door to
save [\h__\h] off [\h__\h] [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up [\h__\h]
up [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up [\h__\h] there's
another one no that's missile
oh missile replenisher oh
[Music]
okay so that was not the door I should
aim for what the [\h__\h] I need to go even
higher to this red
door wait
H go left
left thank you
thank you thank
you hi want to you want to do
it worth it I would say
because what if I fall
now what which way I can't see I'm blind
I'm blind I'm
blind I'm blind I'm blind I'm blind I'm
blind right there's already one coming
again you mean r oh
there
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] come
here that was my last one
maybe
okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
calm everything
calm we want to go in with a I mean even
there's no way I'm going to like first
try
him
right so I'll have to do this fun stuff
again as well
oh wait I still have threee missile uh
super
bombs
what great great great
I
am I
am not
winning thank you camera for
nothing thank you why can you change the
camera when you're like this but why not
as a ball
what do I do here how do I get up
there I try jumping maybe a little bit
further
back I did the bumb
jump I did it
though don't let it go just
go come
is that it that's it he's becoming a
butterfly beautiful
butterly remember the scan but I'll take
damage while doing that can't you just
tell
me e that doesn't look like Ridley
anymore use all
[Music]
beams too much info
you can just jump
in are we just like running away
now
what I want to fail I don't want to do
this stupid puff
again the apparation known as Meed
Prime is the source of phasin you are
the source of phasin we're not fighting
rightly anymore
really making it immensely powerful a
genetic flaw makes it susceptible to
certain weapons for brief
periods oh so cuz you're purple now I
was susceptible to purple
now only Tad is a TR is truly rable
other attacks are a
nuisance offensively menro Prime has
number of natural and mechanical weapons
at at disposal of course it
does basically
that the whole game for
this these include Ultra frigid breath
multi missile snare beams and Par
particle wave projectors it's massive
strength and Barb carice car car make it
lethal inm combat recommend maximum fire
power
when engaging this
enemy you could have told me the same
thing guys why do you keep on making me
scan these things you could have just
told me shoot purple when purple and so
on shoot Lots until then well a bread
coat there we go that's
exactly what what that the only thing I
doesn't tell you is that when it charges
go panic ball into a tunnel in the floor
okay I think I will
fail but
well I mean that's just not a brief
period is that where is that hole that
you talked
about I can currently see nothing going
to change color now huh there no color
okay I see yellow
that's cool because I can use my super
special weapons okay it's going into a
hole is this where it charges but I
thought I was going in the hole oh wait
we just follow it okay it's maybe not
charging
time what's color
next what oh White
okay the the missile thing with the
white uh one I don't think it's really
doing me any
favors oh oh what is that did I step on
something it spit
out stop ah is this all your meem of
charging
[\h__\h]
out there okay okay okay ooh I don't
know if I can already now
no no no
no
no oh
no where the
colorless okay I now I get it
nice
nice is that flying
Stu follow follow follow let's go
we crazy for following this
thing okay how am I doing so far do I
have a
chance when it goes colorless after I
stunned it that's when it does the
charging thing huh you get little do I
understand fly up with extra health I
didn't even give me time to pick it up
though oh just following me I'm shaking
guys have to shoot the flying bits to
get health
oh just shooting not sucking it in like
normally
Che destroy them first bring them down
what what what bring him
down destroy them they drop them oh they
drop they drop help okay oh oh I'm going
to
fail oh what green what no I don't want
to no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no what how do I how do I how do I
what what is that what how do I how do I
not make him do
that I didn't I don't think I took
damage as long as okay um okay as long
as he does doesn't eat me okay okay okay
he turned
red no purle
what is that what is
that
well yay we did
it oh wait I'm I'm standing on something
that hurts
oh y I did it right
again wait how how how how how to I I
can't get out I can't get
out how do I get out how do I get up b b
no I can't turn into
okay can I help thank you no I didn't
get
it can I can I have a place
get oh well I don't need it I don't need
it I don't need it
I oh my God I'm doing good I
think full is a full e tank did I oh did
I get it
[Applause]
okay at least this one gives Health man
like sometimes oh
nice oh wait there more
[Applause]
oh that's
missiles what the [\h__\h] just
happened oh wait what red sorry sorry
guys yes I am officially call
blind or just stret
out what I forgot how to beat a
ball what what
no no no no no can you not no I don't
know he TWiT on every time I I hit
him is this friend full
the calm Cal
those were bombs I thought those were
our
[Music]
friends please don't change
[Applause]
color that again I remember that
move a
let's
go they still following
me how do I have to kill the bumps
first before they kill
me I think maybe it's still manageable
but I don't want to underestimate this
sucker like I did with the with
rley what is this game that you playing
[Music]
I don't know which button it is I keep
on forgetting about I guess as long as I
don't get stucked
in what purple
missile he's almost
dead oh why why why why why
why are you going to stay with that
oh oh my S
down my S no no no don't I don't see my
help I'm doing it does he have a second
space like a second Health but why did
I why did
I why did I do
again what's happening
kill
him oh he's blocking my missiles I
thought it was
working is that is that it
no why is music Still intimidating
no there's
more
no you're not sure if I'm going to first
try it
now his face is
easy
no
no I don't want to lose now tell me how
to do it
[Music]
those shits after all we've been through
you tell me to
scan you know you know
that HP is a very
very very important resource right now
so might speak so much
there you will have to stand on FAS on
some point well FAS doesn't hurt me
anymore does
it he only has thank you he only has one
attack a ground slam with energy you can
jump over okay so like what we've seen
before with others when he spawns met
no Detroits power bombs them to damage
him you have to St and in the phas and
pools he makes and shoot
[Music]
him okay I mean that sounds simple
enough depending on how long he wants me
to do all of
that you need to use phas and beam phas
and beam what is that it will drop
puddles of phasin I'm shaking from time
to time at times it will become
invisible to your comb advisor so you'll
need to occasionally switch to per at X
Y oh sometimes I see it sometimes I
don't oh God I'm
shaking see it or see the phasin on the
ground
being what I get a ph and
beam pool beam can also kill other
Metroid
oh what you get when standing in
fing oh I'm
shaking I will mess it up I
fail Andoid Atomic sneez a standing
group start
blasting
okay when he Snee I do jump
when then I stay in group and I
bloop oh I'll I'll
Panic okay now now he know
what what was that the St how do I
[Music]
that
help please no please give me
down what is that
[Music]
oh wait there's a
goop holy goop where is he though ah now
I have to look for him
I will 100% fail
this I missed
it I missed it
[Music]
unbelievable I am not ready to do this a
second time
[Music]
can I look no
no is this is this
[Music]
happing uh
yeah he's so
scary he's making new go
no he's making no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no what do I focus on should I take
care of the metroids
first
yes okay
[Music]
a hor movie
good
huh
I I'm going to cry I don't see him I
don't see him
[Music]
did I see
something no I a
little I'm not going to I'm this is the
second time I'm
done does it work on them too I'm not
going to I'm not going to do this
another time I'm sorry guys I'm not I
don't know I'm not
know I'm not doing this another
time no of course
K panic
maybe privately but no not
today I'm still trying though does it
work on them
too does
the big bomb work on those minions too
yeah I'm out no
more
oh I know I can shoot these
ones oh but I need to focus on killing
him he just made a
puddle it was prob be them
[Music]
[Applause]
too
no no
no
no I was trying to switch if you did
maybe you hurt cuz my control on my
d-pad is [\h__\h] loud I was trying to
switch I don't know why it didn't
work
no no no
no most frustrating [\h__\h] in my
life I don't want I don't want I don't
don't
want it's not even the time issue it's
just
[Music]
a I don't want
I don't have faith don't have faith in
me what if I have to disappoint
you I don't want to do this again
[Music]
so annoying
m
[Music]
smoothie
don't be so
cute why am so
s
SMY
poofy h
they just go
[Music]
away just go
away I can't jump safely if feel like
there all the
time oh my god do they spawn endlessly
oh my worst [\h__\h]
nightmare just back
again
I long time no
see where are we going to do the thing
huh you and
me here want to do it
here
nice the missile room is kind of useless
for me to go to isn't it unless I guess
does it look
somehow for the red super chat goodbye
missed
[Music]
it oh my God
going back should I I no look at my
health holy
[\h__\h] and they like no they don't even
give me
anything greedy little bastards
no I'm still in the beginning so I'll go
back for health
because every every single Health
counts what was I
saying
[Music]
man man
this is not like that time
where um I got really really I tilted
but like frustrated in Zelda game that
is
different because there I was under time
pressure you little
[\h__\h] now I am here
so much earlier than I
expected but the game is
Just genuinely frustrating
me
possibly
more than any other game I have ever
played
[Music]
really going to make it anyway I'm going
to waste another bomb on you
no no I will
not
bye byebye bye
More Than Sunshine yeah I think so More
Than
Sunshine at least sunshine I feel
like you know there's like a generally
more happy vibe in that game that kind
of projects onto the player I would
say that's what I was just talking about
Skyward Sword final plus it's a
different story cuzz I only got that
frustrated about it because of the time
pressure that
really made me drop all my spaghetti
you have cramps in your toes that's nice
I have cramps in my fingers we have
cramps
together we United in CRS
how does this start work
again oh I just follow
right then you do that again don't you
or are we staying here
I oh than no we switching location one
more time I remember that
how many times more am I going to do
that go we going now okay we're going
now we're going
[Applause]
now this is our home
ow
oh
an oh
sorry I'm so quiet now
oh what oh going down one more
[Music]
time what
goodby ah what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
that was cheap right thank you right
yeah
me hey that's mean that's really mean
what the
[\h__\h] oh
such a panic ball moment
[Applause]
oh oh
help
[Applause]
a
[Music]
but they still purple but there's still
purple he's purple again
no no no
no sorry I'm
stupid he gets
really rough at the end
oh wow the missiles are gone he took
them with him
okay well I mean I have maybe what one
or two more health bars than before
maybe not even I don't even
know do
[Music]
I knowledge
yeah oh no him I mean like jumping over
his like thingies is pretty simple it's
pretty
easy let the camera
switching when I'm like not sure am I
not seeing him because I have the wrong
camera or because I'm on the
[Music]
wrong like am I just not looking at him
yeah but
ow uh
okay but at least I'm not missing the
first chance
here first chance is kind of important
because here he still doesn't spawn any
metroids there's no puddle now right
it's already on
[Music]
think okay found him pretty
quickly oh why did I sry panic ball
it's
tradition thank
you ah it looks
different
ah oh
so what did that charge missiles and
bomb super
bomb that's it's
too
okay
um okay okay okay okay okay okay
thank you thank you so much you're so
nice right now for giving me all those
little healing
thingies I don't care about the Miss
though can you give me Health only
please wow
y
okay did I pick up the heal
no actually now the normal vision is
even more confusing to me I got useed to
the other
one and he's really got this pattern now
I I got to figure it out to oh oh that's
that's a problem um what do I do now cuz
one is a
Metroid one is a Metroid I can't
even hold
be add them
or go for boss I'm shaking so
much this Kill Boss is almost
dead get out of
it
um where where I unfortunately uh do not
see him and this little sucker got me
good
[Applause]
oh it's the
charge I don't see oh
there please be nice please be
nice
ni9 um
what what
no get
out why did you B I didn't even press it
I
SW I think it killed the Met part
otherwise by now it would have
probably done the thing
okay come here please
please I
did I did it guys why does it what
you're not splitting are
you well not bu so good right
now let's fake happy
yay yay
yay no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
resist leaves a really bitter taste in
my mouth though
crate a collapse imminent evacuate
immediately cut scene please not don't
make me do it
now okay we evacu while we re
evacuating thank you guys yeah I only
lost one so it's not so bad I know I
know I know I know faith and savis has
been well rewarded and now a new star
shines in the universe been well
rewarded with what
samarin what future and fate a
waiter what future and fate a
waiter that's how you end the game
asking that
question all right people were confused
in the beginning of the game too
apparently who only played the GameCube
version that there's voice in beginning
yeah and then there's also wish in the
end Apparently that is normally not in
the GameCube
[Music]
version I got 80% of the items that's
pretty good too I know if you if I got
it how many per did I get
in I'm happy with what I
[Music]
got of course I didn't get 100% never
planned on getting the
100% those metroids I feel like I would
be so much happier if it wasn't for
those stupid ass metroids man they
started everything they started all the
[Music]
trouble no Nar in na version Oh that's
interesting why not
maybe h no idea I got at least 70% oh
why no face TR which means you may not
have completed the game 100% yeah I mean
I know that I knew this was going to
happen I can just watch a video on
YouTube if I want to see it thanks for
the pinky how much will be the cutle
from Bounty but so are the bounties are
the artifacts or just that experience
it's like offering someone exposure for
the sake of having them work for me oh
well I pay you but I'll pay you in
exposure they meant to be a pain of
existence in every single game
great s is how hunts bounties for
exposure what for real for real
[Music]
uh fish and M mro which one was that one
the the the the separating one oh yeah
before that they were fine with the ice
beam you know before that they were like
totally fine actually when I figured out
I can use the Ice Beam on them and kill
them quickly with a missile after after
that most of us took more than two tries
beat it wow I'm a pro gamer
what gets paid by the
Federation Other M confirms that the
riters don't know what a bounty hunter
is
what this was technically not an
endurance room I wouldn't say so I felt
like I was enduring quite a lot of
[\h__\h] I was definitely enduring maybe not
time but yeah other
stuff well well well
I was 12 oh then of course it will take
you more tries
Manan I'm sorry guys I got so heated but
damn you must understand you saw how
cheap some of that stuff
was you must
understand I don't play these kind of
games
[Music]
often oh yeah I also did not play on
easy I played on normal I know that
doesn't sound so impressive but thanks
for bringing it
up I played on normal weird flex but
okay that's right I could have gone the
easy route but I suffered for this game
in normal as like a first time
player my first Metroid
game thank you
if you would put so close to hand I
would have been disappointed that's what
I thought too that you guys would be
disappointed and then the archive would
have an even more bitter aftertaste so I
can't do that so I I try thanks guys man
thank
you I died on meta Ridley 20 times and
then quit yo I 100% get you but you were
probably also much younger weren't you
so much on heart for last boss it was so
frustrating oh I can imagine thanks
Kevin thanks
everybody is there a lot of dump scares
in the recent Metroid game oh no oh
no as one that played many many times
that was a fantastic run don't say
that don't be so nice what is that
profile picture though that's
terrifying ah I would say like there
were some very frustrating heated
moments today with bosses but besides
that I did a marvelous job
okay in the
last part
yesterday and
today and even before that last
week I was like getting
good it was also getting
[Music]
good the first run for that last boss
was a trial run anyway you always need a
trial run like no one can expect you to
know everything already right
away right both bus it's like a boss
rush and then if you already tried
running the first one then no way that
you can first try the second one when
you're already low on health that much
damn was pretty nice though for him to
throw so many charges at me so
nice thank you Mar
Pippin di like four times of the five
bosses not many people can say
that I don't I don't I don't
know why you not so convinced you're
100% right though thank you I'm just
trying to talk it better into my
head thank you moon dog St for this game
a good time with very limited depths on
this origin difficulty it's pretty damn
good thank you wow Earth you look
different that's SM my ship look like a
beetle where are we going now huh Samos
Samos w
oh the cutest W was out
there heart difficulty unlocked as if
I'm going to play that ooh
71% total time 17
[Music]
hours Master Game
Time 1 and a half and you know I'm a
streamer I tangent in between and all
that so that wasn't too bad
that was uh plus 4
hours and I I I I collected low
stuff plus 4 hours so in the future when
the game time says something just add
like how much percent is that I don't
know you guys got to do the math you
know what I suck at math my first playr
was 23 hours with similar completion oh
yeah well I I I got some I saved some
time today by going through a guide with
artifacts but I feel like maybe a lot of
people do
that oh yeah I'll check out the final
the real ending the 100%
ending losing in game is part of being a
gamer you just have to learn from your
mistakes and progress that's
all thank you guys I'm sorry for being
so salty man I mean that's also just
being a real gamer isn't
it like I
remember whenever I watched my brother
playing
games like often he would like really
get really really angry and scream and I
was
like why why you get so [\h__\h] angry
why just chill it's just a
game and I feel like when I play games
privately I don't rage as much
it's real honestly I I will say it's
mostly just because I'm streaming and as
a streamer you're being put under a lot
of pressure but now I can relate a bit
more like
maybe you
know I I wouldn't really rage privately
cuz then I just put the game down and
then or or I don't
know I might just look up a guide for
things
or I might not play a game that makes me
rage like that in the first
place but you know what this was so
worth it for all the super cute SAS wava
fan art like oh my
God that is so worth it it's like oh my
God thank you guys for the super cute
fan art and Sam SW it's so cute I love
it like what some games for some
reason is this the one that they
mentioned some games for some reason
call for more fan
arts than others it seems here beautiful
this is from The Morbid U that Gastly
weabo on
Twitter yeah and that seems to be I
think that's it that's the one thing you
talked about oh wait what is this that's
also cute some more Samos swaba fan came
in while I was this is it that's the one
from
simpleton some more came in while I was
playing look first Sam
SW headat are chill then B and catch
play with me but I prefer this much more
over the metroids glomping me
that's the
worst thank you
guys I love it I love it this is so
worth it that was so worth it for
getting these cute fan arts man I I
didn't know I would look so good as
[Music]
Sam who did the thumnail oh it's in my
Twitter like
reply but let me tell
you um on Twitter his or her account is
@ fullart art full Heart Like myo art at
full heart art absolute
genius absolute genius so
[Music]
beautiful a lot of Myro games crazy
differences I know that there's also
this like um blue teal blue turquoise
tur light blue it's more like a light
blue huh probably light blue suit
right that one that one's nice too that
one's cute wait is that zus that's for
Metroid Fusion oh yeah that's why you
see that she's like she has like a
blonde ponytail
right and she's really cute
Fusion suit
Salon Fusion
suit no that's not the one I
mean oh I mean it's very similar
though I mean the Zero Suit oh yeah oh
oh cutie
PTI that's
right that's probably the
most fan service one maybe cuz you
actually get to see her face and all
that
[Music]
which isn't it kind of romantic that
that's what we really want to see that's
what we do 100% for in this game what
everybody like suffers for the most just
for the sake of seeing a little glimpse
of her face isn't that so
romantic isn't that so
beautiful
you you little s fans do anything for a
little Glimpse suffer through so much
trauma I couldn't I
couldn't that's why they put her
in Smash
twice oh twice as different characters
or just as with different
outfits is she really in there twice
[Music]
what in the original smash you could see
her without the suit sort of what is
that a
bug now there's two different o cool I
didn't realize that I must have seen it
before but I never really like
registered it in my
brain well anyway to give like my
thoughts uh I started this not knowing
really what I was getting myself
into only that only knew that well it's
kind of
a childhood memory for me
too as I said in the
beginning um I I thought I played a
little bit of the game like there were
Snippets of memories in my brain to for
like having played it as a child turns
out it was really just in that outside
area where you spawn when you begin the
game so that brought me absolutely
no nothing no help at
all oh yeah I just remembered that a
little bit wa was way too small wa wa
was not ready also W probably thought
game was scary and too difficult
H now look at me now little W little
small w w finish this whole
game suffering so much with little small
wow she if she would see me right now
she would probably think I'm like a
super cool gamer like really cool for
being able to withstand all of that bam
she'll be like wow so
[Music]
I don't know why she's speaking
Japanese but you know get the sugus
across has to be
that
so I was honestly uh somewhat of a
pleasant
surprise I didn't think uh there would
be so many like
bright colored I know this is a weird
point to make but bright colored p Pages
because I thought it would be like dark
all the time I was glad because I don't
know I need I need games to be
brighter yeah the Remake was really
remake remaster was really pretty
too
yeah no like something having more
brightness and colors in it um helps me
get through a game I don't know why
yeah a lot of games are just dull and
dark and blah and I don't like that so I
like the ice levels and the sand levels
desert levels and the talent Overworld
and all that that was really nice even
the lava world was after getting a
little bit used to it it felt a bit more
comfortable The Chosen L was interesting
but you will you will never get me to
scan all of the those like you know I'm
sorry to all the big Metroid fans but no
no no no
no the chos L was good though I like the
way it was written and all that but all
the [\h__\h] pirate
lore what on Earth that I would have to
play it in German or so maybe but in
English that was like brain Overlord at
all times pirate lore what the
hell they were teasing me with that too
much for my brain I was trying though so
many fancy words I stumbled over my word
mouth tongue too many times remember to
scan the credits what credits are
already
over what a coincidence hot H
Miami okay
okay I think I didn't have an issue with
that
one yeah but I'm just happy to play
another very nostalgic childhood
GameCube
game getting those crossed off my list
next one is 1080
snowboarding although that's N64 not the
GameCube we go even further
[Laughter]
back yeah
um I want to say I apologize for every
time I got impatient and I'm like where
to go tell me
I'm
sorry but thank you for helping me and
um I appreciate it did you ever play
Starbucks Adventures of course I did of
course yes that's another one of those
did I never really got very far cuz I
was lacking the gaming skills but I
absolutely loved it like what I saw I I
just loved so
much I never understood how to progress
in the game though
I kind of want to revisit that game too
I wish they would bring out a remaster
of that cuz I mean to me when I think
back of
it I
imagine the highest quality furry
Graphics ever like I guess there were
good cut scenes weren't there like high
quality cut scenes that's how the whole
game stayed in my memory but probably it
was very very low on polygons wasn't it
[Music]
I
probably doesn't really look as good as
I think it
does e there's a [\h__\h] fly in my water
how did you get in
there
uh crystal crystal is so
pretty so pretty I was thinking of mini
metroid or like one of the bees or so as
well when I look at it oh my God I'm
brainwashed than cube games be do be
like that but now like nowadays maybe
they are like outdated but back then
they were
beautiful and you could impress a
human's mind with a really low amount of
pixels and polygon so damn I was
really I was really already impressed
that back then it was like a beautiful
world I remember that Overworld I don't
know if it was really an Overworld but
that Overworld was you know that that
main area that you were in was like a
shop and and
some I think there were some
dinosaurs so
pretty scan that water hell
no I like this ending
bgm would be good for Super Chat reading
[Music]
GameCube 60448 with highis oh yeah oh my
God I love game I wonder they're
probably never going to bring out a
remas of that huh or
remake maybe I have to figure out how to
game captur your GameCube
because after playing this
one
damn damn
I am really tempted but people probably
wouldn't watch it much would
they no no not prime two I'm talking
about um Star Fox Adventures Star Fox
that's the one right uh no wait I mean
the one on the
GameCube yeah Starbucks Adventures oh
yeah well I mean it doesn't even look
that bad he looks quite fluffy Crystal
looks pretty good
what that looks like a Metroid dead
enemy on that screenshot where crystal
is running outside in the rain wait this
looks literally like a Metroid game like
the area there too looks like straight
out of
Metroid what the
[Applause]
[\h__\h] help I'm
traumatized
yeah oh yeah that's the
oh
nostalgic oh man maybe one day until how
long is that
game
time uh 13 and a half oh as much as
Metroid Prime but I feel
like difficulty
wise Starbuck Adventure is probably less
difficult no anyone who played it
[Music]
before
Oh what that game was originally not
supposed to be related to Starbuck at
all but at some point they've decided to
slap Starbucks and Co into it what the
hell I could never get past the first ER
me neither but maybe that's just because
we were
young it's very beginner friendly I
think so too more puzzle
based well maybe it's in the
future if I lack a game and I want to
play something nostalgic and old remind
me that I wanted to play Star Fox
Adventures even if I don't make it into
a full play through even though I mean
if it's really just that short then I
could we could uh we
could sacrifice some strings for that
you need to find a copy of the game ooh
I mean I used to have a copy of it but
that is
probably taken by a
void oh sorry I just realized the bgm
has been loud for a long time because I
raised
it
sorry is it okay it's kind of a
banger I don't think we have the
Gamecube or the games
anymore 600 lb and want to have some of
my V2 plushies in the video I'm making
for it is it okay if I use your plushy
in the video what does that have to do
with lifting the 600
lb are you lifting 600 lb of v2o
plushies what I'm lifting 600 lb and
want to have some of my vtuber plushies
in the video I'm making for
it is it okay if I use your plushy I
mean of
course don't quite understand are you
are you lifting 600 lb of
plushies be a lot of plushies I think or
are they just in the background
how much is 600 lb it doesn't really
feel like a flex because I don't
understand how much 600 lb
is what 300
nah how can a human lift 300 kilog that
is probably impossible for
human I can't even lift
birie thank you um M well much
nah proof for didn't
happen Pixar didn't
happen
[Music]
h i was
I you are not noral excuse me but a
person who can lift 300 Kil isn't normal
either in that regard impressive but
isn't normal
deadlift St Adventures game games game
discs are secondhand oh yeah that's
pretty cheap $40 that's like way less
than a normal game for the switch costs
nowadays I guess it's not so much in
[Music]
demand I can deadlift more than 200 2002
no way put on no way pcks or didn't
happen no
humanly
impossible I will not be in charge of
your legs breaking when you take a
picture of
that yeah that's that's the normal price
that's
fine going to get a weird fix
now all according to Kaku you know that
Meme that's going around twittering I've
seen it like a couple times now where
someone is like you know this thing I
absolutely hate it uh BL blah blue I
hate it so much I makes me feel sick
disgusting BL blah blah blah and then
and then something like give me pics no
oh I totally wouldn't want to see pics
if what I don't understand something
like that where they're just like asking
for pictures by saying they hate it so
much try to prove me wrong kind of like
that and then everybody sends those cute
pictures I should do that with there's
no way somebody can live 300 kilogram of
anything really that I
[Music]
know I'm not late on that Meme
train no way that just is really recent
like
now I just saw one
today yeah it's kind of
dumb yes you are
well insulting
well I will not take this
slander okay I guess since we finished
early I could read some super
chats fine I guess you guys are my
little PK Champs
[Music]
thank you guys once again for watching
the play
through sorry for the
suffering um but I did have some
fun today was not so much fun except for
the artifact
hunt the other times were way more
fun but yeah overall it was a decent
good experience
I'm proud of myself for finishing
it that's for
sure and
yeah it's nice to have this in my
checklist of finished and streamed games
I'm very
proud
guys
no now yeah now I made all the Metroid
kfp is really happy that makes me happy
to
I always strive to make every single
person in my fandom
happy with collaborations that you
didn't expect with games that you didn't
expect stuff like that songs that you
didn't
[Music]
expect
yay yeah tomorrow is a collab in case
you guys are leaving now tomorrow is a
collabo not on my channel I will link it
on my Twitter maybe I'll make a
community post I I'll see if I remember
if I
want and uh
[Music]
yeah don't you dare mention Mass Effect
to
[Music]
me all
right what
isn't that from today's stream that I
just went on YouTube main page and I
see isn't that from
today I might be
wrong no that's from yesterday okay okay
you shall be
forgiven the w w okay I said I said I
didn't say WP W today I said glomp glump
today didn't I today was all about
glomping
no no Mass
Effect you know what I will stay on the
[Music]
screen I'll stay
here so you can see my
achievement press a but I like this B GM
what if it goes away after
[Music]
that shut up about Mass Effect
no I like this one right
now oh I have access to all the big gems
oh
Nar oh well oh well so last time I
finished the super chats oh of the after
talk
so apparently next up is a Metroid
stream didn't I however skip eventually
something and then
R didn't I read super chats from the
second Metroid stream already I think I
did so I have to read the ones from the
first one
now I
think yeah yeah okay okay
okay
fitting
very on topic
[Music]
cringe
pinky it's
okay this one has tons of Reds and yeah
that's why I skipped
it all right all right all right come to
Brazil k no you come to Austria what the
hell I've been to Brazil two times how
many more times are you going to force
me to go to Brazil without you paying me
a visit a single time
huh come to UK oh flights already
booked I literally already booked
flights I mean rmt booked flights
yesterday
surprisingly expensive I don't know if
it was the date where just generally
things are more expensive
now like it was cheaper before it may
have been a
[Music]
date going to
UK might ask you guys for some more IDE
of what to do in London because last
time I was in London when it was ice
cold we already did some
sseeing we checked out some places
already back
then yeah I don't think I'll be doing
any meetups with uh like British
YouTubers because I'm with rmt and I
don't want you know I
actually
um that would be quite a DJ Vu because
last time when I was in London with her
of
rmt I that was the first time I went
there and there was like an longtime
internet
friend who was doing similar things that
I did for years on the internet
um who I thought I cannot let this opin
this opportunity go to meet her so I
asked AR if it's okay then I just go
away for like an hour or to to meet up
with her to have a like a cake and a tea
in a little fancy
[Music]
cafe oh yeah yeah yeah we did back then
we did the HP um like London guide tour
so it was like a guide tour but uh HP
them anyway so I I I I you know already
back then I left her alone to meet
someone back then but that that was
really nice um and I don't want to want
to do that again yeah so this time just
aren
me is she single oh I don't know I
haven't I haven't like talked with her
like Dad in a long time
but we'll catch up in London and I'll
find
out HP you follow the computer company
have I not raised you well enough so far
that HP makes you think of Hell project
by now I mean it's not what I was like
talking about but
HP should
not should not ever make you think about
the
monitors should make you think about
hell
project
or happy
rter happy Ro that's a new
[Music]
one it's Beau
exclamation
still you're just making excuses now
what who the [\h__\h] is
that
company C Li
hackard but anyway
H lord of the
prings you mean
Pringles okay guys enough
bantering enough with
that r d r
d oh
wa I'll read that one
quietly oh
no thank you that's really sweet R thank
you so much I'm glad I could help you
glad to have you here thank you sh for
sharing
that greenbird
than green bird n
but now I can read it confidently I know
exactly how to read your name NP
[Music]
NP F thank you for the
pinky coner was amazing we had a Big
East Coast us meet up to watch you Tanto
we're posting pic on Twitter yeah I saw
many many I love this gaming series D YK
Samos is a part BP I didn't know that
she's raised by choso space BBS and was
infused by their DNA to make her Warrior
yeah I didn't even know that when I
chose
it if I knew
that if I knew
that I may have played it earlier oh but
I guess likeit the the the the the the
Metroid Prime remaster when did this
come
out maybe it's good that I waited to
play anything Metroid
related wasn't it recently yeah last
month
so maybe it was meant to be thank you f
long
than yeah also it's really sweet that
you were at the meet up too that's
really nice my East uh Coast gang I'm
happy you guys got together
yeah wait was worth
yeah yo go thanks for the
rainbow oops forgot to put a message in
there haha oh no did it again how silly
of
me well I don't have much to say she has
a lot of super chats to go for and W's
voice is important all I want to say is
I love Kiwa she's the best
oi I really appreciate that though even
though
even though that's a little bit you know
wasteful of your super chat I appreciate
that thank you so sweet I was thinking
of
[Music]
me py Dy soon JY thank you for two
pinkies why does it start so sad again
like it makes me doy dokie
oh hi K is with a heavy heart but I must
say during four Fest someone was able to
rock it to my number one o she
spot her name is
Ki I think she's a secret horony member
because she's also a cute BB she worked
so hard for her fans and looked so
beautiful on stage that she made my
heart go doy doie you during whole 27
she took my favorite song in the cover
album and made it even better a and wait
a minute I'm starting to get the feeling
K is K never mind was said you my number
one of
course thank you you're so sweet I feel
like you're becoming sweeter with every
year that
passes thank you here's a kiss for
you that's quite the coincidence that
that was like your generally favorite
song out of those Deo songs and we got
to sing that nice lucky lucky
lucky now you must listen on repeat
forever thank you thank you Richard good
[Music]
night thank you guys GL you enjoyed
GH what my favorite Deco
song m
thank
you let's hope you never get sick of it
J Monkey py D soon V than the gamer cre
than soon flppy boy than soon for the r
chat those Dr days of Bing are over
rewarded with the long awaited Metroid
lovely to have you back
kiaha oh
yeah I hope your family friends and
cutos for you and unfor forgettable
homecoming party thank you very much
um there was no homecoming party there
never is I guess I just go and leave and
come back too many times that it's not
special anymore no one ever awaits me on
the airport either I just quickly jump
into an
Uber it's always the
same yeah I remember like in my very
first couple of
trips or like after moving back
from uh from Japan for the first time to
austri you know when everything was kind
of like yeah
blah I think back then you know when it
was still
new people would sometimes come to you
know but I mean they don't have to do it
now all the
time yeah oh she was is
[Music]
gone oh you're back oh you're gone again
oh you're back
[Music]
again yeah in the fun made me feel
things made me feel things too I get
you
amazing please um write that to the
artist on Twitter
[Music]
anyway thank you so much B boy I'm glad
I'm
back um but you reminded me of
something that I think I may as well
share
because we talked about it before and I
don't want to leave you guys in the dark
about
it
um cuz it's a happy
[Music]
message not a very
oh clear one
but I have received another happy
message
today after
pushing
so there may be a delay and it might not
happen on the exact
date but I will get my birthday concert
this year
[Music]
yes now I still don't
know if it's really going to be delayed
but since they mentioned it it probably
will
be I hope not too much I'll have to
figure out like when to go to record
it cuz I I'm pretty sure I'll do it like
pre-recorded and then it will need some
some time to be
edited um but yeah hopefully not too
long yeah as long as it
happens thank
God I don't mind to delay at all yeah I
hope it just doesn't like go too long
until like September where my
anniversary would
be like August at the latest would be
acceptable yeah when I go in June that's
for different
reason I'll go to Japan in June and end
of June anyway for different
reasons that is already kind of set in
stone yeah but yeah so I just want to
let you guys know that you
can um happily look forward to it
because it will happen
[Music]
is this this is the going to be the
third birthday of me in this
company the Third
oh my God so yeah my third
birthday is finally going to be a cover
produce birthday
concert yay yay
yay
Hallelujah I deserve it so I am
happy I'll be three years old k
I'll be three three years
old
M
yeah so moving
on thank
[Music]
you thank you
okay before we piss anyone off thank you
for laughing by Sean on thank you for
the two
pinkies I know I
know you are possibly the most happy
about this game being Chosen
One thanks for finally playing a Metro
game and fulfilling my birthday wish
from 2 years ago
this one is perhaps my favorite game
from my childhood and it holds a very
special place to me because of just how
Eng grassing its world was oh what your
favorite Metro game
nice these past few months of your
stream have been rough for me but your
decision to play this helped me power
through while the idol stuff has never
appealed to me seeing you play games
like these is what gets me excited to be
a fan of you as well I hope that me
being very salty for without
it didn't sour uh the
experience
um
[Music]
uh you have no idea how amazing this was
a loy oh you're also one of those KF K
of Metro
primers not too much thankfully oh
that's good I
mean o there were some o o moments today
I'm glad it didn't destroy everything
um I tried my
best thank you for helping yeah all of
the big Metroid Prime fans were always
so helpful in the chat thank you guys so
much for like using your brain trying
your best to
remember where to go what to do even
though for some of you it may have been
a long time since you last played
it thank you thank you thank you also
thanks for the mentor Prime fan you did
want to thank you very much of course
you did how could you not thank you so
much than for
everything unfortunately M prime time is
over
now and sorry to say there's no plan to
play another one anytime
soon but oh yeah the helmet the helmet
I've been wearing the whole time was
from you too yeah thank you it's been
coming very much in handy
yeah prime time no I wanted to say
unfortunately maybe my conscious made me
say
fortunately I feel like I said
unfortunately yeah but yeah thank you so
much thank you thank you thank you for
supporting glad you had a good time and
enjoyed this these couple
days gum cobbler an mental Jetty ah
thank you for theed Super Chat by mental
Jetty k for fast and excited for you to
play one of my also for you one of my
favorite games Sun tips scan
Lots safe
lots listen for sound Clues and enjoy
music sound
Clues sound cloes like what I only
remember Pirates being hinted at by
the
sounds sound CL of
powerups I never paid attention to that
throughout all of the
game
funny but I did enjoy the music feel
free to run past stuff thank you for
saying that and finally yes everything
is trying to kill you but don't panic
game is quite forgiving early on was it
though was it I don't remember anymore
it's been too
long and then I get good too
[Music]
fast you guys what I'm honestly like
what sound
Clues what
please I'm in the same camp oh thank
God I never ever heard such a thing I
swear they exist yet in your
head
roasted thank you mental
Jenny thank you so much for the mental
support literally d d d
thank you so much I appreciate
it boom
roasted James Jackson thank you for the
r chat today I reached one year of KP
[Music]
membership I feel like you were around
for a million years I have a lot in
common with my potential you have a July
birthday oh you do not drink alcohol
coffee use corded headphones not ear
let's go love sella games and you want
two
CS oh for the blue r no wait that we
didn't talk about that until yesterday
what two
CS the last one only the last one I do
not
understand got
him how dare you
[Music]
I was just like feeling really happy how
we were connected in so many
ways and that ruined it
all that ruined it all James
[Music]
Jackson what the
[\h__\h] being
B no one no one ever expected especially
not for my loyal kind respectful sweet
chickens I'm so
disappointed I need an apology from you
apology
letter you love you tanto uhhuh uhhuh
really you're trying to fix things up
like
that
Sasa but I don't know do you really get
a kiss for that
[Music]
what's my
[Laughter]
sentence
um three
months usual room stks Rising once again
I haven't brought enough people there
anyway ah simple yeah that is so cute
thank you for drawing it I love it
[Music]
I feel like though personality wise you
know you couldn't have really known this
but I feel
like it would be the other way around
cuz uh chuny wony is a little bit more
of a scared cat would probably react
more like teal one smoovie and smoovie
would be the one to attack
it but that's just you
know kiaha cature
all right
James you get half a kiss and when you
get out of the usual room and you're
nice again then you get the rest of the
kiss I used to send them by the groups
yeah yeah maybe I should again cat L
noted
Mr thanks for the pinky
[Music]
difficult and doesn't progress the story
oh well nobody told me that not sure not
anytime soon and last says good luck Tel
they updated the game for modern day
controllers and there's three different
control settings you might need a test
those all need to find one that feels
good even if you wind up not liking it
thank you for choosing to play it fin
the way wi you
reminder well well well I did change it
a little bit sometimes the motion
controls came in handy so yeah thank you
for that for telling me that
[Music]
D I am
hungry Sky D suck punch
D
th for the I've been hoping someone in
my would play this hope happy to see you
hope you enjoy the game thank you thank
you thank you and oh you must be so
happy and all the other Metro Prime fans
I'm a man right that he wants to play it
so wow wow wow it's like a boom a
Metroid boom going
on oh my god did I did I set a trend
again like oh my God so just like me
like I always do this yes so expected
like I knew I would totally start a
trend cuz I'm such a trend
set
[Music]
yes thank you
oh my God
stop
stop so
F oh I want to see I'm a
raging
oh but if I watch her play
it I'll every time I watch I'mma play a
game that I know how to play which is
very rarely the case I want to help her
and backseat or that's not only alen
like anyone when when I watch someone
who plays a game that I played before
then I want to back seene and help not
really I wouldn't call it back seting I
mean they literally like just like me
ask questions into the void then how is
it back seating when I just answered the
question like how do I do this of course
I'm going to answer if I asks me a
question directly because that was of
course directed at
me if somebody asks a question it's rude
not to answer it yeah I know she doesn't
like back seting but then she shouldn't
ask the
question it might just be not you know
like a streamer thing where you just
comment on everything I have that too
sometimes sometimes I don't mean the
questions that
seriously when I say oh how do I do this
should I do this while I'm like doing it
anyway
[Music]
yeah yeah rhetorical questions yeah the
illusion of a
question She Can't Ban me but I also
like you know she always helped me with
stuff
so it would be nice to for once be in
the position of being helpful you know
so I'm looking forward oh I want to see
her play
it I will try to not back seat too much
but uh cuz am is like the perfect person
to rage at
things she may rage even more than me
who
knows she's going to go like hi
yeah I love it I love when she
rages I hope that maybe you guys like it
too when I rage but there's there's
different kind of rages even with am
there's like the rages where you notice
just like really really frustrated and
that's like not that makes me feel bad
too but often she rages in the in a
still kind of fun
way that's fine that makes me
happy no I will not tell her to scan cuz
I would never tell anyone to scan ever
except the
[Music]
chore also I won't have to because the
chat will tell her to scan
anyway I don't have to do it everyone
else will tell her I I will not take the
fall I always laugh at Amy raging it's
fun to see herself oh my God cow Caren
how how can you say something like that
when I just yesterday or the day before
yesterday or so sent your Amed noises
clip to Amed
directly and now you are here enjoying
her suffering telling me that so so
[Music]
openly I sent it cuz it was so
funny man
now you can set this time stamp of this
as well no no no no
no I'm a normal teammate
oh so what am I am I an unnormal
teammate this this the same as like me
with P Senai I used to say that like I
don't really like to see
her suffer that much but then other no
saggies seem to really enjoy
that and I don't know
don't quite enjoy it as much as the
other no saggies do I
think
H
yeah
yeah what is it what is it I'm just too
much of a kind
person thank you Caleb so
much H Kevin
[Music]
oh Lord that I don't have to scan space
pirates invaded her home planet as a kid
and she was the only Survivor bird
aliens saved and adopted her and gave
her the bird DNA and bird superpowers
and bird technology with the bird magic
Wow birds are amazing every time like
also in like you know Lord of the Rings
birds are the saviors why is why are
birds so cool
huh I'm glad that the media picks up on
that
[Music]
Epson
YX you must not be happy with how I
played the game cuz you told me K make
sure to scan
everything 100% scans did you really ask
me to 100% the scans like
unironically are you here wrench man
cool were you really wanting and
expecting of me to want 100% the
scans did you have any
realistic thoughts there that I would
really do
[Music]
this I'm sorry if you really wanted that
if ah it would have been
fun I'm
sorry I'm really sorry to
disappoint I did not have the patience
for that
[Music]
of course it's not
impossible but it is it is out of
character for someone like
me no it's okay thank you for being
understanding I was worried cuz it
seemed very important to you okay then
we good shake hands the social artist
[Music]
d
oh what that should have been like DLC
or something unfortunately to for the OG
version did not make it into the Master
you could use the fusion suit from
Metroid Fusion by
connecting uh the GBA Game it also made
the OG Metroid
playable
damn it's getting
loopy [\h__\h] it can't get loopy that
was
amazing choosing to save now we finish
this game of when you sell your you will
start a new game
these kind of questions at the end of
the game really always confuse
me thank you for telling me what to do
even now I need back seating in this
kind of
situation why why are you question why
are you of course I want to
save I guess I think well do I maybe not
I mean I'm done do I want to
save I don't
know oh
no questioning myself
again
y I want to hear
music is it an
extra W this one gets loopy I have to
say
I was
quiet
sick imagine me reading super chats to
that
H
ooh funky
[Music]
that was
nice kind of melancholic
[Music]
though are there some more happy
ones oh Cho Shrine is
nice can't listen
is that
it I'm lacking 1 2 3 4 5 six
[Music]
traps right I'll listen to this for now
of course I skipped over the space
pirate
song sounds very Star Fox Adventures
like well I can see
that oh okay this good this is
good this is good making me a BL T
though
[Music]
and my seat for hollow 27 was the second
row from the front center of the venue
yeah I think I saw a picture where you
pointed out where which one is you so I
could see your performance clearly so
glad that I could seeare you and Shout
out your
name wa the BM can you not Loop
it
for oh my
God are you okay
are you okay s Chan Sal CH hurt her leg
because she was uh like hit by a car
because she was wearing kiaha cosplay
shoes
[Music]
inocent
no I'm wondering like I was asking whose
fault was it but like generally you
always want to say that it was the car's
fault because I mean
hello person walking is just person
walking yeah don't get
isied they have to be careful because
they have so much power in the car to
hurt people I got to be careful
but well well s joh nonetheless you also
got to be careful okay don't you almost
broke your
[Music]
leg be careful
s okay have to Bonk you with shank
sh okay be careful
hope you're feeling better by
[Music]
now got a out of it so probably worth
it gamer D 92
d c
d quick s m of humans still alive s was
raised on colon that was destroyed by
Pirates led by space Dragon Ridley
she was adopted by CH of Space Birds
okay that part I know thank you
Optimus you
apologized you the one who told me to
not tangent and just start playing the
game hey K I want to apologize I'm still
new to your Phantom I'm used to Mor
having the game already booted up and
being ready to play as soon as getting
ready to start the screen as soon as
getting ready to start screen appears
it's okay I'm sorry too
like it's just you know normally all my
viewers appreciate me Tangen
thing and um
yeah so I felt like ha H don't complain
it's only been half an
hour yeah in this house we
tangent but I hope you didn't feel um
you know
no like now you can't you don't want to
watch my streams because I threatened
you with a
Jun well you don't seem to be here now
so that's already a bad
sign H Mama
Mia oh face of mine is pretty
long uh thank Lord we smash thank you
soon a than for the r chat if you go in
back into controls and scroll down to
camera
you you already read this you you spent
a red super chat for telling me that
that was so helpful
though thank you you didn't have to do
that thank
you
turn also yes can provides most of the
gam L thank you m man what a
Chad it was important job but damn I
want to give you back the money you
shouldn't have to spend money for that
mental J D as live
than Scotland oh beautiful e thank you
for the
red amazing performance at four Fest T
trly showed how great of an idol you
are
sweet thank
you I'm glad you think
so more idle kiaha come coming in summer
time yay look forward to it you have to
stay kfp until then and then forever
after that as well so there's no end
inside um so have
fun
Kevin
R Unwritten
Birds P Super Snake Mario than for the
pinky hm
hi K I wanted to tell you I was able to
watch a h 27 concert oh and I must say
your performance was amazing you and M
may sound so good together o thank you
also going off topic but I love your new
hairstyle it's so cute and love the
glasses as well thank you oh man I
should ask for an update on
glasses let me ask maybe it was
forgotten
[Music]
hello just
checking
okay
okay messages
okay okay okay many
messages s my storry ner show my beloved
yeah I want to use those glasses I
haven't used them since want to get to
use them where was I oh yeah ah so yeah
Super Snake Mario it will be a little
while most likely until glasses will
show up again please hold the line
please please wait for it I will bring
them back when they are fixed cuz right
now they
are a little bit too
buggy little bit too
glitchy can't ignore that
one sir
956 damn what the
[\h__\h] well with all
[Music]
well
well thank you for your first ever Super
Chat watching Tom Scott's YouTube video
of him getting over his fear of roller
coasters it's amazing how phobia
sometimes can be broken with the sheer
for of will eh you think that will break
my phobia I mean I wouldn't even say
it's a phobia cuz I still ride roller
coaster
it's just they feel really terrible I
still do it sometimes though that was a
great video really Tom Scott I I
sometimes try watching his videos
but I don't know I always feel
like yeah I'm not a fan either this is
going to be a hot take but I always feel
like um I learned and gained nothing
from that and could have used my time
better like his titles and his
thumbnails always sound so interesting
so I sometimes try it out and then I'm
like I somehow expected something else
from
this every once in a while give it a try
and it's just like him standing there
blabbering blabbering
I'm so sorry some I feel like maybe one
video I enjoy I enjoyed the the
drivethru one the um was it McDonald's
or
so that one oh and I think recently he
made uh was it recently there was a
video that I watched where it was about
um
eradicating a
species see those those kind of videos
are more interesting I think to me
because he actually walks around and
does something and shows
something sometimes he's just standing
there for the whole
video and
talking and then I don't get
it sure that was Tom Scott right a yeah
the New Zealand this this is impossible
but New Zealand is trying anyway I
watched that one that one was kind of
interesting I think I may have watched
the I tried using AI it scared me one
and expected so much from it and I went
out of it with
nothing what defun land oh no you all
tell me watch do
Funland myly interesting
interesting little tidbits of info if
the info isn't that interesting you then
I can't see being unsatisfied I don't
know wait he has a video that says these
chickens save lives well maybe I should
watch that
one cuz it's about chickens and I have a
personal connection to
chickens hey is this the one about for
the roller coaster this can't be it the
title already scares me this roller
coaster doesn't stop automatically
that's not it
right she's holding the break oh my
God that's not it
right all right I'll look it up I'll
I'll dive a bit more through his channel
give him another
chance on his second channel oh okay
maybe sended to me on
Twitter where was
I uh
where was
I I
he with d gaming clone D Peter C be D
gamer Dan D am I going to get cancelled
for my opinion by the way please no
please no please no please no he does I
like some of his
videos the jester D no not by us okay
resident l
[Music]
d okay you don't even know who that is
okay
good then you can't be
mad I like his um accent
though I in fear I like listening to him
even if I don't like what he's talking
about because I like his
accent it's so beautiful
he's a good talker
too if you don't get cancel for
pineapple pizza then nothing can touch
[Laughter]
[Music]
you I have too much power now we for the
pinky well what did we learn about
saving remember Dash by locking on
and mashing be okay by now I know that
let's get used to it you can do this I
remember I started playing this game
just like you you'll
adopt I did adopt I and I
overcame no I don't remember that ass
plant
no D shinda thank you for trying to help
you also very really helpful for out
thank you
red you got this
dangel did I got this maybe I got this
afterwards thank
you for the support mental support very
necessary 73
7at engineering D Patrick Hall
than flurry B thanks for the pinky good
luck from flurry Bol K I played for this
game recently and some parts really beat
me up too you got this and thanks for
playing it for us thank you
recently did you also play the
remastered one probably
right thank you very much for the
supportive kind
message thank you
soon I mean you beat almost every bus
that made you salty on second try yeah
it's like the sheer willower that I
have I willed my skill into
existence J
with
Rafael X7 the
G thank you for the pinky
congratulations on big shoulders oh oh
yeah what did I not have them in the
beginning that's too long ago I don't
remember having no big
shoulders oh that was a different time
you know I saw the draft of like blue
who made my gun blue also was trying to
make me a whole suit and she made the
shoulder pads with coton face shape and
I really wanted that that was so cute
but she gave up it's fine it's fine now
it's too late anyway but uh I thought
that was look really adorable
man it wasn't cursed at all no it was
like so naturally implemented it was
perfect it's kind of big for an asset
yeah I don't know I I felt I thought I
wrote a reply to you but then Twitter
maybe didn't like send it properly but I
was going to say you don't have to do
the whole suit just the just the pads
would be nice cuz they look so cute I'll
just just throw on the shoulder pads
only oh well oh
well maybe that reply never came through
I should have written a
DM it's okay but they were so cute you
have such great ideas and your assets
are really cute thank you for making
them K
dun BL artist dun ran thanks for the
pinky I have to drink water but the fly
is in there if I drink it it kind of
goes
back
okay uh greetings Tel I'm late to the
after party but big congrats to you and
the other girls on a bright four Fest
thank you was really happy to see do you
my favorite of yours ah and you dancel
of the Ian unit of course your MC and
duet of your fellow BBS thank
you yeah was a big big Gua day thank you
very much for watching it
than of course I'm still it's a tiny one
like not a big one it's just like this
really small
fly it's not a big
deal don't freak out you're
[Music]
gross it's
just
don't don't
drink shame
me I'm not going to get new water it's
fine this
way I can't reach it cuz it's a tall
Tumbl
glass I want to finish this I'm almost
done
thank you really I'm glad you enjoyed it
so much thank you
sh if you like do you then I think
you'll enjoy my EP that I'm planning on
cuz I'll I'll have some more like kop
inspired songs in there yeah xtm than
you need to chat than but also non Kpop
inspired again Jpop inspired as well too
mayap leave Dy soon sunny days sweeping
the cloud away the out the way h on my
way where the air is sweet can you tell
me how to get how to get to H life
street is
that inspired by another song's
[Music]
lyrics Sesame stre oh oh I'm ashamed now
because I say I love Elmo
oh I don't even know the melody of
that fake fan
yep I'll take
it thank you D
may I appreciate
it
AER help this is how I get
cancelled black get gamer Dan
dap
D Kurt
Johnson doler or
doler
M mayf for minky put this towards a
budget to make satellites that can
broadcast live Holograms in the night
sky world domination is a Shir yoan oh
my is this the stream where we started
with those crazy ideas
wow wow wow wow you seem motivated all
right you are into this I will support
you I will not stop you from putting
money into
that thank you I am
a ninja spanheim thanks for the red
super chat you're the smartest you of
all time also cat is the best
movie spankenheimer
something you said the other day that
made me doubt
you this is helping you out big time
[Music]
again was it about
cats it may have been about
cats
Brandon C than the CH you way to Big
Brain congrats on again on forfest Boss
your performances are always iconic
really looking forward to your long
streams again thank you I am feeling a
little bit exhausted by them already so
good that tomorrow has been changed to
uh collab
only in the evening so I have to prepare
some stuff anyway for uh upcoming stream
VR stream see what I can
do and just
generally I have to watch Tad lasso I've
been saying I will watch Tad lasso for
weeks now and I haven't yet got into
it like I always like
H end up just like falling asleep
quickly to some short something and I
don't want to fall asleep to like while
watching T last cuz I'm already like
always so tired when I get get to bed
but I'm actually grateful that I can
fall asleep so well these
days yeah so maybe
tomorrow oh they don't release all
episodes at once okay okay well then
it's good that I'm waiting
maybe thank you
[Music]
c phone thanks for the r CH between
watching you shining on stage at forfest
and getting to spend my birthday with
you and ifp for the thir year in the row
I'm one happy Tim King thanks for being
a constant source of Tears wait was this
your birthday then screams laughs enjoy
my beloved T you also employee number
please phone happy belated birthday
[Music]
congratulations happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear Fone happy birthday to you your
employee number is
257 if you know you
know hope it's not
taken oh s also wanted the number all
right all right one second no didn't she
get the number for the date of forfest
I'm pretty sure I gave her that
number all good 257 is free nice it's
not a date
yeah it's not a date where does this
number come from what do the numbers
mean
Mason for Lu yeah you can have that
number you're welcome phone
con did you have a birthday
cake tell
me I'm waiting
you had raspberry cheesecake let's go
I'm so glad you got a
cake
niceu you don't know you don't
know yummy I'm I'm happy for you thank
you for supporting me for a long long
long long long time not giving up on me
still being here even today
[Music]
D
lpj oh a
rainbow without any text from a
mysterious
[Music]
which day of Fest oh no didn't we
already decide she can pick whichever
she
prefers maybe day one because that was
when I was in
it the 10 message in the Milestone ah ah
cuz I got angry maybe
yeah I was like final message what the
hell oh that may have happened yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
Rowan Hood joined in between also for a
wordless pinky by the way thank you
ran
and and Evans l
d oh my God I'm done and I feel like I
read
ah
yeah yeah I read as much as I made in
the Stream So that
was no not quite I made a bit more in
the in this one that I made in this one
current one so I I am did a little bit
more like in terms of reading
Y and I mean this was a big hurdle to
overcome
anyway yeah the infinite Super Chat Loop
we'll get there we'll get there don't
worry we will get there
eventually I am exhausted now so I will
take my leave thank you guys for
watching H
tomorrow I'll be on Nina's Channel I'll
keep you updated on
quitter so I'll see you there
okay thank you for suffering through it
with me hope you guys had fun and in
German we say I'll be the
same
[Music]
byebye
byebye byebye byebye thank
you h
[Music]