[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
so
[Applause]
hello
attention please it's raining in kiara
let's go hello kitty kitty's working oh
my god i can't believe it
[Music]
hello from the maldives
[Applause]
are you guys seeing us properly are we
like pixelated or does it look fine even
if it looks fine now i just want to say
um
there might be you know some some
hiccups because um even though we're
using cable if you looked at my twitter
you saw that
it's even with the cable it's shitty
yeah it looks good oh i'm so happy
like we thought that you know maybe
cardboard is necessary but apparently
not yeah this is pretty good for
i expected way worse
yeah
yes download speed and um upload speed
are doing their best
yeah it's okay they're gone but doing
but yeah we're also gonna
it's like it ain't over for xl uh
melon soda
it's good it's good
yeah what are you having i'm having also
a melon soda apparently but if you guys
looked at our um twitter actually we
have um
uh some
non-alcohol champagne with us like
originally when we entered the room they
had a big bottle of real champagne there
but i was like oh i guess i guess elena
is going to drink all of that
but then they offered to exchange it
into like non-alcohol
uh champagne and that's what we were
drinking uh-huh yeah it's good
it tasted tastes good i don't know i
don't have much left oh well
i mean there's still more
yes if you ever wanted yes
so um in this stream we're first of all
testing if streaming is possible at all
second of all we're just gonna
um tell you guys how our travel went so
far
it's like a status report yeah yeah
um yeah and then how you know oh we're
also gonna do
the gift
it kind exchange feels like you know one
of those like christmas thingies or
you're like preparing a present yes yes
yes yes also if i turn off the bgm you
guys
this is real wave sounds do you hear it
do you hear it i think you hear it
obvious
you'll be back is the room still there i
know i think it's like um
can i try it oh
i still gotta
just come back
come back to me and they need to come
back
yeah you hear this this room we have the
the doors open right now and you know
our our
um we have oh hi yeah there you are
we have a house that's like literally on
the water that's kind of like
for when i thought about the maldives it
was my idea to go to the maldives
because
i saw all these pictures about uh with
these houses on top of the ocean
basically like floating
that's why i wanted to
come here one day and elena joined me
yeah i didn't when did i ask you about
it way back i feel like
like few
months oh no i remember was it in winter
still i think like early early this year
maybe
i don't remember but yeah i've always
actually wanted to go to the maldives
like i see like a lot of really really
nice pictures it's just like always at
the back of my head you know but then
it's like oh what occasion and like you
know if i go alone it's kind of like i
don't know
yeah but then wow suddenly a message
oh hell yeah
i to write something oh yeah
should do you guys want the bgm on
because sorry don't ignore that i want
to write making icing i want to say
um
wave sounds are real
i just want to note that for people
coming into the stream and they're like
one of their sounds real wave sounds oh
you guys can hear the waves clearly yeah
try it try this
you can hear it in the headphones
it's pretty loud like it really is
pretty loud because the waves are pretty
strong the wind has been really strong
right now it's actually not raining
not raining yeah was like oh that's
actually pretty warm outside
[Music]
hello
i i took your kohai
vacation
i'm being yeah i'm being borrowed i will
return eventually all right one more
thing whoopsie all right
all right because people gonna ask
questions this is of the lamb yeah this
is all collabs
let's go we've already said it like in
in the in the course of the past let's
say one or even two months i think both
of us mentioned going on a maldives trip
a million times but people are still to
this day asking where are they are they
in bali what they're going to vacation
where where
yeah
we're in maldives guys we are living the
life it's happening yeah so like we're
going to talk about
everything
maybe for like an hour and then we're
going to go back to vacationing but it's
good to see that streaming works because
that means we can use um
i brought my capture card and we both
brought our switches yeah so we were
thinking to play some kind of a couch or
co-op games maybe maybe or maybe super
smash brothers because i'm really
excited to play something or or mario
kart no no anything anything really yeah
anything i also have warioware which is
only couch up i have that on my on my
switch so we'll play some game maybe uh
keep an eye out on rayna's channel
because it might be on her channel
eventually maybe maybe maybe
yeah
it's not getting unless you keep on
drinking and drinking but it's not
getting less
forever like you know refill oh i want
to get something i'll be right back okay
can you bring the bottle over oh sure
thank you
where's my okay
and she goes
this mic picks up like a lot of the
sounds man i hear your stomping sounds
sorry stop stop dum dum dum dum dum dum
here i wanna
[Music]
oh pouring sound it's it's like foamy
it's like this
oh
here it could reach okay just try to
plug it in and uh yes i will try
oh yeah you need to charge the camera
dana's camera yeah hello i am back nice
nice okay can you not get any closer
we have um you know a hotel room set up
so cables everywhere chairs are weird
these cameras
it's kind of like you know the you know
the imposter game where you have to like
connect the kids
like that
yeah yeah yeah
okay so we should start from the top
like uh-huh talk about your retails are
structured that's amazing yeah we need
to be stretching talk about first of all
how the whole trip was like the plane
ride and all that do you want to start
oh sure
like i don't know uh
we went like with normal planes uh and
then
but the surprise was that after a plane
after like the normal plane apparently
like in order to like get to the uh
where we were staying we needed to get
we needed to ride another plane which is
a sea play i am if you guys know animal
crossing and we're crossing iran
it was actually my first time going you
know on the sleepless it was me too
interesting to the moment i saw it i was
like oh that's total airlines
look it's dodo airlines the whole
process really felt like uh you know
just going in a ride like in a you know
a theme park actually
that's not starting from the top
i have i have wrote notes and i started
i have notes starting wave before that
fine you do it then you leave okay well
for for example okay
first of all i was really um stressed
out about uh like for example luggage
and all kinds of things like because
like my airline allows 30 kilogram but
the seaplane only allows 20 kilogram
so i found my my weighing scale that you
can like you can put it on the
suitcase and then you lift it oops
oh that was loud and then you lift it up
and and i i
i did it once when it was at like 17
kilo and i added a few more things i was
like this should be fine and then i
brought it to the airport and
i i waited and i was getting really
luminous and then it said
20.1 kilograms absolutely perfect i mean
okay that's zero point four one it's a
little bit too much but that didn't
didn't matter so yeah all good so that
was all according to keikaku
um i took a flight by the way from i
didn't take a direct flight because when
we were looking up the dates for the
vacation uh-huh i
um we only looked for like a departure
on like
sunday and monday yeah and if i if we i
didn't i didn't tell you but if we would
have looked for the um
uh departure on i think what was it for
friday and wednesday then i would have
had a direct flight
only on two days in a week there's
direct flights man and
didn't know that because we only checked
for like sunday i don't have direct yeah
man [\h__\h] but yeah so i went on a sunday
night we both um was it sunday night for
you too um it wasn't like sun this was
like
on gobby hours of monday
sunday night ish so i went first i went
to dubai the first flight was nice
because the two seats next to me were
empty and i could lay down and i was
watching movies i watched um
that new relatively new movie uh from
this i think it's disney it's um
encounter
and then i watched i didn't watch it
fully but i watched uh
the like that gucci
oh i've never actually i haven't
actually watched you know the one that's
lady gaga i know but i didn't watch it
yeah i watched that one um uh i want to
continue watching maybe on my flight
back uh-huh
it was pretty interesting
yeah it's pretty interesting oh man
and then i tried to sleep but in the
first flight which was like five hours i
only got like 30 minutes sleep
and then i had a layover for three hours
in dubai uh-huh which i was so [\h__\h]
tired but i found a nutella cafe there
i told elena we were like on whatsapp
when i was in my layover uh dana was
like still like uh no wait you were also
somewhere over there i was in singapore
singapore singapore and then
see this is where you have to tell
something you forgot about that so now
you remember what did you tell me
so listen so so um i did get her but i
did get her something else uh so in the
in the
duty-free thingy from indonesia like i
got her like a really something
something really nice something i i've
never even tried before in my entire
life it's like something something a
nice chocolate was made out of like you
know the c c
kopi it's like copy lua chocolate yeah i
think people in chat um some of them
will know but they're like kind of fancy
and then you know um because uh my my
bags are kind of heavy i had like a lot
of to carry um
basically i got off the plane on
singapore and then i probably either
forgot it on the plane or in the
bathroom because i was like
the time zone was like really confusing
i was like damn do i have like two hours
or one hour and then i was like in a
rush and then
yeah i talked to like the lost and found
guy and then they were like yeah trying
to find it in the plane and in the
whatever
but
they couldn't find it and i was very
very
upset yeah
you can't really get them like really
anywhere else like not singapore not
like yeah
and then
and you panic messaged me and watching
like oh my god i'm so sorry i got you
something but i lost it i'll try to find
something else for you in singapore yeah
but then like there was i couldn't
really find anything that you know i
think wow
i mean there's like chips i don't know
if you like chips
there's like chips over there if you
want oh oh oh but that's not the thing
you want to get yeah that's not the
thing i wanted to give it to you
i mean that's okay she reassured me and
then i guess you know okay don't worry
my first flight was also like her like i
had like an empty seat next to me yeah
that's best but i can't really i
couldn't really like lift the thing
though oh that sucks that's like um
probably like
usually that's only for short distance
flights they don't let you lift the the
handle thingy yeah so i put like i put
my jacket there
i want my jacket there pretty handy even
even when you can't lift it i have a
good way of getting comfortable there
like you sit sideways with your legs
angled like this
over the armrest and that's really
comfortable you can even sleep like that
if you go like i didn't even think of
that because like i'm i'm actually like
aisle gang i used to be wrong again but
then it's always really awkward if you
have to like go outside like to the
island you have to like skip all these
people excuse me i'm sorry you know i
had i had window seats for all my
flights i specifically chose window
seats and yeah uh-huh i need i need my
windows seats because i was also taking
some pictures i wanted to take pictures
of when my my dubai to maldives flight
would arrive in the maldives and then
yeah on the flights from dubai to
maldives that took about four hours i
tried to sleep but i couldn't because it
was [\h__\h] crowded and cold and
terrible really uncomfortable one of the
worst most uncomfortable flights i've
ever had really really um but i was able
to see um like when when the plane was
getting uh down on the maldens
i saw some of those islands you know
that
and i was like oh
well that looks so cool because there's
like there's maybe you guys know but um
the maldives has like over a thousand
islands um but then there's like a lot
of islands that are not even inhabited
but that also you can't really build
something on it and then there's islands
that are not really even islands con
like yet because they're so like low-key
under the water but you can see that
there's like
like something raised there you can see
it from above it's really cool there's
so many
and then i landed and then uh oh then i
landed and dana was in the maldives
already before me no you can tell them
what did you do
yeah okay so
she didn't sleep right she watched
movies so so me being the yeah you know
i don't sleep so i never sleep before a
trip so i can just leave through the
whole trip you know like if i'm in a
plane i just instantly
you know when there's turbulence it's
just like you know it's like oh it's
rocking the baby it's time to sleep
so it's like whenever there's turbulence
i'm like but i thought maybe there
wasn't any turbulence on my end maybe it
was kind of oh yeah right yeah
i'm talking about yeah
i tweet i think did i did i tweet about
i'm not sure anymore i took a photo and
i wanted to tweet about it um
in my second flight so the one from the
dubai to molins i
we had like some crazy turbulences i
think when we are already very close to
the maldives you know which are
currently in the monsoon season so i i
figured there might be some troubles and
uh we're going through this this one big
ass [\h__\h] cloud and
it was crazy i've you guys know i've
been on so many planes but those that
turbulence was the first time in my
whole life that i thought i might die
and i was like and we were shaking and
shaking and it was really yumbai and the
people next to me were also looking
scared and panicking and worried and i
was holding on to like the seat in front
of me
and i thought oh my god what if
something falls off of the
the wing of the plane oh my gosh yeah
and and and you know what one font of
mine was
because recently i talked to my my tax
person and she mentioned that i should
probably um
like you know
like set uh
officially set who gets like my
my my money when i die you know i should
do it before i die
because it could happen anytime and then
um in the plane when yeah my will
exactly when when all the turbulences
were happening i was like [\h__\h] i didn't
set my will though
yeah [\h__\h] i didn't do it yeah i should
have done it earlier [\h__\h] i'm dying here
on my trip to the mountains and i was
also writing about my electronics
because i brought so many electronics ah
yes we kind of like split right
i tried to try to but then yeah the
stuff i brought we couldn't really use i
brought so many [\h__\h] electronics i
have free phones with me one of them is
a work phone to a private phones i
brought my [\h__\h] huge alienware
a gaming laptop which is really heavy i
brought a mouse i brought the blue yeti
travel microphone i bought the elgato
capture card i brought the switch
i hadn't brought my ipad yeah and my
headphones yeah they never brought some
some amplifier buttons
because we were missing like one thing
i'm missing one piece of course
technically i can use it but you can't
yeah
and yeah and then i got my switch
controller and some of the switch stuff
basically the dock was under my
responsibility yeah we need to dock in
order to stream so we might really uh be
streaming some switch games yeah it
would be a shame we didn't use it yeah
now that we brought it we have to use it
yeah what about the food though
on the plane and on the planet oh
it was okay
um yeah same that was also like okay i
didn't really eat much so it's funny
because like on the plane uh the second
plane uh to the mall divs
because it was like a three three three
so like one row has like six people and
then i saw everybody
everybody in the and on the plane
they're like a couple oh yeah
and then it's like
and then you know i was i was with this
one couple and then
our outfits kind of oddly matched like
really are we
we're temporary relatives
now oh yeah i noticed that two next to
me was also couple actually like i saw a
lot of korean couples oh right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe
maybe in korea the maldives are really
popular i wanted to say
but yeah
that was a trip but mostly i'll upload a
picture of that [\h__\h] cloud that
almost killed me i have a picture of it
yeah when we left i was like i gotta
take a picture of this [\h__\h] killer
clown man killer cloud
write a strongly worded letter to
whoever is controlling the weather maybe
combo
yeah and then uh we arrived i knew that
dana was already there early and the
moment i entered the airport you know
leave the plane and then go into the
airport i i noticed that i was like the
last one um in front of a like huge
amount of people standing for the
immigration yeah and i knew oh this was
going to take a while so i tried
connecting to my internet and tried to
connect
to to contact
and i was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i don't
know if i can make it for the seaplane
because on the website or generally like
um also on seaplane information
generally it said like either that like
at 3 pm or 3 30 pm or something like
that would be the last seaplane i think
because they can't do it
in the evening yeah it was really
worried because it was it was like i was
at the
immigration until three p.m
there was no line it was just like us
basically and then yeah it was awesome
did you get asked like a lot of things
what from who from the like from from
the from the like immigration no not at
all i was so nervous about it i was like
[\h__\h] did i really have everything that
they need from me what if what if they
want to do like a test on me and what
the [\h__\h] do i do
and then and then
it was fine i gave him like my passport
and then the
he didn't even look at my vaccinations
oh okay okay yeah
oh and i did i showed him my qr code
because you have to do like a
registration before going to the
maldives but really it's not a big deal
yeah and then after after he looked at
me he said take off your mess look at me
and like i'm glad this is me
and then he was like okay go detail what
that that's it
wait what was that game papers please
yeah i felt like wow i'm playing papers
please but i'm the person
yeah it was really not not that strict
as i thought it would be there are a lot
of worries that i had that were um maybe
understandable but then yet not
necessary and then i got my um
thankfully because i waited so long on
the immigration i got my um suitcase
quickly i ran out of there and i thought
later would be standing there waiting
for me
i was i was waiting for you the whole
time but that was the time where like um
the person was like yeah maybe let's get
your luggage and everything to the car
first and then come back
i insisted that i wanted to wait for you
but it was just not a lucky time but i
wrote to you like on what's up yo dana
i'm coming out now i'm i'm i'm done and
then i go out very slowly i look left
and right and left and right and i told
i showed lena a picture of what i'm
wearing and i think i really stood out
yeah the problem is i wasn't there
she wasn't there like what the [\h__\h]
where where is she
i it was just that little time window
see i was there for so long i was like
waiting for you you know the people
started like coming out right now
you know it's okay eventually um we
wrote like and one said where the [\h__\h]
are you and like
i'm on the left side i'm like where the
[\h__\h] which left side from which point of
view is the left side yeah
yeah finally we found each other and um
i'm sure people are curious of what our
first uh impression of each other was
what was your first impression it was
it wasn't really your first impression
but uh when you sent me uh you know oh
i'm gonna be wearing this i'm like well
our suitcase color oh yeah
yeah we have the same color suitcase
basically yeah
yeah yeah we have the same kind of
suitcase same size same size same color
so that was pretty interesting
it was um and and my impression is it's
it's nice to be able to hear bird boys
and likes around south
instead of their headphones
that's always still that's always like
my first impression ever like i see
somebody for the first time it was so
weird like obviously
you look exactly the way you look right
now obviously but but it was still you
know when you meet someone in real life
you look a little bit different only a
little bit maybe like huh we weren't we
weren't wearing makeup baby or something
like that something like that it was
like
venus voice coming out of
like where where am i hearing this from
where is the planet where it's coming
from
exactly
and it's like huh
it was like like we met each other and
we tried to give you tutor
and then and then reyna was already like
oh the the the hotel guys he's over here
he's over here and she tries to like
immediately bring me over and i'm like
wait wait wait wait wait i stopped her
for a moment because i'm like this is so
weird right now isn't it so weird
i'm sorry i didn't know
i was like wait wait we need to like
you know take like a moment to
realize what's happening right now
i'm sorry i thought
i didn't know i was just trying to make
us not miss the same place
the thing is about the
the hug and maybe my first impression of
dana is um
let's just say i was wearing high heels
that are like about 10 meters tall
so then it was surprisingly small
and i i i rarely hug like people that
are like smaller than me you know so i
uh
i tried with my 10 meter
i'm trying to hug her and she's like so
i'm wearing i'm wearing negative sandals
yes yes negative meter sandals yes and
that's what also maybe made the hug a
little bit awkward
some better hugs than every time
yeah
and then and then we went to the hotel
guy and he brought us to now he this is
now see this is how you this is how you
tangent you first start off really
really early with the plane and now
we're getting to the seaplane
yeah oh oh the first thing
what what was the first thing you
noticed after coming out of the airport
uh i was expecting
there to be more shops
oh my gosh
okay okay yeah yeah i thought i wanted
to buy some stuff yeah i wanted to buy
stuff and then you also told me right
yeah if you can like buy stuff and i was
like you know what i'm gonna like arrive
like earlier than you anyway so i'm just
gonna spend like plenty of time to like
shop and maybe i can buy some nice stuff
but then yeah i should have probably
researched better
wait they're in the malls they see
they're
[Laughter]
uh no the noise in the background is the
wave turn it off again the music then
you hear the waves
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
what's the waves guys and the wind the
wind is really strong
but yeah
um oh yeah when i got up you know i
i didn't know that for example when i
went to japan i i
like felt in the summer really humid
humid sound humid somewhere but um in
the maldives i expected it to because i
read that the weather is really humid
but i went out of the airplane and i
i felt it was really humid but it was
like a different kind of humidness from
japan right yeah it was it was close to
indonesia
that's why we don't go out much
i thought it was okay though i feel like
at least maybe maybe right now maybe
maybe the motives can get even worse and
hotter than this but i felt like
japanese summer was
way
worse like in the sense of it was
negative heat strokes you [\h__\h] i
can't take it but the moment is actually
it was nice but i immediately noticed i
was wearing sandals you know high heel
sandals with 10 meter um something
something
exactly yeah but i noticed immediately
that my toes were getting like weirdly
wet not sweaty but
quickly those are sweatiness they're
funny yeah so they brought us to like a
a special
vip lounge where we had to wait for the
sea plane we actually ended up having
way more
extra time right yeah so we just sat
there yeah we were drinking some
i was drinking coca-cola because i tried
to stay awake because um i ended up
having like two hours of sleep in like
30 hours in the course of 30 hours
um but
later was picking
herself some
multi vitamin juice and she was like
come open this can't open this no and
i'm like native no you okay because i
know that kind of bottle i don't know
that i mean i know that kind of bottle
but you know it's like not very common
over here over here i mean like over
where i live it's the kind of bottle
where you twist it and then it pops yeah
what she said
and it really it feels really good when
it flips so i was like
are you really that weak what the [\h__\h]
is happening so i take pain
but the second time i did it once i know
how to yeah no
so i opened the first one and then
rainer absolutely chucks it down really
fast and she already takes the second
bottle i'm like wow hydration damn girl
yeah hydration check everybody make sure
you guys are hydrating but you tried it
again and you didn't immediately get it
i said you have to like twist it to the
side until it pops and then you did it
and then i got it yeah it's the learning
process everybody i'm getting better
each time yeah you learned i'm surprised
that you guys don't have that kind of
bottle over there i mean we probably do
but it's like not the most common one
yeah
well now you learn something new i got
something new i learned the auto opening
um special bottles yes usually i'm the
one who asks other people to open my
bottle because when it's really strongly
closed
and you ask me to help you support your
seatbelt
oh yeah
in the seaplane and i couldn't close the
seat belt
oh so yeah we were we were chilling in
this in the in the lunch i was trying to
eat something we were like um talking
about all kinds of kinds of things
because this was the first time that we
um
were together like this in real life and
we chit-chatted a lot we were really
excited
and then finally the sibling comes
and
we board the plane it was funny because
i
there was like only like three steps
upstairs yeah yeah and it's so tiny it's
super tight
from the window right and then it didn't
look that
tiny from but it was tiny i mean there's
bigger sea plants but i was really
really small because it didn't stop at
any other islands it only went directly
to our island and it only carried like
we were like seven or eight people
i think inside
yeah and uh
we i thought i was gonna fall into the
water and i was stepping into the
zipline it was so tiny going through
that baby door and then the baby seats
everything was tiny and then elena
closed my seat belt
like yelling each other's ears and then
we're like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] and we put out
our whatsapps and we're typing in there
instead of yelling yeah
yeah it's like
[Music]
that was fun yeah it worked out it all
worked out in the end it was really
insanely loud because we maybe also
because like we were sitting uh at the
window seat right next to the propeller
but then there's also a propeller on the
other side yeah i don't think it's gonna
be whichever side you use
not that crazy
i mean
no i don't think earplugs would have
been
necessary but but you know if there's
earphones we can't hear each other
anyways yeah
yeah
it was just not made for talking so and
then we flew and and that was like elena
was getting quickly she was getting
really really tired and i'm like later
you already slept on the previous plane
you should stay awake so you can look at
the scenery
and then after like five minutes or so
i'm like where's the scenery it's water
it's water can i sleep now yeah the
thing was if you leave the maldives main
island then for a while i guess you
don't see that many islands no but then
a little bit later
again a little bit later we saw more and
more and more and more islands some
small ones
um yeah it was pretty you saw some
ah yeah they were pretty
and then we finally landed but oh don't
eat my hand
oh oh my god we landed so nice it was it
was pretty it was a smoother landing
than a normal plane on on ground i would
say
but then
once we were in the water
and trying to dock
the waves were so [\h__\h] strong it was
like a bounce house it was he was i was
like oh i was like closing my eyes at
some point because i'm like yeah i don't
want to like accidentally and they're
like
yeah when we got out of the thing like
we finally like stand up and stuff right
like i thought i was dizzy from all the
rocking turns out that it really was
rocking yeah so wildly yeah yeah it was
funny it was a nice experience first
time yeah it was so funny because like
they do provide that you know the the
reverse drinking bag
i thought you know in front of us was
also i think i'm pretty sure it was a
100 sure it was a korean couple sitting
around yes yes yes and the girl she
seemed like she was getting really sick
too i don't know
like she was like doing this right yeah
and then
the problem was she also had the huge
event the fan the fan right in front
right in front of her face like on the
second row it was fine but i can imagine
yeah in the first row it really annoyed
her she was holding like some paper in
front of her face yeah trying to
stop the all the wind going in her face
and it was she was not feeling so
well-liked
yeah
oh yeah i felt like are they okay i'm
wondering yeah the other person seemed
to be okay if i was like yeah
and we stepped out of the plane and we
were greeted immediately by a butler a
lady but look cute bunny yeah she's
really sweet
yeah and she was like mvp
yeah i'm gonna be a butler 24 7. and now
i'll bring you i'll give you a tour and
i'll bring you to your room and all that
so nice yeah
and then we um after walking over that
nice um
path over the water i was like i was so
excited i was like hopping over the path
what do you call that
yeah
the bridge looking thing yeah i was
hopping over like yeah yeah oh my god
we're hitting it and we did it oh my god
oh my god
and i was trying so hard to you know
cause i had a hat on and then so it was
so windy oh yeah it was only me i was
like you know i want to be i want to be
all carefree but oh my gosh
you know
i had a little story about the wind did
that happen today but later on oh yeah
we'll get there maybe i don't know it's
already been almost 40 minutes
maybe for next time maybe next time yeah
we can keep some stories today was
another funny day um but it's far from
over we're getting a massage later right
ah yeah i'm so excited like you know
like uh yesterday i was like oh my gosh
you know what i'm so excited about i'm
so excited about this massage
yeah we had like a choice of different
massages and elena was like which one
should we do
and i said how about this one we're
going to do a thai massage
because i i really like thai massage
because it's very strong but it's also
like they kind of stretch your body you
don't have to stretch it yourself um so
it's like a mix of massage and
stretching i really like it
and and we're gonna do it uh
at the same time i wonder if they put us
in the same room but thai massage is
usually with clothes
usually
i hope we can be in the same room i
don't know i think i'm going to be
falling asleep anyway
i don't know i always want to no matter
how relaxing it is i always want to stay
awake for massages because i really want
to take in
all the oh yeah all the kimochi
pressuring on my skin like i want to be
aware of that
but you know i'm just so bad i try to be
away did you know um yeah i had a
manicurist thingy and i fell asleep
never had a mannequin before
yes yes yes all right wait we already
went too far we need to go back again so
yeah
yeah and then we are right now everyone
you know where she brought us like with
the
with the what's the card oh yeah we we
went on like a tiny like uh the buggy
cart kind of thing like a golf cart like
yeah like a golf cart i was like yeah
yeah and then it's like oh
she showed us around like basically in
the resort there's like a bunch of
restaurants there's many restaurants
and they actually you know i didn't
think
but they already like actually booked us
like you know like yeah
i'm so sorry
there's so many restaurants but for the
first night our butler already booked us
for a restaurant and we were like oh
that's cool thank you for choosing for
us but the first one she chose was like
you know yeah it's four so for
tonight we have fancy sushi and sashimi
and i'm like oh oh
do they have anything else there she's
like so like no that one is delicious
and i want i want elena to enjoy it and
eat that but if they had nothing else
we're like okay maybe yeah i should go
somewhere
i don't have to eat yeah i would rather
like us so like uh they switched us to
know the restaurant yeah yeah yeah
yeah but wait we went to so she gave us
a tour and then we got to the room
and
and what did we do we didn't immediately
go to dinner we unpacked we unpacked i
did a little you did a lot
yeah i unpacked everything nicely my my
suitcase is empty for once
yeah yours still has some stuff in it
well i'm gonna grab you oh but she
showed it she also gave us a tour of the
room and we were both like screaming
because it's so [\h__\h] nice i'm sorry
for swearing but it's so exciting so
nice everything's so so you know like
the you have like a really big bathtub
yeah yeah it fits it's like a
freestanding bathtub like yeah it's not
on the wall it's in the middle of the
room and it's like it fits two people
yeah if it's two people it's so it's so
wild and then everything's and we have
two sinks two yeah yeah
and then and then i don't know like the
sinks are so cute too i don't want to
give too many details maybe i'll try i
took photos so i was planning on showing
you guys photos after the vacation so
you can see oh the rooms are so
beautiful
yes yes yes yes yes
yeah but we were jumping around and i
was like saying sorry to the butler girl
that i was acting like this but i'm so
excited and she was like it's okay
i guess she's probably used to it yeah
and she also said that like she she said
that she only works here for one year
and when she first came here and also
still now she's she's still like really
really is amazed by it i thought she was
would be used to it but it's not so not
quite the case yeah
and then um yeah we chilled we unpacked
and then we went to dinner and she
picked us up again with the golf cart so
nice we also have bikes but so far we've
only been using her with the golf cart
because we're too scared to get lost
yeah it's it's weird it's just you know
the whole island is one resort but um
it's just there's so many like
wraps yeah it's like there's like okay
now we're like over the water okay but
then like all the restaurants and all
that are on the on the main um
like island from the resort and there's
like a lot of like it's like a sorry
it's like a jungle there with like a lot
of palm trees and coconut trees and
small pathways that only fit the golf
cart yeah it's like a maze there it
probably looks better like during the
day more visibility but once it hits
night time it's i was like wow i think i
won't be able to go back but she seems
fine with picking us up i mean it's her
job though yeah yeah but we want to try
the bikes eventually hopefully not get
lost
any mosquitoes we haven't seen any i
haven't seen any actually
but but the rooms came with mosquito
repellent actually and the mosquito
repellent is indonesian yeah
so i had they never read it out for me
yes yes i also made her read an article
in german but you know it has nothing to
do with the vacation so oh yes that's um
yeah she was explaining something to me
and i was like i need to uh understand
this in german because it's too
complicated and she was like can you
read it i'm like why do you want me to
arena
every day that i hear germa okay yeah
i guess it's cool she was also when when
i was setting up the stream she was like
oh your discord is german oh this is
german okay yeah oh my god german
discord oh my god
because see i'm so used to using like
plain english
[Music]
i put down another app what was that
oh yeah when i installed a program on
this laptop for some reason it installs
it in japanese
yeah because i don't think it has like
an alternate language for the
installation thing
yeah yeah
okay that makes sense yeah but i have
everything mixed and that's confusing
yeah like it's not every day i see
german words
um
okay
let me look at my notes if i'm missing
out on anything if i forgot something
okay so i said i told her okay i'm not
often alone i'm not allowed to look she
drinks a lot i mean in sense of she
hydrates herself a lot but those
airlines yeah you can look
i can look okay elena arrived early got
stuff airplaned loud couldn't talk got a
bit sick on the landing very bouncy
greeted by a butler nice girl two for
seven minutes gave us a tour of the golf
course yeah there's so many things to do
on the island a lot of the things cost
good extra we're thinking about taking
some kind of
sports lesson maybe but it's pretty
expensive it's pretty expensive yeah
we'll think about it that's interesting
just for the experience um
uh we're both really excited about this
vlog it's gonna happen today and a
little bit uh our our thingy is really
pretty spacious elegant we made oh yeah
we said we made the right choice because
we were like yeah not sure about which
which hotel to book right yeah yeah yeah
and i was like maybe this one because
the photos they look that i don't know
the photos that i love they look the
nicest in my opinion yeah but then we
waited a week and we're like let's let's
decide in a week we need to think about
this yeah then we were still kind of
uncertain but i'm glad we chose this one
yeah the only problem i think of this
one is that it's so far away that we
have to use the
sea plane it's really expensive man
it's more expensive than the flight from
it's more expensive than the
normal plane
for me too it's crazy
oh well so backed up big enough for two
great hey i really i'm not missing
anything there's some fruit not oh yeah
besides the champagne they also have
like some like you know nice bowl of
lots of fruit there and for me it's
really fascinating because there was so
many fruits that i didn't even recognize
she was like is this a dragon fruit
he's that a dragon fruit oh my god
dragon fruit oh my god it looks so cool
but what is that i don't know what that
is
[Laughter]
yeah is that like a mango oh no it's
different
it's different it's different you have
to try it yeah i mean you could always
take it it's so cool because they have
like tropical fruit here that we don't
usually have in australia maybe do you
guys have it in indonesia oh yeah we do
damn we don't have that because we have
different weather i mean we import a lot
of fruit but
i don't really see
i don't know mangosteen i think if you
look for it maybe you can find it but
it's not very normal so there's like
mangosteens as much of a mango to like
you know grapefruit and grapes they're
different right they're totally
different yeah
true true true okay it makes sense any
durian or they not that we have seen i
don't want to i don't care about it
so okay oh yeah then it actually when we
arrived it was still like somewhat um
early the sun was going down and it went
dark so quickly
yeah and when she was explaining we
could still like see stuff outside yeah
once she's done we're like looking at
the window like wait why is it
completely dark that was only within 10
minutes yeah
and it was still so early we were like
oh the sun goes down so early here but
it's probably because of the monsoon
season
that it gets dark earlier like it gets
darker like way later if it's like super
sunny right yeah it was pitch black no
and then we went to dinner and you know
it was really nice that maze um
i said that it's like you know in the on
the main island where she drives us
through with the golf cart it's like a
maze but i think it would be so nice to
just take a walk there because there's
like lamps on the ground and some yeah
some they have some lamps on the trees
as well and there's these these thin
paths with those lamps on each side
it looks really really pretty it's so
pretty yeah at night like i'm kind of
nervous about walking around at night
like i know it's safe and all i'm just
gonna get lost yeah but like during the
day especially like because yeah um we
also went basically you know because the
day changed but maybe that story is for
another time basically it definitely
looks easier to navigate during the day
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh so for dinner we ended up going to
like
southwest like a mix yeah a mix of
southeast asia food it's pretty good i
liked it
ordered some things that she recommended
what did we order um like some chicken
satay that uh the thai dish with the
wrapped in the leaves yeah uh chicken
satay something something yeah
and something else that's something
something
i don't remember the names i thought you
would remember
yeah i don't remember because it's not
it's not really it's a chicken chicken
we we had chicken dinner yeah one of
them was kind of like yakitori
it was really good but different sauce
that yakitori would have normally
yeah peanut sauce was yummy and then we
had on the other one was the one wrapped
in the leaves and you know i think it's
really cool um we ordered those as
starters
and i was like worried about if i wasn't
with you i probably would have just
ordered something really safe basic that
i know what it is
but because you were there i was like
even if i don't like it you can eat it i
can i can have a trash can and you know
it wasn't
but i ended up eating it just fine
because it was so yummy and then on the
main course you had
i had what was it i just had meat i
think right
[Music]
wait what
a curry
uh
what was it
masala
no we're not muted anymore
yeah
so basically we had like a bunch of
curry right but like all of them were
like spicy yeah a lot of the choices
were spicy so i didn't have i wanted to
try something else but most of the
choices were spicy and i don't really
want to force myself to eat the two
spices that day i learned that you're
pretty sensitive to like spicy yeah like
even the you know the little side dish
that we had we had like some shrimp
crackers and then we had two two kinds
of sauce like the the
sweet chili sauce which is not spicy i
think and then [\h__\h]
sauce
like oh i think it's spicy like no i
mean i was that was still edible but i i
had about like you i sensed it to be
spicy i sensed yeah yeah yeah like in
the back somewhere but it was okay and
uh oh then we had some nice dessert and
oh we had nice mocktails really oh yes
yes i had the coconut
they looked so fancy the pink coconut i
think i had some raspberry mint mocktail
yeah
and we were chit chatting while doing
all that and we noticed like
the restaurant we went to was actually
um pretty
it looked it felt it feel it felt pretty
full i guess because not not every
restaurant was open so all the people
kind of went there
and uh you look around and on every
table there's a a
guy and a woman a girl and a boy couples
every table is a couple and then it's
just us
you know the girls having a nice girl
vacation
they know the flowers yeah they have
flowers on their toes i'm like one time
probably honeymoon those are probably
honeymoon yeah
but yeah it was
it was nice yeah it was just interesting
i even like you know on the plane i was
already feeling like
damn
yeah and then like i was kind of like
self-conscious in the
in the in the in the airport like in the
immigration because like everybody's
like yeah
you're alone and i'm like
yeah
and then maybe because i know i'm alone
i don't know what they think of me and
then uh this was past immigration but
like you know they have to before the
baggage claim they check you again right
it's like yeah and then that guy's like
so um what do you um so what's your
occupation i'm like i hate the class
nobody asked me that
oh i don't know maybe maybe they're just
like why is this person alone what's
that sound it's probably a seaplane this
probably isn't going to be allowed in my
earphones
it's not like they're asking me like in
a super like sassy interrogative thing
but it's just like
i know i'm the odd one out here you
don't have to make that obvious
you don't have to make that obvious
very difficult yeah the dildo airlines
they have a really [\h__\h] long loading
screen man yeah fix your internet man
oh well uh yeah and then we went oh yeah
we went back to the hotel room and
we just like
started to it was already pretty late
like 11 p.m we started to calm down and
we we did some social media updating i
locked reyna in the bathroom why didn't
you do that that was disgusting i was
just dead
whether it's like sturdy or secure i was
wondering like i saw the log outside and
i was like don't you have a lock inside
so i closed it outside and you were like
no there's no lock there's no walk
inside apparently no but the thing is
like it's like a bathroom and then in
the bathroom there's the bathtub and the
sinks and all that and then you go like
a room further and you have a shower and
you know the toilet which we obviously
don't use because we're idols but those
rooms those rooms have a lock just like
basically if you take a bath then
you can't lock yourself
yeah inside you know
but you know normally people come here
on a honeymoon and
probably they wouldn't care about like
talking about the bathtub having your
husband walk in while you're in the
bathtub taking a bubble bath you
probably don't really care you want them
to walk in on the other side so
you know like we have that window right
like you can definitely like if
so there are some some parts that are
although there's a curtains though oh
you can pull down the curtains there
oh yeah yeah if you wanted to but
usually um
i don't think elena would swim that far
to see
i mean you know that story is for
another year
oh and then um
you know i'll tell you something funny
about nina
she's like
we were like lying on the bed and just
you know both looking at our phones and
talking a little bit in between and uh
partially we're also like sitting on the
balcony first uh in the dark but just
listening to the wave sounds that was so
strong uh but then on the back we were
just chilling some more
and
and then i was just watching i was
looking for some things on my phone and
then suddenly rodayne is like
what are you doing
yeah oh i mean let me like you know
you're you're you're like we're
vacationing and you're checking your
phone huh you were checking no no no no
i'm checking your phone because you're
checking them all out
so i guess she's not going to talk to me
it runs off time but we're like about to
sleep and you know and but the thing is
i think she was waiting for it because i
was i told her that i was going to watch
netflix yeah i want to watch with you
and i'm like okay okay we can watch
together but i wanted some phone time
before the netflix time where's the
netflix i'm like and she's like get up
turn on the ipad i'm like okay
just give me a second
it's like it's like a like a child
telling her mommy i want the ipad
i want fun i want to watch some good
hospital comedy before i go to bed yeah
oh yeah so um i i i downloaded the whole
season of scripts you know for i thought
that maybe i needed on on the plane or
so but i ended up watching plane things
so
i didn't use my ipad so i still had this
whole season and i'm like
i don't know what you want to watch but
you mind watching scrubs with me and she
never watched scraps before no i've
never watched the book incredible i'm
like yo let's go you're gonna like it
you like to do it i liked it i
liked it
i didn't have a i didn't have a stand
for my ipad so we're just kind of like
collaborating with the huddled together
and then had a pillow standing there and
then the ipad against it and we were
helping hold the ipad up and launching
scraps for a lot i
i started falling asleep so she fell
asleep
she fell asleep i'm like what at some
point i woke up i'm like wait but i
think i missed a lot i think i'm
sleeping
and then okay then i'm just i'm gonna
stop after this episode because that was
also feeling like kind of sleepy watch
several episodes it was good yeah i will
watch more now one more thing i'm gonna
tell you guys
um
in the night first of all it was really
[\h__\h] loud i woke up in the night
several times the storm was so loud yeah
it was loud and
now this is one thing that dana probably
doesn't know
huh
fact number one
keeps on uh
scooting over closer
yes so i felt like i
i was very very very much on the edge of
my bed
i'm sorry i didn't want to push you back
and i still hadn't like for me there's a
lot of space is fine so that's okay but
then
but then
most of the night you were you were
looking towards me you know
not to the outside of the bed but on the
inside and then
suddenly
i
i hear you turning or something and and
reaching out your arm and suddenly
you poke my spine
and you went down like
no i i was trying to go to sleep the
whole time
i just did it for her that's why she was
laughing but yeah she like i don't know
i was like is she awake does she want no
from me because it felt like a poke like
hey quinoa wake up
but i look over and she's sleeping and i
was like
no no she just went like move your
finger a little bit on on my on my spine
i'm like what what's happening i was
wearing pajamas okay we're both wearing
pajamas
no i was like is she gonna move her hand
but then like she didn't move her hand
back he was like reaching out to me
stretched out with her finger i don't
know what what in
what you thought you were doing
i was sleeping i guess you told me you
told me you were like kind of awake in
the middle of the night yeah yeah that
was after
yeah at some point i got up and i i i
tried
i woke up i think i woke up because like
of the noise and then oh yeah five
minutes after i woke up from the noise
you were touching my back so i was like
okay i'm i'm wearing a wink now
i'm not awake
and it's right now
i wasn't
it's there
i was i was trying to sleep for like two
hours it didn't work so i got up and i i
i tried to turn the air conditioning a
lot a little bit quieter which worked a
little bit
and drank some water and then finally
finally after two hours of being awake
at 4 00 a.m uh-huh finally fell asleep
again and after that it was fine i slept
like a baby after that okay okay and
then we woke up
and
it was so nice because like we don't
have a tv in front of our bed sorry
sorry dude i have a tv in front of a bed
which is a little bit sad but yeah we
have
the whole ocean view yeah we have ocean
views yeah so we wake up and
finally it was bright outside
and you see this
ocean
in front of us just ocean you know no
houses or nothing in front of it just
ocean
uh-huh was so nice so nice the waves the
wind yeah
and the weather was actually pretty
clear when we woke up so i was like oh
today might be the day right now it's
clear as well it already rained like
several times so the weather report is
absolute [\h__\h] if you go to the
maldives during monsoon season even the
weather report for the coming four hours
is [\h__\h] don't believe anything in
the weather report it changes the whole
time
unpredictable tropical monsoon weather
yeah so i don't i'm not going to look at
the weather report anymore right now
it's sunny i want to go into the water
me too i was thinking like you know
before the stream it was really getting
warm and i'll say hey kiara like light
on the hammock it's really nice oh let's
do it let's do it ah that's just uh the
the memory is uh the chat just died but
we can look here we're gonna end it now
anyway because we wanted to do one hour
what about the
are we gonna do that oh the kids
exchanged okay okay okay okay
well well
i think loki has a pinch what i'm
getting what i got her because i asked
her for her sizes yeah yeah yeah i was i
don't know if you heard that story if
any viewers told you about it but um on
one day when i was shopping um for
myself i i saw like necklaces with like
initial
initials on it and i was like i kinda
wanna get that so i asked the lady i
thought maybe it was too tacky so when i
was asking the lady to search for an r
for dana uh
like i was getting nervous maybe maybe i
shouldn't get it and she was looking and
looking and looking and looking and
after five minutes she tells me oh sorry
actually we don't have r and i'm like
okay maybe that's good okay okay okay
okay because i didn't get your dad and
then i kept on thinking like i wanna
give lana something
something something no not something too
boring
and then i figured
you're probably not gonna wear it
ever unless you get to austria
yeah hi
okay here comes the gift exchange please
open please open
i hope the size fits though otherwise
you have to get it like maybe oh yeah
changed a little bit how do i open this
kfp i think knows when i got it
what is this
have you ever seen uh austrian german
traditional clothing ah it's called a
danda
so it consists of the the overdress with
the corset and then there's a under
blouse oh
is it supposed to be that shirt because
yeah
and then it's a an apron
and i think that's so that's it yeah
that's the whole outfit you can wear it
with like high heels and and you uh yeah
you need to
put all that together i wonder if it
fits you guys i got her at the the
colors odena blue
yeah the whole candle is blue with some
roses maybe she will upload a picture on
on twitter maybe oh no i messed it all
up it's okay oh look i want you to put
it on now
okay you want to put it on wait no but
i'm wearing the swimsuit yes
yeah we're both in bed
[Music]
but i need to tell you like
think
there's like a
difference like the one i got you it's
more like a fashion dandel oh yes yeah
so
um
there's like way more
proper ones that are really really
expensive this is this is just a fashion
dental okay but if you want if you ever
come to us from germany germany you can
still wear that it's totally legit
there's there's like an oktoberfest
there's a lot of girls wearing the kind
of fashion dental too the difference is
that the fashion ones are usually a bit
shorter
and and the fabric is a little bit
lighter and all that
wow
yeah i hope i like it
you know i ended up getting something um
really small for you but like
yeah i actually like soda to like you
know um
people like my relatives and stuff but
it was like kind of too
last minute i think
i went a little bit overboard with my
thing
and then they were like
you're so dumb why didn't you like give
her like basic or something because like
you know indonesian pattern
yeah yeah i know um it i mean like this
is your scarf like yes it's just it's
this kind of i remember you girls
talking about it in your outfit reviews
yeah and they're like oh no like like
make a fancy outfit out of it i'm like
oh my gosh why am i so stupid
it's not the last time we meet you can
still make it if you want
because of course but mine is very very
small
it's so nice i want to see like i asked
you your favorite color but then yeah
look at this at least yours has proper
packaging mine didn't have a proper
package
it's a cute little pink box but i want
to take a photo before i open it i want
to upload on twitter
with all the cables around
all the cables so
and i'm taking a picture for you guys
there's like an owl on the tag and then
there's there's something behind it too
oh
oh cute
yeah
your your doodles are so cute
there's like a little doodle of us i
don't want to put it like that yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay
yeah it's just something small i'm like
i ran
that's all yeah you told me your
favorite colors like basically uh okay i
don't know how to open that open with
your teeth maybe with my teeth
there's like a like a double ribbon on
here yes
trying to
untie the present we're getting there
we're getting there
also maybe you guys saw on twitter but
um today we had like really nice
breakfast the first breakfast yeah
healthy breakfast even though it was
insanely windy we chose to sit like
outside right in front of the water the
lowest front the closest to the water i
just wanted to have that special
experience you know and it was nice we
got some nice food okay i'm opening it
opening it it's um it's it's it's oh
it's a bracelet oh it's so pretty yeah
it's like uh it's like strawberry like
rose quartz kind of thing that bird
isn't that like that one that that like
kind of floats oh yeah
yeah what do you call that bird i know
how this is like uh the one that's
always on the hibiscus um is that a
hummingbird hummingbird yes yes little
pretty yeah and there's like a spare you
know if you want to change the
hummingbird with something else i think
there's like yeah i i put it like really
i like the hummingbird thing okay
yeah
that's like the default thing that they
came with but
i think the hummingbird i don't like the
hummingbird
the stones are so nice it's pink wait
i'll take a photo of that
oh thank you
so girly
it's so girly
girly
[Music]
now kelly also gave me a bracelet now i
have a it's funny that it happened twice
because now everybody gives you
bracelets
how do they say that do you know that
meme uh-huh if i had two
eyes yeah if i had two nickels for every
time um a girl gave a reachable gave me
a bracelet i would have two nickels now
it's funny because it happened twice or
something like that yeah yeah yeah
yeah
is that is it um is
for for like a ring i would be careful
yeah yeah yeah thank you
i like
so relieved
like at least you know don't feel bad
about yours because yours i can actually
wear all the time but the one i gave you
is like very specific
yeah that's what i'm thinking i wanted
like something light and then you know
you might wear and even like you know if
you can't wear it then you can keep it
like somewhere safe somewhere safe i
will wear it again
we're going to hang out on our
water over water balcony i want to sit
on the hammer yeah and then we're going
to get a moustache and enjoy the rest of
the day guys uh-huh and uh tomorrow the
day after tomorrow we're gonna stream
again and we'll try to let you guys know
as soon as possible it might be the next
one might be on lana's channel guys so
keep an eye out for that okay
that's
pretty much it hope you guys enjoyed our
chit chat about everything that happened
so far not not quite everything but
okay okay okay okay
oh sorry oh my god our setup is really
super scoffed yeah the setup is unstable
but at least the the internet will
stabilize the stream
the us glass and frames is only
1.0.1 so it's actually okay wait where
is that i dropped frames uh bottom
bottom there i didn't ask are you
reading it in german asking that's in
their frames oh yeah i never look at
that it looks good right listen to
frames there's 72 yes come on wow the
things you can do with five gigabytes
upload and download
i'm not even five man
yeah there's probably gonna be more
reports coming eventually
it's still it's like the second
day ish yeah kind of the first one if
you were i guess yesterday was just half
a day yeah half a day i guess so yeah
so stay tuned about nice it's been great
so far even though you know
i have to say i was very very very
worried about the weather and yes it is
stormy but it's not like i couldn't get
into the water today i already
yeah i already went into the water today
and i think i'll be able to go again if
i want to it's just stormy but at least
it's not impossible too i wanna
do you want to talk about it no that's
for another child okay again
keep it keep it for another time
more stories on clumsy dana later coming
soon
thank you everybody we're gonna enjoy
our vacation
and i'll see you soon also there was a
little video up if you want to see us on
the
beach uploaded a little
video
please please
on my channel you can see the short one
although i wanted to upload the
different version i uploaded the
unedited version which i guess was fun i
wouldn't say honestly like i i didn't
see the end result right like i couldn't
tell i thought it was like oh okay it's
supposed to look like that all right the
end result wasn't much different i just
added subtitles and and like cut the
beginning and the end a bit nicely
and now there's an awkward laugh at the
end
i thought it was endearing it was fine
oh that was by the way
when we were in vr chat and i was like
yo can we like quickly take some things
from my channel for later to upload
during the vacation i'm like sorry guys
i'm gonna go grab some ocean and bird
puns and then i told raina what to say
and you probably felt when you were
saying it you were probably thinking
[\h__\h] this
this is not funny and i'm like it's okay
the unfunniness will be the funny thing
about it yeah yeah so embrace embrace it
let's go yes i'll go down like i like it
with the laughs see okay thank you
good good now
okay i'm feeling very humid i i want to
go into the water yeah me too
um but uh i guess i can't can i of
course you can okay
all right the fifth no how much was it
it's [\h__\h] floating it's so expensive
to buy things here
mine was
how much were they like oh it was over
50 because you're mine was 90. 90
[\h__\h] dollars us dollars
for uploading that honestly on amazon
would probably just cost you like 10.
it's insane they we went into their
shops and they have some crazy prizes
you bought a
she bought a phone you know those
plastic water phone cases and it was
fifty dollars fifty dollars did you get
that for five dollars somewhere even
less sometimes i mean like technically
like it's nice that they kind of have
everything but yeah on the other hand
it's better for you to like yeah bring
it yourself if you can yeah
yeah this this is the problem that you
like on a resort island if you want to
shop outside of it a seaplane costs 700
us dollars
so it's cheaper to buy on the island i
guess but it's [\h__\h] expensive here
it's so expensive either way
i mean you know it's not like we have a
choice at the moment right so it's like
all right our choice would have been to
not buy floaties at all
but i wouldn't survive without floaties
i won't
but i haven't looked at me
oh yeah that's really damn she has a big
scratch from
yeah
yeah something basically when i was
swimming
from the ladder uh but i wanted i wanted
you know those those the tube the ring
tube thingy that's just really that's
chill i like that yeah we saw some other
okay
[Music]
i wonder how you say it in the maldivian
language oh yeah i don't know any data
altogether
like a dish from mom
no no no don't hit me five times in
german no no
very educational spirits in germany
thanks guys for coming bye bye
bye bye
thank you
[Music]