[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
do
oh that was a lot of excitement
i am so excited today i was listening to
a lot of mozart
um
yes
no i'm sorry
oh yeah i do like mozart mozart is such
a genius
oh
thank you he's my bff
oh wow but
i mean
the last
the f and bff
i'm not sure since he's
probably yeah
he's been dead for a while not probably
yes yes he's been dead for a while
but bff yeah we used to be friends i i i
was marie antoinette in one of my
previous lives oh wow
yes
no wonder your party outfit's so fancy
oh thank you fabulous well um
nice to
meet you cronie
yeah
nice to meet you
collab one on one oh yeah oh my god oh
my god you look like me you look like me
hey
it's like that one spider meme actually
no you were why do you have more armor
than me why is your skirt black is this
like what happens when you play online
and you play the same character
character they look a little bit
different
wait what because i don't know what
you're wearing
i'm wearing my my red skirt you're
wearing a black skirt
do you
what's your what's your armor i'm
wearing studded leather
oh
uh wait what was that
what was the enhancing button again
inventory
no no
oh god i was like
team
[Music]
um
pressing all the buttons i want the
enhanced button
there it is it was fp
no f
f
yeah
oh zoom
zoom
yeah we're wearing the same we just have
different colors of our bottoms
i think this is so that we can just like
so that we don't look too similar
really i think mine was crazy like this
really yeah really oh i think it's
because of our
boots
oh oh maybe
let me take off my boots i'm wearing
chain boots
oh
my boots don't change ah cuz
okay you're uh mine don't change my
looks but your looks are changed by your
boots yeah
the mystery has been cleared up
well well well these super strong super
talented
amazon girls are going to slay some
disgusting monsters outside there in the
world we're probably not gonna
get that far but i just thought it would
be cool to play
together because crowd you started
playing it too right where's your
where's your sense of optimism we could
get far
no we're not gonna get far but that's
okay
um
have you already
like taken like accepted the quest the
first quest from
here
of course the radiments lair act two the
first one
yes correct
oh you have it but you didn't start it
yet right no
then we shall do it together
we gotta go into the sewers
sewers okay louise are you using
mainly the bow or mainly the spare
uh mainly the bow
me too
ay
i tried to last time i played i tried to
switch
uh but i i don't know i don't think i
did a good job at switching
i think w switched yeah
yeah but it's just like i can't think of
it i keep on attacking them on close
combat with my bow
so i appreciate it but i heard you're
not very good at the game that's good
but you know the the point is to have
fun um
yes yes i'm already lost dude with you
you're in this dude
yeah yeah but
you're dead
what yeah
is that his name
yeah
no no you have a dude
it's it's a it's a girl or is that mine
shouldn't be mine no no girl is mine her
name is anna
yours is a dude
yeah his name is
niraj
mirage yeah okay me maybe adder and
no love can be a couple
oh already that's a that's a quick
shipping that's sailing okay um
and about yeah before we go are you like
do you have like potions and stuff you
good
is your inventory empty we gotta
probably sell a million things i hate i
hate the fact that oh i heard that you
had issues with like the inventory
because if also because of your ocd
it's just just a teensy little baby
i can understand though it's so where
are you going it's so triggering do you
want to sell things
it's like in the middle
find it sell selling places in the
middle here i'm trying to buy for a
stash
because that's where i usually pour here
here here here yeah
plus yeah okay
you have some fancy things in your stash
are you hiding diamonds in this stash as
well crony
i saw you hiding diamonds in the
minecraft stash what do you what do you
mean i don't i don't know what you're
talking about you started and then you
you didn't want chats to see for what
reason
oh
just you know
i guess
wouldn't they be like amazed that you
have a lot of diamonds why why are you
ashamed crony it's it's not about being
ashamed it's more like uh
you know i might give
people bad ideas of chats like oh you
know they have uh cronie has this in
this kind of armor set so
you think they're gonna tell someone
else and that person's going to steal
from you no way
potentially
no who do you think the girls are
no no no
woman did take some stuff from me but
she didn't she didn't know it was my
stuff she thought it was automatically
generated but i think by now she knows
she knows your boxes are your boxes no
it's gonna steal from you you're
paranoid crony
just a little teensy bit i mean after
after what happened with um
[Music]
iris
um
oh oh irish stole from you for real
sauce no iris
i i hope not but
follow me by the way
right yes i can't multitask um
where do i find um the potion
oh you want to buy potions uh
perhaps other does decker no good
evening deckard's useless no potions
lysander you
what do you have trained he has potions
[Music]
iris explode everything says chad
iris like make your things go boom
boom
not
egg
[Music]
i
i can't remember off the top of my head
a secret yeah you of course you can't
remember you snuck
i'm sure you know exactly what happened
you remember
hey let's not sort the details you're an
interesting type of person crony i need
to get to know you more
you're mysterious
yes thank you um but my sense of
direction is very horrible
thank you
thank you i think the sewers is it is it
the the this this place here
oh sue it's level one yes i actually
when i played the
the alpha
the closed alpha from this game
um i went past this point i already did
the sewers
in the alpha but um that's pretty much
all as far as i got off those the sewers
and a little bit more okay
okay
let's dude
let's find what are we what are we doing
uh find rather man's lair in the ah yeah
it's a hammer i think it's a hammer
i usually just go around hoping that
i'll find something at the end of it
no we have to fl i remember we have to
fight someone who has the hammer i think
he stole it or so
wait where'd you go oh there you are
i am the one that looks like you
it's sisters
or the enemies
it's kind of peaceful here you need to
make a party what
let's stand still cronie cronie
we need to make a party
can i make a party
i'll help you
die
ah
accept oh now we're gonna party uh so
now we share exp a lot oh and i guess
quest items oh [\h__\h] oh man i'm i'm
poison oh you radioactive
radio ragnan
in the middle of the enemies maybe do
some more kindness
against uh what's what's her name uh
yeah
i thought it was pretty damn good
i think really it was so sad
no this is a great job at kiting i i
wasn't able to do the kite thing that
well
you're gonna be my kite bunny cronies
hide those enemies take that damage yeah
why is anna are not fighting [\h__\h] can
you fight tell us
yeah i had the same problem with
another girl named amplista
are you collecting
um
grand charm hey i can't forget
wait how does this
how do we share items there should be
like a random um
like item goes into a random person's
inventory thingy really
there's no as i'm saying there should be
as we need it because otherwise i'm
gonna pick up better everything like the
greedy [\h__\h] i am what's a squelch
eh eh first to pick it up to get it okay
well crony um
first who sees it
finders keepers i see okay yes
let's go it's just just fair
you want to go there oh you want to go
there
because i think that place is blocked
off
wait what's going on
combat shine
can also only one person take the convex
rhino are you
kidding me
i'm sorry
how do you play
the apple together when when you can't
decide when when you play with greedy
people this is like a cooperative
competitive game
okay i'll give you more things because
you're kohai now i need to take care of
you
oh dear those are big oh damn
i didn't have many
oh crystal sword
crystal sword whoa
oh that looks fancy
get out
i hate going back to the town
to sell items so much so
at least now we have two inventories
until oh god i'm poisoned
oh this is bringing back bad memories
it's okay
oh yeah and dario was poisoning too yeah
how long did it take you too
shrine for you oh yay
how long it took me to kill on dario
yeah
uh chet how long did it take me oh my
god there's a lot of enemies
chad tell me
i do not remember it's been so long
wait did you play a didn't you play it
two months ago or so
it feels like five months ago
five months really there's a trident
crony
and the wolf head you take that i have i
don't have space
oh no i'm over burdened again and out no
i didn't take me an hour what are you
talking about you did it really fast i i
rc what does that mean i i rc
if i recall correctly
oh
i can't take the rest
do you want to take the trident
yeah
but we should probably go to the city in
a moment
that city
first try did i first try
i think like in the outfield
i had some troubles
uh
but then when i did it again after the
alpha i did it first try maybe oh wow
yeah but that doesn't mean anything it
was a horrible fight
no wait just kidding no i think it was
actually really not that bad now that i
tried to think back
i was probably not that bad have you
played the original before
when i was like
nine years old or so my mommy she's a
gamer and she loves diablo too she could
probably totally um lead us for the
whole game and play the like she will
how do you say it as she could um
she could carry us yeah and but so i saw
him playing and then sometimes i would
play around i wouldn't get very far but
my mommy was playing it i would play a
little bit but most of the game was
really scary so i couldn't play very
much
which very scary could
what was the name
what was this oh my god oh god what was
the name of the
the first that i never could get past
the first the one in the graveyard uh
chad help me graveyard blood raven yeah
you remember the first
boss that you have to kill
oh
yeah the one in the graveyard
i could never get past that one so
i was quite the chicken gold clothes
clothes
seem very excited about the goal
teamwork crony teamwork
teamwork i don't know
golden yeah
let's go
should we go back should we go back is
your inventory full yet it is full
yeah mine too kinda yeah i should kill
these
skeleton
boys
i think we're doing great so far yeah
this is a lot better than whatever my
playthrough was
it's more fun playing together than
playing alone
yeah there's a lot more action
yeah
it's so fun this is
i i i know that diablo 2
is kind of like
like online play
is what it's known for but people really
enjoy about it but i never played it
online until now yeah um i played the
i'll go through
oh it's damaged
it's damaged
i take the gold you take the damage
level
okay i'm so sorry i'll stop i can't stop
i'm a bird i like shiny things i can't
help
like oh you can take it and it's damaged
guns
are you able to use my portal oh yeah
anyway
like sell some stuff
i get to save scrolls nice
yeah the next one you're gonna open okay
it's only there okay always identify
first
i want that night
that's pretty cool
you know the problem with us being the
same class is that if we get bows and
stuff that are good then we gotta fight
over it but no we don't have to fight
over it i already collected it so
did you get a good one
i got a better one than my current one
yeah
damn i got a golden um arrow that is uh
two hand damage five to twelve my
current one is
two to nine
and it got enhanced damage maximum
damage one two three fire damage poison
damage fire resist
do you want my old one
ah
no i think i'm
good but you know what i'll sell it it's
better than yours two to nine
no
i think mine's a little better
but i can sell it
[Applause]
you must wait a short time to trade with
that player but why
oh i could just drop it on the ground
since we're the only ones in the game
true you have to accept the the trade by
the way oh
check
okay
thank you for cleaning up my inventory
that was all i really wanted
thank you i'm so hashtag blessed
going well so far
using cronie to get more items
just you wait
yeah i'm gonna be salty if you get a
great item that i want them
okay ready to go back where was the
portal
down here yeah
well
seems uh you're not going to hold back
on getting all your items so no no no no
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
here's zoomer level three come down
where'd you go
i went down to the one level three
oh i think the portal resets uh when you
enter the portal
oh
are you not here with me
no
what
wait i i i need to oh so we can both go
to the portal to go back to the city but
we cannot both go back here's another
one i opened one but where is it for you
so
okay you are what the hell
so weird maybe it doesn't close as long
as you don't
enter the portal okay i need to go after
you if i call if i open the portal then
i also need to be the last one to enter
it
okay
well we got that's all
understandable
like
my sucker
died
it's a shame that they're all skeletons
why because they're monsters they just
kind of burst open and die and there's
that satisfaction of oh interesting
thoughts man
i'm so sorry
oh yeah let's go
i found the ring crowney
you found a ring
and i already took it
i see
oh oh oh my god i'm so sorry why am i
hurt why am i hurt because i'm the
phoenix and you shouldn't get too close
i guess oh wait i think we have arrived
because the quest lock updated oh god oh
god oh god no don't die karoni don't
kill rap oh god oh god
oh
i'm not ready
not ready for what uh just
hold that
just everything
where'd you go
did your dude die
oh oh you're already fighting though oh
god no you're not gone
[Music]
where are you where are you
where are you
where'd you go
where did you go
why are you over there
why are you somewhere else
here
dude i didn't tell paul i'm keeping him
alive for you
i don't know how much longer i can take
oh god oh no i have to kill him
it was right there it was just around
the corner and then you went in the
opposite direction i think
that's mine
oh there's a long ball but it's blue you
can take that
what's happening
he didn't really uh drop any good those
what is that what are the books of
skills carry anymore of course take one
i'd pick one
okay
book of skill
uh
return to
we did it we did it
oh look at this oh wow fancy you'd like
somebody
yum
right okay
horadric squirrel what's that
what is that exploding arrow what is
that don't you want to take it
i have no more space i mean i can't get
rid of that
wait where is the shouldn't you take a
scroll as well because i already took
one
oh i mean i did oh really oh okay that's
the case wait did you get the book as
well
yeah you can get a book if you right
right-click it then you can learn a
skill for free
yeah i got exploding arrow
oh that's what you mean ah
okay what should i get i already have
exploding arrow i think um
what is the quest item oh that's the
quest item that's the horadric
now quest already updated uh what should
i go for
i can't use it
never ignore the passive and magic skill
they tell me
yes yes
yeah if i ignore them um like
[Music]
a voice you have a chance to dodge enemy
missiles when attacking or standing
still
nor hold on
i already have exploding arrow i'm free
okay
because i'm overburdened again
i mean i
can't it's okay we could just open up a
portal and we can just higher level
enough okay
okay i'll make a portal
okay
yeah yeah
wow
already did the first thing crowning
yeah
so easy
indeed
atma is here
up up yes
they say that the taste of vengeance yes
vengeance yummy
sweet i find it to my liking
in addition to my thank you at my
attitude i have spoken on your behalf
with the rest of the townspeople
the merchants have agreed to show their
gratitude i want wares and services for
freedom this is at lower rates
i mean
that's expecting too much out of these
people
huh i'm the phoenix empress okay
yeah they they
they don't care about classes here
they're just more like i need money i
don't care if you're the king or
hey
what is what is the scroll though
what is that you show it to
oh oh it's completed i guess now we dump
it
ah oh the deckard kane wants to see the
scroll
oh the one that i'm talking to
oh
[Music]
hope you guys have lightning resistance
what do i see what do i hear crony
doesn't read lord by the way oh you
never read the text that they tell you
[Music]
oh all i see right now are horadric this
roderick
it's it's because
perhaps because you're with your senpai
who makes you nervous you can't focus
rogic this herodrick that what
uh okay
um
we were so quick we can already do
another one uh the hierarchic stuff
search the halls of the dead under the
dry hills for the cube search the maggot
lair under the fire oasis for the shaft
searched the claw viper temple for the
headpiece this is the one that i was
trying to do
until last until the very last moment
when the uh closed alpha was happening
but about to close down i think this was
the one i was doing oh my i was in the
maggot player i think but i had i was
ugh we're gonna have a pain uh in the
ass looking for this place in the first
place because i remember i was looking
for like an hour to find it
oh joy
oh
oh pretty rain
cold resist is it gonna be cold where
we're going
maybe i should save up on this skill
which one
i have one skill choice yeah
um i have three in explosion
is it good so
yeah it's very good
okay we can make everything explode
together
hell yeah
yeah
yes then
[Music]
he changed
to tony what was the what was the p
again to put things into the
hot
hot bar
oh uh you need to drag the items in
first
like in the first slot and then you can
just shift click
oh
ah
also at first i have to fill these up
yeah yeah
it was really like how that works it's
such a pain especially when you're in
the middle of a boss fight and you run
out of the items there right
you fill it up while you're fighting
that's what you were doing with and
ariel i saw that
such a pain and then i dropped my bow by
accident that was fun
oh no
all right
oh
i guess let's let's go wherever the exit
i guess let's go here find something
what are we looking for
i'm not even sure what are we looking
for freedom
different places
i think you took that
no no good for you you take what you
saved well you can get
whoa
my god
yeah that's why we need electro
thingy yes try to not get killed crony
just don't die got it
is the btm too loud by the way guys
how's the volume i didn't even ask you
guys yet
fashion
no more fountain
oh no
[Applause]
don't look at it for too long it's okay
okay uh balance seems fine it's fine
okay oh good
oh good wow
what do you
call this uh it's a it's a oh
when when you got a
uh
it's something something world uh eats
eaten
something
what do you call that
[Music]
there are so many electric stuff i'm so
confused
a dog eats dogs
yes doggie dog world
oh doggy dog world that's what i wanted
to say wow
why is it suddenly bullet hell
right
oh you you took that gold okay okay i
mean i mean there's so much gold around
here it's okay all right what is this
head
there's a dungeon no it's nothing it's
just getting ahead of itself
in the right direction
yes um
how how long has it been welcome to holo
talk with cronie um how long has it been
thank you for it
since you joined a whole alive
like 30
four months now
oh
so short it feels longer than that
does it yeah yeah
i mean time does fly
just
you lose track
light healing
i'm gonna take everything
this is a very um
doggy
uh panicky hollow talk
how did you like the
the holo myth outfits huh
the new elephants
yo it's so nice it's so nice and the way
you guys prepare for it
like some of the speculations um with
the art
like the outfit
was pretty accurate
kind of surprising yeah yeah
for especially for gouda i think most
were super accurate
um
and also inna's
yes
she has
big i think
because of like the type of streams that
she does a lot of fellow artists um
became her fans and then
whenever she does like outfit
predictions
all these super high level super cool
talented artists give it a try
and they just provide the best best art
ever it's fascinating
all right
i was just standing in it
you're stepping up your game i see i see
disgusting dinosaur birds
darn
don't mind me
what that was the matter with them
they're just
walking around
like
weird little thing
there we go that was easy
anyway i actually the topic that i
wanted to
um
kind of go for was
if crony
were to get a new outfit
let's say a casual outfit because i
think that's the first thing you guys
need a casual one
uh what would you want it to look like
roughly like do you want something like
really
realistic like a knit uh sweater and a
cute skirt that's like
the i don't know um
a checkered pattern or whatever i don't
know what what would you imagine you
would want to go for
i wanna i want to imagine you in those
clothes
casual outfit
if it's casual probably
like just regular
jacket like a jean jacket jean
oh denim girl
you know casual i like those
i want to see you in denims yo
oh like you're already extremely skinny
but you in skinny jeans damn
imagine her skinny
jeans hall of the dead is this where i
need to go uh
huh you guys this is where we need to go
nice
going
what oh
there we go i'm poisoned
okay so crony in in skinny jeans that's
something i want to see too
do you have any other
outfits in mind though
yes
um
one thing now that we have casual and
now that we also have a elegant party
dress
i do kind of want uh
to make everyone's dreams come true uh
since i am from austria
i want to have a dandel our traditional
traditional outfit yes yes
i want to have a dandel are they just
gonna endlessly
get out of there
yeah but i think it's gonna take a long
time until
i am able to present that to everyone
um yo that would be so cool to see
yes standalones are so cute i think
they're
one of the
most attractive traditional clothings a
country has
are you sure there's no bias involved at
all
perhaps
yes
you're not gonna agree with me no either
i agree like it is
it's really nice the colors and all that
it's just
it really pushes your boba
holy moly your your milk jugs would
overflow when you wear it
yes you're made you literally made for
dandel oh fan art please guys please
wait already now it's all good
wait what let's swear i mean
i had to think of noise senpai
because oh yeah
he's a milk queen with the
with the cow
extras that she has for her casual
outfit i'm not i'm not just pulling this
completely out of my butt
she has she has cow accessories for her
casual outfit okay this is true this is
true yes yes did you see that she
actually did get a an outfit inspired
after a
german gender
oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah that looked kind like really nice
yes but it is uh like i think it goes a
little bit more in the japanese
um
stylized dandel
i would want it to be
more
accurate if i do it since i am from
there
i want it to be very accurate i think
noelle's was also a little more of like
fantasy themed
and she's from whole life
yeah yeah yeah what was that it looks
yeah fantasy
really cute on here
uh what was different like notably
different from the usual
the the patterns used and the and some
of the shapes for her dress are just not
accurate um but that's okay like i'm not
saying like this is not okay or so yeah
yeah yeah it's just more towards like a
cosplay um
cosplay of a daniel rather than a real
dandel uh it's like a i guess like a
like a dandel inspired outfit
yes
oh that was anna
how do you get out of the poison
it's okay
probably dead uh oh
oh she's still alive that's unexpected
mine was always that was your dude you
didn't hire him back
did he die and then oh yeah
oh yeah he died
wait now i found the proper word pop
cultural dandel yes i guess so that's
probably a good way to describe oh pop
cult
[Music]
yes yes
you would look cute in one too
crony
and
you as well
of course chain gloves chain gloves
soon we should perhaps
go to
uh
where's the door
go back to the city soon
and the map says there's ah there it is
oh
nice
oh my goodness
oh my goodness rooney would look cute in
most things yeah that is true
but everyone would
i want to see you in a white knit
sweater and then uh skinny blue jeans
oh
yes it's simple but it's so charming i
think help
i think it would look really nice help
where are you
no don't take that don't take that don't
take that i'm trying to organize
i took it let's go back into the city
yeah
come back alive
we should go to the city and you can
hire back
yeah with this dude oh
grace who goes there yes 900 are you
kidding me
yeah it's expensive i'm gonna keep him
alive
should i lend you some money my dear
kohai oh no it's okay i am
rich and hard
okay also i think i have money
who who's going to heal me okay thank
you
how much money did you get
uh
i have 20 000
money oh
i'm loaded
shiny things
yes great things yes but i i don't see
them uh although like the sapphires and
diamonds and all that i keep them
for whenever i will ever need them i'm
not selling them
a ruby
wow
wow okay
i do not need the stamina potion so get
that out of the way
[Music]
rod
beautiful
okay
sorry i'm organizing um yes oh no
problem
me too
[Music]
understandable look at that i don't want
crowning to go crazy here oh crony could
you
um next time you play minecraft if you
want uh i was looking for someone to
organize my my my chests in like oh
really
you do that for fun don't you yeah is it
is it really messy
um
it's young it could definitely use some
organizing
ah okay okay oh my mom by the way is
also
extremely
experienced when it comes to minecraft
and i think she would um be super
excited when if she would see your
bunker
oh yeah i mean she loves minecraft
yeah yeah yeah she seems to be
a gamer
she is a gamer yes
okay are we ready to go back you should
go for the portal first
already ready
this this one this one
i think is it
what is this
this
bed level three yes okay
here we are
back again
right into it
what a [\h__\h] surprise the explosion by
the way
ah here
the exploding arrow is amazing are you
using it did you switch it yeah
okay
good
oh here's a dude that's reviving them
don't you dare no reviving no no only
phoenix can do
you know crony when when you were first
announced and i saw that you were
well timed
um
i thought that
you know we had some connection because
i'm the eternal phoenix but then
everyone grouped you with ammet and i
was like
why
for me
i guess it's the first spot that yeah
you should be grouped with ammo and not
me but i also have a time thing going on
but you know you can be part of it too
really can we be time buddies you amen
me
heck yeah
that's gonna be so much more
lore
lord lord oh god
before the stream by the way everyone
crony shared with me that she took a nap
in her car
she was sounding really really tired the
moment she
joined the vc but i have to officially
announce she was on time
and uh
it was all good my worries they they're
wait we're going i think the wrong way
there were there was no need for worries
she was on time um i just heard some
rumors that crony is usually not on time
which is ironic because she has time
your reputation is worse than you really
are i think there have been only two
incidents that i can recall
oh oh but i don't exactly remember what
it was now but it was there was two
words there was kind of brave from you
to
kind of admit it or like i guess you
have no choice if people already out you
but
but like in myth when people oversleep
we're kind of we try to hide it we don't
even most of the time we don't even say
that someone overslept oh god
oh god
kill him first
are you dead
yeah
wait
yummy
can you open the portal
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh god i see no portal i know i see a
portal
nice
i spawned right in the middle of
everybody i need another portal all
right maybe not one
there's still a portal
okay
please survive please just run away
i'm trying
um
it would be cool if you like could kite
the enemies away
i'm trying oh god oh god uh wait where's
my there's one of my bunnies
okay uh uh where's my i did it
where's my other buddy i could see it
here right okay
did you kill them all
is that my body pretty much easy
eight thousand eight hundred gold
is that where is that where's the rest
of my money cronie
uh right here
we got that we got the quest item the
cute by the way
didn't i have twenty thousand where's
the i have only nine thousand now
granny oh
no no no i didn't
i i only have something you shouldn't
have picked up no
took its toll apparently that's true it
did say something like that what they
took ten thousand gold from me
yo that's a little too much
[Music]
that's why you need to put your money in
your stupid stash all the time
oh i forgot the phone
callie come on you didn't have to do
that please mamma mia oh no
oh come on okay but we outta here go
grow new let's go
but it's okay you have like
not okay money
you still have twenty thousand right
no that one's in my inventory i lost ten
thousand but i have money in my stash
that i realized i have fifty thousand in
my stash so
that's that's a lot
i think
i think you need to worry about it then
twenty thousand
it's like
fifty thousand
we already finished the second finger on
you think you're doing so well this is
fun
yo we're like more funny than i thought
it would be
we're like breezing through this game
damn
this
the cube oh the cube that um
council was announced with
oh prank to the cube and then the spear
you guys wear the cube right
yeah and when was that
orb
cube spare orb
all right
pray to q pray to the or but then
cone
pyramid
cone yeah
the cone
yeah yeah
there was so much leading up to you guys
debut
so much lore and where is it now crony
where is the lord huh the lord
is in our hearts if you
if you try you'll find it
it's there somewhere
[Music]
wait the cube
the cube oh the cube
the cube is extra inventory crony
in there i was told before i remember uh
put your books in there
was there something you couldn't put in
there what was it let's put on charm
oh i mean you should put it in stuff
yeah like the charms i guess that you
always need but
wait does it work like if you have it in
the in the cube it still applies or do
you need the charm directly in the
inventory chat technically it's an
inventory right
oh charms are not active in there
oh
okay i thought so
charms won't work okay
okay but but we can put the the huge ass
books in there and i guess maybe some
extra potions perhaps
well
i mean
more inventory space yo
no no transmuting
i always wanted this
more space but then i think that's do
you ever get even more space than this
chat because this is still not enough
this is not enough it's kind of i need
my girl i need my
my helper
should i get a different helper the one
that you have
yeah you should it's actually much
stronger
i suppose with better sense of direction
why
oh
really
i'd like to think so yeah we need some
tanks cause we suck at tanking
um actually better mercenary
should i just get
the most expensive one wahid level 15.
oh
they have different skills
[Music]
i'll i'll go with
waheed
i guess put everything in here
[Music]
welcome to the theme
what now we have two friends actually
where's yours
did yours die too you gotta get yours
back too i think oh man why does he keep
dying every single time
cause you won't protect him enough that
he should have just tried to not die
more
like
you know he's a mercenary he's supposed
to take care of himself why do i have to
take care of it bro
oh
damn i gotta give him
do i armor
armor or this maybe
[Music]
how do i how do i check their gear again
give them
oh yes
i don't have a weapon for him
oh
boy where's the weapon that i gave to
the other lady
[Music]
do i have to buy a weapon for him
what do you have nothing
you have quite a treasure there in that
horror cube
okay whatever i'll wait until something
drops and use the cubes transmute uh
you'll be pleased to know buy something
where who is selling the um armory stuff
here
this dude
you can combine gems in cubes so
apparently yeah
can we i don't remember how
jewels
maybe
maybe tell me if you managed to do it
combine same gems
okay three to one gem okay
so
one
yeah
so if i transmute
what happens
what
oh god i'm really scared what if i'm
doing something wrong by clicking on
this
ah
don't worry
are there these all uh is it is it
trident or a bardish also okay for this
dude
take okay you gotta take all the items
though okay
yeah i knew there was some
something weird i had a bad feeling
okay
so you can
get all the chipped jewels
[Music]
to combine it into one gem apparently
wow
let's see
but i don't have any armor to
socket it into anyway what did you get i
got a flawed diamond
[Music]
it doesn't have to be the same type of
like for example three amethysts
or three diamonds or so
[Music]
did you
put the three like three of the same
oh yeah i put three of the same uh
uh like chip diamonds
okay let me put my
what ammo bling bling
how do i make it into a flawless diamond
then
[Music]
you don't need you're already a flawless
diamond cronie
oh cringe i know
but thank you of course you know you too
yeah
you're just
eternal beauty
oh thank you i admire your confidence
crony
[Music]
i know
wow
you you and your charisma crony
it's fascinating i can learn so much
from you
why you're perfect oh my goodness full
rejuvenation potion okay so if you have
um if you combine three
rejuvenation potions you can make it
into a full rejuvenation that heals 100
life in mana
yo not bad
not bad i will never use it
probably
are you also the type when you play rpgs
where maybe especially in the beginning
like healing potions and all that is
kind of rare you just end up never using
it
because you feel like you don't want to
waste it
for when you really need it yeah that is
yeah are you are you like that
very much so i guess ah yes fellow
hoarder yes very nice to me yes
yes yes but i hoard without ocd so my
hoarding is messy holding
uh
can you combine stamina stamina potions
or any other health potions because that
would be useful oh there you go you want
to clean your finger by combining
literally everything crowley do that on
your off time let's go explore cronies
you're you're right
yes i am right
oh hi
hey i like that confidence let's go
[Music]
now we didn't find any waypoints so i
guess we gotta walk again but the
question is chat
by your experience should we walk into
the same direction again is the next
place we're looking for usually like
past that or should we go in a
completely different direct direction
because we need the we need the maggot
layer now
is that same direction okay where are
you corny
no i'm organizing don't mind me um
no no
okay
i need to control your ocd crummy
kiana is in control that's just so
therapeutic
where's your where's your helper you got
it okay okay good
for your pu ferro pudic yes yes i don't
have any dry hill if you find a waypoint
let me know
okey-dokey
what level are you
uh where do i see it oh wait i found the
portal
oh the waypoint
yeah the waypoint wait where are you
where are you
never mind this is a well
just messing with you
not see you on the map by the way where
i i found that probably
that's what you found
we're crowning chronic dog i'm here you
are i thought you will ran back to
organize your inventory again secretly
i could
no no no no
is this satisfying when you step on
these scorpions try it
this one's alive
i
can't i can't stop there we go yeah that
is
uh satisfying and disgusting
so you like crushing bugs
crony oh i usually do you have a bug or
a spider in your apartment or so are you
the type to try to kill it or you just
have to try to set it free or you just
have to ignore it completely i just
ignore it completely
are you not scared of any type of bugs
uh i am scared of all of them
but you just ignore them because you're
scared you don't want them to get too
close
yeah and i don't i don't want to kill
ants i don't want to kill
except fruit flies
they can die oh you wouldn't even kill
an ant are they too cute
too slow
cronies what's going on here
[Music]
i know why you said oh
oh i come dad
hey
why do we gotta fight
we're not fighting we're doing teamwork
we're taking care of one another making
sure that everyone gets some treasures
yes yeah yeah yeah of course
we're
doing fine
yes
i wonder which direction we should go
[Music]
i don't want to look for hours again for
this stupid matter there i really didn't
like that one
you kind of i hope you're not
claustrophobic as well
i'm not
okay i mean in game it's fine
crude because the next place makes you
feel claustrophobic
by the way if you still have exploding
arrow on you maybe should maybe think
about switching it every now and then
because exploding arrow takes up so much
mana oh
oh i turned off accidentally show your
allison map oh
how do i turn it back on
do you guys know uh push f 11 and f12
really i can't use that oh what's f12 ah
thank you
[Applause]
chad knows everything
i do oh crystal sword but it's gray
no maybe not
like ray is just the ones that are uh
no
are green ones useless maybe they are
grey is good though it's talking oh
you're right
thank you
okay come with me crony that was a dead
end
let's go back
oh maybe this way
so gray is either ethereal or socketing
oh yeah yeah yeah
that could be true it's been a lot so i
forgot completely oh there's a there's a
saber cat
sample cat with disabled face
just like cronies
oh they might drop something good
yeah
there's a yellow golden enemy
i can't carry it
i took the club i gave you so much time
to take here's the sapphire sapphire go
crony go have fire it's a flawed
sapphire but it's sapphire
oh my goodness it's beautiful
oh
nice
and we're gonna have a flawless sapphire
it's gonna be great
i was just trying i was just i was just
i was just um
having fun i knew there was nothing
good dropping anyway so i was just
messing around you know
i am over burdened really really yeah i
just just did like panic cooking
oh my god
[Music]
i got
i got you
what do you mean i'm possible wait guys
i ran out of ambrose oh no you take the
take this club is danny
rose
are you good
yeah yeah i know i'm good i'm good i
heard staff was really good to have
oh
crony help i have no arrow
oh you haven't for now i can't side with
the javelin here here i have
arrow
oh thank you
crony
yeah
i keep a backup just in case i see that
as a peace offering
[Music]
a peace offering yes charmed wait
why am i other
there you go
okay
[Music]
oh
that was a quick level up
you got a level up
oh yeah you asked me for what level i am
i am
[Music]
i am i am
i am level
yes
what am i another waypoint the dry house
waypoint let's go oh come down to me
crony and activate it
how do i check what level i am here
and with c
c
oh
i see
and we didn't find the sewer's level 2
waypoint for some reason we didn't
explore well enough
shame on us
ah
wait it goes upwards there i think
that's the way
man this map is huge
is that what we're calling
yes yes spa race is maggot lair in the
[\h__\h]
oh
i've seen these dudes and bugs life
oh true
wait is bug slap the one
uh
with
was it was it ass
no yeah
with the blue ants
it's not a ant z
not the
not the ugly version it's the cuter
pixar version
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah i think
i think i watched it when i was younger
[Music]
anything good dropping crooney oh no not
really honestly
you disgusting ill
why
that sand mad it looked disgusting oh
that's a sand maggot oh it lays eggs
you you you you oh
thank you
we needed to know that
what's that what's that
oh they come out of the ground
isn't that nice
what okay wait uh shall we
how's your inventory looking right now
kind of
full but i think i can manage what about
you
a little bit longer
a little longer is good a little bit
longer
nice okay get this out of the way
raised crony actually went that way okay
what is that
weird pink black hole what
found lots of money
you came too late crony why why why you
like this
we are never on time
it's everyone thank you it's too late
crowdy why
it's okay
as your manager says you should get an
analog clock did you tell your viewers
that your manager told you that
no
cronie told me before the stream that
her
manager told her the clock
to get an analog clock
yeah
sounds about right
i can't believe you would have a
christmas present someone will give it
to you
maybe hey actually that would be a
pretty good gift
i think i ran out of arrows again okay i
think it's time there's a waypoint
okay but i gotta go back i'm gonna open
the portal oh i
wait 23
defense
i'll put that to good use
nice
oh
you're so good
i can't carry anymore
[Music]
okay
now i really got the goal
really gotta go yeah we really should go
right up pretty go
oh
oh i guess we can just use the white
point
uh to loot golem
[Music]
let's sell some of our beautiful
belongings
indeed i feel like we're getting closer
to
the maggots place
i can't carry anymore
this is true
stay awhile and listen
[Music]
what scroll of town nope
oh narash is dead
what
oh no my buddy's dead again
no again
yes whatever it happens you give him
some armor to protect himself
i did and then he died
she just went off and died i don't know
why he just decided to say oh you know
what i can't i can't and then he died
weakling
we don't need weaklings in our team
hey
you understand you get it
just keep him dead ow
not enough never revive him again
i'm good to go i can't carry anymore
where i was here
back at the way point uh you're here too
oh yeah
did you um
did you not pick that up on purpose
which one
the blue cap and the javelin
oh
yeah yeah
why not
i i don't have room for it
how about you use this waypoint to go
back and sell some stuff
wow what a genius idea that's what i
just did
i'll i'll sell the stuff for you then
thank you
and that money's gonna go to me right
yes
you're gonna give the money to me right
yeah
here i'll give you the items
whoa chain boots of balance wow you
actually have so
yeah i haven't switched out my boots in
a while you can have this
azure heavy boots
mine are better
what
i can't i cannot i can't believe you've
done this
what
what it's a dog eat dog world get used
to it
gotta get used to crownies learn from
your senpai how to stay alive in this
world
[Music]
in this rough beachable world yeah you
can have that if you need
[Music]
why do i have this
what do i
[Music]
why don't i have these gloves i thought
i had something better what i'm so
confused lovely mine are really shitty
too i only have white leather gloves
with defense free and that's it
that's really crappy whoa
they're so expensive though
yeah we'll find something eventually
well that one
[Music]
yeah yeah okay
i guess i should revive my dude
yes
i'll look for the maggot layer where is
the maggot
just die so quickly
that's weird mine doesn't die so quickly
i'll put that to good use
what could it be what could the reason
be
you you
can your teammate also equip a shield or
uh
no because he must wear like a spare or
something some item like a two-handed
item uh-huh
i need a key
can you just take it from your stupid
cube
there's a key there and then
there and then put it here and then all
right this was the thing this was a
thing this is a thing
key
oh organizing why why am i like this i
just don't want to order to pick you up
again no no no i got it don't worry
i mean
yes kiana mommy kiana i have to pick you
up again cronini
give me i'm almost done
you say so i will wait how good is your
japanese cronie
not very josudez
oh but your your
uh
korean is incredible please teach me
sensei
my korean is just
it's not that great but
can you um can you give me like a like i
have this i have this to go french
sentence whenever i say people think
that i actually speak french uh it's
really because most as well and it means
do you want to sleep tonight with me
i got it from no i got it from a song
okay i got it from lady marmalade
and i was wondering if you could give me
like a really sexy korean sentence that
if i say it
people will think i speak korean for
real
oh no
um
i think there's an equivalent
uh phrase in korean for netflix and
chill
oh
what is it
um
would you like to do netflix and chill
with me tonight yes yes good that i need
that yes yes in korean please
uh okay
yes
i think my pronunciation is off can you
see
it's pretty good it's um
are you actually asking if we want to
eat
ramen yeah like you know it's kind of
like do you want to come over to my
house and have some ramen
yeah yeah
mocha is eating right
you say it differently than it is in
japanese so the korean pronunciation is
kind of different yeah um
[Music]
okay thank you very much
no no i have to say oni
what was it again
out of curiosity then do you have um
something that you can teach me in
german
not yet first i have to tell you
something crony you're first of all
going completely in the wrong direction
please go to the right side north or
like gosh darn it i've been walking in
circles all this time i'm so bad with
multitasking
what did you say that sounded hot
no it means like just just take it out
from the fridge
how did you get up there
wait no before that how do i go up oh
that's how he's doing
where did you learn that
from google
[Music]
there's parts of it i taught myself
through duolingo and parts of it a
costume i just learned from from google
oh my god
is that the most probable word for
boobies custom uh
yes
yes question mark
all right i wanted you to teach me
korean anyway so finally i'm getting my
lesson
yeah yeah
call it
yeah and then custom
don't learn that one
that will i will i will be forgiven
because i am uh i am
[Music]
gaijin i don't know what i'm saying
i don't know
why are you saying impossible
oh uh did you run out of arrows no no no
no i used the wrong bow
i don't know what you want
you wanted to learn something in german
uh
cronie how much german do you actually
speak the guten morgen
she said to me before the stream she did
use the word scheisse i was very excited
because we do have that as an icon and
the member's like what what you want me
to not ruin you say so image you don't
have a facebook image crony do you oh
no oh don't be so mellow dramatic crony
it's over it's okay
i haven't ever
[Applause]
[Music]
how do i
you take the thing that i wanted to say
that's okay
i can't use that
why can't something else
[Music]
[Laughter]
eh oh
no no no no no no no
it's it's nothing it's nothing it's
nothing important it's nothing good
i can't
wait so you want to learn
you said putin morgan but i still don't
know how much you actually speak or
understand i'll put that to good use
none at all is that it gutenbergen and
scheisse
my crystal sword
what do you mean crystal sword
do you have the do you have no it's okay
i don't know
oh yeah okay yeah
must be imagining things
did not
take it
i don't need it either
pretty shield
go go crony we need to find that that
other quest item um
that i cannot i cannot sleep
wait
oh my god what are we going to do about
all this
stupid electro damage
ah just keep healing
yes yes mommy
why
oh sand megan oh there it is
but yes
um what else do i know guten morgenta
yes
yeah crony is good when she is knocked
what
you pronounce the word not in a way that
it means naked
but knocked crony enact is good too and
no it's it's all good
warned helm
no you take this
horned helm
oh why
why it's so cool it's vampirin only
mamma mia oh
what a shame
um
okay so
do you want to learn
a sentence like the one you talked you
thought taught me uh-huh
yes okay um
[Music]
what could i teach you i guess this was
a dead end
um
yes it was
is there
see i don't have many good german pickup
phrases
um
[Music]
i'll just i'll just say
this to mia
um
when you say chad about that that's just
kind of
charming isn't it
[Applause]
it's pretty long
let me
give you a second
what did you call it
when it turned dark
it will dark help
oh it's we're going through the night
slingers
i was just trying to find a piece of
paper to write it down here
i don't know
maybe it's one enemy because the the
moment i stepped in here they started
making it dark
maybe
okay
maybe this is just the area i guess ah
we jumped right to the next question oh
we skipped this is a different quest
okay
about the strange doctors now let's get
out of here granny come with me okay
okay
goodbye
you're gonna die again wait is it not
gonna get brighter anymore
yeah
okay we need to go to the city and ask
drug nuns
yeah
where do we i wanna go to the maga layer
where the hell is it
maybe maybe the upper have we looked at
the upper area
yeah it's blocked off
there's nothing there i guess we gotta
go down
again
maybe we missed something in the
bottom area
[Music]
where is the mega oh do you think it's
that pink one over there
pink pink
yeah in the in the center area
like follow follow me i guess i
i gotta write it down because there's no
way that i'll be able to memorize that
i'll give you a shorter one
oh
[Laughter]
okay a shorter one was
[Music]
easily translated into english to
let us dance tango horizontally
really
wait when is that usually used
i thought we're doing like flirty flirty
sentences
but why tango horizontally
oh
[Laughter]
someone in my chat wrote that you
suggested it
my suggestion was way more innocent i
was saying uh at home in my drawer i
have a i have a a drawer drawer
free
empty for you because i'm asking you to
move in you know
yeah in my closet i have a drawer empty
for you
i was saying that and then they were
like this is too long
okay
uh well okay let's i'll try to memorize
the other one how's the okay oh you two
say so for the horizontally tangled
dancing
i mean
it's just face down no it's just dancing
it's this is dancing what's up
okay okay the other one my suggestion
was um
um what was it again uh
um
so how's it
no was that what i was how was i saying
okay different one different one let's
let's make it but that's not good enough
it's so fun coffee with me that's not
good enough
[Music]
uh
the chat is only telling me long
sentences it's too difficult for cronini
uh
[Music]
let's uh let's go to portal
god damn it
can we can we go to town so then i can
sell myself yeah yeah yes yes are you in
here where are you
i'm here
yeah
i'll think of a good german sentence
while we're selling
uh could you open it because i can't oh
yes i can bless
i think you have to bring the book back
into your inventory every time
how about
[Music]
oh why is it so dark
well yeah because they're not we have
reactivated the quest it's going to stay
like this until
we fix it
let's talk to drogon and
it's broken
[Music]
where's the blacksmith here
black smith i saw the blacksmith
somewhere
wait you want something repaired
um probably you're like
right next to that girl kane is is
pharah she repairs stuff
[Music]
is my old one still better chat
because it has more blue effects
okay
what am i
right i'm doing i'm putting this
oh i like that one
ah slow dangle i like that one that made
me say so enough for a crony
i'm afraid
are you sure
yeah it's kind of long though
uh
ready better getting better off getting
a second bone arrow
okay
um
so
[Music]
yes
it's been from ariatsi
can you destroy the absolute moment
what it's a bit long
it's been
uh here that if you have an accident on
the street they're gonna take your car
and stuff
so yeah you're saying i am from the adac
it's been from adi
it's been
from
[Music]
yes wait how do i ah
oops
been from i don't see it
eh
wait did you see did you see that
message
no how do i type a message
can each this hold the app
that's cute when you say that
very cute
being
bombed
at
see
[Music]
is
it basically means i'm from the towing
service may i tell you home tonight
oh that's smooth
can you say it in one go
uh it's been
ish ish or ish
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
yeah
yay
new phrases
are you ready to go back to our maggot
lair and destroy everything in our sight
yeah
okay what are you trying to do with me
you you clicked me
really it said you agree you agreed to
train you oh
man
my my
poor [\h__\h]
no wait i could just open another one
no need to be so dramatic
why can't i just open it like that yeah
come here with me okay let's go
i'll give you some
i'll give you some of my scrolls and
return no no no no i have more than
enough i think
we're fine
but
but you can
you can give me some of the beautiful
shiny items that are going to be
dropping left and right that i cannot
i'm
you're already doing it though
we're going to speedrun this place oh
whoa
what's it eats stamina
what why are you not shooting
oh my boat oh i don't have any arrows
oh
oh i have some extra but not very many
let's see if we can find some
drops
i dropped some did you take them yeah
thank you
not many yes we'll find more arrows
actually
uh i think even before cronie debuted i
asked her
if she could
if we would do a stream where she would
teach me
oh here's arrows
if she would teach me uh koreans
it still hasn't happened when are we
gonna do that cronini
whenever you're
really good
are you up for it are you
do you think you're a good teacher
am i a good teacher
not exactly i don't really know
what to teach you to be exact
is there any specific topic that you
would like to learn
uh
i mean i already tried teaching myself
some basics for duolingo but it's been a
while and i kind of forgot already i
think it's i was trying to
teach myself the the signs the um
uh
like how to write korean uh-huh but
chad agreed that duolingo was doing an
absolutely horrible job of teaching it
like
you know how they're like built
like you can combine
small pieces into another letter right
uh-huh and and duolingo just didn't
explain that part at all
oh
no it took me a while to realize that
and i was just trying to remember what
they look like and what they mean by
um like associating them with uh what
would a turtle turtle what are they
called again
turtle turtle rangers no not through
what are they called turtle ninja
turtles oh
teenage mutant ninja turtles yes
if you turn them around the korean signs
they look like ninja turtles to me
yeah
that's the only thing i was able to
associate that with so if you could just
teach me some more basics
that i would really appreciate
communication basics
communication
you don't have to teach me the the
writing i guess that's probably better
to learn
on on their own
right
yeah yeah yeah
you're fluent right
i'm
maybe can you do some
korean asmr for me
i don't like asmr but if it's you
speaking korean i think everyone gets uh
like tingly feelings
oh you wand
do you want this you want you want
well it's okay
it's crappy though
i know
then i have better
things to pick up
why that no
anyway i'm so quiet i already have some
good stuff i found something
uh
i found something
uh legendary
oh when you weren't looking i think
why'd you pick it up when i wasn't
looking huh because you were somewhere
else i think you know we could share
this beautiful moment together
we cannot share this item however it's
unshareable
we could take turns
level two
next legendary item is yours
oh my god
look at her look at her speech picking
up everything
no no no no i don't know what i'm doing
and this place is so disgusting
when you play together in diablo
i think i was previously told that like
the more players are in the game the
more
easier
no the other way around oh they they
adjust the strength of the enemies
apparently is it true
because they feel
i guess they feel about as strong as
they would be
when um i would be fighting them alone
yeah it's true 33
more hp
apparently
yo this this place is so disgusting i
can't even walk on it
my
buddy died again standing
no crawling your body is so weak fire
him
already
i've been
i've been moving frustrated i can't move
past you oh yeah my bad
why can't i open the door
crunch wow
these people so strong
which way should we go crony
i can't why can't i there we go
going this way
i have no idea what i'm doing
whenever i try to rack up skill points
and i try to
allocate them i have no idea what i'm
doing why are you
dead cause i'm dead should have put my
money into the stash again please open
portal
yeah
you're so strong what the [\h__\h]
why
i have zero money wait you just don't
die okay stay alive stay safe i need to
sell some stuff
oh
can you oh buddy oh no don't die don't
die i need i need some money to hire my
friends again
[Music]
wow they are very durable
oh oh
yes
oh god uh
okay that's one dead
oh god i'm
no don't die did you i'm cornered yes i
did
okay
you can stay alive a little longer
wow that's very caring and so passionate
away
i'm on my way
oh my way
crony
i'm coming
where is you where is you
oh wait i only i don't have my i don't
have any weapons oh god my body is all
the way over there
i can't pick it up i can't pick it up
why can't you pick it up because because
enemy waiting here for me okay good huh
okay now okay
okay
you want to take my money
what no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
i lost the money a lot of money i need
to get some more money i can't carry
anymore oh oh man oh man i can't carry
any more oh man
oh man um
oh man oh man where do i uh get out um
oh man acclaim more beautiful
i want that's an anime called clown
clamp more yo we got so many items here
we need to go to the city again right
away yeah i can open the portal
okay
whoever sells their stuff fastest can go
your items for too long because you have
to go back quickly
[Music]
bye
wow
wow should i keep this for some reason
well actually i'll wait for you because
the portal closes
oh okay you can have the rest that's
there
no no it's okay that's not
a very fair competition i'd like a
challenge fair because i already took so
much stuff
really
no i'm coming okay
[Laughter]
i mean
i had a different portal but it's like
all the way in the beginning so
what
okay here you go
here you go she says
here you go she says yeah yeah it's it's
there now okay
okay
but it's all gone now
no it's not no it's not crony
are you bullying you're senpai no what
what have i done to deserve that you
said you picked up so many good things
oh you did it you did it because so you
wanted to quickly uh i see i see nothing
is left here i understand
okay you can come now
come on huh
why let's move on i want to finish this
dungeon
come on
come back uh
no yeah come here no
not yet
let me just uh sell some of my stuff
oh you have something to sell oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah cause i stopped buying
you can have it it's okay you can have
it
really
nice
of course you deserve it
thank you thank you
and
so
you continue to contribute so much to
this game and
that's not sarcasm right okay i'm here
not really i don't know maybe it is
maybe
it was a dead end
let's go
oh for some reason i thought that was
the end of it
no unfortunately not
i think this is still way bigger
this place i remember i spent quite some
time here i was rushing through it but i
couldn't
find anything
do you wanna uh
you now have the opportunity to say
hello to my mom to meet my mom because
she's watching this stream pretty sure
oh
hello
uh mamaroni
mama roni mama roni
mama tony mama tom why are you putting
why are you putting your own name on my
mommy
are we planning to marry or what's going
on or are you planning to to hit are you
planning to marry my mom i'm sorry
mummy
mommy
no mixing up some things here cronie my
mom is time mom
what's the magic word
please yes
does your mom watch your theme
oh god i hope not
does she know what you're doing
uh
yeah i think so
oh did you tell her or did she find out
i feel like she would be able to tell
considering how
ice cream
oh
oh where are you you you're living in
the same
place
yeah yeah wait how do i get through
oh no you gotta move smartly
what
yeah it's kind of buggy here what the
hell
what and
yes what the [\h__\h]
what bonnie
how do i uh what
now i'm in front of you but yeah i can't
move either
egg is on the ground
ah
but i can't
kill it
[Music]
true maybe with the javelin yes okay oh
i don't know the reason the javelin hits
where is where is waheed by the way he's
alive but he's not coming either will he
like teleport to me chad because i see
him bugging around
oh there there he goes
what the [\h__\h] was that
don't you dare kill me
didn't put my money back into the bank
again uh oh man yeah
no killing direction do we go crazy
okay over here
okay crony says so
oh nice show
nice if we went a different direction we
would have probably wandered around for
one longer
oh
but yeah i forgot oh my god oh my god oh
my god i lost my train of thought but
oh hello
mama told me son
no not sean
mama son
hello
but she's not japanese so you don't
really need to add any honorifics
oh god hold on
miss mama
[Music]
oh distracted i lost 11 000 money again
never give me money in my inventory oh
god i can't even get my dude back okay
um can you make a portal please yeah
oh
[Music]
why would they do that
how dare they
where is my body
did you take my money no
what oh
heavens forbid no the few monies that i
had left
how much did you have
i don't know they took 11 000 so
it's okay it probably wasn't much death
to start look look def takes my money
and leaves me her bloody scythe
thank you callie
legit she gave me this this was the item
i picked up
so you lost 11 000 right
yeah no but def took it you you you
don't have it probably you don't have uh
if something was dropped from me it was
probably way less
because you literally pay the game
like
how many percent
of your own money chad is there a
specific
specific percentage
i don't
recall having this much gold no
well i thought
i did twice didn't i so you probably oh
yeah once once i got a little bit of my
money back but there you go
oh my god
crony donations
thanks for the super chat cronies thanks
for the red super chat
[Music]
now move please
can i send you another
yes if you want
i hope i will not lose it by dying again
i think it's wrong why are you giving me
more money
why so that when you die again i can
keep the rest
i'm kidding
i don't understand the logic but okay
i'm kidding thank you for the pink super
chat cronie
i would feel less guilty about taking
your money i mean why anyway monsters
monsters yes
wow she's so generous thank you for
support supporting my cause
thank you always
we both have no helpers so let's see if
we can even survive this from now on
i will probably live
i'll stay behind a little bit
but it's more little bit difficult you
got to open those doors from close and
then and then they attack you then they
swarm you and then you die
yeah oh my god
what is going on
no mana
level
is fully restored oh this is a okay this
is a gold enemy
it's fire
i think they're weak to fire holy [\h__\h]
kind of good feeling potion healing
potion thank you thank you
oh god
did it drop something good for you
oh no
um yeah i also only dropped the uh a
blue one for me
you gotta follow me specific this is for
you because that's something uh the same
thing good that you picked it up
i
had that
uh
i got that previously the same item i
think which one the rune
yeah
good for you good for you crying
now
to pick it up
now i feel a little bad considering
you're like oh you can take it like
can you call me a place i don't want to
die alone
why not
i'm kidding okay
um
show this and this
oh yeah i need to wait i need to do
stats wait a second right maybe i need
um
what was i stating on chat probably dex
huh
but i feel like i need more vitality
i'll start a little bit here 14 stat
points remaining oh wow i didn't have so
many stat points
i have nothing put it all into divide
okay let's go
let's go i'm stronger now crony hey
i'll protect you
together we are
immortal
oh my god yes
no we don't need to be together i'm
already immortal you too
oh yeah
but together we're even stronger yeah
how old are you now i'm like infinite
years old i lost i have also no h not
really
hey
yay for vague ages in hollow life
english that's the beauty of it ain't it
okay we we got that
done
how many levels are there here in this
dungeon chat do you know
gonna die
yes
me too
oh wow what a coincidence
there's three oh we're already in the
third one okay it shouldn't be much
longer
saber unless you how do you feel about
have you ever played or watched fate
crony
i've tried playing face grand order oh
my goodness what the heck
can we like load up before i think that
might be the boss yeah
yeah i have no mana uh let's go back to
the city for one moment yes nice
you read my mind crony
that is the bus
let's get ready for it it's probably not
that strong but uh
yeah let's put the money into the stash
but a little bit let's bring our buddies
uh
i'll cost like what 1 500.
and then
[Music]
for healing
honestly cranny i
felt like
this
collab with you might be my
last time playing
this game on stream but
somehow this is a surprisingly good
collab game so i kind of want to do
more yeah i wanna i wanna play more of
it even though i died so many times
it's a nice challenge kind of grows on
you and
i would i would like it if we can collab
more too you know
okay oh yeah
okay
but wait i need to i need to buy some
or maybe i have some in my inventory i
need some mana thingies
it has none okay
well yeah
but yeah i need i need the korean
knowledge because i have you probably
too but you know how hololive has had a
recent
influx of korean viewers and they're so
sweet
i just want to be able to
give them some content
let's let's uh learn some korean shall
we
teach me teach me oh
my gosh
yes
no no no no no not that one forget that
one yes that one yes important knowledge
no you can forget that one it's no no no
i'm ready to go
really i just finished organizing what a
coincidence what a coincidence we're in
sync
i
give me a second
no where are you going dude dude come
here he wanted to fight the bus stop
hiding the bus
i'm waiting for cronie
oh are you already back
yeah
but i'm not doing anything i'm just
waiting
okay give i'll be there in a quick
second
wait no no wait i'm i'm going there
again too i need to store some more
money apparently i sold
anything now okay
white white white what what oh crony is
at her stash what a surprise
where else would she be
where you belong in front of your chest
just like in minecraft
all right let's go
wait
my potions
my
potions
yes
who has it pharah atmosphere open
another portal interesting case that is
a good idea let me open it like here
why do i have this
who had the potions again um there's two
different ones that have the potions in
the middle there should be at least one
that sells potions in the middle area
close to the
a little bit like left to this oh
lysander okay
[Music]
nice okay
you should be fine now i think i am
ready let's no yeah
let's make it burn
yeah we will make them burn in about 10
seconds
yes let's go
let's go
let's
that is a lot of
disgusting
oh i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
in this [\h__\h]
oh we killed the big one already oh
that's kind of underwhelming
oh
[Laughter]
i saw it i was nothing yet
i didn't take a single item oh really
like everything
that was a quest items i think oh
darn i got almost nothing from this but
okay okay you got so like most of the
time i was picking up other things so
it's good it's just funny how you took
everything
you learned from the greatest from
takanashi kiwala
thank you thank you you have learned
learned a lot i think through this
journey and i'm so proud of how we have
developed our friendship today
here i made a portal over here we can go
back
oh this
item to is
yeah staff of kings oh wait is that the
second what did it say we need search
for the maggot where for the shaft shaft
it did you pick up a shaft
yeah i picked up with the staff of kings
yeah is that that's not the quest item
is that what
cute it is the staff what that's
confusing it says search for the shaft
the claw viper no this wait what
maggot layer on the far right is this
for the shaft but the chat the chest the
chat says that the staff is the quest
item so it's okay it's the typo
roderick staff
at the quest text got mixed up in diablo
2 resurrected okay
then we got everything we need no
problem
okay we got everything let's go
i think
we was already pretty late uh over here
so i think we should leave it at that
but who is the quest person again i know
we're not done with the quest yet so we
can't give him what
oh but wait he has something to say ah
yes the shaft of queen kings yeah esther
shaft
the staff of kings
oh
shaft portion oh
he wants us to unite the cube with the
head piece what
yeah don't worry about it she's
okay we can't do it now we need the
headpiece okay so we got the cube and
then we have the shaft and then uh later
on we would get the headpiece to combine
those two
well that was fun
yeah
yay
[Music]
party
touch
corner i hope i wasn't um
two
to
[Music]
two dominating today
oh no no i learned a lot i
i learned that you have to pick up items
and then as soon as possible
yes before the other one picks it up
that's the easy rule pick it up before
someone else does it's a dog eat dog
world yeah it's a doggy dog world it's
the main takeaway
yeah that was just my way of teaching
you that it's tough out there youtubers
there's like millions of youtubers now
you gotta you know step up your game to
stay relevant in this tough world yes
yes yes this is a real wise knowledge
from a philosophical phoenix
i can't
store ah
she's not even listening she's talking
no no no no no no no no
i'm occupied i'm occupying i'm lucky i'm
listening
confirming it no no no no i'm
i am paying attention it's a doggy dog
world it's a doggy dog world it's very
dangerous out there
and we gotta look out for each other
yeah
exactly see i've been paying attention
been taking notes
guys it's it's it's all good yeah cronie
is busy that's what the chat says cronie
is busy you will last way too short
no but thank you
thank you for always looking out
thank you crown name
thank you
actually uh
i think the first one from yeah random
knowledge the first one from council
to message me was crony
before the debbie like the first one
once once we were in the same discord
remember first one
[Laughter]
[Music]
crony was very interested in this
phoenix lady
i was interested in everyone but yes yes
of course yes
i'm a huge fan of you just kidding that
was not how it was
that was not how it was almost closed
i love you please when i have an
autograph that's no no that's also not
it
to see you in my dms please slag into my
dms uh anytime please really
yes
okay i'll try my best when i'm awake
[Music]
that is probably always the opposite
time of when i'm awake but yeah let's go
one day our pets will cross like
like this
[Music]
i believe in it i'm looking forward to
that day cronie please teach me korean
sometime soon and let's let's continue
diablo sometime in january
yeah yeah
yes yes
that would be cool because it was so
much fun we should at least finish like
um
i would say i mean not the whole act
maybe because that's that's tough but we
should finish
the the staff quest and maybe the
tainted sun quest so that gets so that
the sun comes back
sometimes
we're great team
we are a great team
maybe
i could save up the
hmm
if i do play diablo
oh are you planning to play more if i
play more
how far do you think i should go i feel
like i'm not going to go far without
i mean if you want to play some more
alone on your channel you you're welcome
to go as far as you want but but you can
also always call me over uh if if you
feel like you know playing oh yeah
always more fun
i'll make time for you any time
yep yep oh oh oh okay
okay if that's the case then
i guess
but you don't have to i mean
so we gotta do some cafe sister collabs
you know
did you guys know we do have the same
rigor so we can uh move
the most in ho how left can you go
uh
oh you can't go even i think you're even
more movable than i am because kathy
rigged you after me
and how how left can you actually go
that's not you can't go further i know
you can go further this is
the limit
no i saw you going further before
how far oh
oh crony i wanted to before we end this
i wanted to give you a senpai advice
uh-huh
i feel like
uh you should
make yourself bigger on streams and on
thumbnails
okay
yes
wait i think you make your face too
small always
my face
yeah i mean
is there a reason for that you make
yourself too small
and it wants you to be bigger so that it
catches the eye better how beautiful you
are
well you know i'm just
i feel like
if people see my full glory it might be
a bit too much for them but
you know what i'll take your advice i'll
try to
make myself
[Music]
shall we and yeah i think we have to
don't forget to save i think diablo
always saves when you exit
save and exit
we made a lot of progress thank you
everybody for watching our diablo 2
resurrected collab
thank you everybody hope you enjoyed it
and check out cronie's channel it's in
the description
give her a sub
like how you looking
[Music]
oh be sure to like and subscribe and be
sure to hit that bell button i don't
know i wasn't really asking you for that
but that's good yes yes go go go
promotion girl yeah
hit that like and subscribe follow us on
twitter as well
yeah
be sure to ring that bell button
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding
okay
um
i have a sentence for you
uh-huh
[Music]
oh my god
where do you learn this
google is my teacher google should not
be doing this
[Laughter]
well
you're such a you're such a shy dog
aren't you no
what
you get so flustered so quickly that's
it's so easy to
i'll get you well
you know my answer to that is um
[Laughter]
wait i heard that before
what does that mean i heard that before
it means i'll think about it we'll have
a great sleepover
it means you'll think about it
yeah we'll have a great sleepover
oh great yeah
yes okay i'll be the one to wake you up
crony because no one else does
sounds like a solid idea
have a yeah evening everybody oh by the
way cronie i have a uh ending greeting
on my channel maybe you want to stay
together with me do you have an ending
greeting
uh it is chris to me
ah wow you're really
that's christmas
you sound like a like a
swiss person almost
me wow
okay um i say and in german we say auf
wiedersehen
we say german in the end um
[Music]
[Applause]
me yeah
yeah
okay
[Music]
and as always thank you everyone and
i hope to catch up with you guys
tomorrow and
the the actual super chat catch up will
be
sometime this week
[Music]
and yeah
kudos to me
[Music]