[Music]
fade away
first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
I feel it every every day
[Music]
the great Wanderer
retrospective
[Music]
three two
sleep talking
friends
[Music]
hinatori
heart Challenger
[Music]
Sparks
my OBS is glitching
[Music]
hi
it's a really really rare 3D small Wawa
oh my God my OBS is glitching what's
going on
hello
that scares me it's like flashing in
white
but it's okay
me I rested not as much as I wanted to
but I woke up like you know after Maybe
[Music]
how much could it have been
oh oh I don't know six seven hours
I wanted to sleep eight you know but it
is what it is
[Music]
and then I felt like after smoothie wake
me up for food I was like
[Music]
probably my daily my inner clock was
saying well 1pm is
the time to be awake for you
takanasikiwawa
um
maybe I'll take a nap later if I got
some time
but I have so much to do
uh but we'll be watching
the Nintendo Direct because I heard this
one's a big one this one we're gonna
hear some exciting things
um
uh I heard some rumors
uh we'll be watching the American one
it's pinned in a comment
tune in for wait it even says here tune
in for Nintendo Direct live stream
featuring roughly 40 minutes of
information focused on Nintendo switch
games releasing this winter
okay so Winter Games Winter Games
is Pokemon
is not announced the Nintendo Direct is
it normally
because usually there's always a Pokemon
game for winter too right
okay they'll do their own thing okay
understandable understandable hands
someone cut off my finger someone
chopped them off I'm like a pirate I
maybe I should attach a hook to my to my
hands they're like perfect to attach
something to it
nope true no your peace
I add the DLC if Pokemon is out yeah I
don't know I don't think we can stream
it anyway so I'm not buying it
um yeah I'm watching someone play it
um
no I don't like accents I'd rather have
how about do you know the most
the best thing might be
fork and knife hands one one hand Fork
one hand knife
and I can always eat with that and then
the knife might be useful for other
things too
I mean generally that would what do you
mean that's lame
you guys are lame it's just very
freaking smart
if you say that's lame I'm gonna
I'm gonna Fork you up
oh
I I did that yes I did
I never used this like 3D wealthy before
I think on stream like now it's in our
app
we don't have to use like we are or so
for it
um
I like the way the eyes move there's no
expression so it can't be sad or
anything
but it's so cool that it's in there
because we didn't even have to ask for
it it was just suddenly there thanks to
henma
Wow Wow henma Let's Go
you can't be said yeah well I mean it's
well Fiona shouldn't really be sad right
but
um
yeah
[Music]
welcome back to my small office
um
[Music]
I thought it would fit also to the
thumbnail I look I will I look more like
the phone than Wawa
in this form we'll just watch this by
the way because it's my day off after
after we watched it uh where is it
starting
I'm like one minute behind for some
reason
uh because I stopped it uh after it's
done
let me speed it up
I will just end this stream no Super
Chat rating or anything
uh I am two-timing it okay I think it's
probably on time now
uh yeah because I got like so much work
to do Mama Mia I have to record one song
One Voice pack
uh one songs harmonies
yeah
oh yeah so yeah
all of that today and I have to also
sign cards a lot of cards it's stunning
Nintendo
direct for everybody who's watching The
Vault I'll try to give you some hints as
to what's happening in the beginning so
you can sync up
the screen just change to Splatoon
yeah I've seen this before though
and I'm not interested in Splatoon
but it looks cute
nice Aesthetics like it's not so
colorful as it usually is
but it might be a new trailer huh
because I've seen like the Aesthetics
before but I don't know if I that looks
like portal
the world looks like looks like portal
in that one in that in that scene
okay uh what should I
um how do I help Vaude Watchers we are
seeing someone in an elevator
and now not anymore
they're talking
I'll try to the subtitles okay
um
for real yo lead with that next time
okay Pearl now check out what happens
when you set this color trip into the
palette First Resource is
German for eight
okay it's probably fine by now
wow it's like you can see it you should
be watching it with me so watch along
oh
yeah I don't understand any of this
foreign
I like the pastel colors though seems to
be
the thing in this
deal is it a DLC or a game
it's a DLC right
expansion pass
looks freaky looks looks very different
from usual Splatoon
um
okay next boom
hello
it'll be our guide wow
no it's it's not related to me
it's not related to me I think
next
I'll snap like like
hey okay see that's how you can adjust
the timing
I'll snap my fingers when they snap them
oh
here we go
is this
is this a remake or
oh no
what is this
is this first time announcement
looks cute
but if they announce it because they
shook the trailer like this it's
probably not the first time
observation and action
it looks looks good
wait it's like to add games
this is like the ad games
riddle solving
in in a in this POV side scrolling not
really sad scrolling most of the time
even oh okay this is like Mario Party
a cute cute cute
oh it's Mario Party
yay
February
who is he
oh Prince of Persia
no
is this a series
looks good
this looks good
yeah right it is
oh it's pretty
oh the music is good too
um
I wonder how different the Japanese
version of the directors
whoo that looks really cool
it actually looks good
looks fun
it will be soft or Rich oh be soft
Ubisoft
that looks nice really nice
usually they're good
looks good what oh
Chase two
oh yeah
um
do they have muscle cars though
paddle to the metal
no
no I don't want to
today
oh
sorry that was genuine I didn't even
want to sound like you know
always makes me wonder when they like
suddenly announce something and it drops
the same day or tomorrow it's like what
happened there that made them come to
this decision
today not
like no they were gonna release it or is
this some strategy because they're
desperate or what oh my God
ah
oh my God
domtender will be so confused
that was cute oh but no date just next
year hmm
yeah let's
[Music]
go
no I don't need to play this you know
who needs to play that Anya needs to
play that
oh
Super Mario RP team
[Music]
who is that wooden boy Pinocchio
is it a Pinocchio wannabe look alike
Gino
he's wooden right
now cute
I like the the
squashiness of them
like the proportions of the these
models
November 17th
hmm
squishiness oh
Nani
or
I don't know this one
oh some people are happy
oh
wait it looks good
why is it remake right
from a DS game
it's like a a riddle
tokigimu
mysterious boy
damn
oh
oh whoa
ah
somehow
dad gave me goosebumps
so the sequel was never released
overseas so this is this is great oh
what's first of 19th 19th of January
I've never seen this before but it looks
nice
oh it was released in Europe oh
[Music]
Snapchat I was late
I wasn't ready
[Music]
maybe that's how I should do screamo
Spark's toad version
wait where's the peach game I just
realized
oh my God
huh
wow making yourself a ponytail suddenly
gives you new abilities
Magic
uh-huh
she's like a Disney princess
Cinderella
is it gonna blue is she gonna blue is
she gonna not blue oh
[Music]
sheesh okay
those pants
I'm gonna make her butt look really good
and people gonna draw it a lot again
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
wow
We're Cute
cute cute cute cute
Shape Shifter Peach the game
cute
at the local looks
I don't know how to describe this this
looks like uh
what does that remind me of
like fire blend wasn't what I was
thinking of but I I guess that could be
damn
looked cute though
layers I love layers oh oh pretty
wait what what company I didn't see this
this is not Square Enix is it it kind of
the art style kind of makes me think
it's quite Enix but it's not right
oh it is okay
um
looks like one of the Holo Stars
oh
yeah yeah battles
I made you yawn
oh she's just chilling on the ground
so is this a series too
looks good
damn so many Square Enix games
what
oh remastered okay well that's cool
though
why that means I could stream it easily
I never played this series before
ass
dinosaur
hmm
I I appreciate remasters of old games
like this on the switch because it makes
it so much easier to stream them
all expansions
oh
oh wait okay wow that's that's a big
difference wow
it's if you look at it like that it's
almost a remake
she is February
why not now
oh
detective Pikachu
I had this game
I've seen that before
I don't know about this because again
those that
those faces they look like did I say
this before I may have said this before
but it looks like it's for like some
kind of like
um 13 year old girl teenager uh uh Pony
game
like
horse horse
racing game
thank you for understanding
nice logo though cute
October well I'mma should play it maybe
I don't know
hmm
don't tell me there'll be a second one
oh DLC yeah what's with it
why are you saying it's just coming to
the switch was it on the switch before
oh it's a port oh yeah
[Music]
wait
uh
that's interesting
[Laughter]
oh God make it stop
oh local new off collab game guys Siri
can make a two-dooting concert stream
yay
oh no I don't know if that is a smart
idea but I I I it came to me so we shall
do it
oh God please don't stop don't
I will not say what it reminds me of but
this looks like something I've played
before
I guess that's just how that genre
always looks like
mm-hmm
whoa
this speaks to me on another level
this looks like a mix of games I've
played when I was younger
tight
you're saying it's gonna be gone later
but if I downloaded once I keep it right
is is that like the superstars
collection thingy
contra
uh I comes out on PC late Ah that's what
you mean so first only switch and then
later somewhere else ah okay okay cool
cool cool
on my door offline
this is like as a stream is such an
important question for me each time when
you say Co-op is it online or offline
oh wait this looks like audience fear
Style
like the art
uh oh my God
[Music]
ah okay very different very different
vanilla wear
what's that mean again
oh
it's kind of cool like
yeah oh oh that's the other three okay
see yeah I got the Vibes but also at the
same time
um that view that POV
from above keeps me
um some Square Enix game vibes
it's like a combination
ah old Fire Emblem
um
I like it
I like it oh
she's filled Amber oh
Atlas
makes a lot of sense they had a baby
Atlas at vanilla where sitting on a tree
kissing kissing and make baby
that makes so much sense oh oh wait a
second
hey Dave
okay
Papa I played this one I think
[Music]
did I only play the first one I mean
back in the day when I was younger
on GameCube I played Eva one or two oh
this was the 3DS one okay then I didn't
play it I only played the GameCube one
and now I of course
as you know played the newest one
on the switch
so it's a port from
DS to switch that's nice
it looks exactly like what we played
though and and what the GameCube one
looks like
like the ghosts and the rooms and the
mechanics and everything is the same
which
if it's a good
good thing that you created sure why not
that looks a bit different the ice stuff
looks undone
like sure why not reuse everything and
make the same thing over and over again
if it works it works
people love Luigi's Mansion
oh that was laggy
[Music]
creeps onto it okay
hi
oh
he didn't snap what does that mean
what is this
containers
are there shipping containers
let's go
where uh
uh-huh
oh
cool in in Kyoto
I
um history
will it be like the Ghibli Museum or
more like something else
[Music]
and will will it be as hard to get in as
Nintendo World and usj
oh
probably not
no Ganondorf yeah
this male girl kinda killed oh my God
why did nobody tell me about this
except for me like where am I
where am I guys
hi snippity snap
I can't snap with my
no ububi Nobi hands
[Music]
f-zero
whoa 99
whoa
what
what a new uh let's let's cancel Mario
Kart tournament to us Empire forever and
replace it with this from now on
how laggy is it
gonna be
this is like
um
Fall Guys
but with f-zero
okay
my unnecessary comparisons I'm so sorry
I see
give me a f-zero new game though not
none are you guys excited about this
I guess
it's fun
yeah no yeah it's silly
ah okay
online members once again winning
battle around
I need to get that that's so cute
this thing is so cute retro
oh it's so small
are you gonna snap no man
oh cute
wait that is so cute
wait that is such a like comfy feel good
looking game
oh my God
what is this League of Legends
wait this is so cute what why would
League of Legends make something like
this
so it's like League of Legends but
Animal Crossing in pixel Style
they make a lot of side caves
oh
interesting it looks cute though
wait they look familiar
what was this again
oh
is this Co-op game
another League of Legends
ah
you have my interest if it's a co-op
game
but I guess it's not
oh no
I'm I'm uh
my experience of Huawei aware was so
overwhelming uh I don't know
what's up
that's me
they know I'm watching what's
[Laughter]
this is this is like
why are we aware but that game that I
played with good on
CE you switch was it
I like it but it's so stressful like it
looks nice now but
how cute
ah but the game is so stressful
move it
is
so stressful
maybe this one's less stressful oh
RPG game games
oh and you then
wow
no
hmm
is don't tendo really screaming I wonder
nah he's fine right
that looks pretty
oh oh the world is so HD well the
characters are pixel it's a it's an
interesting combination of styles oh wow
or something like that
[Music]
stay in sting
interesting it's very unique
PPP
oh it's a DLC
kind of cute
but I
I don't know it's it's it's kill the
pixel style aside the Aesthetics are
really cute in this one
so is that a farming game
poor Groove
is that well known
Advanced Wars Middle Ages oh I like that
idea
wait is it really that
is that what it is
this is cute but what if what's with
this pixel game segment
they're doing it purposefully right
getting everything together
I would like to play this
20 years ago no maybe 15.
another one
I can see someone streaming this
has been playing this what really no way
oh
this is definitely a stream game I can
see it
it's nice Pomo loves this game a few
other Japanese girls have played a Kyla
played it
wait so
was it did they play it on a different
console
the fight or finally man
oh
Daisy
[Music]
Kong you said that way more excitedly
than Funky Kong what's this bias that
you have oh
Pauline
I had absolutely know nothing about
Pauline and never played a game where
she was in pizza
nobody asked for pizza wow but sometimes
you don't know what you should be asking
for and you're happy when you get it
where's my bow said
wait was bow said I can't remember was
that something that fans completely made
up or was it
I can't remember anymore
it's it's become so Canon
it was fan made oh God it's so Canon
though
oh what
new new maps or among us too or
um
this is why I hate mushrooms guys
happens so often
oh they're stranded on the night I'm
gonna play them on the island instead of
in the universe okay cool cool new map
oh
oh it's like survival in the wild I know
a lot about that
welcome to
the fungus
uh-huh
wait is it gonna be only on the switch
version
wait it's already 38.
big announcements dokle wasn't this
supposed to be 40 minutes
I feel like I'm missing something big
I I
mean even then there's only one big
thing now considering the time
uh
it's Nintendo Dover
honey honey
I thought this would be more hype
it was just a normal Direct
better be good ice no snap
oh
Paper Mario
it's cute
okay
why it looks really good but I don't
really have a connection with Paper
Mario
I looks good though
[Music]
um
it looks good and might make me want to
play it
um
Dom tender will be happy
Thousand-Year Door
[Music]
is this a remake or a new one
or frozen your door what is that the
music track or
it's a remake
okay
oh no not you
[Music]
the second Paper Mario game uh-huh Yoshi
oh
I'm enjoying the soundtrack a lot
my God the music
this is a music remix remade too
it must be right that's what they do
with Rema remix wow
the Thousand Year Door hmm
that's that's it that's all you got
Nintendo
it looks good though who's cute maybe
I'll play it
it's possible dad well you're in love
what you're talking to a machine will
you teach me this thing called love what
the Peach how this bird are you
where's Mario where's Mario in the
machine or what
uh-huh
hmm
yeah no the graphics look really really
really cute they did a great job at
making the the paper gimmick
look even more HD hmm
2024 but nothing concrete but that's it
oh wow okay
hmm
um
uh excuse me
where's my
where's my snowboarding game
[Laughter]
where's Daddy
you promised me years ago no months ago
um
it's not out yet no you would have told
me you guys would have told me I've been
waiting I checked like a while ago if
it's out by now I thought oh it must be
out by now it wasn't
[Laughter]
no no no it's like upcoming it's one of
the things upcoming on the online
Nintendo online rate the Nintendo Direct
it it it it wasn't just a normal one I
thought it would be more like whoa whoa
what was it this oh
it had everything I want that's good I'm
happy for you I mean there definitely
were some interesting games there but it
just felt like really normal you know
what I mean
yeah I
guess they did
switch continues to be their most recent
console
um
well
or maybe that's why
they're not bringing so many new games
because
oh wow you know what I mean
ah oh yeah apparently there's also a
state of play today at 11 PM my time but
I won't watch along that one because
yeah I'm sure that one has gotta have
great announcements though
maybe I'll watch it but not stream it
how do they tell each other hey uh
Playstation Channel I'm doing a Nintendo
Direct on this day do you wanna like you
know
same as these you know and then they're
like hell yeah let's go uh I'll do it
also on this day or why do they choose
this day they must they must like
they text each other
muffin Xbox
it's deliberately right but like is it
maybe like friendly or is it like one
company hears that the other company is
doing it on the day so they decide to do
it also on the same day to get their
attention but like is that really
necessary I feel like you it's not
really necessary to do that so
[Music]
um
like why
ah
what's happening
oh yeah right oh man I missed Tokyo game
show I've been like several times like
maybe I don't know five times six times
seven times in my life
I really like the new game show and it's
been a while
[Music]
yeah I've been I've been many times in
the past
um 10 years
um
[Music]
you would love to hear tangents about it
seems really fun
it's just you know you know how
conventions in of like you know America
or Europe and so on you know how animal
conventions are there
um so Anime conventions like that don't
really exist in Japan ironically comic
is very different for example compared
to anime convention but TGs if anything
gets a little bit more closer to that a
little bit it's so different but a
little bit and that's why I really liked
it when I was in Japan I was like oh
yeah
I like this more than comicat hmm
yeah but it's still very different
because it focuses on you know having a
lot of Publishers there which Anime
conventions obviously don't have but but
it's like you know because comicat is
all about dojin like like independent
people you know having a ton of
like little tables next to each other
crowded as that's that's very
different the the atmosphere is closer
to an anime convention with TGs in my
opinion but yeah
and also yeah it's just it's just a bit
more interesting but for me seeing all
the Publishers booths yeah they go all
out
um yeah
hmm
yeah so uh nothing really that
what what even stayed in my memories
uh
uh the peach game is possibly
the most interesting to me
um yeah I have to re-watch that peach
game part
some people were are apparently hoping
for something called Silk song right
what's silk song I only know Silk Road
ah this game it's like Hollow Knight
an upcoming game also people already
know about that one
I only know
Silk Road
what wait so crowd the game I mean the
MMORPG not the real
Silk Road the surface of Silk Road guys
were so shitty you could never get in I
think from my memory
one of those games one of those online
MMORPGs where the servers were like
impossible to to enter
um
but yeah anyway
oh my God everything's glitching first
it was OBS now it's my chat window
what the hell is going on oh well guys
thank you for watching uh it's my day
off so I'm gone now gotta keep it short
and quit some snacking and I'll go do my
work
[Music]
um
record like free things today I will
record free things today and I probably
have to
sign a couple hundred cards at least to
catch up because it turns out I have to
sign like
uh
zero What's the accurate way to say it
0.5
like half
the amount of what I thought I was
signing I'm signing extra
just
just because I have to
and they won't even use it probably so
great
yeah 50 more
basically in case that I up fifty
percent of my cards they will use that
but I I don't I've signed like I don't
know 400 500 and 400 maybe 400 cards
maybe so far and I know by fact that I
messed up four maybe yeah four cards
so is it really necessary apparently yes
I've been told I have to
um
what if I just
I will not tell you of my devilish plans
yeah in the case it gets damaged and all
that but the way I have to package it to
send it back is so carefully packaged
trust me nothing is going to happen to
these cards because basically they
arrived already like
you know you know you saw those cases
probably in my member stream they arrive
in these like plastic cases 100 cards uh
per case so they're all like separate
even inside the plastic cases there's
bubble wrap and and paper and it's
sealed with tape and all that and
they're really like solid and then all
these plastic cases are in a box that's
also like secured with like paper and
bubble wrap so it's like
super super
secure okay
nothing happens to these cards
ah and I have to like send it back the
same way
so
um
yeah yeah of course it's good that it's
so secure because you know don't wanna
when I wanna lose and waste all these
cards
um anyway I'm gonna go maybe I'll also
take an hour nap because I was supposed
to sleep long anyway I
mean Savages and tomorrow is memory is
only three streams I'll see you there
and then on the weekend we have
uh GTA DLCs on Saturday and then uh
Sunday night
um this is gonna be a late stream again
I'll have Baldur's Gate with the group
as far as I remember I've been
[Music]
please buy my uh merchandise if you care
uh if you want my
my
uh uh here
yes it link is in the description my
third anniversary uh merch uh
merchandise and also we renounced some
more yesterday
uh on streaming in the Amish stream the
collab stream we have a few more things
no pressure though but yeah maybe I I
would I would I guess out of all those
things I would recommend if you don't
have the plushie yet the plushie but if
you have the plushie then I recommend
that keychain
um the unique one where we're like
looking sideways
our profile
um
that one is pretty
anyway thank you bye bye
what's up thank you for the support
[Music]
thank you