[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
hello everyone
double audio
double audio what what
really oh yeah it's fine
[Music]
you made me worry because i tried to
figure out what to do with the audio
today because i gotta i gotta let you
guys hear
discord but not hear my my desktop audio
from this
from the concert but i figured it out
thanks to ina ina helped me figure it
out
how are you doing guys
today we are watching together
whole life
live second best be on the stage
when did you hear that go
i had to change a bunch of my audio
settings it's very confusing did you
hear it
you heard the echo okay okay
i'm so confused right now yay
[Music]
beyond the stage i think we are all very
far
beyond the stage because everyone's
sitting at home right now
uh i am doing this watch along on both
uh day one and day two
by the way if you guys have your ticket
i know many of you are saying hey i have
money i don't have the ticket broken
hell yeah
but for the people who are actually
watching it together with me
um it starts in 30 minutes
and i'm doing the watch along on both
days you if you already have the ticket
you should be able to already get in and
there's like music playing right now and
the chat
there's a chat as well both on spwn and
on nikon
and today it will be only my voice and
maybe some of the other
life girls might give me a call because
uh
originally i was gonna do this alone but
the other girls are even though it's
probably a really bad time for most of
them
they also want to watch so uh they were
asking if they can join my
my stream a little bit some of them
maybe ina is definitely gonna join i
don't know about the other girls we will
see
if they decide to join
but yeah and
what else uh yeah stream is starting in
tournaments everyone
and i know many of you also had problems
getting the ticket
some of you probably still don't have a
ticket even though they want one
everyone check the description though i
am not
i have said i don't understand why some
people cannot read it's in the
description and
in the pinned comment i am not showing
the actual concept
you guys gotta have it open on your own
in another window you gotta pay for it
because this is paid content
it's a concert that you have to pay
money for it's a professional concert
though okay
it's an actual concert okay i'm not
gonna stream it i'm just gonna be here
and reacting with you guys
and maybe partially translating some
things
mc portions like when they talk and so
on i'm obviously not gonna
translate the songs but
i probably be translating some of the
mc's i mean
i'm not very good at life translating
while people are talking we talked about
this in my member stream yesterday
i'm not i'm i i'm not a professional
translator so
translating while people are still
talking at the same time as me
is gonna be hard but i'm gonna try to
give you guys a
a rough overview of what they're talking
about which is what i got permission for
uh from my broken sending a red super
chat
did you buy the ticket though did you
buy the concert ticket though priority
is my friend
priorities
priorities okay
what was i talking about oh yeah i got
permission to
uh talk about what's happening i was
wondering because like obviously this is
paid content
so i wasn't sure how detailed i can be
with what's going on but don't worry i
got uh my manager
and my manager told me what
is okay and what is not okay actually
basically pretty much everything is okay
except
i'm not allowed to show the stream uh
the concert on stream of course not
of course not
um oh yeah so yeah uh
if you wanna watch it but you can't
purchase a ticket now
i think since this
since the uh the live concert
will still be available a few days after
uh maybe you'll be able to buy the
ticket afterwards still
and then watch the archives pretty much
i'm not sure about that i cannot promise
but
the only thing i know is that there will
be an archive of some sort for a little
while
not not unlimited but it will be for a
certain amount of time
oh yeah yeah my watch along will also be
aircraft yes yes yes yes yes
in case you can't watch it right now but
you want to watch it later with me oh
that would be that would be lovely
oh yeah about the new opening and the
new uh screen here
all of this is um free materials
i got some free stuff
to make it more christmas themed it's
snowing in here it's snowing
the loading screen was also cute right
for the loading screen i
i was i'm using takuma's gif
animation thank you dakuma oh thank you
for another random
chat here's my watch along ticket you
paid the wrong person
that shocked me because that was
suddenly very loud
what's going on what's going on there's
some advertisements going on okay this
is not whole life related though
hey can you see how many people are
watching this no
dark mode let's turn dark mode on oh
yeah
hey should i write a comment i can write
the comments in my twitter account
hello no i'm okay better not better not
okay then the concert is starting in 20
minutes wow
let me let me check in on my members if
they
casper has been very noisy again let me
check in on my members if they're coming
on hunt
surprisingly everyone's awake
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] casper
casper is like super noisy
i'm always like oh my god casper is like
so close to making a new hole
there's like um a new campaign
with like a bunch of free girls from
whole life and some
some other youtubers and some real idols
some something in my campaign am i in my
campaign i don't know
that was just an advertisement on the on
the stream right now for the people
who are watching without watching the
actual concert
okay how many of you guys are watching
the stream but are not watching the
concert
because they couldn't buy a ticket for
whatever reason
maybe oh my god it's gonna be boring
guys
i'm just gonna be screaming and inna
will be like
are you guys for real oh my god there's
so many
my card rejected oh down your reaction
is enough oh that's cute
though is this where i can buy the
tickets no
no no no no no
oh my god i hope you bought the ticket i
hope you guys bought the actual ticket
everyone's
everyone who's super chatting i hope you
bought the actual ticket
wow here's my payment for the ticket
thank you guys for the memberships too
i'm fine with watching your stream and
watching your reaction because i'm used
to this youtube and investing days and
he does watch-alongs all the time
so you never watch what that youtuber
watches you only watch your reactions
thank you patrick chen entertain says
kiana it's because of this water long
that i decided to buy the ticket oh
see it's because of me am i getting my
commission or not
whole life being able to experience this
life of you and kfb will be
unforgettable yay
just kidding by the way i'm not getting
a commission i am doing this
completely on my own will
say
also i uploaded my weekly schedule today
but shortly after i uploaded
unfortunately
did you guys see my weekly schedule
right after i uploaded it i
got the information
that i have to move hello talk to one
day later so
uh fire emblem will be one day before
but the same time and whole talk will be
one day later but the same time
do you understand which will
which means that holotalk this week will
not be on friday evening for america but
it will be on saturday evening for
america okie dokie
i don't want to remake the whole
schedule so you just gotta take my word
for it
okay even better okay good awesome
awesome
yeah the next question talk will be on
senpai
a hint for the secret co-op yes
uh it's not on my channel
it's on someone else's channel and
the person who i'm collabing with
is on day number one it seems
performing on day number one
now who do you think it is it's someone
you someone who i didn't collab with
before
hair color
blonde it's not so much of a secret
anymore
i i got permission to already talk about
it but
someone blonde
but it will be a japanese collab i think
because um
as far as i know that person doesn't
speak uh
english
not at all i think all right
let me tell you it's a very sexy it's
very sexy
well all the blondes on here are super
sexy
actually most of the most of the blondes
all alive
there there's not a single i mean maybe
vata my senpai is not so much on the sex
side maybe more on the cute side but all
the other blondes
are sexy wouldn't you agree with me
[Laughter]
look at this picture and tell me that
the blondes aren't like super
hot
agreed yes i think vatami senpai is um
could could be sexy if she wanted to
but she's more on the on the cute side
what the hell am i talking about
i i'm actually worried a little bit that
i will be able to watch
the the show um in over 480p
because as as most of you know i'm in
japan
and right now is not quite prime time
just yet
but around 8 p.m which will be in the
middle of the concert
prime time starts and that's when my
download speed goes from 300 mbps
to 1 mbps i am not kidding
and my upload still stays like super
high which is why
i a streaming is not a problem streaming
itself is not a problem since i'm not
showing anything
so upload speed stays around 300 400
mbps which is insane
thank god but
i might not be able to watch the concert
in anything
above 480 feet
even right now the quality i set it
pretty low because i don't want to risk
it it's okay
i'll watch it in higher
quality later
i could if there's a possibility as well
that
maybe maybe my stream my my concert
stream
the concert itself not not this stream
but maybe the concert itself will even
crash
for me in that case i will watch it on
my phone with my pocket wi-fi
with my mobile wi-fi
oh a concert that
could be oh is that
that is the is that the chocolate card
thingy that they have going on
no that's not it that's not it something
else like
you guys must be so jealous of me
because i live in japan and there's like
so much going on
like whole life related like apparently
in like in like convenience stores
they're selling like whole live
chocolate right now and before they were
selling whole life curry and whole life
potato
chips and all that kind of stuff don't
rub it in
and there's even more coming
they just don't stop they just keep
pushing out these these
these contents oh my god
please stop this painting i've never
been more jealous
and i think oh yeah right now there's
like on train stations
in tokyo uh on one specific train
station
there is uh also a whole life character
is
pretty big i didn't see it yet because i
don't go outside
[Music]
cute
i don't quite understand what that is
the advertisement that just came up oh
wait
you might hear my voice sir
listen
we're doing like english members are
doing narration
now it's japanese but i think english is
following
i can't hear a thing well you probably
don't have a ticket
uh the warnings on the screen yeah guys
don't take if you have a ticket
screenshots are okay you can upload
screenshots on twitter and whatever but
no clips no video no audio
okay
we will block the [\h__\h] out of you if you
upload any content that
besides screenshots we will block the
[\h__\h] out of you
are they gonna are they gonna play the
english audio we recorded like english
an english version of what's going on
right now
holoen members
maybe after the japanese version
it's me and kelly
money
exactly
huh
yeah that was us on uh on the
on the first day it's me and callie and
on the second day it's the other free
girls
announced
no it's the second generation of
indonesia again
announcing an indonesian
ah
let me ask you guys something let me ask
my manager something for you guys
if people are people still able to buy a
ticket afterwards and wants to stream
afterwards because for the people who
bought it already they can watch it
afterwards right
but if you buy a ticket later oh it's
possible it's possible guys
you can still buy a ticket after the
live show
um okay oh gilgio that's awesome
since so many people you can buy
afterwards
until 11 january so that's enough time
even if you're not
able to get a ticket right now because
uh of survey issues you'll be able to
get it until
january 11th thank you
all right the archive is until january
11th as well so latest time to buy a
ticket is
january 11th 11th okie dokie
oh the announcements are over
here i'm happy that
they put me and kelly together for the
announcement
which was not we did not decided okay
let me just say it was not
it was not us who decided that it was
the staff who were like
oh it would be the best choice to put
takamori together yes yes yes
they know even the management is
shipping us improvement stamp approved
bunk i want like a stamp animation that
i can play whenever on
my screen where it just suddenly there's
a stamp
stamping the screen and it just says
approved or denied i want something like
that i'm sure there's something like
that already
am i allowed to hum
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
please come for us okay well
done
we're just still waiting it's four more
minutes guys four more minutes four more
minutes
can you believe this is only the second
concert of whole life i would i would
think they would have already had more
concerts but i guess like because
especially this year
it's just difficult to have more more
than one concert
i'm worried about my internet connection
oh which also means in four minutes uh
ina should join
oh thank you my credit card keeps
getting rejected
oh man i'm sorry for the guys who
weren't able to
get the ticket on time because of
that are nothing you can really do about
anything about
it
system too busy
since yesterday but why okay guys the
tickets have been out for how long a
month maybe
why don't you just do it on the last
minute this is exactly
why you buy things beforehand and not on
the last minute
but i know i know when i went to school
i also did my homework on like sometimes
even on the day
an hour before i should give it to the
teacher
i know i know i know no blooney tantrum
i'm sorry
getting called out i'm sorry
hopefully um hopefully next time
whenever there's another concert maybe
it will be a bit easier for overseas
people to access
because there's more and more overseas
viewers
oh guys guys i'm allowed to hint
something
the en members uh are not participating
in this contest a
contest in this concert but there is
something something something something
in the intermission of the concert that
you might
uh want to look forward to
i love how my own love makes me feel
what makes me makes me laugh about
myself
nice
i don't know how much i can translate
for you guys because i'll be too excited
probably
i've made you uh i've brought your your
hopes up
sorry
why am i nervous
okay time to look at the actual screen
and not in my
at my guys chat let me know if
something's wrong on
on my on my stream
because i'm not i only have one monitor
still it's coming tomorrow i ordered the
monitor for tomorrow
it's happening
two kiara chilled
oh my god
ten nine eight seven
six five four three
two
[Music]
i
i i i i
i i
oh
[Music]
my
hey
see
imagination
is ready to do this for three hours or i
don't know how long it is but
oh my god vatima's boobs are wobbling so
hard
those bulbs
am i helping your imagination guys
is so different
[Music]
wait i love the size difference though
it's obvious that one
one one of the girls is very huge
very tall excuse me
boing boing boing boing
[Laughter]
amazing
yay
[Music]
you're welcoming all of us
and breathing hard
elbow their best to hype up the stage as
the opening act
oh they'll introduce themselves now
[Music]
she was waiting for this moment
do i have to translate the nah baby
noises baby noises baby noises
baby noises
she's a she's
out of breath
tmt
yay
it's just basically saying uh hello this
is me
let's have fun together
she's excited please enjoy today
oh she was she was very uh
looking forward to one day stand on the
stage with the others
same
oh oh someone is gonna sing solo
from the fourth generation
oh
[Music]
me does that make sense i can't speak
english
oh
yeah i'm delayed a little bit not only
because of the stream but my
my screen my my concert is delayed
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
hmm
oh my she's so good
oh yes hit some high notes do it
yes
hi this is beautiful
wait is it is this an actual
stage with a screen on top of it or am i
yeah it is right because the stage is
not 3d the stage is real but the screen
on it is a
a screen right looks like it
[Music]
yeah like mikko's concert yeah
yeah i wish i could be
like at the stage like in front of the
stage
and watch it like actually happening oh
man
oh it's so pretty really
want to see it for real next year
but i mean guys probably next time
maybe probably i can't watch it as a
viewer i might be there
up by my up on like i i might
actually be up there don't you think
so no no next year
cute she's so cute
your singing is so good
get those get those chicken glow sticks
out there
nice
very good very very very good i see a
camera moving in the bottom this is
surreal
solo
wait what is this song
what is the song
echo
wait she said she's singing good
hey hey hey hey hey
a a a a
a a hey hey
oh yeah swing that tail swing it
what what what was wrong about saying
that
oh boy boring boring boy oh yeah boy
i can do that too hey
hey
[Applause]
oh my god
the crab walk
her eyes look crazy
oh i can't do that
i can't do that i can't move my
my head away from my neck
wait it's buffering for me
don't bother coming it's buffering for
you guys too
it's buffering for me no
[Music]
oh come on she's just [\h__\h] bumpery
oh come on please
let me put the oh it's back but that's
probably more delay for us guys
ah but i can wait i can go
there okay now i'm back on time with you
guys
those hips were hitting my internet too
hard
whoa crap you guys too now
are we on time pretty much she's left
the stage
oh her original song
cat sheep
oh i buffered for a second
[Music]
wave your hands everyone
oh
cute
[Music]
oh
oh this is so cute
your singing is so good too
[Music]
oh
everyone wow
[Music]
oh
i only buffered for one second though i
think i'm pretty close to you guys still
[Music]
oh
this song is really good with an
audience i hope she can sing it with a
real audience
sometime
she's asking if you're ready to enjoy
this day
it just started let's [\h__\h] go hype
that's what you sing
[Music]
cat
boy
cute
so good amazing amazing
your singing is so good oh my god what
the hell
did she just um what do you what do you
call that in english
did she just do a cartwheel i can't do a
cartwheel
i hope she can teach me how to do a
holy [\h__\h] you can do an actual cartwheel
they're talking about their feelings of
about their own performances now
and praising each other
oh no
which generation is next
and by senpai
oh which generation is next
here wait you guys hear enough can you
speak again
[Music]
wait a second wait a second wait a
second wait a second wait a second which
one was it again
wait wait which one was it
oh wait i'm confused which one was it
wait wait
wait what's going on ah
okay one second i'll do it like that
how how about can you talk
hello oh there we go this one was it
okay okay
what's up welcome
[Music]
hi i sang over for you guys but kiara
muted me so that you can hear it
i'm not on purpose not on purpose you
know it's watching the rest of the
concert with me together i suppose
uh i would hope so did you watch the
the first part up until now yeah i was
uh i was running back from the shrine
i'm telling you back up welcome back
wait i gotta make the concert audio
laura for you and there you go
it's okay i'll just speak louder
but i want to hear you
oh yeah
i'll make you louder in the discard ah
your maximum discard goddammit i think i
mean for the stream it's no problem i
think they'll hear you
nicely
for the viewers there's a video right
now where
every member is getting introduced ah
nice soon
who is next who is next wait are you in
do you already see which song is next oh
there we go
oh my gosh
i'm gonna spoil the stream
i i i i i
i i i i'll be doing this the whole time
uh
[Music]
so cute
they're doing the choreography
someone call kelly because i'm about to
die from cuteness
ah
[Music]
one day we will be up there do you
realize that
i don't know if i'll make it carol of
course you can don't die
i'm dying you're ready you're ready
yourself was so cute
how many uh uh i know your age is uh re
redacted was it
but you probably like a million years
old aren't you you can do a few more
come on
[Music]
this is my favorite whole life soggy
though
i sang this in my in my debut didn't i
um as far as i remember
yeah you don't even see her hands
hi
[Music]
foreign
i like i like the chibi that you drew
for senpai
that was cute
oh i'm gonna cry
[Music]
bye
ah
[Music]
my
that was cute and so pretty too everyone
was
dancing as well
yeah so this is welcoming everyone to
day one
oh it's kind of sad with no audience we
gotta scream louder you and me you know
oh
i love her idol outfit i mean it's not
it's not then the whole live idol outfit
but like you're updated
at the right it's so she's getting
another did you know she's getting
another update
like two days from now
no no no um yeah yeah then i heard yeah
she's getting
[Music]
okay i shook my head too fast
because if i said you should look at her
being an elite idol
oh my god how cute
uh
oh my god
so cute she's so tiny
oh my gosh she's really small
[Music]
onion
very cute need to poke need to put my
finger
into her belly button i'm sorry i'm
sorry take it back
keep her away from stealing senpai
is my next total talk guest by the way
for away don't worry it's uh only
through discord
hmm
m
did you just on purpose say some kind of
joke in japanese which implies she has a
big
uh chest because she said muniga
but in a way like never mind
[Laughter]
you're like a good like 20 seconds
behind me
you gotta you gotta react delayed enough
for me
oh yeah but you're watching it on nico
nicole right yes
oh maybe maybe nico nico is a bit
earlier
what are you laughing about inna in the
future
you'll see you'll see
the idle step a point
point amazing idle step
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
good morning okay
[Music]
stop reacting so ellie are you following
me
[Laughter]
is it have you tried to try
hi
me
can you hold it like 20 seconds faster
please
you should be slower oh
for everyone who doesn't have a ticket
my in senpai is doing a really sexy
dance right now okay you better regret
not getting a ticket
is
[Music]
foreign
enough fangirling
her movements are so cute
did you even see that that pop-up when
you saw it 20 seconds ago the
this life is sensitive pop-up
in japanese
she got banned
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
you're so early that you're too late for
me
she is so amazing
[Music]
[Applause]
my
foreign
what
what did you say uh taking my headphones
off for obvious reasons
oh you're taking your headphones off for
obvious reasons what
oh
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
yay oh my god the way she walks is so
cute
oh my god
ugh
[Laughter]
aah
ah
[Laughter]
laughs
[Music]
oh man guys
i love you being good
my
[Music]
can i see
crying
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah oh
oh my god she's so cute yeah
oh my god
oh my god i don't think i've heard this
song before
yeah i don't know it either what this is
it's just so adorable um
does someone know the song in the chat
oh
i love her she's so cute
oh my god i need to blow my nose
myself for a second i need to blow my
nose
oh i'm back
welcome back let's see if piccolo senpai
sings one more time i might cry again
you know there's still group songs right
yeah probably i
feel i should probably sing with mikko
senpai
[Music]
um
oh lucia is so cute what an angel
her voice is so soft
so calming
hey
i like the green blue color theme and
the graphics as well
[Music]
she's turning around turning around
oh my god oh my god kawaii
oh my second
i need to re-watch bakura's uh song
when i'm like calm and not streaming
i was like screaming so much
good thing you cannot re-watch the
stream yeah until 11th january
um again and again and again and again
yes she's asking if the comments are
hyped up are you guys hyped up the
problem is the different
her feelings have arrived in my heart
oh she told us she loves us oh my god
guys did you hear that she loves us
she loves us but she probably loves me
more than you guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
what don't spoil me
miko senpai is coming
that was amazing
okay she she claimed yesterday in a
stream that she
can do more than her usual battle dance
she said she practiced a a choreography
mm-hmm let's see that thing shut off now
maybe i think so
oh
i love this song
hmm
[Music]
sakura or the people who are who don't
have a ticket
it's really pretty there's like
there's a uh cherry blossom
petals flower flying around
and she's doing a cute little dance too
it's all pink and your voice is so
soothing
come on
oh
mm-hmm
[Music]
she's so cute no
indeed elite idol i have to agree
wait it's making me emotional the song
is so cute
so pretty
yay
who's next tell me the future you know
what does your ball say
what what it's a message from mikko
senpai
oh wait there's someone behind her who
could that possibly be
so right now on stage is mikko senpai
and money senpai
[Music]
she said exactly
oh she messed up her greeting
[Music]
yay
mikomari
she said that she's getting a lot of
happiness and energy from seeing
so many comments uh rooting for them
you know i know you understand this i am
i'm this is kind of awkward i'm
translating
from my viewers i know you understand
this i knew i said yeah
it's still awkward
but i'm glad you're here with me either
really yes yes i love you
really yes of course i do
i love you don't doubt it i love you
oh there's a announcement
[\h__\h] she's saying
her announcements they will they're
going to marry
[Laughter]
that'll step
oh sh maddie said by saying after
practicing so much with mikko she has
been
um feeling some special feelings towards
because stephanie what the [\h__\h] is
[Laughter]
he's doing a very extreme version of the
idol step
idle skiing i would call that
ice skating
uh she's saying that in the first um
whole live concert everyone was just
dancing randomly
when sss was uh being performed but this
time they
actually had an a little choreography
and everyone was doing the same movement
so they definitely improved it
mm-hmm
they're talking about it's uh like a
song and do something by song
oh why somebody
says that she made her choreography for
her
own song on her own and then the
choreography kind of helped her fix some
parts
interesting knowledge
okay
talking about the comments again
who's next who's next oh
oh what's next
it's still black for me black black
black black black
so black there we go
all right so for the people who don't
have a ticket
joko sensei is now singing fan service
alone on stage
[Music]
oh
ignore me
[Laughter]
are you standing in the crowd with like
a headband
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you cry you're like yeah thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's me that's me you described
exactly me
what do you mean i just described myself
oh oh
oh you too are you
are you ready
what are you laughing about
okay
hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi
i'm very quiet oh
mata
[Music]
broke my voice there
cute i love this song i love honey works
maybe say you're spoiling me again
is my little senpai next applies
surprise
i guess it's mellow senpai next
oh
violence trigger
is this a what is this song
violence trigger vocaloid maybe
vocalized okay when in doubt vocaloid
think it's violence
trigger if i read it correctly so
right now it's medicine by alone on
stage singing
violence trigger what i think maybe
vocaloid
go low light and latency mode okay
oh yeah uh where am i now
what what exactly does low latency do
again
buoyancy uh right now i see her
uh walking to the right side now she
moved to the left side she's walking to
the left side
are we on time now you know she's um
it's hard to explain what she's doing
she's walking to the left and now
she's going back to the right side
and now i'm caught up okay okay okay my
chat is saying i'm caught up
[Music]
probably you are still in the future
probably
oh god she's so cute
i love her outfit so much it's quite um
open here and there but i love it
not youtube friendly not the reason why
i like it totally nuts
uh-huh totally totally
i didn't know this song but it's a good
song
oh i am fascinated by her beauty
that singing was great amazing a pass
everyone i think you're gonna call up
now
[Music]
oh
red heart alone on stage
it's just this is her original song
though
oh my gosh she's so cute
bad heart grand heart
red heart
etm
we have full version has she never
published a full version up until now
apparently the chat is like
apparently this is a new thing oh i knew
the song but i didn't know there was no
full version of it
oh the first full version oh
see i didn't even know that the chat
taught me something thank you guys
hi hi
i didn't see that coming
well whole life english is uh now
represented in this concert as well
because this is a
fully english song from an unofficial
hololive english member
unofficial official member
whole life english represented
red height red heart
red heart
red heart red heart
red heart clap
clap
cute
[Music]
thank you for representing whole live
english in this concert
oh i know the song
is it how that works probably yeah
sounds like honey wigs
okay
sounds like honey works
um 27 which is pronounced as deco nina
yes
yes oh baby
yeah i love this but my brain
doesn't work same thing
i think i've been awake for too long
oh
someone made a pun in my chat uh dicko
nina with the last few letters
ena in big
hinting at you ina
your bad pun fans are in my chat
[Laughter]
oh says the person who put up the uh
like uh yeah on twitter
that was amazing and edited it was
amazing
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you liked it
it's a birch jokes okay bird jokes are
best jokes
i don't know i think some of it flew
over some of the people's heads
you know
what
this is uh
insanely adorable
i love the way she sang that part
yeah you can hear her emotion in the
singing
she's like dude just tell me you love me
already what the hell
oh that was cute
oh my gosh who's next what's next who's
next
oh it's an emc part i think talking part
again
cute oh my god
oh they're saying they're super super
nervous
but the comments are helping them very
much they say
oh my god the boing boing is too strong
holy [\h__\h]
playing boy the boy duo
free the boobies i i i like this free
the boobies
let them let them feel the air don't
hide them
oh what
they just they just hugged each other in
a very
very tedious way
[Music]
they kissed that was not a hug was it a
kiss what
it looked like a like a hug to me i'm
not sure i have to re-watch the
situation
they're saying that hatama's english was
very very cool very
very in very impressing
now they're talking about senpai's
performance saying that otamamushi was
really adorable
and then she was freaking out behind the
stage
they got a lot of practice in dancing
and singing for this day
oh they felt like when they were
practicing they felt like oh wait i'm an
idol they realized it
can't wait for you to do the same kiara
me neither i can't wait let's go
now maybe they can take me in tomorrow
i'm free
i can cancel my watch along i can come
i can sing hinotoni just put me in there
as
a cardboard it's okay no problem
my my life to the cafe papa made me look
so
good anyway i almost look like fruity
yeah she's asking the audience to use
the hashtag and uh asking if everyone
already tweeted about it
i don't think it's already trending
number one according to my chat so
oh
is it really trending worldwide number
one she just said on
in the concert that it's uh number one
worldwide
wow a number three worldwide
worldwide number one it was one of them
oh
nice story everyone keep on tweeting
keep on tweeting
i'm running really low on energy oh
no problem oh how
are you oh what
did i read that right i forget
yeah i'm crashing i read it right
i read the kanji good job
thanks but she sings so beautifully
oh right now it's azuki senpai solo on
[Music]
stage
you're very emotional
where can i report illegal transmission
uh
i don't no
i i guess you could tweet it to the
hololive official account
or go on the whole live official
homepage
and report it there there is a contact
form there
they should see it pretty soon the cover
official homepage whole live official
homepage cover has a report form
thank you for reporting like thank you
for wanting to report by the way that's
uh
very appreciated
oh what
oh very nice very beautiful
your singing is so pretty
ah oh
she sounds like she's crying
oh my
dog and look
this is so good yeah
i have to simp what do i do with these
feelings that i i need to simp where do
i set my super chat
oh man i wonder if our goods are still
on sale because i
remember seeing man i wonder
her uh recent concert goods
the hoodie look really really good oh
ah that was beautiful
nice and bye
that was beautiful so emotional
a closing bye
ah my heart
okay for people with no ticket aqua
senpai is on stage right now and she's
insanely adorable
is her song
[Music]
even with choreography oh
cute that's i think the most
choreography i've seen today from
someone
ah she's so cute
how can someone be so cute how
oh she's so cute oh my god
oh my he's so cute
you guys with no ticket you're missing
out on something right now you better
get it afterwards
you can still get it until 11th of
january okay
guys
there's still time use the money you get
from your parents for christmas or
something
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey ah she's so cute
oh my god that's really um out of all
songs that have been performed until now
that's the most choreographed song yet
well she didn't have her uh solo concert
not too long ago
oh yeah i didn't watch that one
it was very cute oh my god
my onion friend i'm also an onion if i
take off my hats
i feel connected to her
ah
that's such an idol song i love it so
cute
oh
[Music]
so cute okay now it's time for solace
by so long love story is the name of the
song
hi hi hi hi hi
oh gee on stage guys
ah she's dancing so energetic i like it
so much power so much energy
oh she's such a good dancer what the
hell what true idol
yeah the real idol of whole life
yago is crying right now is crying are
you okay
[Music]
hi hi hi hi
she told you guys to comment more
follow her order she is she is number
one her life i know
do
good super chat
yago are you okay
[Music]
yay
[Applause]
wow i would say that's 10 out of 10
that's worth a 10 out of 10 mode
mikko marine
[Music]
are talking on stage right now not
singing talking talking for everyone who
doesn't have a ticket
let me help your imagination
i want to check if you guys are still
energetic
yes yes you are nice so
you guys are still kinky gang
my senpai's movement is just so
so so cute
uh
oh information what
was it just she said there there's like
it's like a like a little break
intermission though oh is it
intermission time
i told my viewers there's something
special in the mission time
i'm not allowed to say what but
well she's talking about what she's
doing recently like uh being on the
radio show with fubuki senpai
oh they're doing an extra radio show
radio show uh
on with four members on how how the
constituent as well
because advertising that she is now a
card in
vanguard
nice sponsorship
it's promotion time
i like how when money senpai is talking
she keeps on bouncing from left to right
how cute you know is uh a bit tired
right
i might have to dip during the
intermission okay okay no problem
yeah tried but i've been awake for more
than 24 hours
oh my god no enjoy the rest
in in bed oh okay you mean you're
leaving right now
oh during the intermission after well
answer the information
okay okay
again after white i guess
but i'll try to watch the rest in there
before i actually like
go to dreamland wait there's an
announcement
what what
later maybe
oh announcement
special what special card pick
carpet card pack a card bag
oh a special card card pack for for
vanguard
um i think so special dick
carpet
so
bye bye are they gonna change into their
idol oh
[Music]
is it intermission time no oh yes okay
probably in this intermission
is where something special will happen
something regarding um me
also
what could it be what could it be
oh my god
play that music see then it was kiana
bgm
forever second that was my vgm
these are original holographs right
what is it yeah there you go okay this
is it
see that's me and at the top right did
you see me and me and kelly
okay listen it's a new version guys
coming soon coming soon
you guys ready
there we go
almost almost
now
once again the management knows what
they're doing
the second uh day it's it might be
different members
but on the first day it's me and kelly
[Music]
tomorrow i might see you in this kind of
situation
looking forward to that
okay i'm gonna go i'm gonna go down yeah
sweet okay good night thanks for coming
bye
[Music]
oh she's gone
thank you enough for coming
[Music]
oh oh a trio
oh they bring that are they idol outfits
oh it's azaki senpai and
soda senpai and mega senpai
adrenaline wait another song isn't this
some
anime song wait i love the song where do
i know this from
oh my god
[Music]
day
i i i i
done
hi
[Music]
oh
hmm
hi no fool
yay i never heard the full version of
this song before
[Music]
sing more so i can refuel my imagination
i don't know the lyrics though
[Music]
is really cute oh my god they're wearing
the adult
idol outfits by the way right now so
before they were wearing their
usual outfits and now it's the idol
outfits
oh my god i want to see the the the
fourth generation in the idol outfits
in 3d oh my god isn't this the first
time
or am i going crazy it won't be the
first time right that we see them in 3d
and idle outfits
maybe they're keeping it until the end
yay go go go
nice that was adorable
oh next is
oh say bye
a duo performance that's an interesting
duo
um
[Music]
i love this song
do
empire is singing in a low voice
oh lucia senpai is that you
[Music]
hmm
um
russia senpai
she looks so cute in the idle outfit
[Music]
mm-hmm
i'm about to unlock my what click clear
voyance i don't know how to pronounce it
and watch the fest in my head
yes good luck with that
i wish i knew the lyrics
god this is this is so worth it guys
okay
who is pickle singing with these combos
are fire what
i mean isn't it isn't it obvious who's
who pick what that standby is going to
sing with
i think it's pretty obvious
by the way guys totally random but i
went shopping
grocery shopping today finally i made my
way outside and i went grocery shopping
and
um chocolate shopping and dinner
shopping so today no ubereats
and breakfast was also fresh from the
bakery i'm so proud of myself
and i bought strawberries and i bought
um a bunch of other things and i spent
100 on chocolate again but this is the
first time after the last time where i
also
spent a hundred dollars on chocolate
it's been a while okay
i think i i last time wasn't that like
over a month ago
oh i like this combination too
hundred dollar chocolate
oh oh my god they're doing
if they're not gonna dance the
choreography i'm going to throw my
pc out of the window if they don't dance
the choreography i'm going to
flip the table they're not doing it
let's wait for the chorus okay don't
flip the tables just yet
don't flip the tables yet
don't flip the table yet we can wait for
the course okay
as long but maybe the choreography is
copyrighted i don't know
papade
[Music]
yes
i know the choreography to this song the
full choreography
[Music]
thank you what is crazy about that i
bought a lot
[Laughter]
for like it's probably enough for one
month
thank you though thank you it's a lot of
the german chocolate
oh camera
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is so
[Laughter]
oh my god tomato
what is that song but oh my god i love
this trio
oh
what is that anime
mikakuni
[Music]
i can't hold back when i hear that song
oh my god she's so sorry look at her
look at her guys are you looking at her
oh my god
i don't know the song i can't sing along
so i'm just enjoying
but they also got a choreography from
for this one nice
hey glad i said bye i love you
anyone who wants to watch it 100 worth
of money hell yeah
and i have to remind you guys how much
like all our streams we stream every day
and all this is free
all of this is free and even our song
covers and original songs are free on
youtube to watch
so up until now if you didn't want to
you didn't have to support it all you
didn't have to send any any money you
don't have to be a member you don't have
to send super chats nothing is
we don't force anything on you
but don't you think a concert
is worth supporting hmm
just saying since everything else is
free content
maybe this is worth paying for i i would
agree
oh my he's god
cute
all right this part is so adorable
they're waving i want to wave back but i
can't i don't know how to wave
nobody has taught me how to wave i'm
waving with my head
oh my gosh
my two favorite i mean i love mikko
senpai as well but my two favorite
memories are on day one
piccolo senpai and madden senpai they're
my two favorite senpai's
so day one for me is insane
so good
but i'm sure they too will also be
amazing
[Music]
oh
oh my god okay sorry i i have to say day
two will be amazing too
emcee time talking time talking portion
yes looks like it oh
talking portion
[Laughter]
that her movement is lame
that her turn was lame roasting
doesn't look so small anymore
they're both so small
[Music]
and once i want my version of that idol
outfit
too
one day
they're talking about all the songs
again uh
talking about the lucia and hatama
collaboration
they had a lot of uh synergy
keep working until that day comes hell
yeah
be sure i'm going to save money to watch
on stage thank you
oh yeah
so much hype oh my god
oh uh
i caused it by saying they um parted the
lyrics
by breast size i guess whoever has the
biggest breasts got the most parts
i see i see interesting
and now they're being a bit flustered
hey
i just signed it for the audience
because i loved him so much and then
akwa senpai was like
you might show it like that but in
reality you're singing it for me
this sounds like takamori to me
they're just teasing each other now it's
so cute
seem to have a little bit less of tsun
soon relationship that me and callie
have
yay oh my god who's next the talking
part is over to continue
continuing the performances
next is
oh it's
uh that song came out at halloween it's
a whole life original song
cute
i like that song
oh
um
uh
[Music]
everyone's so adorable
yeah christmas is not happening it's
halloween uh in three days it's
halloween
24th december is halloween guys
see ya
let's see oh
sorry when i when i listen to adult
singing i have to do the
otaku calls and i i went to
so many idol concerts years ago from
hello project
so i'm very used to doing all these
calls
you do you tango thank you
uh
there's a spider in the top left there's
a spider
how do i eat the spider mahatma someone
called hanzo
there's a spider it's gone now it's gone
it's just a spider
oh my god the spider's back oh my god oh
my god oh my god
[Laughter]
whatever saved me from this party
for people who don't understand how tom
i did a stream the other day while she
was eating uh
she was cooking and eating a tarantula
yes i am not kidding
i am not even kidding
this is so exciting this is so worth it
oh my god
senpai
they're doing a duo collab
torah
[Music]
sorry educate me on the song please
it's original collapsing with a game
what
watson is watching it too i know i know
gura and i'm
watching it but um i think they're too
tired to join the watch along
they are in discord but i think they got
up just for
the concert yeah everyone's tired
but callie told me she might have time
to join tomorrow
like for me probably because
like many of you i another
i didn't know who alive when it was
first created
but come to think of it i guess these
two have been around
since like pretty much when mikko senpai
has been
since the very beginning as well no or
right after senpai
right after i suppose
so this is this is very
special very emotional
having these two dance together
buddha only took a two hour nap oh yeah
it's really she was streaming
uh minecraft for quite long huh
i had no life to do yang oh yeah
that's that's interesting yeah hmm
[Laughter]
is
yes
what the hell was that tease what was
that tease
okay um but they were talking about oh
we we made a
do a duo together shouldn't we sing our
song something like that what the hell
well we have a trio now uh
[Music]
foreign
and now i think i understand what it
is
cut it missy diggo i've been brainwashed
and the only thing i hear is caramel
that's the only thing i hear
karen
no where's the curry
do you think regular's mom is watching
on stage oh now that she knows she must
be watching
isn't it which she just found out and
suddenly she sees her
daughter on such a huge stage
[Music]
for everyone who's not actually watching
they're not actually singing kind of
messy
they're singing a a different version of
the song
that they had in in collaboration with
uh karen missy
kind of missing
they go
i love the chorus
go go
[Music]
hmm
hi
[Music]
you
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
yeah their voices do sound very good
together indeed
they harmonized very well yeah
that was good wow and they did a lot of
dancing too
[Music]
shuffle shuffle shuffle shuffle
kiss me choose me wait
oh my god
yeah it's kind of red red team red red
pink
true
oh i love money senpai singing voice
it's so pretty
but everyone's singing so well
yeah it's an italian song isn't it
no problem no problem
all good
count
getting those emojis
these are our cecil idols singing for an
educator game
very say so top say so idol
and you guys call me bottom left okay
what
[Music]
good evening to you too
welcome
you would sing that as well well yeah if
i would get such an offer of course i
would
[Music]
hmm
see guys i was um first i didn't plan to
do a watch along i wanted to watch it
privately but i'm glad i can watch it
with you guys this is fun
thanks for watching it together with me
thank you all
it's not over yet though
thank you yeah yeah you applause
come on give me pekka mikko now give me
pekka mikko i need pekko mikko in my
life i need oh
because i thought he was going to stay
on stage and then get pickled
on there oh yeah
oh everyone
oh they're saying thank you for tonight
she's saying she would have loved to do
it in real life with everyone but
unfortunately
it's via the internet
but she says that all of your um
supportive feelings are
coming across to them even if it's
through the internet
um
she says that thanks to everyone's
comments it it became the best live
concert ever
oh everyone's gonna say the ghost will
for next year
oh her goal is she wants to go beyond
the stage for real and
go to um visit all of japan not only
you know tokyo or he wants to do a
countrywide tour he goes empi
oh nicholas senpai once to improve her
dancing and his singing
until next year in next year
lego senpai
she says today was a lot of fun
she wants to improve her dancing and her
singing as well
she wants to become a worldwide idol
next year so that
internationally everyone becomes hata
matama whatever that means
a fan of her i guess
ako senpai
a goal for next year
oh
she wants to become uh number one in the
universe
even though up until now she said number
one in the country number one in the
world but now she wants to be number one
in the universe next year
see you on senpai
oh she's saying after two years she
still doesn't feel completely like a
real idol
but she hopes that after standing on a
stage
like this and performing like this she
hopes that in your eyes she will be more
like an idol
up until now she didn't dance or sing
much but she wants to challenge herself
next year
and do more dancing and singing next
year senpai
she wants to power up and shine more for
you guys by doing more
voice training and more dance lessons
and asking you for your support next
year as well
and saying she loves you all
oh she said she wants you guys to look
more uh at
idle version piccolo and practice more
dancing singing
since today and this year she couldn't
meet anyone in real life she next year
she wants to meet everyone
come from her side oh my god wants to
become bigger
she's asking if you can keep up with her
with her
uh young fresh
age
they will keep on doing their best
and hoping for your support from now on
to me to little hoping
for your support too
she's saying that next time it's the
last one what about
what about
oh it don't make me cry
don't give me piano music
oh you're crying
it's me it's cali too
mommy
i'm crying
[Music]
oh
or did they just come down
looks different yeah wait this is so 3d
[Music]
wait a second what do you think in
generation for idle outfit no
no
oh my eyes i'm sweating
what is this sweat coming from my eyes
ew
hi hi hi hi hi
[Music]
hmm
okay
[Music]
guys
i'm part of her life i'm part of that
i'm part of that
what you're watching right now
mm-hmm
[Music]
bye
i need to blow my nose
you know mm-hmm
thank you villains thank you
[Music]
making you know what
oh
[Music]
i'm
come on
[Music]
it's really over hey it's me
it's really over
thank you for transcending cara oh thank
you i hope it helped
i hope it helped you
emma's calling me again once again
takamodi
i guess it's
represented
it's over but it's not over there's
tomorrow
there is tomorrow
wait oh my god inna i didn't see that
inna threw me something
what the hell
anna drew me something wait it's all
thrilled
[Music]
[Laughter]
yep that's me move the towel sweating
of the light sticks with some glasses
apparently
apparently i wear glasses like
uh-huh and messy hair bound back into a
ponytail
and some sweatshirts and some i don't
know
what are those shirts uh-huh that's the
idol otaku look thank you ina
oh man oh it's over
wow that was that was really really
beautiful
oh man did you guys enjoy it
i hope you enjoyed it are you guys gonna
oh sony oh thank you guys for the super
chats too
oh
[Music]
what about hello you watched the concert
right
yes i did i did how was it how was it
how was it
did you cry i cried i i i was really
close to crying
a lot through a lot of them it's just so
crazy
it's like unreal that we're part of this
group too yeah and like seeing everybody
they
they put some they have so much talent
they put so much work into it yeah
i think it's gonna be there too they
also did like a lot of choreography
compared to the last time it was much
more choreography
and i think everyone really improved
compared to the first festival
and i'm sure the production quality too
because it looked really nice
yeah oh could you imagine like if this
wasn't
via the internet if we could have seen
that like actually in an audience that
would have been even better
yeah especially because they put so much
work into all the effects and stuff
yeah it was really high quality
[Music]
do you remember any songs that you like
the most
uh i really like adrenaline oh
and then also though and it's like um
[Music]
i sang that one i went absolutely crazy
when they
said i was thinking first of all i love
the song too yeah
and i love background but obviously
[Laughter]
but in the beginning the opening act
senbon sakura was also amazing right
yeah yeah they did a really good job and
then we had some solos
as well oh man
oh man oh man i'm so i'm so emotional
it's like i watched a real concert this
is my first time i watched a concert uh
like live on on the internet though and
not not in real life
my first time but it felt it's still
even though it was the internet it felt
still
like we're very close to them right yeah
it was personal felt felt close yeah oh
man
so soon we will be on there maybe maybe
also here hopefully also i'm sure you
have noticed in their intermission
and cali were featured in a song so if
you think
i think if the audience will think
logically then i think we will come to
the conclusion that tomorrow
the other en members will be in the
intermission
maybe could you give us any confirmation
on that
uh i can either confirm nor deny but if
you use your detective skills
uh to investigate this this case you
might find your answer
i'm pretty sure i know the answer
i i do i do i know the answer
oh i'm looking forward to your narration
as well tomorrow because today the
narration uh in the beginning and the
end was also
uh callie and me and tomorrow are
probably
probably i'm just guessing it might be
amena and gouda
probably just a wild guess i don't know
where i'm getting these ideas from
honestly
it was really cool to see you guys up
there too and like hollow id
too to see them up there is really
surreal
um it was a lot of fun i can't wait for
tomorrow are you gonna watch it tomorrow
as well and stay up like really late
yeah i i fixed my sleep schedule
yesterday but now
[Music]
now see every time i fix my sleep
schedule it's also messed up the next
day already
there is there's no hope for us amen you
and me we're stuck
i remember i remember before we debuted
we were both like always up at weird
times
ah oh man it's still the same we can't
fix it
but but that's the good thing about like
um having this
job i guess we can we can stream any
time and i i i
like the ball if you stream at crazy
times that you
that normally no one else is awake in
your time zone then maybe you can get
other people's from other time zones and
that
that would be yeah they will be very
happy about that so yeah there's always
people that are like i'm so glad you're
streaming at this time yeah
wait tomorrow tomorrow you're you're
streaming
not are you streaming tomorrow oh that's
good so you can sleep a lot and then be
awake again for the
for the second day yeah are you gonna
you're gonna do this again tomorrow are
you gonna do that
i think cali is gonna join me uh but if
you also wanna join if you feel
awake enough if you have enough energy
you're welcome to join
yeah i was too tired to today but i'm
sure you guys even nina had fun huh
yeah i had fun i don't know about inna
i think i was very disturbed by my
screaming
i know you're gonna be really excited
over this like
i could just i could just i could hear
it already before
my number one uh idol
is not in the second day so i might be
more calm
yeah yeah who's tomorrow what what is
that
tomorrow is uh fukuki senpai matsuri
senpai akira
miu senpai
so i i guess there's uh
did is only fourth generation
uh performing on both days i wonder i
think yeah
i think they're the perfect friends yeah
they're the they are the opening act on
both days
but other than that the members are
completely switched out
from what i understand oh yeah because
uh
senpai didn't get a solo song today but
maybe she'll get one tomorrow oh yeah
definitely yeah luna senpai also has to
sing solo
i like how luna senpai after the
first song they had a little emcee
portion they were talking she was
already out of breath
so good that's what i like to see
well i mean do you have a stamina to one
day perform on stage like that
uh i think so i like dancing like uh i
like playing uh beat saber that's how i
warm up it gets the blood flowing oh i
dance while i play too
and uh i i'm working on my stamina
well you're getting my hopes up um i am
generally
let's say before i joined whole life i
had quite some
quite the stamina but after i joined
whole life it might have gone down to
uh minus degrees whatever that means
too much netflix yeah too much sitting
in front of my computer but
if if we were to perform uh for a
concert one day i will of course
practice my ass off yeah i think all of
us
all of us probably would you know i know
you know and good are trying to raise
their stamina too now yeah ring fit
adventure yeah
oh yeah well but they they gotta do that
too
more than once a month though it's not
gonna help if they do it once
a month yeah that's true but i also have
ringfield adventure it's quite fun
i gotta do it on stream too i think
everybody would be really excited
did you play ringfit adventure on stream
before no
no is it can we expect that sometime
[Music]
for a while for a while no no pressure
no pressure
maybe maybe if one day alma becomes 3d
then then we want to see that's when i
want to do a ring fit adventure when i
when i become 3d that would be great
yeah i think that's that's much better
do all the cool stuff
when
i don't know i'm flexible but uh the
flexibles aren't very long
that's that's okay no problem you every
time you fall you're about to fall down
you can just zoom time travel and then
go back to the moment where you were
still in a good position
okay that's how you win the game what do
you do you just burn down the
burn down the twister mat
i just fall whenever i i'm about to fall
i'll take callie with me and fall on top
of
i think it's her she'll be my security
pillow
she's a good pillow very much
oh well i don't wanna i don't wanna keep
you awake for much longer and i i would
uh
i think i'll say goodbye to everyone now
but we're doing this tomorrow again
yeah okay tomorrow too oh yeah i would
be happy if you would come amen
let's enjoy it together okay
and there she goes thank you guys
everyone for watching
uh i'll do a i'll do a
superchat reading tomorrow after the
watch along tomorrow today i'll
i guess i'll i'll not do it i don't know
hope it's okay it wasn't
that much but i appreciate all of your
support guys thank you guys for sending
me super chats
even though i'm not even performing but
i appreciate it very much
and i hope uh did some of you like at
least uh
like um how to say uh
some of you did did my did my
translation help some of you at least
i forgot the word that i actually wanted
to use but yeah
yeah really
oh oh i'm happy to hear that
oh yeah yeah yeah they didn't talk that
much anyway it was mostly singing so i
could keep up quite
well your hype kept me awake very good
so let's do this again tomorrow amen
might join you know might join again
kelly might join and we might have even
more people
calling in kelly might call
in calling in cali cali calling in
funny
i cried two times i think tomorrow i
might be able to keep my cool a little
bit more
because there is no peculiar and there's
no marine senpai
but there's another amazing oh my god i
can't wait for fubuki senpai solo
please tell me she's gonna do a solo
performance of uh
of um her song she has to she has to
give
the third festival the the third
festival coming after this
maybe we'll be able to see in an actual
concert hall again that would be great
yeah say fun party if i oh my god if
she's going to sing
say fun fall i'm sorry you guys have to
mute me because i'm going to sing along
the whole time
oh please
we would never mute you but isn't it
awkward because there's definitely some
delay between
me reacting and you guys and your your
guys's
uh concert stream isn't it awkward when
i'm always
singing delete
will it just oh did you guys adjust it
or was i just always with low latency
latest it's pretty close oh really i
turned it to low latency later on
uh it seems to catch up better with you
guys
um i'll do that tomorrow as well and hey
my internet survived oh my god
plus i love your energy thank you i just
like watching a concert on video with
friends
oh am i your friend
your reactions make the experience
better i'm happy to hear that
did you switch to nico nicole at some
point you were perfectly timed with
no i didn't i i switched um to low
latency i was on the same side but i
switched to low latency
and then i didn't have any buffering
problems after switching to low latency
afterwards even out of sync your energy
improves the concert
oh thank you i'm happy to hear that
really
thank you so for everyone who wants to
keep staying
up and in one hour and 15 minutes
there's
going to be an after talk i think on the
official whole live channel
with four members i think i don't
remember who exactly is gonna be in
there
but there will be an aftertalk with four
of the members who have performed
does someone know who who will be in
there does someone know
oh wait this fubuki senpai will be in
there even
so no not the member's dad oh
when i saw your whole talk segment
during the highlight reel oh yeah oh my
god when i saw it i was also like oh my
god i made it i'm proud of myself
this was so worth it here's to you being
on that stage someday hell yeah thank
you
martin kanata
thank you those are the members who are
going to be who are going to be
in uh after talk stream uh i think
on the official whole live channel i'm
pretty sure about that yes friend no
wife
thank you guys thank you guys for the
super chats
thank you thank you guys so much for the
support thanks for watching this
together with me it was a
it was a good decision to do it
i hope i'll see you all tomorrow at the
same time i know for many overseas
viewers it's a quite
the bad time for a concert
but we'll do it again tomorrow this is
worth it the watch long made us feel
like going out with a friend to see a
concert oh
thanks for the water long thank you for
coming
11am in germany oh that's not that bad
that's actually pretty good i guess
thank you for the commentary kiara thank
you for listening to me and not muting
me
thank you you didn't have the
vr set on the concert what no what
what you can watch this with a vr vr set
what
just tell me if that's a thing or not no
you can't okay okay
dude you're giving me a shock right now
that would be cool though um i need the
senpai
no i don't think so i i think that was
just uh someone
randomly making something up
maybe next time maybe a whole live fruit
festival maybe then lisa said
thank you for coming thank you why are
you watching along
riso thank you
let's watch it again tomorrow
i literally cried at the end me too
the moment when that when this when that
piano started and there was like
black white uh images popping up
that moment already i started crying in
the first second i was like oh
this is getting to my heart
the piano oh my god how dare you come at
me with that piano
it's so emotional yeah oh man
it's so good i can't wait what they got
in store for us tomorrow unfortunately
there was no pecomico which i'm very sad
about why was there no pickle mikko i
have to
i have to write uh i have to write a
strongly worded letter
to cover now so i'll see you guys soon
i i need to write something down for a
cover i i don't understand this i am
going to write a complaint
write a letter to yahoo i will i'm going
to write it
strongly worded okay strongly worded
yeah we need to make will make them come
on
sorry but that's just something i was
looking forward so much
and i was bamboozled i was bamboozled
and betrayed
okay so guys i'll see you tomorrow thank
you so much for watching and in german
we say
auf wiedersehen
a strongly worded letter will be in your
mailbox tomorrow
our feet are pretty close close enough
[Music]