[Music]
n
no
[Music]
w
uh
[Music]
oh
oopsy cute cute
assert cute assert assert what am I
asserting huh tell
me uh K KY ke wait
yes there we
go uh
hello I already have your cards
yay is that good wait am I too no I'm
fine chuny is so cute she chose like a
super weird place to sit on top of AKA
all of my map
equipment even though there like I I put
it on my bed
in the corner corner of all
corners and uh there's so much other
space where she could lie comfortably
but she chooses to sleep on a very
uncomfortable
looking Hill of cables and
equipments no it's not actually yeah
maybe it is
warm maybe it actually might be warm cuz
it's charging
always
charging moap my cat soon yeah you know
what I just
saw this is new YouTube added something
new to Super chats I don't really think
we need to ever use this but it's new
so as a jerk I want to use it you can
now start or set goals for super
chats um
okay how about oh ah it's you you don't
[Music]
choose that's weird you don't choose an
amount uh in like currencies you choose
the amount of super chats that you want
to
receive and then what colors doesn't
[\h__\h]
[Music]
matter have you guys already seen
somebody use
this this seems was like I I mean okay
yesterday I took the day off so maybe it
was here since
yesterday no no yeah it's super new do
you guys see it you you guys probably
don't see the menu for creating the goal
right I would assume it's in the chat
window is set a
timer how
about we make it an hour share how you
will
celebrate get inspired with examples
your celebration should didn't include
anything of monetary
value everything I do has monetary value
though how will I celebrate when I reach
my
[Music]
goal
I I will eat
you start
goal
allegedly burn this
V nice nice oh V
nice that's what we want okay so now
it's
up who wants to be the historical
participants of the first 30 people to
reach a goal on my
channel yeah V Let's Go V eat me H
you're like a you're like an aliceon
Wonderland you're like one of those
things that say eat
me m
oh see they they really want to be eaten
this is a really good goal a really good
offer trade offer accept
[Laughter]
it ah you want to participate but it
doesn't load
no you volunteer but then you shouldn't
be counted for this oh
my volunteers don't count volunteers you
should do it separate L well you're
always
volunteering that's a bit more than 30 I
don't know I can't count but that that
looks like a bit more than
30 guys you may or may not be applic
applicable apply for this anymore
because it's past 30 you're not going to
get eaten I'm sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
time to be eaten hey increase the
goal no I'll just continue to to take
advantage of you guys of your guys's
combined one brain cell stretch goals
stretch goals how about the more
more uh super chats okay here I'll make
one oh when I click it again it says
goal achieved thank you audience for
making it possible thank you audience
for making it
possible I'll show you no where did it
go is it still
there let me take a picture this is such
a emotional
moment no I can't I can't take a proper
screenshot because when I go out of the
window it
disappears my beautiful message wait let
me take a photo with my
phone
there this is
historical
wow what a what an amazing achievement
that we have achieved together it
wouldn't have been possible without you
literally literally like ah my life has
changed because now now I can have food
because now I can eat you I can eat good
that rhymed by the
way okay where did I save
this ah is this
it okay here we go look at this
[Music]
whoa gold ch yippe
beautiful yippe we need to celebrate
this here
okay um share how you will celebrate I
will
stretch my body after this is the
stretch goal I will stretch my body
after the stream get the joke but it's
it's something you really would want
because I really need to stretch so that
my body doesn't get more [\h__\h] up the
more I stretch the more I will be Healy
here stretch goal my goal is
live oh man this is
so I mean I feel like for for holo it's
unnecessary this this feature but I'm
going to I'm going to introduce you to
it
anyway I I would understand like for
maybe smaller
creators or if you have I don't know I
don't know some big
project that you're working towards I
guess I guess Cali could yeah Cali could
like cuz she was like saving up for
music vide she could use this for music
video um things but yeah I don't
know I shall use this to
stretch be should to yay stretch you
guys should stretch too man the earlier
you stretch every day in your lifetime
the better over time your body will not
feel like [\h__\h] when you're already in
your
20s
uh me for my cats should I stretch my
cats all right I'll stretch my cats
later
[Laughter]
it's it's already fum season
guys I have a lot of fum problems
already why I don't understand why I
already have fum
problems but okay before we play can I
talk about my food
Adventures oh it went above 30 last time
it cut off at 30 that's weird maybe
maybe it was like two people sent it
absolutely simultaneous cuz now it says
31 out of 30 do you see
that goal
achieved
yippe yeah now it doesn't go up anymore
even though you sent another one Mark
Panka but you weren't counted who is the
31st how did you do it you hacked
yourself into my
goal bug have to have to to report this
bug thank
you H well yeah so before we start I'm a
bit proud of myself because you know
recently I I didn't feel like ordering
my hellofresh boxes because if it's I
don't know it makes me feel so pressured
and all the all the foods are almost a
lot of them are really
like not high effort but there's so many
dishes that would be much easier that I
could have that I could be making saving
time because I'm not always motivated
enough to properly cook like the proper
meals uh so yesterday I made Aloo which
I did a while ago too but I don't know
it didn't it it felt
so you know you use a lot of oil for
that right and it somehow when I eat it
at restaurants it always feels very
light but when I made it myself with all
the oil it felt very like G
like I don't want to eat too much of
this um yeah but this time when I made
it I don't know somehow I nailed it it
was really good
and this time it wasn't so
heavy and then the day before I made
carbonara and okay I will admit I did
not get all the like best ingredients I
used cheap pasta I used random bacon
that I had left over but it was pretty
good looking bacon uh cuz it was left
over from
hellofresh and it was it wasn't even
like a block of bacon it was Stripes of
bacon that I cut so it wasn't like the
typical bacon that you're supposed to
use for
carbonara yeah um and the cheese I I
normally it seems like they use two
different cheeses that they make to
balance it uh I only used like one type
and it was it was
already uh you know scraped shaved
whatever and normally you're supposed to
do it fresh from the block of cheese
graded yeah shredded yeah yeah parmesan
and pecorino but I think mine what what
even was that something like that maybe
it was I think just a fake parmesan or
so N I don't know something like that
though at least it wasn't
like
stupid whatever mozzarella or cuz it's
not supposed to be
mozzarella but even with these shitty
ingredients just by watching uh one
YouTube short recipe
tutorial I nailed it it was so good I
never made cabonara like this before
like I made cabara several times in my
life now
and I don't know until now I never
really tried to do it really
authentically but this time I used a
recipe that was pretty authentic yeah it
turned out good but I was a bit worried
that I would get
salmonella because the eggs are so
raw like
huh basically you make your mixture your
egg mixture stuff you you use your raw
eggs and you put a lot of lot of lot of
cheese p in there and then you you mix
it into like a paste so to say it should
be pretty thick actually and then when
your noodles are finished and your bacon
you know you have your bacon in your pan
with the bacon is supposed to give out a
lot of its own fat so the the the pan is
supposed to be pretty fatty and then you
you put the noodles in and no worries if
you bring a lot of like of the noodle
water with you that's good
because you will need some of the noodle
water uh to uh like make this like thick
paste that you made into a more creamy
sauce
so but the thing is you're already
according to this recipe you're already
uh supposed to like kind of have the
heat turned off when you pour in the uh
the this paste because otherwise you
know you're going to get scrambled
eggs and just the noodle water is and
the Heat of the pasta and the remaining
heat in the pan is supposed to you know
cook it a little bit I guess but not
really but then I was thinking
yo is this still kind of raw is this
dangerous at all cuz I barely had to
spend time in the pan but I'm not sick
it's been 2 days and I'm not sick so I
guess this is good it was fine I guess
yeah EU eggs are safe Rock wait wait
wait wait wait wait I always hear that
about Japan I didn't know that applied
to Europe as
well what about American eggs eggs eggs
eggs you and Japan are both safe what I
didn't real
what what
it's finally well then where is it not
safe it seems like mostly everywhere is
safe Americans wash their eggs
what while EU and Japan don't wash their
eggs you mean what do you mean wash was
the shell of the egg the outside how
does that affect the
inside people say us eggs are not safe
us eggs super dangerous how
haa dangerous
eggs kind of cool
though oh I've successfully shamed you
into actually cooking yo you should
really just try something as simple as
alio you can add your own protein in
there I did it just without any meat cuz
I like like lighter meals um but you can
just throw in some chicken breast or so
in there Alo so easy like Mama Mia Mama
Mia
Al literally like you know if you really
have nothing at home you might have the
ingredients
for it's so good old news American eggs
are safe these days we shall test it I
shall go to America and eat 10 raw eggs
10 raw eggs Challenge and we will see if
I will die
it's a matter of life or death but it's
okay I'm a phoenix I shall take the
challenge for you guys I shall take the
bullet I will do
it I'll sacrifice myself for
you and if I die well then that Super
Chat it will be your
fault isn't isn't that a great thing to
live
with but it's okay it's like fine
because I'm a
phoenix so you don't have to feel so
bad but honestly I I I I don't want to
eat raw eggs anywhere anywhere on this
Earth
ideally but like in Japan what what I
will accept is like dipping things into
raw egg not like I will when you know
there's some foods where you dip
something into raw egg or you have a raw
egg on top of a food that you will then
scram scramble not really scramble it
won't be cooked but you mix it with the
rest of the food I will do that but when
I dip something into raw egg I think
like a lot of people they will go like
all in and have like a [\h__\h] ton of egg
all over whatever they're
dipping but I'm I'll just like just a
little bit just a little bit of a
dippy
um just just a tiny not too much it's
nice with br but not too
much
yeah 1 million total super chats in one
year and you do a stream where you eat a
dozen raw eggs you want me to [\h__\h]
die you all do you guys all want me to
[\h__\h] die why what did I do to
you what did I
do well well well uh um I like to stall
so before we start let's talk about the
schedule for this week because didn't
stream yesterday but here's the schedule
yippee uh actually more streams that I
was planning to
have I don't know what happened uh today
we're playing inscription which people
have been saying this might be kind of
like a freeart stream if I want to
continue it not a I'm open to it if I
like it a little goody to shoes I think
a lot of you guys never heard of it
before um so it's pretty niche but I
think you know it's set in Austria and
it's a
fantasical horror narrative Adventure so
I thought this should be interesting you
know we should we should give it a
chance it has like this like um like old
school
anime uh
style yeah we'll see how that
goes don't know if I'll finish it though
because it's also pretty long definitely
not finishing it in that stream
apparently because it's apparently 12
hours
H that's on your wish list okay you'll
get a taste of it from my
stream the Yuri Forest game yeah
apparently there's like some
lesbians let's
go finding them once again I feel like I
don't even have to go looking for them
anymore and then Thurday the 3D
Halloween Shenanigans stream is kind of
spontaneous yes so don't expect uh too
much like in terms of super planned out
uh it's we're kind of winging it
um
yeah uh I'm I think I can do it archived
I'm planning to do like a call in if
people sign up if enough people sign up
for it like maybe at least threee
um and some singing and some just like
Shenanigans and then Diablo 4 we
continuing it where we left off a long
time ago because the
DLC is
out uh and I want to play the DLC with
some girls there's a couple of girls who
are interested in the DLC and we talked
about it and so we're going to uh finish
the main story on our own first to be a
little bit more faster but you guys said
I can do it in one more stream stream
kind of
surprised and then box shot roulette
with Ana I literally like talked about
it with you guys like oh my God there's
a multiplayer now let's let's plan a
collab and then a day later Anya is like
hey who wants to play boxshot roulette
and such lovely people signed up for it
and and I also signed up for it so we
have a little collab I think it will be
on Anya's Channel probably I assume so
and then eat in the tunnel of gigy okay
most of you guys probably don't know
what Eden Eternal is unless you looked
it up by now but I used to play this I
was so addicted uh I played a lot of
free toplay anime MPGs back in the day
and Eden the turtle was one of my
favorites um and I played so much and
then it died but it like was revived a
while ago uh they revived the server I
don't know how active it is I I made a
character yesterday just to like save my
name uh and there it didn't seem like
super
active but we might make it very active
if you guys you you can join us and play
alongside us because it isn't free to
play on the mm RPG let's
go yeah we'll be riding Alpacas yeah
that's the like the main Mount there's
other mounts too but the main Mount is
alpacas yeah so we're going to play that
and finally that was I I didn't expect
it but suddenly got uh perms for it on
Monday so I was like oh okay let's
squeeze it in I was waiting for this and
I was also waiting for a oneon-one
collab with gigy we were we had a bunch
of ideas but finally yipp finally and
then we're going to finish one monali on
Sunday so yeah that's how the week is
looking and never note um Mirage Mirage
suddenly um is very close to 1 million
so even more than before I now am far
far far behind on okay not that no
yeah I'm pretty far behind on the
rewards I definitely don't have a chance
of catching up now
um uh yeah it suddenly had a big boost
I'm guessing like sometimes YouTube
holds back
views in bods and then like I guess like
automatically tries to like
verify them and then it holds it back
and then it come like then then they
give it to you at some point so I'm
guessing that's what happened because
suddenly went it went from 800 to 900
something it was kind of crazy I was
like what the
[\h__\h] help Suffering From
Success so give me some time to catch up
of course you're getting all of this
nonetheless if not even more stretch
goals
[Laughter]
yeah thank you guys for streaming it we
can reach 1 million very soon
yippee
yeah a capella um I I want to make a
little video for it actually so
um that is I I could just upload the
acapella the audio but uh I have an idea
for a video so yeah got to make it first
won't take too long I
think but yeah okay enough stalling
enough stalling I'm
sorry I'm I'm
scared nah there's it's not that scary
right should we play in full screen chat
or in this like smaller
window what do you
think Oh wrong hand oopsie
small
works okay window is fine some people
say full screen
but yeah no I'll I'll stay like
this uh okay
[Music]
wait freaking have an
earworm I have a freaking earworm
how loud will this be will this even
show up hello there we go there we go I
I literally just opened the game and saw
this and F okay I'll leave it at
that uh let's
go cute little
button devolver digital love him okay oh
time to figure out what's on this
thing um that's not what cc sounds like
normally oh it's German
no can I change it in game
sh why why are you German okay there we
go
ESP
H Chinese I don't know how to say this
either
English reset with Engish there you go
German always works no German not always
works English always
works okay time to figure out what's on
this I swear that's not what's she is
this they credited her
wrong or they used the wrong sound
file that reminds me of the
song Ah that's it that's it oh wait
wait let
me
[\h__\h]
wait I need that
again was aligned to the
left uhuh okay I'll fix it what do you
mean it was cut the left side was cut
off or the right side was cut off
[Music]
ah there we go how about that okay okay
what I wanted to do
is wait wait wait wait wait
wait okay time to figure out what's on
this thing for time
[Music]
yep that sounded like the intro
the from Mara stole the
sorry okay I'm done I'm done I'm done
[Music]
ah
continue I'm getting gas lit I never
played this game
before is this
gaslighting worth the reset I would say
so
uhoh oh
[Laughter]
God another Challenger it has been ages
aw you've been alone here perhaps you
have forgotten how this game is played
no I never played before I don't even
know allow me to remind you gas
lighting woof woof play the squirrel
card
I was going to say I don't have a
squirrel card what the hell
anywhere squirel now play your
sto aha interesting the S stands for sto
or what
what what how does this
work I have to scroll
back what's on top of my square wall I'm
killing my squ r w Stones cost one blood
sacrifice is supposed to be
H is this this this means costs one
blood this part or ah this part
maybe wolves require two sacrifices you
don't have enough
okay the blood okay oh ding dong ring
the bell to end your turn and commence
combat combat about we just playing a
game
ding that ding sound was not satisfying
at all your sto stands un
opposed the number on the bottom left is
it's attack power
one stabs with card ouch your St dealt
me one damage I added it to the scale oh
fancy I love that they should do that
with like Pokemon games and Magic and Y
and
everything what a nice
visualization you win if you tip my side
all the way down oh cool cool cool cool
oh you did it yourself well I
win oh your turn
Okay coyote your St stands stand in the
way of my coyote ah is the positioning
does that matter like uh it has to be in
front of me to attack me or
what my co you dealt two damage to your
sto okay that means your sto's health is
too less yeah if a creature's Health
reaches zero it dies okay but I guess I
had three so now it's
one z turn again okay you may draw from
your deck or you may draw a
squirrel uh why a squirrel specifically
is it always squirrels I guess so wait
is this my deck then it looks like it's
only one card
how Reckless of you what do you
mean
why no more comment you not going to
tell me what to
play I don't even know what I can play
because uh [\h__\h] I should have I should
have gone with the
squirrel yeah I get it I get it I know I
know uh yeah how okay how do I what what
can I do then
yeah yeah I know you were lacking
sacrifices for the yeah so can I just
attack
you how do I attack
you ah Belle oh will he still attack my
sto oh okay good job because you are
learning I will
pass your turn oh thank you but he's so
[Music]
nice you've drawn all the creatures from
your deck what the hell that was a small
deck I guess my deck was already
trimmed a squirrel is your only choice
okay
squel and now because I have two cards I
can sacrifice these two this fear not
the Beast is sacrificed but not removed
from your deck
okay it suffering was real but you will
see it again oh want to try he's trying
to make me feel bad about that sacrifice
but you're the one who making me do this
and then I place my
wolf and then I guess I attack by ending
my
turn mhm see this way I got that one
card for free because he kind of passed
his turn maybe this was my Kaku all
along cuz he's got pity with me free
Dage free weights on the
scale is
pass why
why are you
passing
so I I think it makes no sense
to sacrifice them
yet
because unless I don't know I want to
see this card I six one
six yeah I'll just let them attack and
the next turn I would get another
squirel will put it down and then maybe
I could
sacrifice but we won't need to do
that you've won this
match they won't all be so easy okay
okay I'll keep that in mind I'm sure
that's true let me recall your story oh
yes oh oh yeah I've heard it a Rog like
and kind of similar to slat SP uh just
because I played SL SP you guys were
telling me that I guess um I see so this
is like battle and then we get a new
card or so and then item shop or
something like that
nice should we put on some bgm because
this game is kind of
quiet tell me do you want some PGM oh no
there will be bgm no okay okay you were
lost deep in the forest
a single path revealed
itself oh should I click it
okay two denisons of the forest
approached you
tentatively a cat yay the undying cat
sacrificing the poor Beast does not kill
it
oh oh that's
cool the CTIC Adder damaged from from
its poison bite is always
lethal oh
[\h__\h] only one may Grace your poultry
deck cat I'm glad you like the cat okay
another creature joins your
Caravan
yippee some of the creatures of seem to
willing to follow you okay
cool moving on you came across an
abandoned sack
squirrel you found a squirrel in a
bottle break in case of emergency okay
cool ah ah it's like an item the if I
activate that I can add an extra
squirrel kind of for free I guess okay
and have a second oh thanks oh another
useful Implement I'll allow you to tip
the scale of
it NY freeze as much as you can carry
thanks wow damn so
nice yeah who put the squirrel in the
bottle poor squirrel we need to free it
we will you were ambushed while crossing
some rough
terrain okay let's fight well why do I
have a boulder on my side why I was
sleeping it was the right play I get it
maybe you'll help me is he mad at me
play along for now money
play you may now see my moves ahead of
time okay what's going on why why can't
I do that
what listen to him when he talking to
yeah I'm trying what is he saying now
what are you saying play along like do
you want me to play you or
not well I guess we can uh we want to
probably play a
squirrel or maybe not against the
freaking stump
oops and the cat too oh
no wait I already your items might
help behold the rule
book ah
ah to use a squirrel is created in your
hand a squirrel is defined as yeah
okay should I put it down okay
should I
already in this turn sacrific
them this
one so we can attack without being
opposed okay should I should I do
something
else I was thinking of the Snapper but I
I don't
know get cat
[Music]
out the Snapper is for defense since it
has oh true
understanding fledgling a card bearing
the sigil will grow into more powerful
from uhhuh
uh-huh but that doesn't really what what
did he mean with I will see his turns
ahead of
time
anyway oh ah that's what he
means mind the ambitious wolf cup with
aent swiftly it detect my
stone that's probably a little
bit okay we got another Square wall I
guess I'll put it up
there and
[Music]
um but I don't know should I sacrifice
it wait uh the the blood thing is is
that like in one turn it needs to
sacrifice like both sacrifices have to
be in the one
[Music]
turn mhm
mhhm try sacrificing the
cat Oh I thought because it doesn't die
it doesn't really count as a sacrifice
but okay cool
[Music]
a nice good cat the Airborne bat flies
over creatures to attack
ah no
waa that was a lot of damage bro you
have good
cards I'm going to get a normal card of
wolf and get my square and can I use
this that's not how I thought this would
work I don't know I that's not what I
expected oh the items you would say
that's wasted oh
[\h__\h] I don't know the value of these
things
yet well
[\h__\h] I didn't think you would really do
it yeah I I wouldn't have done it if I
knew that I was pulling out a
tooth
um yeah
huh uh not sure what to do
anyway I yeah I guess those cards were
not necessary
um
okay at least the bat is gone and the
stupid Boulder is
gone so how about we sacrifice sacrifice
put the wolf down
wonderful
nice oh already my turn again should I
get normal
card yeah another wolf I don't really
have many cards in my deck
huh but I guess in this case I can just
just attack
again yay it looks like caramel like
golden popcorn not like Toof you
prevailed and tracked onwards past the
now bloody
terrain
sick do I get a card now oh yeah new
card
a sparrow yo this means I can also
attack
directly or a wolf cup we already have
wolf cup so I think I would go for the
sparrow yeah flying is
good what is
this You' stumbled into some strange
stones in the midst those are indeed
strange what is this you were compelled
to choose a worthy sacrifice one that
will will be lost forever
no I have to get rid of a
card N I don't want to get rid of any of
these th trimming
no the
cat no but the cat is so
great you looked upon your menager and
selected a healthy host
what pick me what
okay
sure what is going on what an honor just
like you guys a ghastly spectacle but
but the soul of the cat ah can he now
not be killed like
sacrificed nice okay that's fine then
that's fine as long as I still have
something that can't be sacrificed okay
okay okay I thought the cart would be
gone forever and I would not get any
thing whoa behold my totem it inscribes
my can canine canine K canine canine
right cuz that's how they say it for the
police dogs uh carts with the Airborne
sigil or is it yeah
Kine oh
what yeah you have a flying dog okay you
have actually two flying things that's
kind of messed
up um
squel oh
[\h__\h]
Bird that's I think all I can
do if only I still had a squirrel card
ah my totem has granted my coyota to
power flight yeah I've
noticed unfair oh wait I'm I'm all
already dead kind
of
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I one more and you lose oh I will die
what do I do when I die do we just
restart from the very
beginning pray for stra yeah can I even
play it though
oh [\h__\h] so
over ah what
now
no you've lost yeah using this as
learning opportunity may be the only way
to IM mitigate my
disappointment get up get up from the
table fetch my Candlestick from the top
the barrel beside the door
why where what
Barrel what the
[Music]
hell oh that
one why what is this
room what's going on behind the
door I want to look directly at you or
do I maybe I don't want
to not sure what time it is it's kind of
misleading what am I supposed to be able
to read this
clock yeah I'm here you why did you want
that why was that so
important what let me explain something
to you
mhm ah there those are my life yeah that
was one of the two mistakes you can make
here if you make it never I must
sacrifice
you what why wh why why so strict why
why can't I live longer why don't you
don't you want to play you said you
haven't had anyone play with you for a
long time so wouldn't it be good for you
to had a to have a permanent play
partner
H you should keep me
alive otherwise you won't be able to
play with
anybody please don't kill
me people die of their killed man
Sparrow oh their reviled skunk its
stench reduces the strength of the enemy
their attack strength you mean and the
another cat I mean we don't have a skunk
so this maybe good to have
what is this
thing take the
cat
okay I don't mind the cat and I guess
this is
resting this was this a sacrifice table
not sure
anymore sacrifice
again do you want me to you did you get
me to get the cat just to sacrifice the
cat again
I'm I hope none of you are cat
owners you guys are kind of
insane she I didn't I I that's not why I
I chose the
cat man how about the wolf the wolf
wolof interesting though I like this
mechanism
very
interesting all right I guess we have a
fight I will redeem
myself
hopefully he's completely insane you see
that right no care for the rules
pathetic really but he makes up the
rules only keeps me around to watch me
suffer you particularly what what issue
does he have with the Stout what is this
grant fear what
Grand fear what he's got a czy [\h__\h]
bear why why why the [\h__\h] he why why
does he have a [\h__\h] grizly bear bro
um okay uh
squirel sacrifice
put down back on the board yeah you got
a problem with that was that not what
you
wanted and that's my turn at least we
already get some damage
in oh my God wait why did I should
have maybe I should have put it
there
ouch uh
should I sacrifice my Stout to exchange
for a
Snapper or so so then I can block the
bear yeah okay no my flying
Stout oh wait he stays oh I I forgot
okay wonderful well then it's not so bad
at
all okay I still my Snapper is still
alive even I thought he would die right
away um
maybe squirrel again or squirrel
squirrel should I put the squirel ah
right I can already do
this oh not bad I'm getting it I'm
getting
it oh
oh oh I think I'm winning why does he
not put anything new on the board he's
so nice to me again and yet he wants me
to
die uh squirrel
again or I guess now it doesn't
matter squirrel to
block yeah the bear
okay and we win
yippe what about your candles huh how
many candles do you have
[\h__\h] why do only I have candles and
then I die or do you have candles too I
don't I don't see them anywhere I don't
know which ones you candle anyway should
we go left or right I guess maybe left
is nice if if I can get a new
card yeah or item I a yeah he fills up
my item stuff right try the fire oh [\h__\h]
oh
no skunk Raven the coning conniving
kiving kiving I didn't know you write
that like that I thought it was k n i v
i n G well but that I would probably
read that as
knifing
can what did that say oh well oh wolof
woof woof I would say
Raven
conniving
conniving the knifing
Raven okay here we go I guess yeah it's
a expensive card a boulder the rock may
get you out of a hard place or a
squirrel oh do I get all anyway am I
choosing or am I
taking oh I he was just introducing it
as a new item okay
um H but this was just one tooth to add
onto the scale that wasn't even so
powerful qu w
okay whoa oh you give me several choices
what it's bleeding yields free blood if
you can ignore the
bleeding
H so if I sacrific the goat I get free
blood but it also needs a sacrifice to
be
played that's that's goat
yeah another
one I think I'll take another one
nice goated card feeling overburdened
enough with a full free items you
carried on indeed I did oh we have a
boss fight huh all right here we
go nice he's setting the mood the trees
seemed too close in the to close in
around you as a chill Mist descended
in the distance you could hear the
clinking of metal on
Stone he's such a good Storyteller a
hobbled figure stood in your
path wa oh what the hell you look better
before why did you have to put on that
mask he h was the prector
heaw okay whatever you say homie he's
doing the prospector again easy boss the
mu's
key the mule
what's the
[Music]
meal what does he
mean not his card a pack mule what does
this mean at the end of the owner's turn
a card bearing the sigil will move in
the direction inscribed in the sigil ah
you mean like in front of the coyote
but then where does the coyote go that
it can't move on forward or what I don't
understand has two abilities how do I
read the second
one just right or
left ah ah so here then
okay okay um s
wall oh can the Stout St
[Music]
Stout this spot you sure can I change it
still
no uh yeah so that you can block the
damage I don't know
man oh that
good I mean it's good to have you on the
field I guess you shouldn't die I guess
but it's okay we have squirrels and
[Music]
stuff
um should I take the
Raven
yeah and then where should we put it and
if it can attack like that uh like
through the enemies can the enemies also
go through the Raven or will they always
attack the Raven if they're in front of
it oh I want to attack the M oh [\h__\h]
a uh
well it is what it is
well we're still alive we're still alive
I could take from my normal deck and
then get a black goat or is that too
wasteful too
wasteful oh I need a squirrel for the
goat ah okay okay okay
H Le needs to sacrifice so this n i mean
ah maybe I could have taken the squirrel
and then a card from my
deck cuz like this even if I put the
squirrel down I'd have to sacrifice both
the scroll and the Raven and we don't
want to do that
[Music]
if I were to try to sacrifice The Raven
does the Raven completely like die just
by being sacrificed or does it only take
like one one hit or
[Music]
so oh it will die
okay so now you're saying I should use
the goat huh
[Music]
so should I place it in front of the
pack
mule probably
right
no
okay now my hand is
empty we'll see how that goes what did I
won I won oh he does have candles I I
hope you didn't think it would be that
easy I will respect you for putting down
your own candles I thought you were
Invincible but I guess this is a boss
fight so I have to kill you twice okay
that's how it
goes that's dar's gold in them cards
what gold in my
cards hey what the [\h__\h] you gold
figger ah go gold I've struck gold [\h__\h]
you what what did he only do that with
the carts that I had left on the field I
should have had left less
no what the heck e what do I have what
the [\h__\h] how how do I get rid of them he
has to kill them I guess wait this is
good for
me I have no
card
[Music]
bro bro okay we reset our
HP that's his gimmick
uh-huh he has to kill the gold saw this
in
there should I put out the squirrel now
I want to keep it to sacrifice it next
round this is bad for you cuz it's
basically that space yeah it totally is
[\h__\h] Blood Hound at least he got rid of
one of my
Golds okay I need something good that's
not good enough you're forcing me to get
another Square
roll
right scat I got to do what I got to
[Music]
do um and then in front of I guess The
Blood Hound what the [\h__\h] is this
Guardian when an opposing creature is
placed opposite to an empty space a card
bearing this sigil will'll move to that
empty space what
but you're moving over to the other side
to the gold nugget side is that what
what you're
saying ah no aha he blocks my new
cards oh okay so he would switch with
the coyote or so no if it's empty okay
okay okay I see I see I see I see so it
doesn't matter where I place him
um G I guess you will die
actually unless you kill The Blood Hound
first I get to attack first
right yeah nice it still
take so much
damage [\h__\h] how how do I win this
still should I put down the
squirrel just for
blocking also how will I ever kill his
mule if the gold nugget is in front of
it
[Music]
isn't this an endless
loop you can no longer kill oh okay but
I can still kill him huh ah then what
did the stout mean with the MU is the
key if I killed the MU first what would
have
happened maybe he just means it will be
easier for me or
what okay okay
okay and should I pass but I I'll die oh
but I no yeah I'll
die oh mu gives
cards
pass and let's play this girl I can't
die we have a wolf you mean the wolf
does enough damage to kill him in that
one
turn the wolf will heal you the wolf
heals me
money well let's see what happens I
guess all right oh off then oh because
it's a
scale all right it's a
scale oh [\h__\h] that how that makes it a
lot more interesting huh it's not just
about getting rid of a certain amount of
HP oh I'm now getting the interest
interestingness of
[Music]
this please drop good card um okay let's
see my sparrow it only needs one
blood uh wait a
second that creature perishes
yeah wolf sacrifice the wolf ah oh Ryan
should I place it in front of the coyote
or the adder I feel like the coyote is
the better
choice doesn't matter yeah I know it
won't attack the coyote but I'm thinking
like I don't want my sparrow to be
attacked by the adder cuz I'll perish
but I guess I'll die anyway if the
coyote attacks the sparrow cuz it has 2
Hp uh oh
I don't know
man uh okay yeah no no no no squirrel
let's
see good good good good
ah
um I guess I can take a card again a
cardan uh now we
sacrifice a
squirrel take r a
snapper put it there and the go
easy I
understand oh his mule moved and I have
no more Deck cards my deck is too
trimmed I need more cards where are my
Jimmy
cards well okay here here's a square
wheel now do your job
nice bye-bye squirrel his mule moved
again his mule is
traversing the
Battleground is that it oh oh he gave me
cut oh oh I see you're putting them in
my
hand dagnabit my
mule oh sick wait I want to use those
cards we're already at the end of the
battle do I get to keep the bullfrog I
love frogs
do I get to keep
it don't get ahead of yourself you need
to draw a card oh I need to draw a card
first
okay sure I'll draw a card
[Music]
first does he block flying
enemies a card bearing the sigil will
block an opposing creature bearing the
Airborne okay but it has to be in front
of him
[Music]
right okay let's
go nice me like it fun allow me to light
your candles once more I won't be
killing you quite yet
yay we did it you're the first in a
while to overcome overcome a boss as a
reward you are granted an opportunity to
select a rare
card how many uh like rounds do I have
to go for how many boss fights and
stuff like how long does this like one
thing
go fre four
mhm child 13 the [\h__\h] is that is that a
dragon Chima poor banana child it does
not die when sacrificed but do you have
a heart to try
looks like a
cimo a
geckle the uninspiring GE perhaps you
can find a use for it I don't know it
looks funny
though
uruli this level of brutish strength
needs no explanation yeah holy [\h__\h] s
seven but four
sacrifices g g g sweep G
what nah
G you guys are just
trolling always get oh because he costs
no
blood and he can still attack uh he's
like like in slay the Spire one of those
really weak but uh easy to use cards if
you have a lot of them your deck is
really good or so yeah ships ships ships
yeah this is a
ship uh oh okay I guess I'll take Geck I
like geckos I'll give you that with the
sound of the pro prospector's pickaxe
still ringing in your ears you carried
onwards
H oh we're starting off with some nice
Fields okay the rank smell of rotten
mold permitted the humid air
permitted every step forward was
answered by some nearby slippers liver
you tread car cautiously cariously in
the
wetlands we're in the wetlands
yay what cards River Snapper and Elk ah
this one also moves like the mule after
attacking if there's a field empty I
guess
permeated
what and he's pretty strong and the
bullfrog ah
[Music]
froggy and frog frog chip
yeah very solid card okay I like
frog um left or right you guys said go
to the fire before but should I still go
to the
fire okay is it like ins slay the spire
or is it different you came across a
small group of survivors oh there are
others faces shrunken from starvation
they huddled around the
campfire uh they looked upon your group
of creatures and
beckoned come warm one of your creatures
by the fire one said oh it gets stronger
plus one warm it by the fire that will
enhances power said another you notice
one of the survivors wiping drool from
their mouth M he's hungry he wants to
eat my
card um sure the
G Okay
g they don't want to eat the G right the
fire warms the poor G enhancing its
power one of the survivors reached
toward it don't touch my G another
gashed their teeth without a word you
pulled the geek away from the fire and
left yep leave my GE alone
my GE is not for
eating
nice Jimmy's a rare Jimmy never shows up
man he's busy at kfp all right what do
you got a king fisher how fun what you
got it's in the water too water born
there's water cards a card bearing the
sigil submerges itself during its
opponent's turn while submerged opposing
creatures attack its owner directly
oh is that
interesting it's good and bad somehow
what the [\h__\h] there's a [\h__\h] spider
ew bees within once a card bearing the
sigil is struck a bee is created in your
hand a be is defined as one power one
Health and Airborne in my hand no in his
hand
right in his hand for sure interesting
and another king fisher wow he's got a
lot going
on in in in yours in his yours his what
what
mine don't don't worry about okay cuz it
will spam my hand or what how is this
bad who over whoever owns a card right
that's what I thought he it's his card
though so now it will be on his that's
what I meant the speeder does the
speeder have anything to do with it are
you cheating bro
yeah
um well squ well how about
that could get the sparrow
out where should we put
it I don't know maybe
here should have a PO
beehive oh they're in the water now
cute
um I
guess strike
beads I still have a goat I'm not going
to use the goat
[Music]
now draw for
Geck no
G [\h__\h]
can I survive no if I just can I survive
if I just um wait for the next
turn I'll I'll
survive a little
bit okay let's
try he's got an OT
cute Square
and then should we sacrifice our
Sparrow for one of these
cards I don't
know I wish
my sparrow had the sacrificing buff
um maybe exchange
[Music]
for well these are all very balanced if
I want more defense on one field Snapper
if I want more attack wolf if I want a
good balance Raven honestly Raven is
kind of good
[Music]
wolf okay we shall put it where the
Beehive is on the far left ah man
at least I got a
bee yippee the bees are s oh oh oh [\h__\h]
oh I'm dead oh I get another okay is
every battle two lives or the whole map
wait
what what
[Music]
happened every
map ah the boss resets them oh [\h__\h] so
now for the next boss fight I also only
have one life
and the battle I can't redo this one I'm
just moving
on
what an a it sub submerges itself during
my turn your turn yeah
okay the
adder and a beaver the industrious
beaver when plated constructs dams
adjacent to it oh interesting could be
like a wall it's like I'm building a
wall a geeky
let's
take defensive Powerhouse the B all
right there's uh three places where we
could go
to this was the was this the
sacrificing
thing we didn't use up all our items so
I don't know if I want to go to the item
place but
fire sacrifice the Beav since it's
expensive give the give the GE power
stronger
Geck what the hell is that my
dick fire for Geck fire for Geck you
mean you want to make the GE even
[Music]
stronger okay
you guys seem to be very much agreeing
on this I see a lot of you have played
this
game Health oh now you're making Health
stronger not attack I see I see that's
good okay wow that is yeah I mean that's
pretty op card
now stop trying to eat my
G um okay fighting time wish me luck F I
try to not [\h__\h]
up
um let's begin of a squirel but uh oh
Sparrow wait what does he have bees only
bees maybe not the best placement I
don't know I don't know about placement
yet you
know maybe I should have
a
um Square
wall should I sacrifice Sparrow and
squirrel for the
wolf I mean I did it but now where do we
place it let's let's let's place it
correctly for once on the right okay I
thought you might say
that all right all right all right
they're gonna hit me with the bees
though which oh God gets me into a
difficult situation again I wish I would
get the get the G to be
honest I think now it's okay to maybe
hope for the
G top deck GE
time where should put squirel into
gold no this time we'll get a gck
okay I might use the goat but ah then I
have to sacrifice my
wolf
no that's a good pull I mean maybe if I
had squirrels to
use wait maybe I'll be fine because I'm
adding free damage he's adding free
damage I think I'll be fine
it's got a mantis oh wait [\h__\h] the
Mantis no oh I'm almost
dead
um goat
yeah damn it wait so the goat needs just
one sacrifice right okay and and then I
and then but the goat gives free
sacrifice
right um
okay wa should I should I go for the
wolf again I could also go for the Raven
and hope that you know I get a
kill yeah okay good cuz the Raven goes
direct
wolf
h h
a wolf you get more
sacrifice all right the wolf is still
has a sacrifice buff bro
[Music]
what oh wait no it needs to can I undo
[\h__\h] can I
undo ah can I
undo I cannot do
okay uh okay then uh
go did I neglect to mention Overkill
damage no yeah excess damage is not
wasted ooh it carries over to the cart
behind them okay but not to you then if
there's nothing behind only if there's a
cart
behind lucky for you
oh H oh God how am I not dead that looks
like I'm
dead um
uh
uh squ
w g top top deck Geck uh okay wait we
have a b
that wait the be also gives I can
sacrifice the B too
right should I do that
mhm
mhm like so okay now we got a pretty
good lineup we got to win this come
on
Yo finally winning he's got so many like
insects on his in his deck now he's got
an ant over
there oh well um I don't really need
anything my I have a oh no on maybe uh G
time I wasted the bee what do you
mean I could have won what didn't need
to sacrifice the
be well we we we'll die and we'll win
anyway [\h__\h] why are you not a
g why are you not a
g y oh well I'll be fine
that's a lot of popcorn on that scale
now G to well I I I I mean even if I
take the squirrel now it's not like it
will be enough to play the Bieber so
this is the G
yeah
yippee believe in the Y yo you got to
believe yay
all thanks to the gck I'm so
proud how brutal of you you dealt me
more damage than you needed to win
however in my game such Feats are
rewarded oh to be precise a tooth to
keep for each extra damage
dealt to
keep the Trapper may be interested in
your spoils oh it's like
money I had in infinite sacrifice in
play I don't even understand what you're
saying is this a fire or what is
this oh you were stopped along the way
by a Trapper looking to liquidate his
pelts uh there was something uncanny
about his appearance but you were
quickly distracted by his Wares yeah
this bear trap or
what care to look at me
pelts where are they where are the pelts
waa oh it's okay a pelt
card that's kind of [\h__\h] up that it
still has the
face um I don't know man I don't know
about that why you putting that in front
of me is it
free Floppy bunny
take yeah free of charge
okay thank thanks
ah please consider me
Bel I think this guy's a psychopath he's
a psychopath um but so how many do I
have do I have to count this can you not
give me like a a counter here 1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9 10 I have
10 can you not put a number there why do
I have to count it myself
aha oh great still have to count though
uh there a golden P I don't know can I
look at what it does or if I click it do
I automatically buy it cuz right click
isn't working right
now get the gold okay can I read it now
no I can't read it bro it's just a
walker you'll see later okay thanks for
your
business he's really enjoying his role
play the man isur this he a [\h__\h]
psychopath he this is a serial
killer the man assured you of the value
of the pals they appear to be useless in
a fight but he mentioned that the
traitor further down the path would
reward you for them okay okay I'll hope
for that I'll believe
you okay um not sure which path to take
I'll leave that to you
[Music]
guys
here
items oh yeah now we have no more items
okay let's go fill me up with some it
ooh scissors that's a fancy scissor
looks like
Allison dark Al Allison Wonderland
scissor if you deem it necessary you may
cut up one of my cards of these
oh a powerful item turns this and and
turn this and I'll skip my next turn
oh a gust from this may lift your
creatures into the air if only four a
turn it has bird
feet nice items
though the wow oh wait I have to choose
from
these should we choose the should we
choose this one he skips a
turn okay
um squel or the
[Music]
tooth
sque oh what another
hourglass sick I'm lucky am I
lucky we're fighting wow what is this
why is so spooky is this a boss fight
what the hell
why is this so
scary we have a tree which I don't
really understand
honestly okay cool it's a big tree so it
blocks flying things King Fisher and the
river egg a card bearing the sigil will
grow into a more powerful from after one
turn on the board
okay can you check the
totem Sprinter at the end of the owner's
turn
the owner are we both owners or only is
only he an owner cuz he's the owner of
the gam or so I don't know a card
bearing this sigil will move in the
description a direction inscribed in the
sigil only him uhhuh okay uh oh we have
bullfrog nice thank God we have uh
something good to start off with oopsie
begin thank you Cody Koy appreciate
it oh oh oh did they hurt me why stop
hurting me I guess we take a
[Music]
squirel
but I don't know using it now no point
right or should I sacrifice one of my my
My
Bullfrog get
wolf buar will die next turn Okay early
death then so
sad okay um here birth was denied
whatever that was going to be I don't
even
know um
Square wall or Geck top deck
Geck to that no no no chances are too
low
squirrel then I guess I'll wait top
de I feel you I feel you and I really
want to go for it but I feel like we're
just going
to yeah suffer too much
top
kick no no no we got to be patient see
that's fine that
works H we're
fine okay and we could go for another
squirrel or we could top top K top top
de
uh yeah okay this time ah
no well I could take a
squirel I'm fine this turn yeah maybe we
don't need to waste that yet we we're
we're we're
fine my wolf is so
strong oh God okay ah he got rid of the
tree all right thanks
uh
squirel we got to set up our deck
now Raven can finish him Raven Will Ham
okay I believe you go for it
Raven oh he was finished
indeed I'm not capable of doing the math
just
yet but thank you cards let's
go I like how we're like doing the
opposite of trimming Our Deck I'm used
to trimming my deck add a raven egg
which I guess hatches into a raven it is
no less conniving in its
incubation can I what does that even
mean actually or never what is this what
is this Mark does it mean I already have
it in my deck is that what they're
saying congrat on the
baby scheming ah oh yeah it do be
scheming it's already looking
out Adder for G why for G he needs a
friend or what when a card bearing theal
damage is another creatur how how is
this helping
Geck m
wait let me read that again the creature
[Music]
perishes
perishes wait wait wait the creature aka
the adder dies or the creature that I'm
attacking dies no matter how many HP it
has add one she even though it says one
attack here
want I attack okay but I guess in
exchange it's also pretty weak with just
one
HP oh uh this is the the thing that
makes them be sacrifice B right um how
about something that stays on the field
longer cuz it's stronger how about the
beaver what
[Music]
Adder the
adder why
add something that's cheap yeah that's
why I was thinking like okay yeah
something cheap but but uh this one has
more HP so it stays on the field longer
is what I was
thinking I'm choosing to sacrifice right
now oh right
oh all right ah cuz we're not using the
cat oh never mind okay so this isn't
always sorry I was kind of thinking cuz
we only did with the cat so far I was
thinking we're um giving any of these
cards the the ability that the cat has
okay and we're going to lose this
card aha so the ader ability we want to
give it to one of these any of these
what do you
think to the golden Pelt
imagine the
gek for the G oh that's how you meant it
see
now oh [\h__\h] the G is going to be like my
boss
card speaking of boss is that a boss
fight oh [\h__\h] I only have one life right
uh-oh uhoh I hope top deck geek maybe
even first draw
g a foul smell invaded our your nostrils
and caus your throat to
seize a hulking Man Hulk Hogan Sat by a
bra brackish pond with his feet
submerged in the dark water he pulled a
hook from a pile of rotting fish and
Rose to his
feet he's he is so Cho this guy tbio
serial killer let's go I am the angler
Go Fish you could be my angle or you
could be my devil right now you're
looking more like my devil though my
friend even though you say you're my
angle there is a way out for both of us
it's somewhere in this foul cabin uh
okay be Sil though I will tear you to
shreds are you telling we to just walk
away from the table and go walk out the
door where's pop
G unbelievable is rigged he knows I have
the boss card geckle so he put it on on
the back of my
dick what do you have a king
fisher well I can already do the oh wait
that's actually wait that's
sick uh
yo
okay yes s wait I can already play this
oh my god let's
go I I know I know
[Music]
which fish hard to choose and little
salmon sque W wait he's fishing my Stout
what the [\h__\h] fresher fish easy choose
fish F fish fresher fish is he going to
is he trying to steal my sto is he
getting my
sto I I I I I I I I I I I see what's
happening I'll be really [\h__\h] pissed
let him take the squirrel how can I make
him take the
squirrel ah he steals the Fresh's fish
will it still change is he not like
committed to that
one okay okay then I I should not play
my Snapper then okay
oh that's what he means with fresh a
fish
mine now go
fish are you going to continue doing
that every
turn no way right it's not going to do
turn that would be really mean every
other okay all right all right all right
all
right where shall we put it to the right
side or to the left
side I've blocked him with the
squirrel is that I guess pretty good let
oh let's keep the squirrel there I see I
see okay um go nice oh
nice H stale fish heart juice next turn
better fish
he already has his hook
out okay I guess this is already the
other
turn maybe top deck gck get a squirrel
oh okay ah okay first sacrifice yeah
okay okay okay
okay yeah new fish easy
choose you're kind of cute as a Fisher
man we win we win oh yeah refresh okay
what [\h__\h] I thought my PC broke too to
Fast Too Soon eh the
[\h__\h] the [\h__\h] that's not [\h__\h] Fair
what are you
doing did I kill him too early what do
you
mean um
what to good an what game soft
what
n are you kidding me
what what do
you what
what okay top take K maybe I don't know
save me if this is scripted then save me
or
okay here I have maybe I can kill
him I can totally kill
him what if I win oh [\h__\h] no hey this is
not fair this is just not
fair top de G
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] rabbit
pelt I could force him to
um skip his turn but I see this is
definitely scripted right so not going
to huh Go Fish hey wa that was in the
thumnail
roll credits I
guess uh you aren't dead yet this isn't
Purgatory though you may think of it
that way before you expire I must ask
you a favor play again I would like a
momento uh you are ve your very own
death
card what the [\h__\h] am I drawing on it or
what that be cute it's quite plain at
the moment isn't it we will work
together to me that I want this to be
the perfect momento of
you oh here are some cards from your
mediocre deck yo you purposfully didn't
show the gecko because that would be
meaning that my deck was not mediocre if
you showed the gecko that is proofed
that my deck was not
mediocre yeah he had the script to win
yeah bro we can put them to good use
please choose a car to draw the cost
from
aha the cost of blood you mean well
they're all the
same
yeah uhhuh we're making our own car the
[\h__\h] golden
Pelt uh will use power and health well
these don't even have half power you
[Music]
sucker
he's scamming
me I never got rid of the pelts he
forced me to V those now choose a card
from which we will extract the sigils
okay
well gek maybe or
wolf there's my
G maybe wolf honestly because the PO
name I don't know I I'll choose this one
yeah I like
that I never did ask you your
name this is the W
card what what will I look like do I
scribble on it the
portrait wait wait it's just going to
like find a a picture of my face from my
PC data or or
uh uh face
reveal you do not need to smile he says
I don't need to smile you guys are
telling me to
smile
Dy what do I look like do I look cute at
[Music]
least and show me my picture here we go
again another Challenger Perhaps it is
time perhaps you can understand
bones
bones aost
you're teaching me a new thing the
resource for aosome C costs two
bones okay you gain a bone when one of
your creatures perishes for any
[Music]
reason
okay but is this like a thing where one
wants to build a deck that focuses on
Bones rather than blood Etc or is mixing
it totally
valid tell me about it hi sto you don't
like to talk to me anymore are you mute
now have you gone through some [\h__\h] from
the death of your ah even from that
wow valid
okay valid not mixing is better mixing
preferred okay you will not lose this
until it is spent or the battle
ends so disant uh
attack a rattler he's got a rattler
maybe I should have put my sto in front
of
that
um new deck no
G
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] what do I
do should I sacrifice squirrel and sto
for Wolf
maybe you have items
no
interesting yeah
okay and then I can also play
my well oh he's still talking is he like
a mascot or
something uh uh one Health okay we can
kill him and the AP
possum go a possum
go people hate aosom IRL but I guess you
you'll be liked in this
[Music]
game
huh can I sacrifice a
possums maybe not now but like later
I think I'm find this turn just leaving
it like that yeah I can okay
cool oh
yeah you hurt my
wolf you must
pay a little bit more a little bit more
but I'm out of carts I only have squirel
now what my deck is already trimmed
again it's
tiny but I'm winning here we
go
nice
uh
oh I forgot your figurine what my my
card what oh my f h get up and fetch it
for me
oh okay it's beside the
save okay do you know have legs or
something what is
this I want to look around is he going
to be mad if I look
around what is this what is
this give
me okay not a hold on
[Music]
okay I'll take it can I choose cuz
there's uh
several
ah I have to choose this
one there's something in the safe
[Music]
H is the code always different each
time cuz it's a Rog likee
or open
open look for the
lock well wait I don't think I
can there's no luy
lies okay
uh no we're good we're good we here I
sorry it took me a while let us continue
okay here we go card cards cards cards
cards mhm Coy Rattler ooh he he takes
six bones wow and a cockroach great I
want my old deck back
please H the unkillable Cockroach it
returns to your hand after that
okay good for a small deck Maybe
roach H
okay UND dying s you know you're free to
get up again to keep your blood flowing
uh sure no I'm fine I'll stay on the
table I'm un comfortable
here what some bone tokens for rainy
night ah four looks like four and the
Boulder and the twoo thingy maybe the
piggy
only got one
item I thought you ah because I already
have to H I should have used one I used
smart or something he usually doesn't
even bother teaching about bones all
right here's a tip I saw a past victim
writing a passcode in the rule book
[Music]
how
to what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
mirror what does it say Bell ah cuz I
didn't see the card yet
[Music]
where's the first page
again
uh wait let me just open the book
again ah 273
ah he did tell me I can get up again but
maybe not during the fight right all
right all right all right Square world
time what does he have porcupine oh I
can imagine what that does
okay but yeah we'll see total misplay
yeah probably [\h__\h] I don't know why is
he so honest he's literally you guys
he's
chat so
sassy I'm sorry for misplaying but at
least I don't know
ah I get it I get
it
um don't listen to the St he's a
hater okay if you say
so uh I guess you know cuz he's a hater
I might just sacrifice
him sorry
buddy um let's put the AP possum here
that should kill the coyote
right
yeah oh what oh oh what he didn't play
anything though I understand that I
killed his turn kind of but he didn't
play
anything did he not have anything to
play he's out of cards already okay
guess this it easy
win what do you mean you're out of cards
[Music]
H at least this deck is also small small
deck huh if you desire it you may stand
now it's like he wants me to look at his
save it will allow me time to
plan all right I forgot the code though
I think it was 273 I'm no Tyrant you may
stay whenever the map is unrolled it
allows me time to plan your next
encounter but do keep your hands off of
my
[Music]
possessions
risky it seems like something alive is
in
here
[Applause]
oh stink bug cute oh hello I wasn't sure
if I would ever ever escape and that
iron Crypt is H is the St around the
stunted wolf this madness must end put
it
away yeah into my deck it goes and the
key is it is the key for
this it
is why is he not stopping me why is he
not just stabbing me right now what the
[\h__\h] is this
he's
chilling aha puzzle
time I don't
understand can I solve this
now need to five
damage
what
ah skink
skink the [\h__\h] is that I forgot that I
have put that there very well you may
add it to your deck and I'll deal you
one every every so
often oh you deal me one what do you
mean you deal me one it's my
deck wait wasn't there another one
[Music]
uhuh [\h__\h] I can't move it
back ah ah right I can move like this
but I can't move it back again oh no ah
okay I see it depending on where okay
never
mind let's try
how about we brute force
it I don't
know I don't know about this one I can't
really
understand but this is the opponent
right the upper row and the bottom is me
and I have to do five damage
on my side to him
right and the left was damage and right
was Health
right how does this not what does this
up here how does this not kill
him oh exactly five damage
[Music]
can I just leave this empty then yeah
okay that's
one two one two
damage don't know
need to learn what this lizard symbol me
means I guess so maybe we can do this
one
later streamers or YouTubers always
Brute Force this part rather than
actually trying to figure out what the
sigil
means uh no okay we learn it by doing
it sooner or later welcome
back that's
me that's not what I look like what is
that weird bar around my
[Music]
neck it's like
um what the [\h__\h] is that
W elk fwn
the Nash and fun it quickly grows into
an elk and after one turn but I got to
get myself right but I'm kind of
[\h__\h]
W you got Frankenstein looks like
Frankenstein that's what I was going to
say
Frankenstein yeah I'm not a good
card all right we'll take the elk FAA
let's go do something good for me all
right I still have like all my items I
guess so I'll go to the fire
maybe cuz I don't know if I have any
good effects
[Music]
really backpack but I have a full
inventory I don't really I don't know I
should just use my items until the next
inventory place
[Music]
uh you guys want to trim your
deck what would we be combining though
coach has a good sigil
a the choice is yours uh what the [\h__\h]
why are you so
stinky stinky the creature opposing a
card bearing the sigil loses one
power okay unkillable when the card bra
yeah
mhm um here when a card bearing this
sigil would be struck a tail is created
in its place and the card bearing this
sigil moves to the
right what when a card bearing the will
be struck a tail is created in its
place and a card bearing deil moves to
the right I need to see an action I
think roach for sigil
okay
for Al go
[Music]
so whichever card I choose will always
come back to my
deck
skink
okay
nice okay battle to
battle let's show him who
boss uh you again indeed our friend fre
me well I basically told them how to do
it you got a plan we have another friend
here you've got to be I wouldn't call
him a friend but I suppose we are in
deep this
time is is that friend behind that
riddle the the puzzle that I just gave
up
on would make sense okay we have stump
porcon coyote
okay um we have a skink and the sto I
guess we'll start with the
skink let's
go I should use my
items should use my
items you but the tail also is like undy
it comes back into
my
what it's hard to call it cowardly
what free tail wait so the tail is like
a block basically cuz it can't attack I
see I see I
see now okay I don't really see a reason
to use my items right now yet fine and
then we also have stink bug maybe next
time maybe I don't
know if the wriggling tail
dies do it porcupine do
it oh it went into my hand not into my
deck
interesting I won't allow you to play a
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry um I guess
I'll take a
squirrel why is it why is it B Bing is
it a chicken
actually here we
[Music]
go a thanks for getting rid of my stomp
stomp
surely
slowly wait tail is like Geck I guess
now
cute uh I don't know what to do right
now uh I'm just waiting for the stump to
be
gone tailor is a squirrel B ah
okay I see
draw a main deck okay main Deck card hi
froggy what's
up ah easy this is a easy
fight I don't know fun I see the way
this is going yeah the way it's going is
you're going to die I can
see what that happens no yeah you can't
concede because I want to Overkill you
to get the teeth bro he can't I just
concede can I decline you may accept my
surrender or you may finish this match
this yeah yeah yeah I will finish it
bro and the feather the feather what how
do I I choose the feather if uh I want
to let him concede no no no no no
nobody no no no
I don't know if that positioning was
good but you
know probably
not I want the font to yes Elk elk
yourself yes I was hoping for something
like this
yippee time to Overkill
yeah let's go that's good we will never
let him concede I wonder if there's ever
a point where it would make sense to let
him
concede
um maybe the Rattler would be
interesting with how many bones we can
possibly
accumulate or elk fa again try puzzle
now I don't really know if I understand
to be honest even after reading
that yeah yeah yeah I want to I I'll try
the one I'll try
it I I think you guys have to help me
with the with the puzzle I don't
understand
um where do we
go left
yeah
okay uh oh plus two Health
okay plus two
Health pick something else why is he so
depressed now uh skink are we
overpowering our skink now instead of
the
G top skink doesn't top deck skink
doesn't sound S as good as top deck GE
though he's had a rough time don't use
skink give it to
rler I kind of
agree I don't think I can go back now
I've
chosen my card oh no never mind I can't
go back I don't know I want to make the
the Rattler stronger actually
the survivors were right about the
Flames they enhanced the creatures
Health spotting a few of the survivors
drooling you made a hey retreat with
your Rattler and the rest of my cards
battle time
again here we go here we go here we
go what do you have a boulder and a wolf
CB
ah weak start my friend you were
stronger in the in the tutorial I feel
like um
let's start with the
skink should I use my
items feel like I I don't know I
no no
okay I want to I want to make this fast
for him make his suffering shorter
well maybe we shouldn't put the elk fwn
right there maybe the elk fwn should be
in front of the boulder or
I or bullfrog for
now alus Cub but by the end of
my is is is my is my aone going to kill
the cup before it becomes a big wolf I
guess cuz it attacks
first yeah okay nice nice
hey it didn't even grow up okay I guess
I did the same thing but still at least
from my case it was Cub versus Cub you
however ethically
incorrect don't appreciate
it my he will die though if I put the
bullfrog there he will 100% die but I
guess is that better
than
me getting the
damage to the right okay
um well I mean even if I take a squir
roll I won't be able to play a card so
let's take a card first a pass let's
go although where to put this AP
possum cuz uh
H paom contact well not much block the
wolf
okay we have to kill the wolf at some
point it's me it's
you wait I could sacrifice the
bullfrog but no way I can sacrifice the
skink yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah sack the
skink put the sto
there put the the oh right you also need
a sacrifice okay never mind
then it's nice that they give him back
right into my hand I thought it would go
into the
dick oh you want to CED
again this game is pretty easy in the
beginning
huh oh yeah I will not let you
concede of course
not 10 memberships thank you so
much
yay more eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs Raven
egg elk mantis oh the fervent mantis
it's prying claws strike both to the
left and the right oh but not straight
in front of it then or
what interesting
kind of like AOE then AOE
damage so should you not put the Mantis
on the on like an edge spot only in the
two middle spots
then or would the damage still go oh no
okay okay interesting oh enhance power
of
course maybe skink or
yeah skink
or skink mantis oh mantis's kind of weak
too sure more oopsy more AOE damage more
stronger AOE
[Music]
damage okay oh boss fight oh [\h__\h] okay
yeah what are my
items a tooth thing a bone thing and the
screw let's use it
all after that I will lose all my items
or do I get to bring them with me by the
way to the next is there a point in
hogging them probably not
right you ah you keep them okay but I I
think I should still not
hog my boss battles are high stakes
tests of your aptitude with one flame
you will e over overcome them or die
fear not I will let you keep the smoke
what the smoke
what because I I have only one HP I get
a smoke card what does it even do we'll
see I think you don't need a SC now you
can use
[Music]
it you mean right away he blew out one
he blew it out I thought I already had
had one gone the incessant Clank Clank
clanking reverberated between your ears
the path ahead was blocked by a
grotesque
figure it was the prospector hea wait we
already know the prospector is he the
gold guy the gold digger why can't I
remember his name I believe I lost some
of my memory in the
[Music]
flash Clank clank what is the smoke part
what I get four bones if I
when a card bearing the sigil dies four
bones are okay but I have to first like
sacrifice it or have it get killed
okay
um
interesting interest wait well um would
it be smarter to sacrifice the the the
smoke then for the Mantis
play and ENT keep mantis for end mantis
face oh
okay I guess
so ah
because likeit can the stink book ah
okay they can't sacrifice so I have to
wait oh no accident oh well oh
no can you please ask me to confirm
things game
I I accidentally clicked on on both of
those
things all right well
then
bro he's got the pack mule
again I didn't want to hog the items yet
so many
bones yeah right okay uh
I got two squirrels already I'm honestly
going to pick from my deck elkon okay U
what
space Oh wait the pH two you guys said
phase two then let's do elk
phone but he's going to kill my elk Thon
wait wait never mind
[\h__\h] no no no I will kill him he's got
one HP never mind oh okay
cool Bonk Bonk Bonk more tooth for the
Tooth
Fairy
God okay I don't really need to do
anything I
[Music]
think I'm going to get this
mule yeah oh face to okay oh [\h__\h]
there's gold no no what are you going to
which
one okay
my
bro huh is he allowed to
do
what well I
guess what is this good or
bad I mean at least unless he has flying
enemies and he's forced to attack the
gold nuggets
all right should we maybe get the
[Music]
squirrel attack my gold please thank you
thank
you okay now is the time
um uh draw a
card maybe another squirrel ah if I get
one more squirrel I can play both the
Mantis and the Wolf in theory if I yeah
yeah should be it can I yeah I think
[Music]
so wolf placement attacks free maybe in
front of The Blood
Hound yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay Mattis right uh first
this and then
this and that should be ah wait okay I
know normally we wouldn't want the
Mantis on an edge I know I know I know I
know but like I don't have
space but he's he's going to die anyway
don't
worry oh
[Music]
carts
yeah my carts
now oh oh no my man
okay yeah m worth it yeah yeah right
because otherwise the mule would have
still taken a while longer to kill cuz
there was gold nuggets in front of it
the Mantis made it
possible Radler oh yeah we have so many
bones oh draw a card um we have squirrel
do I want the
squirrel I think we maybe want a
[Music]
squirrel I'll take a squirrel
I have so many
bones he's so done for he's so done for
him putting gold nuggets there is kind
of a disadvantage for him now he can't
attack me with those enemies if he had
flying enemies then it would be good
actually but he doesn't have any flying
enemies so what are you doing
[Music]
bro uh-
um I don't know Square wall oh [\h__\h] I
can't sacrifice enough to
play The Raven but okay we can do
this and win was this a boss
fight I get it I get it hey I relive my
candles
doesn't quite feel like a boss fight my
friend tutorial felt more difficult I'm
I'm going say it again rard give me give
me a good one give me GE top gck
G and a pack rat The Prudent packrat
never doubt the utility of a well
stocked
pack
oh interesting the Eternal serpent death
strengthens it forever
forever oh sh [\h__\h] you guys like that
card
right oh oh oh busted
okay okay it's the strong as it goes
crazy so we want him to kill my card
okay after the heroing encounter with
the prospector you gathered yourself and
continued
onwards let me
see uh the the air grew thake with
moisture the buzzing and chirpping of
insects drowned out the sound of your
footfalls you beheld the wetlands again
but this time you won't cheat in here
with grizzly bears will you okay guys
you want to help me with the puzzle I
legitimately don't
understand
um
help I need I need help please
don't attack the second from left okay
so I'll leave this
down but
then am I no no I didn't BR I knew what
I was doing I knew what I was doing I
knew what I was doing I knew what I was
see second try that that couldn't
possibly be a brute force that was just
me actually understanding
it formidable creatures those ants very
well uh I will add them to your deck I
can make them available for future
challenges thank
you he's so
nice even though I'm going through his
things how did you do it um I understood
the thing with the tail and so on
[Music]
mhm
yeah let's see what you got for me
amantis Louise that's another player
wait is that is that is that a player
that was here before
me oh [\h__\h] he's not is he good though
he's he moves to the side and he's the
like he goes into the
water but maybe we take another
mantis
okay it's pretty bad just like me what
is this is this just a skipper or are we
voting cuz that looks like a voting
thing go right
yeah oh removing a card
oh no okay uh what do we
choose what is this when a card bearing
the sigil is played an ant is created in
your hand which I guess is is a good
sacrifice to make or oh wait oh but ah
the card would be gone then right I
can't I don't want to sacrifice or botos
mantis on undying
snake
oh
oh oh did you have that in mind when
when telling me to choose the Mantis
thank you Mobius thank you thank you
good
night sleepy
time okay here we
go what does he have bees bees and fish
King
Fish ah this is a good placement
actually okay
and your should I throw out should I no
I can't can't yet okay let's
go
nice
mhm i' say s square
square behind tree was safer
true it's okay we'll give Auto BOS the
safe spot should I sacrifice the Mantis
to get the oros and the
aasum because you
know no just attack
okay you want oros to die though I guess
so at least for
now early
on
um Conor
play Squirrel into auts into massive
Overkill
sorry sorry
bro wait bro
sorry I'll pass some time baby here we
go attack Yoo
ah oh
W wo wo wo wo that was a lot of
teeth right another person oh there's
like a bunch of these
huh
uh he's got the poison thing and he
costs bones and he has free
health he seems okay if you guys would
agree that's solid I guess
know okay there are more riddles okay
riddle me
this uh what do you normally
say should I go left or
right not
sure maybe
right Batman really me this Batman is
that from the Batman movie
ah we have not food once said but
perhaps one of your creatures will join
us enhance its power well you're not
going to eat it right they're never
going to eat it right I'm kind of
worried with that
statement nope nope
nope uh what it's
power they might it's
RNG how high are the
chances not yet b or
mantis not on first turn
okay okay bring
it the power of the Autos was enhanced
by the warmth as one of the survivors
began pulling a knife from their pocket
you RI
you I miss GE me too he was a nice
little G cute always left
behind something nice for me
okay here we go he's got a bullfrog
okay I'm going to place it here cuz I
don't want it to die by the
way from the
bullfrog what do you have a okay pretty
basic
stuff
um yeah I don't no man I I don't want to
sacrifice the elk
yeah
okay okay okay we're fine
[Music]
ohow squirrel
are we playing wolf or ant
Queen both seem
good might need an
item wolf this is di
jant okay well my wolf does free damage
I could get rid
of maybe the coyote
yeah left there there
uhhuh and you I can't do anything with
you yet should I choose should I use my
item I don't know if we're going to be
okay oh but my elk moves to the left
after the attacks right so then it
blocks the the the
Frog I think oh wait it doesn't move oh
there we go so blocks frog
I guess another squirrel because I I
don't know it would be nice if I would
uh draw something that needs
bones but I only have three
bones block rler with
scrl squirrel
block okay
smart smart people another Adler and the
he's got a snake
deck wrong snake
oh oh
oops dead no no what if I do the tee
thing also maybe maybe maybe
maybe I lost no
use maybe I don't
know an ant
crate okay I have two
candles does the I forgot does the board
reset yeah
okay I hope for more well sorry okay we
have a new field like something with
blood should we go left or
right yeah I feel like I was a little
bit misled by the
chat new
one blood for the blood God is a card ah
choose not a specific beast but decide
the cost that you wish to
pay
aha ah bones times what and free blood
and two
blood so I don't know what card he's
giving me I just know what the cost will
be of the card maybe
free bones bones bones bones bones aome
okay what were you expecting I don't
know man aasum is fine I like aosom in
this
game I'm okay with that oh
items what is this again did the use you
may cut up on ah yeah uhuh
uhhuh
um I think maybe
[Music]
scissors and
andies okay let's
go
Advance hands for Greetings look there's
a third talking card somewhere around
here
personally I hate the guy biggest
killjoy ever but he's the only one of us
with a plan to get things back to normal
what's normal anyway here I don't know
if normal is really that good he's got
some really basic cards again okay
nothing
special but uh o spider go away go away
I had a funny thing
today um I was sitting in my garden with
my cats we were having a good time and I
suddenly
noticed cuz i' I've noticed that there
was like long strings of
spider uh silk spider webs like just
single single spiderweb going over long
distances uh and and I've noticed that
but I didn't get rid of it or anything
but
suddenly I see a spider flying flying
towards me but not really flying she was
like on her um on her
spiderweb and she landed on me I was
like he
yo how dare you how dare you the
audacity but I I literally watched it
flying over to me and Landing to me or
on Me
Slowly don't tell this to don't tell a
yeah she had a spider problem
right um they all they all kind of
suck I'm not sure what the best
placement is do I want to fight the
bullfrog or do I want to go like you
know beyond these enemies and
attack uh cuz this one if if I plac it
in front of the king fisher I would
attack the dude directly
right in front of the
bat
okay you sure uh yeah I guess so cuz
Chad told me so
though couldn't be
sure oh he's got a sparrow behind it oh
wow wow wow already
[Music]
hurt I don't like this right now
because rather
than
squirrels I don't know I guess I could
sacrifice the sto and the squirrel and
no no just no I mean like
squirrel because
[Music]
H yeah cuz they need bones and
like even if I sacrifice the squirrel it
feels kind of wasted because I get blood
and the bone and I feel like I would
like to use the blood too you know what
I
mean should we should we skip his
turn his
turn but do I do I use it
now or like do I do my things first I
don't know how that
works have to draw first oh yeah okay
but I I don't know what to
draw maybe a squirrel I
guess squirrel stalk would work it will
give you bones ah you mean just putting
it on the field and letting him kill it
or do we skip his
turn we could skip his
turn they
fly cut one of his
cards let's skip his turn I'll pass my
next turn
good so should
I it doesn't matter if I put down the
scel now
now I'll just
uh I can draw again
already should I do squirel
again block with the
squel the bullfrog
maybe okay ENT turn first
I'm obligated to
pass
yeah now I don't
know
um I'm in the pickle I don't know deck
okay oh more bones okay bones bones
bones
Malone
H okay then I just already ring the bell
cuzz I got to I got to let him kill the
squirrel
[\h__\h] you die if your ring bell you think
he'll uh he might kill
me should we cut the Sparrow
I'm just going to cut this barel can I
or can I not if it's not on the
field are the diving
one okay we'll just we're just going to
go for it am I safe now or should I
still use the the toothpick
okay you should be okay I hope I hope so
I hope
so okay we got do we got bones we got
two bones we can put put out the stink
BG but
man n this kind of
[Music]
sucks I mean
a r should I I don't have enough bones
for a rattler I can only play the a
possum or the stink bug AOS a stink bug
is kind of
better I it weakens the one that I that
is in front of
so stink the middle oh cuz the diver is
coming
okay should I use
am I going to
survive feel like I might need
to just I can't do ow I can't do the
math I'm scared I I don't
know that's my biggest problem in this
game I think going
forward um uh
um why don't you kill my cards bro how
long does it take you to kill my [\h__\h]
sto just kill it
already squirrel block squirrel
okay I want some
freaking
bones
okay well at some point his deck will be
empty for sure enough you want to die
too
we got one
bone it's not good should we block off a
squirrel
again yeah I got to get
those I got to get those
bones thanks thanks ow ow ow ow ow
dangerous
dangerous he overkilling me or
what wait how many bones we have I can't
see two
it's ogre what have a posum
now squirrel a yeah squirrel again
um posum does one damage well the sto
will kill the bat
now
um but I won
wait should I not play the aasum
yet it's okay you
win I
lost oh wait we're fine actually I guess
cuz I brought the the scale
back did I I don't understand uh free
bones okay
Reggie I guess it's your time h ah
sorry ah
hi elk
fwn
H he still got more
cards oh
[Music]
um okay I don't know how about we
sacrifice a squirrel for the Elk phone
but the elk phone will be in front of
the
tree that's good that's fine okay I
guess um
yeah okay one more turn Maybe then we
got him maybe or
two he the elk will move to the left if
the sto ever dies but the sparrow will
not attack the St it will attack me
so we're so
back you thought I was dead and turn and
you
win okay sorry this is confusing me go
away no that's not what I want to see I
want to just ring the bell I want ah let
me ring the bell oh I have to draw
that's why I can't
okay I forget to
draw not winning yet not quite
yet work or
end well okay but what if I end this
turn this is the turn
there we go finally that's a weird
fight oh felt kind of
weird C
time moose Buck moose the Regal moose
the creatures of the wild Make Way for
it oh oh they do you I
See Seven health bullfrog and a
[Music]
mantis Canadian power for Canada Oh
Canada yeah but we're going to go with
the
Mantis it's it's so um expensive o I
guess we want items because we don't
have any
anymore maybe we get lucky with some
hourglasses and
stuff uh card is
good gold disc good
h no hourglasses bones may be
good hope you like my choices
guys yeah yeah okay cuz we got so many
bone cards too now the mud tugged hard
at your feet forcing you to slow your
pace the rank odor caused your stomach
to churn and your eyes to water it was
the rotting fish that hung from the
branches around you a huge man
approached he loves what he's doing he
loves his storytelling Go Fish ah no now
we have to F of fishes
[Music]
again is he fishing this turn already or
next turn next turn right
surely should we uh should I play the
Mattis right away or wait for
[Music]
later later
that's is a good
start okay well we have free I
think
um I place it
here so the Mantis doesn't attack in the
front right it only attacks here and
here
right I could since this is a boss fight
I could
already eat my bones my bone Piggy and
bring out the Rattler is that a bad
[Music]
strategy although it's it's probably not
even enough it it probably has four and
I would be up to five no need
okay okay Second Face okay okay I'll
have more bones then all stale heart
shoes
yeah but now not so stale anymore you
say are you sure still the same
[Music]
so we give him a squirrel then just a
squirrel does that take us does it count
does it give me a
bone oh that I wasn't I didn't really
realize I didn't realize that the
pushes his bird
back oh no I told you to I all according
to Kaku of course of course of
[Music]
course
okay
um should I just like keep the squirrel
there and not kill it
oopsie just put my sto to the left or to
the right
cuz left I guess I can attack him
directly I guess even if I put the sto
to the right it won't be able to attack
this
thing or left but it can block it can it
mantis will kill it anyway oh my
squirrel oh
true left or right side not middle bad
play he
says oh it's going good so far mantis is
gone all stale hard
choose okay I
could first of all let's take a
squirrel wait he's fishing he's fishing
I was
thinking taking some bones but maybe too
early still scissor or
[Music]
frog oh man mind play yeah was I want to
play the
Rattler but then you guys are you guys
are saying play the Rattler but you know
I have to take the the
bones where should we put
it it could kill the Frog so in in front
of frog is
[Music]
fine no pH left
is f okay I'll put it there and then no
what bro you scar me I thought you were
ending my
turn okay take fish it's not fish it's
squir world but sure if you like this
kind of land fish enjoy it likes nuts so
make sure to feed it lots of nuts
goldfish okay okay H I guess a
s I have one
[Music]
bone let's see what the deck gives me
what I'm saving up for
[Music]
okay oh we're almost
winning oh we can totally win this turn
may
maybe but we'll we'll bring uh a
squirrel for him
can't play the a possum
yet
okay should we wait if I put the
squirrel in front of the squirrel will
his king fisher
like uh
disappear window now
regardless yes yes yes yes let's find
out yeah I want to see that I want to
test it for science
okay I guess we won't see because I
killed him before he could
fish ah
man
unfortunate go
feish which are you fishing or not Bait
Bucket I we never saw that before
because last time he just spawned grizly
Bears coward
don't tell
her that he's not going to fish for his
own Bait Bucket
right elk
[Music]
fwn um I'm really not sure what this is
going to do
oh what my my El attack wait
what H that's scary does four
[Music]
attack ah ah
ah
what wait a second if I kill the Bait
Bucket it becomes a fish
what the
[\h__\h] I could cut one of the cards
though I could cut one of his uh
fish
[\h__\h] I'll I'll cut
one out with
you um
elk is terrible here
why
why wait we have we have enough bones
for an aasum but we'll
[Music]
see do I want to
play
[Music]
myop
yeah
[Music]
okay that's a good amount of
damage
okay I I I I think you didn't want it to
move because the elk would attack The
Bait Bucket or so and then it would turn
into a
shark I
won I won
prie do something
cool
yippe see this is how it goes if you're
not cheating with your gries need a
light yeah
thanks hope you learned your lesson
grizzled anger angler defeat the angler
my reward
long elk what what part of that is an
elk I have no words for this freak of
nature what it doesn't look like an
elk g pack
red the middle part why don't
what it looks looks like a rope or so
gek gek is
back gek so
popular you considered one of the angles
catches him as a meal but the rank odor
deterred you dinner would have to
wait and I would have would have like to
eat some fish for dinner I like fish a
frigid gust of wind bowed unwelcome into
your
lungs the beauty of the falling snow
failed to distract you from the chill in
your bone bones you had to send it to
the Snow
Line what is
this that's new is it you arrived at the
inky black mouth of a
cave cute peeking through a strange
Beast lurked Within that's just you it
spoke past one of my trials and I will
be yours in a raspy
voice free creates will be drawn from
your deck they will decide your success
or failure
eh But first you will choose a
trial okay the trial of wisdom the
threee drunk cards must have at least
three sigils among them to
pass
bro oh I can ah okay this isn't what I'm
choosing okay the trial fth the free
Drone cards must have at least six
Health Combined to pass T power for
attack to
pass what's the most likely to get out
of my deck then I
guess
threee effects whatever six health or
four
attack
yeah one can only hope let the trial of
power
begin one three okay we we go through
y
yippee the Beast revealed itself it was
a raven with a cool effect a Grizzly
with a cool effect and the man is with a
cool
effect
huh FL card into more power more p is
already Grizzly what do you
mean sheesh Elder grizzle czy
grizzly super bear like this
super super what was it was it a pig no
was it a
pig in 7 days to die after eating lots
of crazy
corn super saan all right sounds cool
kind of expensive though the inhabited
gri joined your
Menagerie and now we go if we have one
item still but we could still go there
or we go to the fire Mak something
[Music]
stronger or bot but they might eat my
card the crackling fire lit the starving
faces of a group of survivors we have
not food one said but perhaps one of
your creatures will join us enhance its
Health said
another imagine if they eat the bear
they'll have a lot of food for sure ah
should we put the G or the or really a
BOS
don't forget about the GE don't forget
about the GE don't
forget
Geck
KCK
[Music]
yay
Retreat geek's so popular they all want
the geek I can't blame
them but geek does not bring much
food all righty lucky drun
you somehow you always or very often in
my first hand are you somehow
influencing this what is this moose buug
he's got a moose in the
mole burrower when an empty space would
be struck a card bearing the sigil will
move to that space to receive the strike
instead oh
interesting very
versatile actually I know want to read
this Hefty at the end of the owner's
turn a card bearing this sigil will move
in the direction inscribed in the sigil
creatures in the way will be pushed in
ah okay I see I see I see everybody will
move
okay oh my God it's got seven
Health he a hefty
boy mole cannot attack by the
way I don't know
yep oh he agrees with that
one okay ding d d
ding
oh yeah
babe yeah ready reie can one shot
oh oh oh well got to get some bones
first got to get some bones
first might have to
uh squirel
sacrifice I mean not really
but sack the St feet SC
oh what
why
why at least we did some
damage okay now you move there bones
bone status is
too and another mole and he's bringing
an L so much
health
o and now should I put I got to put
another squirrel right I got to put it
where the Moose
is will I be
okay yeah
bit B
right how many bones now three frie ah
okay okay okay I'll draw a card I'll
draw a c here
[Music]
fry and squirrel I keep maybe I'll
keep yo let's go
ow almost died maybe I should have put a
squirrel there [\h__\h] y
it ah more bone cards
well Reggie will kill the elk too right
we're fine we're fine we're fine we're
fine should be
okay Rie op Rie
[Music]
M okay nice nice nice nice nice nice
That's
[Music]
good y oh get out of the way moles
ow no I was
winning I was winning what do you mean I
was
winning
n Raven elk
beehive The invol Beehive when is
attacked you will draw be I fumbled I
threw but is so okay
probably beehive be be be be we can be
so
busted I guess could be good sacrifices
right okay ah [\h__\h] oops we can either
get rid of a card and then fight or uh
get items and then isn't this also a
fight what's the difference between
these two
get rid of a card okay items mini boss
oh left is harder trim the deck all
right U what might we want to get rid
of I do have a lot of
cards um well you're a cockroach so
the tiny
antt one of the bone
cards it's it's I like the bones but
it's a bit too much cuz
yeah yeah I feel like it's a bit too
much but do I want to get rid of a cheap
one or an expensive one cuz I'm feeling
a possum might need to
go m
yeah sheap is generally good but at the
same time it wasn't
really it it didn't feel
needed Oh What a minor Boon of the bone
Lord there's a bone Lord you will start
each battle with one extra B what I get
some I thought I'm just getting rid of a
card I didn't know this had such a good
side to it
too oh is do I did I get a bone because
I sacrificed the bone card or would this
also have what happened with a blood
card free Bone hey
hey I didn't know the bone bone
Lord bones for the bone Lord also know
known as the
boner okay what do you got he's got
Raven eggs and an elk
F we shall eliminate these
quickly by placing a
mantis nicely and we oh that means we
already can place an a never mind sorry
aasum sorry I spoke badly about
you sorry cuz actually oh
what that makes up for my lost previous
round
right redeemed
I redeemed
myself
yay oh hello I have the most H [\h__\h]
pelts again I don't want your
pelts that looks like I can at least get
the expensive one but you giving me one
free one
right wait no let me
buy
[\h__\h]
oh oh
last time I don't understand last time I
I I got to pick the free one and
the I swear to God this was different
last
time the one below to leave what the
hell oh cuz last time he stopped me what
[Music]
mean maybe I should have gone for
items but okay um we're imbu
something maybe mantis but wait do we
have a yeah we have a new
mantis don't do the G this time why
not mtis for Reg
ooh ooh I like the way you're
[Music]
thinking
interesting he still keeps the the death
effect right the insta
death he's dual wielding now sick
salutations you don't have to greet me
like that I don't want to be GRE readed
by a
cockroach snowy
tree
card why is there two s free up here
again fren creature
every besides that nothing
new salutations it it is quite
um quite polite I
suppose all right Square
Wall go beehive go let's see how this
works wait should I have put it in
behind the tree
[Music]
maybe oh no it's fine we wanted to get
struck
right
okay wait I can place a stink
bug
nice stinky
time
be so the bees should I treat them as
squirrels or not
quite kind
of
versatile not quite they do attack okay
now they fly over they could fly over
the tree no wait this blocks the flying
thingies okay
well well my stink bug will kill the r
no it won't it will ah [\h__\h] it won't
kill R
[\h__\h] maybe let's see what I get a wolf
damn
it maybe black goat time I don't
know yeah I was hoping for the Mantis
too yeah cuz I could afford placing the
Mantis sacrifice Hive to kill the yeah
okay what Hive and a be
right whoa whoa whoa whoa he even killed
the cub in the back
nice how many bones only two
Raven ah this kind of sucks I feel like
I might want to drop from the deck and
then drink my goat
juice theum okay well I do have the
bones for
[Music]
neum I was hoping for the Mantis
so oh now let's
go will I survive I'll survive I'll
survive I'll be fine oh thanks for
getting rid of the
tree
now
Groll deck
deck Alon not bad but
I would have to sacrifice
something well wolf will kill
Sparrow a possum will chill with a
tree uh stinkbug will kill Raven so I'll
take the free Raven damage I guess I
must elk can kill the left
Ren sacrifice a possum
okay no
ah yeah it will transform but yeah it
can't kill it right away I was confused
by that
statement um
[Music]
H skink it is
you I am happy to see
[Music]
you I could sacrifice the stink
bug and then place the skink where the
stink bug
was not stink putting in
[Music]
work oh wow
now too
late it's a raven
now no no no no I regret my actions I'm
sorry what what what no please don't
don't don't touch me don't touch me no
no no no no no no no
no
no game over do I have to start from the
beginning again
no
no stay there no need to move I'm afraid
you are not dead yet hold still no
please revive me I'm Phoenix you don't
even know that where did I put the
camera you don't even have a picture of
me or take a picture of you
huh pathetic do you really think I would
leave film in there do you have any idea
what C the camera is capable of give me
that
you don't want yourself to become a card
you could be such a strong card behold
your death card what do you mean she
begin to Ink it what choose a card to
another lava card do I got one each time
choose a card to draw the cost from uh
good thing we have only ones this
time mhm
use the power and
health oh wolf
maybe fix your goddamn light in here
please choose a card from which the
sigils oh
[\h__\h]
oh how you like that H maybe you should
have let me continue playing now I have
this overow power card what are you
going to
do can I use the same name as
before one thing now remains I almost
capture your
massage smile cheese oh now you want me
to
cheese
yay so every time I fail in a run he
makes a card from me that I will get in
the next run is that how it
goes I had such high hopes for the last
one me too man why do I bother trying to
teach you I know I'm
sorry you you will learn as we go
thanks or you will die
yeah a gift from the angler hey yo but
what if I want to quit
now and uh like do I get to keep the
card and
the this angle thing
for next
time it's saved okay you see he was
defeated recently and wishes to redeem
himself it would be unfortunate if you
were to fall to the perspective before
he was given that chance this Hook is
powerful you may steal one of my cards
of it m that's cool for that reason you
will not find any others along the path
use it
wisely it seems the lowly stink bug has
made its way in
but it's delt so it
stands wait what these are your cars
that I'm allowed to steal these just
look like my own
Cards start what what's it always
Square looking a little weird looks like
a
bunny that's my stter deck uh
[Music]
oh thanks oh he was just showing it to
me
okay okay I think we will end it here
because I failed miserably um but we'll
play again sometime for sure this can be
my new slate
Aspire just because I need to read super
chats anyway and it's getting late
anyway yeah that was good though that
was interesting very interesting
actually definitely
got me
hooked yeah I'm learning so if I want to
last save 33 seconds ago okay so I can
leave
nice wasn't so spooky after all even I'm
glad fantastic game yeah very good how
long has this game been
around please please play again it was
very worth yeah please teach me again
guys I'm obviously a lost
cause yeah feel free to stay if you want
to hear the me yapping through the Super
Chat reading let's move to my office
yippee it's been a
while uh right I've moved things around
here damn
it didn't clean up
afterwards where's my
chat where are you
where are you
here and then we'll turn on some
[Music]
music you did way better than me in my
first well but I had your guys'
support you probably just played on your
own without voices in your head so you
got to give yourself some credit or
unedit me unedit your
oi let's see what do we got should I
play spooky music
[Music]
or oh found a treasure in my
Trove
oh oh God I don't think this is supposed
to be Halloweeny but somehow it fits I
think
ah this is too hyped though how can I
read Super
Chat oh the
[Music]
saxophone okay I think I will get rid of
the screen though and we'll move back to
the
middle oh [\h__\h] wo
oh my God don't mind my arm being kind
of cut
off I just go down
here
wow you the dance cover of Mirage did
you post it with a hashtag on Twitter or
on YouTube or where I will check it out
took the booster there was never a
booster seat on there it just kind of
sank
down no you didn't post it at all what
do you
mean or you just didn't use a hashtag
how am I supposed to find
it all right where do we have to
continue with my super chats where did
we stop last time anybody got the info
the Deets a thank you part
three of
Zelda nice thank God you're always
[Music]
here okay
um I'm by the way I'm not really tired I
slept so much but I just like to yawn
sometimes I
guess I've been like napping so much but
like legitimately yesterday my neck was
in so much pain today is kind of
better but yesterday I really thought
like oh my God if I feel like this
tomorrow I'll cancel my
stream because like the I don't know if
it's is really a pinch Nerf or so but
something felt really like [\h__\h] up and
it was it was like affecting my whole
neck and going up my head my the back of
my head was so bad it was really
annoying but I used like everything I
have at home to kind of mitigate
it I feel a little bit better it's going
away I
think it's going away but I just had a
massage like two days
ago but I think it's getting better
maybe one more day or so or two
but this is just a recent
worsening yeah I'm I'm used to being
constantly in pain so much that I just
like kind of ignore it but this is a
recent development of it being worse
than
usual so yeah not not ideal
[Music]
freaking eyes there
classic love them moving around
[Music]
spooky it's
okay a pillow or rotate mattress n
really I just I want I want to buy a new
mattress but I think if I buy a new
mattress I have to buy a whole new bed
cuz my my bed is like one of those beds
where the mattress is the bed you know
what was it called
again uh you know what I
mean so if I put a mattress on top of
that it'll be so
tall yeah right now I only have a th
mattress
topper so
yeah a box spring yeah yeah and and if I
got a new bed I would like it to also be
a a bed with sto storage cuz I have one
right now and it's like so helpful I
store a lot of stuff in
it ever found out about the hotel P Mees
kind of yeah but it's a bit confusing
I'm not sure like I found out that
um you know it's it's a
chain
and um there there uh hotels in Europe
use similar mattresses but kind of
different but they're all kind of like
similar and um I could get one from a
European supplier I guess but it might
not be 100% the same and I'm not sure
there's no place to test it out I think
but I could hope that all the mattresses
are good because they're all expensive
and
[Music]
stuff and and hopefully like they would
all be similar or I could try this stay
purposefully stay in one of the the
hotels from their chain in somewhere in
Europe and hope that they have those
matches that you
know supposedly they should have yeah
and then I could make my decision
through that but going out of my way to
stay in one of their hotels just to test
the mattress who does that
H and then steal it uh I don't know if I
can do that maybe if some chickens in a
trench coat help me
out wouldn't hurt to check more vacation
I wouldn't say it's a vacation but I
don't know if the uh I need to check if
they have hotels in Austria I'm not sure
otherwise I guess I'll go on a little
trip for a day or
two find something else fun to to
justify it yeah yeah I guess I could I
could maybe I could go to London
again and ask herb to meet up with
me London surely has like every [\h__\h]
hotel chain in the
world not too far
either sounds
good off collab I don't know if we could
an off collab but the surely in off
Twitter space why not Paris I don't know
there's nobody in Paris no no Hol member
in
Paris but um H like in France I mean as
a whole Ian I I do know someone in Paris
who um like showed me around
before uh and that was really fun but I
don't really have a good reason to go
[Music]
again you can all meet up for a you
vacation well I mean right
now not really reasonable because I am
going on
a
um how
long I'm going on a how many nights is
it free free
nights uh Spa trip with my sister and
then that's this uh November and then
certain cute girls are visiting me in
the beginning of
December but we will be streaming for
that of course that's not a break we we
will be
streaming so I know
ah I don't know I won't say it yet I
mean I think it's pretty obvious but I
won't say it
yet but I'm
excited I'm excited they're also
excited you organized it that fast oh I
didn't really do much I
just um figured out with them together
what date would be
best when I have time and when they have
time
she said it on stream back in the in the
days it was December who me
them I definitely have no idea H will
they meet your
cats
perhaps will you show them a Christmas
Market I don't
know if there will be
maybe we'll do all kinds of things
hopefully stop asking
questions Halloween collab of some of
the myth girls like watch a scary movie
I think it's kind of too late for that
now to plan something like that
now everybody's schedules are already
filled up and uh I think Ena is not
available is she I think
she's again not available for streaming
now
and uh yeah cie schedule is full and [\h__\h]
daa I don't know
she I I don't
know so I think it's too difficult to
set something like that up so last
minute
sorry sorry
sorry yeah but there's still a lot of
like Halloween fun Halloween streams
going on here and
there maybe Christmas maybe we can set
something up for Christmas I don't know
a myth Christmas collab but then again
you know I don't know man I
don't you know what I said before about
my
collabs all right let's read super
chats um let me bring out the
thumbnail part three is this the part
three yeah I love my thumbnails for that
somehow Zelda makes me always so
creative with my
thumbnails thanks to the assets though
cuz the assets give me some
ideas
yeah I don't know
[Music]
honestly I would love to hear this music
while playing incription
I kind of like
it it's kind of a
Vibe yeah eating
lemons
[Music]
yummy here we go what kind of break the
mood I don't know about that this is I
like this kind of mood too we can switch
up the mood take a 47
Ultimo MK thank you for two wa wait you
wao you sent a double
rainbow crazy
lad there has been so much going on for
me these past three months I passed my
exams finished my apprenticeship got a
new job IRL got a new job at kfp am
night and moved to New City ooh where
did you go lots of things have changed
but something always Remains the Same my
love for you
[Music]
oh proposal incoming but I'm also
painfully aware of the fact that I was
so busy back then that I was barely able
to watch your streams or be there for
many of the major events happening
during that time well it it seems like
that didn't necessarily like make you
lose your interest or so so I'm glad
because if you often if
you nice super cool for you
know resta
[Music]
so I'm glad you didn't lose interest
while taking a little bit of a step back
from
me and so I want to apologize for that
incent this rainbow to properly
celebrate all your achievements since
July including your upcoming 3D live as
well as upcoming was it upcoming oh it
was still upcoming at that point H as
well as myth's foury year anniversary
myth forever five and while I am added
let me also use this opportunity surely
also in the name of everyone kfp send
you all the love and big hugs in the
world in order to make these sad times a
bit more bearable thank you I'm really
bad at comforting words but I hope that
this can bring you a little bit of
Solace and happiness sorry that this
message is like all over the place it is
not kind of bad timing on my part for
return apologies but don't worry let me
use the remaining space to spread Amit
to love because you can't have a rainbow
without
Amit a thank you so much you don't need
to apologize
anyway yeah I'm glad that you got some
stuff done that really needed to be done
and I'm proud of you for prioritizing
that when you had to because maybe you
wouldn't have passed your exams and so
on if you would have um not been able to
focus on that so good selfcontrol and
all that so very good good discipline my
discipline is chickens I'm so proud my
new work is kind of rough H may maybe
it's just the beginning maybe just the
first few months and weeks maybe it will
get better over time
hopefully but it's nice to have you back
in any case and I I wish you the best of
luck thank you for the incredible big
huge rainbow M MW MW MW MW MW MW thank
you such a Chad and yeah I hope you're
living the best life in dorf I I hate
you for being able to get that awesome
tonu man
and nah it's not
fair
ah all the restaurant
I'm so
jelly and now you don't even have to
book a hotel when you go to doomi or
so it was okay T shut up what do you
even
know you have no
idea you don't match
box I'm timing you out you need to you
need to learn
that your words have
consequences timed you out usual room
for 10 minutes
bye-bye hey is Miku coming to dle I I I
heard about like I saw from friends
going to her concert in England in
London yeah like yesterday or the day
before
yesterday melon soda yeah melon soda
really is not uh like a normal drink to
be served at tonkatsu restaurants in
Japan but they do it there and this do
because of the gimmick you know because
it's like oh foreigners will love this
[\h__\h]
so as I told you guys before they used
to have in that tonata restaurant in D
they used to have uh the the craziest
dessert ever that normally you find only
like in in Koka
places usually in Japan in a very
particular Koka um
chain um you know the toast the honey
toast and I used to love eating that
there but both tonat and the honey toast
are still
filling it's a bit rough to eat that you
have to eat that with so many people
together cuz the serving is just so big
but they got rid of that dessert menu
the honey toast years ago and it's so
disappointing because now there's no
other place that serves honey toast here
but in the first place I would have
never expected any place to serve honey
toast in Japanese style anywhere in
Europe
can't you make it at home doesn't of
course you can make anything at home but
I mean effort and honey toast I think
you
know needs to be a nice big ass loaf of
bread I don't even I have never seen one
of those loaves of bread in here in the
bakeries has to be a particular loaf of
bread you know could bake it myself but
that's a lot more effort
too but you guys were supposed to have
good we have good bread but I mean I
guess one could try to make the honey
toast without the huge block of bread
you can just make it with a smaller
piece of bread and then it's also way
more edible alone I guess I guess sure
sure
sure you can Rec recreate it oh well but
I'm lazy French Toast French toast is
different but I I do want to make French
toast one of these
days Moving On Studio ra thanks for the
pinky T hey you know what Teno you're
wonderful I just wanted to say that
thank you you're also wonderful what a
coincidence we and Jinx each other on
our
wonderfulness thank you for the sweet
words aluda thank you for the red super
chat are you here in the chat W it's my
birthday and my four year anniversary to
being introduced to H life oh my god wow
huh Can you remind me how you found us
I'm I'm interested I feel like you told
me before
maybe was it just clip
lips just wanted to say thank you for
being such an amazing Kam ooshi and
inspiring me to be more active in
pursuing my goals in my own life love
you forever people like kfp I'll be
golden in a week yay you are golden now
ah gig video on YouTubers
oh and then did you like check me out
first or did you check out others first
and then somehow came to
me alud
doing Holo talk with my chickens
again not a hold seven
S I see call saw you clipped on redit
fell in
[Music]
love can't relate how how can you fall
in love with me at that time but thank
you I'm glad you
did thank you
[Music]
I the
goat thank you m mwah MW double red
super Chad what Chad glad you're golden
now hope you're happy with the
goldenness cuz a lot of people are
sending in
complaints
[Music]
unbelievable I'm very happy being golden
let's go oh that's what I like to
hear my fiber is no failure she's my
queen
oo yellow is my favorite color it's gold
though close enough I guess gold is just
a fancy way of saying something's yellow
huh F banana D black hamster D and the
quos artist for the pinky I just
finished the EO W yesterday one Temple I
beat without knowing one mechanic it
used hopefully you'll see what I didn't
you got this SP tell me what do you
mean now that I'm done cuz I'm not sure
what you
mean l Mark Le D luas thanks for the
pinky yesterday was my birthday Vienna's
house is me and H H vas house are really
beautiful but taking the train is like
in Germany first a truck drove in a
bridge and later a bomb Fred sbook train
sessions sure that was an
adventure that's that sounds just really
unlucky
honestly I don't I don't think it's
always like that that that's really kind
of a
rare Coincidence of things coming
together
H but I guess um I think Austrian trains
are not as late as German trains in
general but a lot of Austrian and German
trains are connected like they go
through Germany to Austria they go from
Austria to Germany so that affects it
too yeah but yeah probably still better
than doche
Bond do bun is a nightmare yeah I hear I
hear so I hear it a
lot the quest arst are you not here in
the chat to tell me more tell me more
maybe another time then
the red Prince of
echos 100
gnomes
[Music]
uh hot W was in your
area to
[Music]
take thank
you okay finished
these twas in your
area another Zelda stream is the next
one sorry I did forget to squeeze in a
Super Chat raing stream this week when I
was making the schedule I know I said
last week that I would would do that but
I forgot but honestly I don't know where
I would have put it
anyway
so we'll just you
[Music]
know we'll we we'll roll with it as we
go yeah
[Music]
yeah at least this stream for example is
kind of short so I can read super chats
and tomorrow I think will be a little
bit
longer Wednesday no Thursday yeah uh the
Halloween nights the stream might be
short but I don't know if I'll read
super chats we'll see we'll
see just because I'm in Fredy and uh but
I I I think we'll see maybe a little bit
a little bit of sub reading
no reading streams where people can
donate but you don't read them so you
can catch up I could I
could oh but the thing uh on W on on not
Wednesday Thursday the Halloween 3D
stream I will do the polar word thing
there so um you
know you guys uh can send super chats
for the P words there and then that
means that that stream will not be read
out loud in the
future
[Music]
yeah new old ones it's just a rerun so
same
menu Cruz D J 47 D surv thank you
[Music]
D thank you Kima let's go Nathan cotton
thanks for the pinky doesn't this look
cute she says like she isn't always cute
thank you you're so nice you always know
what to say why do you always know what
to say casim than oh big
u ah I see that was the night where
right after after Zelda we had the 3D
live now we D the quest AR D great J D
thank
you D skeptical Panda D Lucas Universe D
hat thanks for the pink
Oh no just found out I won't be able to
watch your concert live later looking
forward to watching the VOD as soon as I
can though I know it will be amazing did
you follow up on your
promise I hope you did I hope you
did did
you are you here I hope you watched it
because it was so worth
it very worth it thank you thank you
thank you if you did watch the vot thank
you thank you thank
you Lucas Universe Lucas
Universe Lucas Universe than J monkey
thanks
pinky our chimpin class ticket to the
one chimpin class ticket to the
anniversary life please thanks again for
being with us for so long K I hope you
and KY will have more wonderful years to
come
together yay thank you also like it's
you just you keep on thanking me guys
but I'm thanking you
we go hand in hand thank you guys for
staying for so long I know there's like
my chat is like I don't know feels like
80% old kfp like people who have been
around for longer than 2 years at
least thank you for being so
loyal and not getting sick of me
H I have only 3 years old what you
mean that's old for a
chicken space of the Fall d py
d why I'm going to get sick of Wawa what
no hey pumpkin milk you missed a word
there I'm sure you wanted to say you you
won't just for membership though oh yeah
that doesn't mean you haven't been here
longer m
I have the Wawa
sickness is it
ligma is it
serious py D
ZF s Simon Sim
FR wait maybe German I don't know Sim
spe thanks for the red chat not pinky
red chat o w W wah sounds very goo gaga
to me thank
you endless thanks for Super Chat as
well this game kind of feels like it was
made for you isn't it looking forward to
the 3D Live later thanks for the stream
oh you think so did you say that because
of the cats or
something I did really enjoy the game I
wish it was
longer
n but I guess it uh didn't overstay its
welcome at least and it was a good time
I enjoyed myself thank you so much for
watching the series I hope you liked me
enjoying
it endless even though it was probably
hard for you to watch but the fry life
maybe not so much thank you thank you
for getting up for it
m you're cool thank you for the RIT chat
since I can't do it later I will do it
now congratulations on your fourth
anniversary for live thank you for being
a lovely a and making us happy for so
long hope you will get more chances to
on stage next year love you wa
more I don't I I wouldn't want it to be
more than this
year but you just mean in general like
yeah at least not like no 3D yeah that
would be
sad yeah we can take it a little bit
more easy next year maybe I don't
[Music]
know can we
though cuz if you think about it yeah I
thought this year was going to be still
even more stressful because I was going
to do the second thing this year too you
know um but now it's next year so but
but a lot of other things will be gone
right like the the the world tour will
be ending and who knows maybe something
else will fill up that time maybe
whole life summer will be back again cuz
it wasn't this year maybe they'll bring
it back next year
H I honestly have no idea at this
point yeah there's always
[Music]
something but even if hold life summer
comes back right I I'm sure I won't be
involved in the same capacity as last
time cuz last time I was in the in the
main theme main theme song and you know
that kind of I guess made me a little a
little bit more busy than
others yeah we'll see we'll see I
wouldn't mind Holo summer coming back I
really liked it maybe we'll even get a
new swimsuit if it comes back with a
year break in between they could make a
new swimsuit
right I wouldn't mind a new
swimsuit I like this one but I you know
I already saw it a lot
[Music]
yeah a lot of people were saying Mirage
sounds like a great song for EUR Vision
can't
really
see that that much but I guess I I guess
I don't know you guys get that
impression
but it wouldn't be a candidate anyway
because of it's release time and because
I didn't sign
[Music]
up I would have go crazy for it I guess
maybe it's it's a great song
you well well well thank you
you're for D Sky d r d Anthony web d g d
g g d Jackson FB D J swar
kingro
blood g a jacob7 re Valentine
D that was all like almost all blue ones
so that went
fast ooh Mir Tak official music video
has some super
chats we shall read those as
well wow look at that beautiful
woman she
slays the gays
what all right let's see Maxwell the
first dun CC D bro dun check for7 D
Speen d oh the pinky such a great day to
be a chicken
right
yay yay yay yay I'm so glad you guys
were there to Hype up the premiere nin
blaz d m a dush for the pinky absolutely
amazing fre life potential to think we
finally got a duet with Iris and fr and
Bloons yeah all that hard work
definitely paid off more than ever yeah
I think I really was able to um
wait aren't there oh that's afterwards I
see the
Mirage sorry the Mirage for live super
chats are after The Mirage music video
super chats but yeah I was going to say
I think I answered a lot of
prayers and long
time desired things with that live with
that set
list now we don't we need thanks for the
red super chat Banger after Banger after
Banger set list mag wow Mir is also dope
those background Dan has got me acting
up nice Haron boss might be your best
friend in life yet I'd say I'd say so
too yeah I I put a lot of thought into
well all of my lives but
um yeah and that one was really cursed
it turns out the next one is also cursed
just by you know the way things are
going so far
[Music]
hopefully will go smoothly from here on
out why is everything so cursed
man it's rough thanks na though thank
you py thank you so much AK sf2 thank
you so much what the hell it at you
super chat I hope it was tasty at least
CeCe G
thank you d hak d go d m d mango
d d Strider
he blank PR pinky happy fourth
anniversary what a wonderful life thank
you I'm glad you liked it I'm very proud
of it too in the end so I'm glad you
think so too sness DX Dan ziply Dan Cruz
Dan R for than pinky congrats on the
successful show B the work put into this
paid off all the pieces fell into place
perfectly what a way to close out the
for fear spoiling us with that Hall of
Fame guest this and an original song
couldn't be proud of Kiana thank
you
yay it was very very exciting for sure
together with the song release
yeah very much
appreciated thank you for watching over
me work my ass
off yeah and shake my ass
off need to drink water Fred screw thank
you for the red super chat Bravo braim
Banger after Banger and now a new song
Holy Kiwa you surpassed yourself you're
more than fire you serve so much [\h__\h] oh
my God I have no words this Bravo
yo you made me say that word for the
first time in a long
time
cut I don't know if that's good or bad
probably bad
but thank you thank you thank you you're
so
excited M mwah Mah fried screw thank
you I hope you like the new
song Black pengu and D jro those s 7 nun
chuny CH thanks for the red chat T you
have outdone yourself again have
I I definitely think the back dancers
added a lot of um spice no but
versatility to the Coro and made
everything more interesting so yeah I'm
glad I did it even though it was like a
little bit um restricting in terms of
time how much time we had for the MV cuz
we had to wait for the motion and stuff
like that but at least the motion turned
out so nice like didn't have to really
do any fixing of the motion apparently
compared to when I do it with my
accents yeah thank you junky chunk alar
D and that is all of the music video
super chats but now we enter the big
one actually there's uh two big ones in
a row the recap also had a lot of super
chats don't know if I can make it for
all of the 3D life super
chats but I'll try to get as far as my
throat allows
it uh and my brain allows me
to um
[Music]
Read Super chats cuz sometimes it's a
bit much when the there's similar
sentiments
throughout many super
chats all right here we go cuz I don't
want to you know I don't want to like
read your super
chats and not really feel it you
know if there's similar messages it gets
kind of repetitive but I don't want that
to make the Super Chat reading feel like
unappreciative and tiring so I prefer to
take a break and then come back to it
another
time but here we go we'll
start we'll start we'll
start BR nachos nachos
so let's start unknown
take thanks for the
pinky it's very late now and I'm com
right now so let
me yeah
[Music]
in
Spa you'll find someone for
it kind of running out of time now
though I don't know I don't know maybe
maybe this year is just not the
year well I'll go off season I don't
know my
my don't
[Music]
know very much
appreciate pain pickle D hello red danan
Prince of Denmark thanks for the pinky
congratulations on the live and the
surprise at the end you worked hard for
today and I hope you can get some rest
afterward and hopefully relax a little
bit hard for today well it was
pre-recorded so well I did stream Zelda
a couple hours before that but
um that's a good thing about it being
pre-recorded I don't really um I only
have to press start and be nervous about
your reception but uh really
there's yeah not too much to worry about
thankfully
but the work it took to get to that was
a
lot can't forget about
that
yeah a
lot Indigo five Alpha thanks for the red
super chat let's go k I always feel
immensely proud and happy looking back
at everything you've accomplished your
hard work is inspiring and your IM men's
kindness is beautiful I hope you
continue to dream bigger and wish you
the best life has to offer wow so nice
thank you so
much your Super Chat is
inspiring thank
you I will try my best moving forward to
not uh be
too much of a negative
person I'll try my best thank you so
much Happ your
pinky crow in the B
night spad The Wiz of two of
[Music]
o2
Al V
faction mp53
G seny thanks for the py go go yeah this
was the beginning this was the beginning
of the life let's go thank you pixel
affection D thank you for the pinky
you're so talented funny awesome and
your music is amazing I'm glad I found
you boss happy anniversary and another a
first for me but hope for many more
celebrations with you ah a first for you
a first uh anniversary stream or so for
you you already have the chicken so I
guess like your first year went by
around that time thank you then for
staying around and for joining kfp I
hope you're going to stay for much much
longer thank you so much for the nice
words dark ninja dun skip Dun don't
worry I won't skip your Super Chat mp53
GX thanks to the pinky happy fourth
anniversary K thank you four years four
damn
years
hallelujah hallelujah can I get a
hallelujah
hallelujah hallelujah
hallelujah dark ninja dun professional
gentleman D Ryan c d Granite 4 dun
[Music]
El L
than space wonderful thanks pinky happy
four four year anniversary K
congratulations on such a long grind and
thank you so much for all you did so far
you have done so much and I'm so
impressed and all struck by you there is
no one I hold high in higher regard than
you love so much W thank
you wow you speak of me as I as if I am
God thank you
wow so
so
flattering thank you thank you almost
saying too many good things about me
almost is it not true Kam oi for reason
oh true good argument okay okay I guess
you should speak of me as a god am God
become as
God your name from content thanks for
the red super chat wordless
wordless NY
kissing my cards for
you chees the g d p Kong decoy John R
Ronin my
CD Galaxy dun let's draw dun Des dun
Dominic K thanks for the pinky I'm
moving and cheering while moving on ow
bro bro for moment for split second I
was like what do you mean you're moving
on moving on from
me I'm moving on and I'm never ever
turning back around around or run again
yeah I'll go
higher care people go higher no one
could take us down if they tried unless
it's me I could take you guys down do
not do not take this
slightly t for captivating performances
likea W fourth anniversary like rocks
this was 24 minutes
in so you were you didn't even know all
the amazingness that was still coming
you're ear sending that Super Chat thank
you thank you thank you thank you I'm
glad you were enjoying it late at
night
tan Omega Corp Shepherd D and cop up
thanks for the pinky ah yeah yeah yeah
finally happened it's this beautiful CU
that
imagine right I'm glad you guys liked it
we kept the choreo pretty simple I asked
the choreographer to just kind of get
inspired by the music video feel free to
add like Ena laying on the ground and me
just doing turns and stupid [\h__\h] like
that yeah and the CH is really just
simple yeah normally I like to do
complicated chos but I also felt like I
had to balance
um you know with how many careers I had
to learn it's good to have some simpler
ones in between because it's really a
lot of work
um
yeah and you you guys got to imagine if
I how many list how many songs did I
have on my set list like 11 or
and honestly learning more Coro more
than one Coro per day is kind of rough
because it it won't stay in my brain and
even if it's like one week one Coro per
day that's only seven coros and it
doesn't take into account that I still
need to practice the coros that I
learned each day if I just learn it on
one day I and then ignore it and never
touch it again I will forget it so one
week like you know I'm what I'm trying
to say is
[Music]
like I I have to spend quite some time
before recording it in Japan to really
learn all the songs like one week ahead
of the recording is not even enough
unless I just go ham and
really 100% focus on Dancing every
[\h__\h] day the whole day but I don't
even have the stamina for
that yeah and then even like squeezing
in streams
still balancing that is hard
yeah and then the muscle sores the pain
from dancing every
day it's it's a lot yeah I did have like
some days where I learned like two two
coros in one day and
then
my concentration
was not the best anymore by the time of
the
second Oro but
yeah behind the scenes it's it's it's
difficult to learn so many coros so some
some are definitely nice when they're a
little bit more simple but even the
simple ones can look a little bit more
special than they a little bit more
intricate than they actually are
depending on how you present
[Music]
them
yeah and then learning aoro Al alone for
just like a solo performance versus
learning it with other
people that's also a lot more difficult
because then you have
formation and you got to like make sure
that things are in syn and everything
cuz everybody like kind of dances
differently sinking things up is
difficult you know it's a whole
thing a nice coolor for ready for you to
stick your head in between sets I didn't
stick my head into anything this time
but I
wasn't uh overheating that much this
time my problem was more like my sore
body and my stamina
and and my my feet I had those
blisters later
on but it went quite well
Mirage
Coral it's so weird it's somewhere in
between it like some parts of it make me
feel like oh this is so difficult and
some parts are more like oh this is
actually not that difficult because the
back dancers are doing most of the heavy
lifting but and don't make a joke about
my butt now with the heavy lifting
thing but yeah um
there was a lot of
like on the recording day actually like
we had to take a lot of
takes immersion breaking it wasn't a
first try first take because well I
wanted it to be perfect also because of
the music
video and I wanted to put out the
choreography video and
everything normally like if I make a
mistake or so I can maybe like change
the camera CA angle and just you
know hide
it but in this case I wanted it to you
know look good on
every angle because I was going to put
out the choreography video so yeah it
had to be
perfect and we had to make last minute
adj adjustments I don't know if I told
you that but there were yeah I think I
did tell you that in the Mirage cap
stream where I made the dancers dance in
front of me kind of diagonally for one
specific move because I was just too
nervous
to get it right even though like when
when the music wasn't playing and I was
like doing it on the sides practicing
then I got the timing everything
completely right but when the music was
playing and we were recording that's
when I get nervous and then I messed it
up and then we were losing more and more
time cuz you know limited recording time
each
day uh
so director son was like okay you'll get
one more take cuz we're running out of
time we still have so much more to do
and I'm like oh [\h__\h] what more take [\h__\h]
I can't risk it like I need this take to
be good so my solution was okay dancers
for this one particular move can you
dance like can we change the formation a
little bit last minute but even doing
that is risky changing formation last
minute
well thank God all dancers you know
they're Pros so they can adjust so it's
really just on me not messing it
up director sounds so sassin no no no no
no my director is really
nice been working with my director since
the 3D debut
so I'm really happy with our work
together yeah yeah yeah good on them for
being able to adapt yeah thank God me
too though I also ad
Ed yeah yeah yeah yeah anyway and d h
Jack for the pinky Tor of the floor what
is your wisdom for real though this
concert has been amazing and the last
four years I've truly been a treasure
thank you a thank
you yeah we just ended up on the floor
there for a little while had to force
Ena to get
up but sorry I thought that looked cute
though
as just chilling on the floor it was
[Music]
cute and that way we got a floor review
which
actually you know thanks to the the
dance floor that we put
out it was actually a legit floor
review a floor review that I could
honestly say I like this floor more than
the usual floor I would really do a
floor review I I I I kind of did a floor
review in my stream before where I
talked about the us bringing out the
floor and the floor being actually
helpful for dancing so floor review was
valid floor review was
important and very
relevant H DOL D and Garrick thank you
for the pinky so proud for the Stacked
lineup I can't wait for everyone to see
how amazing you are congrats for another
year thank
you I I hope that I got a lot of people
who maybe don't watch so often to
see what I can do yeah and maybe make
them think well of
me thank you so much I worked hard for
it just never KY thank you for the pinky
thank you for performing I Tak forever
you're welcome it was about time it was
a the I don't know you know that was
kind of like one of like the last
addition to my set list I think
and I told you guys before it wasn't
originally planned but it all worked out
nicely and it feels like it had a a good
spot there it was meant to
be dreadn thano tanuk D Ringo D dreadn
thank you again oh you sent it twice
oopsie Louis World
[Music]
f um oh am I already revealing merch at
this time cuz voice packs
what at 38
minutes
[Music]
H for the red CH watching my hotel in BK
hey love you and thank you for always
working hard for kfp thank you for
taking your time to
watch I really am glad that you were
there thank you cist I hope you had an
amazing time an amazing experience
watching thank
you neo Persona
D thank you D Dean GF d
yeah Kina let's go he I am
a thanks for the re
chat happy fourth anniversary
[Music]
D freeze STP D BDK D GD thank you for
the red super chat congrats on the 3D
anniversary life wait wait mate let me
change the bgm
oops let me change it cuz like it's been
a long time listening to that uh
congrats on the fry anniversary life
even if it was late but you outdone
yourself it's been amazing hope for more
exciting years copia looking forward to
see your performance in Jakarta katur
yay thank
you
mate you're
going to
Jakarta did you already tell me that
maybe you
did oh my
god let's
go traveling for the
Wawa that's exciting I hope you will get
along with the ID
Bros do you know do you have some
friends do you have some Bros that you
[Music]
know yeah have fun hope you can do some
sseeing yeah I need some good food
[Music]
M let's go sounds exciting man to travel
around the world for these concerts and
meet overseas fans who all like the same
things but are like just live living
completely different lives that's so
interesting
I wish you all the best thank
you random cusion thank you for the red
chat what a wonderful Anniversary
Concert I really like the unique and
evocative
Coro
evocative thank you for being in the
world together again through song and
dance well what does evocative mean it's
not provocative right what's evocative
chck it keeps on sending me updates for
the next wait it might be finished no
not finished okay maybe on
Halloween nice it's we might do um we
might do the fauna we might put out the
fauna short first because we're still
kind of waiting on Callie's new
model brings out that Witch is already
present ahuh
what what
what what what what is that evocative
evocative brings strong images memories
or feelings to
my interesting zap I didn't hear a
zap chicken salad I actually had chicken
salad yesterday it was really
good chicken salad chicken salad chicken
salad not not chicken soup
now you imagined that
zap you have your own
zapper what did I do not you not you
don't
worry yeah I guess you must be hearing
your name a lot these
days well no obviously you know you're
asking a question knowing fully well
that I didn't upload it
yet forgive me it it hurts me too to
open the Tik Tok app each time so it
takes a lot of like courage it's hard to
open
it
same oh anyway thank you so much random
gion now I learned a new words too I
feel so educated
yay mwah mwah mwah thank you
wrench French Cool D epic zeros D and
fancy thank you for the pinky finally
bloing hey nobody expected
that yeah I was purposefully also like
keeping myself from singing it in Kadoka
streams because I thought if I sing it I
should sing it in a 3D life
sometime yeah to make it more
epic since you guys are like several
people requested it over the past years
so makes it impactful right
yeah log 82
D chicken for the pinky pek peek peek
peek W this conent is so good love you
my wa Kam oi doing what again mixes to
those bangers love you you
were German W goes hard thank you w
can't be forever V you said my name like
10 times in that Super
Chat brain rot chicken
you do you have brain rot W brain
[Music]
rot I want to say you do a next time you
should record
it I
demand why bring up
Ski h oh because brain wck jce Invader
Danish and Rogue ra or wreck or r d
thank you for the red chat just wow wow
happy fourth anniversary thank you so
much thank very nice of you hey hey hey
than glad you enjoyed it even though it
didn't even end yet quacky D soon oh
wait I forgot kiss Rog r r r
r thank
you H quack Idol business regulation
director thanks for Pinky hello
congratul on a spe spectacular fry life
Great Performances and guests overall
consider this life ibr approved yay
don't think I'll let you off for the
violations though what you will answer
for those as well as for the death of
tanaki
Shakara don't worry tanaki Shakara lives
wait when did she die I think she lives
I'm pretty sure she's
alive thank you though I'm glad you
approve of the life at least night spare
hand danan Jazz cash dun tripod dun
Angie Angi
dun I don't kill her she's a phoenix
just like me I mean she's ostrich but
she's also Phoenix you know she don't
question
it space d OK mik D Electric heart
thanks for the red super chat I don't
even remember
that absolutely Banger performances line
up in Coro tento happy four years and
hopefully for another four years
seriously amazing job wa eight years in
total TTS would be so
crazy but wait isn't like soda Senai at
this point close to 8 years because when
I joined wasn't she in four years and
now four years have passed how long is
yeah ah okay they're about to hit
seven wait that's gen zero they don't
all they're not all uh here the same
amount of time right sort of s by
son s is at seven whoa
whoa that's kind of crazy sheesh
wow I mean like literally cuz in the
vtuber
world like she's one of the first
so it's
like nobody has done it much longer so
it feels
like
whatever how
long she's in here it will always feel
like so long because there's just no
example of someone being here like being
a for like 15 20 years or
so
[Music]
damn like so now you're asking for
another four years of me and I think 8
years is kind of
insane I don't know if I can do that
that sounds so long that
sounds I don't know if that sounds
doable but back in the day I didn't
think like 4 years were
doable you know it's just
like hard to
imagine where I might be in four years
and yeah I mean if I'm still like happy
doing what I'm
doing if it still makes sense at the
time I will stay longer you
know but no one can
know at this
point and in any case like I don't think
I can
go like as hardcore as this for 8 years
like no break cuz cuz like I never had
really like a long
downtime where I didn't
stream a good
[Music]
amount in order to achieve such a
lengthy
score I would definitely have
to at some point maybe take like a more
chill couple of months or you know but
that will then lead to a
longer time all together so got to
think several steps ahead think long
term
yeah a gap year yeah
yeah no for now I still feel like I I
have to still go hard I think I stream
quite a few hours this year this
month October I think I have
like my streaming hours are quite a bit
there and and uh people don't even count
the members streams which I do like
weekly
so yeah I went over 100 this month
how much with members we will never know
unless you do the
math I streaming longer this
month yeah so at at this point in time I
still feel this like
pressure to have to continue
delivering you know and I'm still fine
like I can still continue doing it but
if I think about long if I really want
to do this like much much much much much
longer have to take it easy at some
point or I mean just
like maybe maybe the way I'm doing it so
far is kind of you know good like taking
vacations here and there although a lot
of my vacation since I still stream and
I still
work but
yeah got to spread out breaks in order
to be able to do this
longer
yeah
so a real
vacation what's that real vacation
usually always have to either do an
extra amount of work before and after a
vacation to catch up or work during the
vacation it's kind of
inevitable but yeah I'm okay I'm
fine I don't want to take a proper
vacation to some beach Paradise again
though
ASAP next year January February
sometime uninterrupted moldes do
uninterrupted what do you mean
uninterrupted Oh you mean like no work
okay I thought you meant like a long a
long time but that would get so
[Music]
expensive no I'm not going to the mes of
crony
but maybe somewhere else
[Music]
sometime still wanted to go on that like
ID trip at some point
but
um is there any good season for that was
every season good
for
Bali I wonder any ID Bros watching
could probably just look up and
Google year
round come to Canada on vacation we
don't have beaches but we have forests
and snow and mountains and bears and
lots of
stuff forests snow mountains we have all
those things in Austria except for the
Bears I mean no we do have Bears too I
guess but not as Maybe the moose and the
Bears and all that maybe not as often as
you guys see them which might be a good
thing now I did like
Canada but it's so far and uh normally I
like to use my vacation for like warm
beach
places but if I get the opportunity to
go at some point maybe through an event
or so that would be really
nice I'd love that because
I know Canada is so beautiful and the
people are so
nice and it's it's
chill glamping with crony the Canadian
world I would love that that sounds
[Music]
amazing poutine I'm saying I need to go
to Canada because they have poutine what
do I care care about
poutine chill is accurate yeah I did
mean the
weather where was I uh oh yeah electri C
you got me a little bit on a tangent but
thank youah Ro rules D needle back
lessons D thanks for the pinky worthless
but thank you feeling Pine D seven and a
switch
blade KF AR cross J Alejandro might be
able to finish these super chats
actually shrimp 569 face pinky happy
anniversary and good fry life good you
mean very good but thank
you I'll finish your message for you
very good thank you so nice of
[Music]
you glad you enjoyed
it say Lou World Dan H thanks for the
pinky dun happy anniversary and good fry
life why do you also say good h wait
that was basically the same super chat
but just added a squiggly El
squiggle weird you wrote it the exact
same way it's kind of sus I'll finish
your super chat too for you very good
than thank you resine thanks for the red
super
chat H El
squigle uh happy belated anniversary
tentel you killed it with the moves
again the the first half was so funny
and cute especially with all the MC's
the second half was such a blast from
the p with all the Epic anime songs wahi
also W boxing yeah thank you I do have
like when I think of themes for lives in
the future I one day I do want to do
like a anime songs focused theme um this
one kind of had a lot of anime songs now
but I just chose those songs because I
thought oh they seem very epic and I
wanted an epic feel I wanted epic songs
that fit the the stage as
[Music]
well so it just kind of happened to be a
lot of anime
songs also because well in general it's
hard to get any songs besides like
Japanese
songs um because of copyright and all
that yeah so so usually I guess it will
always kind of go in that
direction unless I do like my own songs
and so on but yeah it was really epic
right it worked out nicely s days I
[\h__\h] love that
[Music]
song but I would probably try to choose
songs that haven't been sung a million
times in our Kadoka
streams yeah thank you rine mAh
s d demon beef d z d Comet 045 D rainbow
thanks for red Super Chat all the songs
dances and guests were amazing thank
you
agree thank you do you have correctly
assessed my life thank
you glad you enjoyed it so true true
words have never been spoken before hi
fructose corn syrup D freak video gamer
D thank you Dragon morph D thank you and
do no l d thank you m d JJ thank you for
the red the chat happy anniversary K
four years filled with so many laughes
and memories thank you for your hard
work
always I guess you sent that while
K what's going on you tearing it down
you just water
thank you I'm glad we could make many
memories together I hope you will stay
and support me
forever it's a
promise
to Mr v
[Music]
d okay
wait um western
[Music]
music I I I don't know how many details
you guys know but from what I know
currently that doesn't
really speak to
me as long as I can't do like archived
videos and stuff yeah and yeah expensive
yeah can be
expensive if I can't do archiv like
western songs and archived kokas and
stuff and uploaded upload song covers on
YouTube and stuff yeah cuz yeah okay
seems you guys know nothing on YouTube
allowed exactly so that's just like put
making a cover and putting it on
streaming
services doesn't quite speak to me
especially if I still have to pay for
the rights for the
song not really interested right now I
just continue making my own songs and
sing arft K
streams
[Music]
yeah it's all right Al Luda thank you
for the red super chat happy anniversary
wava so many amazing performances going
to be listening to this over and over
again really thank you B views
go thanks to aluda thank you so much I'm
glad you enjoyed it t d should thank you
right
watermelon waiter thanks for the
thinking happy fourth anniversary made
the whole world hear your Divine voice
and bring them Joy I would hope so I
hope more people can hear it so keep on
spreading the word for the lava thank
you watermelon
waiter I'd like some watermelon now
that'd be so
refreshing o 176 tun thank you for the
recipe chat happy 4 anniversary to my
kamhi the show was just amazing both
your solo performances as well as the
songs of the guests were fantastic and
Mirage is such a banger one of the best
concerts I have ever seen oh that is
some High
Praise thank
you than thank you so much M for the
kind words I hope you were streaming
Mirage a
lot as a thank you for a good concert
thank you very
much y Kam oi will continue to do her
best
you Quantum Cola Quant Cola thank you D
for the pinky wow the range and quality
of the cor of Coro this life has been
seriously Innovative and impressive
you're an amazing performer thank you
and happy anniversary thank you oh thank
you for you know paying so much
attention to the Coro as that is
probably the hardest part about these
lives yeah than is
yay unknown thanks for the red super
chat my o is truly the absolute best in
the world I love you thank you I love
you
too thank you so
much I'm glad you think
so thank you a you're so
nice you're so
sweet oh she W We R she
W she
W
she hello no
lights you guys did you guys know you
have such a fancy name I don't know it
sounds so sophisticated it sounds like
you're the Elites you it sounds like you
have money it sounds like you live
uptown you're the Uptown
Girls I said it wrong again is it no
Elites like the
elite like I just said Elites about
you probably
then no
Elites excuse me I did say that you s
you guys the name makes you sound like
Elite the Elite of the
[Music]
elite so
cool it makes you seem so
fancy yeah yeah I said Nova lights but I
then said that makes you seem so
sophisticated and like the
elite very true thank you for
acknowledging our
superiority well but nothing beats my
campy chickens there's nothing more
sophisticated than a chicken
at least my golden chickens are pretty
sophisticated
looking the novel lights are our enemies
oh my God they
exist yeah bit you got to do something
about them destroy
them cut them up with your
scissors we can help you we can be hired
for support and Aid kfp has much
experience with weapons and
fighting for many years
now pretty
good could recommend 10 out of
10 we'll fight together for she
we we
stand positively
towards sh Willi
yeah we have a tank including a
driver shondor calls for Aid you shall
have
it okay if this can be a RCI no no no no
no no no no hello hello hello
misunderstanding we are here to fight
not to be
eaten the bacon are lit the bacon are so
lit chicken
bacon no
nah that wouldn't
work yeah well guys I'm currently
reading super chats but uh you're well
very welcome to stay and hang
around probably finished somewhat soon
with these from my Frey
live
yeah I'm kind of far behind as you can
tell cuz that's a month ago
almost
t d thanks for the red super chat it was
a great life potential your efforts in
this summer didn't turn into Mirage it
becomes a miracle M I'm really
appreciate it to show us the wonderful
performances I'm so happy that you're my
best Kami oi
Idol
oh uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
I need to study Korean again I've been
telling myself Tak you've been paying
for premium dual lingo four months now
and not opening the app any
day of these months it is time to
[\h__\h] learn Korean again I will try my
best
because
perhaps it will become
relevant soon
again anyway thank you so much M money
come on
down hopefully next time I'll get a bit
more smooth with my Korean reading again
but at least I can still read it kind
of you still have your audible subscrip
I do the bus pass no I don't audible I
seemingly do but I can't I don't know
I'm not sure if I'm I know how to use it
though I don't know if I'm logged in I
don't know which account it is I don't
know I don't
[Music]
know I'm more upset about me not using
dualingo but still paying for it that's
ridiculous
only one way to solve it or two ways
cancel or use it h as like zie D I am a
t beep D salous beats thanks for the
pinky K you have such a perfect sense
for what will make the most Peak
Performance ever thank you for noticing
that putting this together despite the
challenges you ran into you always
impressed me he not remix Mirage
everything Peak how can I even pick a
fape m are those your top threee
thank you thank you
D yeah definitely ran into a lot of
challenges for this life had to change
many songs had to change many members
had to change a lot of things so it was
cursed but it came together nicely but I
hope that next time we'll be
smoother fingers crossed thank you so
much PF D Patrick FB D Jacob 47 D for
the pinky absolutely incred life of the
appearance of blooming con something
I've dreamt about you singing for years
in an absolutely fantastic General set
list and guest groups with great
performances Mirage sounds great
congrats thank you I'm glad you think so
I hope you've been streaming it ever
since with all you got honestly with how
close we are to 1 million it seems like
yes you
have thank you so much for the support
and I'm glad I could make you happy with
blo and GRS I'm I was really um
delighted by everybody's
reactions everybody was like hey yo hey
yo what what no way
[Music]
who I felt so smug when I saw the
reactions yeah and that made the life uh
trilingual English Japanese and German
was
present
amazing Ash dun rocket 3497 dun sword
Works dun flaming pants D FAA thanks for
the red super chat Amazing Life wa I'm
on fire a new song I love it oh God
careful careful I need to fire proove
you guys before I do such performances I
guess it's kind of dangerous huh maybe
you shouldn't have jumped into the fryer
right before to cover yourself in
oil thank you very much
sta please listen to
Mir many
times Jim Tracy thanks for the recip
chat guys I see the end oh my God oh my
God J Tracy says absolutely amazing
concert Kiana all your hard work totally
paid off stacked guest list fun MC's
incredible performan thank you thank you
thank you I'm also glad when people
acknowledge the fun MC's cuz you know I
try to make them fun I think of the
topics and lead the MC into something
interesting I would hope so incredible
performances of magia with way Muna a
German song topped off y off your
awesome new original Mirage best a she
ever
I love you thank
you so
[Music]
nice chicken aggression right now
sorry Sor
kuren Kur thank you very much oh in
German even
yeah for
[Music]
the myself again dangun Alvaro dangun
thank you CR thanks for the
pinky I can't believe I'm almost done
with these super JS oh my God this life
was amazing I can't believe I can't
decide which is my favorite performance
takot kiaris beat eater magia sticks
Helix ketchup lemon CR Mirage everything
was so C youo your hard work definitely
paid off because I can't make up my mind
have you since made up your
mind what was my
favorite I think in terms of
overall Vibe and
impact might
be
Mia
maybe maybe but
I don't
[Music]
know the most fun
and rewarding
feeling was maybe beat
eater I worked hard on that Coro and it
was a lot of fun with
[Music]
EA and I really love the song
I've had that song in my mind for a long
time ever since waya did that
cover yeah waya introduces me to good
songs I didn't know how based the that
game
was that Vocaloid
[Music]
game yeah she's got good taste I love
love her I love Raina did you guys know
that I love Raina I miss her what the
hell oh wait right we're having a collab
uh this week though all is good we're
good we're
okay wons me too me too W I miss her
she's so dorky I miss
[Music]
her I miss
her she makes me
[Music]
feel
good I love
her than soon nipp come down for the
pink Super Chat a great Freddy live
thanks for the great time thank you
always for your time with us thank you
thank you so much for waking up from my
Fredy live and always showing up and on
this special occasion for supporting me
and cheering for me come on
[Music]
a space wonderful thanks for the pinky
this was amazing W you gave us a
phenomenal concert I love it so much so
many good performances I really love all
your solo ones H Kima Blum and Mirage so
good thir group ones was magia sticks
Helix and M I see I see you like the
Epic ones especially thank you so much
I'm glad you enjoyed good choices good
choices Andre go thanks for the red
super chat that was incredible what a
great show Sasa my favorite whole life
Idol congratulations VA by your
favorite I like to hear that thank you
so
[Music]
much glad you enjoyed it hopefully we'll
get to do more stuff like this in the
future and Nene diesel dang I'm
surprised I managed to finish reading
these I guess it was like just a a lot
of bigger
ones but still that was a a good amount
of super chats that I got done hello
hello
hello praise
me praise
me I read a lot yeah even though there's
a lot of big ones that have big
text thank you thank you oh no oh no
we're past midnight I
know I'm turning I'm turning into
pumpkin Wawa which actually isn't so
unfitting for Halloween
[Music]
week don't forget to stretch oh
man okay maybe but first I will make
food I'm
hungry does the gold thing just always
stay up there do you guys still have it
up there I still have it up there
doesn't seem like I can get rid of it
can
I no it just stays up there
huh when you click on it do you see the
same thing that I like put a photo uh
about
photo
[Music]
yeah yeah a yeah like it bugged out
there it got an extra one so it's 31 out
of 30 this whole time
[Music]
Yi anyway good
game good super reading good talk good
talk I have to do one extra okay I mean
I'll I'll do 31 minutes of stretching
then maybe I'll try 31 minutes that's
kind of long normally it's like 15
minutes of stretching routines or so but
I'll I'll try to find a long one
then what why are you
angry did I do something to make you
angry simply even
your even your profile picture is angry
now what did I
do no
simply why are you so angry I'm sorry
[Music]
it's the alt account
oh how did you get bonked why is your
alt I guess your alt account is angry
because it got
bonked okay so it's not because of me
good good good good
good deep blur oh oh so deep couldn't be
any deeper than that
[Music]
okay guess I'll die uh guess I'll
go
n let's go sleep no but first food and
then stretch and then
sleep
yeah
die it's okay I'm Phoenix I'm
Phoenix I've been so sleepy always like
I fall asleep so fast I can't even
really watch anything but also I've been
like kind of lacking a show a proper
show to watch these
days maybe you guys can recommend me one
like something
like okay I still need to actually still
need to finish the that Disney plus uh
show what was it again
um that one
show but yeah shun maybe I just finish
that today or I'll
try ah psych Arcane arane huh breaking
bed yeah could watch I was hoping more
for something like Phantom see like like
Witcher or Game of Thrones but I feel
like I already watched all the good
shows like Vikings
[Music]
Etc don't don't recommend me The
Sopranos yeah Arcane is kind of fantasy
huh but it's animated right like 3D
animated there more thinking of
something like you know The Witcher you
know I'm I'm even like so desperate that
I'm thinking of watching that um
spin-off show that you guys said was so
[\h__\h] maybe I'll enjoy it who
[Music]
knows well yeah I've been watching a lot
of us related things just for
entertainment these
days uh don't have much else to watch
but it also is kind of
frustrating uh it's too much now in the
beginning it was funny but now it's like
G watch Young Sheldon what I guess
there's probably like newest Seasons
that I haven't seen yet because they're
not
as um updated on like uh I think Amazon
is where it
was it ended already this year or like I
always forget like what was the last
season I watched and then I can't figure
it out and I just rewatch older
Seasons don't trust the be no never
heard of that
Merlin
interesting oh a couple people
mentioning Merlin what do you mean it's
CRA Camp campy campy as in
like gay
campy
campy cuz I only remember hearing that
word in in like uh when I went to that
comedy club in London I heard about it
for the first time camp like Camp wasn't
that what it
[Laughter]
was maybe that was just Camp not
campy we know time I already watch me of
time Westworld Shadow and bone that
sounds new to me are those on like
Netflix or so although like even if you
say yes it depends on the country
sometimes things that are on Netflix in
one country aren't in the other W HBO
anything that runs on HBO is like not
really available to
me it's annoying
Firefly no Buffy
NOA is that a new
show or an old
one I feel like I heard of it old oh
from the '90s
[Music]
[Laughter]
advantes of Merlin okay where is that is
it on that
that sounds kind of nice I like the the
sound of
that that's not Ultra well yeah I do
watch a lot of like shows on the 90s
like isn't friends and and and Seinfeld
and so on from the 90s I do watch
those think Merlin's on Netflix oh cool
Merlin
Netflix is it good does it have only one
season or what
H something here says Merlin got removed
from Netflix bro Merlin leaving Netflix
in December 2022
bro
H but I'll try to find it maybe it's on
Amazon or
so oh that that also looks kind of old
is this old no it's not that old right
why does it look so old
[Music]
Castlevania is it are you talking about
an
anime Buffy
Angel those kind of like Vampire shows
and so on I don't know I don't
[Music]
really somehow it gives me like this
feeling that it might be like Twilight
and and I'm not sure if I want to get
into this tackiness of Vampire
shows but if you guys say Buffy is
good oh [\h__\h] making myself unpopular
again okay I'm gonna go now thank you I
got some some suggestions please feel
free to tweet them at me too because
I'll probably forget what you guys
said far far far above okay okay and
okay then in German we say in psych
psych psych okay okay I'll look into it
if you write it to me on Twitter too
enjoy yourself thank
you good
night tomorrow early kind of early start
because I'm hoping to
play longish
we'll
see yeah goodbye probably will not make
this uh the stream reservation until I
wake up
so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah see you
thanks for watching incription we shall
try it again sometime in the future
[Music]