[Laughter]
hey i said it's a ultra low latency
[Music]
though
foreign
i can't join i can't join um
and uh she's trying to set up the
internet and electricity another
important thing
this house is full of nothing but empty
boxes and trash
see i'm a little tired uh a little
emotionally exhausted but it's cool
we're gonna play a game
[Laughter]
[Music]
awesome
oh my gosh everyone's voice is just bye
let's party
oh come on come on i wanted to just once
god damn it ah [\h__\h] my life
okay
maybe it was a trick
keep cucking maybe it's part of my plan
i'm so tired
we'll probably play this game again
another time
um
hopefully
waiting for a second okay so i just have
to i'm at the mercy of someone else
all right hold on eh
oh thanks senpai
i know i could be tricking everyone i
could be tricking everyone into thinking
that i'm not an impulse
i mean that's kind of an ingenious thing
right
uh-oh nana
is
[Laughter]
where was it
she was in the same room as the body
on the way out oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
is
foreign
please pasta
[Laughter]
you can't
okay here we go
[Music]
oh man all right
okay
okey dokes oh we need to okay there's
some urgent things happening here
reactor meltdown in 15 seconds oh my
gosh come on guys we gotta go
oh man wait
hold on keep getting stuck okay
the homies got it i think okay
we're good um
all right then let's go this way
sick let me senpai
let me send pie
oh today's good four one
five four yes no
okay boom both on stuff i saw that i
fixed and also didn't kill me
okay okay
all right leave it to the master oh wait
hold on
wait hold on there we go
the best
you guys see me completing tasks
i ain't suss
i don't know i don't know how i feel
about watson watching a little sauce too
that's something to hide
oh to the rescue
i got this okay eight oh eight nine five
ah
okay okay
i guess well couldn't have couldn't be
both on senpai either
because both on senpai could have killed
me many times
hmm who could it be
see what other stuff we got hold on
can i use this check the cameras guys
what is happening there oh
to the rescue
hang on
oh kusatori
okay maybe kusa thought he's okay
i'm putting the pieces together i'm
noticing who's been helping
that's important because then it's
process of elimination
all right let's take a look at the map
uh electrical
we've almost done it
i think i'm getting the hang of this
game
come on hurry hurry hurry
dick darn it
come on come on
oh five huh is it okay all right
we're good we're good do your tasks
yeah bye oh my god
um
m
you doing amen i was on the left side
and then i found you guys i was mostly
on the left side in the
engine rooms buy the engine rooms yeah