[Music]
do
ah there i am
like like um
reporting
stance or reporting the
the battle
oh kiara's going coming in first oh my
god i'm behind her right behind her now
oh my god what she's gonna do
she has a red shell oh no but then in
the very very very back you know has a
blue shell so that's even worse oh my
god phono doesn't even want to be number
one right now
you'd be pretty good at it too kiara
oh no no i can't only maybe in german in
english i can't think of words so fast
in in german maybe can we have a preview
it's a little bit in german
maybe maybe while we're driving then i i
have some things to talk about then
yeah i'll try okay
okay so amma's audio was fine i think
next uh fauna
kovana
[Music]
oh hi
i'm from hollow council
and i'm
happy to be here today i haven't played
mario kart in a long time i think we're
all a little rusty
yeah
it's been a long time
i'm always resting a little bit
oh wait wait so can you say one more
word i didn't even check the audio just
one more word
okay
okay i'll raise you a little bit
uh shh that should do the trick
uh next
no no i'm on my stream on my stream oh
no there you go hi
wait were you muted the whole time no
this is just um just to my end um not on
discord
it's cause it's cause i'm moving my my
audio set up so a wonky i need to set
everything back to normal
hi
i'm taking that as a promise i'm writing
that down you heard it here enough's
gonna be safe driving yeah that's right
yeah yeah hopefully
wow hopefully you'll be slow
wow
and last but not least kiwawa is here
hello this is my voice i'm always [\h__\h]
at mario kart hopefully
the
advantage of
you know all the roads being new will be
a disadvantage to all of us
no i've never i've never played the uh
new uh
yeah did anyone try to put testo did
someone test jean no
i don't even know what they are to be
honest
good
okay
uh also sorry last time we wanted to
stream this
had a little incident but here we are
thank you thank you girls for
rescheduling
you know phoenix sometimes catches on
fire it's just everyday stuff yeah
better watch out for the hair you know
i'm giving you the world right now you
guys are having so much distance from me
because you're scared that i'll catch on
fire again
i don't like the heat
sorry
it reminds me of the time and the off
during the off club here
was that
the ride and then it says no smoking i
was like yeah yeah i told my people that
i'll tell them that
you
no smoking and i'm like
yeah what you know i don't smoke what do
you mean
and she just repeats herself no smoking
i'm like okay it's so so what
do you mean
i couldn't i couldn't get myself to
finish you know finish the looking hat
[Laughter]
you lick your finger and you put it on
them and you go it's
all right how do we how do we i think
wait it's it's fine
yeah oh yeah yeah ready to go
yeah and so everyone who wants to join
us so that so just so that you know like
after an hour
inaudible
do we want computers
yes
hard computers yes
yes you
do
okay
150 is then with people 150 yeah okay
how do i turn on tilt controls
do you have the wheel
did they have that for the switch
a wheel i don't think so oh oh
okay so is this the new stuff
oh is there only four new tracks or no
yeah like oh 12
no yeah 12.
12 times wait are they oh
oh guess these are not okay okay
oh wait wait was it paris oh paris for
example already in the previous one
it's like snow land or um
[Music]
have enough time to try them all i'm
sure
yeah
sound like a oh is it just like sweets
themed
it's like a diner oh yeah oh so cute
[Music]
oh the track map itself looks simple um
like
[Music]
this
is
yes computers
oh it's a socket computer i keep getting
hit with something
[Music]
that's my hand amendment
i
huh
[Music]
the worst time to get i don't know
it's a bit misleading there isn't it
oh there we
[Music]
it's okay go i beat the cpu
oh no you already finished oh my gosh
i can't start
you know it's in first place
oh i haven't played in a long time i
have because she's going to be hard too
look at julina winning
the muscle memory
[Music]
yeah it's muscle memory
practiced too much
and like a long time ago it's just in
your head it's a long time too
me and fana really want the penguin
yeah
[Music]
with my chicken mask you know it's so
funny
[Music]
so dramatic then maybe i if you know the
new meme video
you know what i'm talking about
[Music]
when i was a child i watched that me too
ow
the penguins hurt
ice ice places are my territory
i feel right at home
you shot that at me didn't you no
that's why why buddy
what have you girls been doing today so
far
we've been moving furniture
yeah you're not busy
how's it going inya did you break some
fingers yet or get some splinters yet
i've been like bumping my head
everywhere oh no
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
so what were the others doing
sleeping probably
yeah sleeping just woke up
a little bit ago
[Music]
i did a lot of stuff today too oh what's
it do
uh
all kinds of things a secret top secret
oh
that just makes me want to know even
more
[Music]
oh sure
that's such a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh i did not practice mario kart all day
no no no no time for that
yeah god damn it okay but better than
before better than nine for whatever
okay
i wanna go visit
bales
let's go to australia
i want new york
have you guys ever been to australia no
[Music]
i guess it depends where you are it's a
long flight it's far from like
everywhere
yeah
so isolated
[Music]
it feels like you should be close to
japan but it's probably yeah yeah yeah
it's like the same time zone or like
summer time so it's only like yeah
an hour or so but
i know that a lot of japanese students
when they go on
a like a school
trip a special one
a lot of these um schools choose
[Music]
australia because it's relatively close
and uh
yeah it's really popular
for school trips oh
oh it's pretty in here oh it's like in
uh rise up that's how you rise up
oh a fancy house
oh no
recycle your bananas guys mistakes
i'm assuming you guys fell on my banana
i felt like a banana was it your banana
perhaps
did your character make the happy noise
like someone fell on their banana is
that worth it
[Applause]
[Music]
what power would you have
um
teleport
so it's easy to get to places to
australia yeah
yeah teleportation would be great
funny
but i don't think i really want to talk
to my cats
[Music]
what if your cat says something weird
for you though and it changes your
relationship forever
no they'll just tell me they love me
no tell them i love them
on your food
what if you like
bump into birds
like
elijah in minecraft yeah you wouldn't
want to bump into me huh
yeah kiara you're on fire you know fire
in the sky you don't wanna you know what
you're always normally causing traffic
air traffic
you know problems
we'll take videos of you and post it as
a ufo i feel like is that a bird is that
a plant oh it is a bird
[Laughter]
i fly with my cape like uh
like a superhero yeah um
oh i don't know what i should have
like i
i like the idea of flying which i can
totally already do but hmm
since i'm already got that i gotta
choose something else what's a cool
skill to have um
mind reading i think yeah
just thinking that i was just making it
a friendship ever again that's the thing
like like
what great park was great responsibility
and being able to read minds
will isolate you
[Music]
yeah i don't think i want but it's the
difference between can you control or
can you not control it though it's like
controlling is also bad though
it's like
you you get tempted but
you're always hearing how many like this
like so many people talk i think like
you'll go crazy
um
that's what usually happens
yeah like edward cullen from twilight
so you can see for me
oh i never watched you guys watch try on
it i never watched it
yeah i read the books
i don't think i watched all the movies
because they were you girls
because my sister and sister loves them
were you like really fanatic about it no
it's just a book that i like look at the
books
[Music]
so this is what it looks like oh you
heard my cat
oh yeah chunky wonky is walking in
so cute
[Music]
[Applause]
you're gonna pay for that
i'm sorry i'm not
not trying to start anything here
really really
i feel like you are no no no challenging
challenging
nice drift oh
[Applause]
oh
[Laughter]
i swear
i was going to be first that was the
third place
i got i got bumped so hard the game
crashed you know
i think i think everyone here
we have to redo this match
so someone you want to make the room
maybe it was fun are you here
yeah i think uh sometimes
oh yeah i think
i think folks
died
and maybe i'mma make the room because
she doesn't stream anyway so she doesn't
have to worry about the what's being
shown
how do i do it
wait okay i'll just create yeah yeah
yeah
we need to revive her
fauna
oh okay you guys can join me
noise
[Music]
did you guys you guys watched charmed do
you know the show oh yeah i feel like
i've heard about it it was my favorite
show when i was younger it was a it's a
show about free witches and
and one of them had the power of healing
one of them had the power of like moving
things one of them had the power of i
think teleportation yeah
yeah i wanted to be like them
i wanted to be like though i want to be
a witch
but parts of the show were kind of
cringy because there was like this one
one of the girls had like this hot
affair throughout the whole series with
this hot demon and all that oh spicy
nice very spicy indeed yeah
you should watch it
they all have names starting with p i
feel like i've seen like these books or
something like
always in the library there's like five
billion of them yeah they have books too
yeah
[Laughter]
so they're just recently and all their
names start with p
yeah yeah phoebe
h prue p p p p p yeah
there used to be only three but then at
some point one got like replaced in the
show
so that's why there's four names
[Music]
yeah
yeah hot hot witches um
is that what you're watching right now
here
no but i bought like the box set the
whole box
you have the dvd collection
yeah because they there is no way of
watching it's anywhere online like no no
service shows it knows every streams yet
so i was forced to buy dvds in this day
and age
i don't even have like
a place
dvds and blu-rays but i like rarely
watch them these days
it's like i like the fact that i have it
and i own it i can watch it any time i
want what did i do
yeah yeah
the only blueberry that i have is from
uh
i think the second or the third holofes
because they sent it to me oh yeah
we all have a team
i have a song
i don't know where anything is anymore
because everything is in boxes
and
ah
i know how it is it's gonna take you a
while huh to get all of that it's okay
because i got i got my family they'll
make sure that i don't
i don't
laze off and leave it
yeah last time i moved it took me like
six months or so until i finally
had
most of my boxes empty but then there
were still like two or three boxes
who which were still like boxes after a
year
yeah
which shows you how much you actually
need what's in there so honestly throw
it away i don't need
much like i literally just have like a
temporary mattress
behind me that's what i've been sleeping
but other than that i've been i've been
looking pretty fun and honestly like as
long as you know you can cook for
yourself and there's a roof and
how dead is phone actually she says we
can go on she doesn't know when it's
coming back yeah i feel like maybe her
internet just died died i don't know but
for how long should we just do a race
right now like one running race let's do
another race to see maybe maybe
maybe she'll come back maybe
we'll summon her with our driving skills
i guess yeah it's very strong as usual
yeah
it's it's down to myth members only now
okay
all right let's go with you okay
wait wait what is this uh 150 cc i think
ah
you can't see position okay uh yeah then
150. why are there teams i see teams
no teams
i didn't put themes on i disabled it
oh
there you go
i thought
you had one job amit
can we still change it i wonder i didn't
think so
okay this should be fine
it's just the friendly race
i wanna go in new york
these two existed before no they mixed
in
they mixed
the into the cups did they mix old rices
and new maces
races okay so i see waluigi pinball with
calamari dessert wasn't done there
before no
i've never seen them before
oh really yeah
i turned it off no no no you're on the
other team here and i think this is
still like kind of like a normal
race yeah or do we steal flags
you'll see the flags behind everyone's
cars
but we don't steal them right not still
captain flag or something
it's like it looks like it adds up the
points of each team
i love by luigi pinball
i think i played that number four on
gamecube
maybe warranties
oh was that you
i was stuck i was just trying not to hit
the wall
it wasn't the end
yeah but today in the day i'll bring it
to gamecube too because then i play the
home game
the pinball so cool ping-ponging
literally out run the ball or like
oh no
chaotic oh my god oh no
[Music]
oh come on do you guys remember
the pinball game from windows
oh yeah yeah really pinball used
windows versions nowadays because there
were some troubles with the permissions
of the developer i think
yes
or something like a real world problem
i watched this whole like 20 30 40
minute documentation about why
the windows pinball game is not in
windows anymore
oh so sad did you guys ever see that
bowling
oh yeah i think it was like a
it was on an early laptops it's like
this really shitty 3d elf bowling game
oh like elf elf
yeah like like little santa elves
oh
[Music]
maybe if i saw a picture
ah
all the blue team are at the front what
where are you elvi
first place no no second place now
the npcs are doing the hard lifting for
ame i mean
i mean
what do you mean
[Applause]
i'm a paintball now
have you guys seen all this new outfit
today
i didn't see it because i just woke up
before the stream oh god you're missing
out on like a legendary i know the
silhouette looks so cool
[Music]
she is like a
holy [\h__\h] like i can't even describe
like oh she's dripping she's dripping so
high
[Laughter]
i'll be first original
oh yeah
ollie looks like a pimp or something
yeah yeah yeah
she realizes like a lollipop and then
she's with her mouth shopping
someone's cool
yeah
i didn't expect that like by the drill
hair
you know because of a certain i guess
yeah that's a certain character
i thought it was gonna be like
fully yeah yeah yeah i expected
something like that too
but no
no no yeah very unexpected
also those fishnets oh yeah
it's so cool
so good man
i can't wait to see the other whole live
ideas second gen
new outfits
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that's i think reynolds
ah rainy cat
i think that was very silly right
i am hi
i am
[Applause]
i don't know when it's happening is it
tomorrow somebody in the chat says it's
tomorrow tomorrow
i knew that was halloween
[Music]
mamma mia
it's not my fault like yeah where does
cats take place is it in new york
probably yeah is it i think
the rules are so hard
okay oh my gosh new york new york new
york yeah i think it is in new york
[Music]
well we were in girls territory
the girls haven't watched a garfield
movie no
[Laughter]
[Music]
all cat related movies are legendary
10 of the 10 word for watch worth two
watches
[Music]
someone stole my eyes oh no okay it's
fine it's fine it's fine don't panic
okay
freaking [\h__\h]
whoa
[Music]
[Laughter]
is mario circuit really not oh there's
because um the the the ones from the
first dlc are already played but we can
play them too
there's two deals
yeah that was from before
i haven't even played the first one
i haven't played the first one either
oh there's two waves
and then
i mean so far
no and then we're gonna have more and
more and more i'm wondering when like
when if we ever do like a
whole live english and id
mario kart or even like you know with
japan japanese members again you know
mario kart tournament
how
we
have to
like limit
the the tracks that we would be using
because i i don't think i want to
practice how many are there now
especially if we do it at the end of the
year then there will be
all the dlcs out all of the waves
they come out by then yeah they say by
the end of the year that's the promise
from nintendo and you know nintendo
keeps their promises right
so
maybe dlc only tournament
oh that would be fun
yeah because then we don't i mean we've
all seen the
already existing tracks a million times
i think dlc only sounds fun
yeah that makes sense
yeah
by the way this track was on the
i think for the first time on the phone
on the phone on the mario kart
i got the wrong turn
oh no no no i played that before it was
actually pretty fun
yeah okay
gotcha
oh no i thought it got at me but it
wasn't it wasn't enough [\h__\h]
i was holding a shell
here we go
[Music]
okay that's fine it's fine it's team
team good
[Music]
carrying
stupid stupid isabel undermining my
coolness
all right and i guess i'm gonna play
this mario circuit man
i wanna see how is it different is this
it looks like this is the thumb that it
looks like well i've already played
before
i mean there's like
which one mario circuit but like
different i'm afraid that's right
oh yeah i guess so wait what are you
guys thinking
mario oh mario's circuit free from like
one of the
one of the dlc ones
i can't find it
that's the third
[Music]
which one is gonna which one which one
is it gonna be oh god no way
i feel like fauna is not coming back huh
okay we can break
maybe maybe a baton ton pass to her
that means when inna leaves after the
one hour then it's the one on one with
me in heaven
we're gonna play with viewers right
yeah but still it's just you and me then
i thought we were on the team
what you're not on my team
no uh isabel uh
isabelle what might be a fitting name
for you i feel like a man what
would be a cute name for you isabel
[Applause]
sounds
maybe a little bit too sophisticated for
you
now anything would be lovely on you
she's just he's a very don't go
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i'm laughing
oh it's cause you're the first of the
blues probably maybe
it's like you sucks
it's a villain
[Music]
[Laughter]
come get me
[Music]
yes
bro don't fro
i don't hear your care i don't hear you
over my weight
okay phoenixes are colorblind
how fun is typing fun
could it be oh wow
oh wow we win
whoa
that's great
yeah yeah yeah
oh fona says she's not coming back sorry
chad
sorry you have to deal with myth only
i hope that's okay
i hope we're good enough for you chad
she's still with us in spirit
[Music]
when we at least got to play like
a couple couple races yeah definitely
yeah yeah mm-hmm let's play mom and stay
mom before you know okay
teams don't matter i think we can just
leave that setting yeah uh
no
okay i can turn it off i turn it off
okay okay okay now you can put us all in
one team that's that's
oh so we don't hurt each other too
no teams
not teams
[Music]
right so i guess that did feel like a
different
mario circuit i guess so
i like that one
like column
different version of that
i mean not only i keep saying on
earrings squid rings
okay now you just reminded me of what
that even means oh
no
that was wrong okay
oh is that
character supposed to eh i'm confused
is that character or calamari when
[Music]
what what you got the booze why are you
faster
because of the cards or something like
that
it's a technical question
but
honestly i just threw my my cart and
stuff together without really knowing
what's i mean there is this one cart
that's like you know the best car that
everybody uses
in the tournament
yeah but i still don't have that i got
all the other [\h__\h]
but i'm not getting that one for some
reason
[Applause]
i hit you with the boomerang you hit me
[Music]
[Applause]
that was a close one
there's a train
[Music]
never played on this map i think
eat them eat them eat them eat them
come on
[Music]
i was trying to go straight but i guess
i'm european
thanks ahmed for laughing undead
[Applause]
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] she's she's
yeah cheating cheating
what
no comment
can't hear you over this first place
trophy
that was fun but very confusing
that's like my life
outfit if we ever do like a whole live
myth whole life hold a little myth full
of english carnival
i think inna would look cool in the
ninja outfit
because i'll be i'll be ninja
hana in every tentacle
oh cartwheel and all my enemies are dead
i didn't get the boost
i got it
maybe i'm the better ninja
i know your dojo better than you know
yours
oh i like the music oh
oh wow
it's so cool though this place is so
cool yeah it looks nice oh
this is like a completely new one
oh since we can't go into japan normally
i guess this is all we'll get
so
oops that's okay oh oh there's a bottom
part oh i didn't know that
i kind of okay to fall down
what the [\h__\h] the music is popping
the shams you hear me
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah
my comeback is coming
back
i hear i hear the shell where is it
going
left no shell
a
[Music]
[Applause]
no driving on the tatami mats please
shy guys
okay [\h__\h] you then
[Music]
let me jump on the trees come on
where is the finish down it's like on
the roof yeah it's like it's like the
edge of the
it's weird
oh that
that was [\h__\h]
you know how the [\h__\h] did you get one
again
how does she do it
[Laughter]
looks yummy
anything's fine feeling cool
and that was a popular one
[Music]
really good lemonade today it was like a
coconut pineapple lemonade it was so
good that does sound yummy it's
expensive though
that's those premium lemonades
those fancy bottles
i had an ice cream puffy today with
strawberries
oh i love you
this time i was not
terrorized by a bee actually was a wasp
last time
i like how you were like oh it's a bee
but then someone's like uh i don't think
that's something
everybody oh my god like ninety percent
of the replies to that tweet were um
i think that's a wasp
don't you know what the bee looks like
and what it was looks
like well i don't apparently
feel like stupid
okay now i know now i know
like me too much
[Laughter]
uh small ammo did a good job at crx oh
yeah
yeah those dance moves are legit
she's so cute man i saw a photo of her
being beheaded though
oh
um
what happened there
wow
i think uh
oh yeah
i think she was just taking a break you
know oh so that's how
that's how she takes a break yeah she's
like a lego man where you could take the
yeah yeah
damn i didn't know that does that mean
that she was having a headache
and so on works like that too
oh this is a different version
so oh probably not what the [\h__\h] this
guy's just doing donuts in the middle of
the road
did you see the cafe food though yeah oh
i didn't see the food itself but i saw
the menu
yeah well the track family was really
good
i think it's funny you became like an
actual fast food manager yeah yeah
[Music]
finally man i've been waiting for that
for so long
oh why did it change now
and at the same time like in
korea there's this this adiplus
collaboration too right and right now
they're also selling my curry my
chihuahua curry with fr uh with kadage
chicken on top so there's a lot of
caffeine food right now in this world
and it makes me really happy
[Music]
wow
wow really really i really use a donut
honestly i should have gotten some
donuts
why donut why do not because the car was
doing a donut
yeah a car when a car does a circle like
it's called
ah
what you call that a donut what yeah
cause if you look from the from the top
tire marks they're kind of like
yeah
leaves behind and then usually like if
somebody's doing that you'd say you'd
use it in a sentence like somebody's
doing doughnuts in the parking lot yeah
if you don't get it i'm not worried
about it
it sounds way too cute to describe
something so bad
a better word forget it
and whatever whatever you want
whatever you want
not random because you could pick a old
one
oh
[Music]
oh yeah
ahmed
oh
really liked your bag in hollow bags
reviews
oh yes
so funny because it stood out so much
and everybody said oh that was really
like i mean like it had personality
[Music]
but i think it was a compliment
yeah you know the whole nuts but but the
question was uh what movie did you watch
with the freddie
the goggles oh it's for um
it was like uh around christmas time and
i went to that the the people that pick
up their legs really high
what
belay
[Music]
what do you call that the rockets
oh
yeah they headed through these yeah
yeah it's real people but they had like
a little 3d it was really dumb it was
really lame
it was like it was like the intro for
santa claus and santa was in 3d and then
he appeared for santa claus
[Music]
that's
nice
and inna's back was so clean and
obvious oh yeah i didn't even have to
blur it like it was so obviously ina i
tried to you know make people think oh
maybe it's eop maybe it's i don't know
marine or whoever draws
didn't have it with her when she was
with us she had her
her ipad for drawing yeah because i
traveled like her last one
[Music]
oh my god
oh that wasn't even you ah
i want to pull it
[Music]
[Applause]
come on give me something good
[Music]
[\h__\h] help
[Laughter]
[Music]
you did well
in my heart i'm first
weren't you like in fifth place until
like right before the end what the hell
i had triple mushrooms and i uh i zoomed
in
oh we're at the one hour mark yeah i
gotta go home tomorrow
thank you guys for playing
thank you thank you
good luck playing with the viewers don't
bully them too much
thanks for watching chat go check out uh
kia who's streaming
amazing i'm the only one now okay
i will gladly adopt everybody come here
yeah take care i'll see you guys next
week bye-bye
bye
good luck
won't get splinters
oh wait i can still be in here while i
end the stream
wait let me let me
i can't i'm gonna send you to kiara's
chat now
see you guys
next time bye