[Music]
up perfect
you don't even know
this
[Music]
my you sh I don't even know what to do
with this
could play a my
[Music]
Mir fall
me
[Music]
see your heart
k
k meow meow meow meow meow oh my God is
she wearing her default outfit I can't
believe it oh my God hello yeah I'm
wearing my default outfit so that you
can see my Expressions a little bit
today classic waa yeah it's rare it's
rare these days let me make myself a
little bit
bigger how are you guys
hello
hello how are you two hats
yes don't get too up about it it's 2.0
wow 3.0 coming soon just
saying
[Music]
we doing good coming home right now huh
you're the coming home
Queen come home
queen homecoming that's homecoming queen
not coming
home same thing today was a holiday was
it where what what why where why
when I just finished work good good then
I shall give you more work later just
kidding but I'm charging my Moab right
now thinking today will only be a short
stream anyway because after the stream
uh Veterans Day oh is that
so um I
am a little bit of a veteran myself you
know a veteran in the v tubing
industry so happy Veteran Day to me
yes I'm sorry no I mean no disrespect to
the veterans I'm
[Music]
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I
surfed I do serve sometimes I serve
chicken when I serve ass
so I'm quite the
server myself do I say also I mean I did
also serve in the
restaurant industry before as well I
served dinners and
breakfasts okay okay I'll stop I'll
stop it's true but I'll stop I'm I'm I
am to be
silenced so uh hello hello this will be
a short stream I am finally getting into
this game that I don't understand yet uh
we're going to play together
um thank you for the super chat um and
we're going to play it together and then
you already see a timer yes yes 1 hour
37 minutes
until an announcement that I have been
looking forward to and I already teased
uh you guys a little bit um it's not
like I'm announcing a 3D life or
something but it it's something else is
uh for me I I'm like pretty excited for
it you know
so we're going to work towards that and
hope you guys like the thumbnail yeah
it's good thumbnail right I'm going
to it's it's perfect I'm going to be in
that exact situation I'm going to put
you guys on the table with shib ropes
around you a 4D life oh if it's not a 3D
life it's got to be a 4D
life H
interesting one
day please no
ropes I will show you the
ropes so yeah okay let me unmute the
[Music]
game well you guys will have to help me
um so I'm not sure if I should put the
code in the community board for members
only or if I should put them in the chat
community board I know you guys have to
like kind of refresh it
and but I have another idea actually
that might be even better
bear with
me bear with me one
second how
about um I'm going to I'm going to put
up a member's only stream waiting
room
okay okay and then I'm just going to
post it there in the chat in the members
only chat genius
has there ever been a Genius Like
Me a Genius and announcement going to be
expensive um
maybe
maybe so okay the members uh chck it's
open I'm just reusing an old waiting
room that I ended up never using now if
you if the members click on that they
should be able to
see something
do you see
it I've revived the waa waiting room
yeah let's go it works now I have two
chats but that chat only for only
for uh Distributing the code okay sounds
good okay honestly I see everybody
playing this card game but uh maybe
maybe we'll try out the Liars dice game
as well liar deck and I'm going to be a
foxy kitty
cat yeah orange cat behavior now let's
do this uh please go easy on me and if
you are able to join um please only join
once don't try again in the next match
obviously let's give other people a
chance and uh mute the stream cuz you
can hear me in game apparently I I hope
so uh don't look at the stream CU
otherwise you will see my cards
okay okay oh wait which one is the which
oh that that's oops oh I oh oh
okay copy copy copy is that
copied the copy button isn't working
there's a copy button here click to ah
did it work I now I have it okay get in
here got to be fast
kfp ah let me post um members chat to
get code oh sh oops members chat to get
code oh
oh oh okay we got a full I thought they
were switching but it's just switching
their looks okay ooh hot spicy
bunny I was tempted to go for that one
but I think
orange uh cat fits me
better okay let's go so guys uh please
don't use I don't know if I can mute you
or so but in any case just don't speak
in the game okay we're going to do it
voiceless that's a fox yeah I know I'm a
fox what did I say or
cat I can mute uhhuh well okay so don't
stream snipe don't don't look at my
cards okay promise
me no looky okay stream Mirage true very
true can I get your okay
uh in the in the game chat that you're
committing to not looking at the uh
stream open the menu in game to mute all
okay and I have to press V I heard this
is my first time I don't know what I'm
doing yes okay okay H
waiting do I go to
waiting they shouldn't need to mute
unless you announce your cards every
around HH ah start ah
oh
oh oh okay wait wait wait so
uh okay guns are
filled no yeah yeah
yeah deck contained six times I can't
read that
[Music]
fast Queen table what does that
mean I don't know what any this means
waiting for first claim you guys got to
help me how to play this game voice chat
ah
here do they know that like if you play
with randos do the randos know wait
there's a timer there's a timer wa how
do I know what they want what what does
the game want from
me you need to play you need to play a
queen play Queens okay how how ah switch
cards select cards ah ah ah how do
I
uh I don't know what I'm
doing go easy on me
please no no yes yes no yes yes go easy
on
me one Queen uhhuh wait how do I how do
I say o o I don't believe you
I I probably didn't play a queen
right what happened what
happened what happened what did I just
do ah just another scarf would a wa
what's happening don't whoa does that
mean does that mean they played a Queen
Somebody told them you didn't play a
queen
but oh too quiet okay okay okay wait I'm
I'm under a lot ofure pressure right
now okay they played a queen but they
accused them you can only accus when
it's your
turn who's whose turn is it right now
one oh they have to play it went back
there oh oh oh I'm so
confused yeah
yeah King wait unnown says
so we can play
anything
one I'll just I'm just going
to I'm just going to do it I'm just
going to do
[Laughter]
it I have to try
it
[Laughter]
liar what ah so you did play a ah but
you said you play a king no no no no
don't die another scarf with a
collection close
one huh I got the call but why did they
not shoot themselves
then oh oh
oh oh and now I don't have to play a
card
huh it was a blank oh so it's not always
okay okay that's a different thing then
okay two que one six chances okay he's
he said they say they they played a a
queen you say you played a
queen okay I'm not going to sus you out
anymore cuz I just
did okay but how do I say something else
from what I'm playing
but
ah so if I choose this is it going to
say
ah one Queen I know I don't understand
this it has to be a queen I don't know
what I
played you always played
Queen but didn't one Queen previously it
said uh King
liar oh
[\h__\h] oh
oh but now there's a queen on the table
so it was really oh no oh wo w w bunnies
still got luck okay so narata actually
played a
queen wow so honest my kfp are so
honest didn't expect anything else from
you
guys no you you lied once though you
[Laughter]
lied the point is to lie yeah I still
don't know what I'm doing after this
round we have to rethink what I'm doing
wa so now they're saying Ace I
thought a Aces table so now we have to
play
Aces
okay I do have many
aces uh switch card select cards
okay go put it do I do I press
e do I just wait for the countdown to be
over
one
ace trust me it is
true
what T why do you doubt your
[Music]
tental now you must pay bring it one
Kaboom ah close one yeah close one
indeed hope you learn your
lesson Aces table okay I'm I'm starting
to understand
looks away in shame shame ding ding ding
ding shame ding ding ding
ding they're so
concentrated what's up claim claim
it why
to why why to why would you throw out
too I'm going to ask chat why two three
Aces
free a Death
Wish
what what Liar
Liar why did
[Music]
you just another scarf with a
collection oh this king's table now okay
so now we need to play king's see okay
so I could have played like all my free
Aces huh but do I want to have an empty
hand
though is it good if I if you run out of
cards you're safe
oh do I just wait for the others
King empty hand save H King uh
okay uh I
don't okay select
uhhuh oh but but if I run out of if I if
what if I uh well
okay do they ever ask for more than one
card in any case or is it always just
one do it do
it what you looking at
H what are you thinking
H want to spice it up a
little come on come
on come
[Laughter]
on did you really think I was
lying nah N I don't think you did either
nah I hope you live I hope you
live okay CL one I'm so
nice I think I just baited them to sus
me out I'm glad they've sus me out
that's
fun when playing on ases every card you
play uhuh uhuh look at my
cards oh you had no
king
not so you thought your only option was
but but but you could have you could
have you could have lied about having a
king you didn't have to sus me
out I hope you know the game back better
than
me we can learn
together okay first time ah ah explains
[Music]
everything you play two
Aces
liar I don't know why are you guys so
honest ah I raised you too well no no no
no and luck let's hope I have both take
the bullet for me why did nobody jump in
front of the gun for me why
why okay Queen's
table could have totally played the aces
but I had a feeling that you you did
play those Aces for real for
real
yeah the nodding queen queen Queen's
table
[Music]
you know I'm a
queen you know it
right
[Music]
yes why why would I play
no to get rid of more cards
faster wait are they re shuffling the
card
each
[Music]
time that the table
changes oh how am I going to get rid of
all my cards so fast
then three queens no
way your luck huh fre
Queens you
sure are y'all are sure about that wow
team work kfp is so
bonded kfp is so
peaceful
um uh sorry I'm still thinking how to
control this game can I throw it out
early do I really have to wait those 15
seconds C there we go it didn't work
before so I I wasn't sure
play play a card you know you want to
one
Queen
liar oh no no no Poor Poor Pig no
no why would you lie though just another
scarf with a colle don't die don't die
how did you know unknown I thought it is
unknown to you but it turns out it is
very known to you who lies and who
doesn't
lie smug
face too
strong yeah so far no bullets one
is 5050 next time
I've Barely Used My Bullets only once
right or twice hey yo Liar Liar oh
[\h__\h] what I know the
absolute
Savage whoa you played three different
cards still got
luck
no
no no
no that was
terrifying you can't you can't expect to
you know just play free fake cards and
nothing
[Music]
happens queen that was that was what's
the word what's the word I'm looking for
daring uh oh sorry I'm talking to the
stream sorry
oopsie the
absolute uh um uh I forgot the word yeah
ballsy ballsiness uh that's not the word
I'm looking for audacity that was it uh
cards cards what are we uh
queens that was close
Queen
audacity
audacity one
Queen yeah yeah I see I believe I
believe you
H one
Queen one
Queen why you looking at why are you
looking up like that you have something
to
hide look at
me look
at I feel bad you you're lying
oh you you didn't lie oh [\h__\h] why why
would you not look at me then why would
you not look at me then beuty and luck
let's hope I have both you made
me the Panic what what that was I can't
believe
this do you still hear
me you made me doubt you and then I
sused you out you wanted me to doubt
you can't believe it
can't believe my o is [\h__\h] dead
yeah can't believe it either
honestly I shouldn't I
shouldn't oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah that's what you get for for
baithing your oi just another scarf with
a
Col close one
oh my God so
scary so scary
G is this what you guys look like when
your feathers are all plucked
out yeah I think so
too the ears I didn't know you guys had
such ears hiding behind the
feathers what what the hell was that
somebody just threw a knife one
one I was going to say also those are
the wings but then what about the arms
are the arms not the
wings one king you guys have a lot of
Kings in your hand oh liar oh
[\h__\h] a
no no that's a 50/50 chance isn't it oh
no oh no bring it
a
no
no no Yay good for
you so
smug all right get out of here that was
a fun first game
gg
gg good job
[Music]
wow this is fun
oh oh yeah oh code is still the same so
you guys oh yeah can
join uh yeah unknown get out of
here okay yeah you guys are you guys are
ready for that huh should I pin the code
cuz oopsie I'll pin the code in the
members chat
okay there you go yeah I have both
stream chats
open but chat in the main chat
members don't use the members chat as
your secret special members chat for
cool people only like a secret club like
a secret part in the club a
VIP don't use it like that go to the
main chat otherwise the main chat will
lose its
live okay we have Holo for life small
Weeoo and
prepo I hope you're one of us you have
you have to be right it's just a very
normal sounding name not very whole life
but I'm sure you are
okay be nice to your boss ah and uh make
sure to close the stream now
everybody sorry no worries no worries
you were good
ready up how do I ready up actually ah H
for Life needs to ready
up can I still uh close stream
okay okay okay
okay
okay I hope they did
it let's go round two and 1 hour 13
minutes until the announcement Mo on
let's
go welcome to the Liar's
bar here we go I hope you have your
stream closed yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
good good good
good don't make me SS you out if if
you're not ssw worthy okay okay promise
MH mhm mhm why is pre power mirror
already so
sus you're
sus you're so sus K why are you always
looking
down what's there to
see you don't want us to see your your
eyes Your Lying
Eyes oh oh God it's kind of terrifying
things she doesn't know are you looking
at your own boobies
[Music]
oh my God oh my God right wow okay focus
focus
um should we do something
ballsy two kings there we
go how those boobies nice I can't see my
own um not really there's nothing there
Fox is so
flat would you would you still love me
if I was a
worm yeah yeah
yipp see how I changed the topic there
so that H for Life wouldn't sus me
out stop looking at you boobs over there
three cards that's daring
oh oh wait what free you fre free CS
whoa
whoa liar I don't believe
it [\h__\h]
wow wow you really wanted to get rid of
those cards huh why you hate them so
much just another SC with a
collection Lu
key I'm glad I called it out Justice
Justice
okay
okay look at my I
see how's it going how's it going good
cards
yeah this feel so intimate that's daring
but you for free cards again you won
want me to sus you
out this time I believe
you I think oh maybe I don't liar let's
see what you
got you did it two times in a row and
pre power miror still just the whole
time looking at her boobs Bring It On
uhoh uhoh uhoh uh-oh lucky don't never
do that
again never again mhm yeah good good
good good good good
good all right what do we
got the only time you're looking up from
your boobs is when you need to look at
your cards
addiction Two
Kings Kings okay imagine
if if they faked it
again are you sure this time small wee
boo
liar no way no you're compulsive
liar oh my
god oh just another scarf with a
Comm oh what this was the last time
right the last time that you lied for
sure I believe in you you need to better
yourself now this is your chance to turn
it all around change your
life
interesting you're an honest one aren't
you no oh my God what do you think
should I sus that out
again two kings so far only lies no not
this time
liar please disappoint me with oh okay
thank you I was hoping for
that thank God okay yeah b beauty and
luck let's hope I have
both is is is that a joke like looking
at your boobs the whole time I don't get
it look at me PR power Miro
you're down
bad uh okay wa it's my
[Music]
turn two Aces what do you
think what do you
think no you don't trust me you
should you should it's good for you to
trust your boss otherwise where are we
going with kfp right we need to have
trust among each other
amus one is oh yeah okay I was hoping
that uh like the the re reverse
psychology doesn't seem to
work yeah one ace h
that's realistic you want to sus it out
no Aces yeah you can't you can't risk
too much now two
aces are you a changed Pig a changed
chicken
okay are you
do well my problem is now I don't have
an ace f and I feel like I'm going to
get sused out now
[\h__\h] one
ace trust
right trust on kfp very important
yeah thank you for
understanding thank you
Ace I know I know they can hear me I'm
purposefully activating my my voice chat
it's not always um I have to I have push
the button push the button push push the
talk one
ace I think you don't have any more
Aces liar sorry
I'm so sorry I feel so
bad I'm sorry no don't die just another
scarf with a Col don't die don't
die I did that I killed you I'm
sorry ah murder has been attempted and
succeeded I'm
sorry I'm
sorry I feel so bad
I will be nicer now as long as you guys
are
nice yes
yes uh what are we claiming
Queens one
Queen take
it the knife is really
distracting scares me
to
Queens I need to check out what's what's
about the the boobies I need to switch
to bunny next
time one
Queen okay
okay one Queen so that counts as a queen
right to Queens but now it's going to be
problematic like it's it gets more and
more unrealist IC to really have those
cards that you claim to have huh what do
you think you're not going to Su him
out
you what's what's your end game what's
your end
game yeah unless you Bluff yeah right
that's when you should maybe Bluff early
so you still have cards later on when
people get more sussy and like no no way
you still have a let's let's just I
don't believe it you must focus on The
Game Stop focus on your boobs
oh damn it damn
it please please Beauty unlock let's
hope I have
both
hallelujah thank you thank
you so
scary uh okay okay okay okay what uh he
is
okay one
ace you got
some you
good
two
[Music]
wow
she you going to believe that that
bunny bunny girl you just don't want to
fight anybody huh you just you just want
peace and play cards I see
H uh uh one ace sorry I still have
problems with the controls
no
[Music]
yes just another scar for a collection y
y oh
[Music]
lucky King's table
monkey
W yeah I could have still could have
still played my my my Joker what do we
have now uh King's table and I have I
have a good
hand one
king
I I will believe because I'm scared out
how many bullets did I already use ah
two ooh I kind of want to sus the bunny
out m
what if I do this is it too too risky
let's do two two
kings oink oink oink oink who's a cute
little piggy oink oink oink
oink Yes Yes actually yeah you're not a
piggy you're a chicken okay beautiful
chicken a beautiful chicken who would
never SS out their
boss okay
liar finally some action oh [\h__\h] two
queens those are not
Kings uhoh chicken
bye-bye one
wa Lucky
Bastard sheesh
no fried bacon
today whose turn is
it one is uhhuh prepar
me do you like
Wawa do you like Wawa more than the
boobs
who do who do you like more your own
boobs or
me me not not me me W Ah that's kind of
hesitating but
okay one
ace yeah yeah that's what I like to see
head banging very passionate
approval liar oh [\h__\h]
oh what are you doing Hol for life why
do you want
to no why won't you be honest with
us
why honest from now on otherwise you
know you you saw what happened with
small
Weeoo all right all right all
right I think it's time we s out preow M
some more I don't think they've ever
been sused
out so it's it's my job huh cuz I come
after
them whatever they do now I'm going to
sus it
out unless it's just one card I don't
know if it's just one card it's very
believable I'm sick and tired of
this you just never get sused out and
now you're playing a too comfortable
game I shall call you a liar even though
your turn is very realistic and you
might very well have an ace liar tell us
show us okay I rest my claim and I might
die goodbye are you going to watch your
boss die H and let's hope I
have hurts it hurts
I just wanted to switch it up a little
bit I couldn't watch this
anymore ah
man may I shouldn't have done it on the
first card first card is just too
realistic to be a lie especially if
they're only playing one if they play
like two or three in the first claim
then oh wa whoa
let's
go oh my God what a God play bunnies
still got luck
careful let's [\h__\h]
go
shees
what that was impressive you kept those
cards there until the
end okay new
people come on now come on now come on
now thank you guys that was a really
good good
game maybe I should look at my boobs now
for one I need to check it out I need to
know what it's all about I need to
understand cuz I don't understand
yet what is what is so interesting about
that
POV I'm a cupcake now
yeah
VI VII v
v why called me
cupcake close stream
okay
okay okay okay
let's
[Music]
begin I can just look down myself no but
like in game I need to see what the
bunny is so
oh I understand
now that's what it was oh
okay
okay you guys are so focused huh H
better stay
focused okay all
right do I have skin and not
fur so
weird they don't care about my
comments um
Ace
oh one ace
back to the
boobs one
is although those nails are
terrifying one
is nice shoulders
too it's like the Grand Canyon here wow
oh
liar show me what you
got
no ah take it for me take it for me take
it for me guess it's
[Music]
show scary try harder darling scary so
scary okay everybody who's sitting at
the
table is wa Yosi yes or no
yes yes yes
yes
su su you got the code from Members chat
I must be your oi then or you just
member
everybody yeah you're just a member of
everybody who's your oi is it uh someone
from
hen uhhuh is it first gen second first
gen ah
is it
go oh what waa I went there right away
is she your only
oi no on on what am I first okay I'm not
first am I second am I third second
second I'm I'm second y okay okay I'll
take it thank you thank you wow I
appreciate it aces I'm I'm satisfied
with that free cards free free
like
it no
liar sorry I have to Su you out again
what God damn
it no no no no no no no no okay I'll
stop I'll stop susing people out please
I'm I'm the streamer I I need to I need
to re uh survive okay yeah okay sh
what do we have okay oh I'm I'm I'm
playing
okay ah no dangerous [\h__\h] what if no
we'll just do we'll just do one one
Queen we'll just do one I'm
scared one
Queen tearing it down just I
[Music]
two queens I wish I could sus you out
for that but I'm in a risky territory
now as you
know two
queens which means you're kind of safe
forever
H I'll s out again soon no no why would
you do that why would you do that no I
no I already chose so many bullets no
why do you hate me so much I hope this
bunny is still I'm scared I'm scared
hold my
hand you didn't even hold my
hands why did I die first
why did it have to be
me those bunny ears look cute on the
table like
that no I'm looking down I'm looking
down but all I see is the table
now
que yeah you guys better play it fast
now oh
[\h__\h] you want to SS it out uhoh the
tension the tension in this room
que oh you landed through you landed
past oh oh oh they've always been an
honest
chicken once again it has been
proven for the boss you shall die
no he'll he'll he'll get what he
deserves
oh question mark question mark question
mark I see nice
cards
one oh you don't even oh risky
risky oh no there the first one right
just it'll be fine it'll be fine it'll
be fine it'll be fine CL one yes yes yes
yes
yes there's speed running yeah yeah I
got to end it I'm first one dead
unbelievable wow again question mark
question mark question
mark you got the wrong cards man to
Kings those are not Kings don't say
question mark question mark don't
believe it it's not
Kings two kings I saw the video by the
way ask some stuff to the St what do I
ask um um
umu um uh uh press if if you if
you sorry I'm bad at
this oh G Fu I I pray for you don't die
this one's for you darling thank you for
[Laughter]
me okay okay
okay
um what do I ask what do I ask
chat if they watch BD what breaking
dimensions three kings three kings three
cards someone's got a Death
Wish wrecking
B do it do it do
it
a okay Su uh play four cards if you
pressed four before on Mirage and Kima
do it do it don't be a coward have you
pressed four before you got to you got
to play four cards you got to do it you
got to do it you got to do it don't be a
coward come
on I don't believe it for sure you oh
Max is free well you you should have
fled
free she didn't let
me damn it
liar
uhoh oh
no it's so over for
you for you goodbye
chicken oh oh lucky nobody wants to come
to me to
heaven I'm all alone up here who wants
to join
me yeah you want to join me you want to
join me to the fryer with
you I can press a or ah
[Music]
oh oh oh that's so
far that's also so far that's also so
far okay let's go back here uh-oh uh-oh
oh [\h__\h] oh no yeah you don't have many
bullets anymore
a first one to come to me in
heaven I feel the
love I'm not alone
anymore how are the cards
guys two queens two queens
don't make the others jealous you guys
should join us up here it's really nice
in heaven they got
Umar oh they want trouble already oh Su
wants to join us in
[Music]
heaven just another scarf with a
collection it's okay it's going to be
fun
a don't need to be scared
it's going to be fine they're shaking
with excitement yeah
one you too should
kiss one King come on it's only you two
left you should kiss
[Laughter]
two kings they're ignoring
me oh
wow I like an honest
chicken
K it's so
[Music]
over no
way I don't know chat give me questions
to
ask we already know the
oshis
two liar yeah that's a
lie
oh just another scarf with a collection
the weather run a marathon or climb M
pineapple oh
okay um whose turn is
it pineapple pizza yes or
no yes yipp yeah oh we got pineapple
friends
pineapple
hey I like these chickens I wouldn't
mind if they stay
alive I just noticed a chat message now
I shall attend to my oosi
a I feel attended to
is liar oh
no once again gffu fu is the most honest
chicken oh just another oh it's so over
now it's so over now oh
W let's
go good job
oh I just I just noticed the Pinocchio
nose there on the trophy
funny okay are you ready kfp to
join
yeah welcome welcome only eat kfp nice
name suu and big head and only eat
kfp you did it welcome and we have 40
minutes left until the announce some
more I think
[Music]
sorry
oh just replying to 1 DM
okay W died so early yeah this time I
won't die
early I hope leave Wawa alive is that
proper English let Wawa
live
please ah try lies dies okay maybe next
round next round next round close stream
okay all right all
right maybe no no no no no oh you mean
maybe about letting me live it can't be
a maybe it has to be has to be but yes
certainly my
queen going to be Fox
again is the queen on a server in Austra
e what does it matter on what server I'm
in in
here ping always there's no ping here
right
yeah no more distractions no more booby
distractions I'm a foxy lady once
again no ping excuses
yeah okay I'm trying going to try to ask
more questions
now hello welcome to the
table all right first question right off
the bat waa number one not if true yes
yes
oh o thank you suzu I'm confused only
eat kfp but I'm not your number
one okay who is it h life
English uh first gen oh both h of
English Okay first
J one okay wait start with only e kfp
first gen uh okay
uh you seem like
a you seem like
uh cie
fan no goba is it goba
again Ena oh you're sad is it
a danger suits you darling yeah a me me
too me
[Music]
too a so sad sorry for making you sad
wait okay uh card uh
King one king all right big
head first gen you said home life
English or not first gen first
gen second gen one
king the
vir admin
admin
Justice no
council wait wait it's not Council
anymore promise
promise no
myth whole life
English is your o not from h iing Engish
yeah I'm calling that out too
liar you
uh maybe maybe just another scarf with a
collection all of
oh
haki
a oh only it kfb loves
everybody big head Ian but hak or one
person
one OSI or everybody
[Music]
oosi Japanese
member ID
member
no maybe maybe they don't like H
[Laughter]
life Advent one yeah I thought it was a
not to Advent Advent Advent
uh
promise uh justice no I don't see any
nods
no okay
well what are we playing
King one king this is
difficult myth
myth
myth one
no ah Hol star is
English
one yeah
no okay one I'm
confused
Yago Yago yo yo Ah that's not whole I'm
English um King
one
king
okayi well done so we have a or
everybody oi a wa oi and a
yagi and a
waa two kings what a great combination
of
people do you speak uh Hey number one
good a
n i see a jum Bud after
all
Goa goo
cute we agree right we all agree goo
cute yeah oneing hey not your heads
everybody
o one
king all right uh oh uh Li too focused
on game we need to sus some people out
Su I'm sorry I'm sorry
suu Su no you don't want to be the
reason why I die I know I know don't
fail me
now close one you're good you're good
suu it's okay suu you know suu that's
what the Sims say to greet each other
[Music]
suu I love Sims
language uh
King let's do a bold one three
kings someone's got a Death
Wish well I am a
phoenix you should you should do what
your heart wants you to
do it's okay I won't fire you one
King damn
it h yeah yeah I know I know there were
some
um uh kanji I can see it in the chat
actually I don't know why it's not
showing in the over
there so probably English not the first
language two
kings
[Music]
interesting liar I am only doing this
because I don't have much better
choice look don't fail me
now we'll always trust wa oh
really oh okay can I rely on
that I'll try relying on
that uh
Queen one
Queen what do you guys think the
announcement will be today huh do you
think it will
be that kfp is buying out
McDonald's yes one yeah yeah totally
could easy I could totally do that I
have enough money yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah care if we must over R the fast
food industry number
one I mean of course you're happy with
that you only eat at
kfp thank you for your business thank
you appreciate it I hope you always
treat our our staff nicely with danger I
you always tip right how thrilling
yeah one Queen to that I say
Dan to Queen
I saw
um okay I'll I'll press I'll press the
button so you guys can hear my tangent
as well I saw a video yesterday oh [\h__\h]
it was real saw a video yesterday uh on
Twitter from the Japanese McDonald's um
SC with a colle a king song
cover no you w hear my tach
now no I shall I shall have you um here
my my holy tangent in heaven and I shall
pray for you hopefully my tangent will
make you feel good even in heaven I'm
with
you uh what are we doing now
Queen one Queen someone's dead that's
what happened and it's your
fault so yeah the the there was a king
uh song cover you are King
but they changed the lyrics and it's in
Japanese so if you don't speak Japanese
it's really hard to understand how funny
the lyrics are now but so for example
instead of left side right side it's m
size L size uh and it's like all like
about eating fries it's so funny
actually it's so good yeah yeah I hope
they bring out like
subtitles yeah yeah thank you but then I
was thinking here's the irony oh wait
it's my turn oh [\h__\h] ah
one okay okay uh I was thinking um they
still sing to Queen I think they still
sing you are King didn't they um but
then I was thinking oh maybe McDonald's
shouldn't have adopted the song but
Burger King then it would like they can
still sing about potato fries
what are you guys even listening to my
tangent when you're like susing it yeah
you are you are uhoh ah ah
[Music]
ah yeah but Burger they could sing
Burger King instead of you are
King Burger
[Music]
King now we will see if what you said
before will stand
true oh wait my hand is way too good
actually one
Queen please don't call me out please
don't call me out please don't call me
out I have a way too good hand oh
where's the bear
going the bear looks so
funny fre Queen free Queens danger suits
you
darling you're looking away are you
lying look at me look at me look at me
look at me look at me are you lying H
are you
lying I must I must SS it
out and then I'll drop everything I got
oh but wait I I didn't want it to be
wrong because I had such good cards [\h__\h]
actually that was ah actually my hand
was so good bring it on ah oh well guess
you'll die a close one nah I
I'd
live N I should have but I couldn't have
played all four cards and I don't know
how they they could have just continued
playing like five of their like the
remaining of their cards ah man
[Music]
okay what ra the most yay hash has yolk
woohoo oh what I'm I'm not surprised you
watch me the most if I'm your second
or uh two
Aces how about that are you are you more
certain this
time yeah you seem more honest this
time I'm not so certain this
time one ace I'll Trust you this one
time this one time
don't get too ballsy
now you're not going to throw out free
cards are
you oh you're thinking too long what are
you thinking
about oh oh that's automatic is it is it
it what I didn't even play I didn't even
press X but you yippe yippe
Rejoice just another SC
[Music]
goodbye W
wins nah I'd
win yay yay yay okay next is Dice so
only people who want to play the dice
game join I don't even know how it works
thank you guys that was fun
you guys are so fun to play with Galaxy
welcome going to play Li dice KOB KF
beat oh I see it in your name I guess I
don't have to ask you who's your or she
dice is slightly more complicated okay
let's liar dice roll the dice no one can
see you roll but everyone's watching
your next move guess how many dice of a
certain number are showing across all
players the bid has to be raised in each
round
think someone's lying challenged their
bit lying about what we're not saying
how what we have do
we challenge their bid I guess we
are di is Head Hard dice is
me I still understand the rules this is
more guessing than
lying guessing game mostly
to guess how many dice in toer I maybe
that's not so good though see we're not
even getting a fourth player cuz people
don't want to play liar D or is it
maximum three people actually all right
I we're we're playing Liar's deck trim
your deck guys come on come on one space
has opened
up is it is the lobby bugged
uhoh oh no there we go myth let's go
yippe okay close stream
please this might be I don't know this
might be the last game for now because
announcement I don't know how long this
will be maybe if we play a faster game
we can play two more in
total okay make up your mind guys oh we
have a bit more variety this time or oh
no pig
pig let's go let's go ready up ready up
ready
up Galaxy you need to ready up I don't
know where I don't know how but you need
to do it okay let's
go here we go yeah pig pig just looks
funny they should put in a giraff
giraffe giraff giraffe in German we say
giraff
a Giraffe and Chicken like an oversized
chicken though I guess or even a small
one would be cute like just a small one
who which just barely like looking over
the table wouldn't that be so
cute that would be so cute please put a
chicken in the game Hello everybody
welcome
welcome hello so Kobe you like Wawa and
Cali Takami let's
go galaxy I thought you're s excited
Galaxy I think your number one is waa
right I mean yeah no yeah yeah
yeah no what yes Waba number
one maybe
[Laughter]
not wa not number
one H one is partially
okay you have two kosis oh wait who was
the I feel like I might know but who was
the second one H life Ian also
right uh
myth uh
promise uh Advent uh oh
promise okay I'll get right back to
you uh uh uh can't think no one ace all
right all right uh promise you said
quason one uh
M excited kns are so
funny wa and
M a
cute
now the beautiful sick Rhino over there
why you looking away my Smith is your
Ori
right the whole gen or
and there's not not one in particular
that stands out to you like the number
one for you in your
heart is it you like them all the
same a that's
cute one so wholesome I think I'm very
well distracting them with my
tangents one
ace cute I like it everybody here is at
least in very much in love with Wawa
[Music]
why are you not nodding hey over there
yeah thank you
okay thank you are you streaming Mirage
guys streaming
Mirage yeah yeah yeah okay takes you a
while is it the
ping it's the Ping it's the Ping
[Music]
wait maybe I should start susing out
some
people
liar let's go I forgot about saing out
people I think we're all forgot this
one's for you D don't
die nice
[Laughter]
okay okay let's
look oh by the
way who who here would say that Mirage
is their favorite wa was
song
yeah okay not you that it's not not a
problem not a problem uh let's see is
who who here likes Sparks the most or
Chima Sparks Sparks Sparks oh Sparks
Sparks oh Galaxy is it the do you like
Chima the
most one or or
or I'm not
sure what other songs do I have
pineapple one Queen yeah oh you like I'm
happy yippe
nice wow so passion about pineapp oh so
pineapple and pizza
yes
no you no no what the hell what about
you Kobe pineapple and
pizza oh yeah okay then I like you the
most out of these people
here how you like pineapple now
H you should put them on your pizza next
time then I like you
more yeah yeah you hearing
that
yeah one God have to play the
game it's not blackmail it's not
blackmail it's it's it's uh kfp
protocol I broke their hearts they broke
my
hearts how about corn on
Pizza one Queen
corn hello corn people liar yes okay oh
that's that's not
fair Galaxy likes corn leave him alone
no just another scarf with a
collection good close
one yeah corn craw Pizza is the best he
special place of heart same same I mean
I mean first song will always have a
special place in in all of our hearts
yeah um I would love to ask kobby what
their favorite c song is but the amount
of songs that I have to go through to
reach the favorite will probably I don't
even I can't even name all of
them do you have a favorite c
song H is it a more recent one or a more
old one
oh wait okay
recent not if recent uh old uh not if
old old okay wait
um one okay
uh is it red oh you said oh you running
in the chat red ah yeah that that one
sick that is really good
I forgot chat but chat shouldn't even be
allowed it's funnier when I have to make
you guys answer questions just with your
head no not not except for when it's
really difficult liar oh drama alert oh
my God honestly Rhino Rhino's kind of
sad not going to lie
like I guess my Debs are catching up
with me that Hawaii shirt ah I'm sorry
no what have you done what have you
done oh a poor
Rhino no not the M
fan man that's so
[Music]
sad I don't know how we can move on from
this one
is you're just moving on from that as if
you didn't just cause someone's death
Galaxy holy [\h__\h]
um
Aces one ace I should call people out
more in the first
round what what what the [\h__\h] why would
you do that
Galaxy what what what what what what
beauty and LU let's hope I have both bro
bro bro why would you do that
you have no chill after you killed
someone you're attempting another murder
right immediately literally immediately
I can't believe it Galaxy I can't
believe
it are you after
me then Kobe we have to do something
about Galaxy or we'll see we'll see
who's next I don't know wait I don't
know how this
goes one ace
oh it is your turn
now Kobe one is
Kobe actually he he probably did play an
ace damn probably did should we call it
out I
know it's going to take us all down oh
[\h__\h] you did
it let's
go ah
this one's for you
darling
y all right all right well you lied now
we have a feeling for how you're lying
I'm going to ask you next
time let's
see
Galaxy be
[Music]
honest yeah yes
yeah one
is did you play an ace Galaxy
free flirting the danger I see how
thrilling really
kobby
really one ace believe it that was a
really friendly OD it's
risky got to trust
Kobe C beat cave beats are
based they're based they they've been
through some [\h__\h] they probably have
been around since the very beginning
cave beats have probably been around
since the very
beginning so they're very trustworthy so
I I believe you played those free cards
but I don't believe you played an ace
now
liar so let's see oh
[\h__\h] should have asked you some more I'm
sorry I didn't inquire I didn't inquire
let's hope I have
[Music]
both next time I'll inquire
properly I'll go through the proper MCI
the free or fake
maybe we the free fake Kobe
no doesn't matter anymore you can be
honest
now I wish it was Ace now oh is it my
turn one Queen [\h__\h] I actually wanted to
play two cards what did I play now did I
play a Joker now
Fu two
queens no playing okay good
good
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I want to get that Ace out but I'm
too scared one Queen
one
Queen liar
oh for real oh no Kobe oh
no no no no no no no careful
careful and I had such a good hand
[\h__\h] I should play more ballsy I should
bring out more cards at
once King's table not good hands it's
easier to be ballsy with a better
hand one
king but I at least I've gotten used to
just playing random cards in the
beginning that are not at
all don't worry they don't hear me I I I
choose to push to talk
was that really a
king
[Laughter]
no you're so
cute oh you're so
cute a you'll get a special place in
heaven you'll be eaten by me after
getting fried another scarf with a Col
look forward to it a damn it close one
oh you're so
cute you're so cute I want to squeeze
your little
ears okay all
right what we doing Ace
okay I wish it was King
bro was it really two
Aces you're so honest is it because I
already like stated at the fact that KF
beats are honest people because they've
been for some [\h__\h] so now you feel like
you have to live up to
that yeah
Li amazing
amazing I I got to respect the KF beats
yo got to respect them I love them even
more now bring it
on do it for Honor yeah for
Honor he can't lie now because otherwise
what I said will not you know it will
not be honored yeah for Honor
que should I ask the question
Kobe then why do you even play Tool
cards two cards makes me want to ask the
question even
[Laughter]
more liar you're a good comedian you
should join all alive
hey hey Kobe Kobe what's up with that
Kobe Kobe Kobe what's up with that in
love let's hope I have both what
Kobe should I should I have asked the
question should I thought that was
already the answer basically that
expression oh man okay okay all right
maybe maybe maybe there's still some
honor
[Laughter]
there King sa I laughed a lot now that
was funny I am amused very amused right
good stuff my tummy hurts from that
maybe maybe let's play some
cards two
kings
one two kings Kobe where those two
kings okay good good for
you good for you
one
king I'm so glad that he's right next to
me I can always ask him be sure I'll get
an honest answer and then later I'll
deal with Galaxy what wh what what what
you don't have a card to play are you
thinking of calling me
[Music]
out I don't know what to tell you um one
a man you should have called me out
though you should have you should have
Galaxy yes you should
have how do I sound
like like not oh
[\h__\h] oh F God that's
slow call me let's [\h__\h] go yeah yeah
yeah yeah come on come on come on bring
it if I W we Von Kobe I'll
win [\h__\h] close
one [\h__\h]
okay here we go here we go here we go
here we go here we
go oh why is it not a [\h__\h] ace
table what the
[\h__\h] wait did you hear
that did you hear what I
said no
good I think I accidentally pressed B on
on the end of my sentence but I don't
think it was
yeah two kings did you play two kings
okay two
kings no come on Galaxy no
no no Galaxy why ask me the question at
least don't just don't just don't just
fail me
Queen's table Len it everybody
onstead only Queens shall be
played only
Queens one Queen just like this
one I know I sound sus hey what free did
you play free Queen's Galaxy
well is it really free
Queens one Queen you played a queen I'm
sure you did
right
yeah one
Queen trying to be
sus oh the bear looks so cool [\h__\h]
let's go let's [\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h]
go oh [\h__\h] just another scarf with a
coll [\h__\h] man he's too
lucky just too
lucky guys we got to end this I have
only three minutes left can we end it in
three minutes can we speed
around okay but let me win
Galaxy come on did you really play a
king thank you thank you that was a slow
nod [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
no I'm sorry I'm sorry no Kobe no no no
Kobe I was hoping was it's going to be
one versus one with you and me oh good
close one still have a
chance okay okay okay all right all
right all right let's let's let's speed
one let's speed
one two Aces did you really play two
Aces
okay two
Aces one
e liar oh [\h__\h]
I'm not sure if that's necessarily going
to end the game
earlier no no no wait no no no
kby we've been through so much
kobby I don't know if I can trust
Galaxy okay one weave on me
bro let's do this quick I have 1 minute
40 seconds uh
Queen one Queen don't do it don't do it
one Queen all right I see we're playing
a speedy
game one
Queen
liar Get Wrecked Get
Wrecked Get Wrecked
[Music]
Galaxy bring it
on so much for I don't die all right
thank you guys love you guys that was
fun I enjoyed it all right announcement
time
bye-bye that was so much fun my tummy
hurts oh so fun GG thank you guys for
participating we should play it
again ah
okay um we we we we
uh we we we now I'm kind of nervous you
guys are maybe expecting something crazy
as I said it's not a 3D Live it's um
it's something that costs
money uh but not just
anything I think you will like it so I
think it's ready I think we can do it I
think we
can bring it out okay all right are you
ready are you ready here we
[Applause]
[Music]
go shut up shut up shut up shut
up let's go let's go this is a kfb looks
normal right that's what I thought too
but then I noticed something weird about
kp's kitchens have you noticed I mean
really taking a look at their staff
they're not what they seem to be how did
we not know missed this before but then
I found
these classified documents each one
labeled with a code I'm going to go
visit their Test Kitchen and find out
what's really going on the world deserve
to know what's going on behind those
closed doors at the new kfp Test Kitchen
but I need your help deciding where to
start I'm very indecisive but I can't be
caught I need you to sign up on the
encrypted email list below below and
every day I can send you what I find
about these files and little by little
we will unravel this Chimera of mirages
that they've
[Music]
created
yay wait did that even say what company
you were working
with it's it's V Ramen
oh
[\h__\h]
W do you understand what this means
perhaps you do
not if you don't know what kind of
company this is white Ramen is a really
really really cool company which has
been doing uh several like vtuber
collaborations already so far um they
mostly do Ramen but they also do other
stuff like sick knives and so on uh by
the way what time is it in PST right
now let me
know oh is it already ah the Tweet went
live too yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
it's it's 11:48
a.m. okay then I
think can I post this oh yeah uh oh H so
go to this site
whoa I posted in the chat let me replace
pin
message you can enter your email to
receive daily updates and more and more
details will be revealed over the course
of the next days it will be worth it to
sign up you might get a special deal um
but yeah a certain agent has started
investigating
kfp the V agent I
guess uh which I should be very
concerned about but I am also very
excited about because who knows what
this will lead to uh if you look at the
their shop they have some really cool
things let me actually show you some of
their um
collaborations what has come from their
collaboration so far I actually I've
been sent since this has been planned
for while I've been sent some stuff uh a
while ago
already um and I've been testing their
stuff so for example here this was a
collab with girm yeah so Ramen
Ramen
Ramen but they also make knives and
stuff let me see can I find a knife oh
yeah kitchen wear I actually let me show
you which knife I have I I think I got
two but one of them I GI it to uh jenma
because she really seemed to like it uh
but this I've been using this sick
chopping knife holy [\h__\h] it's so cool so
this is also like the girm design and
it's like really big it looks way bigger
IRL it's like I think you're supposed to
chop like big chunks of meat or so with
bones in it I don't know but I'm just
chopping anything with it's so smooth
and has really nice patterns that uh I
think they're just like um that's what
you get when you get Damascus steel
knife I don't really know much about
these things but yeah really high
quality cool products from this company
V so yeah real Damascus of course but
that's why I've been saying that this C
collaboration might be a little bit on
the expensive side but it depends you
can decide yourself how much you will
end up getting and so but you know you
know you know this is in the realm of
possibilities and I've been just super
hyped to let you know about what's
coming yeah yeah yeah yeah so the Tweet
is out there I'm going to retweet it now
too let me quote retweet
it oh yeah oh yeah are we in
danger let's go oh my X
kfp yeah so actually let me follow them
now because it would have been too sus
if I followed them on Twitter earlier
you guys check my the people who I
follow yeah they had a booth and had a
weekend long offer where if you try to
haggle Tim you could get a good deal oh
really yeah they seem really really nice
and and you know they have cool
collaborations and they put a lot of
work and and uh love love and passion
into their products and I thought that
was really really interesting and when I
uh first found out about this company
you know I I I was
like they do vtuber collaborations I
kind of would be interested to do my own
you know um so I ended up actually
telling management that I'm interested
in the collaboration if they are and our
management reached out and Vite was like
hell yeah let's freaking do it and
that's quite a couple of months ago many
months ago but this is where we have
arrived at and I'm so excited because
what you are going to get is a huge
lineup uh I think probably this is the
biggest biggest perhaps the biggest
lineup they've had so far I actually
don't know but I feel like it might
be yes and it's just going to be so
exciting I'm so excited we're GNA we're
going to extend our kitchen um lineup
cuz like so far I've had the pleasure to
you know bring out my own merch but you
know I can't I don't think I can't I I
don't think I would be able to bring out
such a high quality Damascus knife or so
or real Ramen like real food and so on
in my own like birthday anniversary
merch Etc like that probably is not in
the realm of possibilities um so so far
I've I've only done stuff that's like
more
tame and more doable when it comes to
Kitchen Stuff as as recently I've also
released like U my my chicken uh
my my egg cups and my salt and pepper
shakers Etc that I hope you got as well
but with this we're going to the next
level
yeah I can't wait so I think every day
you're going to get some reveals so
follow Vite the white Ramen Twitter make
sure to follow them to give them some
support they've been working really hard
on making this possible and supporting
me and loving
kfp so yeah um I will also once I get my
hands on the final
products please Customs Austrian customs
please let it go through without any
issues or else I will send kfp
to send their regards but once I get
everything I'm going to do a proper
cooking stream the first cooking stream
in my new kitchen that I've had for a
while now um but yeah I I'll finally do
it a proper cooking stream with whatever
we get from
V so
exciting is is it that's why I have my
small hat on no not really but you know
I wanted to look a little bit more
official for this
purpose are you selling a knife we don't
know yet we don't know it could be
anything it could be several things it
could be anything that V is capable of
producing okay I'm too excited that
stream was overall too exciting I need
to calm down it's a really cool collab I
know it really is it really really is
I can't wait can we already reveal
everything
please yeah but what does it says what's
going on at the KF test Chicken Kitchen
kitchen and chicken wait k
chick if you change around the letters
for kitchen I'm pretty sure it says
chicken
almost the test
chicken uh agent V is investigating
these strange codes and nothing is what
it seems you decide where it goes and
which dossier is revealed next every day
at 12:00 p.m. PST a new episode releases
but the dossers will only be sent to
those who signed up for the encrypted
emails uh so zero out of 10 I
see yeah that's the trailer I just
showed so sign up sign up sign up sign
up yeah yeah yeah yeah congrats Mom
thank you I'm so
happy I don't know if you guys expected
this I think I saw one two kfps recently
over the past weeks days and weeks kind
of guessing that there was going to be
some V collaboration but uh from what I
saw it you didn't expect it to be in
this scale you just expected it to be
one thing but it's going to be more
than why is it playing
suddenly oh just cuz I why did it play
again oh you didn't hear it good good
good good those desktop audio
muted thank
God that was so loud It's just in my
head it's all in my
head expected V or height yeah I know I
saw I saw some people guessing height
yeah yeah yeah there have been many
height collaborations so far but um I
think you know that'd be cool in the
future too but Vite for me was like for
you know
extending my kitchen lineup was
perfect
yeah
yeah it's more on brand it's very on
brand yeah and it's it's just so sick
like if you guys are going to see what
we've been working on you're going to be
really really excited I
[Music]
think yes oh yeah I think um
um I asked previously
about uh
about uh if it's like pre-order or so
I'm pretty sure the answer
was that it'll
be
pre-order but uh if there's enough
demand they're like open to re pre
reopening the pre-order
again in the future or so something like
that I think uh
yeah I think uh they'll probably uh give
you clear
information
[Music]
anyway was it
here I yeah
pre-order um
yeah and then maybe in the future we'll
run more
waves okay and I'll leave it at that uh
little crunchy little stream uh fun and
short and knu in German we say knu and
I'll leave it at that because uh there's
a birthday stream from Cece coming up
and I'll lead you to it yeah yeah yeah
her first birthday so going to keep it
short quit on
knack I'll see you tomorrow for eeden
Eternal with giggy and Shi once again
thank you so much for the fun time today
in German we say in
byebye bye bye bye bye bye
bye merch is kill merch sales have ended
thank you for your support thank you to
everybody who bought the anniversary
watch guys love you
[Music]
you