[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
okay your local fox
is back
how are you doing how are you doing
how are you doing
there you go
yeah
[Music]
i got my cool hair again
yeah
let me fix it
[Laughter]
here
yeah no when i look up i don't quite
like it
a bit higher
no
it goes down so low
why did i do that yesterday
maybe
fixing the hair you gotta fix my hair
man to look good for you guys
that's tough
oh god damn it
i shouldn't have
shouldn't have fixed it it was fine
i guess it was fine no
here
no that's too sideways
how about here
no
[Laughter]
bad hair day
well i guess i'll just not look up
i guess
i guess i'll just not look up
but can we do it a little bit higher
how about here
oof
oof put a hat on yeah i gotta hide that
hair
nah yeah you guys probably don't notice
such a big difference anyway right
you can't
you can't notice when it looks like this
that's fine
it's fine i think
[Music]
what if i attach it here
oh
we can decorate my tail
if we wanted to we can put something
like a ribbon we can put a cute ribbon
on
i kind of want to do that gonna want to
make a ribbon right now
oh yeah i'll just keep it like that
extra tail fur i i can extend my tail
the fire like sharp bend yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah i wanna make a tail
wait a second
don't worry i got photoshop already open
i have my pen
should we what color purple
purple maybe purple maybe like the scarf
okay
ah
[Music]
let's do this
did you guys see uh
id second gen is getting new outfits i'm
so
excited oh my god i'll be honest with
you
i may or may not have already seen
reyna's outfit
not gonna say anything
but i haven't seen the others so
i'm excited
yeah baby
special treatment
well you know me and vana we like to
share things with each other
i i had her listen to my
upcoming song and you know
she
she um returns the favor
so indonesia
[Music]
oh new outfit is always so exciting
i wonder i wonder what they're going for
in general
okay the ribbon is
ribbon is getting there sorry
i want the cute tail ribbon okay
[Music]
yo
hey
you guys are welcome to make decorations
for my tale too
i'm sorry for the 30 minute delay
because i i was um
urgently cleaning my apartment because
it was turning
into a [\h__\h]
it was getting pretty bad
so i needed to clean it urgently i i
couldn't
i could not
take this anymore
especially considering that
um
i'll be gone for a while and then
somebody has to take care
of the apartment aka my cats
so i wanted it to
look somewhat okay
okay
i think um i mean it's not the best
ribbon it's not the best ribbon
would be nice to have a nicer ribbon
like a look like a ribbon with some lace
but i don't have the time for that now
okay okay that's good enough
export as png
tailor ribbon there you go
yes okay my cat likes to attack me
why
my cats would never attack me
they love me so much okay give me a
second
i'll put
the ribbon on my tail
[Laughter]
tail ribbon
[Music]
oh it's cute
so how does it this is where oh
my god it's so cute
[Music]
it's good
oh
cute okay
it works really well yeah yeah it fits
perfectly
except for when i go like here but oh
well that's because there's no layers
but that's okay
[Music]
okay now that we um are perfectly cute
i am gonna
oh it's so cute
oh
it's so cute okay now that we look like
this i think we can play the game
i've been looking forward to playing
some more
the cover unit
you
there you go
hey
and i have a sandwich before the streams
i think
i'm covered i'm good for a while with
snacking
but in case i need something i have some
maltesers with me
maltesers yum yum i've been snacking on
them for the past few days yum yum yum
yum crunchy chocolate balls yeah let's
go
but for now i'm good uh why is there a
black bar on the sides it's not only in
obs it's also here
oh well
and i think
i think i have a feeling we're gonna
learn magic this time
and maybe have some cool or a cool boss
fight
i have a good feeling
about that
so
we got pretty far last time at least in
my opinion we made good progress
and
made some good upgrades am i why am i
lagging you
[\h__\h]
am i lagging so much
hello you're good quinoa
unbelievable
the game um yeah maybe because i just
got into the game
okay
so we have um
four four flasks
some dynamite some you know that kind of
stuff
oh
but yeah i don't wanna
i don't actually wanna put it up there
oh well
[Music]
let's see that actually works
now hold it there for now i don't want
to accidentally use it so
yeah
fight like this remember to roll
remember
all good
so we stopped here yesterday
uh-huh i don't think we're done
exploring here but i got stuck somewhere
i think
oh yeah this one was pretty
pretty
strong actually i mean in terms of
health
yeah
yeah this garden is so pretty
it's so pretty here and not so many
enemies at least in this area
[Music]
also i think birthday merchandise
is gone now
oh yeah right you can walk here i forgot
there's damage today so thank you
everybody who got it
yeah it's um
it's over
now it's over oh no
i hope everybody who wanted it
was able to get it
and um you know meet and greets
uh decisions
will come
soon hopefully and then i think it was
september right in september we're doing
the meet and greet hey i know you again
okay okay okay
and it was fairly easy i think last time
we ran away from that thing that crazy
only takes two hits what
what
okay
then i'm not so scared anymore
maybe
what do we have here
i think i think we did not go here
uh
last time
so many alligators or whatever the hell
those are
[Music]
okay we need to get back into the groove
we need to warm up a little bit it seems
[Music]
enemies
no don't you dare
oh oh oh
oh that is shooting
what the [\h__\h] what [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] i
can't move
hey what just happened did you kill your
friend
oh my god come here
okay he's dead
did he just ice me
i swear did he just freeze me yeah he
did right
what
okay that's pretty dangerous can't let
that happen too often also can i get
over to that chest
no
gotta be careful
ice ice baby ice ice phoenix
also i have vitamin water with me i
don't normally don't normally drink
sports drinks or so but
i felt like it today you guys drink
sports drinks like on a regular basis
do you think it helps
the chops wow wow they're so hungry
so many holy [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
yeah i know my stamina i know i know
yeah
not only that but
uh just got let myself get hit too many
times because they're all chopping at
once
crazy alligators
if you guys saw you have another
keychain me i mean
i have i have so much long life
merchandise will have english but
to be honest i don't really like put it
anywhere besides in a cupboard because
you know
i feel like you know i can't put it on
my back i can't put it on my keys really
because like i don't want people
to see
same with the t-shirts and the caps i
wish i could wear the caps i would love
to wear the cats because i don't have
any other camps
ah but
that's the sad thing i have so many so
much merchandise and i can't really use
it but i keep it safe anyway so that
at some point when it doesn't matter
anymore
then i have
and i can't like because it's still in a
good condition i can show it
around i can be like hey did you know
that you know once once upon a time
i always kind of merchandise you don't
believe it look at it look
and then i can use it myself
yeah where did that go before what
ah right and then down
here
oh [\h__\h] that was stupid
i hate them okay i i officially hate
them
oh god come on just
go [\h__\h] yourself
i forgot to focus on these [\h__\h]
[Music]
that was so
unnecessary so unnecessary i don't want
to fight the the laser babies again i'll
wait there they come right out of the
wall oh
we can try to like
get a good break
yeah yeah yeah
try me try me
the problem with these is like you have
to kill them while they're so close to
you because i think like previously when
they followed us they were shooting us
from like pretty far away it's not like
they need to get close to you to attack
you so once they're far away it's really
like difficult to get them down take
them down
um
okay
[Music]
yeah jump on your dead body on your
friend's dead body
try are you too fat to come up here look
at him panicking
your friends were able to do it why are
you not able to do it huh
okay i'm pretty bad so far
i'll get better
today
[Music]
it was good yesterday what
happened oh
another one of those paths
oh chest hole
there's some water paths that are pretty
hard to see that they work what is this
carrot or
really
[\h__\h]
okay okay well [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
okay one down now this one just has to
come over here
would be nice
i'm gonna kill you please
[Music]
yeah it's okay
okay all is good
i'll be careful
[\h__\h] okay
okay now i i have i have fought you
so many times
right or left
it's all about improving yes
i will improve i will improv and then
probably everybody will prop when i
improve all right
you guys can't decide either oh there's
another chest there
how do i get there
i'm gonna go this oh no
it's a little [\h__\h]
i can't reach it
you [\h__\h] it's so unfair
i'm gonna die
oh does he have a shield
doesn't matter i'll ambush him
[Music]
come on come come come over
what i reflected it
come on come on come on
come on what am i supposed to do huh
[Music]
come here
if i could reflect that one at itself
[Music]
there we go okay hallelujah
it was about time ooh some more dynamite
oh we have seven now
that's pretty based
me
on nanako
[Music]
oh
my
there's one here
what a luxury
donkey chun
gladly taking that
i didn't expect that but that
helps a lot can we upgrade no
a thousand that's gonna take a while
one of these again
i've seen several of those but
this
can't go there
what is this weird futuristic metallic
cube
is it telling me about a new
whole live english generation huh
oh well for now i i don't think i can
reach it
[Music]
oh yeah right he's back okay no problem
it's good because i wanna
um get some money
i want to get some money so i want to
grind some enemies
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what am i
doing i'm gonna die i'm gonna die i'm
gonna
where am i uh
okay this is pretty bad it's pretty bad
okay
no no no
[Music]
[\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
that was stupid
but that was a big enemy wasn't it i
don't think i've had one of those before
[Music]
turn around for one second
but the thing is it doesn't really make
use of that moment
stupid thing
doesn't make use of that moment when i
am frozen
why does it not just reflect straight
forward
come here
there you go
what's the mukazu
skittle
hot damn i lived but what cost did we go
this way
gosh i'm out of flasks again
is this area clear now
it seems so
[Music]
there's a chest
i must be able to get there
[Music]
ah
but there's a wait there's a path below
and let's get there on a different way
okay there's a way up and there's a way
over here ooh
just got home from work straight into oh
hello
thank you for going straight
to me
that's how it's supposed to be
also good morning to everybody who's
watching in an early time how late is it
guys
what's the time what's the time
10 a.m to am
2 am oh
10 am
10 am 9
12 midnight midnight
a.m
9 00 p.m and 11 p.m 7 00 am 7 00 am oh
my god
[Music]
there's barely anyone in my time zone
and
where are my europeans
you know what i i know i know the the
big mean boy is going to come back but i
want to try again
it's good anyway for warm up so
i don't need to heal
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] did you see what i just did
again i still don't know really how to
activate that
i still don't know how how about
how did i do that attack with my shield
i still don't get it
oh it's some europeans thank you
i am european
what's that mean what does that mean
tap the block button
uh wait that's not what
ah
[Music]
double tap
huh take some stamina
must know
okay no it's just a really really slight
short tap but it's kind of hard to do to
do it
do we want to test it out hello friend
you're looking at me why why won't you
come over huh
can i get only one of the enemies maybe
only you perhaps
wanna come
no
no really
i see you're you're that kind of a guy
you need an extra invitation special
invitation
but that was a mistake
from you
oh what what
[Music]
you surprised me
at the worst try though oh oh oh oh what
you noticed me you're gonna come up all
the way here all right good that's some
workout for you
waiting for you
oh no he's still down there okay he's
gonna go crazy over my existence
[Laughter]
this game has so many treasure chests
holy [\h__\h] upgrade
what is this
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] oh okay i thought it was a
skeleton it was a rope oh wow where does
that one lead
ah shortcut and just
[Music]
first things first a berry
we still have yet to use any of the
berries but okay
nice shortcut
leads straight to
ah okay
nice berry
[Music]
nice berry i had some strawberries
yesterday but
even though i ate them the same day i
bought them and they looked fairly okay
looking at them in the supermarket
when i did a closer look
i realized
they were all pretty
[\h__\h] in a bad condition but oh well i
ate like half of them
that looked acceptable they were all
right
oh yeah right now
it has my color
[Laughter]
oh
holy [\h__\h] what
that's a lot
[Music]
moldy berries i know they were at least
not moldy but
oh
wait did i just fall down
did i just
did he just trip i saw his shadow
tripping
or am i tripping
no i'm here
oh i didn't know you could get there
from here
always test the edges
okay did i did i see everything now here
i went to the chest
okay
i think we're good
let's go back up i guess did i miss
something
no okay
okay what the actual [\h__\h]
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me what the [\h__\h]
no
hey
[Music]
how am i surviving this
so far
okay okay okay mistake
okay just kill me i don't care
oh
i almost did it holy [\h__\h] good first try
i wasn't even [\h__\h] prepared what the
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh
well now
i wasn't sure if i should use more bombs
because i was feeling i'm not gonna make
it anyway
ah
uh time for an upgrade please
i can take this one more attack oh
that's very good
yeah second try we can do it
not so bad i see i i already saw like
some of his attacks like he does the the
shooting
he does the the twirly and he does the
bunk
can i do another one
oh [\h__\h] no not like that that's not what
i meant
uh
i can do this but i don't know what it
is
well it must be something good right
what is that mermaid's feathers
sp
what's sp
sword power
[Laughter]
hmm stop stop
stop i got some stamina
oh
oh yeah okay
cool
cool okay
oh
well we got two upgrades
we've been strong enough a question
though is there a shortcut
so don't
don't want to
uh i don't want to lose any hp before
going there near the rope but was that
uh
was that straight ahead
i think it was
maybe i can go down
will he notice me
no
okay what if i go this way
okay
you are here
[Music]
nevermind
okay fight me here
[Music]
okay i will um just uh refresh again
what if i refresh this thing now
will i disappear
they do this a bit okay
yeah those buggers man there's a safe
point near the rogue yeah yeah yeah but
like hmm okay i guess i'll fight through
these first and
and then
oh we'll go to the save point and then
we'll go back for the rope okay
sounds like a plan
whoa did you see that i tried it but i
mean in that moment it was unnecessary
i just kind of wanna try i want to try
it out but not in an important fight
like a boss fight
i hate you so much
go [\h__\h] yourself
uh
do we have to go up first
up here and then down the rope
yeah see you later sucka
i'm gonna make it disappear
with magic
[Music]
here
eliminate it you never even existed in
the first place
okay
now
oh [\h__\h]
so many nights are passing by
it's gonna check i can't do anything
else okay okay okay okay okay just
checking just to make sure you know we
want to be this the best version of
ourselves that we can possibly be
you know always aspire to become a
better person
a better
version of yourself
i'm i'm only gonna use the dynamite
when i'm when i feel like i'm already
having a good run because i don't want
to waste them so
maybe only like if we're like halfway
through
young
okay eldon ring in cartoon version ikuzo
i'm nervous
i'm nervous but we're good i'm nervous
but we're good
[Music]
find me
oh oh circle ah
okay
good timing
yeah this is a bad run for example
yeah background okay let me do it again
no problem see i didn't waste any
dynamite that's good
but you can already get some hits in
before he even like starts doing [\h__\h] so
that's good
i gotta make use of that in the
beginning
where's my body where's my body
i kind of messed up
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] good
you can't even get close to me
i like it when he does that because he
only shoots straight
pretty easy
[Music]
i can't even see how much damage
foolish foolish
[Music]
ah
what the [\h__\h]
let's go
and where's my reward huh
[Laughter]
yeah
at the end i was too scared to mess up
because no more health so i just threw
some dynamite
but i think that was alright
how do you just get rid of something
oh well let's keep the stick there
i perform best and a lot of pressure
do i enjoy go back to save
why i don't think
boss enemies revive
it oh you mean maybe just to heal
they don't revive right
i guess yeah i can save
it won't respawn so
actually that does mean we can just
go back and
heal ourselves first
and let's see what's after that
stacking cheddar
yeah yummy cheddar
one of my favorite cheeses
out of all the cheeses
it's a magic item what
what
where
i want it
where's my reward
just money 200
that's a long path
oh oh but that does leave the area
go back
what what what you're telling me i could
have
used a magic item against the boss
monster
if i would have found it before going
here
that's not fair
i feel like i looked at everything
though
didn't i look at everything
oh wait wait wait wait we're not done
here
as always
[Music]
have you seen what i just killed over
there you really sure you want to pick a
fight of me the part-time hero of the
fancy hairdo
yeah
[Music]
there's a little cave area
oh it's a monster that didn't even
notice me i sneaked up to him
look at what i'm doing i'm so strong
holy [\h__\h]
can i go here
no wait i'm
i didn't go here maybe i didn't go here
[\h__\h] jumps man what does that remind
me of that reminds me of something
that reminds me of something
i think dogs
i think
i think it reminds me of some video of a
dog
oh you can go down here
why did i not go here first
if this is why then
[Music]
what is this
what what is that
[Music]
oh my god
oh
an ice stick
[Music]
i could have
who needs magic when you have skills
yeah sure but i could have used that on
the boss fight and even maybe
i could have even maybe done the first
stride and
gotcha
that might be useful though to shut up
those [\h__\h] flying
laser shooting
squares
when they're annoying me because the
reach looked pretty
big just now
really
[Music]
all right how much money
now we're gonna go
that one path now
because now i think
i explored everything right
i must have
you can perfect parry their shots with
the shield
oh
six hundred cheesecakes i can make one
big insane beak
insanely big cheese cube but that
the small ones are more fun
oh
the west bouncer wow oh my god the
second bell
we were so close last time holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
wow it's pulsating
amazing
she did that
pakanashi kiwawa did that now what
we rang the bells now what
yadi mastakido suzuki
what did it say in checklist at the
beginning
ring the bells i did i did ring all the
bells and i went to
all the places maybe did i go to the
flooded well
and then what do you do after that
maybe to the mountain to the sailed
temple maybe
open
open the big gold door i guess so
where are we now we're there okay what's
a fast way to get there maybe above yeah
go
past the dark tomb maybe
okay
yeah no one is here
oh shortcut
does that help me to get there now let
me drink some more water yeah that was a
fun boss fight but
thinking that we could have done it last
time makes me
a little bit triggered
yeah we finally just got magic but i did
not really get to use it yet
so
[Music]
the boss looked cool yeah it had cool
moves unfortunately it didn't have any
like second phase
i feel like that would have been
nice to have
but can i even pass by here no
[Music]
you have to walk around the right side
here
this time i take an easier boss
i think it was pretty damn good though
it was not just
maybe it looked too easy to you guys i
would say that was skill
pure skill
where am i going oh yeah
does this help me
can i get to the other side
down here
[Music]
i have the memory of a chicken what why
i'm trying to get to the door
i don't remember how to get there
i'm going a long way i just want to go
anyway
what about this way
was that anyway
oh could have been anyway
[Music]
ah that dude is here oh no
i ran
[Music]
where's the where's the big door
can i look at my map yeah okay
ah
we are now
ah okay we're getting closer i'm gonna
go down and then left and then up and
then right and then
yeah maybe or or or i go down and then
right
that should be possible down right and
then straight
nice give me those cheese cubes
[Music]
i don't want to find the green guy
can i okay was i supposed to
be able to walk past here
ah behind the
fountain i think it's possible
there we go it's not that end me
you just have to look around open your
eyes all the possibilities
[Laughter]
secret wait i i don't remember finding
the secret before
it's the third shop
oh no uh
huh
what
is this like a is there like a hidden
path here
is it a maze
ah yeah i think i no
oh
okay okay okay we're getting there
ah
i wonder what that is there must be
something really special
holy [\h__\h]
invisible secret crap oh my god oh
oh
oh oh 99
oh come on i kinda expected an item and
now i gotta walk this [\h__\h] path back
well 255 i guess it's we don't need the
money because the upgrades are really
expensive now
okay
see ya
see
tons of cheese yeah some blue cheese too
there was even a pink cheese
well i guess it was worth coming to this
side after all even though it was a dead
end
there's a reason for everything
guys
a reason and a purpose
for everything
now where do i go
see
like
here
there's a path in front of the waterfall
but that one's broken for me
which is weird so this is an old map
that's not accurate anymore
that path is gone
that path in the middle that one's gone
ah i guess we gotta go up and left after
all that's an outdated map
[Music]
no thank you
i wonder if those ever
like will be needed
at some point
we'll treasure chest down there
oh now we're here getting closer
yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes
here we are
i think
just gonna
say hi to
mommy
in stone stone mommy
one more time and now let's see
can we open this now
where are we i about to open this before
no right
i was pushing me away rude
[Applause]
what awaits us in here
[Music]
mommy sorry mommy
sorry
i made you a new tail ribbon with a bell
oh
did you put it in cave props or where
did you put it
is it a cute one
does it make ding ding sounds
wouldn't that be interesting
like imagine if live 2d
like um gets to a point where you can
connect certain sounds
with certain movements
like having
certain pieces of clothing make a
certain sound like level or so
and a certain movement and you know like
a bell
when you move like this make it ring
that would be holy [\h__\h] that would be
like
2.5 d
because you add
a certain aspect of sound to it
i could probably turn it off but that i
wonder if that's possible it sounds very
complicated
maybe
maybe lip smacking sounds i don't know
i guess you don't need them because
you're talking anyway
what could you do
i wonder what you could do with that
maybe for enos tentacles give it like a
slimy sound
[Laughter]
wouldn't that be hard to program
probably yeah
seen the dumbbell really like actually
like automatic or auto automated
or like self activated
sounds
i know indies can do it what
no way i bet ya was working on it i
don't think so i'm sure he has other
priorities right now
like getting everybody in the hole alive
uh
what was it called
the 3.0
because the only ones who have it now is
first gen
it's gonna take a million years until
ian first gen gets it
it's gonna take ages
don't wait for it
oh it's cute
[Music]
it is cute
a bell color for my tail
oh my god i have to try them
i have to try it on
[Music]
i'm becoming more and more of a cat
oh cute
cute the bell is quite big yo
maybe the bell should be on the other
side though to be honest because it's
going to be cut off a lot but maybe not
maybe not maybe it's fine this way
oh double ribbon
[Music]
why should we just do one more i don't
want double i think i want double ribbon
okay double raven let's go
to the town
[Music]
oh
did
good
but you see you can barely see it i have
to go pretty far to that side
[Music]
maybe kitty kitty
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you please make more
[Laughter]
maybe we can put
ribbons around my
ears
or ribbons around my ribbons from my
braids
i wonder if i can attach it let me try
something in theory
wait a second
i'll try
can i
oopsie can i smoothly
put it on
on my
braids
like if i were to
[Music]
maybe i have something ribbon like
already somewhere
a different kind of ribbon
oh
[Music]
no
oh
uh i guess i'll try the tail ribbon
okay
oh no no i moved to the wrong ribbon
okay let's put this here let's put this
there
let's bring this like this
i'm dressing up right now don't look
embarrassing
and this make it small really small
ah
can we make it move with my hair no
oopsie goddammit
um
want
okay i think i can
uh
at least show you what i'm doing now
i touched my scarf by accident let's put
it away for now see what i'm trying to
do i'm trying to put it here um
maybe if i look up
no
oh no
[Music]
i mean the size would still have to be
adjusted
but in theory i can do it oh [\h__\h] i got
it detached again
oh
then we can make like custom ribbons for
my braids
[Laughter]
oh
wouldn't that be cute actually i wonder
okay if there's any girls in here you
know what i'm talking about maybe easier
but imagine having um like you know you
know when girls put like ribbons through
through the whole braid
and then it ends up at the bottom but
you see it going through the strands of
the braids you know what i mean i wonder
if i can attach that
it might look really scuffed i mean we
can't do too much like super
super crazy stuff but one second let me
fix
some things i also want to try putting
it on my ear
make this bigger
and make it
ah
okay
oh cute though
oh
i did a cute thing
oh no needs to fix the scarf again
the scarf is difficult to
oh
see what i did with my ear
cute
but the scarf is [\h__\h] me up right now
i'm such a mess
for christmas i can put a little santa
beard on my face
genius
oh i think i got it okay we'll have to
do it's kind of high um
it's kind gonna apply
oh that works that works
not perfect but that works
this isn't even my final form
[Laughter]
oh wait i'm too big
okay i think that's about right
okay
uh oh yeah we're in here now okay
[Music]
ear raven adorable right oh my god lag
what is this
three
free something
free signs
and three foxes
nice music here
there are no secrets here
oh
there is never no secrets but
yeah that's nothing
what happened to all these foxes
whoa
what is that
[Music]
put something in here i suppose
okay i can't put anything in there right
now
that's for later
hexagons
[Laughter]
where the [\h__\h] am i oh oh i walked down
some stairs
yeah of course i take it
[Music]
hey three seconds
in front of the
big
thing
and then
yeah
a for three seconds
a
is a in my case x
or
wait what's a
it is x
okay right now it doesn't do anything
is that the praying thing
is that is that the praying thing that i
was waiting for
i feel like i tried that before and it
didn't work
who's this
ah exit
which exit wait but there's two exits
isn't there
is that just uh
wait no that was just one
i need to hold the button i was holding
it
but i guess i never tried it in front of
the big
uh
steel
square thing
the big steel brick oh now we're up here
around that
big building okay
dead end
what
ah no there's a chest
or something like that wait what
he looks ah it's hard to see what's
going on there
and now i got it
easy no damage kill
hello
so
where were those things like um we want
to try it
praying
in front of one of those right
let me try and see what happens
jesus cubes oops why am i
there you go
let me see can i see it on the map
[Music]
uh
i see
the
the fork but i don't see you i know i
see it at the very beginning
the very beginning and we're now at the
very top so we're gonna go to the very
bottom
the very bottom of the page there's the
the big thing over there
yeah
also can i go up there already
[Music]
that's leading to the mountain according
to the map
wow where's this place
cool
sick
i don't know if it's cold
or if it's
i guess that's snow is that supposed to
be snow it's kind of like
sandy too but i guess it's snow it makes
sense because we're in a mountain
i'm sure even if i go all the way to the
top there's nothing for me to do there
right
it's probably for late anyway
[Music]
oh there's something about the coins in
the well
two three four five
what there's a pattern
[Music]
oh wait i can still continue throwing in
more
huh
why is it
what
what did we get when we did that the
first time when we threw in three coins
what did we get the first time
[Music]
because we already threw in for free i
got us i got a space for the cards
okay
okay whenever i find more coins i'm just
going to continue throwing them in
but anyway uh so we have the the ring
explained up there uh it gives us death
uh-huh
and we could also get inverted ash a
lucky cup
and a muffling bell there's still so
many items to get you
ah and then
oh we can get so many slots actually
okay
what is this hints and clues
wow so helpful
[Laughter]
for your temple you need free keys okay
where are they
ah maybe it says go to the monolith
first
ruined a tall question mark
something with a crab
and then
what
oh yeah
[Music]
oh my god maybe that's why fubuki has
that
[Music]
checkpoint dead
old burying ground
[Music]
yeah
we can't do anything here but that's an
interesting page
[Music]
let's go back
he can go so fast in the snow and yo
also i want to look for secrets here
no nothing
[Music]
or is there something
no not really
i'm sure there's something here
there must be something
[Music]
somewhere
surely
check by the mountain door oh it's too
late i will surely come back here at
some point
and then i'll check
every little corner
i miss the path near the victor whatever
it's okay
it's all right we're gonna come here
eventually so
i need to oh my god
mm-hmm
i need to go all the way to the bottom
oh there's a chest here
nice
money probably no oh another berry
should i just keep all those berries can
you like use them later to craft or are
they meant to be for like singular
simple use um can you not camp right in
front of here please
oh well then i should use them like this
if i really need something
i really need some healing
there's no checkpoint inside
but right now i'm fine though
where am i
you're okay can i get to the bottom
from here
not really
ah no i probably can
just run down here and down here
i can make it home in time
are you going home now did you finish
work
what's going on here what is this by the
way
[Music]
did i just see yeah i saw there you go
it's also been popping up did i ever
enter here
yes okay
[Music]
yeah good luck today everybody
am i going the right way
now no ah it's over there on the right
side
okay up and right
and then
we should be able to get there finally
not here maybe
i wanna go to the big stone
that stones the big steel
statue thingy
wait i can't reach it
but see it's working
but i mean
not really but i can't reach it it was
there wait to get up there i don't think
so
let me know
ah
going down here
[Music]
there's a piece of paper there too oh no
i can't get over there but i can get a
chest so
[Music]
oh
where does this lead me
[Music]
i have a secret
why is this room
let's pray i'm just gonna pray at
everything now it doesn't do anything
how am i supposed to remember all these
secret rooms that i can't do [\h__\h] with
right now
for later when i can do [\h__\h] with it
how how am i supposed to remember it
looks like a puzzle eh but i can't do
anything with it now can i
[Music]
break them down i wish i could take
notes on the map
so that one is like close to the
monolith
thingy here
but
[Music]
oh yeah something but a big waterfall
behind it i think
yeah
yeah yeah
indeed
okay
anyway
that was
apparently
not something for now
however
we're gonna pray on this thing now
there we go
finally that does something
where are we in the afterlife once again
oh oh there's a piece of paper
table of contents really
a long long time ago
civilization
holy cross
did we have this before the power to
defy death
[Music]
holy cross
civilizations
question my question my question mark
mumma mummy lure
um
so
are these the pages that i already have
only or also pages that i'm still
getting i think we're still getting them
too yeah
memo
and let me write down something
why is that dlc huh
oh man the path is broken
oh but there's more over there
how do i get there
[Music]
oh the developers memo not mine
well they were more of the golden
platforms so i don't know what else to
do so we're just gonna go check out the
rest of the golden platforms i guess
where's the other one
[Music]
i know
okay
up and then if
possible and now here left okay we're so
close actually
okay i'll find you i'll do you the favor
and the honor
there you
go
warriors want to
die fighting anyway
it's the most honorable death for them
right
on the battlefield back in the medieval
times
see how i'm taking them all apart so
easily now
a piece of cake is what it is
[Music]
oh yeah
okay now let's finally quiet here
hey
we can
pray in silence
very religious fox i i i i
[Music]
same place but not really
okay
what the [\h__\h]
this is like in the ellen ring arena
the big sword
can i has no
what can i do
[Music]
can here pray at the sword
no
story
it is the sword from the title screen
indeed
okay wait i can also pray at this one
huh okay
i'm not even praying i don't even have
to pray
oh
where am i
uh
i don't see myself
i'm not on the map anymore right i'm in
the room at all
um
i'm here
i teleported myself
oh
i think that's where they wanted me to
go
we we've been here but only at the
bottom and i think then we got stuck
then we like had a dead end because we
went from the you know down here
down here we killed a blue bird
we walked around
now we're here
[Music]
desert level
can i see myself here now
do you guys see me
i don't know where i am am i not
supposed to be up here i don't know i
see me in the top middle
the icon of yourself is really hard to
find
the top middle there you go
okay
so we have an interesting map ahead of
us
it has four monoliths so i guess they
want us to pray at all of them
they do have numbers so i guess let's
try to go to the left one first and then
to the right one
since they have numbers why the hell not
why the hell not
look at that look at the crabs
don't really attack me
yes
but they're pretty weak
how deep can we go not very deep
oh but
we will have to
explore the water to make sure we're not
missing out any secret paths in the
water
or so many crabs the crabs are having a
crab meeting
they're having a
a crabinar
um a crap
vengeance
a rape
but there wasn't a pink one there was a
difference between the crabs right but
i'm not sure which one doesn't matter it
doesn't really matter the birds don't
like me
the boobs really don't seem to like me
that's all right
they they you know they don't realize
i'm actually a phoenix because my
disguise is just so convincing look at
those ears
[Music]
and the tail with a bell
it is convincing i forgive you for not
knowing
hold it
a secret path that's meaningless
[Music]
oh
i don't want to freak you guys out so
much
they're funny i like them wait
that's the wrong one
oh
oh they look scary
hey we want to go to the top left one
actually
oh no
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
and they're down i have become too
powerful
wait that's one of them
since the maps are outdated
could it possibly be
that the monoliths are not actually
where they
say they are on the map
wait
no we just saw one of them
but here's also a piece of one of those
maybe that's something else
and i want to go
ah there's a shortcut there for later
how do i go to the
left one it doesn't quite show me
wait there's a big ass chest right there
let's go there
so there's a big fat burp sitting on it
but that will be
nothing to stop me
[Music]
the chest looks special to me
could be wrong
it looks special
yo
come here
oh [\h__\h]
interesting
yeah
okay no the chest is not so special
after all
for some reason it looks special to me
oh but we get an item that we didn't
have before mushrooms
is that a single item to
uh to heal
stamina and magic power maybe
because it's blue
i'm guessing
berries heal hp
no
hey never mind no no no no no no no
they're over here well that's probably
just to upgrade magic power though to
have more magic power to begin with
okay
mommy sorry mommy i pray
doesn't do [\h__\h] okay
let's go this way
no i only have the ice wand right now
and it took me a damn while to get it
and i didn't even get to use it much
i should have gotten it before the boss
fight that's so mean
[Music]
oh
the door is barricaded
i found an opening
but i also want to check
what's here nothing
okay
understand
what this [\h__\h] is leaking
it's broken
never saw it leaking before oh there's a
big freaking crab over there
looks cute
but is that a boss monster
out so out in the open i doubt it but
oh
but we don't have a slot for it do we
what does it do
no we do have a slot do we
no you don't
what does it do
wait
um
if we get a hint of what it does
no it's not
it's on it's one of the bottom right
ones but
it doesn't really tell us what it does
makes your body explode bigger
oh when i revive myself
okay you you might want to use this only
when you're dead and you're walking up
to your dead body
so
switch it out
at those times so now it's kind of
unnecessary
[Music]
cool
interesting
don't know if we'll need that so soon
but yeah okay that's it here
there's no way to go any further there
can we go to the big giant crab
not that i necessarily want to
[Music]
but i'll take it apart and then i'll
serve it to cali
sideways it's so cute
oh
lovely lovely
it reminds me i really need to get my
aquarium going
i've been waiting on some things
to do that yeah
the good thing is i can make it so that
it auto feeds itself that's an option
so then i don't have to worry about it
when i'm traveling but i still have to
worry about my cats so not that it
really makes a difference to be honest
yeah fancy i'll get one of one of those
um blue
crayfish
excited
this is so the color is so beautiful
they stand out so much
[Music]
definitely saw that
new enemy
i surprised you didn't i
but when he bounces when you hit them
it's funny
birdman no no no no was it a frog man
it kind of looks more like a lizard
we can go down or we can go this way oh
is that
oh
okay
i guess we have to go down is that the
frog place
it could be should i be here because
there's all these
all these thingies for the grappling
hook but i'm not supposed to have a
grappling hook yet right
maybe that's what maybe i get it inside
here and then it will make it easier to
go back up
perhaps
aquarium is the other feeder for the
cans
two birds with one stone yeah
yo so far the frogs have yet to get a
hit on me
kinda weak
but what what
i hear something
glowing [\h__\h] it
well i can't even kill you from here i
don't think i'm
yeah i need a grappling hook to get
anywhere here oh my god thank you eodin
i want the bucket back
the game looks cute is it difficult but
everybody told me it's difficult
but i don't know
i'm actually
not struggling that much with it
i guess i'm lucky this time
does anyone know if i get the grappling
hook in here
or if i should not waste my time here
and go somewhere else later
now and come back later when i have the
grappling hook
because this looks like it's made to be
for the grappling hook you get it here
okay okay so it's literally just for
getting up easier later on once you have
it okay okay
then i shall proceed
hook shot or whatever frog's domain
[Music]
oh a frog onsen frog hot bath
it's lagging i'm lagging
oh my god stop lagging
frog spell
killing them
while they're bathing
what movie does that remind me of
[Music]
weak
game of thrones did that happen in game
of thrones
[Music]
i don't think so that was
something else
every slasher movie slasher
what is that
oh
wait what is that creepy ass ceremony
let's go he's looking is he looking at
me
oh [\h__\h]
yeah he's looking at me
i'm not here
you can see me for the wall
this place is screaming
[Music]
why
magical mythical
maybe i should change my disguise to
looking like a frog so they accept me as
one of their own i can't even talk their
language so
this is a cult oh yeah it does look like
a cult
first like this is a cult
interesting here you would think there's
a secret but there's not so it's too
obvious
what is that eye
what is going on here
are they trying to assassinate him
is this like
or are they having a discussion
[Music]
oh i need i need a crack grappling hook
let's go this way
[Music]
he left the room for a moment why is
that you do
frog statues or
alligator statues
of the right we're gonna go this way
[Music]
there's a chest
you reveal the secret
investigator actually before the stream
while i was cleaning
i was um watching the city skylines vlog
from amen
just on the side i wasn't like 100
paying attention most of the time
but i liked i liked the city that she
built the shape the curved shape around
the lake
yeah yeah yeah nothing makes me want to
play more city skylines on my own too
so we played it for our members only
a while ago
it was a good design yeah
yeah it was pretty good
well they remember this week perhaps
yeah
could happen
i want it to happen because there wasn't
one last week so
i'm gonna try i'm still thinking
uh how this week will turn out a lot of
things are undecided so
i'm just gonna go with the flow
hope that's okay for you guys
before i go that way i go this way
oh my
oh my my
watch along yeah i think
even if i do it from korea
i do have my extra screen
and we could maybe probably do a watch
long yeah
and to be honest that might be the best
option at
uh during my trip for a member stream
it's gaming
i don't know
i mean i have a gaming laptop but you
know
um i'll test out some things we'll see
how it goes
less things to go wrong yeah
and we haven't had one in a while so i
think it's fine to do one
more berries
[Music]
no no
secret that field would be fun
garfield
yeah i wonder did i never watch that on
my own
i don't
think i did
oh that's connected oh
i must sleep now good night thank you
for coming
please no why not
was it bad
he's strong was he kind of strong he
felt stronger
you know what i wanna maybe try out one
of the berries
[Music]
oh that heals quite a lot
not yellow dog
[Music]
i mean that maybe wasn't necessary
because i still have all of my flasks
but
just felt like it
cats is way worse
it's so bad it's funny but is it
worse than cats i doubt it
why are all cats related movies bad man
do cats some justice please it's not
fast
you're gonna make people hate
unreal cats just because uh just because
all cats movies are bad
[Music]
it's you know not what i personally
think but just what the general opinion
is okay
now the combat now is way smoother than
in the beginning of the stream today
gotta go
get used to it yeah warm up
anti-cat propaganda
eraser cats is good
lion king that's not necessarily cat
related but i guess so lions
you know what i mean like proper
domesticated cats
[Music]
man
you can even lick me what the [\h__\h]
yeah a bit
back to the frog spa
but now i'm not wasting my time with
that
got no time for a bath
i have to keep on moving moving
i want my
hook shot and i want it now
can't wait any longer
but we haven't had a death in a while
you know
every once in a while
[Music]
what should we talk about guys there's
something to talk about
[Music]
for now
the meaning of life
my dinner yesterday
oh i ate burger king
very happily i ate my beloved crispy
chicken
two year round oh my god they're coming
up soon on you
oh no no with no oreo shake but now you
make me want to have one
[Music]
you're moving oh my god i'm just like
prisoners
[Music]
that was the first time in a long time
that we had those enemies so completely
oh gore
[Music]
did you see that canada cosplay in
others other people's meeting greens
yeah yeah she actually wasn't my meeting
grade two but on that day she wasn't
cosplaying but she told me she was gonna
cosplay the the following day and i was
like i'm gonna keep an eye on um an eye
out for you
and then i did see her in the audience
during the panel so i was happy
yeah
she was like in the front row hmm
yeah yeah
mmm
hope the burger was tasted yeah it was
good
had a lot of salad in it
and then uh what was i gonna say oh i
can tell you something embarrassing
from today
um i'm ashamed
oh wait i should maybe heal with them
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my god
there we go holy [\h__\h] that was
unnecessarily
mamma stupid
and now we have berries we can use them
that was close
those were they were strong right yeah
i have a
a long weapon
nicer
[Music]
secret
no secret
a lot of things here make me think
there's a secret but there's not
bamboozle oh my cheese cube
give me that cheese ah secret here maybe
oh
well
then i have access to that already
before
that's kind of a shortcut to those
enemies
then
oh there's
oh it's just stairs here too okay
kind of disappointing
airport reveal i'm not gonna get myself
airpods hell no oh that's not the
embarrassing thing yeah so um
there's this one
official recording
uh
that
you know i need to do that keeps on
being delayed not because of me but like
you know one one time is oh the schedule
change uh this person can't make it this
person can't make it leave a blue
or this person is sick and so on
and
golden door open right there
and so
you know we had a
recording
set for today
six am my time
uh
i was like oh man when i said that i put
it in my calendar i was like oh man six
am you for real
every time
official recordings are
oh
very very often at 6 00 am for me
made some shortcut again
yeah no but the thing is
this one
just this morning
when we were supposed to be recording i
guess
i got the notice that it was being
delayed
which is great because
i didn't see it until like 10 am because
i actually
forgot to set my alarm i didn't see it
in the schedule because it's up so high
because it's at 6 00 am
and i would have always left actually
for the first time in
ever for a recording like that
i would have actually overslept and i
would have been so
terrified because like you know what
happened i i opened my eyes at some
point because this movie was like
and then
i look at
my phone to check the time and when i
open
the the screen
it's like
i don't i don't think i want to go here
first do i
no
it's like it gives me like a
notification
for the recording and i'm like oh yeah
wait [\h__\h] is that today
[\h__\h] if that's today that i just missed
it and it was
i was
really scared of opening discord you
know i was expecting messages like kiwa
kiwawa you awake hiwa hello kiwawa
but nothing
so i
i look and look and look
and then
i see the message
itself involved i see the message that
it has been delayed and i'm like
thank god
oh he stopped
[Music]
okay i tangent it for too long
apparently and now it's gone
now done
okay i guess we have to go here
delayed before the record you know like
i don't know i think probably like
an hour before the recording or so
oh no really close to the recording it
was delayed
and i was really happy actually
oh
hey alert
oh no i kind of wanted to attack the
other things with that
no
yes okay
couldn't have gotten any better than
that
the problem is i don't really have
any hp i guess i'll eat another berry or
would be nice if there was a statue
close by
should i
heal myself
with the berry where is this gonna go
a shortcut another shortcut that's good
so we created two shortcuts already
now we're in this room
[Music]
could go down but
maybe the best thing to do is to go back
to the bath
maybe one of the shortcuts will help us
with that
where does this lead
oh that could yeah perfect absolutely
perfect
come becky
a chest what a chest
[Music]
where
not here right
[Music]
you mean even before oh i should upgrade
oh yeah
no the one in the green water i was
standing in front of it it wouldn't let
me open it maybe we have to drain the
water
because i was waiting for the prompt the
a button prompt but nothing happened oh
[\h__\h] not that
this okay uh
that's probably magic power
but
rather than magic power
[Music]
attack or
ocean or hp
or attack and hp
[Music]
i think i want to attack an hp for now
i always do this
uh
yeah hp
we can do magic power then too yeah
get the small ones higher before we go
to the big ones i guess guess like
overall stronger than just making one
thing stronger
yeah
and then here this one
[Music]
today yeah apparently it's international
cat day too bad i'm a fox today
[Music]
okay oh yeah we got a lot of hp
noise yo it's all now we're ready for
whatever comes wait
that did not only give us more mp it
also added a charge to the ice
weapon
didn't it
i think so
nice
okay
i wonder if we're gonna fight all of
them
or just
because what the hell is going on there
it looks like yeah something was stolen
they took it
the ones that are like oh the group the
group took it probably because they look
like people who would steal something i
mean
look at their cape
we're gonna kill them and save the dude
and he will give us the grappling hook
shot
that's probably what's going on but
that's still a lot of people maybe i
should use
can i throw it from the top
would that be reckless would that be
foolish
i feel like it could work but
i know i fell down
um oh he's helping me he's helping me
he helping me
no he's not
they're all attacking me
[Music]
and i wasted the dynamite
i thought i thought you know he would be
helping me because i'm helping him
[Music]
that's kind of rough there's like
so much to deal with
and they get a head start because i
i
fall down
he looks like a cult leader oh maybe
[Music]
yeah the mage keeps on like bumping me i
don't really have like
space and time but we'll be we'll we'll
get it right we'll get it right
no
okay
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
yeah um
what the [\h__\h]
i know i should have used my eyes but
also the ice takes a lot of time there's
like a delay once you activate
um it takes like about two seconds like
he charges it
so in that time i i'm gonna like like
previously the first time i tried it i
get attacked while i'm charging the the
weapon
run past them and take it
oh
should i do that
is that foolish
it's foolish ambitions to try to
huh you're trying to kill them kite the
enemies
right are you kidding me
[Music]
i want more hair ties
oh thank you
i won't put them on now but let me check
cute
[Music]
oh
nice
thank you
maybe for tunic part 2 or so
part three or so i don't know or even it
doesn't need to be too weak but thank
you
what
this might work
i don't know what's going on but oh [\h__\h]
oh my god oh my god
oh my god i'm doing it
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] i kind of thought i that that was a
bump i kind of knew it
oh my god
i felt like
somehow
it might actually be what they wanted to
do to actually steal it and then just
run away
because it is pretty tough
and then the start was not good because
i was bugging around
holy [\h__\h]
is that a grappling hook
what
interesting it's like a magical
grappling hook but jot them up
damn it too late but
i wanted to explore more oh well
hopefully i didn't miss on anything
important
oh
oh nice
oh you can go pretty far
[Music]
hmm
ah can i
attach myself to you
yeah oh go away
[Music]
that's not good that's not good that's
really that's
good need healing
i need healing
i need feelings
but exciting we finally have the
grappling hook that opens up so many
doors
and now we're going down but then i
still want to
do something there though
i feel like we still need to
i'm not satisfied because there's
there's still
some things
[Music]
let me go back
no but i can't go back from there
what was the other way to get down
that one chest
maybe you can like get it out of water
with the grappling hook i wonder if that
works
[Music]
foreign
hello
i should be back i think
[Music]
sorry obs i had a hiccup
but we're back we're safe all good let
me try the grappling hook on enemies
it works i'm like a frog though it makes
so much sense that you get this item
here now because they have the same
thing they can do it with their tongue i
can do it with a grappling hook
oh i like how you're actually really
able
to like fight the enemies even when
you're like in between two doors
respect
because that's not ooh
oh okay
for you
that's not always uh possible in other
games
oh secret
secret chest
see it's good that we're coming back to
explore
oh it's just a berry
okay uh was there something here that we
can raise with the grappling hook
something special
[Music]
was there something here
i'm not sure i don't think so
oh i'm happy you love me but no need to
spam it or was that a mistake
did the youtube chat lag for you what
nice
damn it
that's grappling hooks too but
[Music]
it doesn't
is there a secret there
oh there is
hey
it's a private onsen room and
a piece of
um
flask
hp potion
voice
okay
finding all the secrets
you're welcome to use my stream as a
guide to get for the game
now we have to go
for the whole overworld a second time
too because
there were so many grappling hook spots
everywhere
i don't want to fight those enemies a
second time though cause that was a pain
in the ass
unless
i could probably
bring them up here one by one
or maybe even like
on that no it focuses on the grappling
hook though
but if i go to
over there
that dude will cast magic on me though
and the frogs could use their tongue
to get me
possibly
and i i can't i see let me try
[Music]
i can't change targets but
what if i do this
now everybody attacks me
[Music]
let me run back to the um
and also the other ones are all just
back in normal position but he's still
casting magic on me
calcium soft
[Laughter]
he's got his eyes everywhere
everywhere oh my god i wish i had a
vision like that
oh
okay so we're going down because there
was a chest there i guess oh look at the
bucket
also
okay
[Music]
oh he saw me
it's a party
uh
go back
okay
okay let's see
can we
i can't focus on the chest still i guess
it's just decoration
unless there's really a way to drain the
water that i don't know about
oh wait i was on the wrong
side was on the wrong side
okay free die in the night nicer
i couldn't see it clearly come on
it was hard to see on which side i was
okay uh what else
oh yeah
where did that shortcut lead to also so
this is uh
all empty now
already showing yeah because i have it
now
i have your treasure
and i will never give it back cause i'm
gonna use it for something good
i'm not sure yet
i wanna go over there see there's
another twist
i'm not sure yet for what oh can i focus
on the enemy let me focus on the enemy
oh you guys
so maybe from here
oh it came from the frog bath
fine with me but did i ever try going
from here
i did it
oh you still have
not enough of me you want me to join
your frog bath yeah
more dynamite
oh they probably give you a lot of
dynamite here because
like at least this one you can already
get before the grappling hook so it
would help you
like for the fight to get the grappling
hook
kind of a hidden wall but the rock kind
of gave it away
okay i think
i think we can go now
oh come over here
let me fight you
[Music]
well i guess we're not ending that fight
feisty frogs yeah
i said i love frogs but this kind of
makes me want to rethink my opinions
because they're not doing a good job at
and
creating a good image of themselves
[Music]
i want to focus on oh i can't
no i don't want to focus on the enemy i
want to
yeah
oh there we go oh maybe i can
change subjects
maybe i can
i think i might
yeah
took me a while to realize that sorry
[Music]
okay i would like to leave this place
now
[Music]
hey
okay i'll just go up from here
oh maybe you know what i'll refresh here
a little refresher is necessary
[Music]
oh
just another point of view but
there's nothing to do here okay
okay yeah
[Music]
okay
dimension into this domain is complete
hell yeah
serving frog legs
soon at kfp kiana fried
[Music]
canna frog
kiana frog
[Music]
yeah frog piano fried frog with ph
actually i guess that kind of works yeah
oh
where were we here before i guess that's
just a different
uh way of entering no
right
okay
this is how we entered
i think so
but should we escape from the different
ah now i will be fine
is it fine should i go from a different
way
hello
i have the grappling hook now i'm so
powerful oh my god all the possibilities
yay
all the new places we can go
[Music]
oh wait we're at one of the
monoliths but it's not number one is it
okay does it really matter i wonder
does it really matter
doesn't even matter
i'm just gonna pray
amen baby hallelujah
yes jesus you hear a strange hug that's
the first one i've ever uh activated
what what now
it doesn't turn into like a warby
platform i guess you just
nothing happens
okay
one down how many to go
three
at least here
[Music]
oh i can use those now too
pretty versatile i must say
oh
not bad
we can hang on to enemies
and those forks
and the obvious hook shot
thingies as well
drop
strong wobble
oh [\h__\h] i made a mistake
okay so go here
[Music]
and then
ah see okay this is how
i can switch between them can i go this
far
no okay so i have to go here
cool cool cool yeah chad is dead
chad is falling asleep oh my god
[Music]
the bird is looking at me
ganging up on me
they're scared because i can one hit
them now
come on wait can i grappling hook oh
you too
my friend you too
yeah
i'm invincible now
so you're soggy kiwama
that sleeping is enjoying thank you
[Music]
it's okay everybody's chilling i'm
chilling too
i'm having a good time chilling
in this game
but everybody's enemy for me yeah
i still don't know what those things are
the the ones that um
the glowing stones that come out of the
exploded monsters oh dear
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] the way that exploded
kind of insane
wait why is there
eight charges at my
grappling hook
book shot i don't know what to call it
that was a crazy blast yeah
yeah what why why why why
why was that one so particularly crazy
big
it uses magic when you are on enemies
oh
i have to keep an eye out on that
i have yet to notice that
i want to go around oh wait i can i can
go from here
[Music]
and there you go
yeah today my fruit is kind of not doing
well weird
maybe my room is too dry or so
but
it shouldn't be
nice for so dark blue because there's a
secret room where you can change looks
and i found it even though it's hard to
find yeah i'm so proud
hey
oh [\h__\h]
i feel so powerful i love it
um
cleaning always ruins me afterwards
yeah i don't think it was the cleaning
but oh that's a bomb that's a bump i'm
not
gonna play around with that don't play
with the fire
no no no
what is this thing though
just the leftovers of an enemy
disgusting
ah oh now we can
is that because it's broken here
oh it's making some weird sound too
you
know i'm also like
dead
where's my hp
wait what happened with my hp
it produces how long how am i gonna get
back
do i have to go to a checkpoint to get
it back
what the [\h__\h] well in that case i wanna
check out what's past that it can't kill
me right
yeah okay
let's get the chest once and then get it
over with
what the [\h__\h]
i can ah
i won't reach
hey give me back my hp
i'm kind of far from a checkpoint that's
pretty inconvenient
[Music]
oh wait now i can open this door oh then
maybe it's not so far away after all
because now
we have a shortcut
and let me go once i guess
was it close
not really
not that close
but i'll do it
i want my hp back now
are you trying for full completion now
but um i'm finding so many secrets
there you go there's my hp i'm finding
so many secrets without even going for
um full completion so
it's happening naturally
and i must say i'm quite proud i'm
pretty good
at this so far
my eyes
oh okay wait so maximum charges for the
hook shot is 10 it seems
okay
okay okay okay
come here
should have done it with the hook shot
now with the
i thought eyes ice was smart
and that they never expected to be
frozen by a phoenix is an unexpected
skill for me to have
you know what i used today for the first
time
because i was cleaning i did i tell you
i got myself
i'm here again i got myself one of those
steam floor cleaners
you know what i mean
hot steam floor cleaners
sounds fancy no it's a cheap one though
and i'm not sure like
how effective it actually is
i tried it and
i don't know it felt like it was working
but
i'm not sure
[Music]
yeah but there's there's like hot steam
coming out of the thing and you
you
mop the floor with it basically
kind of cool
[Music]
steam for floor yeah yeah it's good for
like wooden floor i guess
where do we go now what the hell uh
we've been here before was there like
something for the hook shotgun
scene goes for cloves only oh yeah
ah why are they not stopping
i thought okay you block them they get
stunned and they stop but it didn't
happen
okay y'all are getting on my nerves at
this point
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
getting mad here
yeah not a deep carpet cleaner it's one
for like actual flooring what was that
did you see that at the bottom left it
was like a spider made out of light
oh and that dude he's hiding there
he didn't expect it and he tries he goes
back
[Music]
what
he didn't expect direct confrontation
like that and he seems to really want to
protect something here
what
that's how you obliterate him oh wine
glass
nanny
nanny what does that one do
does it make me drunk
what was there an explanation to that
it's not even written on here oh
it doesn't even exist on this menu
then i guess i shall find out myself or
there's even more on page 51 which we
don't have yet
secret wine skill
what could it be
what could it be no no no
no
um
attack up defense down
attack of defense down
oh because you're drunk ah i feel like
that kind of makes sense yeah
i'm not really drunk but maybe that's
just a way to
put it into an icon
i'm not sure if i want that right now
uh
let's go back to
the normal lineup
oh
oh you could get there from here now
okay but uh yeah he was definitely
protecting something cool
something that is worth protecting
[Music]
oh hello oh big boy
come here
oh let me take care of you but not if
you bug into the stone that's not fair
that's not fair that's not fair
that's
honestly not fair
no that's not fair where the [\h__\h] did he
go anyway hey
no i can play the game too
i told ya
okay i don't i'm not even gonna blame
him for bucking into the stone because
i'm the one who brought him down here in
the first place even though he was up
there that's all right
you want to come down too
[Music]
yeah that's what you get
for being a frog
not that there's anything wrong with
being a frog i love frogs
anyway yeah steam cleaner so i have more
equipment to clean my apartment now i'm
trying to keep the
keep the floor
clean or make the floor clean
somewhat
but
i don't know if it was worth getting it
i feel like
i feel like it wasn't worth it
i regret
i know well
why not i guess why not it's also kind
of exhausting to use it because it needs
a lot of strength from my body
towards close oh
really one of the tallest i guess it's
up there yeah i see it but first i go
for the secret
[Music]
huh
where am i going
[Music]
what
are you telling me there was a path here
[Music]
shortcut
unbelievable
wow
you know on twitter yesterday and
replies a lot of people told me like oh
i've been playing too many but you found
not a lot maybe two people told me i've
been playing tuning when you find more
secrets than i do
i'm very attentive in two week it seems
get down
[Music]
doesn't really help me though
but we found the second one we can pray
at it now
um
[Music]
that is two out of four that is if
there's really still four standing
because i saw a few broken ones at least
i felt like i saw them but maybe they're
not
actually broken maybe that's something
else
will that also drain me if i come too
close
what the [\h__\h]
yes it does
oh the air okay um what the [\h__\h] should
i risk it anyway and check it out
because like before we got the chest for
that but like i can't go down right
that wasn't here before was it really
not
yeah
i guess not i would have noticed right
oh yeah because we were in that room
did the impact of me
praying break this thing
i'm turning him on
because the pipe is broken
[Music]
no because um that that was probably
already broken the path but
you know when i when i made this thing
go down
maybe the liquid started flowing or so i
don't know
well
okay how do we get to the other two
assuming that there still are two
more i don't know
are there still two more
[Music]
activate the tower down there too tower
[Applause]
[Music]
breath of the wild kind of [\h__\h]
maybe i am done here
i have to go to the middle
in the calamity step or leak or in lake
[Music]
oh we were not here before i think
yeah we didn't oh that one was easily
accessible sorry i'm not gonna kill you
don't worry oh my god but these things
may kill you
[Music]
wasted
uh
oh come on
[Music]
okay okay okay you're making me mad
okay okay
[Laughter]
those [\h__\h]
[Music]
these monsters they really love cheese
don't they
you'll pay for that
wait
we learned about this secret shortcut
i'm taking it
well maybe maybe i was not necessary
[Music]
i'm gonna have the rod i don't know what
rod you mean i have the ice thing i
guess i could have tried using that one
too
hmm
[Music]
anyway let's try it
i was fighting
something impossible i was fighting a
glitch
okay i'm good i'm good i'm safe
hooray
let's fight this dude again just to
bully the [\h__\h] out of him
as long as he won't attack me while i'm
passing by
i will leave you to your business of
protecting an empty
okay now it's not funny
you little shits
[Music]
i was saying he was protecting an empty
no
no no i'm not gonna survive this
[Music]
no words have no words this
i know i know panic this is this is me
when my kitchen was on fire
sorry
maybe maybe this will help you
end your suffering
okay
do they want to
come out or now okay well then i'll just
pray
amen
[Music]
what else are we breaking now ooh
look we did something there i do want
the chest though how do i get the chest
also oh you see they're like uh one of
the right is not lit up yet i'm lighting
them up
diagonal ones oh now it's leaking there
ew
you yavina i feel like i'm not helping
with the environment right now
i'm very sorry
mommy
can i go diagonal from here
[Music]
yeah am i helping the world on my
damaging the world
[Music]
it's depleting even when i'm just close
by
how do i get
out of here it's dangerous
if it spreads in the whole ocean and
everywhere i go it will hurt me
see is it safe to go
i can go here right
okay let's get away from here
run away
the bird is white wait boys it's still
blue and it's just a lightning
no that one is
white maybe it gives me some special
oh it is blue it is blue it's just a
lightning okay never mind
oh those three statues have glowing eyes
now i mean i'm assuming that this one
also has glowing eyes we just don't see
it so there's one left over there
oh and we can go with the grappling hook
from here
the hook shot
[Music]
what a rack made out of hair strands
make a good filter for oil spills it
absorbs it effectively and economically
thank you that will come in handy when i
have to fight a huge orcs oil spill and
have so much hair
left for some reason
that i can rip it all out and make a
rag out of it
that is very interesting knowledge what
the hell
oh a big crab let's fight you
oh
oh probably explosion no what
that was three hits really that was
nothing
you for real bro
they're all you got to offer
i thought that would be stronger
and now we are here
can i
am i going up
where am i going i'm just going around
the side
i haven't reached it eventually
yeah i also thought it might be some
kind of small boss
i guess not but it looked cute i feel
bad for killing it
you know what i have been improving
recently
you know for the longest amount of time
i didn't have a dining table
so i told you guys right that i eat
i confess that i eat on my bed
[Music]
a lot
there's another one
now that i have the dining table even
though it's shaking and rumbling
i'm using it i'm eating dinner and
breakfast and stuff on the dining table
you know i thought that even if i get a
dining table i'm probably not gonna use
it much so i only just really got it
because i thought when i have guests
over like my family my mommy and so on
it would be nice to have a dining table
[Music]
uh but i didn't think that i myself
would use it
[Music]
but
yeah i'm actually using it and i enjoy
sitting on it but the um the only real
reason
why
it's more
[Music]
endurable for me it's because i also
have my ipad there ready for using it
while i'm eating so i definitely always
need something to watch
because my tv is in my bedroom
so when i when i eat something i want to
watch something
so normally
i always had to go
to
uh my bedroom
to eat
but now
now i have the ipad and the dining table
yes
i finally sit by my dining table when i
eat
yeah no no bugs no i don't spill [\h__\h] on
my bed
i'm careful okay
but
yeah
it's better now
and i think my dining table is pretty as
you saw you know it's that kind of like
white marble look or something like that
i don't know if you could call it marble
is that a marble aesthetic i guess so
if we break something again if we spill
something again doesn't look like it
this time
yeah anyway
so i'm more sophisticated now
oh of course you show up now
oh no no no no pulley please
um
oh they killed one of their friends okay
cool
keep on doing that
[Music]
i don't want to waste all my charges
either
oh [\h__\h] that was useless
okay there we go finally wasn't there
one more
i guess it
i guess it died somewhere
funny okay much do i have oh we have
over a thousand again let's go
fight in large ground bus run
is there gonna be another boss fight
i don't know if i'm mentally prepared
for that but okay
we have to oh the music is so chill wow
all the drones dead hallelujah
[Music]
oh that's so nice
so now we activated everything i'm just
gonna heal myself once and then we can
um
think about
what to do in the middle we probably
have to pray again
will i just let me pass by normally yes
i'm gonna kill the bird again i guess
maybe we can get another upgrade even
let's see
[Music]
it's an old beyonce song that i really
liked oh can we we can lift it oh
a shortcut on this side now
boys
[Music]
this game is more souls born than zelda
but i don't think zelda wants to be like
a souls game
okay
now what will happen
in the middle
what's gonna happen when i pray
are we gonna summon a big boss fight
or a shrine or what could it be
bert get out of the way now
this is not a place for you
oh my god
what is this what what we just do it's
going back
other wait do i have to do it longer
oh maybe i have to do it longer it's a
longer ritual i thought it was over
no it just closes itself
walking's oh before it go okay
[Music]
okay i'm in
don't hurt me
[Music]
question my question question
somewhere in the sky
very up
high my god
are we ready for this
do i pray again
oh no maybe i go around here
[Music]
hello camera angle
wait
i just remembered
you know that key that i saw at some
point i didn't get it i never got it
remind me when i leave this place
to get that key
what
ah
it's a library or something like that or
maybe just somebody's home
[Music]
oh interesting it's so big
it's not made for foxes maybe not at
least for small foxes
[Music]
a great library huh
can i kill you
no
what
it follows me
[Music]
you're my pet now
can i do something with you
you're stuck
well feel free to follow me maybe i need
you to like stay somewhere i have a dog
a table dog
[Music]
hey
what the [\h__\h]
can you be my shield move move what is
that thing they will attack me if i go
there right
[Music]
oh there's another one
oh it run away
you're scared uh you're sick of
following me
no you just don't gotta go past that
point huh okay
[Music]
can i
wait maybe it's not an enemy because
i can't focus on it
oh it's not an enemy oh because the eyes
were glowing i thought it was alive
oh
wait
it's one of those uh
fox child statues a sad one a grave
what happens
oh i'm gone again
whoopsie
here was grave ah
[Music]
what is this
what can i do
nothing
i don't think i can do anything
end the game okay
[Music]
okay let's go to the top
wait this is whole place for end game or
is there something for me now
[Music]
because what else did we do the
monuments for
yeah it must be
there must be something that we can do
wow
it looks so pretty
i love the
the way they use blur in this game
[Music]
and light
very nice
nice
[Music]
nice i like this place
it's kind of weird it makes you think
like what happened here
[Music]
oh
look at the drawings
that reminds me of the table
can i take the messages
oh i can't take them
[Music]
cathedral
someone had a [\h__\h] coffee or tea mug
on top of it
and who says wearing this allows you to
to do something extraordinary wearing
this wearing what
and then there's just everything i can't
read and the number 10 and the number
three and number six
ah
at three there's the number ten
where's the number three on the map
see one two three there
ten tiles
maybe and then
this is like a is it like um
maybe the whole dungeon or so it's like
a puzzle yeah
like you can only walk a certain amount
of tiles or so i know
or
i have some ideas but we'll see and then
10 is free let me oh
that makes sense 13 is six
not sure
we we'll probably understand it when we
get there
[Music]
who's that what's that page
what is that the beginning
from the beginning to the end is that
like
all the places we have to go through in
the right order
[Music]
i don't think i went in that order
but maybe that's just uh
uh open other pages in the glass yeah
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
the door in the mountains oh we already
went there and didn't know what to do
more info about all the items you can
get louder echo we have that one
times four
oh the explosion is times four
and then oh we have the ah the tincture
at the top in the middle
attack up defense down
okay
[Music]
and then there's a couple more that we
have yet to see scavenger's mask
apparently that one is important or so
because they put
a big fat line underneath
[Music]
i'm curious i'm curious about the ankle
that one is probably going to make you
able to jump over
certain distances
because there were some spots where it
really looked like you have to jump or
you have to learn how to jump eventually
i want the anklet
[Music]
there's so many pages here sasuke
library
[Music]
coming
the quarry on this place is scary
oh that already is very scary
cavity monster the rich rooted cigarette
gun
that lower me asthma are we gonna get a
lemurs ooh
friend
last echo wait we already fought against
a friend maybe we also fought against
lemur is in um
in that grave place
a swamp old burning ground the swamp
this zone is extremely dangerous and is
best left alone even if you're feeling
brave only ghosts are permitted to enter
the inner ground is this like an extra
level
[Music]
uh only ghosts maybe a certain mask
yeah maybe the scavenger mask
would let us enter this because then
with the scavenger mask that kind of
looked like similar to what we when i
just saw there
maybe with that which page is done
[Music]
where did the page go
oh
yeah
maybe with that
does that look like that maybe not
yeah maybe not
[Music]
find out okay
i know i'm just just you know in my
brain i'm unraveling everything
thinking out loud
what is all of this and who the hell was
doing all this
[Music]
what if i pray here
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
i can't keep it up
but i activated something
i activated something
it's um turned on now
oh there's a statue here
okay i'll save here once
and then let's try
teleporting wait there's a chest here
let's try teleporting at the golden um
[Music]
thingy
and then i wonder if with that i can
always go here whenever i want
as long as i use a golden.com
there are two more tests
any upgrades oh
one sec i guess can i go back
two more chests they blend in so nicely
that i didn't notice them i suppose
also i can go up here
or did i come from there no
[Music]
ah
oh
we're gonna go to the top
wait is that for later
he's gonna push me down isn't he
let me go let me go back i'm not ready
for this i think i think i think i think
i think the order is
find the chests go to the golden
platform
see what that does and then go to the
top
he'll just probably push me down
[Music]
where do you guys see your chest
let's
oh there they are
[Music]
they blend in man
oh lots of money okay okay
he's not taking a leak
here and now we can get a big upgrade
all right nothing else we can do so why
not
potion upgrade
okay if we find this is good
now you're ready i don't know should i
check out the golden platform first or
the dude at the top
what do you think guys
[Music]
the dude
okay maybe he will not push me down
let's see
i hope i don't regret it
hello
is he a fox i think he's
big fox with a nice sword
are we gonna
okay
no i don't think i'm mad for this fight
no way
i'm not supposed to actually win this
right
looks too difficult
[Music]
maybe maybe maybe
maybe okay
oh
no we can't do quite a lot of damage
okay i'm taking this as a experimental
try
[Music]
[\h__\h] hurts
oh not so bad though
[Music]
okay
that's manageable
that's kind of magical but oh no
oh
[\h__\h] i haven't focused on
oh that's quite the tough fight though
i only got him down like a little bit
more than a fourth
i guess it might be better with that
second weapon that i supposedly could
already get the second magical weapon
and the
the hook shot doesn't always work on him
like sometimes i'm able to get him close
to me sometimes not and i'm not sure
where yeah my damage is kind of low
[Music]
i don't know if this is for me now
is it really for me now
[Music]
about the timing it works when he's
charging okay
i've had a feeling like that
i mean we can try a few times but i'm
not sure if it's
really
worth it i'm you know the previous boss
we also managed without the
ice weapon even though
i think most people have the ice weapon
at that point
uh or you would want to have it and then
now here
we have a
a problem
because we're missing another weapon
apparently
um
but we can try
the boss is my current objective okay um
can i go up the stairs please first oh
do i have to oh man
[Music]
okay that's kind of wasting the hook
shots if i use it like that
[Music]
oh
okay i have to kind of roll over that
[Music]
yeah oh no okay that's a bad one
oh okay
i'm not really hoping for this run to be
the run but
try to survive
test it out
okay i'm out of
[Music]
oh how come i have 10 charges for my
bookshelf right now actually surprising
[Music]
there we go that's why he dropped some
those enemies at me so that i can get my
mana back
i barely do damage man
[Music]
atari
yeah i don't know about the ice i guess
i can try
um
[Music]
whoa
that's a good start
[Music]
it was a good start but i think i'm
really
[Music]
um
wow
[Music]
he's letting me damage him so much
how far does it go okay not far enough
but i have to test that one
[Music]
[\h__\h]
so i already have no more
potions
no more potions
[Music]
man
i'm dying
[Music]
pretty good but i wish i had a bit more
power
[Music]
i had a lot of lucky moments where
he just stayed close to me for a long
time
[Music]
if i just get
more attack
or
something
more attack would be nice but attack is
currently at four next is 250 and we
need those thingies i don't know where
they are you know it's not random
they're at specific points and i
wouldn't know maybe if we explore the
overworld a little
bit uh with the hook shot now maybe we
can find more stuff
[Music]
i was me catching the moment
if we spend 20 30 40 minutes on this we
could probably maybe have one lucky try
where we actually managed to kill him
but i don't know if you want to suffer
so much for this
maybe just you know
exploring first and then coming back is
the choice now
[Music]
no i i see myself
being able to do it even now
but i don't think it's worth the
suffering
we'll come back here i hope it's
relatively easy to come back um
i wonder if i can use these
teleportation fingers to come back
because yeah
that one wasn't activated before
so
[Music]
there's one in the back there
what's up here
[Music]
how [\h__\h] i go oh mommy
mommy
sorry mommy
mommy oh she's waving at me
mommy is in horny prison
and you have to save mommy
mommy so this is the afterlife kind of
somehow
maybe i don't know i'm a ghost when i'm
here she's a ghost
no you have to save mommy okay which one
leads where i don't remember
it doesn't matter really oh a surprise
doesn't really matter because oh well i
mean
there could have been better spots to
spawn at but
i just want to go into the overworld to
explore so
anything works really
i didn't have any specific point that i
wanted to go to
but
you guys are welcome to give me a hint
of the rough whereabouts of that extra
weapon
spiders
no
yeah yeah i know there's some spots in
this map with the hook
up the mountain
the mountain
now
[Music]
we weren't there just recently
okay on the way
i'll just keep on having my eye open
for
oh yeah
for anything with a hook shot
mark
[Music]
the key
the [\h__\h] key but like what would have
that been for anyway because i didn't
see any doors if we ever see a door then
we'll go back there because we know that
there's a key there
if we see a door that needs a key to be
open
ah oh oh
i can use this
as a
shot thingy
right wait can i get
that i want a piece of paper but maybe
that one is really
for
uh
like the jumping skill that i'm guessing
we get with that anklet
[Music]
the toys are on the same area
well i don't really care what we do as
long as we do something
so
okay
desert ecozoo
where do i go again
when i go for the desert
i don't remember how i got there
maybe i should just go over through um
one of the teleportation things it's
close by anyway
oh i got there for a teleporter to begin
with
okay explains a lot
okay
[Music]
oh wait this is where i can't
walk past dough
this one that's annoying
i have to go for a different one
bye
why
must you be like that
shot no
[Music]
i thought maybe now that i have more
options to teleport within that
maybe it would allow me
to use it to walk over but no
okay
oh
can i
why is there never never anything
to grab onto now
please give me something to work with
ah there it
[Music]
east is still unexplored really
i mean we were there before but i guess
maybe there were some parts i
missed out on
okay
which one was the one for
the ruined call what about this one
the speedos oh okay
this one is not it
yeah the bottom right one is wrong maybe
this one
bottom right is library
this is it okay
uh
[Music]
so how do i get there because i feel
like
i explored
every single corner here
[Music]
but
it must be something some way
of getting like
maybe if i'm down at the bottom from
like you know
before where i got stuck
not actually here but
okay
oh yeah like we had a secret here maybe
on the other side
there's the same kind of secret
maybe no we went for that that's nothing
[Music]
is a mystery to me
no i expected a lot of backseating
to be necessary
for me to get through this game
but
i'm doing
most of it smoothly on my own ah oh that
wasn't too hard
okay we got the key and we'll throw it
away
i have yet to see the door but the
supposedly is close by
i will paint my subscription
i passed it
you saw the door
wait what about if i go back here
[Music]
oh
ah okay i passed it
i passed
i it the chest
who was the chest
where look behind where you can't see
[Music]
waiting for the prompt
no
no prompt
no prompt okay
[Music]
oh you mean maybe uh
no
it was in plain sight
and that one down there i opened already
that one i opened too
you don't mean that one right
close to the hook
on that one
okay okay now i found the chest but we
have to find the door you guys already
saw the door
oh another one of those i forgot what
those i know that's an upgrade item
um but it wasn't attack was it
it was not attack probably
it was defense now okay i'll take
whatever i get but
[Music]
okay where's the store
the death is still good i guess we can
do it right now
sumima sorry oh i didn't need to do that
oh well 200 only some cheap what a deal
oh my
amazing
i was there
is it reachable for me
[Music]
another chest
i love those chests
oh there is the door
oh
you didn't see that just now you saw
that a long time ago huh
i thought you meant like i you saw it
because i just walked by can you stop
what the actual [\h__\h]
it used to be able
to be stunned by my shield
not anymore i guess
can i upgrade my shield please
the spikey ones don't stop then how are
you supposed to
maybe before they even get out of the
ground you're supposed to use the hook
shot or so i don't know or
or before they get out of the ground
you're supposed to use the ice because
once they once they go at you they don't
stop
you have to take damage but i'm
wondering if there's a way to do it
without taking damage
some things may stay a mystery to me
forever
more piece i think and then we get a
full new flask a fifth one which also
would be one of the more helpful things
for the fight that we're trying to do
[Music]
oh another shortcut here
okay
hmm
[Music]
a piece of potion
is that it
have i fully fully explored this area
now i feel like i
found everything
that can be found
when did i
i think i did
[Music]
didn't get much of your help but this
time i got a little bit of your help
thank you very much
yeah i've been here before
all right then i will
er
no i can't upgrade
i will
i don't know
i don't know what i'll do
i guess we'll explore the
even the mountain or the forest
the spider forest that i guess i
oh
i previously
ran away from because they were too
strong
yeah yeah okay
[Music]
ah
maybe there's even a teleportation
platform
wait a second this one's new this is the
secret
hey let me fight you
i can't you're leading me
wait it's not much of a secret maybe
this path itself
oh no this is a secret it's a chest
oh we have a magic potion which we have
yet to really use but
that's quite something
something of value
now we found it all
[Music]
foreign
i thought they were like mama potions
for some reason because of the looks of
them
those are bombs
oh i can totally use them in the fight
too then if i
run out of
[Music]
stuff
okay
awesome
[Music]
now i have like seven of them
wait a second i want to leave this place
[Music]
was that a teleportation thing in there
right
what's that
no that leads me to the sky
uh castle i wanna i want an easier way
to leave in this place
let's go up here probably
yeah
okay
[Music]
what is the closest
place to the east forest hmm i guess
just
the old house because the other place is
basically unusable
the other teleportation thing
down there
it's right over there let me use it
please
want that weapon first
okay but
i don't know where it is
ah [\h__\h]
again
[Music]
i don't know where it is
menu sword
very mysterious
you get greeted here by a [\h__\h]
massacre every time
actually you could like keep on
teleporting in and out and in and out
and
okay we're going to the mountain first
how
oh
all right
[Music]
sorry guys i don't really have much to
talk about today sorry i know you guys
always like my tangents but there's not
much to talk about talked about it all
yesterday i think
except for my table
and uh
and my steam cleaner
and
[Music]
yes one of the things i
was hoping for oh
there we go
[Music]
one more potion very valuable
monsieur scottis on it
with tata scalia
okay
i want more of those
more of those nice surprises
emergency brake laughs no i ran out of
them i think
just chilling companies enough ah
[Music]
i saw your parents real interview did
you have fun there
oh well it was honestly just a written
interview
um
[Music]
but yeah i took my sweet time it
actually takes quite a while to write so
much i didn't want to
i mean i could have just written short
answers but i wanted to
make it actually worth reading
but
you know i always talk so much in the
stream so it's not like that any
of that interview was
new info to people who watch every
single stream of mine i guess
if you only watch a couple then maybe
what if you watch every stream and i
know i don't think there was anything in
particular new
it's just like i i am
somebody who shares
oh
[Music]
that's funny
i can stand in here
i'm somebody who shares so much of you
guys so
a streamer who shares a lot so
i don't have
any super exclusive secret things to
share anymore sorry
your stream convinced me to buy this
game and give it a try i'm glad like
it's honestly so good
it's so worth it
oh
[Music]
i never went up here
was this always here
like like this right now in this state
[Music]
wait is that the weapon you want me to
find
i thought we're gonna go to the mountain
and it's there
not quite the mountain
[Music]
nothing happens when i pray
please don't tell me that i was always
there
eve but then i wonder because i only
have three slots to fight
i guess i
i guess the grappling
shot
barely worked anyway grabbing hook so
maybe i should just have the fire and
the ice weapon with me
let me see how it works let me see
18 charges
oh give you yeah it's a long distance
weapon basically
oh
admin
that's why it has so many charges oh my
god okay i mean okay even on him it
didn't do much damage so it's not gonna
do much damage on the dude either but we
can recharge
our mana and it also recharges the
charges on the weapons so
so
it definitely helps
now i would just appreciate one more
attack
upgrade um
yeah let's just go to the
forest and hope that we find
one of those items
yeah you got a grind
damage very low
okay there's no need to go to the
mountain anymore right
[Music]
in some way i kind of now found it
accidentally by myself so i'm satisfied
i didn't think it was there
i didn't even know i was going there
[Music]
how do i get to the east um
maybe
i don't know if it's a dead end
maybe we have a shortcut yeah we have a
shortcut
the forest fortress is close
of course fortress worm
okay
here we are again i didn't think i would
come back here
you guys are telling me to go so i hope
it's wet
[Music]
it doesn't work from
here ah oh i was like where do i go down
okay
oh yeah here we didn't do [\h__\h] here
ah
can i pray here dead yeah okay but if i
pray here
[Music]
what did that do
was this already
lit up i guess not
there's also a well here but i have yet
to find
a new golden coin
it's taking its stamp sweet time now we
can pray at this one too huh
great
what
longer yeah longer
very dramatic there's a piece of paper
[Music]
why is the automatic answer no
oh
covered it in a forest
wait are we gonna get the first
seal here maybe
[Music]
oh
on top of the sky maybe we'll get that
one after beating the dude
[Music]
yeah he might have the green
and here we might find the the
pink one
[Music]
again the same battle fought uncountable
times
air to the air
it's like cell like link basically
okay
um
i have high hopes now
it was a good choice to come here
i think
i don't know what's the intended order
but
i'm beneath the eastern vault oh
wow
oh
there's a hole there can you go for that
yeah
spooky
[Music]
a little bit more light would be nice
i'm scared
i really don't like dark places like
this i also don't like haunted houses
[Music]
but the haunted houses i've been to so
far
we're actually kind of lame anyway so i
guess i just don't like the idea of
actually scary haunted houses
i think i've been to like maybe haunted
houses in disneyland
and the haunted house in
the minecraft that mikuchi
with mikuchi
she built
i guess that was lame so i mean not not
lame then like
it was amazing okay but i mean like in
terms of how scary it really was
[Music]
sorry
i didn't mean it like that
everything she builds is amazing okay
oh it says spider
oh [\h__\h] i thought i had the grappling
hook
[Music]
huh are you doing another sports vessel
i'm not sure i didn't hear of any
planning yet but would be nice because
it was fun last time but it's a lot of
work and
but i think you know mikoti definitely
has the motivation for it you saw me
you're going away from me is it because
of the light
scary light
it's good that's my advantage
spiders hate wallet i've seen enough
spiders
in a bright environment
doesn't even recognize them the middle
ones
or they're feasting on something
[Music]
ah there was something about them with
uh the
like don't they also have a page about
them
where am i mixing things up
yeah there we go
don't be fooled the mark on their backs
is a trick about like how much money you
get from them maybe but not the batters
i have to kill all of them anyway wait
before i go there and check
okay i think that's the secret so i'm
gonna go there first
mario was getting very long yeah
end maybe you can print it all out
ah this makes me want to watch lord of
the rings
not that i
like that part of the spiders in
particular but
but you know
it's actually one of my least favorite
parts because it's [\h__\h] creepy
where should i go first
[Music]
watch along part two
i already did a watch long a long time
feel like it's a
you know a waste to do the same one
again i know we all love
the rings but you know
don't go away
kind of obnoxious man
oh that one is strong wait oh
oh [\h__\h] the direction was kind of [\h__\h]
that one was strong the blue one was
strong i have no more charges and
they're going away from me
[Music]
cheese cubes
yeah the blue one was strong too
wow
oh
wait i don't want to go so far there
were secrets and i didn't go to the at
like like perhaps that i didn't go to
yet i thought this was like a shorter
dead end path
ah it triggers me
i hate this
when in rpgs they're like
you have two paths presented to you
i always try to assess
ah [\h__\h]
which path is the
the one they wanted to go to to continue
moving on and which one is the one
that uh leads you to a dead end but like
a treasure usually
yeah
knowing that i missed something
kills me
it hurts me come here you [\h__\h]
am i walking
what's strong
lots of
cheese cubes
oh what
but there's so many rooms
oh shortcut
and now it's so confusing i went so far
oh berry free berries
[Music]
this dude was also in the manual
oh
all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right
where'd you come from what
i've been in that room before there was
no spot oh ah it's a skull
huge amount of members weren't around
for those early love of the rings you
know what how about we watch wildlife in
korea
although there are long movies maybe we
can only watch one or yeah
one at a time but
yeah if you really want if you really
want to oh what was that again which
upgrade hp okay
i'll take anything anything helps attack
would be best but okay
to make the suffering shorter
what is going on they're praying at the
monolith
what is going on
will they hear me
no
just wait a sec guys
it's not me mama seen them oh coin oh i
don't know if she knows lord of the
rings hmm
[Music]
anime
anime watch along and we can do that too
yeah
you know if i if i watched all the
movies i want to watch with you guys
then we have to do so many watch alongs
you know i don't i don't want to spam
you with watch lungs
i know that not all of you
like them some of you do but not all of
you
which is understandable you know
what can they even do oh pretty big
swings with the
candle but
ow okay i should have seen that coming
okay
that was the first time ever that i was
on fire i'm guessing if you get hit by
this dude with a candle and you're also
on fire
[Music]
let's pray and continue this
peaceful
magical path
[Music]
i like spending time with you even if
you don't like the movie you mean you
don't like little drinks in particular
nabi mama probably didn't sell a lot of
drinks
economy is better choices
people of culture will say lord of the
rings is the better choice hey just
kidding
just kidding both is cultured both is
cultured
i guess depends on the anime though
the eastern vault
no but i'm unhappy with my choices so
far can i go all the way back
i'm not sure like which um
[Music]
which path it was anymore but i want to
go all the way back because i'm unhappy
i feel like i missed out on something
fobo
it's the bubble
was it here
yeah
all the fomo is getting to me
[Music]
there was one path yeah
also
wait there's two different paths here
too which one did i take originally
ah this one yeah yeah
oh
what if i take that one
and i get the chest somehow
is that one of those lasers
oh
[Music]
until now i didn't care which item i
would get any upgrade would be fine but
now i particularly want attack and now
i'm not getting it
where was
where were those two paths
just maybe around here
it's confusing to go backwards man
was it here
oh [\h__\h] now i'm lost
at least i know that where there are no
enemies i've already been to
i guess
is this what it just came out of yeah
okay
so that's a circle
use rope start from the top
[Music]
no
what about this
monkey
did you hear her wow
wow
just saying hi to you guys
hi
oh she flopped down the moment i touched
her
but when i tried to move
[Music]
there she goes she knows immediately why
did she come here and then you know
taunt me
and then the moment i i i like move my
leg you know in an attempt to get closer
to her she runs away and then she comes
back she goes miami again
your cat does it too
she wants me to um
run after her
such a girl
ah that's where i came from the boxes
are back
not a hotel coco cut out
tracing back everything
we've traced all the way back now i
really don't know what that path was
anymore uh wait this was
good night
no there was nothing here okay
then i went here
and i went
i don't know where
what was this no
[Music]
bright rim of water remember this one
this room
damn it
[Music]
i missed the rope oh i wasn't in
particular looking for the rope though
this is just a place that goes in
circles
map yeah there was a map but
which one
snap
but it doesn't show me anyway does it
because i'm underground
or
no that's a frost domain
under the island beneath
there it is uh but you know if only i
knew where that path was i should have
looked at the map when i was at the that
path
[Music]
ah but interesting it's not that big
actually you should probably watch
emma's blade i should watch her watch
along
nah
and i'm not really into watching other
people's watch lungs unless unless i can
just watch the movie live with her in
person
that's more my kind of style
i'm thinking it's past this point at
this point
[Music]
and now we're at the top here
and what was this
oh
that
[Music]
no
maybe it wasn't worth it maybe maybe i
just imagined another path now i'm
feeling like the dungeon is gaslighting
me and now i feel like it never existed
to begin with that choice
of another path
i
oh i'm leaning
[Music]
[Applause]
this is the
worst dungeon in terms of knowing where
the hell you are
[Music]
it's not like everything looks the same
but a lot of the places don't have
anything so remarkably outstanding that
makes you remember it
and the order of how things are
connected
okay i think i'm giving up
uh
a circle has two entries you took one of
them and the other one is the other pass
you are searching for
circle has two entrances circle
ah the circle
oh
so you mean it's connected in the end
anyway so i don't need to
because i already checked out everything
maybe
[Music]
yeah and see where i am but i don't know
where i was at the point where i was you
know choosing the path
okay
[Music]
okay we'll just move on then but where
would how where is where is moving on
is this moving on or is this going back
i think it's moving on yeah yeah yeah
yeah
that was the circle
another
i'm trying to
remember
by looking at the map where certain
spots are now can i go for this one oh
you know it was oh i was testing it out
and the other waterfall it didn't work
there but it works at this one
oh
[\h__\h]
ringley
wrangling what does this one do
that's quite important that's um
the muffling bell
it does something with the monsters ah
maybe it um pushes them away
ah
nah nah that that's more like a weapon
what does it do
it makes your footsteps quiet
like
the whole time i'm wearing it they don't
hear me when i'm
like i'm more sneaky
[Music]
now now for now i'll continue with this
well good to know if we ever need to be
sneaky
then we have the right thing for it
ah this way is it this way ah
this may be my least favorite dungeon
well it's all right yeah
i need to drink
don't need to be sneaky yeah
yeah we have yet to have like some kind
of like stealth um
part
of the game where stealth is like really
the theme
and necessary
[Music]
thankfully so far also no escort mission
ah
alright um
am i going to rock by now
i think so
am i
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah like if you play this game
completely on your own without you know
a chat to tell you about certain things
then i guess you just have to test
these things out on your own
but like especially the muffling bell
how do you notice the effect
like because i don't think the
it's not so obvious
you have we would have to like complete
the whole study of
you know comparing how enemies react to
you but how would you have that idea
that it's the enemies
you know
in the first place that that is
that that's why you see a change i think
that would be
kind of tough to
understand like others are a little bit
more obvious but like
that drawing
where was it was it here yeah it looks
no it wasn't no it was here it looks
cryptic to me
like
even now that i understand what it does
ah wait that's a fox is that a fox i
don't know that doesn't say anything to
me
that doesn't tell me anything that is
very confusing i thought i guess the one
on the right is a fox drawing
that that one
but i thought it was an enemy drawing i
guess it could be a fox
and the left one an enemy but even then
like what does this mean
the other ones you know this these ones
make sense
yeah these ones make sense
oh the others don't have an explanation
maybe they're very obvious
loud echo that one makes sense too
maybe
yeah
anyway continuing i want to look at the
map again
ah okay so we're in this big room now
yeah yeah yeah we already took care of
the enemies and we already uh pushed you
down this thing we're back here it was
not worth running back there was nothing
it was really an illusion man i really
imagined there being a choice of paths
because in the end it was all connected
i'm sorry guys for dragging you through
this
i hear
mice or spiders or whatever
what is this cult session again
have this path and we have the other
side is that something
no
okay and i have to go this way
[Music]
we're chilling
it's just
the rpg experience and i'm sure i wasn't
the only one who was thinking i was
missing out on something right right
oh you want to come up here are you
coming up here oh oh yes
welcome to my domain
oh you're coming too oh
they're all coming to me how nice of
them
i don't have to walk so far
now this one has uh a couple more yeah
[Music]
okay i was too reckless i kind of
expected him to be stronger and put me
on
oh fire
at this point i don't care i'm on fire
and i don't give a [\h__\h]
can i block him
no
i think he still put me on fire
[Music]
what is it gonna stop
never
how do i roll does it have to roll
oh my god
oh wait there's a there's a page just
wait need to go up
[Music]
well i shouldn't this gives me another
thing to think about my kitchen fire
again
if i was on fire i guess i could have
rolled around with my apartment
oh what is this
the librarian yeah yeah yeah i'm about
to face him soon holy cross cathedral
god i wish i wish i knew what this was
saying
but
you see those signs on his chest hmm
it's another sign that he may carry one
of them and give me one of them
boss of the scavengers
what the [\h__\h]
rooted cigarette we've heard about that
rifle
built out of auto bolt parts but can
only shoot one scavengers with this will
try to keep their distance
miners greatsword beefy scavengers use
this to crack open odd architecture and
you huh
bombs watch out for miners who use these
is this like are we gonna be in some
kind of mine dungeon at some point
what
or can we build these things
we will find out soon
[Music]
which one was that
sp
[Music]
stamina
please please attack come on
get everything except the one i want
[Music]
okay
i do roll a lot yeah i have to roll a
lot in that fight too because he shoots
a lot of things at me and you know
gotta
get away from him let me just check out
this stuff before i activate anything
[Music]
um
oh
can we activate that after you know okay
i'll do this first
crane
to the box
gone
amen
[Music]
that's what the fox says
nice praying guys
oh see now it's activated yeah yeah i
thought so i thought so
okay praying time
and now we can upgrade a few things
that took a while
because it had to load in so many
enemies that i have eliminated so many
of them
okay i'm gonna do hp
and sp for now
i think
i wasn't quite having that many issues
with mp during the fight so
not that important
apparently four points in attack is max
i can get right now what
oh [\h__\h]
really
okay then i have to rely on the other
upgrades and the the fire weapon
magic
okay
[Music]
we probably until we get to the library
and we probably will be able to
get this upgrade too
just need a bit more money
[Music]
is that the way out
oh no it's um oh the oh
golden big dog
[Music]
there's another entrance into the same
room
i wonder which one is the smartest
that is the lowest level
hey
five five four seven three four is max
yeah okay but like
[Music]
at the very end right like in the whole
game
oh
[Music]
i don't know where to go first there's
another one of those
[Music]
which which fight do we pick first guys
follow the pipes yeah that one led
outside
but one also leads upstairs
cultists everywhere yeah and then
there's one here another entrance exit
oh there used to be a mommy statue here
what is that
and and what is this
i'm going so far
no
okay that leads outside maybe
oh i'm interested in that game yeah yeah
i had my eyes on it for a long time
it's in my i want to play it someday
list for sure
okay i'm
gonna go for the
big guy first i guess i don't know yeah
why not
[Music]
uh someone from the top
okay we got this one down but what the
[\h__\h] is and he will probably cast magic
even when he's still in the room next to
it isn't he gonna do that like in the
previous dungeon
no
maybe that was a bug
what if i go back in it's gonna continue
[Music]
yeah okay
oh there you are i can just bring you
down here
try me sucka
little piece of [\h__\h] come here
[Music]
[\h__\h] coward
oh oh i see i see
i think you're safe there
yeah
it's over now
big f to you buddy
i hate them so much
they think they're smart cookies man
okay we activated one side one sign is
done
interesting
then we go out there and we activate the
other side i guess or
wait
i like how they fall down okay i guess
we're going yeah we're going outside
you like seeing me like this well like a
pro gamer
my default stake you mean
okay
there's a lot of fire bombs here it's
kind of dangerous to fight here
but okay
[Music]
yeah easy
a fast kill to make you suffering short
not the dead body
[Music]
interesting that i can move dead bodies
though
[Music]
okay don't run into the bombs
[Applause]
[Music]
no let's pray here doesn't even do
anything because
you know because it's not connected with
anything
[Music]
how to connecto let me explore first
is there something here
secrets where are you
you can't hide
i want you you want me to don't you want
to be found i know as a secret you want
to be found come on i know you do
[Music]
hello
don't you want to share
your dirty little secret with me
i think i
i know it's just like on the right side
somewhere
the
the base of it
perhaps somewhere here
oh my oh my god
to death that's how it feels that's how
it feels stop hurting others with that
if you don't want to die like that
yourself
yeah run secrets run
run run
run
[Music]
wait is he gonna
continue doing that even though he's in
the one no that's a different guy okay
the one in the water actually died
that's nice
[Music]
oh no there's another dead hero
grape how many dead heroes are there so
many dead foxes why
why are they all dying
ah
it's a jumping
oh wait what does it do what does it do
what does it do
i was curious about this thing
no it just makes me faster
i think
i think i'm faster
yep it just makes you faster
ah that's that's okay
yeah i was hoping i could jump with that
[Music]
okay
do we have to remember these locations
and come back to them one by one later
oh my god
just give me those items
one of those is uh
the top give me the tofu over there
that's the attack item i want that one
[Music]
maybe those are the final upgrades you
can get here
how do you get them you have to walk
over
ah
jump is similar to hook shots
oh really it's not actually a thing
like bouncy shoes or something like that
and they're back the enemies are back
just because i went to a different world
[\h__\h]
okay
well this place hmm
no wait are they gone it was just that
one left
interesting
i thought i killed all of them
okay
okay okay so i think i know where if
it's not here then i know where the
the monolith is
it's on the right side but one more
level higher perhaps
ah the one i heated into the water ah
[Music]
i thought he drowned he should drown
that sucker
hmm
oh no no
they're everywhere
chest oh my god
the edge of the world man
it's kind of dangerous here okay is it
one more level higher
[Music]
oh gain
just a chest here
so many magicians
an influx of magicians
angel panic cure really
[Music]
i'm not panicking i'm calm i'm i am
i'm well prepared for all these
situations i'm a warrior i'm not scared
oh no not two of them
oh it's not good
[Music]
big boy
ah
what the [\h__\h] is this place
what am i coming for
[Music]
ah
shortcut or something like yeah i had
stairs
i i really like the level design though
[Music]
yes i'm going
okay i ran out of class so this is not
funny anymore no bullies
i thought that was gonna happen
oh there is someone on the left but it's
not the face
where is it it is the base
i'll keep on getting cuter
it's cuter and cuter no more hats i am
now the ribbon lady
stairs and dad are we done here then can
i go down what's here though
no going down yet
all right i've already been here
no
i've been at the lower level i think but
not on the chestnut
oh barry
i like ribbons
and i like those
lynchy cat ears
i do feel
cute
how are you feeling guys you feel cute
too or you feel something else
[Music]
oh we're gonna throw a coin into the
well
oh this is not the beginning ah
and now we have a shortcut to that space
ah
[Music]
feeling hot it's hot
handsome mmm pizza cute myself mmm
squishy and fruity oh
i'm feeling dunky
thanks
you're cute enough for the both of us
feel handsome that's good
you go
go go handsome chicken
crispy and delicious
[Music]
oh we can do the mp
i feel like a nugget
you are a live chicken so don't worry
about that
[Music]
you look very much fluffy and feathery
and alive to me you're not a nugget but
it's probably your vision of the future
you have a gift you have a gift and you
must use it
[Music]
just checking for secrets
okay enemies are
unfortunately all back
come down
[Music]
all of them are back
don't waste my time
i already killed all of you
[Music]
i knew fighting next to that was
dangerous oh well
okay so we activate this it leads to the
left and to the top right
activate
amen
oh no no not that one
you wanna fight you can't touch me from
there can't touch this
[Music]
oh where does that lead that one
where did i send that one to
that direction doesn't lead to nowhere
because those were already bright over
there
angry in german
[Laughter]
i will be very satisfied german channel
yeah
i will not be fulfilling any cliches
of angry german
yeah i will very i will be very
sophisticated and calm
at all times
[\h__\h] i hate you so much
oh my
easy clap
ah yo i hate
keep on interrupting his
spell his magic spell
all right oh now it's gonna open up the
big door we're done we're done we're
done
[Music]
is
i mean previously there was no boss
behind the golden door right yeah it's
just a portal
and a mommy
or maybe uh maybe up there there is a
bus
oh there must be a bus because they're
not gonna give me that thing so easily
because this time yeah i'm getting
something for it let's not activate this
thing by the way
[Music]
okay
well i wonder which is gonna be stronger
the librarian or this one
because
i feel like the game
led me uh to the librarian first but
wasn't there like uh
i'm also already way stronger than
before but
it's hard to compare but where where was
that thing
what page am i looking for
uh
was it the beginning actually
this one
okay judging by the order at the bottom
there
it does seem like they want you to go to
the forest temple first
interesting
i found this one pretty easy compared to
the librarian okay
this box is a lot harder
oh my god
mixed opinions once again all right well
whatever
at least the statue is like
close okay
danger danger
or something like that um should i
well
let's see first maybe we change our
weapons later depending on how it goes
oh dear
it's a big area oh there's going to be a
huge bus
looking at the ruins
gonna walk around
ah
oh there it is
do i attempt to take it
and then fail damn okay i should have
gone from the other side
i attempt to take it and then it comes
to life
oh
[Music]
what
is
[Applause]
okay just running normally works
actually i thought i had to throw but he
shoots so long
no
i hate them
i think i preferred a librarian
what
jesus
uh
i am i have a different
mm-hmm
i do have a speed boost is that why i
was able to just run away from it
maybe that's not normally the case
that was humbling
what the [\h__\h] hey
[Music]
okay so i definitely need the the
grappling hook shot
for
the [\h__\h] that he's gonna shoot out
easier to run away from this one what do
you mean right away i have to hit it
i have to kill it and have to get pretty
close in order to hit it right in his
face
[Music]
oh you mean run away from the laser
okay our damage is fine oh it's pretty
good okay that was a good one
okay okay cool cool cool
oh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
i don't even care about the laser
monsters we're moving so much
i mean run away from the moving monsters
oh did he just kill that money anyway
[Applause]
yeah that's what you mean probably with
running away
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
damn that's a huge [\h__\h] bastard
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
that seems to be a weak spot does that
do more damage
i really don't want me to get his ass
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
let me go
trust me bro
let's go
i have no healing no
yes get him yes
[Music]
[Applause]
my body i didn't even pick up my body
let me get my body please can i have my
body
that felt so good to do
took my let me take my body
i i was not expecting to do it on the
second try
and to be honest second try at this
point is first try because
i just had to take a look at it first
you know
i don't think that even counts as a
first try
thank you thank you thank you thank you
and yeah yeah running away from the
things that he sends out
works well enough they barely hit you
because you're constantly moving anyway
and yeah they have no chance and then
often they get killed by their own
mother anyway i'm slagging so much
i love my gamer boss
yeah the boss was cool though i liked it
um very intimidating at first
but manageable
then
gamer
the gamer yeah
flying things can be one shot by the way
one
[Music]
yeah the noises were funny too
yeah yeah yeah i couldn't focus too much
on the bjm and noises but something cool
was going on
it's a screw
i guess we can take off the pink thing
but we don't know that we are supposed
to do this yet maybe i don't know i
don't know we just put it in here oh
yeah oh okay
oh
the first one
hold it in yeah
ooh pink diamonds
hi
yay
oh what's going on
[Music]
okay that's a cool way of revealing that
like one by one
slowly but surely oh it's wanting me
again like with
skulls are you sure you want to take
this yeah hell yeah
i got finally the first of those three
gems and now at the librarian we're
gonna get quickly the second one
we're quick quickly going to get the
second one
hell yeah baby
uh so much fun yeah to be actually like
decent at the game
thank you guys thank you yeah it's time
for a rematch i'm i'm stronger now
i'm relatively stronger and um
but the thing is like
i
yeah the grappling hook didn't do much
for me i think i will go with
this lineup oh i have 24 shots now
and then
[Music]
the ice i feel like i never got him with
the ice either when he was close enough
to use the ice i just hit him normally
and it worked fine because he stayed
by my side
pretty long
so maybe even this is an
option
but i don't know we're just gonna
experiment i don't wanna waste the
dynamite
uh right away i guess
maybe we try like this first
did i get it with ice i don't think i
really got it much
really
okay okay
okay let's go with fire and ice a song
of fire and ice
[Music]
we are back again all ready for the
second gem
i am [\h__\h] ready
we didn't get the attack we wanted but
we got a lot of other stuff
it's time for doom baby
rematch dan
i'm scared though because the stage is
so small it's compact but it's small
there's not much space to like dodge
and he flies around it that sucker
[\h__\h] coward
but okay
okay come on
i know if i'm ready one
we're in a boss fight rush in a bus rash
oh my god
[Music]
one boss after another
okay
[Music]
okay i made a mistake
okay i could have got one
okay
okay i'm being not so careful but
[Music]
it's no problem so far
oh
foreign
[Music]
i was trying to use my eyes
uh
[Music]
now
i was having so much fun because it was
surprisingly easy to get him now with
that weapon because actually it
recharges so much
i wanted to if only that one hit was
focused on him properly because i did
shoot one more fire right there
so it does surprisingly more than i
thought it doesn't do much damage in one
hit but you can like spam it at him and
it never really misses if you focused on
him
oh that was fun you know look i'm glad
it didn't end so fast because
wait why are we here oh i didn't
activate the other one because
it's fun let's fight more you know
i want to fight more
and that was a basically a first retry
i basically got him okay i basically did
it
i basically did it
i let him win i wanted him to have a win
[Music]
i wasn't even focused and i did a lot of
mistakes too in like
in the beginning especially i'm lagging
so much what makes me lag so much
i'm a gamer pc okay
oh here we have my body as a bomb too
now that's cool
stop lagging please
oh the shrine oh i'm not dead
yeah no i mean i guess no whatever it's
not that far because we're literally
right at the teleportation thingy
computer please oh now it's back to
normal
what the hell
okay
see i wasn't even doing that well
i was very um
i feel like the flight was very messy i
was just i was just shooting shooting
shooting shooting there was not much
skill behind that either
i can't even say that was a lucky
try it was just suddenly he was so weak
[Music]
thank you for recharging my weapon and i
am obliterating to win
[Music]
he's giving me so many
oh
okay i'm making many mistakes
but it's way too easy oh my god
that is just crazy
i'm giving you a chance to go back
[Music]
what a winkling
what
absolutely asserting dominance here
you must okay
i am such a gamer
oh tunic makes me feel good about myself
wait i'm so i'm
i'm smiling so hard oh my god my face
hurts
what what
was he too intimidated
what
so sloppy yo even i was making a lot of
mistakes like i kept on letting him hit
me
have i just become too strong huh i
didn't even get an attack upgrade
i just got the the magic wind wand that
you're supposed to have at this point
anyway in my opinion so
yeah in the time when he flies around
outside being able to damage him during
that
weighs a lot but even then when he was
here on my platform
he gave me way too much room to hit him
way too much time
can i have the sword too dude
please
no
there's not actually like a secret uh
ladder over there is there
no
just checking
i'm a secret hunter
thank you guys you know i'm so proud
because everybody said oh this game is
so difficult and i can see how it's
difficult but i'm having a great time
actually struggled against this boss but
i did the first two but even at first
you know
when i didn't have the fire wand it
still
seemed doable right because i got him
down half
and that was without being able to do um
long distance damage
yo
you
[Music]
[Laughter]
but the problem is that probably until
the next time we play tunic
um
i'm gonna you know oh it's already been
five hours oh my god i should probably
end it it's a good point to end it maybe
but the next time we play it we're
probably um
you know taking a break like at least a
week
no probably more
so
i will need to
get back into it i don't know if i can
you know quickly
get into my groove if there's like two
weeks in between
[Music]
sadly
but
we
cleared like two or yeah two dungeons
uh one the ruined at all
the big at all
two dungeons if not free even
yeah i don't know
and
oh we also cleared we did two no we did
three bosses today three bosses
oh holy macaroni
[Music]
wow
we did so much today actually
we got two of the gems
they shown here oh they are shown here
we're just missing one
[Music]
so exciting
i'm so excited
yeah
we got much stronger we found a lot of
cool stuff um we found two magic weapons
[Music]
hell yeah
i hope you enjoyed it today i think i
guess i'm gonna read some super chats
even though my froze hurts but it's only
the ones from this stream so
i might be daijoubu especially with a
fruit candy um
yeah let's do that let's move to my
office but give me a second for uh an
idol meeting
moving
[Music]
let's listen to this
do you hear this now
[Music]
so i'm so satisfied
the game is so satisfying to me right
now
you hear it okay
let me let me fix uh let me first of all
pray because the praying saves right
i just want to make sure that if it's
okay to leave the game now
and oh only an oldie
is a good track yeah
it's uplifting
it's fitting right now oh goodnight
it feels great when the game cooks with
you yeah it really doesn't
[Music]
i'm on a [\h__\h] high right now
i i
i'm i'm probably enjoying this way more
than you guys are but
uh
that's that's probably definitely
entering
my hall of fame of favorite games
and i'm impressed that it does that you
know it's an indie
holy [\h__\h]
like i love the aesthetics i love the
gameplay
i love the
the parts of the story that we
the crumbles of story that it tosses at
us
it's so much fun and i feel like it
makes me feel good
it's really satisfying to see you're
doing an amazing job eating all these
things
tuning these will be more appreciated
man
after i'm done with this playthrough i'm
gonna
recommend it to all my all my whole life
english members
vata i should play
too i think what i would like it
so a quick uh idol break and then
[Music]
so
i was giving smoovie some cuddles
i was holding her it was sure
i'm cuddling herself
[Music]
right
i want hurt you i promise i won't
obliterate you like i just did dad
who was that dude what was his name even
i don't even know
i'm the librarian twice you know i'm i'm
actually
glad
and i didn't kill him the first time
there
the first time in the second try i mean
because
the second try
was even more ridiculous
really easy and funny
the way it was so easy wasn't so funny
yeah
my parents are not particularly good in
two slides
no but
nah i'm not gonna take that argument he
was strong in theory but
he cannot win against this cute
kitakatto
let me fix my scarf it's my
face oh that's good that's good that's
pretty good um
please
[Music]
my mom sent me a meme about cats
she says today is world cat day
and
it shows me
an image a screenshot of a tweet
[Music]
where it's a normal
tabby kitten looking up to
the statue of an
of the i think
egyptian
uh
cat goddess bastard
looking at it and asking do they still
worship us no no the goddesses do they
still worship a child and the kitten
still alive says
well i [\h__\h] in a box and they clean it
and then the goddess says good good
you saw that yeah my mom sent it to me
anyway
[Music]
what else is going on
looking at my discord mentions does mama
do you have pets not currently um
she i mean
she had chickens but you know they're
gone by now she wants more chickens she
wants new ones she's planning on that
but she's building a shed for the
chickens
uh first and then takes some time
because she's doing it alone and she's
kind of trying to improvise with like
improvised materials
of her lot because like the lots that
she bought um it came with like a
million trees and like a ruin of
some shed or so
um and you know
also she had to like heat out all the
weeds that were like all over the lot
it's quite a big vlog
that was insane amount of work
yeah yeah
very educated chickens
they cute they eat everything
they do they do
yeah yeah yeah
yeah she's been working on that for
years for like 10 years now
um but nowadays more actively because
now she actually lives there before
before that like actually even more than
10 years but before that until recently
like recently i mean like until
one and a half years ago maybe or so
before that she was just going there
every now and then
whenever she could
work on it but now like since that
while ago she's been
living there and actively working on it
[Music]
and then every now and then my my
brother and so on
would like come by to help her
but it's
really far so it's not so easy to come
by
yeah but most of the things she's like
more or less doing on her own or trying
to
somehow you know it's like
it's not in the middle of a city it's
like in the middle of nowhere so she
tries to
with the few contacts that she has in
that place
tries to
get help for the things she needs to do
country life
yeah the thing is also um it's in
it's in hungary and
she doesn't speak the language
and
that's a
problem because she has communication
issues often
[Music]
yeah so actually whenever i say i visit
her i'm i'm actually leaving the country
yeah it's because in hungary like houses
are very cheap and and lots are very
cheap
very very cheap
like generally everything is cheap there
but you also
earn basically no money
no not at all
that's why
you know it's a neighboring country
and like uh at my previous workplaces
there were always a lot of like
hungarian people working who moved over
from hungary because you just can't make
money over there
[Music]
yeah
yeah that's what she's up to let me take
a break
[Music]
wow for the same reason rubble doll
the other way around yeah
make money first in your country then
move to cheap country
to live even cheaper with your lots of
money
[Music]
while the others move to your country to
make money there in the first place
[Music]
because they don't even earn enough
money to live in their own cheap country
because
they don't pay [\h__\h]
interesting isn't it an interesting
circle of life
life hacks
we live in a society
you like my tail
it has a belly
[Music]
brazil
oh
probably similar huh
[Music]
you could probably also do that
in greece i think living in greece might
be cheap too could be wrong though
and spain
spain is cheap too
and then germany austria is expensive
italy i don't know
france is expensive but it
changes
probably very generously depending on
if you want to go to paris or not
yeah
grace is expensive as [\h__\h] is it just
cheap to have a vacation there and not
cheap to live
[Music]
switzerland super expensive yeah yeah
very famous switzerland is very famous
here
for
you know you can make a lot of money
there but it's also really expensive to
live there
so what what some people do is they work
in switzerland like at the edge of the
country
but then they drive home
maybe even only over the weekend or so
and they live outside of switzerland
have cheap rent and then drive over back
to switzerland to work see that that's a
that's i guess something that you know
you guys in america and so on
can't even like
quite
imagine i guess
because like our countries they're all
so close together sticking together
but depending on the country just by
going over the borders so many things
can change like economically
yeah
crazy
crazy it is
what kia
yeah i know that states have like
different
taxes and stuff
isn't true that in washington there is
no income tax because i was told total
and i was like
what the [\h__\h]
i want to live in washington
[Music]
hellman is the truth
because that sounds almost unreal
right it doesn't sound real
is it
you pay other taxes
not as good as it sounds
no state but there's still federal
wow
oh well
not that it matters not that i'm moving
actually to washington so
it doesn't matter in the end
state level then i wonder how much
how much the
federal
takes
[Music]
double states don't have income taxes
and that should never be
never been implemented federally
[Music]
okay we're getting into political talk
here
i mean i find it interesting to compare
the differences
but yeah
let's read the super chat
only from today
[Music]
what do we have what do we have what do
we have what do we have
i'm so happy i finally remembered a
certain
key shortcut keyboard shortcut that's
really useful
and you guys taught me before and i
finally learned this by heart
windows shift
and then arrow button moving windows
some some windows without you know
moving them with your mouse just moving
in with the keys it's very useful
because
um
there's a certain program that i use and
i
sometimes i have trouble moving from one
monitor to another
yeah
and now things are way more efficient
and faster
oh you didn't know
you didn't know it it's useful
if you have like three monitors
especially
it's useless if you have only one
monitor oh yeah
my favorite set of windows struggles
you opened my eyes
i taught you something yay
[Music]
i didn't know oh i'm teaching people
something oh my god but i only learned
it from you guys
[Music]
oh
wow wow i taught so many
detectives yeah
[Music]
um
i'm not only gamer girl today i'm also a
technical
genius
today why doesn't this work for you
lever you only have one monitor or you
have um
you don't have a certain window selected
or
where or your
your on the mac
oh no
please call the it hotline
have you tried turning it on and off
again or off and on again first of all
[Music]
okay i'm gonna rinse the potatoes
oh oh one two oh my god one would is
this like a low-key
um rainbow without the red one but two
pinkies instead because you can write
more stuff i guess
no
thank you
after a five hour drive home from crx i
had some time to reflect on this weekend
it was totally a whole live event for me
yeah i can imagine like i heard that the
event itself was like relatively small
but that's probably just coming from
guys who
who went to
like uh
anime expo the other day like compared
to that it's probably smaller
but then everything was like so filled
with all the live
viewers and content
that it felt probably like yeah like a
whole live expo
yeah holy [\h__\h]
we took all of them i ate everything on
the kfc menu even got the non-listed kfp
donuts
what they were not listed items i didn't
know about them what the [\h__\h]
i was able to buy holo merch from the
artist alley and omocat witnessed all
kimono ah augustus ellie and omokan with
this all key wow videos ah even the one
at the kfb stand i suppose so
everyone in the hollow meet exhibit
the showcase feature attended each panel
even the concert digest wow yeah i heard
there was something going on like that
they showed apparently
like um
high quality version
of the concert not the the livestream
version but like uh basically the
blu-ray version
of some songs
in the theater there
apparently and then jago was there in an
almond smaller
yeah i didn't even know they were gonna
do that
oh thank you i'm gonna eat korean food
i'm also gonna try to eat some spicy
foods even though i worry about
having to do some leftovers maybe nabi
mama will eat it for me if i can't eat
it but i want to try at least
we got a picture with small almond noise
yeah
damn
nice happy for you
they did so much stuff yeah
that young got this all over you've got
this autograph oh man trevor winning may
not have squawked with any kfb again
but it was still an effective epically
fun time
big thanks to everybody involved so i
feel that holy me showcase hasn't
reached its final performance
it was the first time so but for that i
think it went like
all out
it can go even further beyond yeah i
guess again i helped inform multiple
guests about it since some of the
concepts didn't know either
about
what
i was thinking it would have been cool
to have had a sign outside detailing
what's inside oh
and the whole live timeline set up with
whole top clips playing to help
introduce new people oh you wanna you i
already got a kfb food stand i don't
think they're either gonna
bring out whole talk uh
you know my content even more promotes
me even more and that's you know having
the whole food stamp thing was already
quite the special treatment somehow but
hey
i have to do something with this food
theme right i have to get something out
of it
[Music]
would have been awesome yeah the
explanation being like i wasn't there in
person so i can't judge well but
i think i can imagine what you're trying
to say
like i can imagine the situation
yeah it's not being very clear
like what's going on
oh i saw a lot of congo it's confused
when they entered those three waiting
rooms at first oh like you mean random
people who weren't there for whole life
that was super cool anyway i'm excited
to see it involve the future love love
pro life and chihuahua yes almighty
walmart got compliments every day even
jaguar's escort complimented the apron
fashionistakiwa makes this up thank you
so much i'm glad you were able to
monkeytsu
in japanese get the most out of it
you just missed on socializing but
but
it seems like you had a great time and
you got really
you got to see really all of all of the
things that were offered besides the
meet and greet though
but still
sounds like a lot of fun i wish i could
have seen everything in person because
it was more than i expected to
the lab experience confused me too what
do you mean exactly do you mean the the
ones where there were the panels the
screen panels to take photos with us or
what what exactly
[Music]
socializing was also my weak side i
always forget it after see that's why i
keep on telling you guys to specialize
because you're always gonna regret it
afterwards yeah
the five videos the girls recorded
ah you mean that the secret ones yeah in
the theater
yeah
i think those turned out really good so
i would hope that everybody saw it but
yeah
you know well
it makes it
[Music]
foreign
um
your father was just hold over the
videos while standing oh
where they like mixing them
if you go into the
at the right moment at the brown moment
and they're just playing
videos and you might think that it's
just
videos there huh
[Music]
uh you just missed
most of it yeah but you're welcome to
watch the vlogs we got pretty far in the
game
we killed three bosses that were pretty
tough too
no
easily
thank you travis team
i'm so happy to hear that you had a good
time and that you enjoyed it and then
you made
some noise memories even on your own and
also i just want to say
yesterday evening
i was
rewatching the panel vlog
because i wanted to hear
and see
the audience properly and hear their
reactions to certain things
and
i know that all of you guys
gave us positive feedback about the
panel
i have not seen a single negative
feedback about it
yet
and i believe that i believe you guys
enjoyed it
but
when i was looking at the faces
in the audience camera
everybody looked so [\h__\h] bored
and it killed me
it killed me
they looked so unimpressed man
i was so worried like when i was talking
in the panel
oh look up i felt like i said something
funny
i'm just trying my best you know to
stall and all that
and then the faces
maybe it's partially because they were
all wearing masks
so
you could only really see their eyes but
i feel like even when you just see the
eyes you see if they're smiling or not
and i don't want to say they didn't
enjoy it but i was gonna say the facial
expressions made it look like they did
not enjoy it
but i know you i think
i from the feedback i got i think you
guys enjoyed it but yes
looking at the camera you guys really
look like you
[Music]
so did freaked me out man
resting face crowd yeah
resting [\h__\h] face resting i'm bored as
[\h__\h] face
but i can imagine you know you truly
enjoyed it it's just it doesn't quite um
look like it on your face for the people
who were there
i'm sure they enjoyed it
i think i hope
[Music]
maybe they were tired i don't know it
was the beginning of the day man it was
like before noon or so i think
wait what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
i just noticed something
oh my god
how am i doing this
on my on my camera you know
not on the obs screen not on the pc
but on my actual camera you know i'm
looking at i have two different versions
of myself that i can look at
but
you know
i'm looking sad right now look the
eyebrows
turned like this
but when i look at
the other version of myself
my expression is different i have the
eyebrows like this but my mouth was
smiling like that one single moment in
the ocha mekino video
and i've never seen myself like this
before i didn't know i could do it how
the hell am i doing this
how am i doing this it looks funny
wait
it looks so funny
why can't i do that here
wait i'm gonna take some screenshots
for you guys too wait wait a second
i never maybe it's a book maybe if i
change this now i will never see this
face ever again
let me take some screenshots for you
guys
i've turned it off accidentally no no
it's updating now because i turned it
off one second
why don't you always update yourself
no youtube's updating too [\h__\h]
not that i need it but like everything's
updating now why
okay i'm done updating but
is the face still there
no
it's gone can i recreate it
no no it's gone how did i do it
maybe if i press two like once
how did i do it
give it back to me
[Music]
also why did my oh i have no my ears oh
it still moves okay there's a lot of
spooky things going on right now
there you go
yeah i want
i want my face i didn't even get to take
a screenshot because i'm i'm not used to
iphone but i chose the wrong button i
turned up the screen
i don't like iphones
you can catch you should do it no it
doesn't do it right no
[Music]
no my face no my mouth was happy but my
eyebrows
were sad and i love that look because
when i laugh it looks like i'm laughing
even more like
enthusiastically
anyway back to topic so
it was funny
and painful at the same time seeing how
the audience looked
bored as [\h__\h]
but it didn't make sense
when lined up with the feedback i
received from you guys so don't worry
guys
i do think you guys enjoyed it it's just
the footage says something different
[Laughter]
we're more intensive than bored yeah
probably yeah you were just you know
focused on listening
and it do be like you know when i watch
a tv show even though i find it very
funny i don't actually laugh at out loud
that much
it i do feel like when you sit in an
audience
you laugh out loud more than you would
do at home
it's just i don't know it happens
naturally
it makes you laugh more right
and but then still i think some of
the boredness was probably just
quietly enjoying it but but still but
still
it made me worry like are these people
really enjoying what we're doing like
this is awkward awkward as [\h__\h]
[Music]
is
i feel more comfortable laughing and
being noisy and private
it's the other way around
that that is
weird interesting
i mean when's about crying i feel more
comfortable crying about a movie or
something i'm watching at home
then in public but laughing i would
laugh more in public just because
especially if you hear the audience
around you laughing
you kind of snicker more too
yeah they did participate in the call
and response and the waving and the wave
and all that yeah i think um you know i
tried i tried to uh include the audience
with their interactions like also when i
what was it when i asked uh who wants to
buy this and then they go like hey me
maybe they raise their hands trying to
wake them up
trying to make sure that they're
engaged
i always want to know if my if the
content i create is being enjoyed
properly or if there's room for
improvement if i need to if i should
have done something better because when
i was doing the panel
because of all the stalling it made me
so nervous and i was thinking this is
not going well
yeah
but yeah
oh they did sound even more lively on
zoom
the they actually didn't pick it up much
in the
in the stream
and zoom it was much louder but every
time that we spoke
it it muted the
um the zoom call of you know their side
so
i couldn't hear it much but every time i
was quiet after saying something funny i
heard them laughing very loud and
cheering very loud so that's a good sign
[Music]
thank you
there's more confidence yes more
confidence i think that convention was
the first time for some of these weebs
don't call them waves
they were nervous um
it was nice to see the
the hall so packed though like really
packed wow what
some seats weren't like reserved in the
front weirdly for nothing but besides
that it was packed
really happy
thanks for coming
i don't think so many people in the chat
actually came
i feel like only three or four everybody
who came
can you just um
say
me right now
one two three four oh five six oh seven
eight
nine ten
eleven
twelve thirteen oh
four
eight really
16-17 really
surprisingly
many
really
i mean there were a lot of people there
obviously but like i mean like in my
chat right now
oh thank you thank you very much thank
you
[Music]
okay continuing miniature pictures
for the rest of the day attention outfit
very cute i hope there is a chance to
see tantra's beautiful scarf after this
game this sky
well
maybe like similar kind of things
different different kind of variations i
love this game and it was a great time
to enjoy it with other chickens i wish
all of you have a nice day thank
i love this game too you guys should all
play it and then report back to me how
you struggled more with it than i did
tell me tell me about it tell me about
it it feels good boost my ego do it
make me feel better about my gaming
skills
[Music]
more
i want to try it out you should you
should it's really good it's a lot of
fun
[Music]
i have to turn on the accessibility
that felt really good
[Music]
thank you it was all for that one final
buzz
if you know you know okay well
maybe i shouldn't laugh too much now
maybe i will i will beg
for turning on the accessibility
later on at the end
i'll beg for it
but so far i mean
it was magical totally
i'm looking forward to the rest of the
game
thank you
time
[Music]
apparently the rain is so strong that
they had um power outages
what
like i've i've lived through some
extremely strong rain rainfalls in my
life
i've yet to experience a power outage to
come with it even during like a
a typhoon
when i lived in japan i
there were a lot of typhoons but at that
point i often felt like
like they they throw around the word
typhoon too easily
like i saw it so often in the news oh
today's a typhoon tomorrow is a typhoon
and then it wasn't even that bad
judging by that
a lot of the things that they don't call
typhoon should have also been typhoons
the streets look flooded what the [\h__\h]
what
is that in seoul
is that happening in seoul or in a
different city in
korea
so it's getting flooded
um
i
i hope that resolves itself soon yeah
[Music]
because i'll be coming to
korea very soon
and it's rain seasons and this continues
and continues
yeah take my snorkeling equipment i
don't have my own i'm gonna buy it
i have to buy boutique
oh my god does this happen a lot in
seoul
only in cell is heavy rain oh man
love it
once again
[Music]
i'll talk to kobo about it okay she'll
fix it
hopefully
oh my god please take care if you're in
seoul
i i yeah yeah
yeah bye
[Music]
people stopping this week you're better
sooner than later please
[Music]
fire in the water
water in japan
[Music]
ill junk tolerate tail ribbons
nope
i don't think
normally
i i don't think any cat would
tolerate that or anything you would put
on their bodies like on this on the paws
maybe you can make them get used to
putting like putting on like a shirt or
something
but
they definitely don't like it no
yeah
cats are not like dogs
you can't have a fashion show with them
like with doggos
that's why there is
normally just
shops for dog clothes and not shops
specifically for cat clubs
[Music]
dogs don't like it either
yeah not much but
i think the smaller dogs are okay-ish
with it
i see i see especially
[Music]
in
japan i think i saw
way more dogs wearing clothes than in
europe
um
[Music]
finished the whole yakuza series oh my
god wow you were busy
now you're playing tennis with
versailles nice enjoy
sounds fun optimus prime thank you
oh thank you
centennial robot thank you in the
undertaker
nice to see you
price
[Music]
wait i love that idea right so free
next whole live
en group is npcs
you know i was reading it
reading your stupid chat text while i'm
reading
you know everything else i have that
skill
it's funny so funny and we have the
adventurous temples the patron gods
councils
and the big bad mythical creatures myths
well the next generation going to be the
damsel in distress and the npcs
i love that idea it's
[Music]
i'm so proud of your weekly
gym workouts
well
at least i went swimming like a couple
days ago
and if it gets hot again
uh like before i'm gonna go again
[Music]
now i'm going on vacation again so i
can't work out oh no i'm you
[Music]
how did the swimming go oh it was fine
um
no it was fun
it was nice refreshing
[Music]
awesome yeah yeah yeah i've been oven
dancing too
actually
well actually it's just the problem is
when dancing uh there's no you know
nothing i can take a photo of that
proves that i did a workout so
i can't like show it off like i did
before
but i think um
i'll i'll continue
dancing
for for like a while as my workout
dancing and swimming
throughout the summer
my sweaty shirt
you wish
let me take and then i take dance my
contours but through over them
[Music]
i don't think that works so well for
me maybe my feet only but i don't i
don't feel the need to necessarily
improve all the time that i'm doing
something
you know
just wanna mind my own business
sometimes
[Music]
yeah
thank you it's true
oh thank you
[Music]
oh my god
is this real
oh that's so scary
like
i've never been
in
a place before that was
flooded like that
every time i see that in the news or so
i'm like
holy [\h__\h]
how can it ever rain that much
damn
[Music]
it's crazy yeah if you google i'm i'm
looking at the pictures right now you
guys
[Music]
oh god i hope
it's gone soon
the only thing you can do there is
weight right
[Music]
oh my god
people can't even go to work like this
can they
is the underground plotted too in that
case like
because like normally the entrances to
the underground are open so
do supports get flooded too
yeah
oh man
so you can't use subway you can't use
your car so you don't have to go to work
right
at least unless you're like i don't know
if you work in a convenience store maybe
you have to go because you have to
supply to others
swim to work
isn't that a crazy thought
wait it out there's no cars functioning
but not this
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
ah
that sounds terrifying i'm so sorry guys
man
yeah oh no oh no you have to stay at
home when you watch my streams on
youtube
wait maybe there's maybe maybe today for
once there's no one standing in line for
the annual cafe because getting there is
a paid in the ass to begin well
at this point
i wonder
if anybody's still standing in line
there today
i'm
i i'm impressed
is that
uh on the ground level
do any korean bros know or is the shop
on a higher level because if it's on the
ground level you can't even really enter
it right
how do you how do you
oh it's on the it's on the ground level
wait what's happening to the shop
is it
is a shop flooded
[Music]
i'm gonna ask
save the merch
the shop was safe for a day
i visited yesterday for a little menu oh
if it was fine yesterday did it escalate
so quickly so flooding
sorry i'm really curious i'm very bad
you guys
gotta cut out looking somewhere no
save the quinoa cut out
oh my god it just happened tonight oh
overnight oh
how long does it normally take for
flooding like that to go back to drain
it all out
assuming that the rain itself stopped
how long does that take
fire in the water
let's know
[Music]
oh
i can only hope for the best all right
continue
uh
and uh this korean super chat is
actually asking about the same topic
[Music]
i'll um flight didn't get cancelled so
far
i think it should be fine to at least
arrive in korea
yeah
i think the flight is not in danger
unless the whole airport is blooded but
i doubt it because it's just like
you know the landing area is just
completely flat right so i don't see how
how such a big flat area
maybe i don't know but i can't
imagine it being
blooded
that will be fine
time and duncan mapped in a junction
reduction
silverado thank you for the
pinky today i was riding an uber
watching the beginning of the tunic
stream oh at the end the driver said to
me it was nice driving with you you were
always smiling
oh
really that's how you're affecting
people foxtrol
oh that's cute
you couldn't help but smile when you
were watching my stream quietly oh
but it's a little bit creepy that
would rather
notice that you were always smiling when
he was supposed to focus
that means he kept looking back at you
several times
i can't help but see the creepy side of
that
thank you though for watching even while
you're traveling thank you
yeah hope you had a safe trip home
poseidon god of the sea donkey shin
hey ho dina samia thank you for the
birthday chad i have been working a lot
recently so i haven't managed to catch
many streams live i have no idea what is
going on at the moment but i hope you're
having fun this game looks cute is it
difficult so i already kind of answered
this book
it's supposed to be difficult but i i'm
just too good for it so
[Music]
yeah
if you were playing you would probably
struggle more with it than me
but that's okay you should still play it
it's really good i 100 recommend it
thank you so much mwah
michael longhorn for the pinky now we
don't really dance winter's dancing it's
induction
[Music]
foreign
during boston
yeah
i was very focused today and and still
screaming sorry
phoenix 261 to the understanding tracy
thank you
[Music]
i tried playing this game a few months
ago and i got totally wrecked you hear
this guys
so watching my intention kicking this
game's ass is cathartic
oh
yeah i'm basically taking revenge for
you that's you can take it like that
thank you
[Music]
i'm on a roll it seems yeah
don't worry again when next game i play
i will suck again don't glory
i will be terrible especially tomorrow
because tomorrow
we will be playing mario kart
and
we'll be playing it
the same time as it was previously
planned but one hour earlier
just so you know
with the girls and with the viewers and
i will suck
that will be really bad
[Music]
horrible
you are welcome to join guys
yeah
i will still bet on you
[Music]
in german we say
the hoffmann
let's
the hulk dies last
merry pippins thank you
you missed this thanksgiving jacob
twenty-seven out thank you
dude
[Music]
even though she never wins
i just never win in mario games okay
brandon danke
look thank you soon
thank you
the game of thrones
so shook that difficult games are easier
for you than children's games like maui
and self
how the other game is so easy that you
expect more of them
you're really good at these games
i don't know what it is i don't know
i also wouldn't say that's necessarily
true
mario triggers the [\h__\h] on me
[Music]
hey i wasn't that good an alden ring i
was normal
[Music]
ah thank you for the flash chats and
then brandon facebook thinking depending
on when the next stream is this is this
might be my last super chat for a while
oh i'm going to scotland for a family
wedding and to scout out the expanding
domain of lady cuhawa i hope you have a
great trip and i'll be into the vlog as
soon as i may oh thank god i thought
this was like um like a more dramatic
and sad goodbye but that sounds that
sounds okay
yeah and wedding
sounds nice and fun
i want to go to a family wedding tour
like any wedding sounds fun like yummy
free food
gonna be gone a week oh i mean i'll be
gone for like a while
not that bond would like i'll not be
putting up that much content
probably so it's a good timing actually
have a safe trip
a fun wedding
and yeah i'll see you soon hopefully
don't forget about me
i won't forget about you
[Music]
thank you for letting me know
thank you monkey thank you
boxing eight thanks for the pinky hey
guys so here's my report from crx oh
interesting the kfb booth was very
popular even on the final day it had a
long line let's go
artist ally had a ton of whole life
posters stickers and keychains i got a
kitchen instead of you and nina sadly i
did never see ya go off
oh
[Music]
are you sure though
maybe he walks past you and he just
didn't notice
but that sounds great i wish i could
have seen it in person oh man
this sounds fun
thank you for going there and supporting
holland live and watching the panel i
didn't even know until after your panel
yeah yeah yeah but i think that's good
that not you know you're not the only
one a lot of people didn't notice until
after the panel
yeah
on the first day you know when when i
had my meet and greet he wasn't even at
the convention i think
because i didn't see him i wasn't told
he was there
he didn't come until the second day
and then after the panel he started
taking all these pictures
and went to the meet and greets and all
that
so
yeah
i wonder if he tried the food
not probably he got some more
proper food outside
[Music]
yeah he was having fun i'm glad he had
fun i hope he was impressed you know i
hope that the ian fandom and the
popularity
left a good impression on him
so that he will
you know believe more in us and invest
more in us
i really hope so i hope i hope he was
you know thinking oh damn these girls
i'm glad i hired them um
[Music]
yeah
there's definitely
a big difference in like atmosphere and
vibes of a
overseas convention compared to japanese
conventions
i wonder what he was thinking of all the
all the crowds
yeah
i feel like you know even if he was
would be wrong walking around an event
like this in japan at most
most visitors would also be very
reserved and not too shy or like
they didn't wouldn't want to bother him
by asking him for a photo
like stuff like that you know
not that it would bother him i'm sure he
would be fine with it
like i feel like everybody's a little
more reserved over there
[Music]
he's probably overwhelmed with how much
people love him yeah
i hope i hope you felt the love he
surely did
i think people overwhelmed him with
cheers when they saw him like probably a
lot of people were like holy [\h__\h] oh my
god
i wonder what his idol's signature looks
like
one of you got a signature you should
show me what it looks like i want to see
it i never saw his signature i mean
probably isn't my contract but but i
want to see his idol signature
i want to see
show me xiaomi xiaomi
[Music]
i showed it where
you posted as well
[Music]
saw something else
you know today i i answered to a a tweet
from um dumb tendo
where you know it's a german youtuber
who was complaining about hot weather
and i was like holy [\h__\h] in german
and then like
people who seem to be both my fan and
his fans
are like replying like holy [\h__\h] this is
the weirdest crossover in history that
i've ever seen and then tagging someone
else like look at this holy [\h__\h]
and then that random person is answering
oh it's the german avengers avengers
then uh someone else is like oh my god i
would have never expected to see a
youtuber under don't tend to his post
very unexpected oh my god kiara is here
[Music]
reaction's funny
he doesn't follow me back though
no this makes that fight just kidding
he probably doesn't give a [\h__\h] about
youtubers and things like what the [\h__\h]
is this what is this cringe
[\h__\h]
okay let me see what everybody
is
this
photo of yago's signature
oh my god
did you tag me you didn't tag me did you
you have to look up your account huh
when i type in trevor i just get like
the dating show and [\h__\h]
[Music]
what do i have to type in again
here's tax bank
[Music]
it's so simple
come on jaggo step up your idol game
[Music]
that's a boring signature
not impressed
oh man
not much of an idol after all
but damn you got something really rare i
don't think he's been giving out many
signatures outside of this event
look at that
[Music]
i'll show it here let's see it all
all of you can see
jago's signature on a day pass of the
event
see it's so normal okay
that is definitely not the signature
that's on my contract
ah fortune signature and sign a new
contract of 10 times salary
oh
[Music]
genius
i shall do that
noise you don't see it yes it's on the
black skirt
it's hard to see at first but it is
there
open your eyes
yeah right right on the skirt and i'll
define
[Music]
okay
okay okay
i can't believe his legal signature is
not juggle
glad you enjoyed the boss fights yeah
we almost feel pity for those bosses
don't we
[Music]
can't call them boss really
okay refreshing
krishna
[Music]
when you come to korea there are
delicious foods such as korean barbecue
and tofu
it's so cute the name is silky
but i recommend korean fried chicken oh
make sure to try korean fried chicken
with this money i will thank you i will
definitely yeah yeah yeah i have korean
barbecue before in germany but
i will try it probably also in korea to
see the difference
i think it was pretty
legit though the place that we
[Music]
yeah i'm went try it out in korea too
yum yum yum yum
and honestly i must at least on one day
i'm sorry but i will eat japanese food
in korea because i assume that in korea
there they probably because they're so
close they probably have a lot of good
japanese food too and i miss i miss
japanese
so
yeah
let's see i hope they have some tonkatsu
i wanna eat some tonkatsu i wonder if
they have a good tonkatsu place
i'm sure they have some good japanese
restaurants too
yeah
yes
[Music]
i went to the place and dressed up again
the other day
oh don't make me dallas empty your
stomach and give what's inside to me
i want i want i want
[Music]
oh my god that sounds amazing
thank you
it was a bit of a line situation for
alma and gordon's panel and then you're
planning with eno but everyone is
definitely cheering
oh yeah i mean i still
i still saw people walking in after um
like continuously
after like 20 minutes into the panel
yeah
they should have landed people earlier
was there even anything going i guess
like maybe like some kind of
rehearsal but we were muted anyway they
could have left in people earlier i
think
yeah because it kind of
i kind of hope that
you know they would see the full panel
but when it takes so long to get in to
begin with
they were counting how much they could
let in all
oh
people got an earlier one still hectic
ah
oh well yeah
that's all right at least you can watch
whatever you missed um in the pod
if you were still standing in line
just like it took on me too
because like my my performance was being
live streamed there were people who were
trying to get into the convention
couldn't get in
waiting outside in the line because
people were [\h__\h] slow because not
everyone wanted to go to the panel
so the ones who wanted to go to the
panel were walking fast but the ones in
front of them who were not
you know wanting to go to the panel were
just taking it easy taking it slow
so
a lot of people couldn't get in and they
were watching the
the
the live performance
on twitch while standing in line
yeah
i should have had like two different
lines the people who want to go in fast
and people who want to go in slow
[Music]
thank you for the pinky you said air
conditioner is all available to install
in your apartment and have you tried air
cooler
now you should get one the super chat
would be the fun also have fun korean
travel safe thank you
i don't know are they really effective i
feel like i used one before years ago
and i think they're not really effective
my my fan that i bought i bought a
cool
dyson fan
that one has been
doing quite well during the heat wave
days and now thank god the past
two or three days
have um been way more chill
it cooled down
by a lot
so for now i'm fine
i just hope it doesn't come back so soon
now it's coming back no [\h__\h] way yeah
well good that i'm escaping
into
a country that currently has monsoon
season
[\h__\h]
but that's better than the heat wave to
me right now okay
let me check some forecasts oh no it
looks fine
looks okay
where i am how about zone
i didn't check the weather report oh
rain rain rain thunder rain
[Music]
100 90 90
90 80
70 60
oh
wow
i
air coolers work but not with high
humidity oh
okay
oh
[Music]
well
it's okay i'll buy a cute umbrella
i do like ame yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah
you know this could still change like
i've seen weather reports that
turned out to be the complete opposite
anyone
you know
i mean i mean whatever i have to stay
positive but even then it doesn't bother
me much because i'm not on a beach
vacation so it's fine yeah
i just want to eat a lot of food and
usually i think i will be eating food
inside so
and shopping also inside so
all good all good
[Music]
sharing an umbrella with navi well
crappy times first time oh i still have
the
mosquito spray from the maldives but i
wonder where i put it if i find it i'll
bring it
thanks for telling me
okay bless you
thank you thank you i know thanks for
the pinky if you searched so close oh
yeah i already did
yeah
i hope i hope it gets better
thank you for warning me i wasn't aware
of this it's pretty bad pretty bad
i'm hungry lulu come sign me down for
the pink super chat thank you hope
you're safe by the way from the water
thank you thank you for the rest of my
chat hey attention now that we have
hollow meets discover still okay with
you going to cons we the fans request
for you to be invited to of course
that's basically what soul popcorn is
wondering if they've gotten more choose
you live where you go
no in the end it's kind of my decision
mostly
for the korean browns are fans able to
leave gifts or letters at the soulcon
for you letters definitely um gifts that
are
thicker than paper
probably not no
um
[Music]
probably not
but yeah um you're welcome to continue
to
[Music]
request me as a guest at conventions
already
even for the next year if you wanna
early next year or so i don't know
spring conventions maybe
i would love to be a guest
to be your guest oh yes
i haven't tried that since last year
continue
national plumbers convention
they will be terrified if they see my
face there
i can't go there i'm banned for life
vancouver expo oh sounds fun
vancouver canada
i don't have magic fans in canada but
i would be honored to go anywhere
honestly
oh thank you unknown thank you that's so
sweet
i'll be always worried about my honesty
thank you for always making me so happy
every single day
thank you for being such a sweetheart
so kind
i'm glad i can make your day better
and be part of your day thank you for
letting me
thank you jacobs monkey
here's some of you i know but still not
so many i feel like the most
canada fans are like i don't know for
crony and inna maybe i don't know
which is fine
it's okay
do you have actual numbers on the
regions of your fans i don't really pay
attention to that i don't look at the to
be honest i
i barely ever look at the youtube
analytics
i maybe look at them once in half a year
to be honest
yeah
yeah yeah i really don't look at them
the only thing i really look at is
uh
how many viewers
the stream i just did extreme i just
ended hand
to see how
uh
how
much you guys liked this particular
stream
how much you like the game or the
whatever i did
that's the only thing i look at i don't
look too much at the analytics
uh
because there's usually nothing new
there really it doesn't change so
drastically either over time
an explosive tunic and the presentation
has always been great and very warming
to older new audiences thank you
i'm happy you think so
wow
i live in alberta i can guarantee to say
oh
i made me a chimpanzee for you but my
ocean and love is amazing
what's going on in your
in your
chat message confused
it's okay i i don't know why what even
what
[Music]
oh man
funny okay
i love amateur
it's okay
anyway every here's the case for you
catch it wow
40 degrees is normal
actually very easy to hang on when you
are at the close um
you know i guess so but still oh my god
[Music]
during the rainy season this year i have
two nickels which is not much but it's
way that it happened twice
yeah especially because it wasn't even
in the same months
goddammit
[Music]
oh
i just got some
work-related message but
he's fine i don't mind
oh this discord i'm i'm done with super
chat and i need food
and uh turn off my brain uh
i have something to do tomorrow
[Music]
early early in the day oh dear
um
yeah i think i have a lot of things to
do tomorrow
so that's why it's actually good that
tomorrow will just be mario kart late in
the evening
i'll see you guys there
and uh
yeah
thanks for today i had a blast with
tunic once again
it was the right choice to play it again
i think
yeah
thank you so much guys um
six and a half hour stream because you
know
rest of the week the streams might not
be that long
[Music]
but here you have your your long doses
of long kiwawa
today okay
treasure it
[Music]
bye bye
i wish i could do that face
i'll request it
maybe
bye-bye
[Music]
see you later
i hope you're safe
bye-bye guys take care
make the most out of your day have some
good food
[Music]
i did
[Laughter]
ba
[Music]
do
meow
[Music]