[Music]
do
so
[Music]
cakey
hello
hello hello everybody
welcome
to
a new series
we're going to play
yakuza 0 today
kyoka
has
yeah
what i have cute chicken on the top
right oh
it's uh yes oh that's um
um cute chick baby chick um
not me not a photo of me no
well it's been a while since we last
played a yakuza game but my voice is a
bit of what you mean it's normal
don't make me feel self-conscious
uh we're gonna probably be snacking a
lot too
because i have snacks laying around and
uh i have a big big hugger
i have
big hunger
it's time to make her proud wait who
you mean uh my dear coco senpai
well i don't know if she's watching but
[Music]
i will do my best
my mom is not here anymore
so that's good
that's good
let's go yakuza zero
he goes up
you guys um i think told me
that this is kind of the beginning of
the story even though it's one of the
more recent games is that true today i
got something wrong
no system there what do you mean
what
there we go
it is
interesting that's good it's a prequel
[Music]
a 10th anniversary project begins no
total i can't open my [\h__\h]
can't capture anymore
[Music]
starting off strong
hey
[Music]
this is the opening
oh my god
that's what will be
experiencing oh hot showers
uh what was his name again the the
the one that with the eye
i thinking
don't cry
[Music]
oh yes your back mustard
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh walking footsteps oh
[Laughter]
great captain thank you thank you
i was just trying to process everything
that i was seeing
um on my obs screen
um you know
something i don't understand when a
window is open but it doesn't open
you know what i mean
you know what i mean no you don't
ours is not open
[Music]
i minimized something and now i can't
open it anymore even though it's
supposed to be
open task manager helped me
uh
uncattle game capture
end this task
i'll be right back
good thing is it still continues on obs
okay wait a few seconds
one
two
three
four
five i hate when it happens such a scam
i guess so
right
[Music]
what let's get right in i am oh
so the thing is that the last yakuza
game that we played was
i had a different battle system because
up until then yakuza games were always
a
different battle system
the the new one introduced the new one
basically
so i don't know
like easy normal so normal okay we can
handle normal probably
but it will be different
oh so this is uh
this is the famous uh
kirill guy right
ryan
handsome
you just beat someone else
what did he do to you
the legend
[Music]
you're a good man aren't you
can i take a bite into my sandwich
what did you do
oh
[Music]
is that a jack book or an ipad
they look so dead
okay
his business here is done
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
your haircut sucks all right
oh
[Music]
tonight
please don't hurt me
[Laughter]
that's nice
they respect him good to see
[Laughter]
all right i'm eating a mozzarella tomato
ciabatta sandwich by the way
um
damn he can speak without moving his
lips damn him too they're both
ventriloquists what
konoma
foreign
[Music]
me
so he's not a yakuza yet
but he's probably gonna become one
[Music]
yes baby
yeah we're hearing that track again
ugaki wait oh we're not talking about
characters is this is this credits or
characters
oh
damn
[Music]
ah the blood on this cheek makes him
look even hotter
[Music]
that's just red wine just tell them his
red wine
[Music]
let her call her boyfriend come on
a pager is it a pager what an ancient
item he has damn
only seen that ever before in scrubs
[Music]
fascinating
beeper
[Music]
his territory chapter one bound by oaf
oh he's getting married beautiful
one second uh let me check something
really quickly
i'll i'm looking at obs screen at the
same time don't worry
i see what's happening
this is where nishiki said he'd meet me
guess i beat him here okay wait one
second i need to check something um
i think
um
okay
sorry i need to say i will need to add a
spoiler alert to the title i just
realized
just realized it
spoiler alert
[Music]
kill you and majima no kiriyo nishiki
what is that the same person
nishiki majima
[Music]
here
spoiler alert
okay
[Music]
okay we're good to go
i'm playing on ps5 by the way
seven two four one oh six huh that's the
quote for what you're up to
really wait no nee she
[Music]
she
no
what
i'm trying to
i'm trying to translate it to japanese
with the numbers i guess the the the
seven could be a na and the two could be
a knee so nani what
you
don't know about the rest the nanny
nanny said
me she did
[Laughter]
yeah kind of stretched but it still
works i'm waiting for you slow ass to
show up
that's right may as well have a look
around and see if i can find him
find nishikiyaba
okay i'm so tall and broad
[Music]
probably not
i i want to hear what that music was oh
oh there's so much going on yes this is
uh in shinjuku i think
i definitely have seen places like this
in shinjuku
so colorful
i mean i don't really
not really my thing but
i kind of usually scared to go around
places like this at least in the evening
time it should be
done
oh
right but i also feel like a
culture definitely definitely exists as
well
running shakedowns on our tariffs
somebody needs to set them straight
before they try anything really stupid
oh really
okay
i guess this is our uh fighting tutorial
is
foreign
[Music]
all right show me what you got
uh
press square repeatedly to perform a
rash combo this is the most basic method
of attacking battle square okay
smash smash
eleven more times okay
can i like lock on
no
wonder
five four
oh
[Music]
okay
press a triangle during a square couple
attack to perform a finishing blow that
knocks the enemy down the knockdown
effect varies depending on the number of
the times
square was pressed to try it in a few
ways okay
like that
[Music]
get out of
cards the here guys on the top uh left
sorry is the music allowed it's really
intense right now the yellow gloss on
the top left indicates your health the
game will end if the yellow part is
fully depleted so keep an eye on your
health at all times
it looks fine right now if the gauze
flash is red it means you're in very bad
shape it should replenish your health
immediately hell for current remembers
use a recovery item or eat something on
an eatering okay
press a circle near an enemy to grab
them if an enemy is guarding to block
your attacks grab them and attack to
deal damage okay
[Music]
the training's not complete it's time to
wipe the the smirks off your opponent's
faces if you get hit you can strike back
right away using uh
remote buttons this is called a resolute
counter you can gain money by knocking
down or defeating enemies uh-huh
depending on how you do it you might get
a bonus too so try a range of different
moves
[Music]
ringing
jingle bells jingle bells jingle all the
way oh
in your stomach
um
it's a stomach massage
makes your bowel movement smoother you
know you're welcome
hello
foreign
i guess so
sounds like i'm sure yeah
really is it really him
um
hmm yeah
damn
getting all those jobs getting that
money
foreign
nope
you guys know in german where there's a
funny word to make fun of uh
mw's
again bavarian bavarian [\h__\h] car
i'm nothing against them
it has the same letter it's the same
your hitbox is too big oh our twofold
oh that's so easy okay i can walk slowly
right behind him so i don't bump into
him
sorry that was too loud right i didn't i
shouldn't get too close to you
i'm just gonna
[Music]
the color is a little bit poopish oh
wait it's not oh that's gold it's not
your car it's not your car
don't tell me it's that over there
i'm a nice guy to hang out with what are
these people that were running into this
yeah
just walk around them
it's like
walking into them
okay
you're gonna invite me for some food
so slow man
walk faster
but cool cool it gives me some time to
look at the area
girl girl universe university students
sm something something
sm
what is this
[Music]
oh
they're completely wasted it's not worth
the trouble let's take a different road
no need i've got a faster way to fix
this oy ahoy on my fist
in your face
yeah
i just need to sew them up a bit with my
face
[Laughter]
what kitty is the aggressive one between
those two
okay let's open them up let's do it
again i can't tell if you're a status or
a charity worker
i don't work for charities
i take these little
lunch money
what do you mean everybody else out of
this scared away yeah without you but
that's how i talk
drunk guards
homophobic
ah watch the heat cause ooh
the three blue glowing bars on the top
left are called the heat gauge the heat
gun starts at the first bar and as your
attacks hit enemies the gauge fills up
shift into the second and then the third
button
at each level your speed increases some
moves require a certain level of heat so
once you are used to fighting keep an
eye on your heat level okay
hey
once the heat goes shift to the second
or third bar here's body begins to glow
with blue aura this is called the heat
mode and the signals that you can use
special heat actions try using heat
actions while still going up the darn
guys okay
oh what
uh uh-huh
[Music]
does that use up any kind of like mana
wow
what what do you want
i don't know where i'm going okay we can
do it again
okay okay
[Music]
nice i love these animations in yakuza
yakuza games
mispronounce what
it's not gosh what is that gorgeous
[Laughter]
gauge
i'll just say gal get in
your training is not complete that
concludes the explanation of the heat
gauge and special moves but the two
drunkards still need some sobriety
beaten into them
get gage
but wouldn't it be g-a-g-e
if it was gage wouldn't it be g-a-g
english language my english professor is
here
just saying you'd think yeah
[Music]
oh gosh it sounds more um elegant and
sophisticated
[Music]
if you take a fighting stance using r1
movement with l will send aha
okay thank you that's kind of like a
lock on like a focus that i was asking
for
okay
um
nice okay it makes it easier are they
still alive
i just got a cute outfit the girl in the
back sparkly
man i already got so much money what is
going on
are you um sobered up
where am i are they are someone up what
is that doing here and who are you
sounds like that's so much love
must be a delicate touch
i remember watching music videos at that
bar then we got to talking about which
idols we liked oh
yeah then some smart uh started making
fun of poor sweet choco chan and then oh
my head's rubbing i can't remember past
that he really sobered them up
he has magic sobering fists what
i think you two have had enough for
tonight go home
yeah i'll i'll go home and watch some
youtuber streams all right youtubers
didn't exist yet during this time
okay
sorry i was just reading the signs um on
the side
well
you okay mister here i'll walk you
through the train take it slow oh thanks
i think i lost my my suica car though
at all's well and that ends well
let's hit the bar let's go
um completion list completing certain
challenges will earn you cp completion
points you can view them from the pause
menu under completion list some are
things that will probably happen on
their own as you play the game but
others will require a more deliberate
effort no no
no no no
no
80s either
one
to access the cp exchange menu where you
can spend cp to earn special blessings
ranging from being able to sprint for
longer distances to earning more cash
from feister big help oh
now your hotel
oh yeah follow follow
what's a waste or damn shame i say
ah
you've got a punch like a two-tone
gorilla and you'll go wasting it on
drunks what do you think that tally was
meant for all that raw fighting prowess
says she's a foreigner gotta make it
really foreign
look i just helped a couple of guys work
off some alcohol that's all yes
yeah that's the point though that's the
problem you want to talk alcohol
you're like taking one you swing from a
vintage bottle and tossing the rest
going from the look of yo yo japanese
mafia eye
something like that
yes
seems like you're pretty confident in a
fight a real dynamite boy
you're calling me boy
don't get ruffled now kade so compared
to me you're practically a taller
hey gary what's the hold up man
sorry so there's some um international
uh uh
situation here
no it says wasting time on this drug i
should just go too much booze is bad for
you grams take care i now hold up wait i
got one pace of advice for y'all
i stop it get some help why i don't need
help
i helped i'm accurately voice acting
and i've got a friend waiting for me
i've got something to say make it quick
i if you guys haven't oh ho
out for a night with your main dog me
and the boys used to really wreck it
back when i was your age
but if you spend all your money playing
around you'll never get stronger you
gotta invest in yourself
what like a gym membership no no
no no that's no better than spending it
on booze i'm talking about investing in
yourself literally you know literature
literally what does it even mean
glad you asked my boy uh here's a
special lecture just for you
ability is now available oh my god that
looks magical
oh my god
i'm supposed to scale down for something
now
fake spirit
that's the first thing i see really
that's the first thing i see i deserve a
bite into my sandwich for that it's
a fate
hmm
[Music]
that when i'm wounded oh
automatically
isn't good
do i need to like in order to get the
second one above i need to first
probably activate this one anyway right
it's
oh
[Music]
and so that's how you do it
um
what's down here oh yeah
maximum health
flying cake
oh
triangle when running
running hmm
oh are these like extra attacks the
little light blue ones
looks like they're extra moves
um
and these are like
um passive
passive
damn stuff
gonna cost a lot of money man
hmm i guess for now
increases the power of your regular
attacks and the heat actions when using
umbrella so i i can't afford okay let's
go for a week one oh no i can't oh i
can't afford anything anymore anyway
okay
money spent thirty thousand
that's like three hundred dollars
okay
oh you keep pouring money into yourself
and with a little training the talent of
yours will grow in no time so keep uh
the woman and wine on the budget here
um investing in myself literally never
thought of that never even knew that i
had a
a menu like that in my body where i
could activate some skills with some
money i didn't know it worked like that
man that's crazy [\h__\h] man
ah i bet you're glad you stopped and
listened now eh
yeah i guess i am
yo kill you
i'm coming
oh that's serious talk at my buzz time
for round two you have a good night my
boy
bye-bye aging foreigner
couldn't even give this magical man a
name huh what a real little man what
weird old man what's his name
um
you can get your fortune here
from a madam
health plaza
um
okay nice beautiful it smells amazing
here like flowers
waxing
[Music]
[Applause]
wrapped around their fingers
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
okay
show me some action
karaoke bar
oh
nice empty
lonely bar
um
[Music]
uh
hmm
foreign
[Music]
is
and then there's the dojima
family which is yakuza
um
[Music]
okay
that we had um
like a dragon
make sure to press the correct buttons
at the right time sounds like it the
better your timing the more points you
will get if your timing is really off it
will not count
when someone else sings you can support
them with interjections or you can
choose either simple or lively
interjections simple injections offer
easier inputs but it won't get more than
90 points for a chance to score more try
lifeline projections okay
um
what are live lanterns then
uh maracas tambourine sing along
okay
[Music]
okay oh
jasmine and
[Music]
can we only do one
i don't know this one so well
i think i've heard it before
oh okay you guys want to hear that one
i want to do both
sing
judgment shin pong
[Music]
ball oh
he's so serious even though there's only
two people listening
oh god what
oh god
oh oh oh
[Music]
okay
hi
[Music]
oh my god it's so difficult i don't know
where the buttons are without looking at
them but i think i'm mostly [\h__\h]
[Music]
breaking the world
i think
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
hi
[\h__\h] no cutscene because that was so bad
[Laughter]
oh man we're close to greatness carl get
boozled
is that my rank
oh no
entertain yourself 10 times i'm always
entertaining myself i'm always
entertained are you not entertained
man
[Music]
um
[\h__\h] there's cat hairs everywhere
well i'm glad we were able to see
karaoke so early on
i don't like wait my sandwich i only
have like two bites left
wait
oh
um
[Music]
that place looks familiar to me it looks
like in
like a dragon
concept
50 a.m
how are they even open at that time damn
um
[Music]
foreign
um
is the same place
someone's trying to what's the word
foreign
someone's trying to set him up
yeah i cannot forget that that mole on
your head
maybe he was
[Music]
then we're watching tv2 at 6 50 a.m who
isn't watching tv at 6 50 a.m
freshly presented
i hope there's no cameras there
foreign
[Music]
is
foreign
you guys like who's kuzai
because i know aniki
i've got to call dojima family
headquarters there should be a payphone
around i wanna pay your phone trying to
calm
all of my uh change i spent on you was
that right
where are the towns
baby
[Music]
wow
okay
bird communication
yes yes
responsibility for the wearing song
i guess i'd better take a taxi to dodgy
my family headquarters all right
[Music]
go to don't see my family headquarters
i wonder if they have like like a taxi
system like we had in
like a dragon
probably not
taxi
why do you mean detours i'm looking for
a taxi when when you don't tell me where
it is so you'll have to look around a
little bit nah
that's so hard to understand okay it's
probably on the big street
i mean detours
map
what
[Laughter]
i'm a
surprised easily so please be nice to me
please be nice to me oh can i take the
how do i use that how do i use the bike
to kill you
i'm easy to startle you
okay
stop startling me i love you
imagine that yakuza game of uh what was
the main character being like a really
easy to start a little
character wouldn't that be funny because
they're supposed to be like really
really
uh
you know badass
i feel like that would be funny
sweat circle to grab yeah i've been
trying that
ah i mean grab the
bicycle now hold on hold no
okay i'll try next time
uh hello let me in
oh wait it looks similar
the
i don't know
could be the same big noodle on the top
right there's a big noodle on the top
right
fake noodle
i love looking at all the signs in this
game
yeah cause i like a phoenix hell yeah
that would be my game i would be the
main character
yeah cause i like the phoenix but easy
to startle
[Music]
am i gonna get thrown out and have to
work my my my way back to the tub
oh
is it gonna cut off a finger or
something
oh god
those flashy
purple suits
these faces oh i'm very sorry so we must
send
[Music]
oh sorry for ruining your golf session
turd mr turtleneck
[Music]
foreign
he called that guy because it's a
japanese insult but it sounds so similar
to his name so i'm making jokes with it
they don't
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
um
whoa
damn it looks really good
bye
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
um
hmm
foreign
so
[Music]
my
okay
is
i don't remember him missing a finger
later on and then like a dragon
no no no no no no you we know you we
know you we know you be no you be
no you'll be no you'll be no no no
you'll be you'll be in no you'll be
no you'll be pleased
no please
looks like that loan shark set me up
yeah buddy
yeah potty
well there's a donkey song bling
i love being in donkey i don't know what
his game is but he and i are going to
what hey boy boy oh
my mommy yeah
you brought a friend oh you're the old
guy from last night
oh finally i've been searching for hours
for me
wait why am i having an italian accent
your rank of booze you wasted
yeah
oh this old town's one big bar it was
made for drinking me and kamojikun here
have been added out in all the whole
night yeah
just certainly
yeah well i'm glad somebody's having a
good morning
you've got a face more sour than a lemon
boy what's wrong i can't promise much
but i'm happy to let you on here
it's uh
i've just got a lot going on right now
uh-huh well all right anyway i had a
favor i wanted to ask you
eh you mentioned you've been looking for
me yeah
actually what sorry but i don't have
time for any of this right now see you
later
thanks i just need you to talk to a
couple guys
they'll be here real soon they'll also
be real angry
oh you're not even listening why should
i take care of you problems the hunger
wakaru
that's a great question awesome they're
real eager to talk to you too
maybe we should talk to them
oh did he just block book
oh oh always speak up the devil here
they are now oh [\h__\h] all right all right
grant's this is the kid
yes
my prize pew pal
who bill i'm sorry i'm the pupil
the millionaire alone i gave these two
deadbeats is way past dude
i need it back and i ain't waiting much
longer
why tell me about it wait don't you
don't expect me to play doyle
that tip i gave you the other day it's
worth all you stop no
why am i
when are you my master anyway boy
i don't really give a [\h__\h] who you are
just giving my money before the big
gentleman behind me gets impatient
oh you don't know who you're dealing
with mr big pants
and mr white pants
bruno here he's got a short fuse
especially for seven times for your own
sake i'd pay up before getting hurt
hey boy
right now
you'll think it could tag big bruno
there in the fight yeah couldn't say for
sure but yes doesn't really matter
either way because you're not going to
drive me into your problems
oh so you think hate beats you
i didn't say that
look if you're trying to baby it's not
going to work it's your depth you handle
[Music]
that's a it down can't have you getting
spooked over jumped like him he's
barking being muscled diamond dozen
bottom of this rocket bracket what are
you even talking about
yeah it's a little whispering voice oh
we weren't really whispering are you
paying or it doesn't get ugly
i told you this is nothing to do with me
oh yes okay all right i'll pay you the
money
wise choice you had money
i feel terrible terrible for all the
hassle of course to tell you what why
don't we make it too much oil
i don't wanna pay me double like i'm
gonna buy that you're drunk off your ass
old man a wife got a money we happy to
give it to you even on wrong condition
yeah where's that
you have your tank back there
fight us for it you have your tank thank
you he beats all three of us the two
million dollars we win and we don't owe
you a thing
well why did you make it to amelia
though
[\h__\h] or not wrong okay
so you're not drunk you're crazy bruno's
famous around here for bursting heads
all three of you could rush at him
wait is the english man gonna join my
team
no
no no okay fights gotta be one one rules
and all three against one wouldn't be
bad
i want to take him on solo well hell if
you don't mind me taking the money of
your corpse i'm game you got yourself a
deal
well that's just lovely
i'll tell you right now i'm not bailing
you out if you don't want to get hurt
i'd start apologizing now
okay i'll call first then
hey are you even listening are you sure
you want to do this
it'll be fine just a little work out
just focus on keeping an eye on the
action boy watch carmoji's move
seriously
and fight
[Applause]
oh
he learns quickly
that's red would he really say that
sounds like something um
a modern girl would say maybe not i
don't know i'm not sure
gotta remember to eat before i do this
stuff
commodity was it what were those moves
just now actually forget it are you okay
you shouldn't push yourself like that
he's fine i told you i didn't ah but you
guys didn't like a single punch on him
ah you're in the clothes homeless dude
bruno's barely got a scratch on them
you're going to try to finish the job
with those weakest punches
i know kamojiko you sit this one out i'm
calling the round as your manager let
the kid take it from here
you know what to do oh thank you tell us
you want thank you don't you boy
oh yeah all right
i meant it when i said i wouldn't bail
you out but watching him just put me in
the mood for a quick round aha
he wants a taste of those moves right
then on onto the on on to round two of
the two million murder parade bruno take
him
come on
come on closer i want to sniff your
perfume you can switch to rush style by
pressing left on the directional buttons
okay
oh
an advantage of the one advantage of the
rash sellers you can evade with a series
of quick steps for pressing x repeatedly
you can combo up to three of them
together
uh-huh
use this to avoid i mean wipe them off
okay
oh wait i can't hold him anymore
okay wait wait
all right hey
[Laughter]
really is this okay
we use rhinestone moves to crush bruno
and showing with buzz when using the
right style you can spend enemies by
hitting them a certain amount of times
attacks on sound enemies will knock them
down without fail so square attacks are
effective against those that are hard to
knock on the ground
there we go
oh [\h__\h]
there
oh
in this sense i can't pick anything up
right
[Music]
i'm holding my controller like really
tightly like my grip is so strong right
now
i get really
tense when i do these battles today for
some reason
ah horses have been brutal barely got a
punch in just who the hell are you
fight y'all fight y'all
no grabs only speed
hold up okay okay okay
okay okay
nice carrio doji my family which family
are you guys with
well wait you're a proper yakuza
sorry sir i didn't know we just worked
for toco credit oh toco credit
i got a chicken to
rip out the feathers with you guys
there's a german saying and who can't
hope for media it's a german saying
directly translated to i gotta rip out
of the feathers of a chicken with you
um
it is really a german state
when you're angry at someone and have
some business to
finish with someone literally
[Laughter]
yeah alberta pluck
yes
well there's a coincidence i have
business with your boss need to meet him
need need to meet with him as soon as
possible you know where he is right now
i'm president i figured he'd be a
dolphin sentence over
i see that's in a building on tai hay
boulevard east right i'll pay him a
visit and then rip his
feathers out okay
you can pluck me anytime
i have a bone to pick with you yeah
that's like it's like that
and tax care of that little depth of
hours right
yeah fine dance damn bruno here we'll
have to cover the difference oh [\h__\h]
that's how our kind of depth collection
works
ah
all right it's a tough world as hell
yeah
better get moving come on bruno
figure it out well bruno
go brother run bye-bye bruno what's nice
fighting with ya
i tell them something oh
just who are you why approach me what
are you asking me is
well people you call me bacchus
bacchus like wine
and i came to you because i had an angry
frog on my back
but yeah nice of you to dump him on me
look if you're in some travel tell me
maybe i can help and that goes for him
too those aren't moves of an amateur
what's his deal
yeah i know i know that wine god thanks
to
medieval festivals
yeah you're supposed to pronounce it
bachelors i think
i'm pretty sure
[Music]
not bat chews by the way
a real stale of battle is what it is
he's got a gig sweeter than honey real
fascinating to watch you should go have
a look too boy
i can't watch his job but he's homeless
right what kind of work does he do
he's a what you call it a festive rs a
podcast a boxer that's right boxer
wood that's not really my scene
that ain't it it's a punch out artist oh
it did sounds better punch-out artist
sorry about that
all right so what's a punch-out artist
the customer pays a fade and they get to
throw as many punches at me as they like
oh wait here's the commodity was talking
okay
i don't think i followed this some u.s
and everything
nah nothing like that come on by and
watch if you got questions i work in the
shih tzu cuckoo parking lot yes
yes
kamoji [\h__\h] here's got a plenty to teach
you about fighting my boy you'll kick
yourself if you don't check it out okay
okay okay i'll go
i'll swing by sometime
it's katelyn you're shouting from the
dorchester my family right i'll be
waiting see you soon bye bye take care
well that takes care of my troubles for
today i suppose i still can't convince
you to take on the world
the world what does that even mean
salvador are you still trying to recruit
me into pro-fighting or whatever that is
that's exactly what it was you've got
potential most men cat i would dream
about the world champion type title coop
videos
is it gonna be like a side side thing
and not some stereotype kid who would
fall for that line if you're looking to
scout somebody keep looking
i'll tell you one thing boy you keep
living straight fights to street fight
you'll wind up with a knife between your
ribs and some dark ally
that's no way to get out
you belong in the light in the spotlight
and i can't get you under all the bright
bright ones what you say you want me
versus the world the ragdoll
[Music]
you're not going to change your life
around because some old jesus
asked you to a giza or jesus jesus i'll
get it i'll give up for now with that as
i made i'm giving up for goods you got
room to grow on a tree i'll keep on
coaching you along the way i'm bothering
you even if you don't want it you've got
skills as a trainer that much i believe
but i'm really not in a position to be
worrying about anybody by myself right
now sorry about hey maybe i'll see you
around all right my boy just steer clear
cher shut up are you trying to jinx me
say a lot of buckles stop drinking so
much wine
sodas
okay
taco credit
okay run
wait am i i guess i'm running now okay
i'm figuring it out
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
there we go
[Music]
you were just trying to hit me huh no no
that ain't happening no no no change
your plans buddy yeah
[Laughter]
oh buddy
wait so can you go into the stores as
well in in this game
it looks like it ah yes
smell burger
smile burger
oh
cool
i love that feature
got your face looks like it's um
two-dimensional
yeah it is
they pasted on like some jpeg on her
face unfortunate okay
i'm sorry about that
hi
uh wait i don't even know if i need to
eat something right now but i want to i
guess free spot
[Music]
can i have a free smile
here
she comes change her same way
maybe she has too much botox in her face
because like literally it didn't change
at all
her lips did not move a millimeter
girl you got too much plastic in your
face
that's all i wanted
that's all i wanted thanks um
these people want to fight
no
you look like you wanted to fight
okay
no sorry
it's really very similar to
like a dragon like the way these
this like besides the fighting system i
like that it's like so similar
i like those features oh right here
here
poco credit that is
that loan sharks office we have arrived
did i roast her too much
don't know what they're up together
better go in prepared oh get ready i
guess yeah
ah it's not gonna be that bad but maybe
we should get something to eat
a little boost we can eat here too right
you're done you're done
you don't please
all right where do i enter from the sun
you're down boys
oh and safe okay
how about mossy and quantity ones
people
know the sample i got sukina beef bowl
so this is the the
oh wait we have so much money holy [\h__\h]
do we just order everything like oh no
okay i guess not
smell beef bowl
manual save with boombox is not a bad
idea oh manual save with boombox i don't
even know how to save in the game
because like in like a dragon you could
buy several at once but here it look
like it's like one by ones but um so i
don't know if you're supposed to buy
like all of them
uh wait so can you not save
uh
no
i guess you have to say for the phone
boo the game didn't even tell me
it's over there okay thank you chat
thank you
uh-huh
you're just safe twice oh sorry
no auto save okay
well then
scoozy
meet goofy i need to get into this
building now
together credit let's go
enter the building
cash lets me level up oh yeah rides oh
yeah right
it always saves twice on facebook
oh system yeah system data
it still does that devil say thing yeah
apparently
they're approaching me
welcome committee
those are going to kill your cousins
[Music]
oh god oh god
i'm spilling orange juice
um
[Music]
this game is really great if you want to
learn japanese insults
wait i still need to learn
r1 i thought that was focusing on
someone
take the elevator
are we done
i want to fight someone
all right so how would i use that
i don't know
we're still in battle music but
okay
oh i don't um arrow is showing me
everything i could use
can i take something with me
oh
okay let me go to the elevator
oh wait i'm gonna have to leave it okay
oh [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
the trash can really scares me okay now
it's done it's gone okay
[Applause]
okay let me try
[Music]
oh he's like really mad that's why he's
glowing red i suppose
okay now so far so far so good
like that i'm able to move around but i
i like the non non-round uh
bass
challenge
oh
heat moves i don't right i kind of don't
know how to do heat moves
hello
[Music]
you [\h__\h] why did you frame me
he has a gun and he's so scared of me
really
okay
moves
if you see try a marker at the top right
you can do a heat move with triangle
okay
is that the one that that shows like a
cut scene
oh
that was so soft
that looked so soft
uh
looks really gentle
[Music]
oh no
he wants to kill me with smoking oh no
oh no he wants to give me cancer oh no
over the course of many many many many
many many years
what a slow way to make someone die
he's poisoning me
with cigarettes
my lungs are screaming
no
cute
um
i guess
because
um
[Music]
foreign
what you gonna do
[Music]
oh
foreign
he's gonna
play a risky game here
yeah we should just uh
kill cousin right now
for being a backstabbing [\h__\h]
not a hudo a number i don't recognize
it's not his number but that's good to
be here that's got to be nishiki calling
i'll find the phone and call him back
okay find a pay phone okay
finding your pay phone to call me see
you bro
it's the
[Music]
oh i can't even go into a restaurant
right now what is that what are those
signs
yes yes i know there's a payphone here
probably maybe someone else
um
foreign
okay
you guys we're not going by taxi we're
just gonna walk
let's go
oh what are you doing what is that sign
it gives you tissues tissues
what tissue tissue
pocket tissues
those people are everywhere in japan and
in summer besides pocket dishes there's
always people handing out um uchivas
fans
um round fans though not the one that
you fold round fans with like
advertisements yeah it's a real thing
they're like everywhere
especially in streets like these because
they um usually have like
if you get a shiboti from uh
a tissue from a guy like this it usually
has an advertisement for like one of
those
one of those sassy
wait a second
one of those sassy uh shops here on it
yeah yeah like advertisements for chiaba
your back is officially cracked
don't don't question the shopkins better
not question them at all
wait i wanna i wanna take the bike
i want to take her by google i want no
no problem
i wanted to take the bicycle i almost
said one million yo
yeah yeah are you sorry how sorry are
you how sorry are you tell me about it
some of the npcs have uh like a they
look like they're out of sims one like
her hair looks like she's a character
from sims 1.
and if you didn't play sims 1 then you
probably don't know what i'm talking
about
but these main characters look really
good them like damn i'm impressed
well wait which one this one right the
more serious looking place okay
yeah you get me you get one thing
um i should buy medicine oh wait oh oh
i'm not gonna be warned about going
inside and i suppose there's not gonna
be a fight round with suica
with a watermelon ramen with a one
that's like pudding pineapple and pizza
for some people probably
but pineapple and pizza is okay
watermelon on the ramen what the [\h__\h]
what the hell
[Music]
ah
yeah i think he looks familiar
i think i've seen someone with a nanny
was him like a dragon
what
m
foreign
[Music]
where the owner is
foreign
it's gonna start floating
um
foreign
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
good
oh
that had some power in it
why why is everyone always using your
fists to talk huh
let's use our lips
love
well you do use your lips to talk don't
ya
what i meant
oh that shop is called mamma mia video
uh cafe mamma mia on the right side
mama mia nishiki should be waiting with
the car i need to get to showboat street
all right
thank god
i feel like uh
um
i feel like it's going pretty fast here
man
i want to eat something first though if
i'm allowed
let me go eat something with this
dramatic music in the background
purple a purple i can buy probably items
to go here maybe a good idea
yeah yeah yeah can i get healing arms
here oh
instant ramen oh yakisoba oh glasses oh
my god i need those glasses
oh i love convenience store food
oh bento bento bento sandoichi bento
onigiri
oh jagariko jagariko
[Music]
which one is the
sensitive one
i think fraga is like uh
what's like um
exposing magazine
that actually exists
king
[Music]
oh wait i can't look inside what about
your friday
oh
a gossip and photo magazine published
every friday by coding sets full of the
most recent political scandals as i told
you
like real life idol scandals show up in
here and the latest love affairs of
trendsetting celebrities
yeah
uh hot dog praise
wait i love the music in the back
cooldowns magazines for men packed with
practical advice articles about men's
fashion and lifestyle oh it's especially
popular among fashionable younger men
spent christmas with my girlfriend that
girl's clothes are so cute
i don't know okay no etching magazine
where are the etsy magazines nevermind
oh the music i could stay in here
forever
just vibe to the music also it's really
hard to get around these corners
okay so you must stand
hello
oh oh it has the same items
uh this is a little health boost okay
uh try just your heat okay why not
health and heat
so this heals health as well
it doesn't say so but i i would guess so
um
oh mama
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah food is healing pantolon's good
healing yeah
get more get more i love bento lunch
exposed to buying normal shampoo you
mean
as opposed to a gravy
legendary drink of rico
supplement effective against hangovers
oh
[Music]
pocket tissues
okay
[Music]
oh that's all okay
buying
damn that cost me like 90 bucks all of
that
okay i still want to go to a restaurant
medicine better okay but i still i do
want some there's limited inventory
space oh then we gotta eat eat eat eat
eat
we can eat one now i guess
uh
eat uh
[Music]
use how much does it do
okay
not full but okay
we got some good food now can i use it
in the middle of a battle
[Music]
foreign
yeah okay
if there's no way to stay inside then
maybe maybe there's like a last bus who
i can save
but okay
uh
yeah yeah
double safe here we go
oh
they say no
of course yes
and skills
can i do the skills anywhere anytime
okay uh
abilities
ah
oh man they're so expensive
let me look at rash abilities
power search increases are probably
gonna test when you're done
[Music]
power surge
all right all right that's probably
why it's so quick and easy to make money
in this game
that's that's that's your car
that's your fancy car i guess it's it's
okay it's okay looking truly not as
fancy as that gold car that we saw in
the beginning
but
it's a
[Music]
foreign
baby queen
[Music]
dramatic
looks like he's crying but he's not
you know
[Music]
foreign
hmm
i was thinking the same thing bro
[Music]
um
oh
sweet
bro
my
bro bruh
as bayless likes to say
bro
but the heads are like
what she opens the door so confidently
i'll always only open it like a little
bit
more very carefully
um
[Music]
then
i
[Music]
please kusen no aniki
ah
wait is he even wearing that one
oh really when is he watching downtown
[Music]
i need to look sophisticated
you wanna fight
huh
okay okay it's one
i have my face still i'm just draw a
fist fight come on
your little [\h__\h] he using my freeze okay
you'll pay for that that's my phrase
nobody else uses that you little [\h__\h]
now i'm mad you
can't know that's my freaking
um
[Music]
his voice was breaking
us
[Music]
mmm
hey
um
[Music]
don't think that dojima will find that
find out about that though
and question your actions
uh
we successfully left it okay that's good
[Music]
punch
okay
[Music]
m
all of them all of them against one okay
oh oh okay
yeah
but not all at once right they're gonna
keep on coming right
really
oh
maybe shouldn't be standing in the
middle of that camera
[Music]
kick his eggs
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
mike
oh
[Music]
really quickly
we can use some help
it's not fair this battle after all okay
let me oh
i could use the bat but
wait how do i
switch back ah there we go
oh chair let's go
ah there we go i have to adjust the
camera all right is there more coming
i'm just moving out some furniture now
for my new place
all right
oh we gotta move now okay
let me fruit
oh there's some stuff here
captain's dead
honey where's everybody
[Music]
you'll pay for that
basket
[Music]
okay but this is really nice we can use
as many items as we want apparently in
the middle of the fight
that was kind of tough sometimes in
in like a dragon that we
um could only use like one per turn and
then yeah
it was pretty difficult sometimes
[Music]
what is that
what's that what am i finding him
[\h__\h] yeah
oh
i was just about to change my
stance but okay because you're still
alive
no oh
hey are you gonna be endlessly spawning
and i have to get out of this building
or
is this the right way
making cash
uh
use heat uh yeah yeah okay
[Music]
what is this problem
i can't grab them
fresh
[Music]
i'm trying to i'm trying to
dodge yo
we're gonna have another uh
souls back sitting situation here
[Music]
she still got me even though i dodged
oh okay now i got a chair
[Music]
i need a [\h__\h] warning yo
oh my god
wow
[Music]
really dangerous man
stamina oh nice kitchen you got here
time to make a mess or maybe make some
curry um
[\h__\h] why are you all carrying so much
money with you guys you should be uh
having it on your credit card you
okay
looking good
dance
[Music]
can we chill for a moment
yuck he's so bad
oh that doesn't even do that much
[Music]
if okay some items lying around here
oh wait where are we going
[Music]
oh here okay
wait sometimes it's just walking with
systems kind of wait no wait huh
[Music]
oh no bro we're going here
oh
i'm not even giving him time to be angry
just take a chill pill man don't be so
mad all of you
[Music]
there's a door here okay
it's locked from the other side
you want to jump or what
from a window
how
what do you mean jump in
what
oh my god i don't believe it would break
like that
nanda what how are your pants already
closed huh
makes no sense
hey i'm dodging [\h__\h]
i know what you guys mean with those
actions
i'm pressing triangle nothing's
happening
[Music]
obs saved my life
you're that dad you keep on coming back
oh here's a [\h__\h] uh knife
nice village
dark souls has told me much
[Music]
oh my god
oh man
[Music]
whatever
oh my god
yo yo yo guys
there's no reason to take out a knife
like that no no no no no buddy no no no
unless there's a wedding cake here
there's no need for that
almost got him
[\h__\h] strong
oh good that we bought so much food i
would be so [\h__\h] if i didn't
i'm bleeding
oh my god
[Music]
oh yeah throw him out
holy [\h__\h]
[Applause]
stop rolling you stop shut up
oh my god
[Music]
good idea
need some help
ability acquired can we get health in
the rush mode too yeah okay
so they're both the same skills but
they're just for different
thingies okay it's kind of weird
um
[Music]
on the ground and then square recovered
and perform an attack okay i'll try that
i'll try to remember that
and we'll try my best
two million increases the power of your
regular attacks and heat actions
um maybe in the rush first
oh we can do both actually
health upgrades work for both oh
so if i got both of the first ones
it means
they'd
um
count double i applies to all of kitty's
bathtubs okay
yeah
[Music]
okay let's get this one too then
all right
okay where are we going next here
okay
seems like we've kind of reached the top
here
oh what happens if i die here
thank you just some guy with mustache
thank you
doji ma you're not gonna fight me too
are you
not
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] what if i died
[Music]
um
can i take my clothes off
match
fine fine fine
i'm not even healed man
huh
[Music]
is already in the middle of attacking me
huh
[Music]
it is
disappears immediately though what the
[\h__\h]
oh okay okay we gave him an opening i
gave him an opening i'm sorry
oh
nice
i just kind of smashed my controller
fire
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh oh oh oh oh oh
[\h__\h] my fingers my fingers hurt
wait
[\h__\h] it
uh
uh only when he's down
it's like a tekken match it feels like
it honestly
i remember playing tekken in the arcade
like a million years ago
[Music]
ah my fingers are getting too weak
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
can i get a left-handed controller
my right hand isn't that strong
[Music]
i respect him for that
he got me there he got me there
[Music]
yeah my right hand my thumb my thumb and
the in between the thumb and the long
the long finger
[Music]
is
[\h__\h] yeah
sick of you
[Music]
one more [\h__\h] head
what's a morning what's my reference you
got it
oh my god
my fingers you'll be your bigger
my fingers are ready to be cut off
take them take them they're useless
now
i beat it without
without heat energy i don't know i saw
them popping up sometimes but it's
quickly gone
hello sir are you dojima
nice glasses
it was a good practice um
for
uh fighting and dodging
for a moment it was 101 before that i
had
uh
when
let me live the family place
[Music]
old man
um
oh
he's thief he's mad
is that for him to document
who doesn't they even get a little stool
for it
or is it for his fingers
and what's that for
why is there a stick
again
wait what no
[Music]
no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
don't go that far please
[Applause]
well someone definitely lost his eubie
well it wasn't us
[Music]
my head hurts i have a headache oh man
be
oh
foreign
hmm
so we're not getting any punishment for
leaving and breaking our oath
but
well
um
apparently
they're really serious about not hurting
civilians
[Music]
even if just a moment ago he would have
deserved it
in their rule book tatemaska
mysterious man with funny shoes
this is
our friend
no
but he's not crazy yet and he wears only
one glove
um
like a dragon or am i going crazy he
looks
a little bit familiar
but it wasn't the one i originally
thought he was
completion bonus of one million earned
chapter one completed
[Music]
touchy banana
different guy oh okay but someone looked
a little bit similar to him i feel like
um
yeah
how many chapters are there
i i looked up on google how long the
game is apparently it's a bit shorter
than like a dragon but still pretty long
oh no
don't worry i'll connect it
and i'll connect it it's a bit uh short
but
that is
not
18 16 16 uh-huh
[Music]
wow
oh no no no
what where four times
same day yes
i'm so glad i didn't die it was pretty
tough actually
[Music]
third longest yakuza game
for the exploding map after the
cinematic is about to come oh okay
climax battle item opened
second chapter the real estate broker in
the shadows
was your real estate broken
surprise you didn't die zero deaths yay
first try good hustle thank you
but
my fingers i need some muscles
[Music]
hot
give you
[Laughter]
thanks for letting me take a shower i
guess wow you must have have a ton of
gel in your hair dude your hair is so
shiny
yoga
and he talks so sick
he reminds me of cubie
he's like
yakuza
warden
i have no clothes now
i'm only at the bathroom
[Music]
i want that corn soup please
wait why are you gonna sit there why he
looks like a robot partially wait stop
eating my food i want to eat
yeah yeah that's a fake hand
like a buster
an arrested development mediterranean
[Music]
his orphanage
well it's really creepy right now man
creepy creepy what the
um
we all wanted
but like literally like you said let's
hold hands
[Music]
blackmailing me with my clothes
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know i'm not dead yet it's probably
still the cause of my family office okay
okay
i two by nine now oh i got my clothes
back
all right
hello lady
hello
wouldn't you like to go out for a drink
with me you're fine
no i want the
i want i want to get to know ya please
no
okay uh
[Music]
where are we right now
this place looks super familiar
we need to buy more stuff is there a
convenience store
then let's fight okay
i need i need some more training anyway
i mean you guys gotta give me that i'm
good at dodging
oh
no
i want convenience store
oh can i take away something youtube you
don't how's my health doing
i don't know okay maybe don't need
that
that's a there could be a servant before
i think
i need to load up on some food and
medicine again
i don't step oh yeah speaking of battle
step you might have heard but uh good
huh
she talked about it on stream i think
but she messaged me yesterday
out of nowhere
she asked me about an idol she's like is
this this girl an idol and i'm like yeah
she's a
voice actress
actually
um
but also considering an idol
and then i was like why why why are you
asking and she was like yeah cause she
she's she she performed on the same
stage so we're gonna be on and i'm like
yes
yeah that's what you mean
that's a huge stage
it's funny how good i realized it now
it seems like yesterday could i had just
a day and a moment of realization
where she noticed finally
that it is quite a big deal to be on
uh
in makuhari performing in malcolm is a
[\h__\h] huge place man
it was like out of nowhere and then she
was asking me because she heard that me
and emma were doing a dance collab she
asked me to um
do like uh
like she wanted me to do a boot camp for
the myth members to teach everyone
dancing
and i'm like okay
yeah sure
i mean
um
i'm good with like choreography and [\h__\h]
but i mean i never really never really
had experience with teaching people
where why are we going here
but
um
yeah i guess i can try the thing is
though that with the wealthy models you
really don't see dance moves at all
it doesn't work well
but
uh
the person who made the models model
slow poly models for me
and ame
also originally already had one for
gouda and was also already
already has done one for
for
ina
in the same style so we can use those i
just think we're missing one for kelly
um those models are actually pretty
good for
um you know doing a dance stream like
that i thought so now i just don't know
what to do
about cali's model if we get permission
to use
um inna's model yeah i gotta think about
that
the cali was in the video yeah but like
with a different model not with the same
style i feel like it would be so weird
if she had like a
completely different model you know i
want i wanted to fit to match
um
i think the one from cali was like also
too close to
uh
her
like like like a like a realistic
version of her model you know what i
mean but just in i think it was like
kind of pixelated
um
other models right now you gotta you
gotta like um i learned this from amy
but you gotta rig it so that it works in
vr and so on
uh and that has been done for
mine and mine and amish models already i
don't know about the others probably
would have to do that
but yeah now i'm like uh kind of like
gonna wants me to do it so i'm like oh
all up for it like actually
i kind of thought about that in the past
already um now that good asks me about
it i'm i'm
more open to do it because i
now that i know that she's
interested
if she's if she wants to do it then i'll
do my best yeah
um
yeah just got to organize models i don't
know if it can if if we can be that
quickly that we can do it before
uh
the
third fest
i don't know if i can make all that in
time
but i'll try and then the question is
also what dance am i gonna teach them
hmm because i feel like i looked at some
of the whole live choreography but um
um a lot of them look too simple to me
but it depends though and
and uh i know a lot of like dances from
like vocaloid songs and idol songs and
so on those i already know by heart so
those would be easier to teach
yeah third face is this month yo
this month
but i would love to teach them a dance
yeah i can i can show off one of my
skills that way and one of my interests
in hobbies so i i'm i really
am happy to do it
and i was so happy to hear good uh for
on her own asking me to do something
like that asking me to teach them to
dance i i felt pretty happy about that
so now i'm motivated
no no more than i don't step now it must
be more
more intricate
not too
not too difficult but like more
difficult than just [\h__\h] idle steps
no no no
no i have big visions
anyway continue
foreign
[Music]
is
oh man the two brothers are kind of
separated now
oh
um
[Music]
on purpose because that's how i
always automatically read it i know you
would pronounce it hahahaha but to me in
my head it's just ja ja jaja so it's
really funny to me imagining that you
guys love like chat
[Music]
oh
i love how these groups of enemies
always have some
name to them
to describe them
that's nice
like a dragon
though
i mean we just started but like a dragon
had funny on them so funnier grips and
funnier names
but i'm i'm hopeful that they're still
gonna impress me here
wait did we even buy [\h__\h] in the korean
store
ah yeah we did we did
hey yo
yes
hello
menacing men
is there a problem
yeah giant man you seem to think you can
just walk by me without a word he is dry
and indeed do i know you this isn't your
turf why should i have to tell you
anything
i'm not here to chat if you don't want
to get hurt you leave all the cash
you've got to get lost
no
oh is this a shakedown you should pick
your targets better i don't have a
single yen for jumps like you
yeah we do have yen but not for him
and i guess we'll do this the hard way
hope you're insured oh
okay
[Music]
i hope
it [\h__\h] hits hard
i didn't die though
but they entered the battle
oh no
it's not going to take my money is it
i got me off the hook okay
[Music]
well i thought i had a chance
if i have trouble with somebody like you
i need to change my training regimen
time to bump up the intensity which is
going to be expensive
if i i want to save up that kind of
money i've got some shaking down
okay okay
what
hey okay man
yeah
you just had the misfortune of meeting
hiroya egashira mr shakedown they call
him mr shaytan
he'll go after anybody that crosses his
path and then he takes everything they
got you seem like you can hold your own
in a fight but that guy's on a whole
different level if he sets his sights on
you you'll run for it he's definitely
more than your average tough guy could
handle
still i wish somebody would come along
and beat all that stolen money out of
him though was if you kill him actually
i bet he is going to drop a [\h__\h] out of
money huh
damn right you did took my whole day
holiday bonus i knew i should have made
you should have made a beeline to the
bankruptcy you be careful too next time
you're sitting on the stack of cash
uh-huh telling me the game is telling me
to put my money in a bank
or use it up in other ways
okay
oh wait [\h__\h] i mean you could reclaim
all the money stolen from you the man is
carrying rarities at different time if
you can take him down when he's
especially flush with cash you can make
back more money than what you've lost
yeah i feel challenged
now
right now that's not that much
uh-huh okay
let's go
oh [\h__\h] buddy please
hey pocket tissue please i would say
ushibody
not quite the same
sorry
sorry mustang
he's super hard early oh is he easier to
take down later on
wait until later now to hold on
can cars hit me in this game as well
hotel the circle is this where i live
ah
um
those are some special hotels here
every time i tell people in in europe or
like in austria that in japan there's
love hotels they're always like what
what
you can drive to cuba's apartment from
here okay
uh i guess yeah
feels like i haven't been home in
forever way too much has happened the
last couple days
oh you're living in a pretty quiet
looking place um
not a hotel
oh up the stairs
[Music]
no sub stories until after the scene uh
huh
foreign
i'll leave the discussion up to you guys
yo so much instant ramen all used
clean it up man
um
nani
[Music]
um
guys
[Music]
foreign
i i just associate
coco senpai with that name so whenever i
hear it i have to think of her
for some people maybe it's the other way
around but because i played yakuza after
getting to know her for me it's that way
maybe nishiki's right and i should
accept tachi bananas offer but i need to
i need more to go on before i can trust
him yeah definitely he's really weird i
should hit the town to see what i can
find about out out about him grab her
info and touch upon his real estate
okay i like how he walks down the stairs
it's so realistic
didn't they say something like this
about
stare our character is walking stairs
before either in the tails off game or
in the other yakuza game
but look at it like he's really careful
you're walking on one by one
it didn't was it wasn't like a dragon i
really like how they make the characters
walk down and upstairs
i really like it
what's it entails up i'm confused now
too
oh
okay when he goes up he skips some
because he thinks he's cool yeah he
thinks that saves more time but when he
goes down he's too scared to do that
i did
go to camelot
yes
let's go what a beautiful day man what a
beautiful day
stairs are dangerous yes i agree
yeah no kaido little
looks a lot more friendly
actually a lot of business people there
um
where are we going actually we have no
no goal on the map but i guess we're
just going to run around a little bit
and maybe fight
well what do you want
whoa no oh it's so effortlessly that
looks really cool
turn around
double kill
man in bliss
oh man i destroyed the whole world
wait it wasn't gold it was yellow after
all
cheese carrot
i think was from nana mizuki called this
critique
and 2000
is this a
this girl
let's go
i like real live discos but this looks
fun yeah yeah
oh
please keep in mind that if you leave
our club you will need to paint your
okay
like i have to push some buttons too
let me in let me in
dance
dance i want to dance
hey there one of the [\h__\h] well some
sweet looks on the dance floor
but this girl
oh basic rules to dance at the disco
press buttons in the ribbon
oh no not again the ribbon came here i'm
really bad at those
use the directional buttons to move your
character's avatar
to the square of the next input icon oh
and then press the corresponding button
why it sounds difficult this frame
overlaps the square border
as you move your avatar you'll see the
number of steps it takes
the more steps you take the more points
you will get for the next curved input
so try to make as many steps as you can
on your way to the next
input icon
what
uh-huh
is matt so just um
in the upper middle of the screen is the
fever gosh
let's
press l1
when it is full to trigger dancing fever
a new screen of a series of button input
icons will appear press them with the
correct timing to boost your score
to charge the fever gosh keep pressing
the correct icons with the right timing
and unbroken streak
yeah it's going to be tough
the right events are raining again so
build up your score to fill the
gauntlets you'll go through levels
there's also versus more in which you
compete with another dancer and one with
the highest score wins
okay
um learning by dealing
learning by doing at least we only pay
once and we can probably dance a million
times for that
which song do you want me to put on for
you oh
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
um
oh
cool
oh i love them all
i want to take you home is what they say
at kfp at the cashier
[Music]
oh my god
i love this one
okay i want to do all of them
i want to do all of
them okay i'll [\h__\h] up really badly
probably
okay
buttons square triangle
circle x
wait well you're saying
about it i'm trying to describe what the
next input
and then press the cursor
okay it shouldn't be
it's probably
not that complicated
[Music]
[Applause]
how do i do this i don't know one
uh
[Music]
hey
oh my god okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
gotta learn by doing keyboard this is
hell really
uh
i'm gonna do this one next
queen of fashion
the outline has
[Applause]
three
two
one let's go
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] wrong buddy
[Applause]
[Music]
come on come on chat one star how has
one star failed
come on
gotta dance gonna keep on dancing
those are really good songs though i
love them
i understand now that it's gonna you're
gonna
click it when it's in the frame now
thank you for that hint
doesn't work with the stick though
that's it with the joystick
warming up
fever time let's go miracle johnson
[\h__\h]
[Music]
so much to do
every day
[Music]
again what was that what does that go
again i wasn't fever i wasn't fever town
i didn't say that i was too focused
but i got better than before again
i didn't say
it what happens again when you press l1
this will get easier
don't dance alone no i want to dance
with you you're better than me
you would have won really [\h__\h] okay next
time next time's the charm
he's sucking love of dance level robin
my head hurts honestly i think i should
take
a i have a
uh painkiller i think right here
yeah that's actually i'm gonna take a
pink color
cause i wanna play longer
my head and my face hurts
what do you want from me
i want that
okay no i usually don't take
like any medicine like that just because
i'm in pain usually i just choose to
take it easy then but i want to play
longer
[Music]
uh
i always say this dance floor it's my
playground and i've been watching the
dance friend
that's when it hit me you got a town for
dancing that's off the scale
are you sure i mean i guess i'm a fast
layer in there
now i'm good i wanna play longer
a little bit longer
i challenge you to battle
shut up i need to practice alone a bit
no no no no no no are you telling me you
don't know what a dance spell is and
that's well no i've never heard of it
oh that's ridiculous the tragedy dancing
is something people do together dance by
yourself on the dance floor and camera
show what's the point
um spotlight [\h__\h]
i mean mahadasha is the holy land of
dance how could you not know about dance
battles unbelievable it's impossible to
be that out of touch
it's so detached it's like backwards
evolution you like a nan excuse me [\h__\h]
you
i've been just tweet once to fight after
all yep okay okay i'll explain
two dances dancing the same song to see
who's better both plans to show their
stuff and the audience reaction
determines the winner
all right i'll get the picture yeah yeah
yeah
you catch it quick for caveman um
let's not waste any time and let's hit
the floor can't go with it
right now i'm not
not ready
[Music]
yeah no
i decide when i dance not you
look at that [\h__\h] you felt like that
because
it's like like cleaning cleaning the
floor but like it's not on the floor
wait as long as you need it okay bye-bye
let's go i need more i need more presses
dance solo
we did this we did that
okay go i want to take some kfb home
l once i'm fevering
[Music]
i'm gonna enter super focus mode again
guys will you keep on vibing
[Music]
oh what just happened
foreign
[Music]
i don't know how that works yet
[Laughter]
okay if you [\h__\h] up the first one it
[\h__\h] up all of it but
finally yo i had some good uh combos
there for a while in the beginning yeah
yeah yeah
okay okay one more
i'm gonna be dancing all night
dancing
that was a great uh golden bomber song
um that is a thing called dancing for
the night or something like that
yeah we're waiting for that one
let's go
let's [\h__\h] dance
[Music]
hey
i
[Music]
i love that song oh my god
can we do it again can we do it again
can we do it again again can we do it
again
loves me
[Music]
me
yes
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
now
[Music]
me
da
[Music]
even though my combos are bad
i love that song holy [\h__\h] what a bob
what a [\h__\h] bob
no mama
we can do medium maybe
another
[Music]
moves too like i'm not watching at all
uh
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
hey
my fingers
[Music]
yeah my hands are getting really stiff
my hands are getting really
stiff and painful oh
[Music]
[Applause]
is this song amazing
my head still hurts when is the
painkiller color work
is it gonna work on my fingers too
i do have to cut my ububies
i completed it though
compare that to my to my very first try
holy moly
[Music]
you know in my free time i'm gonna max
all of these
you're gonna come back max then you're
gonna be like yo
[Music]
so that would be so proud
sometimes i get stuck
weirdly out of the way
[Music]
that was way too early
oh
[Music]
okay
okay come on come on
crumbling under the pressure
absolutely
[Applause]
i push the right button but like too
early man because i get too too excited
i feel like i gotta i can't miss it so i
gotta be early
but better than the previous try
a
apple pie joe
sorry guys you gotta deal with this for
a while
you guys i'm in my bubble now i'm in a
different world though
no more yakuza no more shooting no more
ubub's the only youbies are gonna you're
gonna see are pointing at the disco ball
this place is peace this place is level
this place is heaven
i feel safe here
[Music]
i wanted to do something cool there
[Applause]
[Music]
hmm
okay
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm not gonna give up never gonna give
this up never gonna stop dancing i wanna
get those freestyles i'm the disco queen
oh [\h__\h]
that was by accident
uh
couldn't
[Music]
very twirkable
10 out of 10.
oh god
at school
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
what
oh
bring it
down twice
[Music]
day
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
me
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
crumble
um
[Music]
[Applause]
fun my fingers my hands
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's the disco queen
if only you landed your favors if only
okay this this time i'm gonna land them
best score of five thousand five hundred
let's go for six thousand
which i can't shake hands she can't
stretch straight stretch do those
stretches yeah dance must stretch
okay
[Music]
sorry
um
[Music]
is
closed
[Music]
captioning not available
my time is over my disco time's over
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
literally not play anything else than
this
okay
oh man oh
shut up
[\h__\h]
no booing the disco quit i'm gonna throw
you out the club but nice number
oh man
oh you would watch really
become the dancing queen maybe that will
be like a special episode really where
we're not gonna do any story we're just
gonna do this
oh
can't you stop now
couldn't stop my hands hurt
my hands hurt i wonder if the
the combos um
of the fever
are
depending on i guess the
difficulty always the same
if i can remember those two or if
they're random
wait we should dance by on him though
let's do that
groupie sun um
only that song
i have uh not tried much with that song
yet but okay let's do it easy first
it's on let's party
destroy him
we start easy we make him think we're a
beginner
[Music]
yeah
okay
oh god i'm gonna be seeing how he's
doing it
i want to see it
oh he's good
[Music]
am i killing him or what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
shut up kiana just don't talk
don't talk
[Music]
huh
this is
[Music]
that's it
i won though i wonder
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
i won against him though that's all that
matters i need to stop talking though
yeah yeah
you wanted to dance with it you wanted
to yeah yeah i wiped the floor with you
you wanted to have a bath let's keep on
battling hahahaha
and all the dancing shake your brain
lose no i'm so happy i can't keep myself
i'm laughing i haven't danced like this
for too long
yeah it's good to hear
so thanks to you my brother
brother what's wrong with that
after all that what else can we be we
dance while we dance talk we dance
together
but look at the back in the background
there's a guy with a golden shiny suit
he's like a shiny pokemon a shiny yakuza
is that how he wigs
exactly otherwise i knew my eyes weren't
deceiving me you've got legit talent my
brother oh thank you
maybe you can even take him
is there a dance monster
oops me and my big mouth just forget you
heard the word brother nothing to do
with you yeah
okay
i don't think i ever caught your name
kill you
here to the dance machine
i have a feeling you're going to be a
big name in the world of dance
that's yeah yeah that's right and that's
why i'm the only one who can teach the
myth girls some dancing moves
he's good
maybe not quite at my level yet
oh
i know i said i would stop but i can't
stop yet i want to beat him more often
where is he is he done for today did he
really leave
did i destroy him that badly
let's look at the people's dance moves
and judge them
he's doing fine
i like her moves
they're all doing the same the girls are
all doing the same moves
um
he needs to work on it
he needs some work yeah
he's doing the booby shake even though
he has no boobies i don't know about
that he's just booing people which is
the worst kind of person to be in a
disco what the [\h__\h]
what are you even doing here booing
people focus on yourself
well i should be the one talking okay
i'm out here
okay that was fun dude thanks for an
amazing night man good music you're
playing in here
amazing music
fun fun fun fun fun fun fun excellent
rihanna i gotta pay 2000 again man
i kind of wanted
if you support it if you guys if i have
your support
you guys seem to be supportive
it's a dancing stream now
where is he where is he
where is he
he's not here
i thought it would be here
all right
local
by the bar
use the
oh who is it
lady
it's been a while
hmm
who are you
i'm michael is your daughter my last
name means rock
dance and that's that implies implies
i'm all about the dance floor
it's only natural that you don't know me
i watched your battle against hisaki
hisaki the guy who challenged me to
dance with my hair
yes him
i've kept my eye on you ever since kitty
okay i thought you might have it in you
to become a dancer who could keep up
with me the dancing queen
i got the picture and now you're
determined i'm working up so to speak
i couldn't put it better you're not just
quick on your feet i see you've got the
real style too i bet you're a lady
killer
huh
i wouldn't go that far i don't kill
ladies mostly men
when i see a man who is better than
dancer than me i can't help falling for
him
i think you might have what it takes to
keep up with me now maybe you can even
drive me right over the top into ecstasy
listen kitty i couldn't how about we
have a dance battle that will set
ourselves on fire
oh i thought she was hitting on me but
all she wants is a dance battle too
accept a challenge
i'll show you some moves you'll never
forget
sounds like we'll both get off on this
phrasing girl but before we begin you
want to know i'm good he's like he can't
even keep up with my shadow so you'd
better bring what you've got
we'll never die the other way
that's the spirit
let's start easy okay
cause my hands are really exhausted okay
let's let our dance begin
[Music]
[Applause]
don't look at the girl guys look at me
[Music]
oh hey stop posing like that not fair
um
[Music]
yes
she's better than me right now
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
uh
yo i just can't anymore
i scared more
my hands are it's not an excuse
ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
cheating she's cheating
[Music]
i know you're capable of so much more
if you want to try to entertain me again
i'll be waiting right here
[Music]
where
i don't see you
the bar
uh
yeah i give it one more track one last
try one last try
probably won't win uh but
i wanna try one more time
shake my hands
gotta win an easy fest
[Laughter]
blackjack too yeah
okay
focus
i'm gonna show you my passion oh no
power
[Music]
i'm sexy
of course i know it
[Music]
[Applause]
hold yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
she has the game
[Music]
hmm
[Applause]
oh we have like the same amount of steps
and my combo was higher but she didn't
lose the
the fever so in theory i'm better
in fairy i'm better
yes
yes just a ping okay i'm just too fast
when it comes to fever
too fast for her she can't even keep up
not even the game can keep up
yeah i just need to get that fever down
okay okay
it was fun oh my god this addict i need
to get out of here i need to get out i
don't even wanna i'm like so immersed
right now i feel like this is a dancing
game
oh man
i'll be back i'll be back
that's the truth
anyway where are we going we need to
investigate on
the dude the touchy banana dude
you want to fight
i just practice dancing so fight you
while i'm dancing
[Music]
i feel so fast
what you still alive oh i thought it was
done
[Music]
where could there be a hint
who could there's nothing marked on the
map i don't know
i don't know where to go
[Music]
maybe they want me to spend a certain
amount of time
what
you called me
what am i fighting
[Music]
you think you're fancy with your suit
bananas
noises in japanese
you gotta translate that accurately yo
where are the translators i have the
word to a word with you
uh please thank you for the tissue
thank you
i don't know what i would even do with
those dishes
[Music]
i don't know where i'm um
i should save
[Music]
racing draft is the racing track
is it like the the mario kart game and
like a dragon
that was fun too
man the [\h__\h] minigames are so good
love it
absolutely love it smile burger
[Music]
where should we go
i'm probably like so far off now
huh
[Music]
i didn't say north they didn't say north
didn't it did they
look i'll try to go north
hello
[Music]
what
yeah
good moves
i'll just give you a little bit of
certain situations oh really
very helpful for certain situations
that's favorite city is that another
place dancers is the same place where i
was in here another dancing place
but this one didn't look like you could
enter it
i actually i have never been to oh a
disco before
never
and i don't really wanna
ah that's that's why that is here okay
i just remember like when i was in
school
um
and we were like on the trip to
we were on a school trip to croatia
like one evening
one evening they kind of like organized
like a
dance evening
and it was just the biggest
cringe fast and uncomfortable thing ever
hmm
i don't know i just
i just uh the image i have of this goes
is just
i i already know that i won't like it i
love that doctor look at it the way he
follows his owner come on
oh
cute cute little shebano
yeah i don't like any of those
activities so
wait that's where i go home
i wasn't supposed to go home
what did you say northwest
oh maybe here
cute taco i want to get a dog one day
when i if i ever have a
if i ever have like a
an apartment on the first floor with a
garden or
a house with a garden
maybe
like i don't want to get a dog now
because i know i wouldn't really have
much time to
um
should take it out all the time
[Music]
like
wow
dude styling
i saw something i can't i don't know i
never get to use it
what
i never get to use this thing is i'll
figure it out maybe i'll look at a guide
or something
oh no it's a children's park
oh
there's a terrible toilet to have at the
children's park
where is that empty lot what the hell
try bronzed out for more heat actions oh
we found the people that we're supposed
to find i guess
uh-huh
wait is this really or is this a side
quest i guess it's a side quest
uh yikes
hey you're right
because i would bump into some
swaggering punk
why
you are an
old man
this isn't going to end well
are you alright and yeah what's the big
idea yo
what a sassy buckle
i'm sorry i let you wear your step [\h__\h]
for brains you not hurt or anything are
you [\h__\h]
all right if that's how you want to play
this out
what
eh
i'm so sorry no i mean i'm in the rest
so please get lost upon gas so and so
okay so he's acting
like a tough guy but he's definitely not
he seems very confused yeah
damn yankee
okay but where is the thing that i need
for the main quest
hmm
what about all these people
oh
sass
what's going on
also sadquest yankee yankee
i'm so freaking stoked man the red
string show by the you can meet your
supers
too red those guys are rockin roll gods
oh this is just the continuation of the
sidequest i guess hey jer
look at my paycheck
uh
and keep your pants on but i heard the
yokumiji silveries are gonna be holding
a q a panel too
no [\h__\h] way they're famous for never
saying a word and letting their music do
the talking i wonder what the hell
they'll talk about
sounds like some bands doing an event
here must be popular with local plunks
alert
is that
uh well while we're here i guess
oh my gosh oh my gosh look at those
people
oh my god what are we gonna do oh he's
the the person they're waiting for
but he doesn't he's he's just putting up
an act he's not really what they think
he is
yikes
gee when's balan you repeat my uh what
you're doing chuffing around you behind
me ugly knob
uh yeah uh sorry i thought i should
apologize for bumping into you earlier
what who oh you're that man
no i should i should be apologizing for
my killers i mean whatever pissed off
sure
um
wait a second could you possibly be
unaware of who i am
not you asking if we met before and we
bumped into each other if we did i don't
recognize you
oh wait a second then so you really
don't know who i am willikers what a
relief
ah
i'm sorry i was rude not to introduce
myself my name is kyo but my stage name
is chris kill i'm the vocalist of a band
let me guess the yokomichi silvers
same band those punks are excited to see
aren't you guys some kind of legendary
yankee band yes that's us we're doing a
street show here later
oh sorry to bug you before you show good
luck he just leaves
where the hell do you think you're going
old man please wait don't go
maybe maybe you can save me
xavier
we mean save you
nanny nanny
are you even hardcore in the slightest
nope as a joke we tried dressing old
punk at the show tourist shock we got
pretty popular with the yankee crowd but
now we have to keep up this charade full
time over time we gain the fanbase of
wannabe punks and the yokomiji silvers
became heroes the rebellious youth of
japan
that whole style is called yonki no
there's more to running abandoned i
thought
so what did you mean by me saving you
i
actually i wanted to teach me how to be
hardcore hooligan kenya is not that good
get you to be a yankee
you see it for the daisy when we also
have to do a live panel meet and greet
for the fans but every member of the
yokumiji service myself included our law
abiding core boys we've never even
shoplifted that same
if we were to talk in front of a real
yankee then realize that we're ponies
fake punks i know that you mention it
the way you talk doesn't match how you
dress at all all right so if we spoke to
our fans we'd lose all our credibility
and popularity in an instant or worse
what if they want revenge on us for
fooling them
they're not hooligans they're fooling
against
okay but do you have to do this panel
thing why don't you just skip it
i don't want to do it either
but our agency says we need to hone our
speaking skills if we want to stay
popular and making us do this we've been
avoiding every situation where we might
have to talk instead of just performing
but now
i got it so you want me to teach you how
to behave like a yankee so you can talk
like one but why am i
why well that would be because you're my
ideal of what a hooligan should be
that confident demeanor your razor sharp
glare
that barbed wire attitude that says
touch me and get cut
and yet you also exceed a sense of
kindness a guy who extends a helping
hand to the weak the whole lincoln with
a heart of gold that's my ideal yankee
well yeah i am a yakuza kind of
you can teach us so we won't blow our
cover more than that i think you can
give us yankee wisdom that will propel
the yokomichi silvers to new heights of
hooliganism
please if you lose this chance that
you're going to be someone may have to
break up please rather carry myself look
at your yankee okay
water
need water i need to drink water
a second okay
i'm gonna get the others okay
oh
sorry to keep you waiting can you sign
[Music]
hey there i'm dynasty my sister is
sleazy but i have no experience with the
ladies never even seen a boob
it is so racist bad boy uncle
i'm awkward probably is caring for
elders
and this is kenya who's going to be in
part the ways of true yankee style holy
ghost oh look at these mamas
please teach us to kill your son
you guys are so polite and proper i'm
starting to wonder if there's anything i
can do for you
oh no please don't say that
well pretty good guys at heart so please
help us
okay it's being pretty good guys is the
problem but i did agree to this
to do this so somehow we have to turn
you and guys into hard-edged punks
yay you know screw please
how can i show you guys to be tougher
now
well maybe you could come up with an
opening remark for a little old me
you're being remark
yes i want to kick off our panel with
authority being open against we
shouldn't come across weak or his this
is hesitant please keep your son i need
a zinger of an opening line to set the
tone
start your engines
i guess
start your engines oh like a racing term
yeah the yucky movement inspired by
western greasers they love their wheels
so true that does go with a yucky
lifestyle so i should follow something
like you get my pistons pumping don't
you think was that the wrong answer
maybe it should have been english
[Music]
that's good and it wouldn't hurt to
throw in something like ram it into
overdrive either
right right i didn't know about that one
i'm so glad we got your advice here son
oh oh oh here's some give yourself a
question
what is it
well the agency told me to tell the fans
about how i spent my days off when i'm
not rehearsing or performing
new days of um makes sense that fans
would want to know their hair is life
from day to day tell us how would you
spend a day off
well i make a habit of getting up bright
and early so i can make some pancakes
after breakfast i take my darling puppy
chibichang
to the park for our mid-morning stroll
yeah and then we have lunch at a chic
cafe to rest our feet and of course my
dog also gets only the finest food on
our way home we do a little window
shopping and i buy some clothes for my
dogo after that i bring down the dramas
i've got on my vcr until it's bedtime um
i really like those those romantic uh
shows here
you just describe the typical girl's day
sorry that really made you sound like a
fashionable young woman i was so
surprised it got intense
i'm
so so scared
oh no kidding you shouldn't shout like
that
you made sleazy tone as you cry that's a
bit much don't you think
oh dear
we should say sorry
oh yeah my bad thought i see it
it's all right wish i started i wasn't
expecting it so
so how would i spend a day off
oh yeah right um
one thing's clear you can't tell the
fans how you really spend your free time
no i guess not but then what should i
say what what should i be doing instead
fighting all day
on the days off you should spend your
time fighting from dawn to dusk
fighting i don't really get it but who
do hooligans fight do you have spawning
enemies or something
it's not about having enemies yankee are
always ready and willing to fight
if two punks lock eyes the fight is on
that's how it is on the mean streets of
commodore troll yep yep yep yep it has
been like that and just so you know face
fighting is considered the most hardcore
and cool
that's why we do it
what a brutal community i can't take my
dog out for walking that warts on yeah
yeah hold on the dog that punks
the dogs that punks keep tend to be
fiercely loyal and firsty for blood
they're often jurassic partners in the
street fight
is that right i can't picture my
delicate chippy child engaging in a
curfel
[Music]
boy i'm glad we could hit you up for
advice can you sound you're the perfect
hooligan role model
ah you're bad boy uncle right what's the
matter well
what was
[Music]
you told him to wing it he's afraid to
talk about whatever even though he's
practically mute makoyaku even has a bad
story locked up in juvenile
reformatories from birth bad boy uncle
crushed packs of punks before he even
finished preschool
well he's pretty much
uh
what he wants to be then
your agent is trying to fit a square peg
oh oh wait that story was fake okay now
hold on peg in a round hole
akku's a man of few words of a crazy
backstory what should he talk about to
make him sound hardcore you should say
that his tongue got cut out in a fight
then he doesn't have to talk at all and
it would sound cool
uh
yeah maybe staying silent is actually
intimidating
hmm
don't you think it would be better to
stay quiet
stay silent during the panel when the
discussion without any talking be a
disaster
oh yeah
no akku was told he's free to talk about
whatever he wants that means he's also
free to not talk at all
that's true but
it would be worse if he were to say the
wrong things and wreck his image for
maku's backstory i think he would seem
more hardcore if he kept his mouth shut
oh
when you put it that way that makes
total sense okay we'll do that that boy
i could stay speechless during his part
yeah yeah yeah
10 out of 10 answers frank yeah
you also made the same choice um
sure haku are you good with that
okay
all right now we'll go over how you'll
run this whole panel discussion
yes please
sorry
i mean you can come whenever you're
ready
i'll be watching from the audience
yes please watch us we're going to hit
this hardcore younger thing out of the
park
we're going to kick ass and stuff
hey here they are put your hands
together and yoga when you silver
oh
they look funny
[Applause]
crazy
[Music]
wow they're so popular when they're not
talking they do look like real greasers
stopping wet high rock and roll off to
school tell us your food
super based
kind of got it mixed up but it works it
works
oh we're not going to see the
performance what lame
lame leg that concludes today's
performance of yoga silvers
just listening to their songs i can see
why yankee kids across japan look up to
crazy kills band
now we would like to move on to special
meet and greet panel discussion with the
bad members
stop punching the air dude
i can't [\h__\h] wait to hear bad boy
aqua's voice
here's the way it gets real they better
pull this off ah
yo gray sounds
where did you go mr silver start your
engines
yeah
crazy
cool you just bros but i got it handed
to crazy cute son he knows how to wrap
his up and kick it
thanks for coming on rocking outdoor
tunes we love you all your romantic
rebels you punks get my pistons plumping
right here under the blood
hoods with
i love you like my turn for drive oh my
i love you like my turbo drive
[Applause]
good the fans are eating it up going
with rice and terms paid off
awesome thank you crazy kill son next we
would like to hear from sleazy taraji
son and bad boy akusan as well first
steps please don't ask son
here's the question we got from the fans
how do you originally spend your days
off
well
uh
if i got a day off i spent it fighting
mostly
he's a beast fighting so i exercised him
two wickets for words oh [\h__\h] i would
pay to get my ass kicked oh man oh my
god oh my god what
just so you know i don't allow nothing
but going bare knuckle in a brawl if it
isn't if it ain't fishy they need to
fight
great agreed
agreed the fans are eating it up i knew
spending all day fighting would wrap up
these punks
and he was lazy
[Music]
that was it
no way
you just stood there voice overall
discussion that says
yes
[Music]
oh my
god good it was the right decision to
not let the quiet echo speak after all
it doesn't take a big walk talk to make
a big man and the attitude speaks louder
than words
yeah
we rocked it
we said this is like an idle manager
game
we managed to down perfectly into
stardom
keep yourself where you're watching
yeah i'm sorry everything good work
here's how we try to apply what we
learned from you about the ways of the
yankee tour panel
the fan response was fabulous i'm so in
shock
yeah it seemed that way you guys learned
well i'm proud of you all
looks like the yoko and she saw us will
keep shooting up door and stardom at the
speed of light
we owe you big time kid your son
a wild shirt
ah that's wild y'all
that was the most fun i ever had
speaking in public get yourself on vans
we're going to keep working hard
on what you told us about the way of the
yankee we'll work on our speaking skills
as well
keep an eye on those kids
the yoko michi silvers are kicking it up
into another gear yeah
give that your best shot yeah yeah yeah
yeah
wait whoa whoa
hmm
nice
we finished the side quest i think
um
damn junkie and
nada
and let me put it on
will i see myself wearing it
no
oh
but how much like
how much does it do by the way does it
like have any stats
ah seven
oh plus seven okay better than nothing
okay okay where the hell do i need to go
someone said something about my pager
uh oopsie
pager
uh
well that's the latest one right how did
we not see
well how does that help me
hmm
sound is really good also it has an
effect oh nice
south of the bowling alley
can i um make the uh
map bigger oops that was not it
oh there we go
uh
r1
bowling alley
where is the bowling alley
uh
i wouldn't be one of the purple ones
oh my god i can learn all those games
here
enjoy erotic videos here
fancy
uh-huh place for drinks and singing
arcane bowling out here oh i'm like so
close to it
behind it
wait my head
[\h__\h]
out
can i not read this one dialogue please
i guess it's a side quest
this is okay if i don't read this one
you can read silently
what you guys know here
it's main story oh okay
uh
uh then you watched your little buddies
around from club to club drinking until
done leaving pretty large for a broke
guy ain't down
we're spying on me
you got them right you know how many
different lenders you've [\h__\h] over a
pork chop
it's collection day and your ass is
getting beat
a female collections agent
that's the depth collector
pattern
she takes on the drops that make other
collections boys run away crying and she
always always gets the cash
her styles bold blunt and brutal
add that to a bulldog's own tennis city
tenacity and you get one main bite my
big boy
you got me boy i was this close to
getting my face caved in over a silly
like
that that a while back yeah
yeah
all right look there boy and we're about
to see what makes our lady miss tattoo
so incredible
i think we can get the money out of me
i'd like to see you try
your ones and your tiny toys do you
think your little butternutter can stop
me
drop the tough act sugar tits
i put a dozen dudes in the hospital with
this baby if you have a tear-stained
apology ready for me though i'll hear
you up
that's my line sugar moves set the part
about hearing you up since you'll be too
dead now make your move
hmm
a no boy no no
showtime
oh hello wow is this our second party
member or so um
[Music]
that's red
oh we learned it from here
[Music]
oh
yes i want to learn how to rip out
someone's arms
that's right
damn
that is indeed red
yeah
son
looks like that was beating down gave
you a few ideas yeah yeah where is here
fantastic boy i hope you're ready to put
them into practice
uh-oh
i don't know if i can
mm-hmm
um
ah [\h__\h] king kun's getting beat to hell
he paid the tab last night so let's say
we pay you back by sucker punching this
crazy [\h__\h] for him
yes
we're gonna help
of course
gentlemen wow what a pixelated shirt
let's get out of here
switch to b style you can switch to visa
by pressing right
wait that's a new style right
oh press
square while near a large weapon showing
a down mark
[Music]
all the weapons have oh
what the [\h__\h] why am i so slow oh
because i'm a beast wait wait
[Music]
hey hey
wait
damn
wow
i need i need something to pick up again
[Music]
can i
can i use um
[Music]
yeah
there we go
can i do uh
stop stop
okay
withstand the enemy attacks when using
resell hold l1 to guard let's um to
guard let's
ah what
[Music]
i can't read sentences anymore
when using b style holding l1 to guard
lets you withstand enemy attacks with
the resist guard
you will take a certain amount of damage
but you are protected against attacks
coming from any direction
bolstering your defense by equipping
gear in the pause menu
further reduces the damage you take over
this card okay
[Music]
hello
okay they're just beating me up now can
we not can we not
i can't hear
[Music]
you made me really [\h__\h] mad man
who is left
oh my god
whole motorcycle
fart whoever owns that motorcycle i'm
really sorry
uh no you leave that girl alone
if it isn't porky's little friends i saw
you boys crawling the bars last night
oh
but i must be hearing things because it
sounded like you said something about
punching a [\h__\h] out if you're
interested this [\h__\h] is ready to go
i don't know ma'am oh this is crazy what
could the man would punch a lady in with
a grip
so pathetic
all right now pick up that sack sack
lying over there and get the hell on my
side i got what i came here for got no
use for him now
yay
okay
no heat run no i'm not trying to do that
i don't know man yes
yes
[Music]
i'm almost too strong as a bear on
barroids
you want to tackle then so gonna
introduce me to my knight you're setting
armor here
all right yeah he's kitties
i remember the name if you've got baja
singing your praises you've got to be
pretty tough
[Music]
sorry guys i need to stop reading so
much
i am trying to learn it
[Music]
um
i am
trying
to learn it
boy
yes
uh
shut up
i want some stupid leads man i also want
some food
i see a restaurant
um
[Music]
you never know when these dishes coming
out i want to know when they come in
handy
[Music]
um
no bowling alley
wait do i still need to go behind the
bowling alley ah
oh hey everybody been looking for you
huh you again you got a lot of nerves
showing up now what do you want
i mean it's pretty clear what i want you
have to pay a production money pile if
you're doing business in commodore chill
you're doing business is this a side
quest for main class
the hell is that it's not protection
money if you don't show up to actually
protect me when i need it and you have
the gal to ask for more
meh
why do you need it what are you talking
about
thank you thing ghost
thank you
i'm talking about the tattoo about the
tattoo banana real estate when they came
and chased me out you people were
nowhere inside some protection
yeah well you know you're not gonna
touch any bananas there
it's complicated complicated minds you
guys are scared and running away what
could be simpler just get scared well
whatever you think
thanks to you i had a real okay now i'm
scrambling my eggs to get new customers
to make up for all the ones i lost i
couldn't pay you even if i wanted to
you better keep that attitude and check
[\h__\h]
mind if i cut in
uh anyone
why
why family are you with
no family anymore
i'm not in anybody's family
yeah
excuse me
well what do you want from me
you're saying you open the shop here
because tattoo banana real estate forced
you out of your last location is that
right
oh i see what this is
you're trying to be this guy's new
muscle hell no
what
our family has handled this cafe's
protection for 30 years wow
okay we're trying to swoop in our turf
halloween war
30 years
if you need protection
for 30 years
maybe it's time to think about moving
your cafe in a more safe area where you
don't need protection
like
um
i don't know
go to shibuya or i don't know harajuku
or
for chill cafe
protection
i loved going to cafes in omotesando
it's really a fancy like a fashion
high fashion
street because the motesando has all the
all the fancy um brands the expensive
ones and it has nice nice cafes
i went there when i was really young i
always went to cafes there
[Music]
shut your mouth and try me i'll kill you
oh
there we go are you happy now guys
i cracked his [\h__\h] brain open
his brain is spilling on the floor
get lost
i'm eating um porky by the way
white chocolate pokey
yum yum yum yum pokey are like
my favorite snacks for streams recently
don't get my finger dirty my fingers and
quick quick snack very crunchy very
yummy mmm mikado
white chocolate mikado
this is mikado but i thought people
would recognize it easier when i say
pocky
i'm not planning on asking you for money
yeah i'm not like that i'm not even in
yakuza i really just want to talk for a
minute
talk about what
that's
doing a little investigation and i'd
like to tell you i like you to tell me
what you know anything is fine
but i know isn't it hell not
besides i'd prefer never to deal with
those guys again they're terrifying
terrifying how what did they do to you
it's not even what they did they just
knew about me like everything about me
like what
my parents home address my daughter's
school where i sourced all the cafe
supplies who all my customers are with
that much ammo they didn't have to do
anything
and to top it off they're not even
yakuza at least with that locked you
know what you expect let's see hmm
yeah
and where would i go if i want to meet
the guy from touch about his office who
played you that visit
they're probably still here finishing
what they started
so uh
the place my cafe was in
they've driven most of the tenants out
so the place is practically empty but
there was one stubborn guy who said the
only way he was leaving was in a casket
some balls that got
very brave
and he's still there
probably they were making him all kinds
of sweet deals but he turned down every
last one
if he's still there now touchy bunny's
boys will be too
go have a look if you really want to get
mixed up with them
all right thanks i appreciate it
um
hakua building
let's go there we finally got a hint of
where to go
huh
a nice suit can i
have that sparkling blue suit
that's a beautiful color
[Music]
wait a second wait a second i want to do
something
okay
back to normal
i don't know what i just used but some
kind of bottle
yeah
you belong in the trash
trash damn
originally someone charged with me with
a blue sparkly suit
or am i going crazy also i think they're
this the colors of these suits changed
again now
maybe i'm just seeing a lot of red
colors
all right
time to move on
like i could just run away from them but
when they yell at me like that i feel
challenged
a by the way
maybe i should tell you guys a little
bit about yesterday
my mom came by last minute
i'm actually with my brother because my
brother was visiting her
and my mom needed something
she kind of lives like really really on
the country side in the middle of
nowhere and
um
she needed
something really not important what it
is but
um yeah so she got my
brother to drive her to me
and we went to
eat some cake i invited them for some
coffee and cake
yeah they were like falling over it
because it was so good i had two pieces
of cake
a banana chocolate cake and a strawberry
cake mmm
yeah yeah and my brother was enjoying
some cake too it was like holy [\h__\h] it's
so good
yeah and then um
and then
my brother eventually left and uh
i had to prepare for my allen ring
stream but before that
uh my mom said that she would clean my
apartment because that one time when i
talked on stream about getting a maid
maybe for one time only um my mom was
listening and
she said yo i just come over there and
clean then you shouldn't hire me and i'm
like okay
because she kind of
promised to do that anyway at some point
i guess like kind of um
to
i think it's supposed to be kind of like
as a
pay payback to
uh for how i'm helping her you know when
one helps the other
yeah
so uh but yeah before my stream we did
clean a lot together we threw out like a
million cardboard boxes again and a lot
of things that i was just hiding in some
corners and ignoring that they were
existing we put like uh
put those away and put it into the
into the
uh
cellar
yeah i just needed something to push
i need to push from someone to actually
do that [\h__\h]
and yeah while i was streaming she
she um cleaned she wiped my floor
hallelujah i just really wanted
my my floor to be wiped because i was uh
too lazy to do that wrap i have a lot of
floor you know big floor
the big big big floor
if you're looking for some floor i have
it i have much much floor
um
yeah after the stream like i because i
didn't i didn't leave my room for like
what how many hours was it yesterday six
hours or so and i walk out
and it's like a completely different
world
it was crazy it looks so clean now my
apartment is so clean i hope i can keep
it up for a while
i hope so
noggies too yeah yeah cause she was
getting some snack for herself so she
brought me nuggies
nuggets
looks like this is the place tachibana's
real estate has been trying to buy up
um no business sense seems touching one
of those boys live up to the rumors
oh one is left snaku it's a snuck snack
bar
the last one standing
[Music]
yo
are you the owner
you don't leave even when it's closed
how to protect it
right or are you from touch
oh finally some voice over hallelujah
nah she didn't play on the ring she's
not really interested
i tried to convince her
but yeah
okay that outside was the guy trying to
get off
the door
he seems nice
wait i'll help you oh
hence you'll help
[Music]
who cares
i'll get a new phone
they'll probably find out though as they
seem to know everything
i can take care of them
[Music]
you know
he's just one random guy that he just
met but i feel like with that one
sentence the way he says it
i feel like i can believe him
i feel like
that one sentence
is so convincing
he will indeed keep me safe
oh what a man
[Laughter]
can he does indeed trust him
is it him
no okay
oh
[Music]
it doesn't sound familiar
foreign
oh
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
it
you're good buddy are you good
wait what
chronology
[Music]
i'm smart i mean
you got to be smart against those
[\h__\h] i mean if you're in a situation
like that then
i think it's smart of him to make use of
it
otherwise he's just losing money going
out early
probably going in dead
sake
[Music]
his baby and his
ladies
that is pretty creepy
[Music]
a real estate company willing to make an
enemy of the tojo clan the owner of
catholic blind
may have been right about them being
worse than the yakuza
i still want a bit more info hopefully i
can track down those other homeless guys
in this neighborhood i usually see them
hanging around park boulevard maybe i'll
start there
all right
it's night time or the sun is going down
look the sky is orange
nice
okay uh maybe we should save while we're
here
yeah sunset is nice
chef
love love seeing a nice sunset
anyway my mom had to
um stay over the night
uh otherwise she wouldn't have been able
to go home
but before saying tonight we made um
some food together because i had some
ingredients for
i wanted to make a
a simple
um
uh
what do you call it again casserole no
it's real
the thing where you throw things
together then put it into the oven and
then you put it out and then it's a not
so fancy looking but very delicious meal
you know what i mean was it a casserole
did you guys call it a casserole
yeah casserole okay
yeah yeah and we made that yeah
my mom was um
kind of suffering
because all the cleaning made her hands
like
i guess she got a lot of the cleaning
material on her hands and she said it
was really um
not itchy but
um
well
yeah irritated very irritated and she
had a few cuts
so my mom i don't know she had a really
clumsy moment yesterday she already had
cuts in her fingers from cleaning and uh
and it was really irritated by the
cleaning [\h__\h] and then when she was like
cutting
um cutting some veggies for the
casserole
and then she cut herself again during
the cooking process several times
and i was i was um
i was grilling the meat that was gonna
go into the casserole
and after a while i was done so i i
turned off the heat of the heat plate
but
i don't know why she did that but like a
few minutes later like maybe five
minutes later
she's like oh this isn't hot anymore
right and then without like
thinking she puts her full hand flat
hand flat out on the
on the stove
and i'm like no that she's like ah [\h__\h]
that's hot and i'm like what are you
doing
of course it's still hot
she's like why is it still on like of
course it's still hot it takes some time
until it's not hot anymore
she kept on hurting herself yesterday
yeah
mommy what are you doing
[\h__\h] pawn point
[Music]
but she's always like ah this matter
doesn't matter no problem no problem
like she's like
she
she uh
always says that
her hands are like
you know
like leather
stuff doesn't hurt her anymore but but
that that actually did hurt apparently
i don't know what she's doing
yeah but eventually we finished the the
casserole and it was really yummy it was
really yummy
yeah yeah
um my mom was um
um scolding me doll for
some things
we're using um margarine instead of
butter sometimes
and for using uh
a rama
creamy sauce instead of just using
schlock salad or whatever schnako was
yeah yeah blah blah blah i was like mama
i use what i want for cooking
hey
yes she was she was backseating me
no no not for actually on that day i
wasn't even using margarita i was using
butter anyway
yeah
i didn't even have it there but
i recently have been using more butter
but i used to use more
margarine and margarine and there's
actually a reason for why i do that
because
um for me first of all it tastes the
same as butter okay and second of all um
usually they're here here they're more
often sold in like a soft
softer form than butter so it's easier
to spread it on bread that's literally
the actual only reason why i've been
buying it but recently i found a butter
that
is kind of like the same softness and
also easy to spread so now i buy that
okay so so stop backstitching me now you
guys are also backsiding me kill thuggle
anyway
can't believe it's not butter
doesn't taste the same
all these backstages my my ex-roommate
she also used to say that she was like
yeah
you shouldn't yeah no i don't want to
eat your margarine you should eat butter
but it's much better and i'm like i
don't know what you're talking about
tastes the same to me
especially if you put like if that's not
the main thing you're eating but you put
like a jam or something on top of it
like bread margarine and then jam
it's like
just
it doesn't matter
anyway
apparently liking margarine gets me
cancelled
unbelievable you got to work on any good
jobs if i did i'd be doing that myself
speaking of i heard cyclists i just got
back from that cake for charging for not
real estate
i seriously bastard i don't think he cut
me in on some of that if i asked him no
i can't can't hurt to ask he's probably
a republican park free
public park free really that's the name
and i'm just standing there menacingly
listening and they don't give a [\h__\h]
no oh my god it's a scandal it's a
butter scandal kiwawa and the butter
scandal
okay
okay chill guys
yeah i had one like really dead plant
right
my mom took it home she said i won't get
it back until months later
because it's absolutely dead she cut off
everything even the still with one
single still okay looking leaf
even
yeah
she even cut that away she said
everything must be cut off and she's got
to bring it home and then put it into a
water bath
because she needs to save my plant
i already missed it but
i know that plant was really difficult
to take care of the other ones that i
have are doing okay
yeah she confiscated my plan
it used to look so beautiful
[Music]
i'm also sad about it
let me have a go done
do you have a green pup no
i apparently don't
but i'm trying i'm working on it i'm
better at it than before
yes
and uh
oh wait i can't get old ah wait i can't
okay
[Music]
i did not beat the plant margarine
and another thing that she did was she
brought some
she has she has like a huge garden
wouldn't even call it the garden anymore
it's so huge it's like a park
and um from there
she brought me some
roots and [\h__\h]
uh
some like starter like a starter kit for
a balcony garden
um
she got me oh [\h__\h]
uh
what's review sell in english
she got me those and she got me um
raspberries some that are supposed to
bloom in summer and some that are
supposed to bloom in
uh fall in autumn
uh yeah that was it for now i think
um
i think it's an austrian word even
though it's german
for a certain berry maybe someone can
look it up yeah
touch you on the christmas red currant
i guess it could be curry
there are red ones and there are i think
darker
purplish ones or so no it's not
johanna's parent no
not exactly
no
i'm confused no
red ones don't wrap i think remission
are the red ones and johannesburg are
the blue ones
i think
at least here
i think that's what we would say in
austria we would call the red ones the
fifth cell and the blue ones
johannesburg
i think
[Music]
so it is current i guess yeah
so so and then she she kind of uh she
bought um she my brother and her on
their way to me with the car they
brought um
like some some containers for my balcony
to put the
uh
the plants in
and also
uh today
uh
after my mom woke up even though we were
supposed to buy together she just went
on her own and bought a [\h__\h] ton of
uh
um
earth
earth soil
to plant everything in and now i have it
all ready now it's all in my balcony and
and i'm so excited to have raspberries
she said that it's gonna like um
she said it's gonna be like really big
it's gonna it's right now it's just like
a stick sticking out of the soil like
several sticks
but she said it's gonna bloom like into
a really really big bush
and it's gonna have a lot of raspberries
i'm so excited to have fresh raspberries
a lot of them
yeah
i'm so excited so i don't always have to
go to the supermarket and buy them
especially with raspberries when i buy
them at the supermarket whole [\h__\h]
there's like most of them are always
really really
bad they they get back like after one
day and even if you just have bought
them you open it and there's usually
already some bad ones in there
so
i'm excited to have them
at my balcony so i can have them at my
disposal
[Music]
they have really short shelf life yeah
yeah
i'm gonna be eating raspberries all
summer i love raspberries and we wanted
to do strawberries too but my mom
couldn't find uh
she didn't have anything at her place
uh she has most other things but no no
strawberries yet i suppose so i'm gonna
buy some strawberry starters uh
in the store and um because i still have
some space for planting so i'm gonna
plant them in there i'm gonna do my best
i'm excited i'm excited um and and and
we talked about planting some more
things she told me i can plant this and
that and this and that in between
i forgot
was easy some other things are more
difficult like basilicum is [\h__\h] never
works she told me
but i would like to have some fresh
herbs
as well
uh
chives yeah i think it's chives
chaps would be cool to have
um
pitta celia would be nice too
but
i don't know
we'll see we start as long as i have
some fruit there man i'm so excited
[Music]
i'm so excited oh my god oh and she said
that uh i think it was the i think it
was the current plant that it blooms
really nicely like it has some cute
little flower looking
um
things
yeah yeah
what's happening
right now
should i buy you some coffee or what
soda
sake
is
good acting
[Music]
like
requires some inventory space how much
okay
uh
you have to remember it
oh well how much space i have
oh wait that's it it like
is that the cap
that's it
five slots
can i like throw it away yeah this card
this card
what was that again
um
i could throw that away guys that was
that expensive
one two three four five okay
here's the item box oh [\h__\h]
great pocket t-shirt
what do you want
socket okay
yeah sake
you want
champagne
sake champagne
scotch convenience store sake champagne
beer
sweet potato shorter
okay convenience store for one only i
have to go to donkey hotel
uh socket
potato sweet potato sochi champagne beer
scotch sucker squash beer
she put a shoju champagne yeah that's
fine i think i got it i think i got it
down you guys wrote it down too so we
good okay here's the
here's the the
convenience store
so most of the things we can get here
dun dun dun dun dun dun hi
let me see
sweet potato show you
uh what is this
beer okay
is this whiskey is whiskey scotch
he did say something about whiskey is
that the same thing
i would you don't know i think i think
so that must be what he means
um
no
kind of
who are they ain't gonna
no
watch the type of risky
uh
will he be okay with this
none for this quit yeah
can i get a donkey holder too
okay
uh so but okay uh
beer and
potato sauce
whiskey scotch okay
[Music]
mijo what's up sorry
i just started working here so
i guess it takes a while to get used to
it and learn about all the different
products well good luck um
thank you sir oh and what's kind of the
new look you're cute
[Music]
my name is mijo if you come here often
we'll be seeing each other a lot so i
thought i should introduce myself
i'm not sweet of her
oh
this could be the beginning of a
friendship with me who interacting with
her will gradually fill the friendship
class you can check the state status of
the gosh at any time in the past when
you do
okay
okay where is uh
[Music]
oh yeah
okay
[Music]
da
now
[Music]
gosh it's fancier oh my god it's as
narrow as don quixote really is it's as
stacked and colorful as don quijote
really is although it seems like we
can't go too many places here because
they're blocking everything
okay it's like this but it's it's
usually more than one floor and more
space than this i mean like more more
items
i love donkeys
doggy hotels
[Music]
oh
donkey water
[Music]
oh
are you guys barely here
and i just barely hear that here it says
awkward
now i forgot what i was supposed to buy
thank god he didn't say golden champagne
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] that's all we can get disappear
okay i guess we're gonna go to a
different convenience store for the
for the scotch
what are we missing now only the scotch
that's the beer yeah we got them we got
that didn't we
suck it or maybe that's also in the
other
oh
show me where's
maybe that's also in the other
convenience store
ah
combini convenient
[Music]
i love you
i love you company
forever
oh man you can't thank you cool thank
you i just made it up
um do you have what i'm looking for
sucky
we didn't get sake yet didn't we
and then
wait he also doesn't have that
what
else maybe kakuvin is okay
it doesn't have the right scotch either
i'm cereal
this [\h__\h] scotch
uh
where else
hmm
sells imported brands
donkey hotel
maybe this purple bowl or one's a
different purple and it didn't have it
do you think the other people will have
it
can i like teleport over there it's so
far away
right of don quixote oh wait there's one
here
pawn shop no that's not it so maybe
maybe
that one
that was so close
now i'm gonna go all the way back
[Music]
how
someone call me a noob uh
[Music]
wow
oh i got like 7 million on me damn
almost 8 million
yeah yeah you better be apologizing to
me
oh yeah
oh yeah i tweeted out that i
had my mom take a nice bath right
yeah she said um
she has some problems with her
her
bathroom at home
so she was really excited to take a bath
in my
[Music]
in my home
and i'm excited to
provide it
so i had her
uh choose a bath bomb i actually have
like a couple of lush bath bombs at home
and i was like i've got this and decent
decent days and this to choose from
which one do you want and then
smell them
and choose one
and then and then i
and i prepared the bath for her
and then it was too hot so i brought her
a cold glass of water with
with ice ice um
ice cubes and i gave her my ipad i said
mommy if you drop this i'm i'm gonna cry
but please be really careful but but
please enjoy and then she said okay i
just want to watch hermit craft and like
what the [\h__\h] is that and i looked it up
on youtube for her and it's a [\h__\h]
minecraft thing my mom
the
video of choice that she watches in the
bathtub to relax is hermit craft
can you believe it can you believe it
she was like oh i just watched this this
is new i'm gonna kind of watch this from
the new season
and then i then i left the bathroom and
i let her do her thing
and she was laughing so loud and hermit
craft
[Laughter]
she was like
nice movie
nice moving
baby i love you
i love you
yeah new season apparently just started
it's a minecraft there's a people a
group of people there and there it is
it's a group of people
who make
minecraft videos
i used to watch them oh
yeah i'm glad she had a good time in my
bathtub
yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah and i have people are really
surprised on twitter i don't know why
but um can i um get close to oh it's
pretty close anyway
uh but i have a bathtub pillow people
were like there's bathtub pillows of
course there's bathtub pillows
there's some low quality ones though
that never stick to the bathtub i got
actually a pretty good one
it sticks pretty nicely it's really
comfy
it gives your back and your neck and
your head
a nice
support
makes it way more comfortable
to be in the
in the bathtub i'm usually more of a
shower type of person
but but i do like the thought of taking
a bath just the thought
so it made it more comfortable
yeah
wouldn't they get wet oh yeah but it's
some material that can get wet no
problem
yeah
did you get the sweet potato i think i
did
so you want the sake apparently
there you go
you don't even need five slots at once
you can just give it one by one
you wanted you wanted the sweet potato
no you wanted the beer okay
apparently
rip achievement what
what one
i used a rolled up towel for the bath
pill oh i guess that works too but
um i think my bathtub pillow is pretty
amazing
ah whatever yeah there you go sweet
potato show too
there you go
oh and she was actually trying to watch
uh my stream on my tv in my bedroom a
little bit but the quality was really
bad apparently and the wi-fi was really
[\h__\h] while i was streaming
so
she couldn't actually watch it but she
was cleaning like
from beginning of my stream to the end
of my stream anyway
yeah and i mean she could hear it she
could hear my suffering
but my mom really insists on
me playing
more games like fps games like she wants
me to continue playing um
um
def loop and she wants me to play this
on it i was like mom i want to play this
on it too okay chill but i can't right
now
and she wants me to play more elven ring
even though even though
she doesn't even want to play it
yeah yeah
but and i i know you guys say based and
all that and then
that i should indeed play only but then
i said and i want you guys to listen
every once in a while cool okay i'll
play those games but
i mean it's just not that easy for me
because it's not my genre and
they're fun to like experience a little
bit and pick up and learn a little bit
but but it's not not gonna be playing
i'm gonna not gonna be playing these
games all the time so please don't
expect that from me um
i wanna i wanna play games you know we
talked about it on whole talk there's no
way to standpoint but i want to play
games that i can genuinely enjoy and
um don't feel too stressed out about
doing a good job in
uh
yeah
i mean
like something like elden ring in theory
i really really really am interested in
it
but
the battle
makes it kind of stressful and i feel
pressured to do well although i do think
yesterday i did do well
yesterday yeah i think i did fairly
fairly well i mean for a [\h__\h]
beginner
um
so
yeah it's okay i mean okay there were
still a lot of stupid mistakes but i
[\h__\h] owned dead lion boss
and enlarge it eventually
but still it still puts me under
pressure and i feel stressed out um
like not insanely okay but still it's
more comfortable for me to play games
like these
yeah and
it's just my taste my personal
preference
and i hope you guys
respect it but you guys are used to me
playing these kind of games anyway
mostly
so i will i will continue to try to
provide to you guys some variety every
now and then um
but
yeah i'm definitely never gonna have
like weekly fps streams or weekly horror
streams just not gonna happen
it's just not gonna happen
[Music]
talk games are secondary thank you
you would start questioning who you i
would start questioning who you were if
you did thank you true
i did tell her
i mean i appreciate that jim is so into
it and like
um thinks about
you know
you know has some thoughts about it and
some input i appreciate that
but in the end
um
people will always recommend
their own favorite games and their own
favorite genres
even
even when it's not my favorite games and
my favorite genres they you know i
understand you know you're very
convinced about those games because you
enjoyed them so much i get that
you guys in the in the audience and also
my mom
i get that okay um and i give them a try
i give them a chance sometimes
um
and and um i i do enjoy some aspects of
it of those games but well yeah it's
just not my main genre
ori ori was yeah that was um actually
not not really a recommendation but it
was i played it because it was an
awesome game and it's really cute and
and um i thought it would be nice to
play on my stream
was very challenging but i did enjoy
that one a lot
yeah um
that genre if you're gonna see more of
that on my channel well
maybe
also every once in a while like once in
no no
two or three months if we have a if we
currently don't have like any big
ongoing series going on
um
yeah
if i have time for it on my channel
i think now
um
your tongue is living
up uh now at the moment we're gonna be
busy with yakuza for a while and elder
ring
um
i guess i'm still gonna continue it a
little bit
not i'm not against it i still want to
adventure a little bit see a bit more of
the game a bit more of the story
when we go of course why are you asking
is it really necessary to ask about
windbreaker i told you a million times
that i want to play with wake up
yeah
i think maybe
if there is not anything else like new
coming out or something that i was
waiting for that i got permissions for
suddenly
after yakuza then we might start wind
waker
um but there's a
always a big chance that suddenly i get
some
uh permissions for something that i that
i feel i have to play that now now it's
urgent or something new coming on out
that i forgot about that was coming out
happy that you're playing it thank you
yeah i didn't really expect um
you know yakuza to be my thing either
but then thanks to a sponsorship i
realized yo
yo this is dope um
i love this my mom doesn't like it
though she says it's too crazy
see to eat your own everybody has their
own taste i'm not gonna push my tastes
onto you guys
i mean
it's my channel so i'm streaming what i
want so in some way i guess you know i'm
not pushing it on to you
but i guess i am introducing my tastes
to you guys but you're doing this
voluntary you're watching my streams
voluntarily so that it's a different
story
um
but uh the other way around
uh
please respect
er my taste
um
i'm also gonna give your games a chance
though don't worry about it
we're watching of course you're watching
voluntarily
unbelievable
[Music]
foreign
i like the voice acting in this game
[Music]
foreign
the champion this drink that may be my
ticket to bumping into taxi by this boys
again
um it's difficult to find a place to s
uh stop
huh
ah you again
i think i'm gonna stop soon and we're
gonna read some pachatos
but this time it's a subquest
okay while we're here let's do it
interesting vending machine over there
never seen a vending machine like that
before
why are you on your way somewhere boy
sorry to hold you up
yeah yeah i want to talk that's right
tell me have you been training no i
guess so
because i have something i like to ask
you to do if you're willing that is
what's with the hesitation that's not
like
a truth is i've got some debt collectors
on my tail scary wounds
mmm you've been running since we met no
no no those two bit jokers are nickel
and dime stuff talking two-ness famous
and i mean that in the global sense and
now they're here in japan or hot in my
heart on my tail
no
no no no
hold on did you seriously try to escape
your mountain of death by fleeing to
japan
oh
yeah and this time there may be no going
back i think there is a price on my head
[\h__\h]
oh man i guess it's too late to pay the
money back then what are you going to do
kill them no
i was hoping i could get you to be my
bodyguard
i figured as much unfortunately i've
already got enough trouble on my plate
believe me it's probably being worse
danger with me around
oh no
that's no way to have a heart please
sure i can't pay a retainer but if you
protect me i'll teach you some of my top
shelf moves that good stuff
are these moves better than you credited
yes
yes damn straight they are they'll do
you right in a tight fight my boy
hmm
oh
where's talking
uh-oh they're coming for him already
ah i think they found me boys
there's a big scary that's right there
um yeah for your head it's just doing my
job so don't hold it against me
that's cool like that more like hitman
no no i don't want to die please help me
boy
okay
kill him
he's okay yeah your kidney doesn't kill
people i know i know
give you no kill lou no no
but kiara yes killed yes yes
is he strong
[Music]
[\h__\h]
you have a [\h__\h] gun
yeah a [\h__\h] gun
really
you're fighting me with a gun
real strong men fight with fits fist
fits face have you not learned that boy
i'm letting you live
can you go back and tell whoever ordered
the heads to forget about bachelors you
hear me
i don't think i'm the only one after
this guy
what
there'll be others on this trail soon
enough he'll get what's coming to him
yeah
damn ah
sorry sorry boy
why do you apologize i told you to watch
out for a knife in your ribs yet here
i'm putting you in danger myself
don't worry about that i'd rather hear
more about the opinion made earlier what
you said you teach me some new moves
better make it quick though before the
next hitman gets here
you sure about this boy
don't have much choice like i said i've
got my own problems some of you extra
survival skills will come in handy
all right
you what you're not teaching me what the
[\h__\h]
teach me
hey bye
[Applause]
ready to learn my boobs here
i guess oh boy
what
you [\h__\h]
i just saved your ass
and you promised me to teach me
something and then you won't do it
oh boy
thank you for reminding me oopsy
class connina
beast
now we go
hold l1 press
triangle i'll never remember that
yeah yeah yeah
let's um
ah
[Music]
what do we have
when i taunt an enemy r2
[Music]
i'll go for another one of those
wrong style he br teaches brala okay
okay
i gotta
up everything anyway
[Music]
there goes my
do you guys focus on one style or do you
mix them
to the people who played this game
[Music]
i think the holding one i can remember
okay
can you teach me something now
hey bye
oh
how do i break down defenses
important standing
[Music]
face squeeze you learned the essence of
face twisting
on your face
[Music]
yes
can we try it out oh there we go okay
we'll get to try it
out yes
let's see if i can do it a heat move
look
can i even activate it
[Music]
twisting his face
sounds terrifying
um
slip past a guarding enemies arms
grab their face
twist them to the ground and stomp them
to finish the job
okay
uh
wow
okay but that means i would have to have
my gosh full
first
and then
at the same time be so lucky to have him
in a garden
dance
so the circumstances must align in order
to do that
[Music]
oh my god
dead he's dead
happens more often than your thing
hmm
okay
defenseman targeting math was using
braille style to take out okay
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
all right
i'm kind of waiting and hoping for him
to but yeah i don't have the
heat yet anyway
wait what the hell was that that i just
saw
[Music]
anymore
yeah
oh he really likes protecting himself
like that
well i got a lot of things to work with
[Music]
stop it
i never push the button fast enough oh
what the [\h__\h]
stop with those two nebula wheels
[Music]
yeah my fingers got too tired
you got scars
oh grabbing breaks it too oh
[Music]
so strong
oh i'm so sick of you
get up get up
wait i want to try that
[Music]
i can't anymore i can't i can't fight
anymore oh
my monitor
[Music]
oh yeah
oh that feels good
[Music]
what oh fro what is growing i thought it
was a heat mold but it didn't do [\h__\h]
sorry guys i'm really bad at this right
now
[Music]
it seems i have slipped
dude help me
[Music]
oh man
impressive
impressive man
out
[Music]
at least i figured i'd have to do that
one
[Music]
almost almost there
is this supposed to be such a difficult
battle
i mean he doesn't do much damage but
he's just really defensive
[Music]
oh good music though yeah
i don't care how to break past my
defenses
i have my tricks i have my tricks
thanks dude maybe you teach me another
one another time
uh
i am gonna say
at that pain pay phone pain phone
that's that's why it's called pain phone
i feel it
did i get healed for that probably not
yeah my youbies my humans have ran out
of steam already
hours ago when i was dancing on the
dance floor oh that was a lot of fun
that was so much fun
did i save did i save
i think i did
that worked right yeah
okay everybody
okay so i'm gonna read super chats i'm
gonna take a
five minute break ourselves
[Music]
thank you guys for watching the start of
a new series today yakuza 0 hope you
enjoyed it feel free to stay stay feel
free to stay
until
uh the end of the stream if you want to
hear a bit more chit chat if you got to
go then you got to go thank you though i
hope i see you again soon i think by the
way tomorrow will probably maybe be the
uh continuing of
um
later alligator i think so that's
currently
what i have in mind
um
gonna start a little bit later than
today tomorrow
oh yeah
oh wait no wrong that was uh no not
tomorrow tomorrow is vr oh [\h__\h]
okay i i mixed something up
i think i wanted to later alligator on
wednesday then
tomorrow
yeah yeah okay never mind then never
mind
scratch that
yeah me and am i doing vr tomorrow
i'm gonna charge my vr stuff oh and i
gotta oh
see if everything works properly yeah
yeah yeah
exciting exciting
okay so give me five minutes
on
yeah
should be
on my channel i think by the way
uh no 12 p.m pst
as far as i know
candy bird yeah
okay i'll see you in a few minutes
please uh stay
don't go
oh
[Music]
hello sorry gotta clean my
office this was for iris
iris's birthday stream did you guys
watch your birthday stream
i made uh because i couldn't be there
live and made a video yesterday
happy birthday video
yes yes yes yes most of people watch it
yay
let me fix the chat
sure
no we're sleeping me too me too
i was sleeping too
and recently everyone's celebrating
their birthday when i can't call in
unfortunate
blood it is what it is
it is still snowing over there in march
oh
uh
well
you know sometimes it does even in april
well i
i guess it's about time to switch to
my normal office again
um is it about to say
is it time to say goodbye
i don't want to leave this comfy cozy
office
but
but but soon i think it will happen soon
because i got some surprise uh another
surprise happening soon
um
put the video back on there we go
there you go so how do you notice
it's still not really quite that um
[Music]
springy yet though is it
let me pick some bgm as well
[Music]
wait a second
wait is it super tangy tub
super chats super chats we have super
tangents i suppose
yeah there might be some tangents here
and there i don't know you never know
with cuba
what do we want to listen to what are we
feeling like
uh music
audio stuck
i'm feeling like chilling
so i'm gonna
whoa
that's a bit loud for me
oh no it's actually fine
okay
chill cafe music i want to listen to
kiwawa's voice ah
sweet
it will be a tangent i notice you you
seem to know everything huh what else do
you know what else do you know that you
haven't told me
might as well leave the decorations up
that is also true
might as well have all decorations like
christmas easter
birthday
all of them all up at once halloween
everything
so you never have to take anything down
and you never have to take put anything
up again it saves a lot of trouble i
would say
and then your place will always look
festive and fun
no
maybe it will have some chaotic energy
but
that's fine
what that is peak lazy you're take lazy
just make a new all year round
celebration and keep those up forever
yeah
like um universal celebration decoration
some decoration that works for
everything
something that says let's celebrate
okay by the way where do i have to start
reading i think there was maybe three or
three super chats or so for elden ring
before the stream started a couple ones
and whole talk talk
i think i have to start with how to talk
[Music]
yes yes okay
there it is
talk recently
i
i've been trying
i've been trying to get it like to be
shorter again
but it always ends up being so long
recently
[Music]
not really what i intended to do
and let me bring my dog
[Music]
i know you guys say it's okay but
um
i want these interviews to not to not be
too long so that you know when people
want to
look up an interview they don't get
scared away by the long
time of the vlog you know
i feel like people
if a stream is too long i mean you guys
probably don't care but some people i
feel like i think streams are
vods are more
approachable and easy to watch if
they're like shorter like a more compact
length
um
and they're like okay this is one hour
okay i can watch that in
in my free time today but
two and a half hours
i don't have the time for that today
yeah it's easier to digest like if
you're if you're just looking for
something to get to know a certain whole
life member
then
you know i feel like it would be ideal
to have an interview that is a compact
relatively short
length
that's why i want to keep it shorter you
know
[Music]
yeah
um i
two hours is like the maximum length i
want it to be i want to go over two
hours man
oh but i feel like i'm um
one reason why it got so long maybe this
time is because i had three clips and
one singing performance usually if if
the guest sings for me i do two clips
only
um but i wasn't sure if she was gonna
sing she actually um
um
uh
she was she was she wanted to do it but
it took a few days of
you know
time
um
to
get all the points across so i wasn't
sure if we're gonna make it in time
so instead i prepared three clips just
in case that she couldn't um prepare the
singing in time
but it all worked out so then i had a
lot of content a lot of material to show
yeah
um
12 hour home talk oh
love so hard on salad i was so happy to
see she was suffering with it too i'm so
glad i wasn't the only one who was
suffering with the motion controls
um
that was wonderful
i did ask her dale if it's okay to show
cause she's raging in that clip i wasn't
sure if she would be okay with it but i
did ask her um i always ask for
permission like is this clip okay the
show and are these questions okay to ask
and all that like of course i check
everything beforehand if they're okay
with it we are bonding through the
skyward sword vein but that's honestly
something
that i felt like
um connected to nuero not the asmr staff
i i can't connect with that at all
but playing long rpg games like zelda
games and so on
um i respect her doing that and
[Music]
all right could be a bit quieter okay
okay thank you for the membership
membership
arigato
yeah the genres i'm glad that there's
other people who don't scare away from
long uh
long long series
type of
streams um
[Music]
yeah noah's studio well she takes it
very seriously
the asmr stuff
so yeah that is pretty impressive that
studio holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] honestly like after watching
like the piccolo asmr i wouldn't mind
trying to do it like at like one time as
a collab you know
that way it could be funny and all that
but i just don't i don't know like
normal asmr i personally watching it i
feel awkward and i would also feel
awkward doing it myself
but if it's like a one-time
one-time collab where
i know she or anybody else who's good at
it will teach me
i wouldn't mind that
so maybe next time i visit japan
maybe i'll ask no one to stand by
to teach me some asmr in her studio
one time one time
whispering you little [\h__\h] emma i might
do that i might as well do that
ask ame
why am i emma doesn't do any similar
not really
it's not for everyone i like it but i
totally understand thank you yeah
you're not destroying asmr yeah that's
cool like i feel like sounds like that
um or i don't know rain sounds for
example cooking sounds i maybe
understand as well
[Music]
but yeah i don't know you know there's
those ear cleaning
sounds and you know cute whispering and
lay on my lap and all that
to me it's just really awkward
it's fine for other people to enjoy it
but for me it's really not my thing
it makes me feel so awkward
yeah if it's like nature sounds that i
think is
nice and indeed relaxing
i still don't usually choose that
to listen to
like randomly or or when i want to go to
sleep or anything
but i i at least get that
like sometimes for example
would you call that asmr like enos when
ina enters streams
her ending screen is like
there's rain sounds
is that asmr
because that is really really pretty
ambient sounds yeah maybe that's not
asmr maybe that's just ambient zones
[Music]
the white noise with the rain sounds
that kind of stuff
yeah it's beautiful
really soothing
yeah
sorry i'm kind of biased
but to each their own really like
if you guys enjoy asmr if that's if
that's what helps you relax or whatever
yo all the power to you
um
and i
i respect people who make that their
content that's fine too i'll just never
enjoy it
i won't enjoy it but you do you
i think it's cool that you do it and
that you um
enjoy doing it
and take it seriously
listen to what you know no understand
what i had to say
i thought was interesting too
i i look at it objectively
i like to look at things objectively
recently
[Music]
foreign
what else have you been looking at
objectively
are you trying to get something funny
out of me
your mom's boobs
just kidding um
recent happenings in the past weeks
i've been looking at those objectively
[Music]
which helps me a lot
trying to
process them and not
get too heated about it not get too
um emotional about it
um like recently a lot of things have
been happening and uh
in order to not lose my [\h__\h] mind
one has to and i want to give this
advice to you guys too
when there's a lot of [\h__\h] going on in
your life
i feel like sometimes
like i used to be like this too and
maybe i still have sometimes like this
but i get to heat it
um oh you might get to heat it
and you you see everything like way way
darker than
you actually need to
[Music]
things tend to be not as serious as you
make them out to be sometimes in your
head
and as dramatic and as
world
destroying
as you think it might be i mean
yeah some things serious some things
that are serious surely
are
a good reason to cry about but other
things take a step back and think about
if
if that is really
something you need to be so upset about
try to look at it from a different
um
angle a different point of view
uh perspective put things in perspective
yeah
i i think
some people might be able to use that
advice
yeah
a lot of people get so upset over just
um
what do they call it a nothing burger
that's such a weird word a nothing
burger
well nothing burger is that
two buns with no no
meat and sign
[Music]
where did that come from
i heard it on the internet
[Music]
a piano burger yeah that would be better
you can easily get wrapped up in things
yeah no i get it i get it
[Music]
yeah what a disappointment it would be
immeasurable
shut up nordvpn
seize the power of autoconnect never
leave your device unprotected on public
wi-fi again
shut up
am i paying you to annoy me
[Music]
anyway let's start
[\h__\h] mayoka
[Music]
no no
no no okay okay duck joseph thank you
for renting
how are you doing
thank you noah for coming uh on and
thank you tanzo for working hard on
another episode of whole talk yes i said
this um when i get so kept secret
who is gonna be the next guest that the
coming up guest was like really excited
hearing that i wanted her on her talk
she was apparently waiting for it
and i'm so happy to hear that
so that means that whole talk has
is well known
uh and has a good
[Music]
yeah reputation understand fine
no i understand fine
i asked through my manager my manager as
touring manager and then
my manager came back to me and said that
uh no example i was really really
excited about it
and i think her manager too but i'm not
sure
yeah
happy happy
that helps me because
um if they're excited about it then it
will be easier to work with them because
for
for whole talk i always feel so sorry
about like
sending them a wall of text asking for a
lot of different things
um
i need this and that and this and that
and this and that please until that time
sorry it's a lot of text
yeah so it can be very overwhelming but
if they're motivated if they're uh estoy
motivada
then all is good
[Music]
not gonna do one next week though i'm
gonna
have two weeks no whole talk this time
um
need a bit more time this time i think
having it literally every every second
week is a bit too much
so it's gonna be in
um
two weeks in between with no whole talk
now and then the next one should be i
don't know i didn't ask anyone yet i
need to
um ask around
yeah i think yeah um
we can always do a second marine senpai
episode but before that i'll definitely
go for pick on our senpai and i'm gonna
ask ask some
other other girls as well
who haven't
gotten their chance if they wanna do it
or not
i don't wanna push too much you know
there's always a chance that certain
members just don't want to be in whole
talk for whatever reason
that's their choice
that's their thing and i'm sure that
it's hard for them to say it like that
like sorry i just don't want to be in
hot tub maybe they're just
maybe they just don't want to say it so
i'll just ask a few times and if it's
still if it's if still nothing comes
back then i'll just take it as okay they
just maybe don't want to be on talk
i'll just
try to read the air
at the moment i'm still not sure
i'll give it a few more tries
yeah
it's understandable i mean maybe maybe
you
don't just don't maybe feel
uncomfortable having so many questions
asked
i don't know could be anything
um
yeah no hate
no it's totally fine
i'll just i'll ask again
girls are busy though they do be busy
especially right now with um
the third fest coming up
yeah i probably shouldn't do a whole
talk until after
afterwards
[Music]
i'm busy too
oh my god so exciting it's in less than
two weeks yeah are you guys excited are
you guys gonna watch it
are you guys gonna watch it
on it
second day
takanashikiwawa performance
i'll make it worth your time
sounds weird but yes
yes yes yes
i will watch it definitely
i'll try to watch it i took days off for
it wow you don't need to do that there's
even an archive
on
[Music]
some japanese bros saying they're gonna
be there in person
[Music]
yeah i'm still planning to watch day one
with you guys yes
[Music]
oh
i'm excited
i wish i wish i could be in the audience
you know like um in the real audience
watch it from the
um audience seat
i've been to that venue
many times actually for many different
events
i know
[Music]
yeah
i'm sure she's gonna watch it
i'll ask her to take videos she'll be so
proud
of me
online the meal
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
well no one gets in the wrong switch yes
yes
you could
[Music]
big chicken suits
yeah well if you see someone in a big
chicken suit it's probably us
who else would be doing that
i'm prepared to be to cry and be proud
i cried too this time
usually when i stream something like
that i
like watch lungs or so
i often
i there's some kind of wall that's
stopping me from being too emotional
sometimes
[Music]
because i'm in streamer mode
but this time might be yummy
this time might be over
hey
oh you know what some people asked
before
sorry i have barely read to protest but
some people asked before to
do like a vault watch along of the day
two later on
and i just realized maybe we should do
it as members only
have it be more intimate
yeah
that's still a vod watch along
and we can react together to my
performance
yeah
okay continuing thank you doug joseph
mwah
and jacob for the seven hours oh wait
don't choose if that's a that's a
rainbow i just see thank you for the
pinky and the whole rainbow thank you
you have eyes like crystal starlight oh
that's a really fancy way to put it well
rip not members don't worry um the first
day i will be i will be
i will be doing a public watch along
and general gave me the awesome floor
attention oh
i can't take credit when you're
fantastic and i do appreciate all your
hard work you didn't get ah
it wasn't even yours
but yeah damn crystal starlight that's
the fancy way to put it thank you
i guess thank you general
thank you
beautiful rainbow
daryl duncan
[Music]
will that be some kind of infinity
gauntlet thing
uh and i know that's a marvel reference
but i don't quite get it um
it's like i i i can't comment on it
um i'm not sure how to tsukumi
on that one
yes
no no because you still need the
interview where i interview myself
potential
[Music]
looking for the top dankest in
you haven't been around for a while
sorry not for not showing up for a while
i locked myself in the oven when i was
testing a new recipe
you always have the cutest stories man
it took me quite some time to get out
anyway
it's time for another hotel i've been
working on a milk chicken recipe oh
i just need to find some good milk
[Music]
what a coincidence
did you
did you get your milk
mission accomplished
i wonder
i wonder what happened what is the end
of the story
what a clinky thing
no all that noida had was a big big
glass of beer
that's all she had
so you probably went out empty-handed
thank you for coming back though nice to
see you hope you're doing well
done
thank you so much hope to see you more
often i guess you're busy though big jug
of beer yeah
ah
thank you for the pinky i got fried and
i feel terrible please can you use your
magic to turn me back into an egg i miss
the days you were sitting on me i have
always been loyal and i always worked
really hard for you why are you doing
this to me please let me live
no no no no no
no no that is the wrong attitude my
friend wrong attitude
i know it's great to be an egg but you
need to
appreciate and and honor and respect
the flow of life of a kfp employee
jumping into the fryer look at felix
doll enjoying it jumping into the fryer
is like you should be honored to do that
you must be grateful
you'll eventually get revived anyway one
time only so
[Music]
embrace it yeah
yeah
i don't know what your problem is
and
[Music]
that reminds me before before the during
the pre-chat uh right before the stream
we were talking and preparing another
sample i noticed um
once again i had to explain the the
salute thing i have to explain that
every time
but she noticed that someone did um
posted a double closed ocean mark
instead of noida's oshima because
they're a little bit similar
she was like oh that's cute they made a
mistake they didn't find the right one
but it's the spirit that counts the
thought that comes
[Music]
thank you thai team
at least you chose the right one
oh come karen thank you
[Music]
angle
um
thank you for the support mwah
i suppose you're one of
the samples
people i suppose thank you
i've been getting cat asmr in my left
ear for the whole stream
oh that's so nice
you know when i'm cuddling with smoothie
smoothie especially
um
and she purrs
and i'm already cuddling with her then
she lets me put my ear
on her belly for a really long time and
like i look i look for the spot where i
hear the purring
the loudest
and then i just
i just
take it all in
because i heard that it has healing
um
healing effects
so i'm like i gotta i gotta load up
that purring healing effect
[Music]
that's asmr yes
the best one
so good
it's interesting that you know i told
this before i think
because somebody likes to criticize
trunker's
purring
but jonker's
she like
the thing is chalkers
purrs all the time sometimes when you
just when you look at her sometimes she
starts purring until you stop looking at
her and when you touch her she always
starts purring always the moment you
touch her and the moment you stop
touching her she will stop purring
um so it's like like a button that you
have to activate
uh and then and then and then smoothie
she doesn't always start purring when
you touch her but once she starts she
goes on and on and on even if you
stop touching her and stop looking at
her she goes on and on and on
and so it's like a more
um i don't know they have different
styles
[Music]
i think it's so cute like chocolate
sometimes i just look at her and she
goes like oh
it's so
cute manual and other purse
it is so adorable
[Music]
she's such a weirdo
counting chickens down
thank you
[Music]
thank you glad you enjoyed it
and there's a vault thank you
thank you i'm glad you learned some
stuff
um
[Music]
now there's only like five elementary
super chats or so so i'm not gonna put
up the thumbnail
yeah one million for dreaming to do
that's right one million
thank you guys for listening to dreaming
tutu
dreaming tutu is uh
yeah the last one
the last one of the holo myth
uh
sound cover collabs that i wanted to do
so i'm very very happy that i have
completed them all and all of them got a
lot of love from you guys
thank you very much
thank you i appreciate it
[Music]
how did the game go it was fun it was
fun but my fingers i don't know um the
game makes me grip the controller
so um intensely that
they tense up and and they hurt so um
yeah i had to stop because i was [\h__\h] at
battle at the end
but it was fun especially the dancing
kicked
off
[Music]
yeah of course maybe already uh this
week
maybe
since we're not doing a schedule this
week
um
yes
[Music]
there is a reason why i'm not doing the
schedule this week it's just because um
[Music]
i like to play it safe right now
i'm going somewhere
and
uh
i don't want you guys to know when
until afterwards
that's all there is to it
i'm not going to america so
most not going to japan
[Laughter]
no no no
no no no no no no one day one day mr
khan speaks donkey [\h__\h]
oh yeah weapon requests
[Music]
ah
handcuffs you know when we did the
omocat stream i was looking for my cars
and i was like do i not have any
handcuffs yeah
because we wanted to
arrest the cutie pies
now i'm thinking
that's that could be very useful
handcuffs could be a cute puffy pink
ones or it could be normal ones
[Music]
what else
oh morningstar i feel like i already
might have one i'm not sure
if
[Music]
i already have maybe not maybe not
okay but a cute one i want a cute
morning star
a cute one you have one i have one
what's that a flail
yeah i have a flail not a morning start
and i want a cute i want a cute um
morning star
okay
i'm i'm a fan of morning stars now
um
is pretty good i'm surprised you didn't
recommend me to the disco
i mean the karaoke was fun i just really
enjoyed the [\h__\h] disco
there's a morning star i mean i already
have a morning star
no not pink people think i like pink
that much i don't even like paint that
much
i know just i don't know maybe a morning
star with some cute pattern
and some decorations like some
stickers and and some
accessories some ribbons
it really i don't know i looked for it
the other day it's i'm not sure anymore
wait can i play
[Music]
can i play
yeah
yakuza 0 ost disco
let's go queen
oh i know this girl clean
i can play that now cause it's uh i mean
it should be fine
extended 11 minutes
now listen to the normal one
oh my god
[Music]
wait can i try to sing it
i mean if it's part of the game anyway
[Music]
where's the difference right
i've listened to it a million times now
[Music]
one second
one more time
[Music]
moving on
i don't
[Music]
oh yeah
is
[Music]
oh
it's too short
[Music]
moving on
my
[Music]
okay
tonight
[Music]
need to stop singing
we'll listen to this in the background
[Music]
i will not be able to
read super chats
we really should play one that i don't
know that well yet
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
one of my favorite games of all time the
story is kino the gameplay is so fun i
just love everything about it i've been
waiting for this uh day since you beat
the episode seven
oh yeah i never recognized when you guys
say seven i always think of it as like a
dragon
night enough
i hope you have a great time on this
channel and congrats on beating margaret
earlier
yeah i'm really curious which one i will
end up liking more
after finishing both of them like a
dragon or this one zero so far i like it
i like it
but i think like a dragon had more
impact on me in the beginning
but we'll see we'll see
it could still change over time
gameplay-wise
i like both they both have their good
sides like
the the one from this one is actually
kind of easier in some way it's
surprising but
the turn-based actually is kind of
difficult because you're so
limited in what you can do and like so
pressured to do the right thing
[Music]
i like both i like um a lot of different
fight um systems
as an rpg fan jrpg fan especially
i i like um a lot of them
[Music]
it's friday
[\h__\h] it's monday i'm sorry it's monday
night not friday night
i know it's confusing i know
only gets easy as you progress oh really
okay
here's this is much more personal
seven hours during one of my favorite
games and one of my favorite burbs lame
well you gotta catch up with the vault
then
[Music]
streams they were tons of fun and i was
on the edge of my seat many times don't
we
your yakuza streams are also fun and
i've been waiting for more so i'm
excited for this to thank you thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed the ellen ring
streams even though they're
so suffering
[Music]
did it actually work
because
i still saw people
using it in the chat
oh but i guess
banning roll doesn't ban
rolling and that's what i've been saying
maybe
[Music]
oh okay
well before i forget it i guess i should
do it now
one second
[Music]
youtube studio
okay should uh work again have fun
rolling everybody
and jim tracy thank you thank you for
reminding me too hi
[Music]
um
thank you for
a double rainbow oh my god thank you
thank you for stack and you barely wrote
anything into it
never sent the rainbow before so here it
is wow
really you had so much space to type
like a [\h__\h] book or something
thank you though thank you appreciate it
very beautiful looking rainbow there
thank you for the support
thank you gordon thank you an audiobook
oh
[Music]
he wrote the lyrics in the super chat
thank you
i feel
i feel beloved
kiwawa your beloved
thank you soon
don't have to feel like a bakka though
it's okay
[Music]
[Applause]
it's gonna be your birthday when
i was looking forward to the stream
unfortunately i started a new job
yesterday i'll catch the vlog for sure
back to peeling celery and reasonable
hours of the day
i mean you're working in the kitchen
happy birthday i suppose like tomorrow
or so
happy birthday
early
[Music]
oh i hope you get i hope you feel better
soon please
i hope it's not too strong
but now you have lots of time to watch
my my my streams
thank you thank you
you did well in elden ring
tai chi
you're usually
someone who really doesn't talk
but you're saying that you
you taking the courage to write one two
three four five six words in a super
chat to tell me i did well in elden ring
[Music]
it's an honor
it's an honor thank you
i know i know
some people may say um usaji but you
know what
i will say for once
for a beginner i did do well and i don't
care what you think
i think last episode was um skill wise
better than the first one
[Music]
and i did watch inna's stream a little
bit afterwards and she was um
on her first episode of elden ring i
think and she was doing the same boss
and
and i mean generally she's probably
better at the game than me but
um she took a couple more tries than i
did for for
for the lion so
so now i don't feel like so terrible
anymore
[Music]
[Laughter]
truly the gamer shut up
shut up don't say that you're just
making fun of me
[Music]
hand built the bus on level at first
yeah the market in the first
series in the first episode yeah yeah
that was definitely unleveled
i mean someone of experience could
probably still kill him easily
but yeah
i've accepted
the reality that i'm
good
i'm just kidding
i did fine
[Applause]
[Music]
um
hey boss i was looking for your amazing
last night good night covered and i
realized it's unarchived and members
content on top of it
i i did
uh karaoke for members once no wonder i
couldn't find it i have the vault i want
to ask you for permission to upload the
karaoke as long as it's unarchived
and lots of time passed
in this case six months you have passed
and it doesn't exist on your channel
anymore is it okay to upload memphis
songs in this case no
no
no no no no doesn't matter how old they
are their members content no no
what i could do though maybe
i was gonna say i could rebroadcast it
but since then the rules kind of changed
so
um
[Music]
and i probably can't rebroadcast it just
like the
the way it is the way it was
because now i can't use the same
instrumentals anymore for some songs
um
maybe i'll just i'll if i have
permission to sing that song now as well
i'll look into it and maybe i'll sing it
again
eventually
[Music]
well yeah members content please don't
upload it
it's members content
it stays it stays within members
[Applause]
yeah it stays within monday
yeah i mean you know
i mean one thing honestly um
um that i've i've been like thinking
about
that's kind of weird
uh with our memberships is like
um let's say i have let's say i have
um
10 member videos
uh
10 months ago
but 10 months later i have
100 members only
videos and then someone who has been a
member all
throughout the whole time gets to see
all of them sure but pays more than
someone who
joins just now and still gets access to
all of them
i was felt like that was kind of wrong
and sometimes i wonder if maybe
i should change it up but
like by taking down everything after
like one month but that's
also kind of sad because then you can't
go back to it anymore
um
i feel like that system
is
kind of weird um
yeah
you guys you guys are fine with it i
understand that
but i just think it's the logic behind
it is stupid
uh
but yeah with unarchived at least at
least for that one it's special for the
people who were members back then
you know what i mean at least something
that um you guys can be like yo i was a
member back then i saw it so it's worth
it's worth it it was worth it being a
member at the time
[Music]
makes it special
thank you though thank you
um
i'm glad you liked it so much
oh man my throat hurts
i've been drinking liters of water
oh man
it felt so fine yesterday but yeah today
was
uh
a lot
thank you kakun
thank you soon for asking [\h__\h] thank
you for the resume
[Music]
wow thank you for coming by hope you
enjoyed it today yeah long stream
long stream but
uh yakuza is so much fun i hope for you
guys too i hope it's fun to watch
there's so many funny characters
yeah sorry i'm losing my energy
thank you for watching trenton
williamson i'm new to these these
questions may will cause you to faint it
or something else what so the question
is that you and kelly are a couple if so
what will you why did i choose to read
the super chat
what will your future kids look like and
what power do they contain with these
why did i read this
sometimes i choose to read super chats
that are not red and not pinkies you
know when i got the time when they catch
my eye
it was a mistake it wasn't
it looks fine the first two sentences
look fine
we're not a couple sorry trenton
williams
the game mccree thank you
and daisy duncan we have a child in sims
4 though
oh man
[Music]
yeah clara takamori would be the name if
anything i guess
seafoam boy thank you i'm really excited
to see you play my favorite game changer
i'm most excited for i'm a vr tutu
despite knowing a lot about it
hi
i'm hinting at something
well then i'll hint too
i i've heard i've heard that seafoam boy
has provided something for that stream
uh without us even asking for it thank
you
i know it just kind of happened emma was
like yep
yo
uh
seafoam boy
provided something
i didn't even see it yet
i did not even see it yet i saw the
models in action in vr chat just wanna
help thank you
thank you so sweet
i guess it will be kind of a surprise
until tomorrow
for me
that's so sweet
i'm motivated
yeah
things like these are easier to do with
such sweet help because like especially
these vr things there's like so many
things to think about so many steps like
making a model designing it first and
getting it modeled by someone then
someone needs to rig it and someone
needs to implement it so that you can
use it in vr and then maybe backgrounds
and all that kind of [\h__\h]
yeah maximize work and i don't i don't
even know
like how most of these things work
thankfully i'm organized um someone to
make the models work for vr chat i
didn't know who even i should be asking
for that
i don't know oh [\h__\h]
sorry i'm really exhausted now
[Music]
wow
based on it yeah like she's juggling so
many things always
so sweet
thank
you boy
thank you i'm looking forward to doing
more stuff together
[Music]
i guess we can use what you made for us
um for that boot camp idea as well
probably
[Applause]
don't juggle burgers they'll fall apart
and it will be all over the floor for
[\h__\h] sake
how many times i have to tell you that
chickens just because there's no
customers in the restaurant right now
doesn't mean that you're allowed to
juggle [\h__\h] burgers
oh my god
you're wasting ingredients
juggle eggs instead yeah but boiled ones
maybe
there were hot foods [\h__\h]
it shouldn't be hard going into the
first place that's gonna be toxic for
the customers what if you accidentally
give a customer a hot glue burger
instead of a normal one then you're
gonna we're gonna have a lawsuit on our
throats and who's gonna be handling that
me
unbelievable think about it guys thank
chicken spin
i have to carry the responsibility
if we kill some humans because of toxic
hot glue burgers
it's my responsibility then i i i if i
get in trouble because of that then
you're gonna go and try get in trouble
too
you're gonna lose some wings and some
feet and all that you know
think fake chickens pink
thanks
understand me
you understand me
they're on fire
perfect perfect they're using the emoji
that's what i like to see okay friday
night let's go to the different one how
about
uh
wait which ones
what were the other ones called
my fukur
[Music]
what about this queen of the passion
oh yeah
[Applause]
i [\h__\h] love the soundtrack
[Music]
kiera takanashi matriarch of the canopy
family captain of the george clown
phoenix of phoenixten and supreme leader
i'm sexy
know that i know it
of the great yakuza who cut up your ears
up
who wants a word with two adventures
uh
i'm hiding them i clip them down
underneath my hair
because for the thumbnail they would
poke
[Music]
the the legends eyes
i didn't want to poke their eyes in them
yeah it wouldn't fit and to be honest i
can't put on the cat ears with this
outfit don't make me say it
thank you pinky
soon
trevor g donkey and the game
[Music]
oh that was so short more
more
i lose it there we go
[Music]
i have to go to bed now good night
always i knew it
[Music]
funny
funny lyrics man
kind of um
jinglish japanese english
[Music]
oh yeah hot girls and boys video chad
welcome back
[Laughter]
[Music]
sarcastic light 476 function
oh yeah the sponsor stream does bring
back memories man my pc was so bad
doug joseph thank you naivety thank you
knife sanchez joseph thank you typhon
danishan lazurio
just finished the game last night what
what a great timing
did you like speed up because i said i
was gonna play it soon
if not then that was a good timing
and you're gonna be very helpful in the
chat i hope
g-set gck e donkeys
yeah they put a lot of detail into it
and i appreciate it although the signs
are really funny because a lot of them
are like funny
funny names for erotic
um
cafes or clubs
[Music]
is red in
chinese instead
[Music]
that's red like the red super chat uh oh
thank you for that mwah
where this one is so short man what the
[\h__\h] it's so good but are there not
longer versions of these songs
they need longer versions man
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's a wrong wrong show wrong show
just
not
hey
[Music]
i can't sing this one yet
uh
plain water
i'm drinking you right now
you're good
you're refreshing
thank you plain water
[Music]
i need you to survive
plain water
counting chicken dancing optimus prime
down kissing
yeah
oh i don't know about that if it's a
simpler time to be in life but
it was probably a cool time indeed
thank you
i'm happy you're playing at this game
now you will know the origins of the
legend of the legend
of legend of legend of legend origins of
course being plural in this context
yes
um
i already bought by the way uh because
when i was buying this game it was on
sale fifty percent guys in the
playstation store it's really cheap
right now
uh yakuza zero and i saw that uh kiwami
kiwami was also on um
sale so i bought that one too
that one was actually 58
sale
[Music]
good time to buy it
i
[Music]
yeah i think ninety is playing keep on
me or was playing kill me
i'm gonna play it eventually not
immediately after zero but i already
bought it so that eventually i can buy
it and i can play
it also always have great deals yeah
they do
[Music]
someone who played key mommy too oh
yeah she's still doing it right yes
thank you
breaking the law
breaking the world don't break the world
break the law okay don't break the world
though
i need it
breaking the lulls
lilz indeed
[Music]
getting to know the legend because like
in
like a dragon he showed up and i felt
nothing so
i know you guys were like oh my god it's
him it's him and i'm like oh cool yeah
yeah he has uh he has a cool aura
mmm cool cool guy he is handsome
yeah not as cool as ichibanda
trending williams dancing
i didn't loop it
look
um
[Music]
we've dodging better
what does that mean
dog jaws have dog joe's dog joseph take
a shirt
cyrix set danke
thank you
you picked up an awesome game just
curious do you need subtitles in the
game since you can speak japanese oh
i would probably get the gist of it but
um
if i have no subtitles
oh sometimes they
sometimes i use some difficult words but
i would still understand i think
[Music]
but they also talk very fast so i don't
know i would have to focus a lot i think
japanese having japanese subtitles
additionally would help a lot
sometimes they use weird words
it's always the thing with these games
and they're two nebula words or punkish
words in this case yakuza slang as well
yeah
something that's just not so common
to me
um
uh doctor
kt junction thank you
[Music]
when did you write that super chat i i
used heats more often later on why
didn't you write that
then i was switching styles too yo give
me a give me a chance give me some time
henry soul says two one one two english
and ellie smith function thank you thank
you i'm doing my best working hard
girlfriend donation for the red super
chat i'm so happy that i'm able to get
to watch you start a game live you're
playing big storyteller produces my
favorite of your content aside from
singing oh thank you
thanks for playing this game i will
watch as long as i can before going into
work thank you that means a lot to me
thank you please continue following the
series
yeah there may be another stream this
week
generally i will aim to play it once a
1.5 times a week
yo that's good
glad to have you around glad that it's a
game that you guys all seem to enjoy so
far
um thank you mwah
anyway
oh you guys even knew who i was talking
about
when i talked about gouda
asking me about that one idol
[Music]
how did you guys know did she mention it
[Laughter]
[Music]
actually i
i've known um i've been kind of
following uh um's activities like really
roughly
um ever since she was
was the call against the sisters and
sisters anime
uh i want to kiss exorcists or something
like that
she was a voice actress for one of the
main characters and they had really
really cute
songs
that opening song was so cute with the
dance it was so cute yeah
um that's really old
it seems like some of you guys know
yeah um
a bit questionable but anyway um
that's that's how i think i think that
was the first time i got to know about
her
um but back then i think she was more
focused on
voice acting nowadays she's really like
a huge solo
idol
who originated from
voice acting
i barely remember the anime i just know
it was questionable
uh i think i might have watched the ova
maybe
it's not something i would watch
nowadays my taste really changed a lot
when it comes to anime
yeah
[Music]
i don't know
i remember when i was walking around in
akihabara like years ago
in this in the station there were these
huge pillars and they had huge screens
on the pillars and yui ugh was dancing
on those screens that was cool she was
cute she's really cute she's a great
idol
she's a great idol so yeah and she's
also um i think piccolo senpai really
likes her too she sings her songs
sometimes
i think they were really cute together
i loved i loved their voices and their
songs
that was the main reason why i liked it
[Music]
the rare piccochan
the
[Music]
i was actually kind of confused like she
wrote to me
um
that she was gonna
she wrote like
we're performing on the same stage as
her and i'm like what are you what do
you mean is she a secret guest that i
don't know about yet why is she
why is she performing on our stage why
don't why don't i know about this i was
legit confused
it took me a while to understand what
she was talking about because it came so
out of the blue
[Music]
that would be a weird choice of guess
it was a stretch yeah yeah
[Music]
is
the game mccree duncan jackson fb thank
you for the pink super chat she is the
day school queen young and sweet lives
for eternity i already said that thank
you
yes
eternal
kiwa
[Music]
thank you very much for your support
i will probably not have any pocket
tissues right when i need them
captain jerkman dagger purple poopoo pro
tip if you have the money always spend
it on your skills it's the best use for
your money okay
i mean so far i've only spent it on
items and disco
and skills
four thousand yen into this goal
not too bad right super some fun
joey duncan
it's not existing this game timeline yet
yeah i played like a dragon fully i
don't know what you're talking about yet
though little naivety dangerous
before i went into work and during break
i caught your two victories over those
bosses and eleanor and kyota damn you're
getting better thank you
let the rage fuel you spike spike to
take down future bosses and prove those
in chat wrong thank you
i heard that the next boss is gonna be
really tough too but
um i want to do more and more and more
exploring before going there i don't
want to
immediately
go there i want to stress myself about
that because there's so much else to see
anyway
i mean honestly as long as the next boss
isn't
isn't as slow
as margaret
then
because that was my biggest problem
um
the slow
delay in attacks
don't know
i don't know when to
i don't know it's having a [\h__\h] maybe
he's maybe he does the same [\h__\h]
[Music]
is way more aggressive
some people say it's easier
[Music]
elemental
i just want to say you're doing great
only took me a while to get used to it
on my first play of yakuza believe in
you and take your time thank you
i will
mark oval
thank you
maybelline 2501
thank you i do love don quixote i i i
used to go there a lot i'm sure at 87
darkest stream because they have
everything
everything motorcycle i'm down there for
the pinky i can't blame you for not
making elephant ring series after
experiencing a real masterpiece like
later alligator yo it was so cute how
the
the makers of the game the creators who
are behind it um
they were like so happy about me playing
it on twitter
and that made me happy too
like sometimes some creators they're
like really supportive and that
motivates me too
to make more content out of it and
appreciate it even more because like you
you really feel
the love and the passion that they put
into it and you know they're not they're
not as big as you know confident like
nintendo or whatever
so
um i feel like they really
deserve and need um
exposure and support like that and i
feel like we can you know support each
other
um they they give me games to um put on
my channel and i put them on my channel
and give back to them
[Music]
endless circles i mean you should voice
acted yo if they ever make another game
i need voice actors please hit us up
i'll do my best
[Music]
keep an eye out on their fan base and
even notice them are the best yeah
yes
it felt so wholesome
i'm glad they enjoyed my stream
they apparently watched the whole thing
from beginning to end it's interesting i
read a little bit up about the about
them it's apparently a married um couple
who um works together
so sweet so
they made the game together so wholesome
what a what a power couple man
[Music]
yeah
so sweet right
only those two people they all only
those two people made that game it's not
amazing
only them
[Music]
as far as i know unless i misunderstood
something but as far as i know
only them those two people was that's
all only had working on on it
to
supposedly was to to show off their
animation skills because they um
they usually do like animation work
and
yeah
the game was
for that purpose somehow partially
i love their animations like even the
tiny hand movements i was like ah
freaking out over it
even the tiniest
hand movements and feet movements oh
it killed me
[Music]
damn wow exactly
thank you
jackson fb thank you we want you to be
happy so if you're streaming your type
of games makes you happy then go for it
thank you for the thank you and your
thoughts i i agree you guys are usually
when it comes to that very supportive
and understanding
so
i feel
i feel comfortable
thank you
[Music]
what do you think about by the way um
about
horizon
i don't know if that would be a good
streaming game but
uh
it's a new ps5 game
with a female
protagonist
[Music]
yeah
zero done flipping west
i don't even know if i can play again if
i wanted to but i didn't look it up yet
but
probably not
[Music]
yeah it's a huge world right
but the thing is that uh the character
um fights with with a bow right
so that's kind of
intriguing to me
interesting to me
[Music]
i think i kind of
already knew that that it was um it
looks amazing and all that but
maybe gameplay was not the best but i
kind of want to look into it at some
point
but now i'm busy anyway with many other
games
[Music]
i want to give it a try though it looks
so pretty
oh crispy that's your naked chicken sky
thank you for the pinky you're doing
great in your first souls game when you
finally defeat margaret that that is a
thrilling moment yes
it felt good
thank you thank you for experiencing it
together with me
suffering with me
um
guys it's almost midnight and i just
reached a point where i'm supposedly
done with reading super chats um but i
have to refresh
and then there would be more
but in theory when in theory i'm at the
end of it
at least in the current timeline
yeah i think i want to go and read the
rest next time that's ok
[Music]
i know that's a joke but you mean like
those dance revolution games i've never
tried one of those before
the ones in the arcade where you jump on
the on the floor
never never did that before
[Music]
whenever i went to an arcade in japan
the only thing i did was take purikura
i always walk by you know in arcades
it's usually when you walk through the
gaming portion you eventually end up in
uh at some pretty critical booths
[Music]
the gaming things they always look fun
but i never really um take time to
use them because the reason why i'm
usually in there is because me and my
friend usually want to take purikura
whoever i'm with
usually a girl
we usually want to take purikura to
commemorate it what is it um it's like a
photo booth but like a cute one where
um the machine will kind of like cutify
you
by making your eyes much bigger and your
skin much shinier and um your legs much
longer
it's really cute and then you after you
take the photos it's perfect lightning
by the way you move over to the other
side and you start decorating and
there's a limited time and then and then
after decorating with like stickers and
shiny letters and all that
and choosing layouts there's like a lot
of fancy cute layouts really cute
graphic design and you go to the other
side of the book and then you wait a
little bit and it gets printed out while
you're typing in your email address and
it will like then send it to your email
address and you also get to get it like
on the strip like in the proper photo
poop and then you cut it then usually
after it's printed out you would both go
to the table and there's usually like
one or two tables close to the pretty
cool with a scissor but the scissor is
like um on the chain to the to the um
table and then you're like okay who do
you want to cut it or should i cut it
and then you'll usually go i'll cut it
it's okay and then you cut it really
nicely for the middle and then you say i
think this one is here then
i'll take the one that's mine and i put
it into my into my into my purse and
then we're both happy and we're like
yeah we have we're looking really cute
but only on those party credits because
they make us a million times cuter
actually you know what as a as a
foreigner it makes you look really crazy
because those particular blues are
usually like um
programmed in the way that they look
really good on on on asian features face
facial features um but as a foreigner
going in there it always makes me look
really really [\h__\h] crazy like a
[\h__\h] alien me and my foreign friends
we always laugh about how ridiculous we
look and then sometimes you can like
choose like how how much it's gonna
alienate you like there's like options
like natural and even natural it's
[\h__\h] ridiculous but it's so cute i
still like it yeah anyway i have a lot
of pretty good i have like a box of all
my pretty color that i took uh over the
course of the past
many many years and it's nice a nice
memory to look back upon and there's so
many different particular machines like
there's actually a huge [\h__\h] um
business behind that i once worked with
a particular company in japan before
though um and and and i know how the
processes of creating one and they have
so many they pulled out so many
different machines every month so if you
go
to to the arcades not so often then
and then then and then you will see
every time you go there there's new ones
oh also the interesting thing is maybe
you didn't notice but um you know the
arcade part you can go no matter what
gender you are but sometimes some places
that you're not allowed to go to the
political part if you're not a girl yeah
because i guess a lot of guys go there
to pick up girls or they used to so they
made it so that only girls are allowed
for some but then you know there are
some girls who want to take purikura
with um with their boyfriends so
there are other there there are other
places that allow boys as well and then
you go in there with your boyfriend i
guess but then the thing is like it
really it really doesn't look good with
men like it looks ridiculous
it works with girls but um
some there's some pretty questions that
are made
to be used with
your boyfriend if you have a boyfriend
um so then you can choose like on which
side the um of the camera the boy is
standing so that guy will be
photoshopped like a little bit more in
the in the
not so feminine way
but it was still creepy but it's funny
it's cute it's a cute memory
um anyway maybe i should stop
i love purikura
i love pudding i haven't used it in a
long time though actually i used to um
my problem was when i lived in japan
that um i had uh i had a different phone
call contract i had like i don't know it
was more like a pain
i don't know how to explain it but i
didn't have a proper phone contract for
a while and and and you know when you
choose the email address that they send
the particular data to um it only gives
you like certain
choices like you can only use like um
a
japanese phone contract emails that come
like with the phone contract yeah this
is kind of weird so um i could usually
not download it but i would always send
the code to like a japanese friend that
i had i would be like hey you are sorry
to know you again but i just took some
pretty crap of a friend can you download
this for me yeah and they would send it
to me
yeah it was weird you can't type in like
a gmail address or whatever it has to be
like a soft bank address for example
anyway i should stop
they would always be so happy though
they would be like yeah don't let it and
then she would send it to me and she
would be like kiana you look so cute in
this hey and i'm like i look like a
[\h__\h] alien but okay thank you isn't
he's kind of cute alien but still cute
anyway i should stop
[Laughter]
anyway i i should stop oh you can also
sometimes you can make videos soon
they're really cute
anyway i should stop
[Laughter]
oh and also those photo boobs one thing
that's special about them to learn
different from normal photo booths from
western countries is that like there is
like really really annoying and and
excited voices hyped up cute voices and
they're like ah let's take a photo let's
stand like this oh so cute next photo oh
three two one go oh wonderful you did a
great job now let's try this clothes oh
best friends forever ah now please move
on to the next pool please don't forget
anything or any of your belongings in
this pool and and carefully go to the
next pool thank you to the other side of
the poop and decorate your paragraph oh
yeah welcome to the decoration please
use these stamps yeah oh these are so
cute oh seasonal stamps yay very cute
thank you very much
[Music]
and then and then we'll be like i only
have 10 seconds remaining nine eight
seven six
five four three
two one thank you please move to the
other side of the pool
one so one
yeah yeah anyway i should stop
oh i want to take purikura with the
girls once we are all in japan together
i never took particular with cali man
yeah we never took particular together
what the [\h__\h]
and once i get them over to japan i'm
going to take purikura
[Music]
particularly
okay okay i'll go now
i'll read the rest of the silver chest
next time let's remember i stopped at
luna morte
remember don't forgo i'll see you
tomorrow for the vr collab i gotta
practice tomorrow to dance before
teaching ahmed holy [\h__\h] i don't even
know how to teach a dance please don't
expect too much of me
ah i hope she i hope she can pick it up
from me
yeah
oh it's awesome
but i'm late what's pretty cool oh come
on
and in germany we say auf wiedersehen
i'll be there
what time oh [\h__\h] i still gotta make fun
fall and [\h__\h] but i think i'll i think
i'll make the stream reservation after
getting up because
9 p.m my time i think
[Music]
thank you guys for watching
when you go to japan take some
particular but but look up first if
you're allowed to go in there as a boy
sometimes you're not and you will shock
the girls we'll shoot the girls the
school girls they'll be like yeah
i mean they won't really say anything
they won't really be like go out
leave
they will have the courage to but anyway
[Music]
do
also also did you know that usually
around the purikura place there's often
always a cra crap crap place close to it
not always though
[Music]
japanese
don't even get me started on japanese
style credit booze crabs they're amazing
don't even don't anyway i should stop
[Music]
oh maybe i should make a stream where i
try to recreate the japanese style
harajuku style crib oh
let's buy let's buy a crap plate i was
thinking about it anyway because i saw
on amazon there's like these these these
crap um heat plates thingies yeah these
round ones mmm
oh i should try
not gonna use hot glue
anyway i should stop
[Music]
oh we could use raspberries from my
balcony once they once they are growing
[Music]
anyway
you