[Music]
oh Ki out
key ah yeah that
didn't that didn't go according to plan
K
hello
hello yeah let's start off
here uh just for the very first
minutes this is
my
y
first shrine visit of the year is called
hatu m in
Japan uh but let me say something first
of
[Music]
all
why it's got to happen on the first day
of the year that's like so
sad like I woke up and first thing I see
is like
discussions on Discord uh and
Twitter about the the earthquake so I
hope everybody is safe in Japan um it
was a pretty big one
so I feel pretty bad that it's got to be
like that you know the first step into
the new
year they have earthquakes like every
day but this is a big one
so I'm I'm sorry it's got to be like
that yeah H man but let's hope that this
year will be a good one I will make a
wish I hope this year everybody will be
safe and
happy and everybody who is watching
whole life will continue to have fun
with us I hope that I will be able to
reach more of my goals
perform more on stage make more music
make more
friends and see everybody's
smile
I I hope that every everything will go
well I wish good luck and good health to
everybody who is watching
this
yes
and here we are oh and here we
are yeah happy New Year and I really
like this you know in Japanese happy New
Year but they also
say which I I like to say that in
Japanese because it just sounds better
in Japanese but it basically means M
please take care of me this year as well
or like nice or hoping to if I don't
like translated to directly maybe it's
something like looking forward
to you
know working alongside you or whatever
just be good to me this year too let's
be good to each
other something like
that
is the short way of saying it yeah
please tolerate
me I should probably say that cuz it's
uh
yeah please tolerate me this year I know
it's difficult to tolerate me um whoa
whoa whoa just move the something around
please tolerate me I'm feeling hot why
am I I thought these cozy clothes would
be coose it but they're hot now let me
open the
window what the refreshening
air I'm dressed really cozy I mean
aimono is obviously very very
warm oh tolerate while
2024 oh
oh thanks for waiting for me I I don't
think I slept much in that nap at
all at some point I woke up to myself
drooling I think I was about to fall
asleep and then my drool woke me
up
yeah
nice nice it's movie wake up last night
uh not really like she let me sleep like
she's been letting me she wakes me up
but she let she lets me sleep pretty
long like
7.5 hours she will leave me alone alone
which is pretty good pretty good pretty
good pretty decent I accept it I accept
it was I dreaming on some delicious
chickens how did they do with the guests
uh like mostly like in the beginning oh
I'll tell you all about it we have
plenty of time to talk about it
um tangent and we'll finish this game
the first stream of the year on the 1st
of January
2024 I will finish a game just like I
always do yeah I actually hello
helicopters
off I actually played a little bit more
off
screen uh after that last
time uh I
I Super
Mario uh
wow I got a couple
more uh stars as much like I got
everything I could find in that snowy
Place think I
got I don't know if you can notice
difference how many did moons oh
yeah can you notice a difference I don't
know how many I had last time but I
think I got like a couple pretty good
amount yeah and I bought some new
clothes too uh I bought the suit or oh
no I bought no not the suit I bought
something I don't
know I need Joy ah yeah joyon assets for
these hands yeah these hands are
ridiculous I really don't like how
they're just so like well I don't know
what I'm doing with them they're just so
H
awkward it's just so awkwardly
positioned and
open the claw grip
yeah yeah uh P fiction hands not quite
not
quite uh so
[Music]
this awkward so but thank and you barely
see my
kimono it's okay I like my my my apron
flaps so that that puts all the
attention on
that and we
oh I'm a
firework W yeah I I kind of knew he
could do that because I see him do it in
other games but I never realized
whoa did I had What It Takes wow I'm a
snowflake I'm a
snowflake yeah yeah I know we collected
enough P moons I got the bunny uh Moon
the other day uh on my private time I I
I was uh I went fishing I found the
fishing
spot I got a big um a big fish so I got
this over here actually yeah I got
that uh I did a couple of things
everything I could find basically
no I went back to that race to the race
where you get like sped up with the
flowers
remember I went back and I tried to get
even higher can we get much higher and
indeed I was able to easily get much
higher it was no
biggie easily
didn't even I even missed a few and
didn't matter you don't have to get all
of them
oopsy this however is a problem if you
miss
it
okay it's kind of fun kind of fun I wish
I could I maybe I can but I thought I
can't go back to the other world just
easily like this like I have to go to
like first fly off and activate that
menu and all that maybe to go to a
different world to get more moons and I
didn't want to do that off stream
because I would have to you
know Skip the scene you guys wouldn't
see it so so whatever here we
go here's my
moons is cie okay she surely is okay I'm
sure she's okay like the air out where
the earthquake is
was is pretty far from her she should be
fine very
far
yeah onto the lunch lunch oh my God
there's literally food all
over what the
shrimps there's a hot pot at the
top
Missy L on Kingdom Bowser can't run
forever what well if Bowser pass this
place then he'll probably have eaten all
the
food and nothing will be left for us
[Music]
damn lunch with
me NY
song
yeahum okay here we go
here we
go I like n's songs and her voice her
singing
voice I love
it frost frosted cake at the wedding are
they not if we serve them at the feet
first
whoa at the
feast the see is how we've got some time
to kill let's review some useful skills
no
no no we should read up on the L Kingdom
next
[Music]
saying yeah that was that was fun that
was cute I think she looked so perfect
in pora's
outfit
it says here in this country is famous
for using a volcano to prepare a dish
that is actually
amazing putting a huge ass hot
pot on top of a
volcano and then cook a you know this
could this could
solve hunger problems all over the
world this could solve everybody's
hunger problems world
hunger could be solved with
this yeah yeah Mario solved
it
oo wow I
[Music]
mean the color theme is a little bit
cancer like considering it's like food
and but it's like I don't know how to
explain so bright and like it doesn't
look taste
but uh in
um uh what's the word it doesn't yeah it
just it doesn't make me feel hungry it
doesn't make me feel like I want to take
a bite it looks not oh though okay the
corn cop thing over
there it's not our
appetizing I
wonder what the gimmick will be
here really like there there has to be
some gimmick that makes us able to go
over there there to those apples or
tomatoes oh
beans wa beans I
think wait I was so distracted because
that was incredible
I I didn't even look where I was
shooting that
yo
[Music]
yo chef hat what's with the chef
hat they have what kind Chef what the
the Goombas what I didn't
notice e no they don't it's is it
because they're on top of each
other the goet he the goet I hit at the
chef hat wow hot Tomatoes
wo can I touch
that I feel like no it goes away I guess
no okay no touching no touching holy
oh no
what oh come
on no t
w o the corn but the corn looks not
edible that's
[Music]
sad oh a the lady is
here oh
man
uh oh oh a she there we
go okay okay okay let's see I don't no
two will not be
enough okay whatever we're restarting so
uh oh I stopped moving
cool
cool oh there's a fat ass bird up
there you're not going to tell me that's
supposed to be a phoenix right
cuz that's going to be very freaking
insulting don't call yourself
that wait no it's I think it's a chicken
it has that thing below its
beak but that's a weird
chicken is that the hybrid chicken that
I've created with combining you guys
with me
is that
it might
be all right uh it's got die time just
leave me some space dude oh I'm
stupid I did it wrong I tried to throw
the Hat on
him obviously that's not going to work
but yeah this is also looking difficult
go
go oh difficult yay we're T
enough our first spon
y got
[Music]
that don't go don't run away I'm
prettier than those
goomas
[Music]
don't go back to the Goombas don't go
back to the
goomas I'll leave them there too ah f
for themselves
hell oh great
okay and let's go how do we move on here
maybe I become oh
yeah
heya
okay that's the gimmick cuz this way we
can swim in this toxic waste
awesome have to do that in the beginning
then what are you doing
[Music]
here so we do have to fight all of them
twice
huh so whole boatload of this place is
stupendous stew for the boss wedding
show but I'm going to head back up to
the volcano to finish off that stew
after I'm done with you we fight
now
emo wait I'm not warmed
up oh that oh hearts come for that might
be good because I'm actually missing a
heart oh okay let's see uh
oh oh I threw off his hat
but that doesn't help
me B I guess I can uh jump on him wait
wait he's so
fat wait no
Hearts
okay
um let me clean up a little bit no no I
can't I'm too stupid to jump at him
there we go ah I'm going to
die ah what is he
doing what is he
doing don't I have to jump on
him oh no maybe just wait again cuz his
colleague did that
too I just trying to jump on him I'm
doing it right like I know what to do
but why you got to be so
annoying oh for
sake why do I stop moving again again
why is it like why does this happen so
often great start right it's not my
fault it's not my
fault they lock me out a okay let me let
me do this first and then we'll fix
it I'm so pissed that it
only oh gives me one heart
back these
[Music]
items oh I can move him to a different
direction huh a he open the heart I got
to pick it up before it disappears
no there we
go I hate this
bastard there we go thank God that was
kind of dangerous to do it right
[Music]
there oh surely we can do it just
fine oh my
God
very unnecessarily
dangerous
okay why it's got to pee like
[Music]
this okay I fixed it the brutal are
after some
[Music]
cooking black be
oh what the what the hell are those
people
wow
okay hat back to normal oh hey we can go
up to the
roof I did not consider
that oh that's I sounded like Mario
didn't
I Yay I got to we going to collect some
of those so we can go to the
shop salt or sugar I'm guessing it's
salt ooh we got to get one of those
otherc
hotheads Moon
here did boss ever learn how to hat dive
we don't need to hat hat dive okay it's
my personal
choice so isn't there one here like how
else are we going to
no how how are we going to get those
where's the hote head it cuts off there
is it like
behind maybe we can jump from my boat my
ship
[Music]
to the
roof that roof oh there is something up
there oh oh
m
yeah okay I need I need more height but
I probably need a different kind of
jump
oh oh oh yeah right that was a
thing uh I
guess about it so probably the Hat jump
yeah but I can't do it I don't know how
to do it
you you like throw it out what the and
then leave it there and then I try to
jump on
it yeah but I'm stupid guys how is that
going to
work that's not what you meant yeah I
don't care but like this should probably
also
work in my
mind
like it disappears so I have to keep on
pressing y but then it's difficult to do
anything dive jump dive jump is not the
one that that I always do right with
the how do I dive
[Music]
jump
ah
oh
what
wait jump and throw and hold that jump
first
what
no jump dead Len
y that's so
cute is that the time Jump jump at l and
y jump at l and y jump at l and
y jump at l and
y wait what
sorry must have pressed it
wrongly you can do it
twice jump that l and y
together not enough distance I I can do
it twice
really maybe there's even a different
way to get up on the building like from
somewhere else easier but
probably probably from where I
originally came from but we're doing it
from
here jump L
what
uh no no what that L ah I pressed
B
sorry guys we're learning we're
learning this is the speedrun PA and I'm
way what is it how did
it jump to l
y no I was too high I was up too high so
I bonked my
[Music]
head
no sorry I always Press
B oh know why the buttons are so close
together
no
no no now I'm too low
again don't don't what have
got what if I you guys say you can do it
twice is that for
real no I don't think I could do it
twice at least at least not in that kind
of
speed what I had first to do it was no
no that's where the learning
stops
no no
[Music]
no that was the right combination though
oh man whatever at least I learned
something
new hold
on no
why is my jump aimim so
bad wait when when when when do I throw
the
Hat
what I don't know what the I'm
doing I got a new a third monitor let's
go wait you turned 18 or you're turning
hold the pro button you hold the hat
button to keep you keep the keep the Hat
you can jump into
it what when what I don't
understand thr cap dive into
C wait what what what what throw
cap oh
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait
wait I don't know I don't know I will
never use this whatever I don't need
it whatever
whatever
woohoo I give
[Music]
up sorry to
disappoint but we learned a new skill so
that's
something this way this way is the way
although wait how do we end up like can
we even go underneath then cuz it's like
under the
ceiling
those purple coins oh ah look at that
boy that's where he is Al what do you
have to do for
us oh oh oh wait oh it starts here oh
took me so much time to get started
at to position myself but it's okay yay
first
[Music]
try okay okay okay okay you guys are
probably really impressed I know I
know can
[Music]
I from here get no I won't be able to do
that huh are you forced to go from the
ship
actually
surprisingly maybe you are forced to go
from
there consider where the face buttons
are I imagine I have that what are you
talking about the face
butts
what are you talking
about no hot hat not jumping high enough
unless I can jump out of the hot head
when he
jumps yeah shut up I
know we're
exploring ah there's probably invisible
blocks there a
[Music]
maybe oh just exploring a little bit now
um actually what is this
corner s
sus wait for me wait for me don't it
won't go away right it won't go away oh
nice nice it doesn't go
[Music]
away yay yay yay um but anyway I want to
go to that side so let's go through
again okay so we go pick up those purple
tomatoes tomato
tomato was it an
apple probably Tomatoes cuz like there's
hot Tomatoes over there
too
Pepto bismal in the fire
why wait what is pepto bismal I hear
that
sometimes I'm so stupid I am so
stupid so invisible
okay there they are
awesome oh my god oh another one
so much effort for this I don't know why
I'm putting so much effort into
that I said I wouldn't be a
completionist for this game but look at
me
now Look at me now look at me look at me
look at me
[Music]
now
can they go like themselves I don't
know like what what do you want like
leave me alone leave me
alone toxic what you guys are doing is
toxic
no I
[Music]
was oh no why he he ran off cuz he was
still like his ass was burning
still they okay his ass is still burning
to this day
guys my
God
don't leave me alone no leave me
alone all my money no why did I pressed
the Buton I pressed the
[Music]
Buton
I don't
know wrong
[Music]
button B
bu oh my
God oh my God okay we're back in the
game now pleas give
Hearts
you what the
man what is this
place
what pleas oh it's a
fork it looks so funny it looks kind of
cute oh wait can I like is it like can I
hang on to
it ah I guess I can throw my hat on oh
that's fun another gimmick that's the
real gimmick of this map I
guess Amelia foron is this
you
i h wouldn't be surprised if am had a
fork version of
herself
I
suddenly felt like eating these potato
chips big welcome to m home to the
hugest
no big welcome uh to
no a big welcome to mount volbono home
of the hugest flavors
anywhere i' show you around but uh
things are things are kind of on a fire
right
now yeah
yeah look at him Tippy
dapping bird they call it a bird I want
wanted it to be a little bit more exact
so I know what the it
is it kind of looks like
me checkpoint okay okay I'll go
back like it's obviously a
[Music]
lady I think that's
me I said it it's okay the elephant is
out of the
room is
it not that not that thick am
I but I I like to
cook I'm kind of red I got a chef hat on
sometimes the bird up there showed up
out of no and took up our St
part just when we were making more of
our special stupendous to too everyone
was getting ready to
begin wow you called it stupid bird and
that's very insulting cuz that's me so
you expect me to help you oh small bird
oh look at those little small white
birds oh my God there're so round round
Birds round birds are a
blessing oh they have yummy stew here
too going to jump in it is it
hot hold up a warning sign you little
you find any right into my soup
gold want to oh yeah especially and
those gold Oh you mean turnips you mean
this thing wait I can't even pick it up
so I guess not because
yeah makes no
sense oh no where's the
[Music]
checkpoint beans I look at
the oh why would you go away why would
you do that
turnips I guess they're not around here
huh they they must be further away I
have the perfect amount of
um of go uh purple coins oh he what
so wait and how do I get up are you just
like doing this on purpose like I got
rid of the boxes that could bring me up
in order to get the
Moon is that was
[Music]
happening are they doing this on purpose
wait this is a turn
this is a
turn I
think a w oh yeah right that was a
thing I
forgot
a what did you
say am I sling up no way this sounds
like something you would say
guys am iing up no way no no no no no
I'm just standing here because I'm lost
and I'm too ashamed to admit
it but I can't get down you need help
huh you need
help climing the US to be a piece of
cake but the B up to to both has
crumbled into the
pieces there is no way up there now
unless you can Sprout the wings or hit
the ride with a flappy to first I was
trying to go for French but now I'm more
Italian oh well whatever they're both
good Cooks
so I like this one too that's cute too
cuz it has a beret but we have to buy
this
[Music]
now
yay St that yeah I'm fine wearing this
cuz this one's an ual chef hat guys and
it suits the the rest of the outfit okay
it matches so that's
fun yes
chef you better not say yes chef to me
from
now is that okay you got it yes yes
Che yes
chef
a
m yo even though my nap was not very
effect like
efficient I think to solved my problem
of being too tired before the stream I
was like my eyes are falling down even
though I had just like woken up had
breakfast I should have been
awake I was so
tired and then I was like okay I'm going
to take a nap now I have one hour to
fall asleep
like 50
minutes fall asleep and get some minutes
of nap
in and smoovie joined me immediately to
cuddle with me perfect so I was like
squeezing her fluff while trying to fall
asleep but it took me a while she fell
asleep faster than me for sure I noticed
because I was holding her
paw trying to sleep and then she falls
asleep and her paw starts twitching and
her nails her claws come out and dig
into my hand I'm like oh ah she's
sleeping this Chef is also
tired worth
[Music]
it a clown
outfit yo because I had some so so much
money I ended up buying the stupid
outfit too and the pirate outfit as
well I bought it
all are you sling off yes I
[Music]
am bye this swim chunky has nipples M
that is an important detail indeed oh
will you let me in cuz I'm wearing my
outfit
yes y let's go let's go worth
it
m na wors than a Soo simmer you need it
hotter do I have to jump in with these
hot hats by in
chance I'm just guessing
it
uhhuh
what that's already worth the first moon
I didn't do anything I thought I thought
maybe I need
more
like
okay what that's so easy that's so
weird okay what happens here I just got
to
survive what
now what now what now
no is
there you have the Moon is
hard yeah uh I can tell because I don't
know what to do
next
uh he follows
me well I mean I mean I'm I
mean I mean I'm I mean I
mean that's not
fair how do you even see
me I could get up
but
damn I have to no maybe if I'm fast
enough he won't notice that I'm
there and will let me pass
no
what the heat catapulted
me but now he's there again he wasn't
there in the
[Music]
beginning maybe if I do it a little bit
diagonal
oh I jumped on of
you uh they certainly didn't expect me
to do that because how am I supposed
to
what I think yeah I need the hot
[Music]
head but they they only survive in the
in the water so to
say
are they they survive in the
tomatoes so maybe I have to Splash them
first but they don't stay there forever
do they
[Music]
oh
true
[Music]
but can I
also make the process shorter by not
getting out of my hot head but like
trying to jump on top of the tomatoes
with the hot head before they even
dead oh yes I
can yes I can
so they even go to where I
am but this is this is kind of far dude
can you come over
here
hi oh okay they're they're pretty
generous on where I land okay that's it
that was
it y
it
no trying to do the other
jum comfortable very
comfortable well I'll take this
challenge I'll take
it
a stalker
Tomatoes no no my
God
no
oh this is very difficult
I mean you guys said so that it would be
so it's probably not just for me the
[Music]
difficulty what do you mean you didn't
know you could land there you you could
fail there you just landed on them what
a what a flex what a stupid
Flex I just need better aim like now
then we're
good okay that should be
[Music]
enough quick quick
quick no
oh thought I could make it
okay they're still
there bloop bloop bloop a bloop bloop a
bloop bloop and a bloop bloop yeah
[Music]
okay
can someone heal me
please do I get healed by
checkpoints I don't want to die again
and lose my coins heal
please a it doesn't heal
me I need
healing I need
healing oh
you know what we're buying the
heart go go to the used spon a the US
spon
[Music]
oh it's okay I want
this it's okay because I know it will be
cheaper to just
die but it's good to have this
heart because it will help me in my
future endeavors for a while let me
in I have to ask you again to let me in
why why do you not just keep the lock
open okay here we go
again the tomatoes actually stayed for
quite some time
so I think we don't have to worry too
[Music]
much
wo
okay oh
no
ah ah ah ah perception
whatever hopefully that'll be uh not too
far oh
God no Mario just hold on to
it get some tomato juice there and some
tomato juice there that was unnecessary
you oh and now I'm ready I'm ready to
take on the challenge again
Flawless
jumps from
takana she's doing it again and proving
everyone y buddy she is a gamer there is
no doubt at
[Music]
all
huh what the
hell that's so
stupid Oh my
God
don't get hurt don't get hurt oh it's
piping hot no tou
it okay I have control complete control
over the
situation okay that should be
enough that should be good enough my my
last
try at this
challenge oh yeah wait I forgot about
that part uh it's okay we can jump into
them
yeah now we just need this one's
attention thank
you get the coins
back and now don't jump too
far
[Music]
Hallelujah
wait wait wait wait what what what do
you mean what do you mean what do you
mean what do you mean what do you mean
what what
what what I didn't exit it exited me cuz
apparently I landed on the side of the
podt are you kidding
me I
[Music]
know no
ah I don't
[Music]
understand I jumped as far as I
could
[Music]
let her cook no nobody deserves to cook
here
[Music]
anymore can I get uh the fake Moon uh
not the fake moon but the that one Moon
again to
heal at least up to three
hearts yeah okay that's at least
something we'll just we'll just do it
without shooting them first because they
come over closer to me anyway I hope hi
hello hello hello they
don't please there we
go them noticing me is so
Random hi I'm here you're looking in my
direction okay oh he's coming
over that's good that's great
okay
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah now we're
[Music]
cooking okay careful if this fails
again I will quiet I will
[Music]
cry
finally
why you
suck this food that you're cooking sucks
you should leave it to
me to your
Chef I've got the biggest chef hat on
means I'm the best cook here okay just
trust
me what does his parrot say what does a
parrot say I saw I saw his video today
and I was chilling in bed still where
some guy likees video video cam security
camera video footage guy is working on
his car in front of his house then
there's like screams did you see
screams
oh oh coins there's like screams coming
from his garage they're like let me out
let me out
help and then somebody the neighbor
calls the police cuz the screams go on
endlessly and he just he's just doing
his repairs on the car and then yeah
then the police comes and they're like
yo we got to call that there's some
Screaming going on from your house and
then he laughs and he goes in and he
says let me bring you let me show you
who's screaming and he brings out his
parrot apparently the parent picked it
up
when he had a child or so
yeah that was pretty
funny
uhhuh what does that even
mean I think for once this is it's
giving me information that I didn't Happ
yet but what does that even mean oh look
at
that
[Music]
oh wait oh I have to jump on
it there's the
[Music]
turnips there are the
turnips a golden
turnip woo got to bring that one to Tom
Nook well not Tom Nook but I I forgot
what the name is of the Villager who
takes the turnips or I just needed the
the uh the golden
one you don't need the last turn
up so no
really Joan
Joan that's her
name ah the others are just
coins
yo we're here
again in the hot Waters Nathan cotton
thank you
D thank you for the red super chat thank
you soon I appreciate
it Happy New Year I hope we'll get along
this year too I guess you could
translate Kyo like that too I hope we
get along this year
too
I'm a
island I'm a island pretty
nice difficult to access
though happy new
year did you
guys get across the year skip
well you all signed up I can tell
because you're here now in 2024 nobody
got stuck in 2023
right
hopefully I sure did yeah of course
wonderful I see something there is it
coins or is it a
moon it's a
moon yay let's pickle oh we should go up
there there's a secret
door I'm stuck in 2013
help that sounds like a you problem
oh
sh I think I'm stuck in 2020 because K
is playing a Mario game
willingly that could be indeed true now
that you say
[Music]
it
the angle is very important
here you got to be very
excited
oh this way this way this way what no no
no no no no no no no no what what what
how do you get to the
side how do you get to the
[Music]
side I don't understand maybe I flick
too
[Music]
hard ah from my hat oh
yeah
okay
no no no wait no I was I was
not I was just like setting my angle in
the right position I didn't flick I
didn't
flick okay that's kind of difficult
because like genuinely I wasn't trying
to flick I was just moving the joystick
around a little bit to get the right
angle but they take it as a
flick oh wait wait that that's how you
do it
guys oh wait but I can I still go
[Music]
there
yes oh cuz I guess you just uh yeah
okay you fall down here anyway when you
do that
okay I thought you had to throw your hat
like
in a different way when when I heard
your guys'
[Music]
explanation where do I want to go first
I
guess that way that that probably won't
work I should flick to another
[Music]
Fork do wait I don't ah I have to flick
to the top not to the
left
right wait and then where do a okay I go
back okay
[Music]
then very
interesting very
interesting
oh how does this work how does this work
how does this work how does this work
no no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no
I get normal coins right when I do that
when I got old purple
coins I don't
[Music]
understand
ah did he not
land cuz I through the
Hat it didn't bring it back to the fork
though okay let's
see this okay that works and
then maybe cuz it moves maybe I should
throw the hat or jump out of it when
it's in the
middle could it take some time but I
don't
[Music]
know
oh there we go there we go there we go
there we go
o i i really find the whole gimic
interesting though the combination of
these
two
things
oh
sorry I'll be eating a lot of potato
chips cuz I'm
unstoppable when I eat potato
chips thank you red
diamond is the first proper Mario game
that I
I feel like it's up my
alley I wish I could I mean maybe after
this I'll have an easier time at other
other Mario games too maybe this is my
way of eating myself
in
maybe where are
we oh the music
changed what the hell how would that
happen
dangerous jump guys can she do
it yeah nailed
itow pretty sure this is a dead end wait
the way you say that surely there's a
secret path or so or do you really mean
it this time can I go up the wall
no okay maybe it really is a dead
end no
secret
blocks for later oh okay so he did mean
it this time it wasn't like a a hint a
wink wink
hint at least they were coins
yeah okay then let's go
back and go up to that moon or so
maybe maybe maybe let's talk about
something how about the countdown live
that was why did I do that why did I do
that
I'm sorry got confused wrong
button it was crazy it was insane there
was so much stuff going
on uh I'm like I felt after watching all
of that I felt like a little bit
mentally
exhausted like the I think especially
the combination of the shuffle medle
with the
hologra it just
made me feel
exhausted it might I mean it was great
but it was so like wo whoo one what the
to another what the to another
to another to another just like what is
going on I can't keep up cuz I only
personally knew about the laplus one
happening all the other ones no idea
cuz I was asked for
permission for laas doing
it and I was like yeah yeah I didn't
even know that they would actually copy
the music video and even give her the
two different options of the white pink
and the black outfit version of the do
you do you outfit is my default it but
you know I didn't know they would go
that far they even copied the angles
from the music video have you
noticed they even copied the
angles
wow they really try to make
it as close as
possible do I need these
gobas as close as possible to the
MB how do I get up
maybe later I'll find
out yeah now maybe you guys understand
why she was practicing so hard these
days what the how does this work
again oh how do I fight these enemies
are they just here to trigger me
yumy oh I killed
it
now you know yeah she did a good job
with the
English pretty good there's definitely
improvement from the first time she
tried to sing
it h very cute it was I I have to say
though I'm so sorry like I I I don't I
think my outfit it's really difficult to
pull it off uh it's not very flattering
on her body
type is
it oh wait I think I have to
to will they shoot themselves here I
don't know what to
do she looks great in it she's so small
and like so
thin but I thought okay I thought she
really had no
BBA but I'm confused because in my
outfit it looks a little bit like she
does I'm so confused does she have bbba
cuz from some angles my outfit gives her
a little bit of curve on her
BBA I thought she was like gooda levels
of
flat is this optical illusion maybe from
the shading that is like implemented in
my outfit I don't
know yeah she patted
it
but yeah um um okay one second tell me
how to deal with this I don't know what
I'm supposed to
do I don't know what what you do
here then we can continue
talking the Hat what I threw the hat at
them course I
did now
I'm
wow okay can I destroy that case as
well
no frying pantel don't anger me in the
kitchen where there's frying pans close
to me you don't want to get into trouble
like this like these cheese
blocks that will not be
fun
wo wow
wow oh is there something
underneath oh what is that oh a
lever all right
no he died in the
end
[Music]
oh now we get the moon okay I see
wonderful all according to
kak Y murder with a
hat you have to get this
more
oh we're getting
closer M oh the ingredients in that stew
they don't
move they're set in
place hold why are you here why is this
one in this
hole a so I can get to this
side wait a second
okay so yeah there were so many like
surprises Kur and oku switching there
were like a lot of couples switching you
know OK switching was really cute they
sang each other's songs that was really
cute but then I don't understand at the
end they they both changed into
different outfits that I've never seen
before did I miss something
what what what was that
from was that from some like huh like
fan art
or ah the music video outfits okay they
did seem a little bit familiar but I was
like from where do I know them okay okay
okay yeah haven't watched the mvs in a
while
no
no okay now mostly I just listen Riv
than watch okay cute so they got like
two outfit changes they
actually they modeled those outfits just
for this purpose
then holy
moly they put a lot of oh that a big
jumps oh ah
ah they put a lot of effort into that
huh they just made it for
that and then I mean what the
what I don't I mean what was that with
M en's outfit
yeah that is uh difficult on on
bigger chested
women very
interesting oh
nice
oh oh that's how I go up but I kind of
want to First go into the door can I
probably
[Music]
can and she was like acting so horny
with the tentacle it was so it was so
typical Maran Senpai of course she had
to use the tentacles to kind of
like pleasure herself I don't know
[Music]
that was really quite
something oh what the hell is that oh
I'm
mistake what the no I'm not ready
for the fight
no
ready no why no don't take the steak all
for yourself what about the world
hunger no share it you're share you're
going to share it right that's the plan
right you're not eating it all
alone you've eaten
enough oh my
God and so why wobbly he are some
serious wobbly Waters in
here wait the moons are right there do I
not have to fight the
bird the
coin the corn had it out for
me oh my God not the wobbly water
no they have to do that again okay I'll
do it another time I want to go check
out some other stuff and come back cuz I
have the checkpoint no
problem but there were so many things
that were shocking but like oh I can't
even what else what else was
interesting what who else got uh oh yeah
Kobo dressed up as
Bales and sang her
song she looked cute in the
really
cute but then Kuba also she didn't only
change into ba off she also got like a
little hair change Midway
through with her Fringe
back yeah and yeah can ah can s was also
a shocker man Senai was a shocker K
Senai was a
shocker
oh my
god
do it was it was really funny cuz that
that BBA pad fell out of her that
silicone bbba pad y oh come
on stons are really looking
bad her mother her artist mom going
angry cuz she always like
really feels protective about the small
chest that she gave
Kai didn't happen didn't happen did not
happen did not happen you were just
uh
you can fall off the cliff I mean I
guess makes
sense a little bit
slippery
stay finally
okay uh
why what's what's up there that I want
to like leave my hot head
great off to a great
start I don't know if that's enough
tomato juice over
there maybe
this
y oh is that okay that's the moon the
the first moon I
suppose and then I should be able to get
another one at least I got
healed
woohoo okay why were we not able to get
back huh at least I saved myself holy
I was about to stumble into it
again uh okay
wait no
I no stop
running okay I kind
of don't like this gimmick
anymore it's just too
wobbly too dangerous all the
time h H oh well anyway what
else n was cute pora was cute uh who
else uh
Iris Iris did lisu looking really cute
and lisu got soda Senpai and soda Senpai
was dressed as Iris which I think she
looked so beautiful in those like darker
burgundy whatever colors violets and
burgundies and reds and darker colors
like wow wow and the the the style of
the
outfit she looked so beautiful in it I
really really really liked it oh my God
I'm not going to make that jump
ever yeah that was that was
amazing I love s saai an iris outfit
that was one of the the most amazing
things I've
seen the most fitting one of the most
fitting
outfits okay here we go
bye-bye
H oh yeah g was um
performing or something like that from C
Senai no not Senai from Chloe
and therefore wore her
outfit which I think was pretty cute on
her definitely not unfl definitely
not
unflattering really
cute yeah I wish I could have done
something too actually so they did like
uh what's it called a survey way before
like if you were to participate who
would you like
to um change with and it's not like I'm
I'm not saying that the ones that did
end up get in there uh getting in there
necessarily requested that maybe maybe
some of those are like Management's
choice but surely a lot of them were
requested
too and I I think I told you I I
requested something too I requested to
be to switch with n and
do or any other her songs and as my
second choice I thre out the idea of me
changing into peas clove cloes but
probably I mean cuz she got like a
change last year with MAA s MAA yeah I
guess she's the S play but with MAA I
guess that probably like they wouldn't
want to like repeat that
and yeah so w didn't make the cut but
maybe next
year
maybe I swear to God I swear to God I
just have to go in with
confidence Maybe
oh yeah I started with FUBU and holy
moly that was incredible
too starting with Fuki Senai changing
into M Senai who obviously they look
great in each other's outfits it just
works because it's kind of the same
style of outfit but
like just darker and
brighter maybe I need like some
speed
I
cannot understand why this is so mean to
me wait it's too cold let me close the
[Music]
window there we
go
okay timing what
timing yeah du obviously it's
timing
obviously
duh oh my God guys
du what
did you see how they scanned MOS what do
you mean MOS what
what
[Music]
what fre
ah what
what
I made
it finally it was about
time I need more coins back for all
these
fails never again am I entering this
premise
okay what else was here I need the I
need the guy I need the
dude one of the dudes is there one that
oh oh hey
hey come back
here
hey what am I
doing
huh no hey
no I don't know I don't know thank you
for the memberships thank
you yeah besides that uh I was you know
the whole thing was obviously
pre-recorded as was said before and uh I
was so I was able to watch it while
having
breakfast really nice really chill just
watching it and it was so good it was so
good one of some of my favorites were I
think the one with crony and
fauna m M what else my memory is like
really
shitty oh turn
up wait wait let me try to remember
things I don't remember anything I don't
remember anything at
all what what what yeah the Cobble
one I really like her cover of that so
some some girls I've
noticed were
doing like performances of songs they
already covered before wait do I get
another Moon if I bring that to the Hot
Pot are you kidding me that's so far
away do I have to bring that to the hot
poot oh my God yeah kobble do they name
kind of the poem one was also really
cool they were kind of dorky sometimes I
love
it they they're just like kind of dorky
in general
haha yo
you do I get it back is it there
again what the hell man what the hell
don't you dare respawn right now
y yeah sure whatever just die just
die you slay during Tokyo Shan and thank
you I I I I think um you know it's a
kind of difficult song but uh was a lot
of fun and the combination of people I
was
blessed to be
included and I have a good
[Music]
time like I want to sing it in full in a
sometime I learned it just for this and
maybe it actually worked pretty well for
my
voice the fast P was cool the fast pad
was so
difficult
uh-oh oh God F part was so difficult
legit
oh
oh I did have a lot of problems with
that where where are we going next what
the hell
uh where are we
going that's not worth one Moon that's
worth five moons if you're telling
[Music]
me what where the maybe I
should what do I leave it on the ground
one and like make the way free here can
I pass for
the the the the uh the
CH to the right where the switch
was they're so
mean stay
there I'll do the
[Music]
thing
okay should we have do we have to go up
here with
the
no with the Tulip tulip
tulip w we always getting the hip
shaking songs well I mean yeah there was
some hip shaking but generally the Coro
was rather simple in my
opinion but yeah it was
[Music]
cute it's gone
guys I have to do that beforehand ah no
I'm not no that Moon I'm done I'm
done with that
moon
no my turnip oh it's not a tulip it's a
turnip yeah my turnip is gone oh that's
ridiculous
yeah we don't need it what do we want to
do next
then get
healed U what are you here for surely
there's a reason can we jump across
[Music]
here
I didn't think
so yeah only only was doing a watch
along and apparently realized that I am
her
o oh she's so cute she's so sweet I
wrote her a message upon watching that
she's like wait I think I think you has
my
Oshi hey wait no I'm stupid I'm stupid
I'm
sorry I was trying to remember how to
dash cuz there was a dash uh button oh
my God that was
crazy no no I hate myself I hate myself
I
hate ah today is not my
day
not can we go to where the hot head is
uh I don't know where that
was whatever I'll do this first I don't
care
anymore that's so sweet because like
remember I used to like kind of say well
Ollie ol's really sweet and supportive
but she's supportive of everyone so it's
not like when she says like I love you
so much that she only says it to you no
she to everyone which is sweet you know
no problem no
problem oh did I already collect all of
them but now it seems like she has a
specific liking for
me I am honored and
and
happy happy to hear that
she's so
sweet you know if someone like oi
someone like Ollie says I her oi then
you know you know we're going strong
because having ollie on my side is like
powerful yeah I know I want to do the
music note but I'm guessing I need to be
Speedy for it and now again I didn't get
to see the controls for being
Speedy h l l and the okay there we go
[Music]
oh it yeah yeah I had to I had
to it's okay it's okay I'm getting
healed here we go let's
mle I had to there was only one left and
I I took
I took the
moment you got to live in the moment
guys make decisions in Split
seconds only someone with me with this
this bravery like I have is able to do
that ooh look at these bell peppers I
love bell
peppers hey what what theck was
that are we closing this so that they
roll in different
places cuz they make them bump off
otherwise
oril oh my
God
hey that seems like possibly what we're
doing I'm almost thinking well then what
is that here
for there's a picture here wait I can
jump into this one can I not
wait that looks like from Super Mario
64 what's
up what a beautiful place you're not
going to let me go
there but I want to go there are you
telling me I have to play Super Mario 64
in order to get there
you
can Yoshi's
house what's which one's the house
there's a star up there what the
no no no no no
no I actually offc screen I I I was able
to enter one picture um and saw another
one of these like islands where I
couldn't go anywhere from
it h sorry I'm not at home but I have
gone to Peach's castle
Yoshi y
okay can I take that star
then surely I can get to it somehow with
a specific style of jumping
right I need to die
[Music]
oh wait let me try this
again my training from
earlier
um okay I couldn't ledge onto this tree
but that doesn't seem to be my fault
is this I gotta go
wait this way this
way this
[Music]
way oh my God wait Secret
oh my
God what lies what do you mean secret
path
what I thought if I go in there like
this I would get to the castle
no they lied to
me look at the oh my God I need to go
there I need to go there tell me how to
go there
there where is
it oh the painting Oh I thought the
painting was the way back
H Oreo cap Into the
Fire play close game
level
unbelievable a unbelievable
bait where do this go
oh oh oh oh oh w w hey not the Hammer
Bros I hate
[Music]
them oh
no
a yumy
ooh
lava
yikes o big yikes big
[Music]
yikes turn the
camera we're on the ceiling we're
Australian now and there's a moon that
will heal
me
Yay good one
yeah this
now good now can we enter where the the
belt peppers are coming from
surely
oh
no okay we
[Music]
can God damn it what do you have to say
anyway I'm here fix all spots that crack
open but just my Lu I can't walk in
there without getting knocked on my
melon wish someone could get a job so
you do want me to get rid of those bumps
no didn't I already do that or did I
miss
one yeah I'll do it for you
again oh that's it
okay lovely lady bumps in the back and
in the
front my H got you she's got me spending
oo spending all your money on me and
spending time on me pleas got me
spending oh spending all your money on
me on me hey what where are
you there you
are I'm going get you drunk Get You Love
Drunk oh my homs my HS my homs my h
I already did that before leave it alone
leave it alone
Wawa I know it's
tempting shall we go up to the pot maybe
I feel like I'm
ready I'm ready for it or
it's not
here wait didn't we have a checkpoint
there there ha there huh a meat PL meat
PL oh yeah it's up there
okay thanks Brendan you only need one
Moon so might as well oh
yeah let's see what happens twitch
twitch twitch who would leave a steak
out like that in the open covered in a
ton of salt or whatever that is
be careful of your
[Music]
Stakes take care of them oh it's being
cured well why was it damag in the first
place
hm
[Music]
okay that side was really difficult but
I'm going to try it
again got to have finger spits in the F
ooh and that I
have
yah what I don't have to fight for it
against the bird
really
[Music]
really what we fight afterwards or what
what are you doing
what you couldn't have eaten those moons
anyway they're not
food oh she's making oh
no the volcano is erupting and I got
shot up in the air
okay she did not allow this other
stranger cook aka me to enter her
kitchen but Lady this is not a
kitchen he BL it all the way back here
that is one angry volcano or Angry Bird
huh and the volcano is still
erting
so what you're trying to say
oh the C wasn't always there
huh oh the cheese also was no there was
it you guys weren't always
here oh no we that the kind of heat
theend to will be ruined we got to stop
the crazy boys but no way can anyone get
up there our do do
two of
Doom nah don't worry guys at least you
got rid of the Goombas here thank you oh
and hey wait you're you're right in the
right place I actually need you to do
some stuff for
me it's difficult to control
them wait oh this one has Fireballs God
damn it I don't need you
then I need your other buddy oh you can
jump in the air
she I don't know if you're of any help
right now one of these turquoise
blocks oh I have to turn the fire
on ah and it gives me a
moon
black
[Music]
okay okay shut up I I hate hearing that
constantly now we need one of
these oh really I think the distance is
not the is it really the
issue oh come
on
oh my
God I I got a Windows notification about
my about my space on my
disc and it's telling me to ride
away oh we have minus 930 GB why can't
you just like use use the other
one what do you mean I have minus oh no
what no no no no no the minus I don't
know what the minus means but it's it
says zero
bytes
available uh wait temporary
temporary data is 212
GB can I delete something here
now temporary is oh is it always safe to
get rid of like it says there's some
stuff oh I have 5.4
13 in my in my trash can 5.13 GB in the
trash can 6.16 GB in the Windows update
cleaning
thingy there's 205 GB in my downloads
but wait does that not doesn't that
delete like everything that's in my
downloads I don't want it to delete when
I my downloads I have a lot of cool
stuff in my
downloads that's not wait is it
Temple yeah don't delete it
right
okay uh
so the rest is
like direct X Shader
cash
Windows
Fedor for Windows upgrade
that sounds like stuff I can get rid of
but it's really small things anyway the
biggest ones are the trash can cuz I
haven't emptied it for a
while
okay
so I I selected 13
GB okay I'm getting rid of it
now 13 GB the track
the downloads I don't know I I have to
look into it yeah I probably could
delete a lot of those things
manually how's your temp folder eh I
don't
know my my temp folder only has no
resign
it
get
it it's taking a while to do it like
it's not
moving it kind of looks like it's
stuck you need her for the moldes yeah
let's keep the temp piles for
now
soon Ollie will have it to you mean
temper she will be a
temp no I think I can really relate with
Ollie
like I wasn't her back to the AI theme
but I wasn't her oi from the beginning
right she just kind of like after being
in the company and seeing people work
behind the scenes and all of that and
getting to know a lot more
people that maybe you don't didn't know
so well
before it it really like shows you how
amazing everyone is that maybe you
didn't have your eyes on
before and I had the same thing oh wait
it's it's close to ending now had the
same thing for example of
Amit like damn yeah like I I feel like
if I if I was still a fan of whole life
uh instead of becoming one of the first
members of the whole life English
generation feel like I would have oi
am but in any
case yeah no like so
many so many eye
opening things once you join whole
life that make you
appreciate things you haven't seen
before okay it's done do you think
that's enough uh free space for
[Music]
now
window
amazing oh wow okay we jump into that I
suppose and then we get
shot do I have a choice where no just
into the next one or oh over here
aha fun okay we have like shortcuts now
and this one do we want to see or is
there something new to check out here
you see these big new chunks huh can I
touch them oh yeah I can break them
they're they're coins now oh look over
here lot of
chunks of stone over here
why if I destroy them do I get
something
no why are there so
many check the that end again that was
that I was thinking of
too yeah okay wait let me get those
again please install another this no I
have another one that's like pretty
empty but like everything is like by
default still using the one that's
pretty full I don't know how to change I
I'll look into
it I'm looking into it
okay
[Music]
you guys are so
judgmental you guys are so judgmental
man pile organization skill exactly not
anyone can do
it
oh oh interesting
should I still try the cannon ones let
me see where it brings
me oh oh oh it brings me here anyway so
I don't have to take the the really
narrow shortcut oh yeah I got those
before I do not recall
that Windows 11 lets you Auto delete the
can't about I keep on uh
rejecting Windows 11 I just had it offer
to me again like yesterday so annoying
leave me
alone why you why you keep on trying to
force me to update if I had a choice I
would still be with Windows
XP okay here uh um the flag is
ghetto flying ghetto
[Music]
oh can I do something special with the
fire here now that I brought him all the
way over go away go away what if I make
this hot even hotter at this ht's even
harder would you like that oh sorry not
you it doesn't do
anything can I do some shenanigans
[Music]
please they missed out if there's
nothing here that I can do with him they
certainly missed
out nice stuffies oh
oo
yo
nice oh wait what's this
what's this did I go through here
before oh thank you for the red super
chat
tasim play some slots slots the toast
Arina game that's winning worldwide Fame
there is 10 coins to play what do you
say a pal can one okay let's
play Yo Casino time baby oh we can also
get like heart containers
the moon comes after The Heart The
Normal Heart The Normal Heart comes
after the
coin so
coin coin heart Moon Coin Heart Moon
coin coin heart Moon Coin Heart Moon oh
wait what how do I ah with my hat oh
okay I wonder how much delay there is
with my hat Coin Heart Coin Heart do I
shoot it when I see the heart all
right it gets faster
oh Coin Heart Coin Heart Moon coin hard
moon what nice number
one coin hard Moon Corin heart
Moon okay it doesn't really feel faster
Corin heart Moon Corin
[Music]
heart wait I could have done it from the
side
get
I I know you could do two at once or
even more coight Moon Coin Heart Moon
Coin Heart Moon Coin Heart Moon
[Applause]
easy L
easy GG easy you want to know how to say
it in Japanese L
show r a k s s h o u rxo
RX
no can I get the hearts
[Music]
too n never mind it's
okay I'm a winner
winner
awesome it was my pleasure now let's get
back to the originally intended
path
maybe which oh there's a tube here okay
ah okay that's how we get to the other
side oh no not the Hammer Bros oh I made
it
through and I killed him I killed him
well in here the tomatoes look like
blueberries
yum
wow
why she
so also gambling house in the desert oh
did I miss it I guess
so what how come I can't reach it do I
have to go with the with the hammer
bro I guess so whatever I don't
care Happy New Year yay yay
yay thanks for the
[Music]
pinky what are we looking at what's that
for what am I doing that for no idea but
okay that looks fun it's manageable you
could qu it
oh oh oh
goodby
oh oh this is confusing to see where the
the purple coins
are there we go I got them is there any
more or can we go up I think we can go
up oh come on it's spaed on
[Applause]
me
cheap very freaking cheap I
agree oh oh by the way guys the Advent
outfits they're supposed to be tonight
right but they're delaying
it so it seems like narissa will have to
maybe do it at my place but no wor
even if it's in the middle of the
night even
then I will I will let her do her thing
I'm going to make it happen for
her because Nissa is going to be here on
the weekend I just kept the weekend days
kind of like a
mystery because you know well
reasons but we'll be
streaming
oh have to jump into it with one with
one of these we'll be streaming on one
of the days for sure oh there we
go you'll just have to get uh notified
kind of last minute guys you will get
notified last minute probably or more or
less last minute
well mystery
spoiled now one of the days one of the
days is
uh uh no stream and one of the days is
most likely Nissa
collab of collab yay y That's how I feel
when I think about that
Yoo have yeah that's already in the
schedule did you see did you not see the
new schedule there's a few mistakes
there like me keeping GMT plus 2 for
some reason oh
ooh
interesting shoot it here please thank
you
works and one over here please oh hi I'm
here I'm
here nice should that should work yeah I
want to talk a little bit about the
schedule as well but uh uh I want to put
it up on the screen while we talk about
it so I don't know no okay let me try to
remember today we're playing Odyssey
we're hopefully finishing it I mean I've
been failing a lot oh nice so I don't
know if I really still have the
potential what do you think
guys I I can finish it today right I
don't mind staying up
longer you know I don't mind streaming
after midnight it's okay ah
no it's cuz he runs so
uncontrollably when he's got fire on his
butt stupid
idiot
oh my hat oh I F I F it at my uh at hat
eight at my stone I can't
talk
at your hat might have just go to the
next Kingdom though oh I guess we could
no well I don't want to like speed
through the game I don't want to be
completionist but I also don't want to
speed through it so it's
okay oh
nice speci
chest
yay oh that's a lot of
money
St
Rising tomorrow we have a members only
year review um I kind of also wanted to
do a public one but I had to squeeze in
a member stream when I thought okay well
I really like talking with you guys
intimately in member streams because I
feel more comfortable and safe for
real
so it's going to be mem stream I want to
collect I already wrote down some notes
I'm going collect some screenshots
perhaps um and we'll go through the
whole
year
y learing the story gos for each world
is good time to leave no no no just a
little bit more just a little bit more
I um no
no stop calm down calm down you
idiot oh my
god oh
man yeah there's a lot of new stuff that
we opened up so we have to look at it a
little bit
oh what what what what is going on what
is going
[Music]
on what was I saying oh yeah so members
only year review tomorrow late in the
evening
and on Wednesday day is the waya
collab waya and me we're going
to hang
woo we're going to hang during the
day
and stream probably an uncraft
K during the
evening
h so get excited for
that I'm certainly excited
well where are we
going why you got to be like that
oh oh did I need its flame I don't think
so oh
oh this looks a little bit difficult
here and then we have a collab of
someone new on
Thursday you
guys cool you guys remember that browser
ruber GX
AA had my eyes on her for a while and
she's been very sweet she's in the chat
sometimes so the time has come finally I
finally found some time for a
collab I kept her waiting we kind of
were saying let's collab let's collab
for a while now and I I never could
really find the
time and now before my break
[Music]
finally
yeah oh where does that leave
[Music]
coins so uh she's going to teach me
proper uh British oh why did I do that I
hate myself I hate myself but I made
it can I get a heal somewhere
[Music]
man
yeah she was making some offers of like
collab ideas and I thought they were all
really good
[Music]
but I wanted something that is like
maybe more specific to her uh so I said
how about you teach me how to be more
British and yeah that's what we're going
to do cuz she's so
briish maybe I'll get closer to becoming
more like my beloved Lily
Allen I hate these enemies so
[Music]
much I already have such a great brid
Jackson I know I know I know I do I know
I don't totally don't need
it just doing it to make I don't
know make make myself more
confident in my
britishness oh I want the coins don't
we
wait oh oh oh wait I can touch the side
of that huh but not the top of
it okay and then I have to like do wall
jump
intricate wa but I want the
coins can't do this to
me too scared to touch those the edge of
it
there we go oh wait oh I didn't realize
that was
Untouchable to I didn't realize the
coins were on Untouchable surface
H coin
more coin more
s oh that's a problem I need a hot head
I
think what can I do it without now I can
probably stand here and get one
I got one mid
[Music]
flight let's
go do I need those
platforms
well I want no I don't need them
whatever I don't need them M doesn't
need them already has everything she
needs from the
shop okay wo we're
ascending top of the peak climb okay so
there was like a path here
too oh the Hot
Heads so if we
shoot ourselves do I get into that
floating island there was something oh
no we get maybe to the pot
again let's
see yeah oh yummy the bird is still here
we're going to fight the bird
now do I look safy I know I
do I've got all the spices with me you
have no idea wait how do we fight it do
I what do I bunk it from below from it
butt
how do they fight
it w w wo wo oh
wait can I ride that up to its
mouth I'm scared to
try yes okay didn't want to take damage
ouch and now
and now oh
tremendous thank you what a
compliment okay before she does that I
doubt I can really damage her but I can
try
uh I'm so slow oh well she's doing it
now all
right now it's swap W oh it's
wobbly it's wobbly no I fell off
no whatever we take
it
d w w wo strong W going
strong
jeez this is like an extra optional bus
right you don't need this at
[Music]
all just for completionist like
me so many hearts to get though it what
okay now
it's very different patterns each time
interesting wow Bo boing oh and
that a cool fight almost all the bosses
are technically optimal I guess
so um oh yeah I didn't finish talking
about the schedule though there another
triple oh I was hoping for another
triple cuz it was really difficult to
get here we have a myth collab uh on one
of those days uh what which one was it I
don't know Friday Saturday
um
which the plan is to have all of us if
if it's not all of us then we're still
going to do it it's going to be fun
anyway I think no matter how many we are
we're probably going to play lethal
company that was at least the idea from
the other
girls and I mean I don't mind it playing
it one more time but then then that's it
for
me no more lethal company after that
probably no no more desire for
it yeah let's move on off away from this
world there we go that was a lot more
moons than we
needed we got quite a few of
them oh wait is there only one more
World
left by the looks of what we have left
to fix it looks like
it now we can head to B Kingdom oh wait
is oh that can't be good W that looks
interesting the clouds are looking very
very
toxic different
colors got to be
careful you ready for something insane
well even more insane than the hogra and
the shuffle
medley
yesterday no
way prob this kingdom is cool this level
is so cool this level goes hard okay wow
wow W you're in for treat all right so
it doesn't seem like you guys are saying
insane because of difficulty necessarily
but since he took time the time to steal
theion Ste I imagine that's what he
serving at the reception seeing as how
we've got some time to kill let's review
some
no triple jump huh now back to our
investigation next up we have the Bowser
in Bowser's kingdom is that Bowser I've
got a bad feeling about this of course
it is who else would it
be are was thinking
why
HD o a silver suit was he always wearing
that
[Music]
why is it such a so to say realistic
looking Dragon straight out of Game of
Thrones let's see you survive this
plumber
boy oh my oh
my no I worked so hard on my
ship you can't break it again why is he
got this Dragon That's So
[Music]
Random crazy RTX on Dragon it is the
year of the dragon
indeed o ruined Kingdom crumbled
then wow Crum crumbled in
okay would you know it is broken again
for sake to fix it we must
collect more power moons the
surprise is there one here
no this looks like a different
game I feel like I'm playing elen ring
right
now are we playing elen
Ring cool
though Dark Souls or whatever
yeah oh
H oh yeah I can hold on that to that oh
money hey
yo and
moon
y oh that was pretty easy to
[Music]
get
STS
okay so that's a schedule
um to be honest I think it might be the
last to only schedule this mon but I I
don't want the the art to be only used
once so I might forcefully make a mold's
schedule even
though it might just
say like gorilla Gilla gorilla gorilla
gorilla on each
day with no time oh oh just because
I want to use the art otherwise it's not
going to be used more than once for the
whole month cuz after that I'm on the
break so I'm just going to write uh uh
maybe stream maybe stream maybe stream
maybe stream every day of the
week we might stream every day maybe a
little bit here and there yeah oh what
are we doing oh it's so cute wait that
you're so cute um what am I doing how do
I fight a now I can get up now you're
not electric and I pull out the swords I
guess one
more I feel like that was what I
was supposed to do right at the end you
you ground pound H to I need some HP oh
I think I know where to get him if I
don't
die oh oh it's only
one
oh
oh oh I don't have to rip out the uh
swords
again oh yeah but suddenly he's got
everything stuck in his
face again as if that never
happened I did never I feel about the
diary idea oh she liked it yeah I told
her about it I told her about the diary
idea so I think we're going to O do that
indeed I kept the other thing a secret
though I asked her about her favorite
colors and all
that oh oh I still made it it it still
counted okay I didn't get
damage
no way is not going with us she's just
visiting me
[Music]
here oh man no no oh my God that's so
much he left for a minute yeah suddenly
I'm in a different game
right
y they with every round they add more
swords and the time gets even even even
even more uh
tighter
so if you're not this fast you might not
make it in one go but I made it
yooo first
try
yeah yeah High Five Guys
[Music]
woo I got a the multimon battle of the
Lord of
[Music]
lightning nice job thank you truly
gamer you're flattering
me we got all the oh that's all we
needed huh what that's all I can do
here what does Toad Say
having trouble finding power mons I can
help you out for 50 coins and then say
scar J because there's no more than
those couple that you just
got there's more talk to the talk to the
dragon o okay let's go back
then oh he's still
there oh well oh I feel bad
what's is he
stuck is he watching me oh
yeah
um he was probably really looking
forward to this year being in action cuz
it's like the year of the dragon and I
if I don't free him he's going to be
stuck for the whole year and not going
to be able to do anything make the most
out of this year or so
so
tired he's
tired
oh
well do I have to get over here to hat
him or is it just
impossible here's my hat take
it okay wait what's this rocket
for rocket
launch
what wait
what we went to a different
world what why can't I
[Music]
what aha
wait what does that do oh I can stop it
ah why is it so red though can I really
jump on
it okay we'll do it here cuz I think
that helps
me get up to the platform on the stone
platform yeah okay I can touch it that's
probably the
[Music]
intention can I run over that I think I
think I can right oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah imagine cuz I don't know Mario
games so well me trying to jump from one
by one by one by one and you guys would
have been
like why are you doing it like this you
guys would have suffered I
know I can
imagine oh I didn't even look I just
bumped against it on by
[Music]
accident no that's not going to work
wrong hat
FR you like it when I become you guys
huh and then
yeah
oh oh
oh there we go
perfect let's go into the
tube T said it's my turn to be
no
you don't get don't get cocky
now
which
side is left the like the secret so to
say wait how wait I can't I can't go
there can
I two
sides I need a CA
shell
nice
ah wait come back
no I was going to jump on it
ah oh oh it kills the new ones too so
let's just enjoy
[Music]
it oh now the shell is chilling up there
okay okay oh it comes back to
life I feel like I could probably Bonk
the shell over to the left
side do I just touch it
okay W it's doing it it's doing its job
is there anything left over there or
probably just more
coins oh but there's also a path
there I got to check it out and which
side doing go keep going left go left
for Moon okay
[Music]
okay
scuffed you guys impressed huh
H okay so probably it's got to be on the
lower
side and then this one
also but is that not too far away from
the
Moon oh well we'll
[Music]
see I mean the coins show up so that's
the sign of it being correct right oh
yeah it's not too far I can reach it I
thought I would be too
small
he oh no
okay then we go back to the other side
and maybe we'll get another
moon but all of this is optional can you
believe it
well okay let's bring the red one to the
middle I think I feel like why can I not
make that jump there's three
platforms
but does it really matter maybe the
coins only show up if I make it on the
most lowest one though
so yeah let's do
that nice
timing this is why I'm good with slot
machines huh I have it in my blood not
always though I failed a lot at these
kind of things
too wait now I'm
thinking is there a path to the left if
I make the staircase
differently no I'm not a gambler I don't
think my mom is a gamble
either you can try no he's just can't
yeah I but I Came From The Bottom did I
not and I'm saying I could go up there
maybe I don't know maybe
not
[Music]
okay
easy oh yeah okay it does connect to
that
but they could have put some coins there
as a reward for me
checking not just walking
by in case you missed the
[Music]
moon here is the second moon let's
pickle
[Music]
W and we launch ourselves back or
what well we're back what do we do about
the
dragon I'm going to try to climb him see
what I can find if that's
possible like over
here where where oh my ah ah no
hey oh thre the hat at
[Music]
him wait till I
can't I can't check him
out I
all at least some coins
back does he say anything
else so tired
no he's just so
tired understandable me too
most of the
time I guess I can let him rest and then
surely he'll have
it he'll have enough power on his
own to set himself
free good luck
buddy I don't know if I'm missing
something really obvious there but I
don't see a way to interact with
them
but we got more moons than
necessary there's much anyways
okay oh when I ground pound all the
cracks you think does that really do
something I want I want to go to massage
and have someone ground pound my
cracks
please and been I've been holding back
on going to massage so I can spend all
my money on massaging the males to the
sound of the
ocean
yeah I mean my cracks like my
neck oh come
[Music]
on you know what I
mean
no architect statu B his castle wa he's
got his own castle man we're going to
help out those to you didn't see the
movie or
what we didn't see the
movie Mama
Mia
oo
oh it's so
Asian
[Music]
wow this is the
shown I'm sure I love that potato chips
that's what it
is
[Music]
what how greasy is that controller
yes the new gibl movie is coming out in
the AUST Cinemas the fourth is the
official start but early Prem is already
what I think that's the one that I
missed that I didn't
watch I don't know what's coming out
here thanks for the info now there's two
movies that I have to watch in the
cinema you mean the one that they barely
promoted even like in
Japan look at them with their
[Music]
hats oh I I have to collect them again
maybe where is the lady though
oh
oh more
[Music]
stream more stream ah okay it says 10 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 n okay it's the exact
amount of
goombas
No
Woman No Woman for the Goombas this time
they stacked themselves for nothing only
for
my
pleasure take it
nothing
damn all of this
work carrying each other's on the
shoulders of each
other really
really hard work and nothing nothing no
one to impress ah what am I doing can I
become the bird oo
cute ah I become bird Pokey bird oh
cute and bird finally I can get rid of
these enemies easily if I'm looking at
the right direction that
is wow oh I got stuck I got stuck oh I
can flick I can
flick oh
cute what that is so adorable and cute I
can be my own flicky
wiy
oh snap slap slippity
La best Capt in game it's pretty
adorable oh the Moon
[Music]
oh I'm going to get the
moon uhoh
oh no
no let's backck go behind the big wall
all right awesome now we just got to get
back
up oh it's pretty easy to control and
like oh what oh
wait I forced him to fall down oh wait
what am I
doing I was just talking about how it's
so easy to control and now look at me
now looks funny what kind of bird is
this supposed to be
woodpecker do woodpeckers have this kind
of color IRL too like the bluish B
oo I bird sounds sounds
right wait where are we going I came
from there right ah this
[Music]
way bye-bye
birie thank you for letting me control
you I really appreciate it you were a
great help
ah go away I want the coins no leave me
alone
oh okay no problem I
mean
oh yeah I got it
[Music]
anyway
lucky very
clutch very clutch indeed between
spinies spinies is that what these
enemies are
called whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
what the are
you whoa whoa whoa whoa how do
I oh oh can you
like what what am I what am I doing with
you are you going to throw that
somewhere an oriental WP yeah w
w maybe I stay oh yeah
and then run away that was the plan
oh okay let's do it
[Music]
again
fck okay let's do it
again oh I'm so
slow no one more more
time
Mario oh
W oh and that gets me the moon okay
wow we're dealing with
some real heroic fights here Mario's
becoming quite the adventurer he could
take Link's job any day Now link be
careful link he might be better at all
of this than you are
link Mario becomes the new Link Link
gets fired Mario does everything in
Nintendo
imagine CU you're saving costs because
link is demanding too much money now for
each
game well Mario is kind of
like cheap
[Music]
Mario he's Super Mario after all link is
just
Link Link doesn't have this kind of
title tells you something I think tells
you all you need to
know
o dangerous
[Music]
jump I just realized those coins
are are those like like
traditional old
[Music]
coins
should I go down
here there's only some coins there but
maybe there's more if I do
something yeah are you saying yes go
down or are you saying yes to the
[Music]
coins burp down here
okay oh
Coan
[Music]
and B again yay
oh do I have to do something with this
wait there's a hole
here no why is there a hole
there hey
yo oh poking your nose in the plaster
wall okay um I
[Music]
mean oh oh dear oh dear
oh do I just trustfall myself there
and then quickly try to poke myself back
in the
[Music]
wall an attempt was
made I don't know if I'll attempt it
again but damn we got reset so
far you go
away
oh what we have to fight him again no
way oh yeah okay we're
[Music]
good wait so far Wait no that's a new
area oh oh okay I was just walking
around I guess okay
unnecessarily
hey yo what's going on
here die oh a moon
piece can I poke those bombs like ooh
maybe
yeah uh kind of
wrong wait wait wait wait I got to stand
straight n too early
nice hot but it's just normal heart heel
[Music]
okay
what how do I
do maybe I try to jump somehow but he
doesn't
flap no
I can't do
it oh I'm bird oh
yeah
okay
wow the one jump that I'm confident
about is the one that leads me to
Victory oh I was thinking maybe there's
secret blocks there
[Music]
unbird yourself I am a bird I can't just
simply unbird
myself you say it as if it was such an
easy thing to
do all
[Music]
right
oh
[Music]
bo
bo oh y boy y
boy what he did it for me friend or fo
maybe
friend
[Applause]
mon is there only one here then I'm done
looking for it
no oh there
oh that
is
important another
Moon same as
before
poking the turret
wall so it was worth checking everything
out
properly
oopsie
[Music]
nice
oh the last
one well I want to check out the ceiling
a little bit too maybe there's something
to find
there I just read the Super Chat fully C
what the
CER after the all I did some
introspection and I concluded that my
love for you and am May no longer be
equal so you are now my com oh oh oh
that's kind of sad because I am Ami Oshi
so hearing you say that I feel bad um
but thank
you I'm grateful but also feel
bad oh oh
man oh they they're doing this here
again but I'm not going to risk it I
don't think I I don't think I want to
risk it although
no
is it because I'm playing Mario games
again is that what did the
trick risk for the biscuit maybe like
not from there maybe there's a better ah
second time maybe there's a better side
to start off like isn't it here
uh yeah maybe
like Yeah from
here
sideway
no don't land no don't land there okay
I'll give it a try this is ridiculous
though this is
[Music]
ridiculous okay
chill y
[Music]
oh I did it I did
it oh I was gaming sweaty palms no oily
Palms potato chips Palms wo wooo did you
see me running on those edges yo good
bird what a good bird what an amazing
bird such a
bird I liking Tony
Hawk skating with Tony Hawk Pro
Skater no I was channeling my inner Tony
Hawk oh yeah oh
yeah looking that's
scary oh big brutal
B oh wor what what wait
what oh
[Music]
wait those statues look really cool and
one of them had like the a Shaw like P
on there
Senpai wait there's some Moon there see
that
there thato seems relatively easy to get
although you can't stick
your beak into these metal walls I guess
so I don't know have to go from
somewhere else I don't know whatever
just
jump jump can I do a wall jump in this
angle I don't think I not not
me
[Music]
ah stand on the
fence is that really the intended way of
doing
it I feel like it isn't I feel like it
wouldn't be
seems too
like flimsy fincky
who hey
yo I thought I was
falling
y while we here let's get those coins
too honestly if Peach marri's Bowser
then she could live
here and this place is pretty epic to
live
in maybe she should marry Bowser I I
take over her old castle with um
Pauline she should just go with Bowser I
[Music]
mean oh oh little shop oh did I get a
samurai uniform or
so why is
there why is there real people here
again
why there we
go yeah perfect outfit I was hoping for
that why not get ping ANP
because what's the word I am
monogamous weep Mario no no no no no no
not weep
he's the real
deal
W he's cosplaying just oh oopsie
oh if I get that you guys are going to
say I'm
lame so I will not I guess even though
it would make the fight really easy I
suppose are we going straight to this
big battle or wouldn't the stream be too
short 3 hours there's no way
there's no way I'm ending it here
right
cute can I get some coins out of them
no it's not the final battle yeah that's
what I
thought okay wait where did I come
from came from here right oh
yeah my
oo oh yeah well first I'm fighting the
brutal again I guess or the ones that
are left over aren't there like still
two cuz everybody has to be battled
twice it seems and I already killed two
of them twice but the other two no I
think like this
yo so cool I don't know much about this
kind of stuff but looks really
cool
oh heart ah are we fighting here then
let me keep the
heart seems like
it D and
fuin that's what they're
called yep the wedding's almost here the
boss is getting ready in the keep up
ahead but you two can scram cuz you're
definitely not
[Music]
invited second time h
she couldn't get enough of
me
uhoh how do I fight her do I become the
bomb I yeah don't I shoot back the bombs
right oh God big
one yeah uh that's out what I did it
right
somehow wait
oh my oh my oh my what are we doing
about this do I shoot
them oh I
could
uh-oh okay I can't get rid of the hot
stuff oh it
disappears I'm sorry I'm
sorry okay let's give it a try oh no not
the big ones again those I'm not
confident
about but
apparently oh
what last time I kind of jumped on her
braids but maybe that was just uh me
being really close to the
bombs okay okay I I'll try I'll
try oh okay it doesn't shoot it back to
her I Ed the
Hat ah okay the Hat onto the bombs
okay mhm short time memory is really
bad
no I barely touched
it no no no
no
that was
unfortunate go away I'm trying to get my
coins you're not going to get my
money not giving you a
[Music]
sent oh that's a problem
yeah yeah second run is always extreme
ex L smooth
[Music]
sailing she's insane she's
[Laughter]
[Music]
insane okay big
ones crazy rabid ladies yeah always
those crazy
[Music]
bunnies the year of the rabbit is
over time to settle down
[Music]
lady okay let's not risk
it
big
[Music]
ones
shoot and please jump properly
[Music]
yeah ooh
I want
to I want to cook a crab on this hot
plate it's like the
perfect stage for
it shut
up
I'm not
interested how do we fight this guy
again
familiar
oh get rid of all the hats and then do I
jump on the hats oh no I jump on him
what what that's
it yeah okay he has like more phases
right do I shoot the Hat o o wait wait
wait oh wait I should I I started with
only two hearts oh no
oh no okay so we just
oh
oh okay I see I see do we just try to
evade him as long as we
can but he gets oh he gets more Hearts
I walked into
him yeah whatever we started with two
little hearts
anyway
you're still coin greedy Perhaps
Perhaps ah well in this
economy I cannot afford to not be coin
[Music]
[Applause]
greedy
[Music]
I'm stupid I'm actually stupid no get
out of there
stop too many hats it's all the hats de
I abandoned for in my life they're all
coming back to me this be for the people
they ah their AES get back to them or
like back at them but for me it's my
hats that I've
abandoned they left behind they said
they're not cute enough for me to wear
anymore or I've outgrown them or
whatever
[Music]
oopsie oop baby a
triple
oh
[Music]
can I jump on them to get rid of
them not that I have the skill that is
required for that
[Music]
anyway ooh nice I still got one more
in oh oh oh oh oh oh wait for
me wait he's so
stupid I'm also stupid
get out of
here even more
hats that's too many hats
dude are you doing a 100 day hat
challenge one hat per day huh you're
coping my
[Music]
challenge get the
hat oh my
God
hat holy that was intense just
because of the hat spam oh my my
god oh I got healed anyway
no
insane that was
insane the Hat battle was more difficult
even though it was quite obvious like
the system was
[Music]
obvious
M what you're eating potato chips but
just salted simple
salted
[Music]
they're so
juicy
oo oh that flut is banger
the myth collab No it should be the day
before I
think
mhm the night
before or yeah basically like 20 22
hours or so before 23 no 26 or
so
[Music]
of course he's got to see of
approval Mario sleep talking there's a
burp on his nose
[Music]
again he's got a poop on his
face that was a really cute birp I
wonder I think I see them in the back
we're probably still going to get to use
them very nice
[Music]
okay last last
one it was a
mistake to eat potato chips it always is
where is every
[Music]
dancing I
know
spikes extreme
[Music]
spikes
okay okay oh there's some
coins where are the mini cats actually I
still have so much like cut veggies and
uncut veggies still from
[Music]
yesterday I definitely bought to many
ingredients although I was already
holding back and I
also okay let's talk about yesterday
let's talk about my New Year's
Eve so I made ret I prepared
ret for my
friends uh if you don't know what Reet
is because apparently a lot of people
don't
know the girls had to look it up I told
told I told um shisa and Ena about it
that that was my plan and they were like
what what's R clut and they had to look
it up I think it's just super common in
Europe basically I mean there's like the
real type of
ret which is like just uh ret cheese
like you you you go to a restaurant they
bring this
huge cut of cheese to your table then
they melted onto your
food like that is I think the original
way to do
it but then there's the the at home
version basically what the
hell oh okay then there's that home
version that's very
different don't know what mites I don't
know anything about
mites why are the coins
there can't reach them um um so that
home version is basically like a little
little
Grill comes in different shapes and
sizes and the top is a grill but the
bottom is like an oven with little
shovels and in the shovels you would
normally normally you would put in like
or would I put in normally is like for
example on the bottom layer of my shovel
I put uh cooked already cooked potato
slices like pretty thick
ones so cooking potatoes is also in the
preparation meal prep part of
that so some potato slices then I would
put like maybe some veggies like bell
peppers grilled bell peppers or
zucchinis or corn or all of it and like
a slice of
salami
and I don't know you can put so many
stuff in there and then on top you put a
fake slice of ret
[Music]
cheese yeah and then you put it under
the grill while on top of the grill
while you're waiting for your little ret
shovel
to bake to
Perfection while you're waiting for
that you uh Grill on top like some more
Meats like chicken and
beef and pork whatever you want we also
did some
sausages um and also for my friends I
thought maybe they would like some
seafood too so I got like some
some some garlic shrimp skewers for them
but only one person ended up eating them
cuz the others weren't much of a fan
either apparently oh the koi wow I'll
enter there later I'm first checking out
the top oh ah
no okay that was a mistake
no no I didn't want to do that no I'm
sorry cheese fun yeah it's kind of like
cheese fun but not really because you
don't dip anything and already melted
[Music]
cheese there's however there's actually
for those grills there's combinations
where you can do the ret and the cheese
fun you like it will have a cheese f
[Music]
you
no I'm so stupid it's so difficult
sometimes you will have a cheese you
also attach to it in order to dip you
you don't in order to dip you don't have
yeah you would have to melt it but
there's no dipping you put the unmelted
slice of cheese on top of the things
that you're putting on your shovel if
you look up rlat Grill I think you'll
find what I'm talking
about
[Music]
oh no I killed
it happy New Year clar a hogy wait isn't
that like something Scottish or so
I needed the
bird that
down
no
oh that's
haggus okay let's go for
swim how do I swim again how do I dive
oh yeah wow that's an insane kind of
aquarium the fish just don't react to my
hat throw at
all what I hear something spark I the
moon over
there
I can just get it from here oh wow no
way oh they're swimming
around just like regular Corin you think
they also would not care I don't know
about that I think they would disappear
oh wow that one's cool the
instant I get into their
view o o you were stalking me for that
you must die
vanish evil
one for I must cleanse the world of
evil until there is no
more and that day shall it ever come
will be a day of Glorious Victory and
joy oh wait I needed
you
[Music]
interesting
O
Okay
W what was I talking
about what was I talking about I had the
Chee even my even oh my
[Music]
God okay H so we're making regl and I
bought so many
ingredients before like the day
before Oh my God I bought uh
80 worth of ingredients even though we
were only four
people and I didn't even ask them
cuz I don't know I feel bad I didn't
even ask them to you know take part in
the payments at
all I bought even
desserts oh
did it hit me though Y no it didn't
amazing and I don't think I need the
bird
anymore oh
Moon first that's actually not that bad
yeah and also I had a lot of leftovers
some things we didn't even Grill because
I was like I feel like this will be
enough let's just Grill all of this
first and see if we really need to cut
open all these other steaks as well cuz
you know what's at stake my
money
[Music]
oh oh
hi what's at stake
[Music]
Stakes yeah like I treated my friends to
a 20 year old meal
basically I was walking along these
roofs for so long I got lost I found
this powerful so it's not all
bad
let's one thing that was pretty good
though is um none of
bus like I don't drink at all right and
then the others they don't
like like one of my friends used to
drink alcohol but apparently recently
stopped or tried to stop just for like
health
reasons oh there you go
so the other two
they like drinking alcohol but they also
don't really feel the need need to so oh
I need a bird every everybody was like
kind of fine with not consuming too much
alcohol so I didn't buy any alcohol and
one of them said they will just
bring um a little bit of uh sect uh like
sparkling wine maybe just for you know
midnight
to cutting cutting the glasses what do
you say what do you call clinking
clinking clinking the glasses I don't
know let's stay on here toasting yes but
they make a clink sound
so
toasting this is
fun just got to stay in the
groove
waa
sick and and yeah so that apparently
that one was left over from last year so
no money was spent on
alcohol they just brought some stuff
that they had left
[Music]
over I'm
scared
yo
okay so cool cuz your see that
guys where I
landed Mama
Mia inner
wall we have infiltrated the inside
here's a new one I guess if you lose one
or if you start
here oh this is like Frogger this is
like Frogger we in a weird way wa wo now
my eyes are going crazy depending on
what you focus on I feel like oh this
one doesn't
move oh
oh
uh do I want the rest of the money
no I'm
[Music]
good eh so Wonder did I bu I bought like
some marinated steak and I brought
bought some non-marinated steaks like
several ones that were even 50% off
let's go and they looked pretty nice
nice pretty good filet steaks um then I
bought those Ro roast BR Ro and good
good Grill sausages and I bought the
shrimps and I bought I bought uh burger
patties because I saw even though I
personally haven't tried this before but
some people said for uh ret uh grilling
burgers is actually also pretty
genius so I prepared them just in
case but we ended up not using
them cuz we already had so much then
there was some chicken leftover chicken
that my uh one of my friends had that
they brought
over uh from their
freezer and what else I feel like that
was even more um but yeah and then we
grilled the veggies and you know we had
a good
time good amount of food and for
desserts I prepared some little cakes
ah oh no give me back my
I prepared some little cakes and I
served them on a platter I cut them into
small pieces and I put little too fix
into them and I served them on a platter
so oh my God I was like such a good
dinner host let me tell
you
wow nice for this one you actually have
to jump and then poke in when
you're
um when when you're
falling yeah Best Host
right
oh this one too do I also get a
moon
wait uh also I had like 10 different
[Music]
dips like garlic dip
oh barbecue
dip there so many dips we didn't even
open all of them I just wanted to be H I
just wanted there to be something for
everybody
huh I wanted good good Yelp
[Music]
reviews sounds like a nice dinner I want
to show you a picture
sure wonder I wonder if I
can let me
see do you want to
stand
[Music]
nice that should
be good I even normally I don't use
coasters but since I had guests and I
wanted things to look proper I I used my
coasters that I have from the
Korean uh collab Cafe
from like what one and a half years ago
or
so
there I just put them there for
decoration on the photo
[Music]
but okay I got the
pictures sent them to JMA first so I can
save them through Discord
T so this is the grill there's they come
as I said in different shapes and forms
like mine has a
special
like Stone Grill on the on the left side
that one was so difficult to
clean cuz you can't you're not even
supposed to clean it with soap or
anything
anything you're not supposed to do that
so you to clean it with just water but
after grilling for a while the the
that was stuck to it was like so deeply
in it and I had to like rub it with that
kind of metal scrubby thing endlessly
and I still have like some oily in
these like little
lower um lower rings on the side you
know what I mean you see what I
mean steel wo yeah I was using steel
wool it got like the the main surface
really clean eventually but it's still a
pain in the ass cleanness wow oh well
yeah we were grilling all kinds of meat
here you see the it felt
[Music]
like H it's like tanaki yeah it's so
cool grilling at home like this I it's
pretty common for people to do this in
Austria or Germany or so I think for
like new year or Christmas we used to do
it with my family too a lot for
Christmas cuz it's easy like everybody
can put together their own things you
buy a variety of things and everybody
just like takes whatever they want and
it's kind of fun cuz it's like a group
activity and yeah you can take as much
as you can eat M and then here's like a
variety of things that I prepared oh
yeah tomatoes and pepperonis and and
zucchini there's a salad there's corn
Sil but s do you know those at the pear
I think pearl onions are they called
pearl onions at the top a lot of cheese
Stacks we bought two different types but
they're both for a collect cheese
they're really um strong
scented strong very
cheesy yeah and the the salami is not to
grill on the top the salami is you know
as I just said you put it like in one of
your shovels and it works really well
under the cheese I like to put it under
the cheese but over the potato slices
and then some more
[Music]
veggies so I really recommend this this
was a lot of fun we were eating for like
2 hours or so
H the myth Coes are cute right I used my
own of
[Music]
course oh but actually so the grill the
grill like they sell these grills in
supermarkets sometimes um like smaller
ones and they
also sell them in like normal like
electricity shops or
whatever um um do we have a boss fight
now should I oh he's
there should we finish a tangent before
we go
in electronic
store okay let me just really quickly
tell you so I I I was so stressed out so
um Sunday was New Year Saturday was the
last day possible to go shopping and I
wanted to buy the grocery is obviously
on the day before cuz I have to buy meat
and all of that um but I also didn't
have the grill yet so I thought oh
should be no problem I have many
different shops where I could buy one
but then I I went out to buy one the
first shop that I went to which was an
Electronics shop was uh completely out
of them surprisingly even though it was
a huge electronic Shop with a huge
selection normally they had like other
types of things like they had fun you or
whatever but they didn't have Reet which
should tell you like how popular it is
to do ret here on New Year's everybody
was out buying one I saw people like
carrying their new ret Grill in a box
away from the shopping mall
mhm yeah so I was like uh well if
the electronic store doesn't have it
would the supermarket really have any
but I went to a pretty big Supermarket
then and they still had a big selection
they had really big ones and they uh
they were supposedly also have small
ones but the small on the smaller ones
were like sold out the ones that are for
like six people they only had some for
like eight or 12 people like really big
boys or some with extra functions like
fund you that I didn't need and but they
were so expensive so I didn't want to
buy them but but it was going to like
close the shops were going to close um
that that one was still I think open a
little bit longer but the Super Market I
had to buy all the ingredients and I I
noticed oh now I'm here not sure
contemplating if I should buy this or
not but I have to buy ingredients and I
have to go back home and uh to buy them
I was going to buy them there because I
needed my my big my big shopping bag
that the one I can roll because trust me
I needed it I can't just the amount of
things I had to buy I would not have
been able to carry that ever in a bag in
a normal grocery bag so I needed my
shopping thingy but I didn't bring it
because I didn't think I would do it in
one go I thought I would buy the grill
go back home leave it there take the
shopping
rolly coasty roller and then bring it to
the supermarket but then I realized I
only have like 30 minutes until all the
supermarket Clos so I have to go
back so I just bought it but at the same
time I was like discussing with my
friends maybe do you guys maybe have one
after all and then one of my friends
actually had one and they tested it out
but then turns out that every
time every time they would turn it on
the electricity in the whole home would
shut down so wasn't really safe so we
needed new one and another one of my
friends said they saw in the supermarket
they saw like cheaper ones in their area
um and they were going to go check but I
was going to buy this one anyway just
for safety in case there's is sold out
over there so I bought it just in case
then I went home I left it there I
quickly went I I quickly I quickly went
Supermarket shopping I had 30 minutes
basically at this point yeah when I went
back I had like 30 minutes and oh wow
wow I bought so many things my shopping
list is crazy oh as I said 80
90 and I got done on the very minute
when it closed the
shop it took me exactly 30
minutes and close and then I went back
and my friend told me no problem I got
the cheap one so I'm going to give back
the expensive one I didn't even open it
going to give it back and I'm buying the
cheap one off of my friend clutch Joe so
clutch yeah I woke up a little bit too
late and then I took my time with my
breakfast that's why I ended up being so
last minute with everything but it all
worked out yeah but the grill though
even on my way home I saw like two girls
in front of me were like carrying the
same grill that I
bought they were carrying it
home and all when I was standing in
front of the grill the ret Grill section
they were like once I I took the last
one from my the the one price class the
cheapest they still had I took it and I
walked away and that in that moment like
a group of like three or four people
relatively young people they also just
arrived to that section they were like
oh oh that's where they are that's where
that's where the reget girls are oh
thank God they were also like stressing
until the last minute to find one okay
lesson learned uh don't fire so last
minute I didn't expect everybody to also
buy one last
minute I could have bought it on Amazon
too I probably would have found much
cheaper options but I thought they are
everywhere in the shops in real life so
let's not buy it on Amazon this time for
once people always get things last
minute yeah I think ret grills are very
popular a
purchase around the end of the year but
now I have my own finally like until now
in my life I participated in many Reet
Grill parties but somebody always had a
grill somebody always had one my old
roommate when I lived with her we did
Reet uh in some either was it Christmas
or New Year some of that one of those
things and she has one so yeah and then
one party I spent with some uh old work
colleagues back before whole life I
think yeah before H spent uh New Years
with work colleagues and they also had a
a Reet Grill everybody has a Reet every
household needs a Reet Grill in Austria
or Germany even maybe I don't know how
you guys stand with that but yeah now I
have
mine that though like rice cookers in
Asia almost yeah yeah
and I would say a little bit less common
than rice cookers in Asia cuz in in in
Japan Homes apartments often even come
with the rice cooker if they're a little
bit uh um if they have some furniture in
it then they definitely have like if
they have a bed then they have a rice
cooker it's a
staple yeah so anyway that was my
stressful story about
finding uh finding the ret Grill oh yeah
oh
yeah quite stressful but it all worked
out buying all the groceries to
sheesh yeah what is it
Peach I met this girl she's she's
brunette I realized I don't really like
blon except if your name is
am you're too late we're after our
wedding ceremony on the
moon
Mario I don't like the moon I don't
believe in the moon the the moon landing
was fake too so I don't believe I can
land on it please save me we're going to
die before we
land well oh
P I lied I lied I like blondes I like
him
[Music]
not you
again but this time looks like a very
different battle oh
dear what the hell where did you get
that from what the is that what am
I
fighting am I supposed to a the
birdies all right now we're
talking oh that will teach you wait
you're sending me even more birdies
they're attacking me too I don't need
more
birdies ass stupid ass
bird okay I'm going to guess it's better
to wait what how do I get up there oh I
can CL what how do
what he's holding what where do I go
where do I go I should have used the
bird okay I guess it can it can poke
into there oh wow okay another try
another
try I need to bir the whole time
huh
okay okay
nice bird in in bination imp person
and yeah hey
no
do we get another try right away hey
okay and then do I poke into them or
what not
sure oh
yeah
okay do they with the side the one to
their sideways look kind of difficult or
are they changing positions are they
turning po Birds got
stomped
nice oh yeah they Chang positions okay
[Music]
okay then that's no
problem can't be soldier soldier
down what the
I should not be in the bird should
I cuz otherwise I'm too slow
oh going
quzy what are those
snakes snaky
boys
what I was on my way to the stone to get
the heart from
it oh
well
all right
birie round
[Music]
two oh damn it that will teach
you oh two at
once I'm
[Music]
coming all right you're going down
first to the Moon you shall go go to the
wedding come on you're going to be late
otherwise
stomp
stomp oh oh come
[Music]
on
number
two now we're back to where we
were going to Doom so let me leave the
bird do I have to make
it run against the wall cuz it looks
like it's kind of like taking damage
more or less yeah yeah yeah maybe oh no
does it just always end after threee
runs who knows who knows what the hell
is this can
I it goes away eventually
right well now it
did no not again I don't know if I can
get rid of this as as bird oh
no oh no shoot a bomb
do
[Music]
it
no no I'm ah
I can't cut myself I'm not supposed
to say
that sorry I'm just
feeling stressed
out one more try this is it yeah I was
too close but they're cornering me
[Music]
well it's good that the fight is not too
easy it's not supposed to be too
easy if it was as easy as all the other
fights we had
we're going to fall
asleep out of
boredom let me get a
heart there are only two hearts on this
whole
map map
stage
y nice pretty fast pretty fast
oh no it's pretty fun it's pretty
fun it's just after the second
one ah the difficulty goes up a
bit I did the wrong jump oh my God
you done you done being
angry so can I actually oh I can shoot
them away from me
[Music]
but might as well no no
okay oh not
rattlesnakes
the party poppers going
crazy
oh God Dam
it
no
okay time for some bombs
guys
Dam
it two hearts
left ah I left my bird
no
birdie oh he knows he knows oh I'm so
oh my
[Music]
God think I'm going to lose
again
yeah a lot of um kind of insane people
in the chat right
[Music]
now calm your
titties it's a game I'm not taking it
seriously why are
you sweaty
gamers
oh he wants one
more nailed
it fear the power of the Woodpecker y
I'm going to fall
off oh oh no don't worry don't
worry one cannot ruin my joy with this
game really good I love
it the rattles staks are back
yooo
I'm not going to get close to you until
you give me a
bird give me a chance Something to
Believe
In all right now this is a fair
fight relatively I mean look at the size
difference but of
course that never
matters a finally
finally ooh he's standing
differently o it's taking down the lady
time one more right
okay the stupid hat
[Music]
one literally the Mad Hatter isn't The
Mad Hat also a bunny or am
I she went a little bit too fast I
needed to get out of
there the M yeah it is right M there is
a
bunny he's going to do the fast move
again isn't he oh he's
fast is there like does he stop when
he's close enough to me or after a
certain amount of steps oh maybe it was
a certain amount of
steps
let
[Music]
me that's okay we got one
hit
uhoh heart
Challenger streem heart
Challenger get me I know I know I know I
know I know I know I know I know too
close too
close
okay here we
go what
no the angle
musuki one more
bomb one more bomb
[Music]
no
no once I hit a bird and once I
miss oh yeah right I can uh wait can I
oh yeah I can hop and kick
[Music]
oh bird are you under there you are
incredible where do I Ascend
here maybe not the best option oh oh God
oh
God oh no no no no
[Music]
no holy I think that was about to
reset
yo
oh happy New Year
nice my triple Moon that was worth four
moons at least cuz of four bunnies four
crazy
[Music]
rabbits happy New
Year yeah happy New Year or as I like to
say happy new
[Music]
n
nobody gets
it
y one stle away and Bowser flee off to
the
moon so we can chase after him with the
Odyssey just follow me onto that GL do
it let do
it okay
I shall do it yeah it's a German joke
cuz in German we say always know is y
yah is year yah but we don't say the r
really we say just
yah and
[Music]
uh you know that sounds like you're
saying happy new yes so I say happy new
no no
n one of my friends laughed about it one
of my friends IRL friends she even
laughed about it still like 10 minutes
later remembering the joke out of
nowhere
what his castle is literally on the
moon what the is
that why is it on the
moon was she do not
really Fly Me to the Moon Bowser took
that a little bit a little bit too
[Music]
literally to the
Moon
me
[Music]
forever I
wish I
[Music]
love like a sella moment
e
[Music]
tacos space
tacles tacles are
pretty
yeah pretty alien likee if there was an
animal on Earth that you would say is
pretty alien like I would say tacos are
definitely one of
those
yeah yeah octopus sorry I couldn't think
of the word the English word
octopuses
are very alien
[Music]
like
octop octop
that's stupid I think
octop octopus sounds better but it's
just embarrassing to say cuz you guys
are going to make a big deal out of
it oh octopie
oh well don't you look thater now stop
making jokes about
the N these two must be over there no
time dly D let's
go I I can't believe we're on the moon I
can't believe it
because how is he able to breathe how is
Mario able to breathe why is that Moon
out
[Music]
there
oh okay I sense
possibilities oh I have to uh throw my
hat onto
[Music]
that now this jump works even better
there oh I don't okay this Moon do you
think I
can reach it if I land on the pole no
probably
[Music]
not no I probably have not cap jumped a
single time no probably
not oh I I could have just climbed on it
from
well that would be too easy okay is this
how you get
there no that's not
it oh
maybe
whatever I don't want to try million
things spend all my time of it
but wait I can hey there's a path
here yeah there's Wedding
Bells
[Music]
ding
wait no okay but from
here ah wait
I
think can I not do that one jump anymore
this one maybe with that I don't
[Music]
know that was the plan but I failed the
jump the head jump I don't
know long jump into long long jump long
jumping long jumping it is not because I
failed
again why
ah and wait that's that's diving wait
how do why why do I fail sometimes there
we
go it's just not exact
timing four times the
[Music]
charm ah oh should I give myself a
little bit more time in the crouched
position and
then
oh we'll do it we'll do
[Music]
it
oh that's something
else I'm pressing forward
[Music]
though
exactly
calculated
woo
[Music]
can I break
these my first moon on the moon oh my
God I'm collecting moons on the
moon real moon pieces hey this kind of
thing is broken here in other places
it's I think it's the same
thing I'm looking
at oh look at those evil Taco
dodes what
happened
no
safe are those pachis that haven't found
the
light pachis that have not found Ena
they're
[Music]
Priestess
Taco dases that are not in ena's control
and
religion a wait a I was already on
him I need to get on to him and
then wow oo I can turn quite a bit in
air
yes o it gives quite a lot of coins for
that
okay for one
kill they need
cookies Tes who are denied their
[Music]
cookies
I don't have to throw my hat do I I
thought I just have to touch him I throw
my
hat you little come
[Music]
here
ho I swear to
God
yeah the year of the rabbit has ended I
said enough of your
shenanigans
didn't you hear what I
said
[Music]
Angry pick
over I hate
those
little holding together spiky boys
[Music]
we have no excuse to
exist okay ooh I feel like with the
flowers I can make it over there maybe
even
with oh oh yay yes yes yes that's also
why there's flowers there to get
[Music]
back let's pickle
oh oh you guys know why I keep on
saying that right cuz it always sounded
to me like he says let's pickle let's
pickle
right well that is a shortcut to get
back for
sure what hexagon what does he say
hexagon is that what you guys are
hearing ing hexagon oh I don't think
that's what he's saying though I think
he's a fan of p
and a secret no
[Music]
Sagi okay I think I need the flower
again n said
that in order to oh oh okay that
works I saw the platform I was like oh
yeah B that's where I'm supposed to
go is that what she heard hexagon like I
I can hear
it I can see
[Music]
it h this world is very calm and like I
don't want to say
boring but so
far
I mean it's cool though it's cool it's
[Music]
cool H wait I'm I'm somewhere totally
different there you
go I'm giving it a chance I'm I'm
exploring oh toad is
here toad what's up how did you get here
the you were here before me are you the
first one on the move
moon or at least the first Toad on the
moon the hole back there is real deep
does that mean that that's where I'm
supposed to
go
ooh like saying oh you have a long path
ahead of you if you go this
way oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah I haven't
seen you in a while what the hell
talk to
[Music]
me
greet greetings traveler and to your hat
as well can you answer my riddle should
you really be answering questions right
now
no ding
dong yes oh ver of correct answers there
are so many other things you could be
doing with your
time to what must I'm done okay but
like what didn't you guys give me
something
before in the
past do I have to jump on you on on your
head what oh I have to come back
later
oh
okay can't give me the reward now
huh
okay then let's go to the seemingly main
path which okay it's like plasted all
over here it will probably explain to me
what all those boxes are
for oh
wowow that's what's inside the
moon underground Moon
Caverns
uh wait the gravity feels normal in here
M too bad too
[Music]
bad wait that's cute
what what is what that's too cute for
Bowser he's got like little ribbons on
the edges of his
fences We Fall Down
I I
guess oh I can become one of
them oh I have to fly
oh oh that's kind of cool flap flap flap
flap oh oh the tanks are back the tanks
are the back
woo they're also wearing fancy fancy
hats they're for sure shooting me from
behind y oh no can I shoot the lava go
away open the
Gat and thank you for the HP oh a bet I
can't jump
uh oh
oh oh
no
FL and return to tank we're busy
[Music]
here split personalities what is this no
key Flappy Bird
kiaha
oh more Hearts oh didn't take any damage
I don't need your hearts all the
time oh it's going to move W wo wo no I
hate them you know I hate
them let me take you you're in control
of me why I in control ah I hate
you and big jump oh yeah cuz oh I need
them for the
B they knew that I was going to do
thatby get byebye oh how am I supposed
to get over
there no can I
redo
no
no that was terrible I Know I Can Do
Better
uh
yep you have to like quickly I know it's
written below but it's still like
there's a there's a face of getting used
to it
again that I'm not
getting they're not giving it to
me
yum let doing it again wrong
timing I feel like I'm being rushed here
[Music]
a okay how my guys can break the walls
hey yo for real oh God great
start oh
my
do they reload cuz they get stuck
sometimes in the same
[Music]
spot is that when they're
reloading
[Music]
why did I destroy
it oh come on
no it was beginning so
well smooth
sailing no
more o o o leave me
alone so so one not good to this I wait
for spawn another
one
no he stopped moving when he reloads for
real oh my God the timing of the
[Music]
lava okay we get another chance in
life I wish there was a checkpoint
here
go
up why no check
poter oh car
yeah ah here we go
guys they do a Switcheroo oh and I get
of course I get
[Music]
kids oh they can indeed break
them C
spam if they have the ability to spam
the Hammers this hard then I should be
grateful that they did until now should
I still take
him feel like I could but it's probably
not the
intention no
okay y I'm not sure how to deal with
this should I control one of them or
just jump over
them well oh wait I need them I have
just realized I need it I'm going to die
I'm going to die
I'm going to die oh wow oh no no control
no
[Music]
control that's so
sad I was going to jump back up and
catch the next one but I tried to
control
him but he wanted to fall into the
lava instead of rescuing his
butt oh
[Music]
no
go
[Music]
away I'm out of
here oh yeah yeah heal nice okay at
least you're back to
[Music]
six make
way
nice one of the
best enemies to take control
of
[Music]
okay
so uh would you
mind thank
you oh oh m
yeah
[Music]
okay
what uh oh uh oh yeah right
no oh my
God uh uh oh yeah go for here I
guess nice
radio sounds the acoustic sound like
radio
when I'm in the bullet what's of you
again I don't remember
you I don't remember
you oh because he sees it
right oh
no timer Yeah by yeah yeah that's why I
didn't go I thought so I thought so okay
uh is that really enough
time uh wait
no holy holy that was scary
that was scary that was scary I was like
wait can he run and yeah can you run
just the mem oh because it this okay
it's not like it disappears
completely I just can't see it
anymore oh okay
okay it does Disappear
[Music]
Completely
oh I'm just slower when I have the
shades
on wait there there was a checkpoint
there oh an invisible one okay thank
God
yeah I didn't remember that at
all but then what's the what's the timer
for ah
okay I
think I think I don't even
need the shades at all maybe I don't
know oh
man no cuz left the the purple
coins show you where to
turn
but
[Music]
still I should at least like I need to
find
wait now it's not there yeah but I think
it starts like here on this
[Music]
golden
block
yeah
the first fail was only because I didn't
really remember and I got a little bit
one
guide but who are you when did I fight
you am I going to control
you I don't remember that oh I
[Music]
guess what am I doing that far is this
like training
here okay yeah it seems like
training yeah okay cuz it is the first
time that's why they gave you a training
area okay
okay
yo interesting do I leave him because I
don't think I can I can't
[Music]
jump but I need him
I killed
him then
like oh okay I can go without him a
little bit these aren't so
fast
yeah he almost punched
me what a
[Music]
meanie ah okay okay this way for some
purple
coins wait this way
for the next
stage let's
go Jimmy oh my God I'm going to fall off
oh I'm wobbly I'm wobbly I'm wobbly oh
that was
dangerous I was close to falling off you
know when you lose your grip a little
bit oh hello
oh you got your Golden Boy with three
hats on that's adorable was he always
[Music]
golden he always
have do you do you remember me you were
ever so rude to me back in this Cascade
Kingdom in you were quite rude to all my
darling brutal which is why we're all
here now no I do believe it's lunch time
for my newly powdered up chain
[Music]
Shopkins oh
my uh how did we fight this
lady oh oh what I went in there with one
heart h two hearts I think at the time
oh
dear oh
no come a oh
oh I'm pulling I'm
pulling okay yeah that is still the same
way basically but now he has hats that I
have to get rid of
first oh my oh my oh my oh
my so greedy
grey you know that I'm greedy for coins
you know that I'm gr for
coins says Ariana gr totally that's
totally what she
said
uh does he charge forever until he Bonks
against
[Music]
something damn it's stamina
no
don't what is baby don't hurt me don't
hurt me no
more Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy
jimy Jimmy jimy Jimmy Jimmy jimy jimy
jimy
jimy Jimmy oh wait I could have maybe
saved myself with wall jumps over
there Dam it
he looks like a
Jimmy everybody looks like a
Jimmy I look like a
Jimmy his name is Chuck well no his name
is
Jimmy he's a Jimmy at
heart it is kind of funny though
how like people people when you look at
them and you hear their name you're just
like yeah somehow that really fits
you but then I wonder like certain
names only really fit you as an
adult wobble so I'm
like when you when you were a child that
name seems kind of
unfitting where certain names only
really seem more appropriate as a as a
teenager or right yeah I know I moved at
the last second my my sweaty spaghetti
fingers yeah like certain names are so
adult Peter in German as well maybe it's
worse in German I don't know
H who calls their child horse like as a
horse some there's a German name that's
called
horse
horse as an adult I feel like that name
is totally fine but oo I would feel bad
if a child had that name that's kind of
weird not horse H
[Music]
yeah just let go of the joystick waa see
see
a
yeah wait to get to the boss fight I
have to do all of that oh dear we better
not fail
now more got more oh it got
[Music]
uhoh oh W that was speedrun that was a
speedrun
though again pretty
Speedy no damage this time one more time
we can do it we can do
it oh dear oh oh oh she kind of coined
me I'm so greedy I'm so
greedy but it's okay this is I think
normally the last hit what I
need come on let me
[Music]
yay sorry I killed all your kids and
your dog and
you
terrible why don't we just all go
separate ways why don't we all have to
fight cuz he steals Peach yes but
besides
that is there really no other
lady that could be interested in Bowser
Bowser for real like you're not going to
be happy don't you realize you can't
force a lady to love
you you should just I don't know maybe
that rabbit lady that I just killed you
could be a good C couple in theory I
think
so you just got to stop forcing it like
that's the
issue
[Music]
maybe if he gave her a choice more or
less just get to know her normally maybe
Peach would even be interested you
know get to know her first and like
become something like
friends
acquaintances Don't Force It
wow I
mean I don't have to give him prop sto
for all the effort he went through for
the perfect wedding for her to make her
happy he is trying to make her happy I
mean he flew her to the
moon was this game inspired by that
song Me to the
Moon
[Music]
first I look
behind oh a
frog frog on the
moon why
[Music]
why that's why that's
why
oh there's something there
oh do you see this it's really
bright but they finally found each other
we always find those wallpapers wall
paintings like
separately do I get a heart container
this time maybe even maybe it's
bright oh the frog is right in the
middle oh no he pooped away
oh okay I just get a heart a normal
heart man wait can I get there without
the
Frog maybe yeah probably
can eyes I think my my middle my main
monitor is brighter than it should be a
little
bit so
oh well that looks like a moon
but I feel like there should be
something here as
well
whoa what do I do do I become the
Bell oh I'm on the
Bell what
now where is the reward oh maybe I can
fall in here there's maybe something
down there but hopefully not the
wedding not going straight into the
wedding ride or is this actually the the
path they want me to take cuz the front
doors are maybe even closed are they
closed they're probably closed and this
is where they want me to
[Music]
go higher I need the Frog to get higher
okay let me bring the Frog here
again
although I can reach this on my own I
think
[Music]
ah oh hey
what
wait ah you charg those things right I
forgot
wait
yo yo yo in in in on the moon you can
save yourself so
easily that's not possible in the normal
world but here you can turn around and
then jump again and turn around and jump
again and get higher and higher can I do
this on the
moon oh it's still pretty
fast wow okay frog once again I need
your help for something we got to get to
the top of the
church with our powers combined we can
do
it we can reach Heights never seen
before oh why that's all there is those
purple coins should have looked above
before deciding that I want to go there
that's it that's it it it's hard to
aim
frog frog come
[Music]
on I have no control over this
frog
[Music]
and
frog Reach for the Stars no no
[Music]
no this is so stupid oh I got
one yes yes
yes
wait these are special right these are
only
here or wait no never mind never mind
they're the same compo they look like
compo compo oh come
on what what am I doing this
for
[Applause]
yay so stupid so
useless all right I'll go in as a a
[Music]
frog let's go she'll love me as a frog
she will kiss
me no
no no she won't love me like
this I know she told me she prefers
frogs I'm not pretty enough like this
her favorite color is green I know it
looks like it's pink oh actually
green she likes slimy boys wait why is
Pauline here she
evil like what is that a huge ass ring
what are you going to do putting that on
her paen why the are you here
traiter why why are
you what why are you happy why are you
clapping she's
crying can I still it looks good
Ste the
flowers they sh the forks are
shaking is the cake there the cake is
there
nice uh just in time why you should have
rejected uh you were dragged
away like why is this audience not
I guess okay this is also kind of sweet
if you think about it because he could
have filled the audience with his own um
people but that would have made Peach
probably very uncomfortable and he's
trying to make her even more comfortable
so he brings supposedly her friends or
her people that are on her
side that is man that's kind of
sweet he's just trying to to make her
comfortable and make her love him and
just no matter what he does she won't
but
Bowser that's because you started off
all
wrong so I must say to this Le
Zone
objection She's
Mine
no no stop just stop where you
going to go to
Mars strong hat strong no don't let go
no I relied on
you oh show down on the moon
we don't want to ruin the beautiful chap
chapel
chapel crashing the wedding Mario that's
tacky even for you also your outfit
isn't halfway fancy enough for the
occasion not that it matters since you
weren't
invited so now it's time for you to make
like a bouquet and get frown
out get ready
Mario well nice ra
sound here's you happily ever
after no time to push the button uh all
right this is familiar we did this
before I become the Hat I wear the hat
and then we P punch oh no oh no oh
no wait I'm
[Music]
here oh wait
what what what did what what did I do
can I become you no cuz he doesn't have
a hat what you going to do now with no
oh my God how do you dodge that so you
going to be on one of these
platforms oh this part
again oh nice look at it but I'm so
going to lose like one
heart we're not going to make it uhoh
yeah yeah um six hearts would be nice
for this fight wouldn't it wait can I
actually buy something that would be
cool if I could buy something right here
maybe one shopkeeper came along
imagine but they don't really look like
they're selling anything
here
H now you can check what's in the hole
oh well maybe there's
a oh yeah cuz I
did oh
no I was distracted
[Music]
what how
do how did I what did I do last
time I I did not know what I did last
time and I still don't
know oh okay well we're going to die
obviously or so obviously going to die
you're going somewhere else I I guess oh
there's a heart there well let's survive
this yeah well okay he turns around
immediately
okay but I think i' I've been figuring
things out
now oh the brick the bricks have Arts
oh right into it we're getting right
into it okay let's actually purposefully
stay further away so it's easier to
jump I jump too early
that'll teach you okay I'm going to
go one to the side camera
please cuz i
f ah where's the heart from the stone
there's none
[Music]
on tanking
control what what okay well those I
don't think I'm supposed to
touch that's
new the fake hats sometimes have hearts
oh
a there's a shop
[Music]
now forgive me for I have
sinned
but I don't
care I deserve
it not baby married no I'll show you
like this was remember in the last
stream where I got a heart for boss
fight and then I ended up doing it with
only threee Hearts anyway
basically not saying that that will
really
happen but it could it could it's a
[Music]
possibility nice see I just needed to
calm me
down this camera
sucks not too early oh but it's it was
okay oh he comes again
[Music]
bastard
mine
what how do you dodge that I do not
understand twice even okay probably last
time will be free times let's remember
that those you can only Dodge not punch
all
right I oh oh
and and back again and Back Again a he
does everything more each round I
think
[Music]
O Okay interesting
interesting except for these
jumps hey I'm here
[Music]
early too
early W early early bird doesn't catch
the Bowser
sadly
[Music]
boy
oh
finally
nice I think I did only need like two or
three
hearts but there's more probably huh
face
two she's free now can you finally use
your supposed magic that you allegedly
have and help me I don't know are we
done she's so pretty with the
ponytail yes
yes
you beat the game he says and
yet new
trouble new
trouble what are
these
Mario he spoke said her name and wow I
don't think I ever heard him say her
name say my name my name
GameCubes not quite wake
up oh you
bit what what are we going to do I don't
know oh now I can be
Bowser and that's how we get through
those
rocks put Peach on my back come on
oo
what what are those
[Music]
memories very dramatic Mario yes te
me now she loves him oh man but at
least Bower gets to somewhat redeem
himself
oh
oh oh brief fire for shake uh shake to
brief okay so far doesn't seem like I
need to do
it oh
left or right oh wrong way wrong way
Long Way WR
[Music]
way
what oh everything's
shaking we're going into the 2D
world go
in you
fatty even into
she's on top of
me
H oh
no oh wait oh
tricky oh no no wait what ah wait no no
wait wait wait
wait
[Music]
was I supposed to keep some blocks there
because I I'm not sure how I was
supposed to go up
higher wait he's making typical Mario
sounds but
in in the like weirdly sounding voice of
Bowser like the the typical sounds he
would make
nice
ouch wooo but like really
low even his fist movement like when he
jumps is very
Mario that way we know it's him it's him
it always was him always was him no no
no
okay so my question
is uh was I supposed to leave something
no no they're waiting for me aren't they
oh no oh here okay here here oh oh God
wait uh wait H brain hord okay we're
back we're back we're so
bad boy smashing
rocks a let's go
even
Beyond I forgot what we're doing this
for oh yeah right cuz everyone's falling
apart and we're like making it fall
apart even more though kind of
oh what the
what is this supposed to be I see the
outside but almost
there um I mean what do you mean with
outside you mean space
[Music]
what what am I
doing I he just trying to oh my
God okay I see I see what we're
doing nice
soundrack very
P this a
sound
like an
anime that's the second soundtrack with
actual like voice that they have for
this
game besides the polline
one ow and now quick get to the
middle I'm on my
way yeah with
lyrics
oh we finally destroying the cube is
that what we're going to do in the overw
world too in the over world in the other
world
oh together let's go all together what
about all the guests we left behind in
the wedding W you oh my God are they
going to die to as well it's just
us what about the
others
Oh wait we're here that's where we land
okay okay okay wait but where did we
come from I thought we were on the moon
we were then in then we went inside the
moon and
then so what we escaped from the inside
of the moon but what I don't
understand is that the ending and all
those cubes that's just like after like
post game optional moons and stuff
the
cute they're cute
together no you no get out of here
this is just like in Super Mario
where
no not
again is there a secret ending if I get
all moons
probably
she rejected both of us did she forget
what I just did for her I went to the
moon for her to rescue
her she has no
idea how much trouble that hey py P you
can't leave without me what the is
she
[Music]
doing this
no why she we could have just like gone
back all together friendly but no
is Peach is creating some
drama are you kidding
me what why
what's
a that was uh I didn't I didn't
say that one on purpose that that was
just supposed to be Peach
but that's just my inner anger speaking
I
guess oh my
God I told you it's in the title I told
you why are we doing this even why are
we here just to
suffer bit is
selfish Mama
Mia we should have stayed in New York or
wherever that
was but yeah I'm happy about Tiara and
my hat being
together those
two seem to have way less trouble in
Paradise than me and Peach I you
don't
damn they have siblings they are what
they are siblings
okay weird typo that one
guy they're S I thought they were going
to
[Music]
marry h i be a Mario game honestly with
how much I've been playing this off
screen I I I was even like feeling like
I wanted to play more off screen than I
could than I did I just stopped myself
always because I didn't want to move on
to a different world or so without you
guys cuz I I I thought I couldn't go
anywhere until later on I don't
know so I just I was just doing
more uh moons in wherever I left off
always but with with how much I was like
enjoying this I think um maybe even in
the airplane or so I'm going
to get some more moons in the in the
post game
way more game left well I don't know
should I be streaming
that cuz I cleared the game I think it's
a nice cut off
there unless there's like a big extra
chunk of story that you think I have to
show otherwise I think this is you know
at least check one level you love ah the
Super Mario can we go to the Super Mario
64 one though the other Castle this one
this one
we got to go we got to
go thanks for playing thank you thank
you so much for playing my
game thank you so much for playing my
game thank you so thank you so
much I wish I could do his voice thank
you so much for playing my game for
playing my game qu oh frogs the the
frogs wait are the frogs the
aliens that frog on the moon was kind of
sus space frck they're green like going
back to the topic that I brought up
of of alien like animals amphibians or
whatever besides
octopuses I would
say let's just go over that ignore that
I would say frogs could be up there
too
yeah oh it brings me
there oh didn't have to do
anything I told you guys to just ignore
it Just Go With It Go With the Flow
who's
talking who's
talking so calm so peaceful like a trip
to the moon kingdom was all a
dream but good thing it was because they
we saved our girl two dear friends that
nightmare is over hoay for us but I've
liked our travel so much I don't want
our journey to end so here comes the
post game yay so many hats need to meet
and I bet if we collect even more power
moons we'll be able to travel somewhere
new so our trip is far from over one
more one more way but for Star let head
up to Beach's Castle oh my god let's go
Luigi Luigi you're
floating tell me one balloon your your
one balloon can lift you
up oh there's special
balloons and
hey bro you sa the princess beat so
proud of you but enough that get this
bro I came up with a new game I called
it balloon World balloon world is a game
where you search for balloons hidden by
people all over the world oh you should
know about that if you play your high
score nickname and profile icon will
show up in other people's games you want
to connect to the network and connect
Sur to oh wait no no no no I I didn't
want
to oops the little the little but how
could I say no to him all right let's
begin thank you so much everybody else
says no to me but at least you my
brother says yes thank God I'm so happy
first we'll move to the starting point
oh dear
okay just I just
oh
interesting you play balloon wel my
hiding and seeking balloons first I'll
show you find it try to find find the
balloon I hide you'll have uh 30 seconds
to find the balloon and pop
it once you leave the starting area find
it will
begin what I have to find the balloon
and pop
it and the error shows me it's there oh
yeah is it is it it's
there how do I pop it just jump into it
oh
what oh touch it okay I jumped off too
early nice work bro you take these 50
coins as a reward oh you get a time I
get a Time bonus okay so this time I hit
the balloon but in the real thing
players from all over the world oh
what oh also when you're playing find it
for real I'll need a few more coins from
you sorry and then you know this where
who are those coins going
to for each three coins you collect you
get one one second other to the time
limit for that round it works that way
both and find it and hide it so it's
always good to remember okay let's try
hide it you'll be the one to hide the
balloon in hided bro and players all
over the world will look for it you'll
get coins for each player who plays
until someone finally finds and pop the
balloon NE right will you guys know that
you hit my balloon that you found my
balloon I wonder if they'll tell you
that's that would be
cute
then that will be so special for you
yeah find my balloon cuz once it's found
once will it never again show up for
anybody else so this is one balloon of
mine or does it is it going to be shown
to several people I
wonder then I should hide
it I will hide it and if somebody pops
it and uh shows me a screenshot
then maybe something nice will
happen how long you take to hide your
balloon will affect how long people have
to look for it and you can take your
time and hide it far away quickly hide
it nearby use your time wisely once you
leave the starting area balloon World hi
it will start also in order to even
Place one H go looking for one in the
first
place I have
to can I go down
I have to
oh oh how much time I do I have oh I
it
ah wait
wait
okay I okay so I only have to uh uh I
have to hide one in order to find one so
that there's always hidden balloons I
guess audio it's okay if the audio gives
it gives you some
hands
I think I found a nice
[Music]
spot find
it no audio breakdowns
no should have muted the game to no it's
okay I hope you like balloon World bro I
think it's a BL way you play it and
maybe you'll earn yourself a ton of
coins if you get really good at it at
find it and hide it want to play find it
yeah I guess so let show me show me what
it's like
did you guys hide anything for me
yet oh I can
choose but there's like only three pages
is it really only these balloons
available right
now or is it a certain selection so you
got to be lucky oh wait there's a
balloon
code I can give you guys a balloon code
but then oh I will be gone
immediately is this one of you guys is
anyone here from you you
guys reward who
oh why is this one why does this one
have more reward for
example but a lower time
[Music]
limit it'll be more fun if it's random
yeah you got to be lucky to find me
oh cuz more people failed it
coins 9 seconds 7
Seconds I'll go
for this one 22 seconds
250 I have to oh wait I paid
75 okay okay that's fine
some people put it in glitch spots a
come on it shows me the direction at
least he wait wrong optical illusion oh
no wait it's not there oh go
yourself I don't
know yeah
great you
suck person you
suck are you it's there on the
top
unbelievable Luigi you scammed
me I quit oh
yeah oh yeah good luck guys finding my
balloon honestly I'm impressed if you
find it that you have to be lucky oh you
got to be real
lucky why have you asked me a million
times if I want to quit or
not oh they have the bike here you earn
extra coins by playing in B's Kingdom oh
for real do we have new stuff here oh
but I have no stars
here
interesting oh my God low polyon
outfit oh my
[Music]
God cute
orange
[Laughter]
99,999 I can't even afford it Super
Mario Sunshine
outfit who what are these
out it's from that
oh all those oh cute I
could be so cute
[Music]
though oh my God what what set
outfit what 8bit Mario C that's so
flat that is so
flat oh my God I don't even know you
need so many coins for this if only I
didn't lose so many in my lifetime here
I I kind of want this so I can look more
girly but it's so
expensive I don't know I'll think about
it
w oh my god let's let's look around a
little bit wow it's like
HD is this the first time in like Mario
history that they like did this like
making the 64
world so beautifully in in
h what is this why is there
Apple
mushrooms can I take apple have revisit
in the way yeah oh AI but he can't touch
water can
he
H
Gardens I'm quite proud of you made oh
do you need an apple in here or what oh
there's a stupid ass bunny over there
you little
he just ran past me
bastard
probably should stay on top of the
bushes a bastard a bastard of a bunny
no oh wait there's a
nut bunny you're not entertaining enough
this nut is more entertaining than you
that's why I gave up on you
bunny I hope you understand what that
means for
you
nice another bike over there and another
toe who dancing these motor scooters are
so cool yeah right they
are okay scarecrow what do you
got where the scooter what the scooter
wait the scooter is
here can we keep the scooter
here
[Music]
can we use it to catch the bunny oh I
wonder
no so freaking
close it's manageable I
even no no I even stumbled a little bit
and it's still I think very
[Music]
manageable there it goes the scooter no
worries I just I just wanted to wash it
a little bit cuz I made it so dirty in
these
fields yay let's pickle that's not a
moon that is I think a
star
what the is
that do we need to stack them again
oh oh but I killed two maybe they
already
[Music]
respawned getting the Stars you didn't
in Mario 64
mhm oh I don't think I'll have enough of
them can I even stack on top of a triple
yeah that's what I
thought how do
I over here
[Music]
buddy I think you have to start with the
triple
no
the double
works with the triple
F can I reset
[Music]
them money money
money can they separate each other
please do it I'll be gone for a moment
maybe they'll
reset I'll bring this to the gardens
squeam wall
wh
wh wiu's singing was so beautiful I
forgot in what group she even was and
what song She Sang but I just remember
her singing was so pretty once
again I wish like she had more
opportunities to
Showcase that gorgeous amazing singing
voice of
hers cuz
incredible
kidding
me oh yeah oh yeah makes sense yeah Iris
and Sora of course yeah what i s by cuz
they were in the group also in the
shuffle
medle oh what is going
on did I bring the wrong nut
what there are planted by the
Goombas
y why that's so
confusing on that one yeah true
indeed
indeed and there's still stag oh
well quick quick quick make your Escape
o there's a little world
here guys I can go inside the castle
right is there oh there's the Goomba
lady is there a recreation of
everybody's favorite inside the castle
level
slide yes no
no Ben it's not worth
[Music]
it I might be extremely bad at Super
Mario 64 and I'm bad at playing it and I
get salty and I gave up and and all
that but you know it's part of my
Nostalgia as a child playing it on the
Nintendo 64 and I will never forget that
is
that boss fre matches or
what is that what you get to do here oh
wait
oh I think
so hard mode
oh no do I get a moon then probably a
triple right at least a triple oh
no
um that was easy where is the hard
mode nothing's happening oh he's
starting to do some stuff
now
easy what that was easy you're going to
to bamboozle me now with a hard mode
right now is where it starts you want to
start like easy to throw me off when it
gets hard oh wa I forgot how to jump oh
there we
go oh oh yeah uh like this a I was
right next to that okay okay okay okay I
just had to remember how to jump that's
all I
needed so even if I didn't finish Super
Mario 64 that doesn't mean that I don't
like it or not appreciated every time I
hear the music or see
anything any anything that reminds me of
it it's just a dream come
true it's
magical it's never too late to go back
to
it you know maybe it's good if I don't
because am I not just ruining my
positive feelings towards
it I think I
am
but I could try again eventually I'm
totally up for that uh
okay yeah well stupid I'm
stupid okay it doesn't come over here
okay
y you just rushing it you just got to
rush it you don't you can't give it too
many
chances
[Music]
impossible that's
impossible it's
possible how do I where do I stand
where's the best place to stand when
they do
that sounds so
funny between two
outside you can't chese that you have to
but I feel like I'm standing maybe in a
spot that's not where very
helpful cuz like after jumping over one
I immediately have to jump over the next
coln or like then then yeah I have two
coming at me at once people
start someone found
it
co someone found it they went right to
work oh
dear
all right first one is
okay oh wait I want to look at the
SH
[Music]
damn I'm lucky I'm
lucky but you can buy heart containers
in the shop right I think I saw it so
you could make it a little bit easier
for yourself with this with the hard
container y it I almost had it I just
kind of jumped into the
[Music]
pole
or is that it oh did I do
it
oh I'm thinking about what they
get I'll think about
it a triple moon but is it a star then
in the in the in the peach World cuz
they only take STAR no never mind that's
a different yeah that's the purple coins
I'm confused but it's still I I
collected a star already is that the
same thing
now or do they just look like Star I
don't
know is this considered the same world I
I I don't
understand but we
didn't can you enter again like in Super
Mario 64 and like it will be something
else
or
rats get out of here
pissed this is Peach's castle you're not
allowed here you're not tolerated
here I wanted to do like a circle
spin hat
thr
oh
where are we going what where
what oh was it
just just was it just for me to reach
him and the egg is it just for
up
Yi right shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake where is this
also just for me to get up
there and find something
[Music]
there there's a star
thereare oh wait there's probably also
one up
here right I can't
see don't trigger me
[Music]
I think there has to be a moon for every
SC yeah I think so too this how you
would get that
balloon I guess but like there shouldn't
be any stairs there to help you
oh
yoow what I'm not getting anything for
that just a little text from the
Hat
lame
but wait he jumps towards
where well the opposite of where his
head is right
so no he doesn't I got it
wrong oh ow well yeah I don't know
how to reach that but
y oh I be him oh I wanted to ride him a
man
okay he run so fast he runs like
[Music]
Mario no
no
so I don't think there's anything to
race here this is just the help you have
to activate to get anything you want
from a pier is my guess but I could be
[Music]
wrong he's so cute he is so cute yi yi
yi what can I do with Yoshi now um there
was that one passage but there's there's
there's water there I'm not sure how how
we could
reach this
here I'm sure that's for Yoshi
right but his tongue is
not just a little is that not
bad oh wait there's other fruits here oh
he can eat that too wo bounce wo go my
Yoshi is amazing I guess I did see other
fruit too we could check the other fruit
out as
well where was that shallow enough for
him to walk in
really so cute I love you so much I love
you see you don't understand I love him
you see skin
on so this he can eat
oh wait does he get like
juicy does he get the ability
to is he getting
thicker does he get the ability to spit
it
out
no I think he's the same size
still but we want to fill up that juico
meter don't
we good job Yosi good jump be careful I
don't want you to die can yashi go on I
guess not
right cuz he has to throw his hat in
order to get on the
bike yum oh down there there's also one
so how do we make Yoshi oh we have to
drain the water we have to drain the
water then maybe all the other things
will also be
oh ah that's where a
star interesting okay another
hold that's what we made him juicy for
but okay I think yeah once we drain the
water we can get all the other things
things that are unaccessible for him
right
now here we
go I'm kind of tired though guys like I
don't know how long I'll continue
playing this I'm pretty tired why does
he have a cowboy hat
on oh
not Yoshi I guess you're going to
disappear but I need this nut and I
can't let it go goodbye
Yoshi enjoy your life life without me
you don't need me to exist you're your
own dinosaur
whatever yeah we should go inside for
sure one more yeah I could do another
Odyssey stream if I need a filler I
guess if I don't end up playing a lot
off
screen oh wait another person
can uh it's still
searchable I get coins let's go it's
still searchable even though somebody
already found it
oh wait where was this thing did I
missed it was it up here oh
yeah oh they failed I whoa okay I also
get notified surely when
somebody wins it
right what if I'm not online then I
won't
know
what was that
for this one hits shef hat
why see have cave I think some of
Yoshi's favorite food is back there yeah
but I mean look at the
water don't you dare I think toad has
stood out for for
Yoshi basically I think he wants me to
kill
Yoshi trying to tell me oh maybe bring
Yoshi here cuz I'm sure he'll enjoy the
food and then I'll bring him and he
dies from the
water is he still there I
wonder probably
not he's
gone
sh okay let's go inside
though yeah yes the chef says he he
probably wants to cook Yoshi into
something
Mario
[Music]
princess she wants to be chased all her
life oh my God though look at that oh
the camera doesn't even want to move
nice Oh that's oh her throne is
there oh they got rid of the doors okay
so there's no level
here no I want to go on the slide I want
to go on the
[Music]
slide
no no no what is is
this I don't know I don't
care you guys are idiots you toads are
idiots pet is an idiot everybody's an
[Music]
idiot she just wants to be chased she
wants people to worry about her oh
Toadette
cute hi Mar looks like you're in another
big adventure that's great archus just
like shy I hope you don't mind but I've
been traveling the world keeping track
of your achievements I stalker I've also
got power to give you as rewards for
those achievements oh you're already
completed rescue princess page
scut thank you yeah of course I did
otherwise I don't think I would be
here you can also say the names of the
P you'll get for all of your
achievements I'll add some hints to the
palmon list which you can see by
opening
okay
byebye oh
[Music]
wait I see the light I see I'm sure I
see
it I can't look any
[Music]
higher
you guys know what I'm looking
[Music]
for I can't I can't see it I can't see
it
[Music]
clicked
no I'm going to
[Music]
cry no it's just a
yawn well that that's pretty
emotional
a oh
man that's so cute that they thought of
that but of course they had to if they
put that rock there I mean they they
have to know people want to look up and
find
something that is so sweet I love them
Marry Me Marry Me you're so cute marry
me oh my
god oh oh it's a
parot hi
what is the secret you're seeking I know
it I know it I can't tell you but I'll
give you a clue Rumble and crumbled in
rematch it's hiding somewhere you shut
up I don't know how you are supposed to
be helping me at all
like he was telling me any available
Stars
wow T
dree
w
w w
[Music]
Missy W I'm so happy here it's like a on
a
vacation the fra have a good race oh
there's a race
here not in the mood
maybe I want to try to get on top of
Nessie again though let's see pre moldes
yeah it's a different kind of vacation
it's like a nerd
vacation makes you happy
you you know into this kind of stuff
okay let's see let's swim
together okay oh oh I'm
sorry I thought I could like get your
hat off and put my hat
on how do I swim with
you what I don't
understand
what it's it weirdly seems to be
enjoying that
though this just decoration
oh another boss fight uh a
refight this one oh was it easy
[Music]
originally wait wait I don't remember
what was this one like a wait ah no not
this one I hate this this one yeah okay
I remember my memories are back we're
even in a different area what the
what wait are you telling
me the the only place where I can charge
and go back to is that little ass
Pond
huh what of course I'm going to run what
the do I have unlimited
water oh rain
okay oh no okay and unlimited seems good
good seems
good okay we can give it a
try guys do I have many super chats to
read up on I I'm not sure I don't think
I do
right
camera sort of kind of like four streams
oh the the upcoming
ones there's a lot of collabs so I
should probably stay on top of
it
nice okay oh yeah wait I'm supposed to
yeah continue even when
he's cuz it's so white it's
sometimes hard to
see where we
are
if if I'm like above
him
nice
yeah it is bright as hell right there's
nothing you can tell
apart is he going higher I'm not sure no
and now he's lower
right oh he's zooming
am I going higher see I can tell I can't
tell did you see how I was like facing
upwards but you really wouldn't
know it cuz he's not really appearing to
be much further away from
me yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah nice
hey okay let's go just stay in the same
place
please hey why does this not count there
we go oh I did a more or less first
try more or
less will you give this one to me as a
first try think I deserve
it the other one was bigger struggle and
the original fight I had way more
troubles in the original fight
yeah
you'll allow it
okay
y
[Music]
nice we're at six hours now what there's
a second one e oh no that's just okay um
why do I not just come back out of the
the one that I went through the first
place I don't
understand let's check in here I didn't
check it yet did
I what fight are we having in
here oh a the one with the hands right
oh that one was
weird
[Music]
oh W who W Who ah ah I'm not I'm not
sure if I remember what I'm supposed to
do I climb on
it
wait I don't remember H what I the Hat
the Hat the oh yeah right oh yeah
right and
then
no can I still make it I don't know must
did that in
me uh just
Escape okay and the hands again oh I
mean yeah we have to make it land on oh
on one of the icy areas so that he hurts
himself it it happens every now and then
yeah me forgetting the main the main
gimmick of the
game con not not me forgetting but
considering it as
ow y y
y considering it as a function to do
something already lost a life so early
it's not looking
good
oh H H
[Music]
yeah
here oh
oh
[Music]
go
away one more but I don't believe in
it no no no
no h yeah right I forgot about that one
I hated that
[Music]
clap I hated
that
how do I what was the why did I was why
was I not able to do the jump that I
wanted to
do oh immediately immediately nice that
leaves us with an extra heart
basically it was at this moment that she
knew that she up yeah she knew
she
knew oh
oh oh
oh
[Music]
you a he's shooting with the other hand
right normally I I always get his left
hand interesting didn't realize that
[Music]
ever
no
no no he does it again he doesn't again
three
times
[Music]
oh here here here go
here
oh oh oh he switches s never mind what I
did it I did it that's
it clutch clutch clutch clutch clutch
clutch you know in German clutch is uh
clapping but you write it
differently
wow another triple
Moon Yeah he was congratulating me
clapping
[Music]
clapping nice
yes let's get out of
[Music]
here oh you
know I want to go to that like clock
level Super Mario
[Music]
64 I want to play Super Mario 64
just for of
[Music]
nostalgia all else is down
here there's the Apple oh wait can I
drain it if I just get rid of
this that make sense oh yeah that's
happening only
one it's not getting
lesso unrealistic but maybe it needs me
to remove all of
them
oopsie
ow he really bonked his head there
oopsie is there another
one W coins almost
50 almost half of them that are
available
apparently
I know know I did play it on the switch
before Super Mario 64 when I streamed it
that was on the switch right originally
anyway cuz I that was this like for some
reason time limited
sale okay this means that Yoshi is able
to walk in shallow
water there was this time limited sale
for
uh where are we going here for fre
different uh Mario games right there's
three different ones The Collection I
played it uh the Super Mario 64 one
didn't it also have sunshine and what
was the third
one wait what was the third
one
G
Galaxy oh my God I forgot about that you
know I would have probably
bought Galaxy separately for the
future
oh
dear oh
wow fter
[Music]
Mario we're going to try the shallow
water now and then we'll end it
soon
must get those coins
though does this heal me when I'm like
low on
health tati tati is
okay oh let's go what's in
here the dragon refight actually that
fight was pretty
let's see how they're trying to make it
more
difficult
B welcome
back oh looking cute from you little
tiawa no it's not a TI it's a crown oh
okay sorry sorry I didn't want to make
you
feel less cool Tiara's pretty nice you
can wear a tiara a b okay I'm sorry I'm
sorry it's not a tiara I get
it but what about a kiaha oh what it's
weird squiggly shaped
ah yo he gave me a lot of time I was
like doing weird
oh
no feel like it's really oh
slippery I get heart oh oh that's
hecking gener
I heart please thank you that's really
generous though oh my
God I have
bit I'm So Far
Away
wait no no
okay two
hearts uh uh
uh
no those
wasn't there one more knife left
in there that I didn't pull out now they
removed them okay is there oh there's
another heart over there go go go
[Music]
go w
w well it'll be like that sometimes
just let's pick
off hexag
[Music]
gon Here Comes El
squiggle mean mean very mean very mean I
think I'm destined to fail at that
one oh come
[Music]
on
nice you thought he said Mexico
Mexico let's go
Mexico get the hearts while I
can wow
I'll
squiggle will I fail
again what this one's so
[Music]
difficult
ah
yes
El squiggle is going to kill me El
squiggle El squiggle no please no oh
wait what if
I I so fire El quick oh oh no get up
Mario
I get get out
there
[Music]
okay I squigle time already okay
okay that's okay I think that's the last
one think we do
[Music]
I have bested you a second time Mr
Dragon your Tiara shall be
mine you better go back to
sleep and
wait until a Shrek or Fiona comes
along or perhaps a
donkey
wow I have two more boss fights that I
could
do
okay you know I stayed up so late
yesterday because of obviously Monopoly
and New
Year so where's the where's another one
that one I
did so I wouldn't go to bed that early
anyway and I don't really have to cook
so I think I can just throw together
some things I think from the ret
leftovers
oh oh nice nice nice nice nice oh what
about this that looks like
something no so I absolutely lost
Monopoly what the hell is
this even though
oh they searched for it but I guess it
didn't win
okay why are you not finding it it's
really
easy oh what does this bar
mean but yeah and
I why is it moving with me oh
here oh
uh do I have to get on top of
them
[Music]
wait I hate this I so I stand
there that's b game yeah um I been to
have I I had I've I've had
a a Monopoly Game of Thrones Game of
Thrones Monopoly lying around for
ages and
[Music]
how do I get back
in not at
all oh it comes
back and I never got to use it until now
we used it for the first time today we
unpacked it for the first
time and yeah I had to for the first
time poke out all of the coins the
monies ah it wasn't even real Monopoly
money that's kind of sad because I kind
of like the look of Monopoly money
some people say
Euros look like Monopoly
[Music]
money I say that is not true yum
yum wait for me no this I don't
want to say this can we go to another
boss
fight the tyell yeah I
I
[Music]
my money I obviously chose Tyrell
because they have tyr
Tyrell the figurines look really cool
and you know those um action cards or
whatever oh whatever those action cards
they
um uh they have a a special holder where
you can put them into and
it's none other than the
throne the Throne of the
game is the card
holder yeah which is really cool because
I was saying like to my friends you
could probably use
it wait what am I doing I don't know you
could probably use it as like a business
card holder or something like that even
that's a way to do
it so if you don't if not playing
Monopoly at the moment you can use it
for different things cuz it actually
looks really good all the fingers look
really
good all the
figurines wait I wonder where where
there is another BS fight for me to
do I wonder where to
go
I want to tell you tangents to
65 hey yo oh nice
catch you can probably afford the 64
outfit
now all
right was that with the um purple coins
right
I'm so tired why am I so
tired yeah I mean I could have afforded
that since a while ago but yeah let's
wear it let's match let's fit
in oh my God what an amazing Choice
here can't believe
it oh my
God I look amazing Flawless oh look at
that like a cuz he's so
[Music]
beautiful
nice cute look at his
[Music]
butt
wow what a butt what a great butt I want
to grab
it
the ca was
[Music]
confused it's so cute
man I don't know where to find what I'm
looking
[Music]
for it be work could it
be oh look at that would you look at
that here's my star let's Pi
[Music]
go Yosh in the cave oh you're right I
was going to do
that wait did I not already do
that main objective two more post game
areas no I
didn't
Mexico we love Mexico
I might end it
here okay let's do the Goomba thing
first and then end it
here we start with the triple or yeah I
think
so the Bonk sound is so
painful
yeah I could either come back to it or
I'll play some more off screen without
you
guys you'll never know until you know I
think we're already full on goomas
so now we got to like walk all the way
around she hates
us
no but but I do it because I love
you that's the Mario that made you my
oie
ah yeah I think this me playing Super
Mario 64 did get a couple people that's
star a couple people
into my streams back
then and Mario Kart as well how do I get
to you lady me lady I can't jump this
far I could probably bend over but how
are we going to do
this wait I should go through the water
I
guess oh
oh oh I feel like I didn't even need
like I could have probably done it with
one less go but even looking at the
height
[Music]
y oh look he looks so original like he's
the
OG holy
holy he looks so good oh what a man
what a man what a man what a man what a
very good
man what a man what a
man okay I think I'll leave it here and
then I Tang it a bit more for you guys
and then I read some super tantos
because um I I still feel like I want to
tell you more about my New Year's about
m
struggles and so on
mhm I say that and I keep on running
around this lady is unbelievable no
we'll end it Wawa has control over
herself and her body I am in control
over
myself I'm tired also why am I so tired
today my eyes so
[Music]
tired hokan did you hear what I said
before I cannot fall behind
also I have a messed up sleep schedule
right now I stayed up because it's New
Year's it's freaking New Year's and my
friends were over I stayed up until 6:00
a.m. okay
okay Hulan you don't have to stay up
with me if you don't feel like it
okay don't feel like you
know you don't have
to what what do you mean I am the one
yeah I'm tired yeah but this is my job
sometimes you got to do your job tired
it's
okay we have to permission to sleep no
not really but I
mean if you're going to like complain to
me about that then you better go to
sleep
first
so let's go let's Pi what the
what
happened oh I went on hyzer and I was
like the first page that opens is like
the one from like currently ongoing and
recent streams and I saw
like 20 deleted vots I'm like what the
I understand yeah they canceled
their
streams I've never seen this before
Oh
[Music]
M
where okay um
[Music]
so sock puppet
finale
Odyssey and close for Advent and
[Music]
today oh yeah that reminds me ah one
more thing I wanted to talk about before
I put in some bgm did you guys hear did
you guys notice did you see that uh the
they uploaded
a a uh let's go in my YouTube history
they uploaded um what do you call it
again like
a like a teaser of all the honeywork
songs and in case you didn't hear it yet
let me let me let you listen to mine and
koop's teaser of our song because there
won't be a music video so you'll only
get to hear it once the CD releases I
guess which is uh it says uh I think
what did it say yeah February 28th so
this is is the only I guess the only
snippet you'll hear from it until the
release here go
[Music]
ahead
that's already
it but I'm hoping that those Suki Suki
Suki Suki I mean it was like created
with that in mind I would say there's a
lot of those like calls possible calls
um so I hope people will listen to it
beforehand to like remember it if you go
to the H honey concert then please
listen to it and then feel free to
scream really loud like such cheers like
su su there will be more of that even a
lot more a lot more it's very focused on
that
I want to hear people really loudly
screaming in the whole venue
so yeah that would make me really really
excited it's a really cute
song Let's listen to it one more
[Music]
time
oh good job guys good job pretty
good Moto I need
more
everybody everybody has to join
in
[Music]
nice that's my song with Bo me and
yeah the other songs also sound really
nice the one that surprised me the MO is
the one from Bales because I feel like
um most other songs have really strong
horror uh honey Works Vibes but the ones
from Bales I feel like they tried to
make it fit Bales a lot and went for
that like I don't know K-pop VI not
really K-pop but like listen this is
this is B's
song in the teaser you don't really hear
her sing
even it's very
EDM oh
[Music]
she okay I never heard a honeywork song
like that that's wow they should make
more stuff like that looks it sounds
really
nice but I guess the the chorus is like
mostly instrumental so you don't hear
much of her in the in the
preview but it gives you a good uh idea
of what it's going to be
like but yeah all the songs are really
fun and then of course there's also the
the cover uh album that they're
making uh with some more whole life
members involved yeah yeah yeah
yeah and oh I'm excited it's going to be
a while until it's out though like two
months ooh can't wait can't wait can't
wait I already pre-ordered mine thank
you thank you very
much B has a birthday this year
oh I mean I mean I mean she always
celebrates it anyway but what do you
mean
because how long is February this year
29 is it is it a leap
year it's a leap
here oh
oh
wow
ohh yeah that's that's good good for
[Music]
her so we listen to some more Mario
Super Mario odys OST while we read the
super chats what could we listen
[Music]
to jump up
Superstar it's
pretty that's better
[Music]
[Applause]
jump with
me jump jump jump jump jump
[Music]
jump I like that this got a ribbon game
in ring for adventure
it did I don't know about
that okay I'm going to read the uh super
chats from the sock puppet
theater uh oh wait I should go into my
room uh or should we go
outside what what's happening
here why did I make it so
[Music]
small you go here or here
where do I have the
picture I have the
picture I'll just download
it oh
oopsy
[Music]
more things for my download
folder wait there it is ah God damn
it now I have a double in my download
Pho okay reading
[Music]
time I didn't see you were in
here
[Music]
we played the game I'm so happy my first
Super Mario game that we cleared let's
go I'm so proud aren't you guys also so
proud wow nobody thought it would ever
happen I mean besides the RPG
[Music]
game
yeah never would imagine this in
2020 does mean you'll clear all the mar
NOP
[Music]
never I'm all grown
up all right let's read these Bab babies
Jacob 47 SP than for the pinky no was
this when crony died she didn't die she
fell into a
coma thank you spank and high for the
support on the video I appreciate it it
was it um I'm I'm proud of my work
really thank you I think this is really
something I I want everybody to watch I
hope everybody has watched it more and
more people person may be over but
nobody can miss out on that
video Take It Monkey D Dominque K marus
men I am a T Jackson FB d j d Dr hell D
Dominic K thank you for the pinky I
didn't expect to genuinely cry and cry
and laugh from the bottom of my belly
time to spend my time with even more
loved ones in the coming days and thanks
for making this come true K thank you
for helping
yay yeah
it's it's a how to say team effort of
course but waa
was wa was the brain behind
[Music]
it well thank you so much and I hope
that your Christmas was wonderful the
day you spend with your loved ones
that's that's nice to hear that you did
that I'm glad I'm happy for you now the
project is over so we can all chill and
relax I mean at least the team that
worked on it that's what I mean so take
your time and relax and
enjoy the nice feedback of the people I
suppose Jim Tracy m d g d j and be thank
you I did
cook I did cook on that script I guess I
really thought people would find it scri
h script SC cringe can't
talk yeah I can't talk that's it I can't
I just can't talk but yeah I thought
people would find it cringe but then
once I had the voice lines I felt
more more and more hi
Smo um proud and confident what are you
doing what are you
do say
hi
[Music]
wheel I have to wash my
hands
[Music]
[Applause]
Co
[Music]
doesn't that feel familiar to you
guys that's why she said hello in the
first place she was just on her way from
her toilet is
[Applause]
it that
girl wait I want to wait can she like
shut up for a little bit I want to I I
forgot I wanted to talk about um uh just
just for a moment tangent about my new
years I'll just put up this picture
for
imagination oh actually I also have I
took some pictures of the of the
Monopoly session too but well you don't
really need to see that but so so um we
ate the recet like first one of my
friends came earlier to help me cut a
few things but before that I was like
cleaning and preparing everything and
and then we worked a little bit together
and then more of my friends came and
actually there was a little bit of drama
beforehand um some misunderstandings
about who is attending which which end
of the year party and all that someone
thought maybe they're invited but they
weren't and then they were like oh now
we're
separate so there was some drama there
was kind of
weird um and also not all of my friends
were there like last year uh on New
Years cuz I wasn't in Austria I think I
said to my best friend next year we
spend it at my place okay and she was
like yeah and then um somehow that was
forgotten because I also in my mind it
was like ever since then it was like
100% certain and I didn't bring it up
again until much I mean every once in a
while I think we talked about it maybe
but uh then recently when it got closer
to New Year's um I didn't talk about it
only one of my other friends remembered
it as well um and most of most of the
others forgot so uh by the time that I
like talked about it she already made
other the plans so we were just four
people because of that but that's okay
we had a cozy cozy come together get
together
uh and uh I I made everyone dinner
basically
yeah and after the food we were going to
we still had some time until midnight
but we like started looking up the
Monopoly rules and like reading through
the the guide and all that and unpacking
all the little little things but then it
was
already getting so close to the midnight
so we had to I was like guys we have to
stop we have to stop we have to like get
ready and so I prepared like the glasses
I actually also took a sippy sippy from
the really really really low
alcohol
um uh what's it called Sparkling V
wine Lighty
flavor yeah I didn't really like it but
I took like one small
sip
it was I mean I know I mean I wouldn't
really want to drink it but it was okay
it was it could have been worse way
worse way worse it was really really low
alcohol anyway
mhm but yeah I have some glasses I have
wine glasses for red wine white wine and
sparkling wine just for the once in a
year occasion when it's necessary so I
brought out the glasses I had the exact
amount actually I only have four
sparkling wine
glasses mhm and then we I yeah we we
poured the glasses and we put on some
warmer clothes and then we went on the
balcony to watch the fireworks and we
have I have to say I have pretty good
damn good view and so that's why I
wanted to
like spend it at my place at in the
first place because I knew I had a great
View and last year my brother was
enjoying it and told me it was really
really good so I was like a next year I
have to stay at home and invite all my
friends because I want to see the
fireworks in my place that was the plan
all along that was the meaning behind it
were your cats doing fine yeah like they
started already like uh firing a few
fireworks here and there in between like
before uh
so actually surprisingly smoothie the
one who's usually The Brave One got kind
of scared and she was like hiding uh in
the in my closet most of the time and
then chunkers actually even during when
it was getting pretty busy in terms of
fireworks she was like out in the open
basically also during the whole dinner
party she was like sitting above us on
the on the ceiling thingy platform yeah
just sleeping the whole time she was
surprisingly Brave normally she's also
like really she's really shy and she's
really sensitive to sound but weirdly
enough she didn't mind so much
eventually she also like was a little
bit like maybe this is too much and then
skidaddled but she she kept she stood
her ground quite long um wow it was kind
of cute to see smoovie scared
actually yeah so uh we went to the
balcony we closed the door behind us and
I saw like chunky wonky was like looking
at
me really curiously through the window
glass and it's like oh is she okay but
she didn't seem scared she was just like
what's going on why is Mommy
outside yeah and then we watch the
fireworks and it it looked really nice
it was really difficult to capture a
picture um but I mean even if I would
have taken the proper one not like I
could have shown you so that picture
that I uploaded was actually quite nice
cuz I apparently like moved really
swiftly when I took a picture and that's
what came out of it the one I uploaded
on
Twitter yeah then it went Kaboom Kaboom
Kaboom and I actually missed the moment
I was like really distracted we were
like
one of my friends is looking for some
countdown radio or something on the
phone and then it seems like we found
one but then like 2 seconds later the
countdown happened and people above my
balcony were like screaming like and I'm
like and then we're like oh oh oh oh oh
it just happened oh what the like
we didn't even we didn't even really
like register it yeah I wasn't really
aware no I wasn't looking um my no I
didn't want to look at my phone because
I I I think I had just the camera on so
that I could always take good pictures
of the of the fireworks just in case but
yeah then I kind of missed
it but then we quickly went like cing
cing cing on the glasses we toasted I I
tried to say something nice like I hope
we can be friends again and continue on
this year do some fun things said
something stupid and then yeah we
watched for a while it went Dawn for a
while so I tried to look at the
fireworks as much as I could could we
stayed out I think for like 15 minutes
was too cold so we went back inside and
we started
Monopoly and that was like basically 10
minutes past midnight when we started
slowly
[Music]
and it
took I was the first one to drop out and
then it took a while until they finally
finished they were done like after 500
a.m. like soon after I uploaded the
schedule actually or right right around
when I uploaded the
schedule yeah and I actually I was able
because there's a funny rule in the
guide book it says the person who most
recently watched The Game of Thrones
episode starts first one of those
friends
didn't watch it at all apparently at
least not past the first episode and the
others haven't watched it recently or
haven't even watched uh um House of the
dragon and I said I watched House of the
dragon at least so that was my my ticket
to starting first so I rolled first and
you know that is a big Advantage if you
get to go first in Monopoly or even
second
but yeah if you go third or four if
you're a little bit so it started
off great I was like ahead of people but
somehow you
know I think in every Monopoly game the
order of the properties is kind of the
same like you start off with the the
first fields are the brown ones then is
um yellow H not yellow light blue and
then another color I think pink and then
it was uh orange and then you go around
that the second corner and that's where
Red is and until red for some reason I
didn't land on
anything what I could
buy it was messed up even though I went
first and then I went on red and I
bought the red of course I think I
landed on a on a religion maybe that I
also bought before I got the
red so then I landed on red but then
like after that I also kind of like I
think I had some other
unlucky things happen where I just
either didn't land on buildings or I
landed on the ones that were already
taken cuz people already were ahead of
me at that point or I went to the jail
and so on I got monopo really early on
yeah um but I did get one cool card that
let me eventually take or like trade I
did I think I did get one of the light
blue
ones um and the red one red one So
eventually I traded one of the light
blue ones with someone else's red one
and got my second red and eventually I
was able to complete my red collection
but by the time that I had my red
collection which was pretty good cuz I
think I was either the first or the
second one with with a full collection
cuz then you can start building houses
which are Towers in this case but by
that time I think everybody else had
maybe not a full collection but a lot of
different other colors and all I had was
one Rel religion and a full red
collection and the religions were really
really cheap like you land on a religion
if you have one religion you only pay
one coin to the religion owner if you
have two religions there's four in total
it gets more and more but even at the
most it really isn't worth it and
somehow nobody was ever landing on the
religions anyway so it's pretty pretty
useless yeah I think the blue one was a
good trade because I knew I thought
really hard about it cuz that person uh
would have had to first get the last
blue the last light blue also from
another person so they were like
scattered they would have to make an
effort first to get even more light blue
like I wasn't like completing their Blue
collection
basically yeah so that went on for a
while like I started building really
hard on red and everybody was getting
scared of my red section but they also
barely landed on it so I wasn't making
enough money
and I I I eventually was able to build
Four Towers everywhere and then even my
first Fortress after four Towers you
upgrade to a fortress or like a castle I
did that and after building my first
castle that's when I started running out
of money and I kept on landing on like
expensive uh um greens
and was it dark blue or something like
that the last couple of um fields on the
map that are the most expensive
ones yeah it was really bad and then and
then when I was already doing pretty bad
and already like trying to sell things
um to get money
back what one of the most at the moment
uh rich
people on the
board got a card that was referencing
the Red
Wedding like explaining some lore about
Wedding and then
saying you
take uh something like you take you can
take someone's
full like color Road whatever the all of
them all of all of a complete row of
their cards basically including
including everything they've built on
top of
it and you know how I only had red and
maybe one religion that was
useless so
um yeah their first choice was to go for
me like everybody was looking at me and
I was
like was like eh no you're not going to
do that right but but there were want to
do it but then eventually I I I like
like the others were also like oh that
would be kind of sad because then she's
going to have nothing to do for like
another one or two hours and she's going
to even though she's the host she's just
like you know maybe we shouldn't do it
but then ah it makes sense you should
you should do it you should do it take
hers and then I started like because
they were feeling pity I started like
manipulating their minds a little bit
too I was like you shouldn't take mine
because I'm going to I'm going down
anyway right now you should take it from
the strongest on the board your biggest
rival yeah and eventually my mind
manipulation worked
out it worked and they ended up winning
I lost anyway but they ended up winning
and maybe maybe oh no but the funny
thing is okay
so so they changed their mind they don't
go for me they go for someone else uh
who was the biggest other rival and take
like one of their full sets one of the
most valuable full
sets and I I don't know if this is even
a card that also exists in the other
Monopoly in the normal Monopoly because
it sounded it was pretty rough everybody
was shocked everybody was
traumatized and yeah the other person
was fine because they still had so many
properties but um
the turn ends moves on to me because I
was after that I do something and then
the turn ends and goes to the person who
was just robbed the victim of the red
vedding and then she remembers they
remember that they had from a long time
ago a
card that can block that can do like a
Uno reverse no you oh basically not
reverse but block whatever someone else
was trying to use against you and she
forgot to use
it but everybody was so shocked about
what just happened that we said okay we
can go back in time and let you have it
let you use it and everybody's happy
because even the the the one who used
the card was even feeling bad about it
and it was kind of like wow that was
really intense that was kind of a like
at the end in the end game this card is
just too powerful we can't do it so yeah
the no you block card was used in the
end even though it was too late and it
just it just made it like as if it
didn't happen in the first place so yeah
they got back the property everything
was normal
again yeah and then we went on and on
and it took a long time I I was like at
some point it was pretty off obvious
that I had no chance anymore so I just
wanted to like end it but it was kind of
complicated to think about like if I
just quit like resign
now like we were really tired and like I
didn't want to like calculate like who
gets my stuff like can I give it to the
bank blah blah blah so we just like step
by step went with the method of like me
selling like every turn and I needed
money I just sold more of my towers and
slowly slowly after like a lot of
painful turns of counting I was the
banker I was the banker too
yeah um but yeah after a while it was
finally over slow very slow death and I
was like okay that's fine and I watched
them for a while longer but it was so
slow eventually I I was like sorry guys
can I do you mind if I go to my PC to
make my schedule until you guys are done
yeah I watched them for a while longer
because it was actually fun even
watching them it was a really really
dramatic game and we should do stuff
like that more often
honestly
well um I don't know how do you resign
in Monopoly like cuz if somebody makes
you bankrupt they get all of your stuff
so I was trying to avoid that uh because
I didn't want to like make someone
really powerful I mean all I had left at
that point was my red properties but it
was a full line
so throw your money and flip over the
board do you leave the table no but what
happens with my things like when they
land on those fields who gets the money
you know like what what happened you
know and all of that was just too too
complicated to think about at 4: or 5
a.m. 4:00 a.m.
probably yeah it goes to the bank right
but like I don't know we didn't want to
think about it so we just let it happen
slowly yeah but the Figures were really
cute really good looking and the prompts
the the the action cards or whatever uh
they were pretty well written there was
one that really pissed me off even
though I think I only lost like three
coins silver coins that's like one
silver coin is like the minimum and then
there's gold coins too which is 10
silver coins there was one card that
pissed me off because I was a Tyrell and
I think you could also be a Lannister I
think we had a Lannister on the board
and I got a card and I was excited cuz
every time you put get a card we did a
thing like there's there's this sound
boox with batteries inside and and when
you push it it plays the soundtrack of
Game of
Thrones so every time somebody was
taking a card we press the button and we
were really excited
like it was really fun so I got exced
excited everybody's going
like and I take the card and we read it
out loud and it
says it says atan always pays their
debts you have not you but like pay atan
always pays her deps pay everybody on
the board one
silver and I'm like yeah but I'm not
Lannister like you give people these
figures to choose from to play as I
chose
Tyrell uh someone else was I think
Barian and we had a stark and I think a
Lannister so I was like wait are they
really talking to me
though doesn't I mean I took the C but
doesn't say that it says at lanister
pays your debts why am I paying I'm a
Tyrell like shouldn't the lanister be
paying it what the and then I was
trying us just kind of desperately
trying to turn it around and be like hey
shouldn't you be paying the Deb like and
then they're like nuh-uh uhuh I'm like
but I'm not a laner what is this
phrasing on this
card I I shall not be slandered as a
Lannister my
God you're the host you make the rules
no we went with completely like the OG
rules we also didn't do the thing that
like even though we questioned it like
if this is a thing or not but we looked
it up when you land on the go if you get
the double amount of money
no you don't so we also didn't do that
you know don't act like the Tyrell don't
have money
though well Tyrell never pays her
Debs the T yeah
yeah my my wife married a lanister but
she's a business lady
okay Tyrell sends there
regards when you play Monopoly according
to the acttion r it doesn't it usually
doesn't last that long it lasted
endlessly it was kind of
crazy it crazy but everybody was so into
it like after like 3 hours of playing it
it being like 3:00 a.m. we were like n
you know like I know it's like really
late and maybe we should pause
it but at the same time everybody's so
into it right now we should continue
Until the End 1 hour later 4:00 a.m.
yeah now it's getting even worse and we
didn't think it would be this long but
we're this deep in we have to end it 1
hour later yeah okay okay it's only two
people left on the field and it's going
back and forth back and forth kind of
weirdly but we really should end it
because like we're almost there and so
it goes on and on until yeah 5:00
a.m. yeah we had fun because we normally
don't play board games like this we
don't really do stuff like this even
though we should cuz it's fun we should
we we should do it more often yeah okay
that was what I wanted to tell you we
had fun then I I let them go all this
time like I was of course like in
between or before Monopoly I was
cleaning the kitchen I was cleaning all
the fins oh my God cleaning stuff after
recket is such a pain in the ass so many
plates so many also leftovers and I have
to go back into the fridge had to had to
clean the grill which is
annoying yeah it was a lot of
work but actually my apartment ended up
still looking pretty clean after they
left no oh then one more thing I wanted
to
say this is
funny like I think it was like 10
minutes or so
before midnight so the thing is my
brother
actually because he really liked the
fireworks uh last year from my place he
he asked if he could bring friends and
watch them again at my place
basically from like a kind of like a
public space
area um and I'm like yeah sure here's my
key uh so he was bringing his friends I
don't know who I didn't meet him I
didn't meet his friends he I said you
could say hi if you want for moment but
he he end up not not coming by to say hi
which is fine like maybe he felt awkward
about it that's fine he did call me
immediately after um midnight
immediately who's the first one to call
me or the only
one uh but
like uh so he was there right and then
he calls me 10 minutes before and he's
like yo wa wa sister um do you have any
alcohol we don't have any
alcohol and the the the the the tank the
car stop place where you clean your car
and where you put gasoline and the gas
station there it is the gas station is
closed and do you have any alcohol and
I'm like oh but he knows that I don't
drink alcohol but maybe he was hoping
that I would have alcohol for my friends
there I was like no sorry I don't I
actually don't like we have this one
bottle but my friends are saying it's
going to be you know just enough for us
and that was
true yeah and I'm like I'm so sorry and
he's like really like nothing like maybe
a beer or something like no we have no
beer here no all we have is this one
bottle of
sparkling wine for four people just to
toast so yeah and and you're too many
people so I'm so sorry to disappoint
you it was funny cuz like on the phone
he I heard like he was like surrounded
by his Bros and
his his demeanor was very different from
usual like
not I don't know for me it was very
noticeably different he wasn't even
drunk right but like he just seemed like
he was you know in his bro
mode very different from his family mode
I don't think I I I I I haven't heard
him like this maybe since my childhood
is this how Bros act among Bros as
opposed to among family
members like he didn't like say anything
weird or so but he just like he talked
differently and and more like cool in a
cool way and also excited more more um
outgoing
way yeah and he was laughing a lot
like and I know I don't know you got any
beards
like something anything is okay I don't
know I don't know he was so open I was
like is this my
brother that was
funny who is
this yeah I asked him afterwards if
everything you know if he still found
alcohol or not if it was fun anyway and
then he said yeah no problem like no
alcohol but we still had a good
time
yeah it's not it's not even just a guy
thing people just act differently with
family and
friends I may I feel like I act pretty
like
sameish
[Music]
sameish I get that but I think I act
mostly
sameish
my sister's the same way when she's
drunk yeah well when people are drunk
they're obviously
different Bros feel the need to show off
a
bit well I act way differently with
family as opposed to
friends not a h you're aware of it you
know you're very close friends of
someone when they treat you like they
treat family yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah well the the friends that I am you
know usually with I've known them for a
very long time
now I'm
bleeding I I scratched my skin open
oopsie again no wa what did you do this
time no I just I scratched myself B too
much no it's okay it already calmed down
that was just one little bit of
blood okay let's read some now I kind of
told you I think pretty much everything
mostly at least from New Year's
yeah cats are good cats are happy cats
are
fine my my friends even even the one
who's not so much into cats who said I
don't
cats even she was like oh your cats
today she was today yesterday she was
very M mesmerized by my cats makes me
[Music]
proud okay let's
go uh Super Mario Odyssey from last
[Applause]
[Music]
time
H yeah my cats are so Charming they have
Charisma I love them I love them so
proud of them I'm so excited for waya
Anda to meet my cats cuz waa I met her
cat dolls and she you know was looking
forward to meeting mine it's it's about
time she said she was worried if if they
would like her I'm pretty sure they
[Music]
will they like anybody but chunk it's
just kind of like people get worried
that they scare chunky wonky but that's
not true you're not scaring her she's
just you know she's she likes being
chased just like
Peach yeah I'm introducing them to my
family Jacob 47 D Cruz D golden I thank
you for the
[Music]
rainbow congrats again on your fre live
it was
again it was trly legendary performance
born from Blood Sweat and Tears mm not
sure about blood but you were definitely
in pain yeah maybe no blood maybe no
blood
but very
painful I know how hard you worked on
this performance and I want to show you
genuine appreciation for everything you
do for us thank you from the bottom of
my heart K this is my contribution
towards the 2024 wa project thank you
and this week I rewatched all your Frey
concerts
I was thinking about my favorite
performances I love each one but the
chus for four blood hon Sparks I do your
pineapple voice fire wait like
all of
them it's all of them except like the
two threee Japanese
songs Oh T Captivate me the most T this
is one 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 nine examples that
you
gave CW is currently my favorite chus so
far looking forward to seeing
retrospective someday also as a fan of
mukat I was pleasantly surprised to see
you perform very ni culation I'd like to
make a poll and ask if you their
favorite W coros as well oh I really
liked how you sang T night in your
pretty showcas oh thank you oh wow
that's that's even further
back yes it's nice that each performance
offers a unique experience because there
are subtle differences in how you sing
your Originals every time oh really
thank you for listening to my chicken
tent just one last thing to add La I've
been wanting to write your fan letter
for a long time now I hope to make this
a real reality in 2024 but I need time
to think what to say that is my New
Year's resolution all right youve been a
long long long time but you know better
send it earlier rather than later cuz
it's going to take a long time to for me
to like see it
probably keep that in the back of your
mind
I don't write
anything like weird that could get you
bulked and ripped
apart for R circulation you know I feel
like you I've already seen it so many
times in other people's lives it's kind
of like a very often done song so I was
feeling pretty not hesitant about doing
it but you know the story I was just
scrambling for a
song that Aki Senai might know and yeah
that might make it easier for
her and I also already knew the Coro so
it was a big help for
me to handle all the coros that I had to
learn so it was kind of like my
emergency choice
but you know I have a connection with
bakar I love bakar and yeah so it's just
a bit sad that
like so
overdone but also like people when they
see it in the live I wonder if they feel
like kind of like oh not this song again
you know I want to avoid that but I
don't know if anybody felt like
that yeah Platinum disco would be really
cute too
not TI now we know it's special to you
no
way cuz I've always want to seeed from
you oh it's a classic I'm sure plenty of
people still get excited I did that's
good yeah maybe just having some songs
that you're familiar with is also nice
cuz like the other like for example the
other two Japanese idol
songs that I brought you guys probably
didn't know so you know
good to have something in there that you
do know
maybe so I'm not like we all watch every
3D live from everyone yeah that is I
guess true
you not everybody does that I thought
you would be never in that nice and
familiar
[Music]
[Applause]
category
[Music]
some of us only watch
anyway like you
huh sounds like cholia yeah I haven't
thought about it like to sing them uh in
the Fredy life yet because I just
haven't had many opportunities to do
that so there's like still many choices
and I I just I mean this is the first
time I really besides the Showcase I
really got to plan out something and in
the Showcase I wanted to do my original
songs pretty much only so I mean there's
just not really been much opportunities
for me to even consider that but it's
not a no for me although I think I
would mostly tend tend to do Idol songs
not anime songs because of the coros for
the Idol songs so I want to I want to
like show some appreciation and respect
to idle songs from Hell project that are
normally not being CH chosen to be
performed in other members Freddy lives
because they just don't consider it
either so it's like my way of also
showing my history that I have with
my love for hello
project and hoping that maybe they'll
see it and maybe I don't know maybe one
day or that that will help me with some
connections even who knows I mean that's
not really the goal the the main thought
behind it but I mean could happen I
mean bye bye by o bye bye bye that could
be a last song oh that that one's m
that one's good wait let me write it
down maybe
[Music]
um where's my where's my PowerPoint
presentation what did I name
[Music]
it if you make
a Google
PowerPoint like on slides slid it's
called
[Applause]
[Music]
slides I found it found my original
slide I've been working on it let me
just as a note as a possibility
[Music]
[Applause]
although
maybe not the next one but maybe in the
next next
one we'll see you'll see I'll think
about things it will take a lot of time
a lot of
planning okay let's go I want to listen
to something more calm please
though what about this
one that's not really that's not really
[Music]
call oh my hand is
twitching
[Music]
so
good new dunk Sy oh this one's good yeah
let's play
[Music]
this doesn't make me fall asleep but
it's also not too exciting thank you
golden again for the beautiful rainbow
mwah mwah mwah than you soon looking
forward to the letter in the future you
C Mike thanks for the pinky the sock
puppet is amazing goofy yet giving me
such a good time now that the Advent
calendar is complete thank you K and
everyone in Holan for making it possible
also thank you for always giving us
laugh and smile when we need them thank
you are you're welcome
to yeah it was it was a bit more
stressful than I thought even though we
like planned ahead quite a bit more than
before it ended up being a little bit
stressful here and there but it it
became a wonderful project and I'm proud
of all of the accomplishments and all of
the videos that everybody made they're
really cute really happy with what the
people did with it so I'm proud thank
you for checking it out every
day yeah and for supporting me and Holan
than you CH thank
rales oh I hope you cheer up cheer up
you have to excessive boot oh what the
300 thank
you at e fre they used to let people go
up to a k and ask Mario
questions it was basically a character
model that was red to react to the
facial movements of Charles Martin yeah
his VA at the time yeah while he was
remotely
[Music]
answering what e free which e free when
while he was R answering questions so in
a way you could say that Mario was the
original V oh cuz I when you guys first
brought it up I was like N I don't know
what you were talking
[Music]
about
holy that's ages
ago there were several events like that
oh my God that's so cool wait is there a
video of
that I have to find
it e fre Mario
uh what do I look
for Charles
Martin Mario this to Sony at E3 and also
does Impressions 1.6 million views
exactly wait I don't think I should be
playing this but let me just really
quickly
mute oh my God it's a
vtuber his nose even
St what
me he censored
himself with a coin
sound oh my
God
that
is
crazy let me show you the video just in
case you want to see
it whoa no my nose doesn't extend I
don't even really have a
nose
what the
hell that's not the old one there's one
whatever this
fine I see the one from 1992 s CES what
they put like some whole crazy looking
rig on his
face that looks like you're doing
3D face Mo up what the
wait it's like connected to his
face or oh they're they're like
definitely not making it the same way
we're doing
it that one's just a floating
head okay that's pretty funky that's
crazy oh he's like inside the camera is
inside of his face sometimes when he
gets too
close what the that's crazy
crazy that's so
crazy let me post this one
[Music]
too that's insane I didn't know
that I wonder if this is what like
inspired the first YouTubers
or if this if anybody paid attention to
this in terms of like oh maybe we could
do this with like an anime and make
videos or
stream like he's not ey was she inspired
by
this I
wonder
H very
interesting
wow okay that is some knowledge that I
think I needed in my life thank you
excessive boot I don't know if you're
going to hear this cuz I don't think I
normally see you around maybe you're a
lurker thank you so much for the big
Super Chat and the valuable
knowledge wisdom has been shared
emus wow I will I will show off this
knowledge to other people when I
can I still the F to
[Music]
up
mu
[Music]
wow wow wow thank you so much excessive
food you seem to be a huge Nintendo fan
cuz you have is that kitty Kong in your
profile picture I think it
is albino d y Channel D the gamer Creed
thanks for the pinky the soft puppet
finale was pure comedic gold Ki it was
so freaking well done both you and the
others did such a phenomenal job with
this year's Advent calendar and it sure
as hell was a fantastic fantastic way to
end it all oh we're all going to die I'm
so dang proud of you man thank
you thank you I'm happy as I said before
I hope I could make the holiday
season more enjoyable to the fans
So yeah thank you so much for watching
everything yeah I did my best I'm glad I
could provide something valuable
hopefully to the
community merry Christmas happy New Year
EV
Evans e who the is Evans Evans l d
Bruce D delar Dan boo 73 D morally
imoral D delar Dan Fred
[Music]
F what the is that
un chat thank you for two pinkies K I
finally became an armored chicken this
November I finally resolved some
Financial family issues that had been
ongoing since a while and that time you
have been a constant Source constant
source of Solas Solas Solas enjoy I'm
immensely grateful for that I can
say Oh that's oh I thought that was like
half or something okay I can say it was
certainly that 3 years ago I made one of
the best decisions of my life when I
joined K yeah you did you have been an
absolute blessing to me and others and
also an amazing Entertainer and
extremely funny as well thank you k I
love you
reasonably
reasonably thank you un Chad what a Chad
you're so sweet a I'm glad that some
issues have been resolved in your
life no troubles anymore
hopefully and yeah I think it was the
right decision I'm happy that you're
here every
day if you say I'm a blessing to you but
you're a blessing to me thank you for
being such a great chicken employee I
hope I can continue to entertain you and
cheer you up when you need
it
yeah I really really hope so I love you
reasonably too maybe maybe a bit
[Music]
more nice armor metal squat thank you
for two oranges that's like 60 bucks
thank you merry Christmas happy New Year
money was tied off the anime Frontier so
I had to wait until now to send this and
I thought why not make an orange
carpet it was awesome this is like like
more like um like a bath
mat sorry but I have to roast you like I
I I'm not ungrateful but I have to say
as a joke it's more like a orange bath
[Music]
mat I think that was a good
joke well I'll be forgiven
[Music]
right it was awesome meeting you at anim
froner at the start of the
month I got some phup questions question
from our meet and greet do you remember
ah wait I answered this right yeah yeah
yeah I answered
this thank for all the hard work you did
this year the Adam calendar became came
out beautifully and Cong on the frey
live it was spectacular I can't wait for
what you have in store for us next year
have a fun trip thank
you oh my you mean my my vacation trip
or what that's the most uh soonish
upcoming
one I'm so excited oh man I can't wait I
wish I could stay there
[Music]
forever I hope we can stream smoothly
there that's one thing that I won't know
until I'm there really but I mean it
worked last time so I guess should work
this time too I mean different Island
but now we're not even like on top of
the water
so maybe the connection is
good yeah thank you so much it's nice to
hear from you again SP d m a thank you
for the pinky T TBI only really has
Mario Kart for multiplayer but N64 has a
ton even Star Fox has a battle mode yeah
I checked and like people also sent me a
list GBA the emulator thingy doesn't
really seem to have a lot yeah um
probably can't play Golden Idol but if
you can't do it also reminded to have
nura bring her copy of I did I told her
to bring her switch and I'll bring my
switch as well so we have like the the
maximum amount of possibilities
yeah yeah it was quite smooth last time
yeah but were we moving or were we using
cut out like standing
pictures think we might have not been
[Music]
moving oh we were moving
oh then it was pretty good
then h
H you really got to convince her to try
tunic Co
[Music]
Nissa that would be good standy for the
first one in moving after
oh
nice well well we'll see what we can do
thank you so much M oh I guess I was in
the middle of that
Festival We'll add a thanish and fish
[Music]
El mon Brandon D comfy mag Z you know
what El see laughing cuz I'm going on a
break maybe I'll use my
coupon you should make a clip for me but
I don't know what you should make but
one that I can upload on my
[Music]
break not
sure well but I'll you know I'll do it
I'll um open my DMs to
you oh hey go I go Ro to
me
see if you have an idea you can tell
me so ready and waiting it's over now we
can talk about a
ceroni in the
future soon soon soon I have to upload
all the things I already have prepared
so as much as possible I don't want to
like even for uploading things I don't
want to I don't want to log in because
I'll see all the things that I don't
want to
see I have to avoid it at all costs and
prepare everything
beforehand we talking English w w she
wrote me a long long
[Music]
message
w w I'm going to
[Music]
cry
what no like something really sweet yeah
like also
[Music]
impressive I got check it out again
afterwards at
done she she
wrote cuz I I told her I have an accent
suit she asked me what tech I have I
said I have an accent suit now and she
she
said they can help me with my accent
suit I'm just like
wow D can you help me
cross
company my accent
suit you you know what I mean
like the only one in my company who can
help me
possibly is am but she doesn't even have
an accent suit so she would just be
guessing she'd just be doing guess
[Music]
work someone from another company would
help me if my ex it's just like oh
man it would be great I would be really
glad but like we just don't normally use
extents I just did that for myself so
obviously there's like not really anyone
who has experience with
it but they have experience with
it
damn
yay that's so nice of
them
yeah I'll I'll discuss off screen but
yeah not
much time at the moment I'm going to the
mold so soon I'm
[Music]
excited so sweet trying to help
me I'm honored I'm it makes me feel
emotional H where was
I yeah here ter d d d Tassimo thank you
for the red of chat I really enjoyed
your sock puppet show and the entire
Advent calendar all of you put so much
work into it and I think it turned out
great also did the other girls like
their Christmas games I also got or for
Christmas from my brother I haven't
tried them yet though oh nice good
choice uh I haven't been able to get all
the steam uh friend codes yet so I
haven't been like giving out the games
yet um but I should remind them I just
wrote like a general message like hey
everybody give me your friend code and
yeah I didn't get all of it so I was
like waiting I should probably remind
them V Hardware survey
no
survey wait I should oh I should buy
them now though cuz the the sale is
going to end ah you
B I need to check who codes I have and
who okay after the stream I'll check
that I'll see who I still
need
yby when is it ending does it say
[Music]
here uh January 4th ah two more days
okay okay okay okay you bought your own
games yeah yeah I bought a lot of
games cold
bin yeah it looks good but I don't
know I'm like hesitant to buy any games
where I'm not sure if I really play
them
10 no I only I didn't even let them know
that I'm giving them anything I only
wrote to like P and FAA I think to check
if they
have the game basically but with the
rest I didn't even check I didn't even
tell them I wanted it to be more of a
surprise but I guess I generally I wrote
a general message saying I did this I
need your friend codes let me send you
gifts anyway thank you
tasim Merry Christmas I hope you're uh
you you are going to enjoy Orie your
brother made a good choice there yeah if
you like the first one you have to play
the second one Nick bear d superan d wak
D what 20 20 wedding rings
super no one VH than naan thank for the
pinky my bird does keep my face notably
warmer and my beard why you have a bird
bird was going to ask you like what do
you mean your bird keeps your face
warmer do you mean me like what but I
don't usually notice how much until I
trim it down every couple months or so
and feel the raw chill of the
air it definitely blocks the wind wow
yeah I guess I can imagine cuz like my
hair on my head that part is warm while
my face is not warm when I'm outside
yeah so it makes sense makes a lot of
sense
makes sense I can I can
imagine oh if only you could have hair
all over all of your face like your
cheekbones and your nose
and your eyelids right if only you would
be warm
everywhere and you would also yeah look
like yeah
well and animal
probably more like a
monster
[Music]
chewbaca I mean we do have hair all over
I guess but it's not really
visible so it doesn't
[Music]
count have you done the pick your
fighter no what what why are you doing a
PN face do I have
[Music]
to I feel like I know what you're
talking about but at the same time not
I'm it's like just vagy in my
brain we technically even have stripes
what
what what are you talking
about silly silly aren't
you silly like it's in your name you
being
silly one of those Paws ah that one yeah
I think I saw it but I don't remember
what I
got I think I did it even I don't
remember
though Channel than I am Paul than thank
you money doesn't change who you are
just enbl you to be you more fre anyway
here
money actually may believe D check it
D oh yeah that one confused
me and Mish wow I think that's probably
in total pinky
probably or even more I don't
know miss you hi thinking back it's hard
for me to believe that I've only known
you for about 3 months now yesterday was
my birthday and I wanted to use this
opportunity to return some of the
happiness the people me said happy
birthday thanks to you I ventured into
this whole we rabbit hole and that was
probably the best decision I've made in
the last few years due to my shyness and
tendency to overthink everything I say I
used to always be a silent Observer but
thanks to the wholesomeness and
welcoming nature of this community here
especially KF I've really felt at home
and had to urge to become an active figh
of the community for the first time in
ages all of your efforts at the Advent
calendar the Christmas K the 3D life and
the streams were a big reason why I was
able to really enjoy and even look
forward to the holidays wow
I know that I still have a long way to
go to completely get through all the
pris I've been avoiding in the past but
you have become a constant source of
strength and joy that keeps me going
anyway I'm just rambling at this point I
just want to say thank you for
everything you do and wish you success
and only the best in the coming year I
can say with confidence that you my C
that take
yeah thank you I'm so happy to read all
of that thank
you yeah I'm I'm always glad when a
lurker comes out of their shadows and
and uh um you see like usually they only
have positive things to say after coming
out of the Shadows so everybody should
do it I'm glad you did it welcome
welcome thank you so much for being part
of kfp and I hope you're going to stay
here for a long time no pressure though
but stay
forever Tas you're welcome I hope you
grow into a beautiful chicken bucket and
then a beautiful hybrid chicken and then
a beautiful armor chicken
yeah slowly but surely going to cook you
slowly
yeah they gather their Sweetness in the
shadows they're charging to explode one
day yeah Matrix free BC danan crash SS
o1 danan free strap danan oh you also
started H in last month decid you should
be my first bang is oh I'm happy to hear
that welcome to the rabit ho and J
monkey oh hi
[Music]
a
hello welcome looking forward to having
you teach me the language of the Gods
soon hey yo we're going to read one more
uh super chat spy streamy thing this
one yay actually it ended up being much
shorter than I anticipated I don't know
why we went through everything so fast
the girls
didn't uh discuss that much but uh I'm
I'm happy with the
results the moment I saw enas I was like
ah
I'm like her designs are so
good I know I feel like I have like more
visions
in my brain that I'm just not sure like
on the skill level like how should I
draw it to even make it look the way I
want it to look um so I feel like I I I
could do more but I'm I still think yeah
my designs were great
anyway I want to redo the Nissa one cuz
you know we're we're wies and still I
disappointed her LLY with something she
didn't like at
all I did her dirty I have to redo my
nervous at
[Music]
design
disappointed n I'm so sorry I I am so
sorry I just thought you look great than
anything and honestly generally I feel
like it's it's good to have like variety
like yeah no you know pre references and
all that and all that but like I'm
thinking like for future streams you
know you want variety like after 3 years
I know like I need all kinds of
different looking
outfits so that I can fit the streams I
also want to my on my own I want to feel
like I have variety because I don't want
to wear the same clothes all the time
and all the same colors and all
that
so nah that is
false
and so I think it's good to like try to
venture a little bit into what would
what you wouldn't even personally IRL
wear that shouldn't even be so much uh a
huge Point anyway like would you wear
IRL like
[Music]
what not necessarily like you know I'm
not going to wear a bikini top
outside unless I'm on the beat but yet
here I often wear bikini top
randomly and like my my fancy dress I
don't know if I would like probably yeah
I mean obviously like
it like how am I going to even recreate
that
IRL so yeah I think um it's good to step
a little bit out of your comfort zone
event
to widen Your Horizon in terms of
outfits and I just think like she looks
good in anything especially cuz she in
within Advent she's the more mature
minded person and the the tallest one so
she will look great in pants
okay yeah like look at crony she's long
Mrs long legs in uh uh promise and she
has a casual outfit with long
jeans and she's absolutely rocking it
blue long-legged lady crony you see that
narissa you could be like
that don't be scared of the pants like
I'm honestly when I saw Cron's casual
outfit I was so I was feeling so
refreshed because like no no hate I love
the casual outfits that or whatever
outfits that Japanese members come up
with um but I feel like it's a lot of
skirts and like long jeans
pants
non-existent so
crony kind of like getting an outfit
that's like pretty normal looking pretty
realistic looking it's so refreshing cuz
like I just haven't seen anything like
that in whole life before
it's nice to she something more real
looking you
know and she's she's rocking it yo like
because it is so normal that's again
what makes it stand
out from all of the more detailed and
frilly and puffy dresses and all that
you know what I mean like that makes it
stand out and gives it a gift it it's
huge
charm you get it right all outfits have
its own charm but this is the charm of
crony's outfit because it's so normal
because it's so casual because it's so
realistic because it's
so basic not even basic I feel like even
an IRL that would be really like the
trench card with the long legs like she
would look like a superm model
[Music]
yeah the cat yeah the cat is really
awesome so yeah that's what I'm trying
to say
like it's worth it going for some
more normal and
different normal and different different
as and different from what you may
want well what you may think you want
but also yeah of course also get outfits
you want like I also also have gotten
like my first casual outfit that's
that's
basically what I felt like I needed but
it's also pretty simple right it's
pretty simple it's it's a blouse and
some shorts and some sandals it's pretty
simple but it gives me so many ways to
use it I can you know it fits whatever
it always
fits and I can keep on adding more and
more hairstyles and accessories to to
it and just yeah have so many choices
with it it's so versatile yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah versatile s this
name that's what I'm trying to say
that's what I'm trying to
[Music]
say
and I'm going to read the rest the Super
[Music]
Chat check for FAA thank you for the
rainbow good good evening waa today my
birthday I have good news I got the
fifth Fest ticket so I'll be there to
support you and stay in toky for a while
let's go thank you for all your hard
work throughout the year for the albums
for the life they were amazing also I
think the Adam calendar and the doo St
puppets were the perfect way to end the
year I love it when I was busy stressed
or tired watching your stream at home is
best to relax and recharge my energy for
tomorrow thank you you're my light waa
love sorry about last time I sent a bit
empty rainbow because I was sneaking to
the toilet at work for standing it
oh don't worry the toilet was very
clean happy New Year and K thank you
first little happy birthday
F happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday dear
FAA and a Happy New Year
[Music]
too
yeah
congratulations you snuck out for me
thank you hope you didn't get caught
hope no one's sussing you out a Fafa has
been sneaking to the toilet a lot since
3 years
ago H why are they going to the toilet
so often several times in 8 hours of
work this has been going on for years
now what could be the cause and somehow
they always bring their phone to the
toilet
H even
headphones
must be a stomach bug and they're bored
on on the toilet while having stomach
bug so they bring their phone also for
emergencies if they need to
call the
ambulance well well thank you so much
Papa thank you for being so
sweet and always so supportive and kind
I'm glad you're still enjoying my work
as much as you did on the first day I
hope thank you Happy New
Year thank you and have fun traveling
happy New Year J ra thank you for free
bankies let me
[Music]
think oh this will be the last I can
send for quite a while so I want to say
how much you mean to me as a role model
K you bring again this word what what's
going on is this trending this
[Music]
word solace Solace yeah that's what I
thought that's what I was trying to say
that's what was in my brain but I
couldn't get it out
Solace
Solace and where was I here
uh you bring
Solace wait you bring you bring Solace
to a turbulent
existence you patiently accept myself
and others despite our flaws and
mistakes any of the things you
accomplished this year would be a
miracle oh the fact you did all of them
is nothing short of astounding and you
deserve all the support for what you've
done this year so thank you for making
this year downright amazing happy New
Year Teno I accepted an offer I couldn't
refuse that might prevent me from being
here so often oh you got like a like a
better job or like a promotion but I'll
always be your loyal Chef if that's okay
and you'll always be my o have a great
2024 you out much love
what new
[Music]
job new
job better
job h huh are you here you can't tell
me
huh
Mafia
suspicious what are you wait did you get
a job at like
McDonald's because you can't tell me
guessing it's a rival
[Music]
company
are you spying are you spying you
spying are you spying for
me at
McDonald's for
me getting that info whatever spices
they
use I'm waiting for your
report don't you dare
disappear you little but good luck
with what you're doing whatever you're
up to good luck with it you're on a I
see and you shall go with your head held
[Music]
high okay well thank you so much for the
sweet words D and good luck
Mah sounds great I'm happy for you it
sounds like a good thing so if you can't
if you say you couldn't refuse it it
sounds like a good thing so happy New
Year as well sounds like this will be a
good year oh also you're working
on K car
I wonder what car you chose for it it
say missing
horn was she missing a horn I don't
think
so just like last time we fall and mo I
love the ideas from you too especially
love that you try really unique looks
and put effort into alternate
alternative hairstyles I want to see K's
hair with ena's outfit is a common
F Ki was hair with ena's outfit okay but
who's the person wear wearing it me with
ena's outfit or Ena with kiwa's hair
[Music]
huh not sure what you mean
but broken ah you mean the broken off
horn ah so well it's not
[Music]
missing I going say bble messaged
me uh and told me or did she say it wait
she didn't message me I think she said
it on
Twitter uh so I wasn't as private as I
was trying to paint it out as but she
was saying she really likes though the
Buns I'm glad I'm glad she likes the
Buns I think she will look really cute
and really big messy bunes or even in
small messy
bunes but I think she should cut off her
hair eventually for uh a future outfit
and I'm I'm sure she will like it's
always like the most exciting thing when
somebody who by default has super long
or super short
hair in a future outfit has that image
change and has like the opposite length
of hair that's always so exciting I
always look forward to that cuz it's
it's the the biggest thing like M like M
doesn't she look so Charming with her
bob with her shorter
hair that is the best
example M oh my God she looks great with
both but especially because of that
transformation because she wasn't like
having that shorter hairstyle since the
beginning that's why it hits so
[Music]
hard oh Iris too yeah Iris
also Mana too Ina
too everybody like such a big image
change how
[Music]
yeah my hair is just like always like
midlength like shoulder length so
there's not such a big wow effect for me
when I go long or short if anything I
think I can only accomplish that if I go
like like KNE length of hair or so or
[Music]
bald I have to go that far to get like a
wow effect I
think which is uh h a bit much but knee
length I I maybe I'll attempt that one
[Music]
time or like an updo like a wait I
already had an updo in my dandal
though H difficult
difficult knee length for even like
ankle
length but I feel sorry for the artist
who has to draw that if I do
[Music]
that by the way the new outfit is in the
works now with an artist that
uh hasn't ever worked with me before so
another new artist and I was I was told
I'll get the first draft at maybe in the
middle of the month first draft so
starting from there
maybe maybe
reveal March
April could be something around that
[Music]
time yeah but I feel kind of bad cuz I
gave extremely
detailed
um uh guidance so I'm not even giving
them much freedom I feel kind of bad I
mean I don't mind them trying out some
more things but the the the internal
side they were kind of making
me create a really detailed guide so
yeah it just kind of happened H next
time I'll give the art just more freedom
maybe that's a good thing you only get
this once a year yeah I mean I tell
myself the same thing but I feel kind of
bad for the artist but I mean they
accept it so know they are fine with it
then yeah yeah got to tailor it to my
imagination but I do want to see their
take on it I guess I I hope they
understand they don't have to like
follow everything like exact same way
and can add their own flavor to it
hopefully
[Music]
hopefully don't want to restrict them
too much yeah but yeah yeah don't want
to regret it
either so they won't have to redo
[Music]
yeah but then oh yeah I wanted to ask
you guys okay okay so
cuz this is already really delayed this
is supposed to be my 2023 outfit and
it's going to come out in Spring 2024 so
I asked staff if we can already start
planning the 2024 outfit in order to
like catch up a little bit and not just
start after this one is done and they
said yeah so they told me I can already
give them like my ideas and so on and
maybe artist wishes and all that but I
was going to ask you guys can you help
me make a
decision um I think I was uh I could
also do a community poll but I felt like
kind of awkward doing making putting it
in black and white on like
a
poll so I was thinking F I want your
help for the
F maybe I'll okay never mind I'll ask
you for members tomorrow in the members
stream I'll ask
you okay I'll ask you in the member
stream remind me remind me
I have ideas yeah I think I have like
two or three ideas of themes and I can't
decide can't
decide or maybe I can even combine them
I don't
know I yeah yeah okay wait I'll write
them down already cuz I going to I might
forget
[Music]
I think those are my two big
Ideas okay let's
go 130 already yeah yeah I'll just
finished this I'm almost done um
spankenheimer chat I'm imagining what
these outfits look like with cat for on
them 10 out of 10 excellent stream you
two are so talented thank you yes always
much get hair everywhere but that's a
good thing right that's that adds points
to the point system I would say thank
you spankenheimer glad you enjoyed
it I hope your cats survive the
fireworks if there's if there were any
hope they weren't too
scared did they have to endure
anything
they're
[Music]
fine are they just not scared they were
firers oh okay so they're just chill
nice that's good I'm glad give them a
hug for me and a I am a
be thank you Sky D Psy D Jacob 47 D
Andre d b
D did you add something to your name
there clond
[Music]
Saloon No he still didn't change the
name I don't know why you didn't do
it I'm still just saying the beep myself
even though it's not there in your name
don't know if you forgot about
it you never came up with something new
either out of ideas manual beeps TASC
yeah cuz especially like we found out
that I even if I wanted to I can't
change the the uh volume of the beep and
I've also
realized I can't combine
effects on this roadcast to De as as far
as I know on the goar I can combine for
example Echo with the
megaphone and and I can combine like
these key changes with whatever else and
the megaphone or so I'm going to combine
everything but I can't do it here like
more and more I'm I'm so unhappy with
this thing but there's not really any
better
choice and I also don't really like the
sound of the Reverb I tried like
changing things about it like there's
some settings you can change for the
Reverb you like the EQ of this one I
don't know it seems pretty same to
me but I don't like the sound of the
Reverb like the I think the go XLR
Reverb was better acoustic
sounding and more anyway it had so many
more options for everything for the
effects and for
everything I don't think I sound bad I
think I sound the
same sounds the
same the re are subtle yeah but the the
the stronger I make it no it it's pretty
strong I think I hear it very strongly
but it's like so it's too Echo it's kind
of weird I don't
know I know I can like record the beep
sound quieter and then map it onto my
buttons here
but do I look like I want to do that
no
so one of the where you can easily add
yes supposedly and I tried that uh I
think I was I was trying to do that with
headphones I think and then it didn't
work I was getting really close to
making it work but somehow it didn't
work I was trying to add my new what was
it
Sony uh headphones when I first got it
cuz I was having
issues with my normal headphones anyway
like attaching them to this road cter
that didn't work like I was getting to
the Bluetooth
thing but I don't know what I did
wrong I don't know what it is would be
nice if I could have used those
headphones the batteries really last
very long too of the Sony headphones but
I also I kind of want to use the hyperx
headphones more often because people say
that the hyperx headphones that I have I
think
are actually like
soundwise the one of the highest quality
headphones you can get for like within
gaming
headphones and I'm like
oh that
good maybe I should use it more
often
but I'm I bought a headphone splitter so
it should I think arrive on the day when
I'm collabing with wait hopefully I can
uh access it um and then I I hope I can
attach both headphones so that we can
sing Comfortably with headphones on and
not sharing
[Music]
earbuds
yeah yeah yeah
and right now I'm still using the pink
um cute one from
Razor they're so comfortable to wear for
a long time so I like them anyway I got
to go I got to go cuz I've been here for
too long and I need to figure out what
to do for dinner but it shouldn't take
too much time and but anyway it's been 8
hours it's uh almost 2 a.m. and had a
lot of fun and we played that game and
we fin that which is amazing um thank
you so much for um following this
journey I hope you had a lot of fun uh
if you like this British may but you
think it's unsatisfying don't worry I
will soon learn to be more British with
aura AA
Aura uh tomorrow is members only uh kind
of late in the evening so probably won't
put up the reservation until like
later uh like after I wake up yeah I
have some stuff to do during the
day um but I'll I'll be there and maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe I will be able
to sign some polar
Awards uh before before
stream
before
oh yeah I have to message the girls
about their steam cards thank you for
reminding
me H yeah please remind me again in like
on on Twitter in like half an
hour thank
you all right let's
go and in German we say I'll reader Shan
or something like that I don't know what
she keeps on saying that girl that
German girl oh yeah mococo she said she
said she answered when I was still on
call with
narissa and Moco said or fuaa fuwa told
me that Moco told
her that absolutely she would love to
wear a skirt like it is absolutely up
her
Alle and like totally like
absolutely and I was like seeing the she
like yeah of course well I yeah I
guess I kind of knew it and I'm like
yeah well I told you I'll told
you and
then I asked some more I talked a bit
more I talked a bit more with Mo go go
and for wa after that like I I asked him
some questions and cuz I was curious
about future outfits like what are they
thinking about and all that just kind of
asked for their
faults just had a little
in in in
interaction yeah right tell y
yeah
obviously stop it please oh does it hurt
you be honest you like the pain I'm
going to go now let's go
[Music]
bye
I don't understand why anybody would
ever have a problem with my beautiful
accent I put so much effort into
it even the kiss was British
right so
[Music]
British
bully
bye
[Music]
boy boy
boy bab bang bye bye
Bab
[Music]
hey hey
baby 2 a.m. brain be
like no I'm
normal it's not even 2: a.m.
[Music]
yet okay
bye