foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
one by one and we test each other's
audio in each other's streams yes
am I loud am I quiet what do you think
guys on the other streams
to me
next up who wants to go next
uh hello testing test test test Emilia
Watson hello hello everyone whoa whoa
okay thank you
I'll make flight thank you for that
[Music]
okay I raised them I'm gonna say
something again
casting hello one two three hello
all good okay
next up
howdy check once oh wow that was loud
for me dang
yeah it's a clappy Mario first practice
Grim Reaper you guys know the deal hey
what's good please die that's all
right yes the ones today I don't want to
die a second time today okay well you've
already filled your quota then so never
mind
[Music]
all right
somewhere I don't know
yeah okay okay yeah that's what we're
doing
nice
I'm very loud in my own ears though uh
gurus muted of course
is that not just the way
I'm going to throw my mouse
oh no not the mouse why did my settings
hello
all right OBS decided to set all my
audio settings to default for some
reason
it didn't start history oh yeah oh yeah
yeah don't worry you guys keep going I'm
just setting up the Discord thingy still
okay okay Emma will be live in a moment
yeah
live in a moment please wait
ah the moon's pretty today
the server is coming together so nicely
it's so pretty we're gonna go to the
game now I think so too um yeah well I
think well uh we should all bring uh the
stuff that we need and in the chest or
two chests so that we can put it all
down safely uh in the in the stronghold
in science so we we have a lot of armor
like in in case we lose it uh we want
some of them some of that in the in the
yeah over there also I don't know if you
if you girls planned on doing the bad
strategy but I could bring at least one
brand yeah to sleep there and have a
safe
so bring your beds okay
you want me to make a chest
uh yeah just bring one chest I guess for
your safe to keep your your belongings
safe once we get there let me make one
an 18. never mind I just remember what
we're doing
yes
I'm gonna make more
I can make more
money I'm not gonna chop someone's tree
down not not this time this time no
other people's trees will be chocolate
okay what else are you I got no no no no
no
I didn't tell them to sleep in the end
I'm telling them to bring a bed to sleep
and before going into the portal so that
we if we die we don't go all the way
back to our yeah guys it's the ultimate
payback I got a nap in the end
I got a tip that we should bring bottles
to like capture the Ender breath or
something yeah you can use it capture
the stinky dragon breath okay bottles
yeah
you can just bring some glass and you
can just make a whole bunch of bottles
too
um
it's really dark oh my gosh I didn't
make a bun okay not like that I forgot
where I put my glass like I forget where
I put everything oh this is a very
beautiful area
the hands-free to be capturing breath I
mean well yes I can be hitting the
dragon and whatnot and oh my God I
didn't capture it the breath
I think you just put you just use the
glass where it's like doing the breath
attack oh
yeah
Hey where's the diamond armor
let me tell you all right so if you go
uh if you're on the way to my house
yes on the way to my house you will see
two chests
I am standing there as well the left
chest has armor everyone may take
two sets I guess
for themselves okay
I don't have many I didn't get many
weapons but uh
it's official
we need to bring food or this shouldn't
be like a we should bring I mean we
should probably
give people too
oh yeah and um after you guys are done
properly come to my come to my house I
can give you guys some a slow falling
potion so you don't die
oh yeah I need I need some shoes
oh everyone take uh two golden apples
from the chest where the armor is in as
well everyone gets two golden apples
okay Nina will tell you how to use them
come in
okay
zip it
out
what the hell is Mojang Auto sword
inventory win what is that why do you
have that no huh
it's an ended I didn't know you can have
an Ender Chest before going to kill you
see like a Dustin like Ender I'm getting
killed
oh this is what we're supposed to say oh
[Music]
I'm gonna take the right one
yeah one more set it was literally right
why not
and two sets total I think okay and then
a golden apple stack right we have the
two two golden apples yep yep what is
super thanks okay it's fine I'm just uh
Journey
access access work uh if you like the
sword is better if you do like quick uh
hits but the ax does more damage if you
do like shorter or slower hits I guess
does that make sense to click yeah
Target yeah yeah yeah Florida's aov
attack
the sword is quick damage like this are
all my junk in these chests
yeah you guys got the food
got cookies
cookies I want cookie ah water book
bucket and I wonder if we want to bring
like something like scaffolding you guys
definitely want some um
I'll bring sand all right forget this
guys I gotta look at the um
gorgeous the coordinates
nothing to buy pops up right
no no no always good for you your
graphics card I'm just kidding
was F3
I haven't played this game in so long
yes
okay are you lost yeah I'm lost
um where did the ferris wheel went to go
get nope went to go get some wood so I
could make a chest but everything around
our areas is owned so I had to kind of
go outside of the area
Audrey I'll give you a chest if you want
sorry I just can't touch anything
anymore okay what is the X what is the
XY Maple area I can't well I I don't
know where I am what is the XY
don't don't hide
Phantoms is it 70 what is it
can someone tell me where they are
[Music]
can someone please tell me
someone please tell me where they are
please give me the coordinates please
of where we are you mean yes we're our
yeah it's uh X
uh freehandle 26. okay
why 79 although y doesn't really matter
and set minus 481 wait I can know anyone
gotcha
okay
thank you oh I didn't hit any of those I
think uh hello cat
hello yeah they're afraid of cats so
they were attacking us
oh really
is that so yeah
that's how I got a lot of the membranes
for the potions
so by the way I bragged I'm bringing
sand in case we want to go up to the
towers with sand instead of shooting
them and I'm bringing dirt because we
probably have to build like a bridge
from our portal to
uh the actual main island and what did I
say the coordinates wrong 330.
and that is x and z is minus wait sorry
it was not 400 it was wait what is that
no no minus 480.
and 470 something like that
how did I get this far away
I was just trying to retrace your steps
and I was like what where where did you
go
I mean I was walking in the darkness
sorry for yet another delay you guys I
had to contribute to being useless at
least once so let's oh that was the
adventures basically like getting ready
for the family trip you know
when am I gonna get there
are we there you brought a diaper all
right there yeah
what the hell are you talking about I'm
telling her the right coordinates
Chad are you trolling
you got I am correct you guys are
incorrect idiots
except yeah thank you Ina thank you
enough
people
there you see it more clearly
ouch oh oh this is this is turning out
to be a bad morning this is a bad
morning baby I'm already enjoying this
hey where was Cali or where is Cali
I don't know we all don't know where she
is
oh wait I thought the last time you
played you were like uh doing the ferris
wheel or not oh I know I I was um a
couple minutes ago uh I went to go make
a chest
um so I went into the darkness and I
went looking for wood and I made sure to
go far away I made sure to go real far
away
where you like shoot it up into the air
yeah I should do that I'll be nice a
flare negative the sky do you see some
of our monuments or like the do you see
any good subscribers I'm thinking about
just dying guys like at this point I'm
thinking
I think I think the problem is that
we're giving her our base coordinate
when she's all the way in Phoenix town
[Music]
where the [\h__\h]
I fell into the
night uh I I just want to die guys I I
honestly I just want to die like reset
Callie
gotta find a torch Darkness oh God what
is this sheep
stay away you are Callie where are you
tell me your coordinates okay 2.99
299 2.99 10 19. 77 which doesn't matter
and then this is the one that's effing
me up that I can't see negative
692. maybe Israel is it down
well not relaxed
oh I think I kind of know where you are
Maybe
yeah
I'm on my way
[Music]
I'm coming too actually I don't know
where you guys are so as Ina if you're
already going then I'll stay yeah I'm
already on my way you're better with
coordinates Cali
hang on
oh sorry okay let's see are you on snow
or grass right now
I'm on grass
uh-huh
glass
she couldn't have gotten far yeah
exactly and there's only one
only one place we can go where there's
trees
pressing on this way
is somebody bringing a leash
so today please do oh sorry I don't want
to leave
one of those like those baby ones that
strap around your chest oh yeah there's
three of them some people like to walk
their children yeah one person with
three children and they're like all over
the place mommy should I put me on one
of those
oh what color
it was like green
Tartan print plaid
okay what are the coordinates Cali uh
305 for x and negative six nine two for
Z and you have five
negative what six
I'm thinking like Kelly yeah it's like
something
okay like I go to Negative X
negative wow where did you go five
negative six nine two I just walked into
the darkness nine really
just tried to go somewhere away from the
camp turned around couldn't find the
camp anymore
huh
I'm gonna get up on a pillar
I thought okay
figures that checks out
are you you got lost really quickly that
might be a record that really probably
was a world record
it's definitely a world record
it's not a difference sir
honestly it would not be surprised would
not be surprised if I was
okay all right and closer
foreign
it's negative 692 by the way I'm on a
tall pillar
I see it well I see um Kiara and uh
because I was about to say Kiara and
Kusa story Kiara and and girl is statue
I think it's kind of hard to miss the
um what's it kind of hard to miss the
giant stairway
yeah there is a giant stairway right
above me too
should just follow that yeah I guess I
could okay please just let me signs of
civilization
follow the moss covered rocks I came all
the way here for this freaking wood I
will sit here and I will hit it with my
hand until I get it even though my ax
has now just broken
I will hit it with my hand because I got
lost for this wood
determination
hey are you guys all ready to go by the
way I'll remember this uh typically
literally holy [\h__\h] pretty much
oh
pretty much do I need something I knew
it was gonna happen I feel like I need
flintins too and yet I didn't listen no
to myself
who needs insects anymore when you can
get glowing ink sex
why don't you even use ink sex for they
seem useless and ugly pink
it's a stress ball
wasting arrows never hold down
just testing I need to practice
eat buckets
did I hit you all right
Oh I thought I hit it I guess I guess
you're back in base Cali
and it's not a bucket okay good I
thought about it do you need a bucket
sorry I have a lot of buckets oh I also
have some some drinks for everyone
Taco Bell
okay you guys think we can play some of
those those Minecraft mini games have
you seen like the Minecraft mini game
servers oh yeah yeah I'm gonna play them
oh we could mod our own I could do it
probably I found the Kelly I'm just
gonna be a lot of fun no I don't want to
do it
hyena I'm a Lost Child
slowly slowly all right where's Ina
until now
welcome Daddy
we deliver everything from humans to
food wait pool tape Where'd I get this
from
yeah
all right Cali in here I love you okay
I can give you one oh it's okay I have
one I made one it's okay I went out of
my way to make one don't worry everyone
come over here to my my lab yes
open up the right chest and take some
slow falling potion okay
you'll need it you got it this time I
got it now I got it okay thanks for the
clap clap clap shot I appreciate it
it's been a rough morning
I think you can take uh
how many can we take I'm sorry you know
uh four or five I forget oh okay I
already have a full inventory yeah I
mean I'll take the leftovers myself so
don't worry yeah okay
you can't yeah can I have buckets five
each five years
and open up uh
there's seven in this chest over here
and there's like four on the outside one
I got something cute yeah
so feel free to take okay thank you for
all the preparation you guys did this is
really helpful you guys are amazing
wow yeah do you have any extra under
pearls on you Mickey I have one yeah if
you guys have any extras could you no I
have something maybe
because I'll I'll bring some place Ross
just in case you know our eye breaks
before we find
okay
are free and the pearls
yeah as for diamond armor is that in
front of Kiara's place yes to my house
okay
did everyone else already take their
sets of armor that you should like take
probably two but what if we die and burn
and then they all burn but if we die
then we'll just spawn back it's on and
then we can try to meet back up in the
yeah
only I forgot
wait here did you take the under chest
where did I put the under chest I didn't
think the end of a chest I took end of
probably from myself uh Callie wait yeah
go back go back okay
yes I see you
two full sets of armor yes
okay thank you anybody got any wood
one you shall wear yeah
the other one in case you died
okay oh yeah and then on the right side
okay
how do you say shield in Japanese like
what the hell happened here
please take one of the diamond axes
one of the balls one of them uh maybe
the the second the first row second one
oh yeah
I guess you can also take that I had
enough back door that someone put in
there that's not you iron sword okay
knock back door and then one of the um
one stack of arrows okay one stack of
arrows golden
no the normal ones the golden ones are
not really not really useful yes ma'am
surprisingly not useful did you take an
ax as well no I'm thinking the the
Diamond one the diamond one the Kiara
asking all the questions yeah can I ask
now wait you actually take one more one
more Bowl because you might lose one oh
okay
all right
which one should I take any of them ah
it doesn't matter oh okay as long as it
shoots
all right
all right and one Stacks okay
yeah
um I am also bringing some snowballs but
I don't have many uh you know didn't you
also get snowballs are you bringing them
too oh yeah I was gonna make this
snowman I gotta go get a shield guys
I don't need snowballs for to shoot the
towers uh like there's towers and you
just gotta shoot the top and the
Snowballs are really good for that I
think oh okay nice idea you guys wanna
build a snowman I'm good come on
[Music]
wait Callie did you get the gold uh you
have to take sorry one more thing two
golden apples from the chest yes I am
I'll go ahead and do that
nice crossbow
[Music]
um
in my house okay one one helmet damn it
here
okay
feeling better iron
your arm
my arm
S
I think I should be good all right
there's somebody more responsible want
to hold the scaffolding because I do not
trust you
bye
enough Austin you trusted
believe in you that Believes In Me
oh should I have a pickaxe you guys
um
[Music]
I don't have a kid are you using
OptiFine or maybe it's all I'm saying it
might be your shaders I don't think Cal
is using OptiFine so I don't know I am
I should bring some shovels and stuff
too I forgot
it's free
chant
I'm so glowy oh
okay beautiful glowing
enough can I give you
um the free enterprise that I have oh
yeah sure
I don't lose everything
we're saying I'm scared of a little oh
shoot them down you can get their
membranes
come give me your brains where are you
where are they wrong kind of membranes
but
membrane that's like when when the
membrane wall of assist have you ever
seen cyst removals you have to remove
the membrane wall otherwise the cyst
will grow back oh whoa that's enough oh
I
I hit that no I didn't still have my
dirt just shots absolutely yeah
beautiful shots
I can't see anything oh all right so are
we ready
I guess on the car
yeah inside the car
yes everyone got their snacks you got
food snacks
[Music]
yeah good all right
yeah oh there's another uh
are we sleeping
horrifying yeah I guess so let's go
sleep let's go get my bed will she come
there's another bed over here
I think I'll have to go inside oh well
hello
[Music]
noisy
okay sleep
ing through this night oh
oh there we go all right good morning
everyone Party Time
It's Time Cali in front of your house
there's a zombie owl destroyed okay oh
there's gonna be ball tosser oh it's
very kind of you yeah there's a lot of
enemies out here oh my oh my God why are
they after me are you okay oh yes yes I
will just run oh I need some torches
outside your house wait wait wait there
Callie okay I'm not moving
or a scally
okay right
explosion waiting for you oh that was
horrifying
come come with me quickly can you take
the end of pearls out of the chest I
have a full inventory okay not this
chest is inside my house thank you for
this this is gonna be ender pearl tosser
am I the here
that's what they're called right oh
thank you
just enough to not hurt my stomach hold
on a second
I have a sausage that's supposed to be
spicy but ever since I ate those spicy
noodles nothing has ever been as spicy
oh
thank you for the sausage
okay
[Music]
um
I'm guessing we're not doing the best
strategies
I'm bringing wood and we'll so if you if
you need to make more bets then
I have one two three four five six seven
eight but maybe nine I don't know a lot
of it I think I can do it normally two
but yeah
normally two depends
oh the pain is going away I think
everyone okay everyone has checklist
everyone has armor yes everyone has
weapons yes everyone has arrows yes
everyone has slow falling potions yes
everyone has two golden apples yeah yeah
everyone has a foot some kind of food
yes I have some leftover in case
everyone has uh one chest at least
[Music]
and everyone has maybe one or more but
more than one water buckets they could
be I mean I don't know if you if you
were and if all of us are that skilled
I'm probably not skilled enough but I
brought a couple of water buckets uh
because if you fall down then you can do
a swoosh
yeah probably I don't know okay put it
on the floor then you yeah get into it
at the right time I guess now
and I have some building material I
don't think we all need a building
material because yeah just one of us
so as long as I don't push each other
off
okay
okay I'll put some water buckets back or
do I I I'll just bring them along
whatever okay let's go
oh my God right and it'll go towards it
yes yes okay guys on it though because I
think you can collect it again yeah oh
yeah
oh [\h__\h]
I have no idea
I think it went that way
yeah they go behind us
it didn't even like usually it travels
and then there's that ping right away
are we um
what
and make it without uh I mean just just
wait here let me see if it works you
throw up or at the ground
I kind of threw like
horizontally
yeah okay
uh
you said chances I went the opposite way
maybe opposite way I went behind oh
there's no way like five years ago
um
okay I'll go see the slit see if it
I'm just following her up oh the extra
ones because I will get lost
Sparkle
follow Mom
let me make one of those was that not
supposed to say Polo uh you need Blaze
words yeah
our eyes as well uh we're supposed to be
scared that you're supposed to do it in
the other for some reason it's another I
don't know I don't know that's what I
thought I didn't know I don't know no
you can do it anywhere
I don't think we'll find it
despawn in like five minutes probably is
there a radius like if we know a block
radius then we can do like a you know a
circular sweep yeah I think there is but
all right let's go the other way blocks
so we can calculate from where you know
through it and then we can set up maybe
okay maybe throw another one it didn't
go that far because it pinged really
quickly
okay it says 10 to 15 blocks okay so
let's go back to the original one and
then search
10 to 15 blocks away from the corner
that you know threw it okay that is so
close
yeah that is pretty close
I'm sure we're just missing it
it could have broken apparently yeah uh
yeah that's true they break sometimes
right away I was it probably this is
probably broken
okay I'm gonna group up and throw
another one everyone
I'm coming back to uh Cara's roof or
sharp eyes on the roof roof party ladies
how's it off that's what Chad's saying
just go up
oh
I I I look I looked all right
one
what I didn't see it I lost it it's like
a disappearance
I don't see anything I was in third
person so I was looking and I didn't see
anything
yeah it actually literally just
disappeared behind are we all using
shaders yeah somebody says it went down
but I I checked in the KFC though I mean
the Kiara's house I wonder if it is a
shaders thing what they found
no I turned off shaders
uh are we right above it
no way there's no way no way
and we then we would have probably like
dug into it yeah Amelia's underground
Subway cave turns way further that way
like to the left but maybe we should dig
straight down from where you're throwing
it in Kiara's house yeah
Kiara your house is Olivia on the
construction you're forbidden to use it
from now on what the sweats
but
somebody says oh it's not a good idea
it's not a good idea before we waste all
the pearls though should we there's no
there's not here all right let's see I
have one too wait throw it somewhere
else where we should try throwing it
okay let's try it let's go into a flat
field like uh is there any other place
like yeah my cabin
I forget how to get there what about
what about like near the ocean
[Music]
yeah like like behind my houses
yeah like we're gonna was gonna make
Atlantis but yeah we went to the second
spot don't worry guys I definitely know
where my cabin is it's just not optimal
optimal place don't let your dreams be
me we'll finish the cabin memes don't be
sad famous and memes boys and girls Tony
already wasted two of those and uh I
have one I think I'm happy to offer it
wait is it under pressure
so as long as there's pearls that's all
we need
the Pearl will travel towards her house
oh yeah this is not very flat are you
sure you're is this what you consider
flat Inna
um
oh well you had to do it too old girl
yeah
surrounded by water
Maybe
oh
baby oh we're gonna test at her house
over there we can do that that looks
flat
okay
[Music]
and you want a ride
I would like a ride actually I have a
boat we can use
okay
flat
Yellow Nice cape
it's getting dark
he's got a tripod on it
like I tried it yeah
okay have you seen your cape pretty cool
all right okay guys
please
okay
look towards in a shrine I guess one
person
trying ruin
our village
oh you don't want to throw it in the
ground I feel like you want to throw it
towards like the shrine like some people
are saying it so of course the sky that
throws the ground like what
slumber party ladies oh Outdoors camping
okay
I'll see about your feet
but what did you say finish
yes
what all right
okay oh maybe if we go maybe enough you
go really high up like on a on some
blocks like this okay
uh what's the easy block okay
dirt
would you like a dirt let's do it from
not too high though because it's good I
think that's good
all right I'm gonna throw it towards
towards the Tory gate okay everyone
ready watch it okay ready okay three two
one
oh
did you see it I didn't see it it's
right here oh
ironic should I build a bridge then
is it under water
but don't we have to keep throwing it
that way until it goes down yeah okay
go again
oh there it goes it's working
is it there oh I got it one more should
we throw again uh let's do it from the
toy gate yeah
you want to throw that one whoosh uh you
do it you know
this is fine I messed it up
okay
oh here we go oh wow it's really far
oh
god well maybe the last two times just
broke
that would be pretty unlucky
do we have to wait we still have like
three spare ones what should we do here
like should we make a bridge or should
we just go in that direction and then do
it again I feel like bridge is just
gonna be wasting blood possibly we have
other boats because if we have the other
other boats we could just go in this
direction a little bit okay
let's go this way until we reach land
yeah who has boats I got a boat who
needs a boat I don't have a boat
thank you gura thank you
let me check in this chest oh yeah there
should be one more Bobby road all the
way here
[Music]
so I'll make one really quick
all right I'm coming
what is that oh it's a trident fart
right
okay I'm gonna throw it again hold on
oh okay okay keep calling this catch it
catch it
I think we can go a bit further before
yeah throw the next one because yeah
we're wasting them do you still have
enough you think yeah pearls all plus
three pearls and five Blaze Rawson that
makes like a couple of okay fine let's
go until we get to land and then uh we
can do it again if it goes back then
you have like a perimeter to check this
feels so cool you guys I feel like I'm
gonna be underwater
it could be
done
walking on water damn
what a Pro Gamer I'm in ah Jesus
Pro game okay
I'll go until yes let's go there on that
Hill
imagine yeah
let's go dolphin
I'm the photographer
I'm taking pictures of us
beautiful
on the way to the Ender Dragon yeah
beat up the Ender Dragon we're gonna
look up epic Minecraft music
all right copyright RTA let's go
there's Minecraft playlist that I'll put
on like a 10 hour playlist while I play
hold on
I'm gonna play all the nether tracks
oh yeah a good idea
oh hello sorry
I'm ready can I play that too
oh no never mind yeah look up the nether
tracks
epic Minecraft yeah that'll give you
remixes from from other music producers
Minecraft soundtrack all another tracks
2020.
yeah there's 500 sounds trustworthy
everyone here no
um
[Music]
oh all right we'll go further then it
didn't break it didn't break it fell oh
yeah
all right all right direction
yes
okay good
this music is being anxiety let's keep
going for like a couple minutes yeah how
many blocks maybe like 500 blocks is
there like only one or is there like oh
we're back at Water maybe we should go
to where those trees are over there
yeah until the tree let's go into the
tree wait I lost you girls me and Kelly
are too far away from you girl I'm not
the only one yay I'm not the only one
that's lost anymore
I see some names I found found you Kelly
you're following me yeah go to the top
of the hill oh wait
oh I see them
yes
right together how far do we go
all right
wait I have someone's
bed
not mine
yeah
all right let's go drive drift
summer drift
Italy it wasn't Netflix
maybe we should go to the top of the
mountain and then
yeah yeah maybe yeah yeah
is there only one or is there multiple
welcome to the mountain I'm gonna is
there multiple yeah that's the one
yeah
oh God I had to get out of the there we
go
there's tons okay bubbles okay so I
guess it's just the one we're closest to
uh-huh okay cool
we should have rollerblades that'd be
sick and go faster oh there's like speed
potions
wait there's a small rails over here
yeah yeah or another another nice snow
though
I also saw like a like a Sephora that is
really close
relatively close I guess
what's what's close I can't wait for
everybody yeah can you go a little
further
uh sure okay just a little
maybe like on top of the yeah yeah oh
yeah I was thinking that to you all
right unexplored territory this is kind
of like exclusion oh
it would have been good to bring a map
oh true fill in the map
we would have needed a really big map
though if he went real far yeah that's
true I want to make a map room exclusive
shift
enough
that's Deutsche let's see yeah I'm gonna
throw it draw from here
what is that did something
how is that naturally possible pumpkins
all right guys
but I went straight ah there you are oh
okay yeah oh that oh there you go okay
three two one
wait oh it went the other way okay so
we're here then oh
he's like oh I turned off
so now we turn back around yeah we use
the eye to look for a portal right
yes
we gotta triangulate or whatever and
then we break Minecraft's number one
rule don't dig down
okay
we bring a shovel to dig down I will
stay behind I don't want to lose all the
stuff dude I did not make a shovel wait
where are you wait I have a shovel I
have a shovel
where'd everyone go hey Watson
yeah where where are we must be on the
streets just be on the trees okay oh
okay on the way
it's getting dark
let's do it one more time before before
it gets dark yes yes
actually how beautiful wait whoa
okay I'm not gonna go this way all right
guys
oh yeah oh I found you guys okay did
someone pick up the Pearl or eye
where did it go gonna
no
oh yeah I have one in your hand you know
yeah I have 11. I eat stuff though it
broke okay it broke okay
oh wait wait it's stuck on the tree on
top of it
no I fell on the ground yeah I don't see
it oh it's real dark sleep over time
ladies
there's a bed over there
thank you okay
hurry that break it is on the tree but I
thought it still hit the ground
I mean we can check hold on oh I have
your bedina oh it's right there I see it
there it is
so much for hearing a break
[Music]
okay 12. thank you it was a
heartbreaking we're going to stay right
okay sorry it's okay and you want yours
back oh it's okay right here oh this is
nice and open
music me too me too okay
point
oh oh that way this one oh oh okay
okay
ikfp workout do we do it like at the
edge of this Cliff here yeah
watermelons
oh oh oh
so I can stand here it's almost down
here oh okay and stay they put sit I can
stay
foreign
I'm really good at standing still and
not doing anything
so the one thing I'm great at at this
game
oh I think you're on to it yeah oh
someone said like some right here
okay me me I'll Stand getting close
[Music]
I can smell you
yes ma'am
yeah
can I move I already moved
hold on
yeah let's stick where we're amazing oh
okay okay the gear how far down is it
yeah I don't know until it's pretty far
down I think we're digging you can only
see it yes
I can help oh no she's digging straight
down
around here
you'll know that because the stones will
change it'll look like bricks I should
probably stay with someone
I don't have a picture
I opened up a cave here there's a cave
down here oh
okay
I'm gonna build some stairs we can Mosey
our way down oh yeah
should have brought toys
oh I dropped the water uh if you guys
want to jump in my hole oh uh-huh
yeah sure raising oh there's a creeper
you know you have an arrow in your head
there you go thank you don't worry about
it
wait no right here like uh oh but I
guess it'll go through the wall huh
I have I have no space
there's a cave build and there's a
there's another chance it's okay they'll
they'll find it
okay I'm gonna stay with you okay sorry
I have no clue
okay okay
I'm gonna start digging down again just
to see
I didn't bring it
[Music]
ah there oh
okay I'll put torches outside
ouch
okay this is amazing
wait hold on one okay
whoa hello hi where's oh there's about
the stairs
can you open the door for me yeah
yeah there we go oh
okay nothing here nothing it's a maze
oh wow so it's like that huh okay so
excited this is so cool
there's like stairs here all right
nothing
because where is zombies
there's a lot of people here I don't
have any more uh torches
don't look at him holy [\h__\h] yeah
get it okay
oh there's a library oh oh cool aren't
there under
so awesome
treasure music
there's uh it can be behind a false wall
as well I know there's like cheeky uh uh
uh joke walls let me buy this is
uh throwing away blocks
this library is so cool
yeah I probably shouldn't try
we can take them yeah if you hear the
spider webs of the sword they go down
really fast oh cool thanks
oh I think I found it
nice
to get rid of the spawner though
oh that was that was actually Espana
that was really a spot yeah I'm gonna
borrow a torch
here I can give you some
I don't know I didn't look at you I did
not look at you I just lost
oh you did find it the other way yeah
there's like literally no eyes
wait you know what I have exactly enough
I found enough to make
oh my God you want me to go get the one
I have I have one more no I have exactly
15. oh dear God oh my gosh okay everyone
everyone
here
[Music]
you're good everyone here
oh my gosh okay someone mark down the
coordinates for this oh yeah good idea
okay got it I got the screenshot it's
great let me make sure I'm absolutely
prepared chest chest guys just in case
oh yeah
bed and chest ladies
yeah bed and chest
stupid door uh
ouch ouch what the hell oh
my God what the [\h__\h] is Olympia
what do we do it depends what the hell
oh there's a thing you gotta kill it
it come out of the the walls and stuff
what are we starting in the chest
um like your second set of armor and uh
silverfish oh
maybe some arrows
water buckets
some some of the potions we don't we
only need probably one phone now
oh no the lava no
that was not me oh my God I did not do
that
oh my goodness I did not do that that
was not me get rid of them
chaos like dangerous
what the hell the bat is about to burn
the portal
well if there's no lab on the portal
will it break it for some reason though
I can't really fall anymore do we break
the spawner I think it's three of them
pour water in the lava
yes okay we don't we don't need the lava
hey
okay so let me put my wax it's dark in
here
so cute though I don't know they don't
look edible how about the uh the potions
you guys the slow falling the potion
yeah yeah maybe bring in one one only
for now I think okay yeah because it's
pretty dark yeah leave it to me I don't
have any
leave it to me
okay I'm gonna start putting the eyes in
20 years
I'm I'm putting two books into the chest
but those are those are um
yeah I will bring it that's right
[Music]
oh wow
can we take a group picture can everyone
get on the stairs
[Music]
actually
well I have a really cool cake too
no yeah everyone look to the front and
I want one too
please yes yes
okay I got it thank you me too yay
damn it when you put the under chest
here
uh thank y'all
what if the front people use the under
chest does that mean
they have their own storage
I opened yours earlier and I didn't see
anything in it oh that means you guys
can use it too cool just throw your
stuff in oh I wish I didn't know that I
wish I didn't know me too oh well
okay well I'll put
wow
it looks like
well okay are you in okay
okay
let's take a plunge ah all right be
careful where are you going what do we
do he's jumping
maybe not all at once because I don't
know how big the platform is when we
land and we might push each other from
where we stand I'm gonna go first okay
Watson all right how is it is it is it
very nice I can't see [\h__\h] wait you guys
okay it's a small platform
um you guys can oh God do we have
building the dragons right here it's
already here oh no
material
then yeah and then we come in okay
I'm working yeah everyone ready yeah
should I be holding something specific
you guys are holding blocks
yeah to build but yeah to build yeah
I'll help
uh do we use the you know do you think
we should use the following potion right
away I think when we when we go in we
can use it when we start the trip let me
start fighting okay also uh Kelly don't
there is a lot of Endermans down there
like a [\h__\h] ton
um okay when you go up to the dragon try
to look down because there's really an
army of Ender Dragons don't look at them
they will kill you once you look at one
of them how do I shoot it I don't want
to do a staring contest with them no no
if you do if you don't wear them or
water and get in it because they can't
yeah
but Cali remember we're not fighting the
Enderman because that's the fight we
cannot win we try to fight the Ender
Dragon okay and we can look at that one
right
okay
okay got it all right I'm ready now
loading
ready one one
I'm loading look just wait it's just
loading okay yeah
climatic
oh my God
it broke
oh
yeah I'm inside you Kiara do you feel me
you see me
badass
whoa
oh no
I think we should probably make a bridge
over to the bigger platform before we
that was too much the portal is too
powerful
what is this place
this is cool here is back in here dirt
I also have a lot
and yep okay that should be enough oh my
God which way should I build because
there's one close to our left or should
we just build upwards because we could
build stairs here are born I got one I
think we should go to the main main uh
platform over there where the dragon IS
F okay
I am in the end
just let amen do her her thing okay
don't go push her what the hell you
won't get anything back
is that normal what does the sky look
like noise to you as well guys it looks
pretty nice yeah it looks itchy
it doesn't look like that in uh
oh
we need to build a we need to put walls
up yeah okay okay
you question do you know when you go
into The Nether and that thing that goes
can you and you can like hit him hit the
the Fireballs back at it can you do that
with the Ender Dragon I don't think is
this what is the smoke can I walk into
it no that's that's fire on the ground
that's the Ender Dragon slime oh okay
okay
we can't build above it
oh God
oh God I'm gonna die oh no ah it's our
platform oh wow I'm in bad shape right
now okay this is bad this is bad we need
to build fast okay
oh is all the stuff still there because
I'll just yeah yeah
how do we make the fire stop uh no I'm
dying
yeah
dang it yeah that's a good idea turning
off shaders might be a good idea oh man
I'm gonna collect more materials
please collect my items please [\h__\h]
um
when the dragon shoots does it break
walls also
I don't know
nice Mr Dragon
stuff it doesn't break
all right we'll have to build your walls
there get your stinky breath out of here
are you big scaly thing
there by chance you guys
your stuff is all still here well I've
got to get here okay I'm coming well
actually maybe I'll tell you yeah I
think the fire is there yeah Fire's done
you can come in okay that's fine I'm not
gonna start over again
I want my things
all right I got a bunch of stuff oh my
God the diamond armor is already so low
we really should have brought all of it
yeah
[Music]
well walked towards the the platform
there doesn't see us what does that mean
hello Mr Dwayne oh thank you wait Watson
this is what is that annoying I turned
them off I turned them off what is that
huh oh it's an Enderman
it my game doesn't work anymore without
shaders
I'm in danger
all right hello
we need to build the stairs you really
want me to step up
I chose
1.171.1 the most recent release
well this isn't great guys oh
oh my bow and arrows are gone
um
I am using that one yeah
wait can you start the day thank you
Watson you don't have to
all right
sure there's there's more outside
do you go outside
okay can I catch the fire thanks zombie
wait uh I'll go and live up oh yeah okay
okay well turn off the shaders like uh
manually maybe I'll be your eyes in the
Sky What's home
watch out behind you we fire fire fire
fire fire fire fire fire fire
okay it's gone it's gone it's gone
are you are you guys already fighting
the dragon oh yeah
oh no uh
let me kill him
can I kill him
did we try to kill one
I mean the others can't see it I mean
this one's already angry so does anyone
have a pickaxe so I can you can't you
can't use uh arrows or range attack for
Enderman yeah
who picked up my stuff uh a nice dragon
that much stuff in here so I don't know
I think some stuff might have fun
yeah that works too uh
whoever picked up Kelly stuff might have
my stuff
Cali got all my stuff okay
should I turn off shaders did you guys
turn them off or did it myself
you have to like reload the game if you
turn them off
okay
yes oh my god oh that's bad
I'm coming
you thank you because here is a bit
safer to give me my stuff thank you I
build tunnel stairs
should be one set of armor and unlike
some dirt blocks some eyebrows um I only
have I only have one set
and what you're wearing your set yes and
you have one extra right nope I'm only
wearing the one that I have hey where
are you guys by the way this is your
this is definitely yours we have TRX
here you go
[Music]
everything that you have is myself
that's okay
okay here here we have my dirt blocks do
you have an overall Instagram no dirt
and and yeah wait can somebody kill me
so I can go back and then okay you know
what let's
[Music]
um
okay
thank you wait I don't want all your
stuff though no it's fine it's fine
there's more stuff uh here she asked me
to here's stream hard challenges
can you bring me one uh yeah we need one
full set of armor because we're sharing
right now yeah there's two full sets
here so I'll bring I don't have one
either and then um
oh do you have a oh damn it the golden
apples uh uh I have two here I gotcha
chat
I just need one one yeah
it's fine oh okay it's cool I'll just
try not to die
oh do you guys have bows how many bows
do we have yeah
one bowl please One Bowl uh a few more
hours please
okay fine it's like a big overgrown okay
there's an extra set okay who's missing
armor right now me me and Cali yeah I
miss him um
I have the bottom Parts okay okay
there's enough
uh there's only one bow I'll probably
hold it because
I have time to get ice cream
dreams
[Music]
one bow
I think I can make some but they won't
be enchanted and I'll be right back uh
can you bring some building blocks just
in case yeah
how do we leave do we just leave the
game and then you have to die oh yeah
all right can I leave these things here
and then come back you guys
Kiara yeah all of my things real quick
oh wow that's loud
all right I'm going to go
Sudoku
okay good luck on my glass bottles
and God I'm such an idiot
all right well I got regular bows wait
Kylie wait wait what oh what about my
entertaining potions the top
the God [\h__\h] damn it [\h__\h]
look look it's gonna kill you yeah we
have three armor tops here three pants
okay three how many shoes one full one
all right one full set
um no don't don't make anything else for
me please just keep it you guys I'll
survive everyone I prepared for everyone
so there should be uh one more set for
you and one more set for me it is
missing but
no I have everything sorry I have it in
right now I was gonna go back with it
hold on I'm gonna be right back
yeah because we could store everything I
mean I guess maybe we can't store stuff
yeah
can I shoot this thing or is it gonna
come after us
depends on what the things
I mean it's gonna kill itself because we
still have to close or get rid of ah
okay
Yara you have pants already I have shoes
and pants
okay
thank you mint ice cream anyone destroy
the crystals all right chat
I like that they're at the top of the
tower right
I've only ever watched speed running of
this so I won't I I barely know what
happens plus I always bead Runners
always have like the uh the like the
program outlines turned on and stuff
it's really weird oh hi
I mean we just gotta get there and shoot
it
okay
I gotta get good guys I gotta get into
this ice cream first though crystals are
the things making the beams they heal it
yeah
okay
I can't get into my ice cream
said nice weather here today what'd you
think girl how's the weather up there
you know
it's a little bit of clutter with the
chance of dragon fireballs
what material is this this is like
sponges and their Stoners whatever yeah
Ender splint uh oh I got it
what do I do with this glass bottle to
capture something oh yeah yeah I don't
don't worry about it I guess yeah and
phase two of Ender Dragon it'll come
down and do like ah bro okay is it okay
to eat the apple now probably yeah right
yes yes okay
wait all right wait where's Cali because
Cali said she uh he'll be right back I
can't I think
I can't re-enter the game now it says
the server is outdated
yeah that's because I turned off the
shaders uh
um I have the same thing just now yeah
you have to download or update no use
use the option that says opt to find the
normal one that used up until now then
once the screen is open uh you click
into options and turn it off manually
um before logging into the Minecraft
server okay uh you know where you can
choose the Minecraft servers before you
click that you go on options and then
turn off uh at graphic settings you go
to uh shaders and then turn off the
Shader manually okay
no no
[Music]
no no no
don't don't touch my stuff I'm on my way
you heard her don't touch it I'm not
touching it
all right she's back in the Yukata for
Revenge you need him I got some dragon's
breath
oh
I like this music
for myself yeah
tell me guys when you're ready
I'm a pickaxe so I can dig
oh wait wait wait
oh
that was sensory overload Captain hold
on I need a what's one this is nice pink
pink step
okay video settings and then
the shaders
graphic settings
oh my God damn sorry keep keep focusing
on the game Sorry one second uh I need
food I need food I need food I'll give
the chickens
chickens I I think you picked it up
again I didn't oh my God how do we do
this okay
is big step part of the game or is this
a remix hello do you have the food
please uh it sounds I don't know
copyrighted
it's literally from the game so we'll
take a risk I'm standing right next to
y'all anyone who has food
dmca
part of the game all right
get it back God damn it I am getting way
too many mixes yeah I got it thank you
all right we're good we're gonna do it
this is not going well
foreign
[Music]
we have to destroy them
they do I don't know can I even shoot
that far
it's only one hit what the hell one hit
as always right into the bullet side oh
yeah did someone look at me don't attack
me guys don't attack me
oh my God and the bullet Bullseye not
Bullseye bullet's eye I don't know
okay let's go
nice shot
that is the second time first try
uh
okay I got a problem I got one
did you get Enderman
oh hi there
uh
hi fellas thanks guys all right
now it's generating Health back
okay following you
scares me back I don't have a sword so
why is the water so tiny okay hold on
all right you guys oh yeah we gotta do
the towels first okay water
all right
hours first oh okay
okay
what am I shooting at I need I need more
arrows no
uh at the top of the towers you're gonna
there's a on it can I put a bed up here
I'm feeling dangerous
it's our only those with the cages right
yeah
someone's without the cages we can do
who wants to watch me now
come on do it again Kiara you
more
can you not drag oh no
think the potion how do you drink a
potion
you eat it like it's food yeah
you had one
how many more do we have yeah
you're going up that way okay oh wait
there's one here how do you blow these
beds up
maybe one more yeah why is that one so
low I'm back it's yet okay I got one
okay
I don't have an ax
right click Roger
face the dragon eat it shoot this I have
no more arrows unfortunately
oh so far
I'm good it's gonna be okay I'll
definitely I need building blocks
I'll find you guys don't worry
material never mind
um I can does anyone have arrows I have
some uh okay uh I have Infinity so I can
spare 14 for you I think
hey I think it's free or something I'm
I'm in front of you behind you you know
sorry sorry Callie I'm in front of Inna
I see you guys
gotta get the one inside the cage thank
you yep
got it I don't have a pickaxe I can't
help and you don't have any books
blocks
because then we could just take some of
these can we chill that would be a good
idea
not I don't even know anymore did we
I'm a little slow falling potions oh I'm
happy
I think someone echoed the Enderman use
some water
oh
hold it
now let's just use a potato oh yeah this
isn't gonna work I don't know what it is
oh oh no yeah someone hey
crystals they seem pretty angry
thank you
[Music]
buddy
well we'll see I guess
I'm missing all my shots regenerates
who doesn't seem to be taking any energy
from any of the tallies anymore
[Music]
does this mean it's still
nice oh nice I hit him I hit him yay
I want to use the bed it's coming down
uh oh phase two
oh boy
oh wow
am I doing anything to it
I can't see oh I don't think my arrows
are doing anything
oh no it's doing something let's go
forward
I think we're supposed to tag it with a
sword right now
bad bad
oh
I have I have one more chicken
thank you kfb
my arrows aren't doing anything
I mean I was hitting for a little bit
but yeah
you're not flying again
or maybe it actually isn't doing
anything all right I see how to do it
now I remember now
these arrows okay I'll pick it up I'll
pick it up oh no you fell it's okay
oh
I have water
it's really actually
excuse me
I'm still gonna win Enderman get lost
yeah bye nerd
where's my stuff where's my stuff
where's my stuff
where did I land oh
I think
what did you see myself
it's raining wow really not happy at us
[Music]
okay you know what
um
I'm taking back some of my water
did he regenerate or not nope that's not
working the bed
oh
you're gonna put fire on top of the
water
don't I
until oh wait there's water
is somebody hitting the bed the golden
cameras don't work if perched that would
be too easy huh yeah
all right no no no don't kill me no I
gotta get rid of this camera first oh
the fire uh
why can't I hit him I hit the bed
oh my God
I am dealing with an Enderman here
oh they were really excited to see us
stay in the water seen the water stay in
the water okay okay yeah that's right
that's right
okay oh wait what the hell uh where are
you where are you buddy
this is not good
we can do it we can do it
an hour
you're gonna kill the Enderman here but
before we kill the tree right
oh they look perfect I can't do anything
yeah sorry I would have grabbed one all
right
I need to
talk to my life Journey please
do it
he's coming oh get the bed
I prefer to die I guess I think I prefer
to die at this point yeah you can get a
sword
oh yeah yeah
okay do it hey oh they need to take my
stuff no way he did I don't think that
he did
[Music]
with me
no
we wouldn't have the aggro anymore I
don't care about the water yeah
I have a sword I'll borrow it oh
don't don't don't hey
oh okay
I'm on my way
oh
never mind I am on a journey
laughs
I don't know
hey I've got like no Health do you guys
have fun is my stuff still there
you died I'm still looking for myself
I'm gonna leave my diamond armor
um
I threw I threw my things out there if
someone wants to take them
Spider-Man
I don't know okay
or no sword okay I have an arm around
the floor yeah okay I think we're okay
are we
um did you pick up my stuff when you
said you're taking my sword nope
was it a yes or no no
Enderman
there's a creeper okay just kidding time
to go back to you guys
[Music]
foreign
ER killed me
whoa that is a powerful portal
prepared when I died
okay
is there a way we can put out this fire
they didn't like no I don't think we
just haven't thought that you know where
car died
I think okay the sword is the bottle Oh
no I got a bottle
I'll fill it
where's the fire
[Music]
what did you find my my stuff okay I'm
nice I am useful again okay let's go
um as long as I have oh shoot I should
be fine
my things
my my helmet and my chest plate I wonder
if my bow is here
are we still doing the the bed strategy
I have yet to get it to work okay it
might be a pipe dream
[Music]
yeah I get him that's not experience
because I've only got a shovel but
I guess I'm missing all my shots
all right all right
there you go
I can definitely be baked nice shot who
shot that nice
but I can't do it again and you'll have
some food
I have a little bit food yes yes he's
coming
I got him again
all right we got the bed in position
who's doing the bed yeah
oh my gosh huge damage
I don't have a sword so can I hit him
with a bucket
can I hit him with a shovel
I can't I can't get it
I'm gonna take that you jerk assistant
[Music]
I'm definitely not helping but it's but
it's nice to feel like maybe I'm helping
Maybe
yay
[Music]
oh the portal
yay
are you guys seeing credits
audio software nothing credits
oh she went through the portal already
oh do we have we have to go yeah okay
[Music]
is it over
what's fun
[Applause]
I was standing on a portal let's go
Minecraft
a speed the player you mean
yes take care it has reached the higher
level now
oh that's like meta gangua
they're talking to us whoa
that doesn't understand
things we are part of the game
wow I like this player it played well it
did not give up it is reading our
thoughts as though we they wear words on
the screen who wants to read next
what about the egg what egg I think
we're at different parts egg I think we
left something important I can imagine
many things when it is deep in the dream
of a game it was confusing let me go
back
maybe I don't know well can we re-enter
the portal
oh yeah you can because like Well in
that and the world there are treasures
and [\h__\h] Cali so from now on we can
explore that I'm gonna build a rail to
the Ender Portal yeah please
but yeah uh my my mission is to get an
elytra as soon as possible because of an
elytra you can fly uh yeah as long as
you have fireworks yeah you might want
to yes
it took us so long but we finally did it
you guys did so much amazing prep work
thank you so much
it's pretty scuffed in the beginning but
a win is a freaking win I'm just
privileged to have been able to come
along to watch The Journey
that you guys prepared so hard for I
hope that my few arrows could be of help
yes of course our power together is five
is stronger than anything stronger than
that stupid end of dragon yeah you're
right yeah flush them down the toilet my
hair is going restless so glad we did it
together yes they played a game
zero desk Club hello can anybody else
say the same that is pretty dope I will
say that is kind of awesome girl
that was like something out of like a
crazy action movie that was just
unbelievable
be the bad girl do the bed
I think I think I got a lot of uh Tower
shots a lot of times
first try shots were quite quite a lot
of them I would definitely give Kiara
the Sharpshooter award yeah that was
really only luck
that was
skip credit oh how do I skip them can I
scroll up I want to get a screenshot of
gal Guru player of games that's gonna be
my gamer title now
I'm changing my hey manager
do I want to skip in
well we can go back
how long are they yeah how long is it
the playhouse no no Kiana hello Ian can
I just go jump real quick back inside
I just wanna um
my Miner
clock eye Phoenix eye Kiana
there we go whatever
in the morning that was a little
nightmare and your man freaking
nightmare
would be a lot of fun to uh oh the
Enderman are still here
yeah they live here oh this is their
home huh yes cool oh I see the I see the
portal thing wait wait where does it
spawn us back how did it go out oh
there's the egg I don't know stronghold
you get spawned back
there's the portal thing
a woman inhaled on me
inhaled on me a woman gathered the items
and she inhaled the player in her body
we got bored
what the [\h__\h] what are you reading oh
here's the portal everybody else skipped
it
wow yeah
you're missing the good stuff here man
where are the treasures we're made from
milk and love the player is made from
nothing but milk and love
the end is basically like insanely
endlessly huge so when you ask for it
there's a chicken of treasure spread of
the millions and millions of miles oh
wow so you might not find it right away
but you gotta travel from like Islands
there's like all kinds of like Islands
separated you gotta build like Bridges
and [\h__\h] to get to another Island are
there more dragons maybe we can go on a
trip I think only one dragon
oh
there's millions of Enderman
is that the egg you know
yes but what does it do
you mean
I can let it land on a torch you can
respawn the dragon with the egg oh just
leave it for now I guess okay okay don't
touch it
it won't go anywhere
become Daenerys
number of words
that's cool uh what should I I don't
know do I want to go there
sometimes
we're being spoken to encode you guys
zeros and ones it's the mark of a true
gamer wow
the universe said they love you by the
way
oh that's nice to know that was very
kind also the universe is inside you
oh that's true that uh the universe
no I'm not skipping the credits I gotta
know more the universe says you're not
alone it's not a scuffed stairwell
egg there's the egg
there and then you never said and my
mommy said that you are the Knight and
my mommy said the darkness you fight is
within you and my mommy said the light
your secrets was in you Emma
you can't get up
girl no she's reading the credits wake
up I know I know
from that horrible dream what the hell
is that
what is that wake up wow did this take
us less than two hours you guys
sorry
in 20 minutes or something
it doesn't take longer to um
yeah only almost 2 A.M here I thought it
would be much later
oh wow
oh Cali Minecraft
we have water or jump into the portal oh
water would have been a better choice
here no that's okay I can go I can see
let's go back in I'm out I'm always for
fun I'm leaving now though yeah like
outside yeah outside still in there yeah
outside we'll we'll make our way back
does anybody have a pickaxe okay
uh just uh read the title if you want to
use it that's important okay
oh stream heart Challenger and Spark
that's right that's right
now do it materials
[Music]
thank you
are you building a what are you building
me
oh oh oh is that a creeper yes
oh no
sorry
oh no girl you can eat
you moved in my line of fire
Mr President
I can't wait for the railway railroad
back here
I want me a whale I want some books
now I don't even be a party
oh nice
too because I lost so many items did you
guys chest
there's books in it there's not much oh
this place is so beautiful
we're gonna take a picture
um I I have something to confess
um
I
I went I I might have been the first one
to open the chest and I might have been
the one who took something out of the
chest oh I was in the chest yeah
two two two books that were in Enchanted
nothing super special oh yeah well I'm
level 68.
when uh
as level 30 earlier
hey how do we get an elytra can we get
that now the what I thought no you have
to look for Treasures in the end the
world yeah oh
wander up you guys
yeah I mean I thought I thought it was
gonna take longer to be honest I wonder
how many Elijah's still ours
over the end there are enough for Japan
members to keep on getting new ones
even though they lose them all of the
time
don't do
how many lies there is no limit yeah it
would take a while
yeah it might take a while to explore
because you have to find the place where
they have it and then you gotta like
clear out
stuff
gotta kill stuff oh
we wanted to take a picture yeah yeah
should we not take take it like in the
end that would wouldn't that be cool
again
and in the end and then we'll just take
a picture and quickly go outside again
sure
wait where is it where is it can I go
back into the middle and I'm gonna go
down the stage where the hell is it
here yes okay
yes
can we get the egg
I think you have to leave it there
leave it down until we know how to take
it safely
yeah let's let's get to the egg and take
a picture in front of it yeah let's do
it
off my
um silk touch pickaxe
I have cutting Corners oh yeah that's
mine
what is that though
I'm here to reunite you here
I did not look at them
thank you
oh [\h__\h]
because I thought something dropped uh
where do we take the picture
of this of the parts
if I switch views will it make me look
at them
just don't touch it
um not necessarily
app
okay I'm ready whenever you want to take
a picture
everywhere
wait you guys gonna get it with this
little touch
this is like Opera nicely
you guys you can't mine it you
definitely don't touch it don't touch it
no touchy
check once then break the block under it
with a torch
now the block under it says you need a
piston yeah just don't touch it right
now
we can take
yeah
the egg is part of the journey
[Music]
get close like maybe in front here oh we
could build like our own pillars right
behind the egg and it looks really cool
we'll each stand on a pillar yeah do you
have uh some building materials
I'm from the
oh I'll take him Cali here you go
thank you oh
[Music]
oh don't touch it just a little touch oh
no oh
oh
sorry panicked I left I panicked and
left you guys
probably better
okay so coming back everyone
no I'm just kidding I won't I promise
destructive
this shovel has achieve victory
laid out yeah but where are you
wow they're real quick they like to move
with the blocks
oh yeah they're real mad trapped yet I'm
watching and I'm a sword zoom zoom I'll
sit here for a million years until I get
there all right I'll just stand over
there I'll just run
ow
I meant
is there a way that I can help you oh
okay
oh
[Music]
they're angry this is gonna be tough
hey with this block
okay
another uh
okay I'll be back where is he okay
I'll be back okay
I'll be back thumbs up
this place is a lot less scary without
the uh
Dragon search how to get the yeah
without the dragon I'm sorry about the
shaders but yeah I was at the dragon as
well
yeah the sky is prettier without this
video yeah it's much easier yeah pitch
black but I mean yeah it wasn't much
better when it was noise
you can get his head
they don't share Aqua you mount it to
the wall that's done whoa use any tool
or even your bare hands hit the Ender
Dragon egg Until It Breaks oh yeah
remember remember Mikko Senpai and
suicide Senpai wearing those ender
dragon heads in the Summer Festival that
was really creepy all right this is good
uh I guess for every picture we can look
into a different direction okay
yeah I think this angle works for me
okay oh yeah this one works for me too
here
wait this is confusing everybody look up
and to the right look look I'll just
look where I can stand I guess that
means that looks am I looking in the
right side yeah yeah yeah
I'm just gonna give this to you a little
up
I can't see
oh oh [\h__\h]
hey buddy
I'm a feeling it's uh they really want a
photo bomb us huh
get out of here it's like all right well
I'm jumping back in the portal we got
one right I think so oh wait I didn't
get one can everyone else
where I stand
yeah
[Music]
to the front yeah
and three two one cheese
cheese
[Music]
anyone else who wants a picture
um I'm let's see oh yeah sure
I look over to you then I should be
looking in the right direction all right
everyone look up this guy ready
[Music]
all right I got it I got it I got it I
got it okay
all right I'm jumping in the portal
all right let's go all right here we go
yay
[Music]
um uh
does anyone want to like go back home or
like is everyone ending now or because
last
yeah yeah I want to go treasure hunting
later
okay oh yeah we're not doing that I
don't know how do we do that
whoa look at it later yeah
uh no I have one
can I have one
I'm I'm playing Minecraft later today
guys so I'll just log out here I guess
okay I'll probably need more stuff
yes there's infinite Treasures oh
thanks so much everyone for the fun time
it's quite an experience
thank you for everything you guys did to
prepare yes thank you it would not have
been easy mode without all of your
preparations
is always cooperating whenever you need
to tell
yeah thanks for the fun times
guys catch you later bye everyone bye
bye
[Music]
thank you Chad catch you later
I appreciate your support as always bye
foreign