​​​ ​Next is, um...​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Takahashi-kun!​ ​​
​​​ ​And we're off with holo's Bonjour.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the official hololive​ ​​
​​ ​variety and talk show​ ​​
​​​ ​which changes out one​ ​​
​​ ​of the guests every month!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a member​ ​​
​​ ​from EN and ID here today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go ahead and introduce the cast.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did I Luive you waiting?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm JP's bird,​ ​​
​​​ ​Takane Lui!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for having me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guest number 2 is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! I'm Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​ ​from hololive English!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a phoenix!​ ​​
​​ ​Thanks for having me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​And guest number 3 is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Pavolia Reine!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am a bird, a peafowl.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Today's episode will feature​ ​​
​​ ​us three holobirds!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice! We got​ ​​
​​ ​a pretty good group going!​ ​​
​​​ ​holobirds FTW!​ ​​
​​​ ​FTW!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways, I'll be the MC for today.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's all do our best!​ ​​
​​​ ​Today's holo's Bonjour is a bit rare,​ ​​
​​​ ​with members from​ ​​
​​ ​EN, ID, and JP respectively.​ ​​
​​​ ​As your first time here,​ ​​
​​ ​Reine-san, how do you feel?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm nervous! But I'll give it my all!​ ​​
​​​ ​My heart is racing!​ ​​
​​​ ​We talk a lot in​ ​​
​​​ ​Japanese on this show,​ ​​
​​​ ​I think this show is a great opportunity for​ ​​
​​ ​you two to show off to the Japanese fans.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone in Japan, are ya watching?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are ya watching?​ ​​
​​​ ​Please keep supporting holobirds!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, as you've seen,​ ​​
​​​ ​we holobirds get along​ ​​
​​ ​with each other quite well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways, let's move on​ ​​
​​ ​to our first segment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Random Rapid Fire Interrogation!​ ​​
​​​ ​For this segment, the newbie Reine-senpai​ ​​
​​​ ​will be pelted with a barrage of questions​ ​​
​​ ​by us, who've been on this show before.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you ready, Reine-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​OK... OK. OK!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, let's begin!​ ​​
​​​ ​20 Question Barrage...​ ​​
​​​ ​Start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please teach us an Indonesian word​ ​​
​​ ​that's easy to use!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mantap!​ ​​
​​​ ​It means "Awesome!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Awesome!​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you like about me?​ ​​
​​​ ​I like how you seem mature,​ ​​
​​​ ​but you also have a few screws loose.​ ​​
​​​ ​"A few screws loose"...?!​ ​​
​​​ ​In a good way!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you went on a trip with the two​ ​​
​​ ​of us, where would you like to go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh... Um... Hawaii!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hawaii, nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​A nice choice.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's your favorite JRPG?​ ​​
​​​ ​Probably Persona.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's fun.​ ​​
​​​ ​Describe a holobird member​ ​​
​​ ​without saying their name!​ ​​
​​​ ​Describe?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's pretty difficult.​ ​​
​​​ ​Their hair is long,​ ​​
​​​ ​and they seem sweet, but​ ​​
​​​ ​they have a bit of a twisted side to them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mumei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Your favorite hololive song (any).​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh...​ ​​
​​​ ​"Love Me Love Me" by Pavolia Reine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please listen to it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Lastly, what 3 things would​ ​​
​​ ​you bring to a deserted island?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, and the two birds​ ​​
​​ ​on top of her head.​ ​​
​​​ ​And that's it!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's all the questions​ ​​
​​ ​we had for Reine-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to go back to that​ ​​
​​ ​holobird question earlier.​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too!​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to hear your description​ ​​
​​ ​of everyone else, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​A mature lady...​ ​​
​​​ ​Who could a mature lady​ ​​
​​​ ​possibly be?​ ​​
​​​ ​She's a mature lady,​ ​​
​​​ ​Lui...?​ ​​
​​​ ​but she's has a few screws loose.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a compliment!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a compliment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Having a screw loose is​ ​​
​​ ​a compliment in hololive. Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​In hololive, it's a compliment.​ ​​
​​​ ​Next is, um...​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh snap!​ ​​
​​​ ​U wot?!​ ​​
​​​ ​My dictionary is lacking!​ ​​
​​​ ​Only orange.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sorry!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's Kiara-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​Describe me for real!​ ​​
​​ ​Like my personality or something.​ ​​
​​​ ​Idol!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's very idol-like.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's me!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's good at dancing, for example.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's Kiara-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​And she's orange.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm the Orange Ranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​And...​ ​​
​​​ ​Lastly?​ ​​
​​​ ​Lastly...​ ​​
​​​ ​Her dancing... skills? No, not that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Her stamina is insane.​ ​​
​​​ ​Her stamina is bottomless.​ ​​
​​​ ​Subaru-senpai, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Subaru-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​We got to hear everyone's​ ​​
​​ ​description. I'm satisfied.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine, what about yourself?​ ​​
​​​ ​How would you describe yourself?​ ​​
​​​ ​Myself?!​ ​​
​​​ ​How about Kiara-senpai do that?​ ​​
​​​ ​To be honest,​ ​​
​​​ ​my impression of her changed quite a bit​ ​​
​​​ ​from our Maldives trip the other week.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh? How so?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, she acts quite differently​ ​​
​​ ​than you'd expect.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow, really?​ ​​
​​​ ​How so, exactly?​ ​​
​​​ ​For example...​ ​​
​​​ ​She seems elegant in general,​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-huh. True.​ ​​
​​​ ​but she also has a lot of cute,​ ​​
​​ ​child-like sides to her​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat? I wanna see what that's like.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, let's go on a trip with the three of us.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's all go to Hawaii together.​ ​​
​​​ ​You mentioned it earlier,​ ​​
​​ ​so let's go to Hawaii.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hawaii!​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now for our next segment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Teach Us, Lui-Nee!​ ​​
​​ ​Hot-blooded Talk Cheminar!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one is my segment.​ ​​
​​​ ​I, Takane Lui, a former top-ranked​ ​​
​​ ​businesswoman in Japan,​ ​​
​​​ ​will teach you communication skills​ ​​
​​ ​with wide-ranging use​ ​​
​​​ ​from business to​ ​​
​​ ​just talking with your friends.​ ​​
​​​ ​With this segment, hololive's​ ​​
​​ ​communication skills will go through the roof!​ ​​
​​​ ​Instructor​ ​​
​​​ ​What to say when you oversleep​ ​​
​​ ​and break a date with your friend?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to throw out a situation,​ ​​
​​​ ​and we'll test whether you can​ ​​
​​ ​give the best response for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Today, we'll be using a variety of prompts​ ​​
​​​ ​provided to us by the viewers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please focus your attention on the board.​ ​​
​​​ ​How to get a friend​ ​​
​​ ​who always lets you choose,​ ​​
​​​ ​and doesn't ever choose themselves,​ ​​
​​​ ​to choose something first.​ ​​
​​​ ​For example, when you go out to eat with them,​ ​​
​​​ ​and you ask them what they want,​ ​​
​​ ​but they always answer, "Anything's fine."​ ​​
​​​ ​So I'd like you two to think about a way​ ​​
​​​ ​to get them to choose something first​ ​​
​​​ ​in those kinds of situations.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thinking time starts... now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are they both answering in Japanese?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm done!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​I did my best to write in hiragana.​ ​​
​​​ ​It was quite the complex question, too.​ ​​
​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​My pleasure.​ ​​
​​​ ​And that's it for our thinking time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's reveal our answers one by one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who wants to go first?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not too sure about this one...​ ​​
​​​ ​Where's our confidence gone?!​ ​​
​​​ ​No one wants to go first?​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, why don't we start with​ ​​
​​ ​the oldest member here, Kiara-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at Kiara-senpai's answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Is there anything you haven't tried on here?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Since we're eating out and all,​ ​​
​​​ ​I tried asking them out​ ​​
​​ ​for something they haven't tried.​ ​​
​​​ ​I like the way you phrased the question.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you very much, Ms. Takane!​ ​​
​​​ ​I should try that out myself.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine-senpai, are you ready?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine-senpai's answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll decide something next time,​ ​​
​​​ ​so what do anata, you want?​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to know what you want to eat!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's really nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​So saying something like,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I'll decide next time, so you should decide​ ​​
​​​ ​what you want to eat today,​ ​​
​​ ​and I'll have that too."​ ​​
​​​ ​True. If you tell them you'll decide next time,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's a lot less stressful for them, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at my answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​My answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​"Since I chose last time, I want​ ​​
​​ ​to have what you want this time!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​This time, Reine-chan's is similar.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the same as Reine-chan's.​ ​​
​​​ ​For this, though,​ ​​
​​​ ​there's no single correct answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-senpai and Reine-senpai's answers​ ​​
​​​ ​were both great, so a round​ ​​
​​ ​of applause for both of them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Really nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seems like you do need to get​ ​​
​​ ​all the mature ladies together​ ​​
​​​ ​to raise the bar for communication skills.​ ​​
​​​ ​Since La+ isn't here anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Poopy hehe​ ​​
​​​ ​Gehehehe...​ ​​
​​​ ​The kids are gone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the next situation!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one's embarrassing.​ ​​
​​​ ​You and your friends​ ​​
​​ ​reserved a restaurant and went,​ ​​
​​​ ​but the reservation date wasn't today,​ ​​
​​​ ​so you couldn't go in.​ ​​
​​​ ​For this, we're the person​ ​​
​​​ ​who made the reservation, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's correct.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine, how you doing?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'm good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wha?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm done! Sorry for the wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you both finished writing?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Done?​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyone want to go first​ ​​
​​​ ​this time around?​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine first. Reine first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine-senpai seems confident.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll go first this time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please show your answer, Reine-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Say "Sorry!" clearly,​ ​​
​​​ ​and then give recommendations​ ​​
​​ ​for some other restaurants.​ ​​
​​​ ​Even if your friends say they don't mind,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's still bothersome,​ ​​
​​​ ​so apologizing first is probably a good idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​Saying "Sorry" right away.​ ​​
​​​ ​True.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then suggesting some restaurants nearby.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, "Sorry about this.​ ​​
​​ ​How about this place nearby?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's close and their food's great.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about it?"​ ​​
​​​ ​I think that's great.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's embarrassing!​ ​​
​​​ ​In business you see this​ ​​
​​ ​all the time as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Apologizing first,​ ​​
​​ ​then giving another suggestion.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm impressed at how​ ​​
​​ ​you got that part right too.​ ​​
​​​ ​You pass!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, Ms. Takane!​ ​​
​​​ ​And Kiara-senpai's answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Apologizing is a given.​ ​​
​​​ ​After that, have everyone vote on where to go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Having everyone decide together.​ ​​
​​​ ​That ends up being more fun, as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Turning a mishap into,​ ​​
​​ ​well not a positive thing,​ ​​
​​​ ​but into an event​ ​​
​​ ​is a pretty wonderful idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't think of that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at my answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​"I'm really sorry! I'll find somewhere​ ​​
​​ ​close by we can go real quick!"​ ​​
​​​ ​It's pretty close to what Reine-senpai had.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I really liked how Kiara-senpai​ ​​
​​​ ​turned her mistake into an event.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't think of that option,​ ​​
​​​ ​and it's pretty charming,​ ​​
​​​ ​so it surprised me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​This situation reminded me​ ​​
​​​ ​of something in the past.​ ​​
​​​ ​In my previous workplace,​ ​​
​​​ ​we had a customer​ ​​
​​​ ​that told us they had a reservation.​ ​​
​​​ ​I couldn't find their reservation anywhere,​ ​​
​​​ ​but then I noticed that they had​ ​​
​​ ​a reservation for that day a year later.​ ​​
​​​ ​A year later?!​ ​​
​​​ ​They seemed really embarrassed.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was really stressful.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's embarrassing to make that mistake.​ ​​
​​​ ​A whole year is a bit shocking.​ ​​
​​​ ​Our next segment is...​ ​​
​​​ ​KFP's Road to Greatness!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Kiara-senpai's segment!​ ​​
​​ ​Please explain it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm actually the CEO of KFP,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'm currently looking for​ ​​
​​ ​a manager for the Japan branch!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll have you two participate in a test​ ​​
​​ ​to see whether you're fit for the job.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you ready? It's a test.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine-senpai will have to​ ​​
​​ ​come to Japan if she gets accepted.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do well,​ ​​
​​​ ​and it certainly won't hurt your chances!​ ​​
​​​ ​Won't hurt our chances.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get on with the test!​ ​​
​​​ ​First up is this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Manager Qualification #1:​ ​​
​​​ ​Proper assignment of staff!​ ​​
​​​ ​A manager needs to have​ ​​
​​ ​the skill to figure out​ ​​
​​​ ​what task each staff member​ ​​
​​ ​is best suited to.​ ​​
​​​ ​In a Japanese 4-character compound,​ ​​
​​​ ​that'd be "Right man for the job."​ ​​
​​​ ​You will be shown pictures​ ​​
​​ ​of four holo members.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll assign them to​ ​​
​​ ​work the register, cook in the kitchen,​ ​​
​​​ ​hand out flyers, or deliver orders.​ ​​
​​​ ​As you decide, please think about​ ​​
​​​ ​who seems best for which job.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​If your assignments​ ​​
​​​ ​are the same as mine,​ ​​
​​​ ​then you're fit for the manager role!​ ​​
​​​ ​The holo members applying​ ​​
​​ ​for part-time jobs this time are...​ ​​
​​​ ​They're certainly... unique.​ ​​
​​​ ​True.​ ​​
​​​ ​Quite a unique collection of individuals.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who handles the kitchen is fairly important,​ ​​
​​​ ​That's true.​ ​​
​​​ ​so please put extra consideration on that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to show their answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do it all together now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here are their answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at Reine-chan's first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Luna-senpai at the counter. Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Haato-senpai at the kitche― Ugh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really...​ ​​
​​​ ​Suisei-senpai handing out flyers.​ ​​
​​​ ​And Chloe doing delivery.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why this arrangement?​ ​​
​​​ ​As you can see,​ ​​
​​​ ​this is my ideal setup for KFP Indonesia.​ ​​
​​​ ​For the cashier counters,​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh... Okay...?​ ​​
​​​ ​I chose Luna-senpai​ ​​
​​​ ​for her appealing way of talking.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can also see her being really​ ​​
​​ ​enthusiastic behind the counter.​ ​​
​​​ ​uwu​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure about having​ ​​
​​ ​her in your kitchen?​ ​​
​​​ ​It'll be fine!​ ​​
​​​ ​I remember Haato-senpai​ ​​
​​​ ​does a lot of cooking streams...​ ​​
​​​ ​She does cook quite a lot.​ ​​
​​​ ​🔥HAACHAMA COOKING🔥​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a nice way of putting it.​ ​​
​​​ ​For the flyers,​ ​​
​​​ ​I chose Suisei-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​She has that charisma​ ​​
​​ ​we could put to good use.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about having her sing​ ​​
​​ ​while handing out flyers?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a pretty good idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! Just like that!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sure people would love it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​I put Chloe on delivery.​ ​​
​​​ ​My reason being that as an orca,​ ​​
​​​ ​she'll be able to deliver​ ​​
​​​ ​your food anywhere: land or sea.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh, that makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's your logic, huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pretty good.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think she fits that role.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's my ideal KFP Indonesia.​ ​​
​​​ ​Tell me the reasoning for your picks, Lui-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay! So I put Haato-senpai​ ​​
​​ ​on the cashier counter​ ​​
​​​ ​because she knows​ ​​
​​ ​how to speak in English,​ ​​
​​​ ​which lets her handle​ ​​
​​ ​foreign customers well.​ ​​
​​​ ​The other reason is that I absolutely​ ​​
​​ ​don't want her in the kitchen.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's true.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let Luna-senpai handle​ ​​
​​ ​the kitchen since she can cook.​ ​​
​​​ ​Chloe has periods​ ​​
​​ ​where she doesn't bathe,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I want to keep her away from food​ ​​
​​​ ​as much as humanly possible.​ ​​
​​​ ​She might pose herself as​ ​​
​​​ ​a significant health risk for the food,​ ​​
​​​ ​That's gotten me worried.​ ​​
​​​ ​hence why I sent her out​ ​​
​​ ​to hand out flyers instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Suisei-senpai does things very thoroughly,​ ​​
​​​ ​so putting her in charge of deliveries​ ​​
​​​ ​would make the entire​ ​​
​​ ​delivery process more efficient.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can see that, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm, okay then!​ ​​
​​​ ​Time for me to reveal my answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's totally different!​ ​​
​​​ ​None of them match!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm, well... There are some matches.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​So first off, I'd put Suisei-senpai​ ​​
​​ ​in charge of the counter.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd assign her there since she has​ ​​
​​​ ​a really charming face and personality.​ ​​
​​​ ​That should make her easy to talk to.​ ​​
​​​ ​I put Luna-senpai in the kitchen since​ ​​
​​​ ​I heard that she knows how to cook.​ ​​
​​​ ​For the flyer distribution,​ ​​
​​​ ​I was considering Haachama​ ​​
​​ ​for her upbeat personality.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's also cute so I'm sure​ ​​
​​ ​that would help in her work.​ ​​
​​​ ​I will never let her set foot in the kitchen.​ ​​
​​​ ​Absolutely no chance.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Same thoughts. Same braincell.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just as you said, Reine-chan,​ ​​
​​​ ​Chloe-chan can travel through water,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I put her in charge of deliveries.​ ​​
​​​ ​With all that said,​ ​​
​​ ​I can say that both of you​ ​​
​​​ ​got some parts of it correctly,​ ​​
​​​ ​so you both passed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do not put Haachama in the kitchen though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​The next skill we test for is this one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Manager Check #2: Memory Recall!​ ​​
​​​ ​Memory Recall!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're all holobirds in this group,​ ​​
​​​ ​so we're all probably birdbrained as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm expecting you guys to have​ ​​
​​ ​good memory recall, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​You sure?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm an exceptionally special bird,​ ​​
​​ ​so I should be fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​For this part, we'll have you two​ ​​
​​ ​look at a picture of a burger.​ ​​
​​​ ​The burger has its parts​ ​​
​​​ ​arranged in a very specific order,​ ​​
​​ ​and you have only a few seconds​ ​​
​​​ ​to memorize the order of assembly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get to our first burger! Bam!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, that was fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​Literally 10 seconds!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's have Reine-chan go first!​ ​​
​​​ ​From the bottom:​ ​​
​​​ ​bun, patty, patty,​ ​​
​​​ ​bun, patty, patty, sauce, tomato,​ ​​
​​​ ​lettuce, and then bun.​ ​​
​​​ ​Eh, uh... Ah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Same with her.​ ​​
​​​ ​My answer's the same.​ ​​
​​​ ​Same for you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep, the same.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh. Hmm, okay. I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bun, meat, meat,​ ​​
​​​ ​ketchup, tomato, lettuce, and bun.​ ​​
​​​ ​This ordering is from the bottom.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep, from the bottom.​ ​​
​​​ ​From right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well umm...​ ​​
​​ ​I guess you two got it right...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at it again!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bun, meat, meat, ketchup, tomato, lettuce!​ ​​
​​​ ​And bun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Perfect!​ ​​
​​​ ​Perfect.​ ​​
​​​ ​Great!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel relieved that...​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't need to give my own answer...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move on to our next segment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Romantic Laboratory!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh la la!​ ​​
​​​ ​This segment will be handled by Reine-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mamma mia!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's her Romantic Laboratory!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh dear me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Truth be told, I tend to​ ​​
​​​ ​make a pastime out of daydreaming.​ ​​
​​​ ​I particularly love dreaming up​ ​​
​​ ​romantic scenarios!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gehehehe...​ ​​
​​​ ​In this segment,​ ​​
​​​ ​we will be given situations―​ ​​
​​​ ​Dangerous ones, to be specific.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll be taking those dangerous situations,​ ​​
​​​ ​and think of ways to turn them​ ​​
​​ ​into enjoyable romances.​ ​​
​​​ ​We should be able to reimagine​ ​​
​​ ​them as romantic scenarios​ ​​
​​​ ​all of us could enjoy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see how it works!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start off with Situation #1!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're a spy and the target is the enemy boss.​ ​​
​​​ ​One day,​ ​​
​​​ ​the boss manages to​ ​​
​​ ​find out your identity as a spy.​ ​​
​​​ ​O M G!​ ​​
​​​ ​Transform this life-or-death situation​ ​​
​​​ ​into a love story with a happy end!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eeek! They've found me out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've already thought of one!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've also thought of one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Damn, you guys are fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start with Lui-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​The floor is yours!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I ended up falling in love​ ​​
​​ ​with the enemy boss​ ​​
​​​ ​while hiding my spy identity from him.​ ​​
​​​ ​When I confess this to him, he says,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I would have had you executed by now,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I actually love you, even if you're a spy!"​ ​​
​​​ ​His clients are starting to suspect​ ​​
​​ ​a spy in the group,​ ​​
​​​ ​so in order to escape their hired guns,​ ​​
​​​ ​the two decide to flee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hold on! Mine's almost the same!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's all! How was it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Really now?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Exquisite!​ ​​
​​​ ​Splendid work!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hear Kiara's version―​ ​​
​​​ ​Yours is similar?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, mine's very similar.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a bit similar?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, in any case, let's hear it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I start?​ ​​
​​​ ​Start!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​So as we know, this is her...​ ​​
​​​ ​This is a spy's love story, and she's clearly​ ​​
​​​ ​in love with the enemy boss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meanwhile, the boss actually seems​ ​​
​​​ ​to hate his current job,​ ​​
​​ ​going as far as to say stuff like,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I wanna quit. I wanna do something else."​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh, I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's all he thinks about.​ ​​
​​​ ​The love affair was convenient timing for him,​ ​​
​​​ ​as it gave them an excuse​ ​​
​​ ​to escape to a deserted island.​ ​​
​​​ ​They flee here too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep! Exactly!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where no one can find them...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's my story!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's pretty good!​ ​​
​​​ ​An amazing story!​ ​​
​​​ ​A beautiful deserted island!​ ​​
​​​ ​Splendid!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's very romantic! Good work!​ ​​
​​​ ​Romantic!​ ​​
​​​ ​Both of your imaginations are very...​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice, I would say!​ ​​
​​​ ​Very very nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pretty much.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​But if you were to do it,​ ​​
​​ ​how would it go, Miss Reine?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, so!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is one of my favorite scenarios.​ ​​
​​​ ​When the spy goes,​ ​​
​​​ ​"Oh nyo! I've been found out!"​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm quite sure that she's afraid​ ​​
​​​ ​she's gonna fail her mission.​ ​​
​​​ ​Easy to see why.​ ​​
​​​ ​But then, the enemy boss says,​ ​​
​​​ ​"Don't worry, I, too,​ ​​
​​ ​am actually a spy!"​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know who he is​ ​​
​​ ​spying for though, but anyway!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ehh!​ ​​
​​​ ​He then says,​ ​​
​​ ​"You and I are the same...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get married!"​ ​​
​​​ ​And so,​ ​​
​​​ ​that straightforward style​ ​​
​​​ ​makes her fall for him.​ ​​
​​​ ​The two then get married.​ ​​
​​ ​And they lived happily ever after.​ ​​
​​​ ​The End!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's really good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hearing how other people imagine it​ ​​
​​​ ​gets me very excited!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is really great!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just being able to...​ ​​
​​​ ​You're clearly getting​ ​​
​​​ ​I kinda get you.​ ​​
​​​ ​real hype for this, Reine-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​The hype is real, Reine-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now for the next... the second one!​ ​​
​​​ ​The second one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start the next one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my god, that's a lot of kanji.​ ​​
​​​ ​So umm...​ ​​
​​​ ​You're an office lady working for a bank.​ ​​
​​​ ​One day,​ ​​
​​​ ​the bank you're working for​ ​​
​​ ​was raided by armed robbers!​ ​​
​​​ ​O M G!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yikes!​ ​​
​​​ ​The robbers take you hostage,​ ​​
​​​ ​holing themselves up in the bank.​ ​​
​​​ ​I got a story now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Same here.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are quick!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, I was―​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to have at least​ ​​
​​​ ​one thinking session,​ ​​
​​​ ​but you're both so fast!​ ​​
​​​ ​I expect no less from the holobirds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do we start?​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I hear your stories now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start this round with...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, if you please.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you're at the bank.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's just the two of you left at that bank.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just two...?​ ​​
​​​ ​All of a sudden...​ ​​
​​​ ​Just the two of them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Y'all wanna know right?​ ​​
​​​ ​So like,​ ​​
​​​ ​this office lady is​ ​​
​​​ ​scared and shaking in her boots.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then, all of a sudden,​ ​​
​​ ​another person comes into the bank!​ ​​
​​​ ​To everyone's surprise,​ ​​
​​ ​it was another robber!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Seeing both the office lady​ ​​
​​ ​and the previous robber,​ ​​
​​​ ​the new guy fires a shot at them.​ ​​
​​​ ​The office lady stands​ ​​
​​ ​in front of the robber,​ ​​
​​​ ​giving him some cover.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She then gets hit by the bullet and dies!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?! Where's the happy end?!​ ​​
​​​ ​The first robber thinks​ ​​
​​ ​to himself, "You saved me..."​ ​​
​​​ ​That's so tragic...​ ​​
​​​ ​He gets into a romantic melancholy,​ ​​
​​​ ​So sad...​ ​​
​​​ ​and starts a fight with the other robber.​ ​​
​​​ ​But he ends up dying,​ ​​
​​ ​so he and the office lady are both dead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Where's the happy end...?​ ​​
​​​ ​They're both happy in heaven.​ ​​
​​​ ​Happy in heaven, huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, yes, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a bittersweet ending.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hear from Lui-san next!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright.​ ​​
​​​ ​One day, a robber raided my workplace.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone was held hostage.​ ​​
​​​ ​But then, a guy behind me whispers,​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Lui-san, run to that door. Please trust me."​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what he said to me.​ ​​
​​​ ​The guy who whispered​ ​​
​​ ​was my unassuming deskmate,​ ​​
​​​ ​Takahashi-kun.​ ​​
​​​ ​Takahashi-kun?!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was the unassuming and​ ​​
​​ ​slightly incompetent Takahashi-kun!​ ​​
​​​ ​He often made mistakes at work,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I decided to believe him​ ​​
​​ ​at that moment.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seeing us rush to the door,​ ​​
​​ ​the robber points at us, threatening to shoot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Takahashi-kun retaliates by charging​ ​​
​​ ​and punching the robber.​ ​​
​​​ ​I manage to run away,​ ​​
​​​ ​and the police come charging in.​ ​​
​​​ ​The police then catch the robber.​ ​​
​​​ ​Takahashi-kun then told me,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I wanted to protect you, Lui-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​So cool...​ ​​
​​​ ​So I... went and made myself stronger."​ ​​
​​​ ​How was it?​ ​​
​​​ ​That was good!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's an everyday hero story!​ ​​
​​​ ​How would you do it, Reine-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a very spicy situation​ ​​
​​ ​that makes you say,​ ​​
​​​ ​"Oh no!"​ ​​
​​​ ​The office lady would go,​ ​​
​​​ ​"Aah! Help me! Help me!"​ ​​
​​​ ​And then,​ ​​
​​​ ​she'd suddenly recognize the robber!​ ​​
​​​ ​It turned out to be her childhood friend!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Seriously?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​"Why are you doing this?!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Why?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Turns out that the robber​ ​​
​​​ ​was brainwashed by someone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, what was it... Mind control?​ ​​
​​​ ​When the robber saw the office lady's face,​ ​​
​​​ ​the memory struck him!​ ​​
​​​ ​And, at that moment,​ ​​
​​​ ​he came to his senses.​ ​​
​​​ ​"Oh, dear me! I'm so sorry!"​ ​​
​​​ ​"I have modotta (returned) to my senses!"​ ​​
​​​ ​"I have modotta!"​ ​​
​​​ ​And then,​ ​​
​​​ ​and then, and then!​ ​​
​​​ ​So there's that brainwashing guy, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​The two of them set out​ ​​
​​ ​in order to find that criminal.​ ​​
​​​ ​As they went about it,​ ​​
​​​ ​the two grew closer,​ ​​
​​​ ​until they eventually​ ​​
​​​ ​started having feelings for each other.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then they found the culprit,​ ​​
​​​ ​and defeated him.​ ​​
​​​ ​At the end, he goes,​ ​​
​​ ​"Thanks for staying with me..."​ ​​
​​​ ​"You know... I've always... loved..."​ ​​
​​​ ​Too long!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry!​ ​​
​​​ ​* This story has been​ ​​
​​ ​cut down considerably​ ​​
​​​ ​Just a bit more!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm about to finish!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're quite passionate​ ​​
​​ ​about this, Reine-chan.​ ​​
​​​ ​We can clearly see it​ ​​
​​ ​when it comes to these topics.​ ​​
​​​ ​That passion burns hard.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's definitely a passion of mine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Intense...​ ​​
​​​ ​And we're done!​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you all feel about today's show?​ ​​
​​​ ​It was so fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​We got three holobirds on set today.​ ​​
​​​ ​There was a lot of passion​ ​​
​​ ​felt with today's topics.​ ​​
​​​ ​When you get all​ ​​
​​ ​the holobirds in one place,​ ​​
​​​ ​it starts getting all noisy and chaotic.​ ​​
​​​ ​We do get pretty noisy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like loud chirping birds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Shrill, screaming birds.​ ​​
​​​ ​The MC for the next episode​ ​​
​​ ​will be Kiara-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck, and do your best!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll try!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be leaving this week, so yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll leave the next episode to you, Kiara-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh right...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's been short, but goodbye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's all have a trip again sometime.​ ​​
​​​ ​A trip!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do it!​ ​​
​​​ ​This show was brought to you by Takane Lui,​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara,​ ​​
​​​ ​and Pavolia Reine!​ ​​
​​​ ​That is all!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's all folks!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for watching!​ ​​
​​​ ​Until next time, see you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye-bye!​ ​​