[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
you know how tempting it is to just
record you right now don't worry i i
have all these noises on stream right
now
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
are you ready
[Music]
i'm sorry i don't think
okay i'm opening my stream are you okay
okay let's go okay let's go three two
one
[Music]
oh my goodness
i've been jamming to this for how long
you know
um 30 minutes i don't know not that much
we only got together 10 minutes ago
yeah
but um i could feel my sanity points
dropped in quite a bit
i can't help it when that music plays i
ain't going
to the guitar
[Music]
it's so good
oh yes definitely oh where's my
microphone there's my microphone hello
hello everyone uh all right
it's another
taco totty collab
that's right whoa
we didn't let you wait for too long
this is right
we're driving safely today no no no no
no no
no drivers i'm hoping following traffic
rules teach me something today
teach you what teach me how to be
good good good
oh i'm not very good
you oh don't lie don't lie you belong
people people know that i'm good but i'm
always like
i'm almost so bad whenever i play with
viewers
how
you you put the mario kart in your
schedule quite a lot in the coming days
i saw that
yeah
i'm aiming for fourth place in the group
y4
um it's not too high not too low you
know just just the right place and kind
of in the middle top ish is my it's my
goal that is interesting um yeah because
i'm also
not aiming for
the top or
and also not for the bottom i'm
aiming for something average because
you know you guys know my strategy is to
not move on to the next round
i'll see you at the soccer cup kiara no
no no we're in the same group so
you know we're fighting for the middle
place we're fighting for the middle both
of us but who
not many people can get the middle
so it's actually kind of a problem
though
you know
you don't want to win and you don't you
will see
well everybody we will start out by
playing uh only with me and ina and some
npcs and then later after the first or
second round or so whatever we'll have
you guys join in and challenge us and we
will crash you like little bugs and ants
yeah
you sure about that
yes we have to we have to like you know
we have to feel it and believe in it
otherwise it won't happen that's the bio
believe it
that's it for you i haven't heard that
one
yeah you should uh join my room
oh oh sorry forgot to forgot to wear
doko ah do i have to go
multiplayer no online player online
online play yeah oh my god
it's been too long
you know i'm actually a bit worried um
that the tournament will go well in
terms of internet connection
oh yeah that's true yeah
cause like just gotta believe even with
uh like you know with with overseas
viewers when we go in the tournament
often the room will just break and fall
apart right
oh
yeah we will have a lot of ping too
maybe depending but you know that's just
how it is with the online games you
gotta
become one with the latency be welcomed
one with the ping oh hello kiara
welcome you see me already
yeah i'm still choosing my cart uh which
one was the one that came
in
ah damn it which one was it again
i have it button no i think there was a
cart that i wanted to use
which one
uh ah i think this one
this one right yet
uh and then the rest doesn't matter are
you going for speed or for control
i don't know oh
that's not good i just chose a cute card
that people said was good
really
yeah
oh oh but but people said it was good
okay so not only cute yeah
okay
yeah gosh this doesn't
matter but
weight acceleration
speed
acceleration
i'll just
um 150 cc no teams normal i have no calm
all vehicles four races right sounds
good to me baby yeah
heart race yes whoa whoa i forgot how to
go i haven't gotten to warm up
normal items no calm
[Music]
oh wait oh well well then we'll just do
against one another first
okay
oh [\h__\h]
japan versus austria
[Music]
i'm already slower than you
ah
why luigi's so popular
the whole life japan girls
apparently it's like the meta
uh
how do i use an item again
oh there we go
[Music]
take it easy come on
yeah
yeah you stole my eyes no that wasn't me
that wasn't you that was not me are you
sure i don't have any items
are you sure you disappear from the map
[Laughter]
suspicious nothing is suspicious here in
yeah you don't trust your gender
[Music]
what fireworks
it's okay once once the viewers start
coming
in that's what i'll be uh
yeah yeah now life is too easy on ya
i'm practicing a little bit off stream
too
me not yet i wanted to but i haven't
gotten to it yet
i actually played oh do you play my car
with your family sometimes no then you
meet up i don't have a family i live
alone yeah
i mean when you like gather for like
mario kart no she plays many games but
she doesn't really play console games i
guess
oh
should we go back and let people in and
let the npc's in maybe first
oh wait wait hold on
leave no
that's it
no
do i need to go out for that
i might have to leave the group a
communication error has occurred let's
go
i'll join you
oh but never mind
okay i'll remake the room cool yes
uh
yes
yeah mama told you mostly plays pc games
yeah
[Music]
okay i remade the room
wait if you play against friends then
you can't put npcs in is that no
did it say no
no
it's just uh hold on i wonder if it's in
here
oh there you go uh normal come easy come
promise computer right yeah computer
okay normal or hard
normal heart yeah
hard i guess because aqua senpai
how hard is that
i'm sure i'm sure it's like the 150
200cc type
[Music]
random let's go
let's go
you have to press the r1 button
i'm going to try also it's our
i can never tell which one is like the
l1 l2 i'm just like yeah
i press buttons that's why i can't play
rhythm games well i don't know where the
button are name
especially the ones on the controller
i'm just like what yeah
go away
get away
oh [\h__\h]
okay
i'll go ahead
oh wait i just realized i'm playing on
obs
[Music]
not in obs wouldn't help me much here
right now
i'm getting myself a little bit of a
handicap so
are you
stupid baby daisy i'm the only days in
here
[Music]
not too strong
this was the npc
[Music]
did everybody listen to mine and
inaudible
yes yes yes yes yes of course they did
[Music]
it's such a banger right yeah
yeah i've been listening to it too
like this
i missed all the coins i think a lot of
people got addicted to it
[Music]
why did i say i like this uh road i'm
doing pretty bad right
[Music]
oh man yeah i think i just have this is
hard first get a feeling again for the
for the
roads and then uh-huh once i have that
down i know i can think about other
things you always do battery steps
when they come
i was always here to stay on the sun
because of that
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
the audience in here so that you go more
to the bottom
you shouldn't be up that high
i'm sorry i don't sneak
all right i'll make a tournament hold on
[Music]
some people already used the ones from
before
oh where's my switch there we go
let's create a tournament oh
[Music]
tournament
oh wait but i can enter by friends and
rivals too can i no probably not i have
to turn them in the train search
there it is
there was a time the last time we did
the we did the enid tournament i was at
least decent i was better than i am now
and i can get there again
probably otherwise i'll end up in the
exactly
a little bit you'll be fine
otherwise hello i will have to go into a
second round after all because i'll end
up being 11 for
12. but that means more
time
[Music]
exactly
did you make it oh
i'm naming it right now taco tony
a 150cc no teams normal items no calm
all vehicles smart steering not okay
no smart steering
[Music]
uh give you the code first yeah
i will not show the code yet
guys don't worry i'm an experienced uh
streamer and yet i have had two hobbies
in a row um that that doesn't mean that
i am not an experienced streamer who
knows when to hide the screen
oops zero
and the zero and an
one another a100
okay
and now
and now hold on let me enter two
oh
where's there we go we shall right join
on the
on the screen
okay i can turn this back on are you
guys ready to challenge taco today
i'm not ready
okay are you gonna show it soon yeah i'm
gonna write it i'm writing it down now
okay because we're both already in
okay there you go
[Music]
welcome everybody done
there's a number
have you noticed that uh whenever
you or me or anyone plays mario kart no
matter what time it is there's always
the japanese bros who hear of it from
somewhere yes and they come at any given
time is it am 4 am doesn't that
especially
especially pick what i see in places
yeah the nose is scary
yeah there's some famous ones they
always show up
they're like in the it's like it's like
they're like so yeah and then they hear
mario kart they're just like
yeah i want maybe they have a discord
group mario
where they tell each other
yeah yeah this girl's swinging mario
gotta
okay where are you guys where are you
what are you doing
i would i like the cheap cheap pizza i
want to do chip chip peach but i'm going
to wait i'm so tired
really which is
i have
fond memories i don't like any of these
but you have to learn any all of them
you have to be able to deal with them
code oh the code is on the bottom left
guys under the uh new song covered with
inna out now sell a promotion
on the bottom line
is there a communication there that's
yeah
no no no no
no
that must be a bug 100
why do they all look the same
no this is the this is the npc like
communication error
what did that happen so are these npcs
that we're driving again
i think so oh my god
[Music]
versus the clones
we can only win now if we have the
winning otherwise they'll take over the
world
oh my god go over the world serious
business
oh it's really mario's
so are they which difficulty are they
they better be easy i don't know
probably not easy i didn't set
damage anything so
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
what's you i see you through no no no no
no
why you keep on blocking them
i know
i was feel so slow yeah me too
right
i need revenge on the clones
we're going star wars here
i wanna see chiara's for hitler
oh no
yeah i lost control
ah
why does this feel so slow i don't see
anything okay i'm back to second oh nice
is this really 150cc
it doesn't feel like it doesn't it
it's 50cc oh
oh
i must have forgotten to uh switch it i
was like why is this so slow like
it feels a little faster than 50. but to
be honest um
you know when i learn songs that have
like really fast uh
lyrics like raps
i sometimes um i turn
it down like i slow them down
to learn them easier
and then i go back into the actual song
speech and then it's it really works
like that's how i learn wraps
so maybe
[Music]
are you already proof
clunkier beat the marios beat the marios
anyway yeah maybe we're driving maybe
it's the same you start out slower than
you can be faster
150 right
yay
i'm pretty sure
racist mario i believe you i believe you
did maybe something got after
hmm
wait wait why don't they even have
there's people here there's people here
senpai
i know that
i'm not alone i'm using tail controls
real people how exciting uh okay
all right real people now you can't go
easy on them my chiara
remove your limiters oh sh
sure
i don't want to show that once you've
heard too much but uh
okay the zelda
kingdom
oh watermelon is
[Music]
oh wait there's two there's all
so many waluigi's
[Music]
that gets me in the mood of playing some
zelda games
i haven't played a zelda game in so long
i'm gonna show you guys my skills now
[Music]
i got it
you didn't change anything did you
oh
look at me being decent
wow kiara
maybe you're just strongest real people
never mind
either you're behind me loser i was
[Laughter]
[Music]
but if it means that you can be brought
all the way to oops oh where did that
rock go all the way to the bottom
then uh that means uh what i was i
thought i lost my point
oh oh yeah i think both of us being at
the bottom is not exactly a good thing
[Music]
against the other whole life members she
will also not do that well probably
yeah
not only me we're gonna let me exactly
hide together
i just wanna rest
me too but
it looks bad for us at the moment
[Music]
[Applause]
and now the ramp is back hey what a
bamboozle
so in the second uh lap it laughs it's
gone and it comes back and in the third
one
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i was um i was stuck in a wall at the
end oh
what what do you mean you didn't give me
a hug i need to
activate it what
you know you did that yourself you did
that yourself
you can't blame me for that i don't i
don't mind you giving me a hug but i
didn't feel it
into following the rules without us even
saying that yeah please leave your game
after one round everybody thank you
what was i saying uh
what was i saying what are they saying
before i realized what you're saying you
love me
who is that weird small vibe of the
green eyebrows
[Music]
it's so fun to see everybody's
creations here
[Laughter]
oh okay member let's go ah brazil
ina come to brazil come to brazilia
come to brazilia and you come to brazil
to visit one day come to brazil
one day but then going outside
come to brazilia
brazil
even if you say like me uh i have
already been to brazil they still
continue saying come to brazil
i don't know if they're even serious at
this point
[Music]
but yeah
i want to go back to brazil
they're like the anime convention in
brazil
yeah
[Music]
two times actually i went to sao paulo
it was very nice oh my god what is this
[Music]
my coins i hate this
oh gingerbread man
did the ginger really bread this man
what oh my his name is boom
slice pop oh no oh he's diving it didn't
get me because i had to start on since
one second ago
oh
time to catch up
nice oh bomb walked by me it was scary
a bomb
yeah a bomb like the walking bomb i
forgot do they even have a name
what oh [\h__\h] oh
hi
[Applause]
one more round one more round
that shell just hit
me well like the music change
oh that kite is so cute oh did that just
happen again can i predict thunder i
once again activated the star are you
the god of thunder
before the pundit
i can predict it would be nice to get
stars
see you later suckers
[Music]
nice nice skipping all the difficult
parts
[Laughter]
no i should have been i should have been
above you guys
but i must say i appreciate it
that was cool i saw you i saw you in
front of me for a split second but
why always at the end
oh
thank you
[Music]
oh my i want to say the race isn't over
until it's over
you know
what does that mean
the race isn't over until it's over
you can't let your guard down until the
very end
is that spider-man is spiderman me
scooterman
that is a
scooterman a very simplified spiderman
oh never knows that's cool oh no i'm
scared
[Music]
it is currently uh 6 00 am in japan
where did i get this
no they just see the mario kart and
everyone's schedules they're just like
i'll be there yeah i guess at least for
en members we have this uh just uh
tradition to put up uh
the schedules well japanese members
usually don't do that so
i guess they can plan ahead for us to
wake up early for our streams
yeah
maybe they just do just a few matches of
mario kart before they like go to work
and stuff yeah this is the new year's so
they might have time yeah also
sunday tomorrow or now in japan
this is spiderman i am going to beat
enos ass
why did i do that
hello do you want me to beat your ass
with my bare hands or with a like a
little uh
a slapping um
what
my items
[Music]
i lost seven items
oh unfortunate isn't it
[Music]
unfortunate isn't it
oh
[Music]
how can i beat her ass when she's behind
me
[Music]
oh no
you lost all the stuff
you dropped something inya
yeah it dropped my heart
if someone didn't take it
out of the way
[Applause]
uh guys remember the last collab
me and ina did
where
i
said something in the lines of
oh
it would be nice if
that was me
as if we would finally do ocha makino
someday huh i said that
[Music]
my viewers are so
annoyed
[Music]
justice
well who knows what i'll be teasing at
uh today that you guys will find out
about in a month
what would it be
[Music]
you couldn't know it's not obvious so i
won't get in trouble for it hey
but yeah finally we got ocha makino out
uh you you were the top batter in
singing you sang the first line didn't
you yeah
it's only cause uh
i only i used to only sing the first
verse
so i was only confident in the first
verse oh you only knew that one like by
height
a lot like the second verse i'm just
like uh
i don't know
especially the the wrap part near like
the like bay and cronies line it like i
because we had to record like this
and
that that little part took so long all
of a sudden they were like oh by the way
you're only seeing the first one
you went for all the trouble to learn
that second verse and then it didn't get
used
but i thought i did a pretty good job in
my recording maybe me too me too maybe
one day i already knew the song well so
oh [\h__\h] so i had no not a big trouble
singing it but i also i remember
i think the
the uh council members they
were saying like
wow the second verse is so difficult
and then it turns out council members
have to sing it
well it's a way to approve your japanese
council members
is that that's like singing japanese
songs it's a good way to practice
yes yeah yeah yes the pronunciation yes
yes
yes yes yes yes indeed
[Music]
oh there's a trick there
oh you get slow even as a ghost okay
okay ooh animal crossing
[Music]
i wasn't able to i was sleeping but
yeah i wasn't able to
i was uh i was i was busy feeding my
family in monaco
oh i guess uh in animal crossing they
also have like a countdown every hour
i guess yeah they do that's cool we did
we did our um countdown on animal
crossing as well oh
you like doing that
because like last year we did it for the
first time because mama niece played a
lot of my ammo across i was like you
know why don't we do the
countdown in
um animal crossing because it's really
cute
oh now we did it again this year
i once again stopped playing animal
crossing it's so sad
[Music]
again it is a big time thing to be
honest
[Music]
games like that they only catch my
attention for like a short amount of
time and then i never get back into it
same with sims
at least for sims like when i was
playing privately it was like that but
now that i play it kind of for for
streams
uh i i played way more often than i used
to and i actually get back to the same
family i used to continuously make new
families
uh when i was younger and playing it
privately like every time i would open
the game again i would make a new family
[Music]
i don't know this time the sun there
wasn't that many attacks on me for some
reason i don't i don't understand why
and i was even driving pretty well for
my standards i would say
but okay you're number one but i am two
times number one
exactly
double number one double number one
oh my god
oh just just so the other round you were
below me no no you're no you're waiting
because
i drove backwards a little bit on
purpose
no not on purpose if there was a driving
mishap look there's a chicken that
is you know the rubber chicken that goes
on your present never have it
actually i think one time we went to
like a like a retreat with like my
um music class
we were grating each other yeah continue
and then um someone brought chicken i
was like my best friend for the entire
like
entire retreat what and the teacher got
so annoyed because i kept like pressing
the chicken randomly
preaching free gym
[Music]
that is an insider for everybody who
doesn't get it
you're not in on it i guess
that's because of the phone conversation
we had right
jim is already free
you said something about jim being still
in the counting when i was like
where the hell is gym
well it was a lunch break back then you
know oh boy
did i just go
maybe
what the hell is going on
oh my god
oh my god i'm getting good items
must be nice
[\h__\h] now i've fallen behind again
because of one little mistake
it happened it's so easy mario kart one
mistake and you're out
just saw a wombo combo
oh man and bullets oh this is great
oh great i'm not so afraid
okay but i'm driving well when you say
cass here come on oh there's no snow's
on my phone
it's getting better
[Music]
hello
oh wait the next item is amazing
oh my god it's so crazy over here
oh
i hate this game
with all my coconuts
[Music]
jim is forever free
free that was not his immortal body that
is fair
gigi thank you
that was not fair
oh this i'm pretty bad at this course i
need some prac
subway
what happened there kiara explain what
happened i had a lucky streak oh
inaudible
that it always comes to my mario kart
rounds mine too
in a posture
for a moment i'm always like oh you're
cool for a moment i'm always like oh is
that real enough
no
look at me i look so derp
yeah you know you need to oh my god
your face turned around what happened
and another chicken as well
oh no
there's a lot of you guys
did you get them to help you what
happened are you sabotaging the race are
you trying to make clones of yourself so
that i get confused i bet that's the
cooler you know or something um
[Music]
i don't know they have they're from
germany they have something in common
inna versus her evil twins
it's okay that means if they win that i
technically win too because they're me
right
that's how it works that's how clones
work
yeah
i think so
no
yeah okay let's rock this
[Music]
look at this
this makes me dizzy
this race this road is really a little
bit like what
like tilted everything's perfect yeah
oh no
[Music]
i almost ran off course
i hate myself with my own bumping huh oh
that happens that happens
take care of your kfp they're bumping
into people on the road
go camping
oh my god
[Music]
i didn't predict those
oh as if i wasn't already fast enough
man
oh come on
oh no
[Music]
this time i wasn't so far away from you
yeah yeah yeah let me try to fix my chat
quickly
i hope it's fun for you guys this is
always nice to be able to play with the
audience you are getting better you
don't lie to me
you are you are you are okay you know
they say they say luck is a skill you're
getting better lucky skill
[Music]
oh you know you know this is our first
collab in 2022
i got a chat back is my first stream in
2022. oh really is it oh
yeah whoo
well you had to get the clip stream
earlier but this is my first with you
hey
yeah
oh theory because now the clip stream is
private this is my first stream
yes so
hold on no i popped i made the sims 4
stream public again that was before 2021
but now it's public in 2022 so no but
originally i mean originally in 2020 and
then this is now now for a little while
yeah cute
that's cute
it's like bae but also favorite yeah
oh it looks like both too good job on
that one mm-hmm
yeah i was like i was wondering if there
was b-max but at least b-mix
you know what game are you looking
forward to the most in 2022
uh what's coming out uh the new zelda
breath of the wild and uh this month
coming out end of this month is um
the new pokemon
oh
what is my problem what else are people
looking forward to uh elven ring haha
i guess
uh
i'm guessing
some side game of tales off will come
out nothing big
yeah they bring out a new game every
year
i think something small
uh probably a new ride looking no no no
probably it's a fact
no but what would i stream
oh no
[Music]
wait
let's start
[Music]
oh
i'm definitely lost in this race no no
[Music]
it's garfield but space
what if for real are you kidding hey
chad are you joking is that what it's
called no that's you guys are joking
right you guys are messing with me now
like
that item i want to use that my bullet
oh i'm gonna get another one
go away you know
hi
go away
[Music]
what happening
this actually i'm feeling better at this
one than many others
because i never go left but people tell
me it's it's better to go left really
doesn't really matter i go every i go a
different direction every time i play
this map
wait let's crawl on me
i am mine i was like
it's not crony it's it's like a imposter
it's a cook you have finished the chosen
ah you i think you did some some
wrong settings
let me read it
let's see if everything should be uh
no no i'll otherwise i'll wait one one
round that's okay
but if i if i like join i'll be in a
random room
oh
well i didn't know the setting is that
we're like that should we change the
room then so we can get rid of the
settings i'm probably not gonna get into
this round of view yeah
no i didn't even join yet so oh oh you
got kicked out too
yeah yeah oh i'm joining already you
could join let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go i
don't know though i think it's fine
because there's like 400 people but i'm
spectating right now i'll make it in
make way for the priestess everybody
move
lay down the red carpet
don't work
yeah you think so oh spectating oh are
we in the same one yeah
who are you spectating i'm a link
there's two links an isabelle an inkling
girl craig mcgee from canada oh
canada
oh we're in different races
oh
there's like 480 people at least trying
to play so how would you wait what does
it say that's somewhere
like when i went out to see the um
see the room it said yeah what 400
people are looking let's make it like a
new room
okay
uh we could go into one of my
tournaments
wait how do i get out of here though
ah
quit okay sorry guys sorry spectators
i'm not very good at making tournament
rooms into one of mine um let me hide
the screen one card
online play i'll write you the number
huh
okay
search by code
okay okay
sorry guys new code
[Music]
there it is
okay and i'm joined
the new the code is updated guys on the
bottom of my screen yeah i need to i
need to update my code mine's not
updated
you but did you already press enter
yeah okay good
new code to this
are you ready
yes uh almost
almost
[Music]
oh no i'm scared i don't think that is
you right here
huh
that is you right here's me
i wanna go to the waterpark
what's the [\h__\h] episode
[Music]
i have only been to like like public
pools but like something dope like that
no
with like
with with with
fancy stuff like that
this is like
kfp people participating
[Music]
they've been here before yeah they
probably had the tournament saved
yeah and we're guessing that i was gonna
go into that one woohoo
cafe you know what to do help me they
never do
yeah
they only helped me in slippery dial
which is pretty nice too
oh yeah those are nice
[Music]
you know before the stream i was
watching
um while quickly eating i was watching a
video i was watching some cooking
videos um
and one of them was how to make
blueberry cheesecake and made me think
of you oh
i want to try it
you should you made cheesecake right was
it easy
it was really easy
did you crash the cookies
cookies yeah
for the ground of the cheesecake did you
make it
crackers
i actually have a box left over i've
been munching
wow
[Music]
also actually when i went to buy food i
bought a fortune
did you give cookie your fortune not yet
i wanted to open it up on stream
oh
and i i don't know if i should see it as
a fortune towards my mario kart uh
winning chances or as a fortune towards
my whole year
[Music]
i need an item
someone just directly through banana
peeler i've got good chances
[Music]
[Applause]
that was me
you could say we're in the same
placement anyway let me open my fortune
cookie down i love the taste of country
cookies
okay
so
buy a fortune cookie says probably
something in german
oh there's something in italian and in
oh here oh
what what did you say
the most
should i read it i'll read it in german
i read it i read it in english at the
end so that you get extra confused
[Music]
the most dangerous heart diseases
continue to be envy hatred and everest
forever is so whatever
what the [\h__\h] is that supposed to tell
me
[Laughter]
the most dangerous heart diseases
continue to be envy hatred and ever ever
rise to restoration
i guess it's just saying that you know
those negative emotions are bad for your
heart yeah then i shouldn't be uh en
envious or
or feel hatred towards people or
whatever and or greedy
[Music]
i see
another one of the
from the other mother
no
i miss sad who hurt you
oh that crunch
that crunch is next level
what is that microphone setting for that
crown
it's yes
[Music]
okay i got a new power
i've had a revelation
uh-huh
[Music]
i haven't played that many
so i can't really give you a good answer
but the one that i i remember playing
was on the ds oh yes yes on the vs it
was yeah the train one the what
there was like a spirit train or
something
oh
[Music]
that is one of the worst um celebrities
oh is it
i wouldn't know i still enjoyed it oh
i'm sure i'm sure it was a fun in its
own way
but you missed out on so much quality
games
i did enjoy watching a playthrough of it
though um i watched someone play it this
that one and phantom hourglass spirit
tracks and phantoms oh
both the s games both not very uh
not very
not that good as as other
games but cute definitely cute
why do you not play any elegance were
you like into a different franchise at
the time where delta was popular played
that many games when i was little
[Music]
she was not a gamer girl
busy with other things huh what were you
doing busy drawing
i'm just kidding
there's a drawing already
back then
as a child
yeah i mean my parents didn't love me
oh come on
i mean i was when i was younger i was
also more watching oh you know we were
so close again
watching
and then people just bumped into me
yeah sure sure you seen that after
you're in front of me kiara
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was right behind that army and then i
got distracted by uh
distracted by
life
oh by me when i was doing stunning good
looks
even though i was behind you how could
that you'd be distracted by that
i can't i can look in many directions
it's so cute
oh
[Music]
looks like a oh i guess you're seeing a
difference is this is that saplings was
that a sapling maybe
i'm into something
it's a green beard to show you know
their greenness
they love
them i love dota
do you also love fauna
[Music]
fighting
fighting fighting
you know now people now that i i spoil
so many things people think that i
spoilers en whole stars
but i know nothing enough you can you
can confirm that right
yeah we don't know we don't know about
anything
like that
if you're talking about the edition it's
basically just open to be the same as
like the id and japanese and japanese
auditions because they always have their
auditions open yeah
i told you guys you don't believe me
anymore
[Music]
i love i love this road
oh come on
no
where does that go oh
[Music]
oh my god i don't love it anymore i was
playing around too much
become serious
you know what was your meal on christmas
uh on on new year's i mean
new year's lobster lobster
yeah my mom needs me some lobster tails
holy [\h__\h] lobster
that's that's lobster
[Music]
leftovers from my freezer the last ones
that i had
on christmas
no no new year's
oh
no i got leftovers from christmas
i don't know leftovers from even before
christmas that i made when i cooked the
pasta bolognese in
was it frozen
no i
i wound it up
well like like
did it not go bad
no you know oh you i guess you don't
understand that because you don't
usually cook for yourself
but when you cook something you can put
it in the freezer and it will be good
for you i know that that's what that's
why i said it wasn't frozen
huh
like like did you freeze it after you
cooked it oh yeah yeah but then i made
it warm again okay okay now we
understand yeah
[Music]
i think our talk was kind of appropriate
because the map was like i see
[Music]
[Laughter]
i know to freeze my food when i make too
much okay
okay okay okay okay okay
okay
i'm just getting worried i'm wondering
because like sometimes sometimes like uh
my sister used to like meal prep for
like the week right but sometimes she
would make too much and then she'd be
like oh you can eat this like like a
couple days after she made it but
sometimes i would go bad like even
lasagna
adventure time
center time well
i haven't watched that show but i i know
what it looks like i don't watch that
much either people say i sound like one
of the characters
oh
really like which one oh
there's like a
what's it like a game console character
oh
demo
[\h__\h] like [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
did i just see two garfield am i going
crazy
i think i'm going crazy
seeing garfield everywhere
what happened to those food
i keep on forgetting to do this oh my
god
the boost at the start
[Music]
you showed up and you were really
excited for northern cro cross
oh
i think that is my favorite song what
your favorite macro song or your
favorite ever song
from that show ah
then you are welcome me lady
i learned that song just for the relays
yeah i learned a couple songs just for
the really
but i didn't do too well because
my lyrics learning skills
i see you aiming at me behind you
oh thank goodness you picked that oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no the wall iris is the fire
i don't i don't even know if humans
exist anymore at this point i'm so far
behind everyone
it's like the humanity was wiped out
[Music]
oh man where is everybody
you know what placement
[Music]
hard to catch up
what are those curves man
[Music]
don't give me better items i want a
bullet
bullet bullet boy that was like a bullet
too
oh wow
[Laughter]
that i forgot to speed so that's why i
fell behind you for a second but then i
had to start and i could quickly respeed
thankfully
nice
nicer
you know
i think i think at least that the whole
life members
will be generally
besides aqua senpai and monument maybe
not as good as these these people like
keep on playing with us
so
are you sure yeah
i'm pretty sure
they get wrecked by their audience too
every time they do they do against they
do get like first place against them
from time to time so
i don't know
no no no no
no no we've been practicing
at least we're not in group uh c was it
was it c or b the one b
[Music]
so
we'll see
[Music]
[Applause]
it was a nice memory it didn't last long
but
thank you that was nice
everybody
[Music]
everybody out of the way
oh that did nothing oh i forgot how to
steer
oh man oh man that cream
that was me
you need some color in your life
this time i'm painting on you in a nuts
you want me like in the music video
[Music]
it feels good to
be painted on
oh this is good i see it's kind of nice
i mean haven't you ever like when you
were when you were a child have you ever
like had someone do face paint on you
yeah it was tickling yeah i like that
tickly sound
coming for number one
that blue shell was mine
oh it hit someone
[Music]
oh my god i don't like ripping you
oh
i'm getting lost
no no i am i'm still way more behind you
but
i'm getting there just unlock me okay
[Music]
i must say an absolutely perfect
rendition of that during my karaoke
really
i nailed it
[Music]
he can always go
and
watch the archive of her perfect
thank you how much i was talking
about top butter
butter
butter butter b
er tap butter
yeah butter
a new word that i have invented
a hickory kicked it off just how like
hickory kicked off 2022.
and i'm gonna kick her and kick off all
these people off of the planet
i see you
carry kicked
yes
i mean exactly i guess
it's gonna be one of those words because
yeah it looks like peter i love it
[Music]
that was without that it wasn't okay
thank god for a moment i was like oh my
god did i sorry
did you flirt with someone else you
recovered fast from that shell
i did not get hit by a show
oh
[Music]
here we go
i feel like
the blue shell
you get it like only when you're like
pretty low right
but
it doesn't really even do much for you
being at the very bottom right the one
who throws it yeah because you're from
number one you're so far away from
getting there in the first place so
how does that help
you in the bottom
the only thing that happens is that is
you can make the whoever
it's gotta get hit salty but yeah just
happy with the place
no
just an act out of spite exactly
exactly
just like
this and everyone has a star in front of
me literally everyone in front of me
except that person
hi
oh no
oh my goodness oh my god
i was doing so well what happened
what the [\h__\h]
i see i'm being bullied
let's start once again
i'm being bullied
i'm bullying myself
where are you
oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
the reason why i'm not so happy every
time i'm
above you is because i know that you're
good and it makes me feel like i
actually achieved something for once
you can do it i believe in you
did you see did you see the the kimono
reveals uh from the from the new jen and
and nancy i was sleeping but i watched
it afterwards after waking up i saw them
afterwards
yeah that one's your favorite oh my
favorite
i would say either
uh coyote or idoha personally
oh
really well i thought and then and then
and then
oh the one from
made me laugh and oh yeah
and when i first saw it i was like where
is
oh no not again the clones oh no the
clones
but i um
i did read into it and apparently what
she was trying to do is uh you know
those itasha the cars with the oh yeah
yeah she said she wanted an ita kimono
and i was like is that actually a thing
or did she make it up
oh i mean
it's like it's
just like you know like fashion stuff
you know like when they
when you go to like where's the place
like harajuku or something and they have
like really like
out of the world fashion kind of hmm
[Music]
maybe it's that it's like i forgot the
boost because i was talking about the
kimono another one screenshot time
frame it kfb
yep it's over
at least we're not all alone there's
still a ghost
yeah
who
apparently is not an npc
kind of successful one person i think
oopsie wow
thanks for the booze
[Music]
wait who was your favorite then
favorite design i really like
i really like
you don't want to see how different yeah
yeah
it's so soft yeah and coyote
we like the same ones
i think we have similar tastes when it
comes to like clothes maybe yeah
oh my bananas
they took one banana
and they threw it to the ground did you
watch my video on my rap video
i did not yet oh my god it's not on my
channel um but it's going around on
twitter and on kanawha's channel i've
been making some videos with kanawha
oh yeah yeah that's the
christmas one
the christmas one yeah i haven't watched
me yet actually
but yeah i saw like little like previews
of it but i didn't like fully listen to
it yet the christmas one
yeah oh you missed both of them i will
send them to you afterwards
yes
yeah i've been kind of out of the loop
lately we're not listening to them
although maybe that didn't hit you
i did not
then i fell behind
i did not she did not hit me she did not
oh hi am i
i see the blue shell
that was not mine it's my world it even
hit me myself
oh
clone party
oh you're with the clown party
i don't know anymore if it's a clown
party or a clone party but there's a
fine line between the two
[Music]
[Applause]
of mario
what's going on
wow
wow i'm not last guys
you managed to get it
congratulations
oh thank you
thank you
now can we get back to the normal people
yeah there's real people now
[Music]
oh cute that inna looks cuter than you
again
how do they all manage to oh sorry
i mean not no no the you the the me you
not the you you the the me the in-game
you what about the real you that the one
that i see
here on my screen that that one looks
beautiful more beautiful than anyone
could ever be in this whole wide world
when i asked the mirror mirror on the
wall who is the most beautiful of them
all day saying into my inner knees
and i i confirm it with them several
times a day
okay so i'm pretty sure about it it's
you see you um
let's go let's go now that we put some
butter or some honey on her mouth so we
can now destroy yummy
oh nico puddings
[Music]
hey honey
hi honey
[Music]
oh well
whatever
this one works fine too
cards that the
the cart that you are riding on
the
the bug one yeah i want that one
i think i still don't own it
oh time to play more maya car
already played quite a bit i feel
not enough apparently
everyone has the fire
thank you
why you say that no
no
and i'll say that you're doing great oh
my god you just passed me though
you don't wait for me i miss you
i can't live without you
where are you
you're in front of me
[Music]
like the explosion like oh
oh
that was nice
wow
i'm really low but that was a good race
for me
potential that was good you're doing
pretty well awesome i wish i was doing
pretty well
[Music]
i want to keep cool
you're you're doing great you just gotta
you know
go can you kick out the ghost she has
been not leaving or is this my oh wait i
don't know i'll probably wait how do i
do it yeah
uh how do i do it can you do it i don't
think you can do it on tournaments
oh my god oh thank you
thank you
thank you thank you oh yeah i want to do
mountain wario please go
how are you
please
you know i'm gonna go skiing in like uh
probably february at this point
you know probably gonna uh
do i know how to ski
yes every austrian knows how to ski
australian austrians yeah austrian
auschwitz a niner in australia
now i kind of stopped saying that
because too many people really really
really believe that i am australian and
have been like talking to other people
like oh
she's australian yeah yeah yeah she's
australian yeah so i kind of recently
like stopped saying one more
everyone over at inani's
audience i am also not australian
austrian in case you didn't know
that's why my english is so bad
oh then
yeah but um
me and my old roommate who i used to
live with
we are
gonna go
skiing for probably like two nights
three days or so yeah
i was looking forward to that she goes
skiing so much and i mean when i was a
child
um
i i learned how to ski in like one day
and i was really good at it so that i
was immediately um brought from the
beginner's group to the
medium group
but then
when i went skiing with kelly a certain
famous incident happened where i had an
oh yeah and i
i almost broke something
a body part yeah
yeah
it was horrible i thought i legit when i
was like sliding down
that mountain
um and then sliding straight into a
fence and losing everything all over
um
i really thought my life was like fading
away but i mean it would have been fine
because in phoenix so of course it
doesn't matter but still i mean cali is
there too so she could probably you know
talk to the person who come to me talk
to herself then oh my god
i mean she's on vacation herself so
you know she probably didn't want to
work
oh my god wait the ghost is still here
oh my next round i'm gonna make sure
that the ghost two disappears what why
is everything so
what
the balance is so weird right now
[Music]
oh i didn't get it controls felt like
extremely weird as if i have changed
something
something i was saying i was saying that
the snow in japan was honestly really
really horrible and i feel like that
definitely
had some part to play in
[Music]
so you are all
number two i see
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i think the snow like type um
[Music]
like really changes how you react to
some stuff too so
understandable
how do i
[Music]
animation he was still in the game yeah
that was weird that was so weird okay
everyone in the room right now say so
check your
i don't see that name they should be
gone
doesn't that name worry you
no i mean
it's my sashimi not of me it's my
sashimi
interpretation i would say
[Laughter]
not the same as before
yeah different are we even this one
looks a little little sleepier than the
other ones i think we're missing people
that was a glitch
uh yeah we're missing people
higher chances for me to win right now
jason evie has he been here before his
face looks so familiar to me
maybe but their their score is zero so
they haven't played ah yet okay this
time i think okay
it's a goal
um a little bit i probably forgot i
learned once
you can probably learn again
yeah it's a lot of fun no wait my my
controls are really weird what the hell
did you actually press like smart or
something
did that do something weird guys
because they feel so wobbly or so like
[Music]
he's trying to get me
is that what it was no i fell down and
then they brought me backwards instead
of to the front and
no no probably not
um
oh my god
oh well okay now i just throw someone
off the map i'm so sorry
oh no
[Music]
oh no the karma hey hold on i can drive
i can drive i can drive
[Music]
i'm sorry oh stop my nose was empty so i
stopped for a moment oh she's really
weird what did i do it feels so weird
maybe that's my imagination
it's the pink
oh
that was lucky huh that was my thunder
it didn't hit you
i predicted it
you learn that from me
uh
how do i slipped off are you watching
any tv shows right now inya
not that many
i don't really watch tv oh
yeah i mean like netflix and someone
neighbor
i haven't watched netflix either
oh my god
what about disney plus
oh i watched hawkeye recently
is that one of the marvel movies
yeah the marvel
disney plush show
oh my god
[Music]
oh
but they could be fake like you the
japanese map
flags
[Music]
wow
oh that's a beard that's so smart
[Music]
oh it is a beard oh cute
creative
i wanted to pronounce it uh german first
fe tuba and that would have meant a
fairy tuba
oh
she's kind of like a fairy he's small oh
wait now i get his feet tuber
yeah
oh
i just want you know feet f-e-e like fee
like v
uh-huh oh that took me a while
that's cause girl godman is in here for
the second time please leave next time
feet tuber
so i was focused on something else
kia i got that internet explorer
thinking el mal and you got that ticket
to the user room congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
[Applause]
you're so fast
you can't drive so fast in the rain
you're gonna sleep
oh i stripped it the wrong way
[Applause]
[Music]
car um and cars here we go
here we go
[Music]
i'm wondering right now why i am
planning on waking up at 4 00 am for in
order to play this game
um just to suffer
suffering is part of the fun right
yeah no but just kidding it's it's gonna
be fun
just like the minecraft thing
yeah it will be worth it and will be
worth it
it's just ironic because i i'm bad at
this for minecraft at least i
i think minecraft is fairer and
yeah you can practice better
it's not so difficult
to get goods
[Music]
oh no don't panic you know it's fine you
can do it
[Applause]
no they pushed me
[Music]
it's okay
i did well in my heart
[Music]
hi i wasn't crying anymore at the end i
was just starting off the cliff again
and again and again on purpose
are you okay
do you need a break oh the i think the
choices of maps is next i don't need a
break enough i need a win
[Music]
i great thank
feeling the next one is gonna be rainbow
road maybe that we're gonna play let's
choose grumble volcano
let's choose that one everybody
let's read the room
[Music]
of naughty children for next christmas
oh oh you're not going to get gifts guys
[Music]
you did so well during en and id what
happened question mark question request
look
hey mario kart is a mario kart is a luck
game you know sometimes you get just
mostly yeah really nice items yeah no
a big part of if you're only an average
player then big part relies on the items
yes yes
of course you could get really good like
aqua senpai and then you don't need to
care about the items but
when you just make sure she uses her
items
not for long
[Music]
nice nice snowy thongs
ow
[Music]
oh that
oh wow
that never hit me before man
[Music]
oh no no no no
okay
kfb i need your mental support
i have a feeling at least for this one i
could
be
above the placement 11.
i want let's do our best here
five dogs oh god
i see you so close to me all the time
makes me feel
more more happy and confident and safe
that's good
that is good
i'm not going to nothing too well here
i'm going pretty well but what the hell
was that how did i have a chance for
that
oh no
isn't there only 10 people in this round
i don't i don't even know
is that so
i don't know
it's over it's oh it's over
it's over
now that was that was that that was that
i've never gotten this item before
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
we are
with your with your power i was able to
get the
the lucky ate item
are you okay
i will say
that
when i
if my placement here is 10 then
in my actual
d group i would probably be 5.
and potential thank you
i already have two pets but i don't mind
more
i meant pat not pet
i want both
i want inna as my pet to pet me
huh
um i mean i want to see the terms and
definitions of this country
actually going to be three meals per day
um is my is my lodging included there's
going to be an all day breakfast
birthday
oh all day perfect
and there's going to be obviously
lodging in my bed with my other two cats
okay okay okay and you will be um
cuddled
at any given time i see you every
anytime we pass by one another what is
in my apartment what if i don't want but
what is it you do want them believe me
are you sure yeah of course you want oh
no we're invaded by the yeah mario again
no mario
what the hell is that
[Music]
we got some real people though
there's just a lot of a lot of uh
a lot of mario what is that name
his eyebrows though
it's like it's like rock lee
from naruto no he looks a little bit
like
that guy from
me
i don't want to say anything
oh i'm dude
ah no wait who am i thinking of no no no
i'm thinking of uh
that actor from handmaid's tale
anyone didn't watch that
you shouldn't it's traumatizing oops
that's the one with uh the red cape
yeah yeah everyone wears red yeah yeah
yeah pictures of it it is extremely
traumatizing
but it's also extremely well made
[Music]
now
i wanted to take a shortcut
i don't think that was a short term
tell me it was a nice shark
[Music]
and i'll
here that we got going on
[Music]
horrible timing
yeah that one
he'll come number one but i don't see
him no
the eyebrow guy is far ahead
[Music]
is
yes
[Music]
okay to make it
god has forsaken me
now triple kiana okay with the power
oh my goodness
finally i feel it's i feel so many so
many chaos this must be it which one is
real
don't see nothing
there's only one with the with the
feathers amy shoot all your ammo on that
grill
you think i know how to aim items
[Music]
the famous hira typo
kaira kiyowa
wow
[Music]
what do you call a rooster that likes
eggs
and disney
that was so bad it made me fail um i was
saying
i was hoping for something good there
[Music]
uh
well henderson
is uh oh that's weird in japanese and
but han sounds like
hen so you know you know because
roosters don't like eggs hens do
you know
yeah exactly
[Music]
i'm at the end of my wits
mario kart does that to people you know
like when you're doing well and then you
get shelled and then five people pass
you
[Music]
i guess we should stop walking on
eggshells do not get shells
or
excellent idea
um
oh come on
oh nettie is your second time did you
not were you not able to leave the round
i guess sometimes people are like too
slow to lean around
[Music]
i'm not even trying this is really weird
your sound
yeah like i hear the music but i don't
like hear
like
[Music]
i feel like my learning
curve in this stream was like really low
in the beginning and then it went up in
the middle and then now it's going down
again
oh same
then i guess that's just my apartment
you shouldn't play the new thing you got
just when you think that you got a hang
of it just like nope
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
i'm here in the back with my europeans
just hanging out what was that i don't
know i see you in front of me you're
like you're like second number
[Music]
you're doing very well you're two and
three and the one and two oh
beautiful pretty impressive isn't it
aggressive i want to do a little
thank you guys
thanks to the ray unfortunately the
power of potentials didn't help me
as i thought it would
originally
you still you still did pretty good
thank you
[Music]
wait what place were you okay
uh i forgot
i don't know i'm too busy looking at the
other kiara's oh somewhere in the middle
i think nero needs to leave haven't you
been there before and there's
another kiana
or someone else's power
our friendship
oh
rainbow no i want it
rainbow row
what
[Music]
but this time both of you look so
similar i can't i can't tell which ones
which yeah they look similar we look the
same
[Music]
again
it's like enos you know the massaging me
but
yeah wait we got colonel here too kfc oh
did you see that i didn't see it but
there's also macaroni these people are
too funny
macaroni
yeah macaroons oh my god
yummy yeah
um i didn't have you ever tried making
macarons before no
but i also didn't like macarons before
that much until now like they weren't my
choice of sweets but i got i had some
good ones the other day and now i kind
of like them oh yes
i never really took a close look but now
i kind of see the world be below that
rainbow road is beautiful can we go
there instead
i don't know how up here we have rainbow
road at home
[Music]
i'm lost right now anyone
oh
now i am
[Music]
i rewatched that clip of me teaching
japanese today it was so cute
you know you sold my items but i'm gonna
steal your placements
[Music]
are you winning i i
oh you got five
i'm so proud of you huh
i could have gone even further but i
didn't see it already ending i could
have used up my script items and been
like ferg at least
i'm so proud of what
that is my best placement today on the
rainbow road that is one of the easier
rainbow roads though
wow rainbow road yay
that bullet kind of saved me though i
got very fast
[Music]
okay
wow that that cheered me up a little bit
now i'm confident again
you want to end it on the high note or
do you want to go for one more one
okay
we
all the other times you're gonna play
mario kart until the uh until the
tournament are you always gonna be
playing against the
audience
um i want to have one where i just sit
in the voice call and whoever you know
like and just i saw it on the schedule i
might join i do want to pre uh i don't
want to join our practice against ghost
too just to see where the shortcut you
did that last time too in the enid
tournament didn't you um i did yeah i
practiced big blue there actually i
should do the same did that help you a
lot yeah
it did actually it kind of like i didn't
i was really bad on my car but they kind
of like clicked like when to start
drifting and stuff so did you only do it
communication error has occurred not for
me
oh man
it's already starting for me but you're
still there no
not without you
hey
oh you're gonna be turned into an npc in
yeah
the robot is taking over you know
i was gonna say did you uh only do that
for like the rainbow road of all all
races
um not all races either a couple that i
remember
the one that i remember was
big blue i did rainbow road too actually
one of the rainbow roads so until i beat
the um
yeah oh unable to connect to other
consoles oh that's so unfortunate for me
[Music]
that's different you're gonna expect it
look at me
no more rivals
i'm always looking at you
right now get out let me let me just
watch actually let me just watch her
i wish i could spectate like you i
wanted the last run to be with you
you're going to come back for one more
right
and we might have to like choose a
different route or or we can do 1v1 at
the end
to end it
[Music]
okay
how do you do that
even when you're not there you're good
and above me i'll do one race with the
screw and then let's do 1v1 so wait for
me when you're done okay okay okay
okay now i'm in front of you
all right
gonna be speed guys uh one day one km
[Applause]
he's speaking the language of the
phoenix
[Music]
i'm guessing that she gonna start you
gotta start right didn't you
oh what was that
[Music]
i'm not skateboarding here i don't want
to be on the rail
come on oh
my oh
such a beautiful drift
oh i got a coin they got a shell of
course
[Music]
maybe the trick is to just not be
starting first
oh i saw i saw akwa by doing that in the
yoshi island thingy like she stayed
behind to be 12.
and then she went all the way to the top
with a bullet
that was pretty cool
i was really impressed with what's kept
up to like fifth like fourth what and
like if you have the bullet in your in
your inventory you easily get first
that's what she was eating for
i think that is a strat
but like it has to be done like
when you know like people you can catch
up otherwise you're gonna be at the back
fur hey i am not tempted
i'm ahead of you
okay so how are we going to do this now
uh just wait for me
i'm on the second
second
or should i leave my group
yeah yeah leave the girl we can just 1v1
uh even though sans just entered sad
wow thank you guys for joining we're
gonna do one more with me and enya
yeah and npcs right after after i uh get
out of here okay i should
i think i can i'm gonna get last
okay
it says i can join your tournament
oh no just wait for me we can 1v1 okay
1v1 me bro one way one without npcs
no that that's like too obvious of an
outcome we need those npcs i know what's
going to happen if it's only 1v1
i mean i'll use a different car i'll use
a different car no
no that's lame too
okay well then we can do it with nbc's
then here yeah yeah okay
here we go
okay sticks not bad right in the uh
right in the middle
right in the middle congrats yeah
gg
[Music]
thanks for joining everyone
thank you everybody
i hope
you guys had some fun racing against
these
super cute top idols
oh yeah
okay i made the room yeah
yeah
[Applause]
two
i'm gonna practice
privately more i'm not gonna do as many
mario kart streams as you're gonna do
up until tournament maybe one race or
four races
oh actually four is the least we can do
we can do 48 but
four four okay hard calm items normal
items race count okay oh my god let me
let me go
150 no teams normal items
all vehicles first
you got it
yes oh look at us dancing cute oh
no
vehicles
my own races
okay
brand new random unless there's one you
really want to play no
that noise we gotta be ready for
everything
oh you
oh is that mine
that was yours someone's doing something
in the kitchen that's really loud
[Music]
oh big blue
oh no that one is the one that's so
crazy
[Music]
no it was not my stomach i'm focusing
now
wow wait that gives money
[Music]
[Applause]
i like the music here though
i remember when i was practicing with
the girl
the music was so bopping i didn't mind
it
oh
i hit someone was that me
[Music]
i don't know the green shell
oh no it wasn't red okay
did that was that my fire
uh no i guess i just fell off the map
well so far better than the last time i
was on this map
it's good
as long as you're you know improving
[Music]
oh my nose is itchy
oh you gotta hold on kiara
i didn't
[Music]
i scratched it while holding the
controller
that's good
honks wait
[Music]
it's a hard npc a hard npc
when we started out i i lost by far
against the npc's right
i was yeah wait you're in like the
middle of the pack but you're improving
you're improving okay
what
oh this map no no no that one is fun oh
someone
hanuki mario
[Music]
i once um
when i lived in japan i uh saw a real
tanooki
oh was it cute it was
oh it was cute and weird
what do you mean weird i lived in this
is it disguised as a human
no but it did something it was kind of
cute like i i lived in a neighborhood
that was pretty um
wow
central
so
it was like a lot of houses and and
narrow alleys
yeah
uh how do you keep on blocking my shells
oh my god
cause i have another one
anyway i was thinking um
and then i was coming home one night
from something i don't know what i was
doing and it was dark and i
i walked through
this one path and then i noticed
something
drinking water out of a like a
like a planter
uh-huh and i was like is that a cat is
that a dog what is that it was so dark i
could barely see
and then oh my god yes it wasn't it
wasn't looking and it looked at me and i
looked at it
and we looked at each other and i was
like legit scared for a moment because i
didn't really know it's like
i don't know would it attack me did
kanuki's
so i stood there for a moment i didn't
continue walking i was too scared
and then
i took a few photos and then um
i think it ran away
maybe
what did i ran away everything i don't
know every i i think i run away
you're
scared i was a little bit intimidated i
must say
what are you doing
oh i missed the item it's fine i used to
live in a place that's not like near a
park oh
and like in the winter i would just
randomly see
like
a deer family
going to eat our grass
[Music]
it's definitely interesting like like i
would be like getting ready to go like
in the morning when
like it's like dark outside and now it's
nice you just like that's the glowing
eyes
in the dark and they just always staring
at me and i'll scare your back and just
slowly munching away at the ground
[Music]
cute
like what's up
not microsoft
it's okay you're still fifth you're
still fifth overall ranking
so my defense i was very focused on
telling my story
yeah
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'll drink oh my god someone sent the
super chat saying happy new year's kiana
i'll drink until you win
you're gonna be drinking for a long time
you're gonna get really drunk please
don't come tomorrow
i know you know everyone so that that
person doesn't get like so drunk he
can't walk
[Music]
because you would call me lame
no no no no
not to be too greedy well here i am
being greedy
i don't like this music
oh this is the clockwork map i like i
like that one
i always miss that shortcut
kind of sad
[Music]
you can do
employee that's drinking for your win
yes for you my friend thank you for the
super choco i will find heart for you so
you don't have to get a alcohol
poisoning
is that a thing that you get when you
drink too much or like how do you get an
alcohol poisoning
that's how you get it
right is it
yeah apparently
well i haven't i've never even been
drunk before so i wouldn't know
no
no no no no no no no
to wake up from your dream
i'm dreaming from your slumber on the
ground
oh
i thought it was just cause you're uh
your very dream
[Laughter]
oh come on
that was
not necessary
[Music]
it really was not
ghost and stuff
come on kiara you can do it beat the
inkling boy you can do it
[Music]
okay
all right all right i i i think uh wait
do i have one more
uh i don't know i don't know is that the
fourth
yeah we have one more we have one one
more okay one more chance to get first
last
come on
is just kidding i didn't spit into my
hands
[Music]
i think i've seen people do that
somewhere for some reason it's
disgusting but i don't know
that's unsanitary
[Music]
um
where are you
[Music]
like there is no tomorrow oh my god
jeff like there is no tomorrow
oh whoops oh no
go back
[Music]
hi
fine
where are you
behind right behind you
okay good job
no easy mode
i can do it i'll get you this is a
fairly easy map i have a lot of control
over this map yes
yeah
believe in yourself believe in me who
believes in you
oh
i should have left it
i was waiting for the right moment too
[Music]
hold on barrio
what npc is in front of you how did that
happen in you
i wonder too they got lucky with items
one of us has to be number one in
to defend our honor
oh
it's over for me
[Music]
i'll defend our
but there is still one one more
in front of myself
oh wait never mind they're no longer
yeah dania okay
she doesn't want to get trapped
[Music]
what's his name again what's that name
again of that dude
it says nice try for me what does it say
for you
oh i didn't see congratulations
[Laughter]
[Music]
you suck that was fun i should probably
remove the code from yeah oh yeah right
yeah
but thank you everyone for uh those of
you want to watch us have fun
um thanks for uh thanks for joining us
thanks kiara for uh suggesting that we
collab instead of doing too solo about
your car street
you still have so many more chances to
drive so low at least this time yeah we
were able to drive together
yeah and if you if you feel like joining
when i'm just just randomly racing
against schools let me know yeah
well yeah and thank you for giving me
um
some
no no you didn't give me confidence yeah
my job here is done
um
but it was fun
i i wanna i'm glad that we're doing more
collabs recently yeah let's play
together yeah some other games perhaps
you should teach me how we started the
minecraft too it's minecraft oh splatoon
yeah it's not the place for anytime oh
yeah but but indeed i have suggested uh
and i just told it in the clip thingy uh
already that i invited kuda i also
invited ina so good aina and me we'll be
going to disney and then one more member
ah
yeah yeah yeah
one more member that's still secret
secret but
yay we'll be going to the disneyland in
minecraft as you have seen there's a
minecraft world of disneyland and i
wanted to try that one out and go there
with some friends
so i figured
not because of milky mouse
oh
i want to learn how to speak like donald
but it's so hard
oh yeah i think that's
it that is so hard on the front
destroyer i think you got to do
something with your mouth but i don't
know are you from kingdom hearts
does that server have kingdom is that a
meme
are they meaning on me that's because
mickey mouse is in kingdom
you know
once one time guru prank called me and i
yeah yeah
about the car
the car
since then everyone's been asking are
they in kingdom hearts
[Music]
now i remember okay i know that that's a
that's a
that's a whole life created meme
you know about our lord and savior
lightning mcqueen
i don't know
i'm actually really surprised that we're
even able to play that disneyland world
because it wasn't disney like super hard
with the
copyright like everywhere like
mentioning even even men i noticed that
the japanese members are even scared of
mentioning disneyland but i just do it
all the time
you remember they always say that as if
as if i mean that's important
disney is dangerous
yeah i mean they're playing a safe right
but then we talk about michael moos
who's who's michael moos
ronald rock
and what
yeah michael moose
mickey mouse
that sounds like a complaint
[Laughter]
all right all right
why do i feel so stupid right now
i think your brain needs a little bit of
break you had a pretty long clip stream
and then this shape so yeah
we'll get some brain sugar
i'll be doing a drawing stream tomorrow
i hope i can
get i hope some of you wrap up rubbed
off on me today for this stream so that
i have some more skills you can feel
free to pet my head you know
okay
okay okay but that's after stream okay
god we gotta say goodbye no no no no no
no no
okay
thank you i hope that wrapped up on me
you all right good luck thank you soon
and thank you yeah we'll see you guys
uh soon
uh
and in german we stay aveenazine and
[Music]
my play style today
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks everybody for today and for
yesterday tomorrow we have a lot of time
to talk so i'm looking forward to that
i'll see you guys tomorrow
good night everybody love you guys
bye
[Music]
wow
wow well
[Music]
oh
[Applause]