[Music]
foreign
do
[Music]
so
cute
[Music]
chunky chunky
and there was a one hand too much
[Laughter]
hello
let me get my controller oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
um look normal to me same yeah that was
100 normal
hello everybody welcome back to yakuza 0
the game that
i play when i don't feel good and it
needs i need something to lift my mood
apparently it's become
that kind of game
hello
therapy game yeah
[Music]
orange juice with me
ma'am
wait
webcam chat um
youtubers video chat that looks like one
of those spam bots but this seems to be
an actual person who's just riding on
the joke isn't it
isn't it
[Laughter]
oh my god
my mods might accidentally
bonk you because you look so much like
spam but even if you're just joking
around
you look like a spambot
on purpose i suppose
spambot
uh
they're too shy now to communicate
they're gone
talk to me come on
say
[Music]
hello everybody
what's up
there we go
ah
it is the last day of march
[Music]
i would hope so i would hope that kfb
loves me why is my
what if
it's not opening properly let me
close it and open it up again elgato
elgato please
march was a long month
you're actually right yeah march felt
really long
kind of like
dragged out
i agree with that
so
oh but it will already be the fourth
month of the year that's also i don't
know feels
feels kind of fast too though like
just just a little while ago it was 2021
man
what the hell is happening with my game
capture card open open i see an obs
uh
it's acting a little bit like a [\h__\h]
right now let me do
task manager
karen be like
task manager i want to speak to the task
manager for [\h__\h] sake i want to talk
to you i want to speak to the task
manager and then they say but
i am the task manager
wait [\h__\h]
because i was saying task manager so
often i close to the task manager within
the task manager
no no no elgato close elgato
elgato please
[Laughter]
you know you know that when you're
writing a message while you're talking
to someone you or or listening to
someone or thinking something on the
side having this having a side
conversation and you you type out the
things
that they're saying to you or that
you're saying to them while you're
typing something
yeah that it's like that it's like that
okay it works now
it works now
and task manager
here's the task manager to close this
aspect yes that's what i did
um
okay
yeah
oh one year anniversary
oh
thank
you ah
i wish i
i wish i could be on stage more already
and
have more
more ways of
uh
doing more stuff like that just saw cali
before the stream
um being on on the swisses stream i wish
i lived in japan right now i could do so
many things man i could do so many
collabs in 3d
um it would be nice
yeah
and a song from giga i love giga so
[\h__\h] much
[Laughter]
oh kelly making all her dreams come true
good for her
say la vie
oh don't say that i hate that that's
like
oh that's just live that's saying this
is this
it's just like the japanese
way of saying
it
no there should be a way
um
background static noise when when did
you hear that
when it
when did you hear that
ah i using the right microphone
ah that's the rain from the game not the
rain but like the the street noise which
is a bit more quiet when i'm in this
window yeah yeah yeah so so so so
why are you holding a corral why should
i not hold one you actually can't even
see the whole thing
this is what it is
it's beautiful
maybe it
was there one
i'll just i'll just i'll just
flip it here
uh
whatever
it might be it might be me around but
that's okay
that's what we're working with today
yeah
new weapon
um
a good old bunking stick he took it from
me no no no no it's my own it's my own
bunking stick
okay
so
sorry um i'll tell you i'll tell you
later i guess uh
i why why i'm feeling a little bit blue
but i'm okay though i took a i took a
um
a recovery nap
after
what happened
and cuddled with my ketocados
oh yeah i'm just a little bit low energy
now but i'll be better later
yeah cat therapy we call that oh
sparkly
well i found that by accident yuki not
some anti-bake art
it was exciting no no no no no not the
inspired snacks they were fine
they were fine oh tissues
do you want me to teach you no
no thank you what what were we in the
middle of doing last episode did you
guys all watch it
did you all watch it
does everyone update us
huh
that's yuki from club sunshine oh really
yes yes yes
yeah
wonderful
yeah we uh
just ended another chapter from kiryu
uh
what happened oh there
um
we found the connection between two
storylines
uh
because the
uh i forgot
yeah i don't know
what i don't want to know what majima
will be doing next though i wanted to
remember what kirio
yakir is going to osaka because
something about makoto
uh
who we now know
for sure
that she owns
the
see emp
lot
i guess is that
yeah
yeah yeah yeah we learned that
from
tachibana
i think
um
and now
majima
will beat makoto's location out of the
kitchen clan fools
yeah their office is on the sultan voted
street east in the third namike building
i knew that i i just i didn't read that
no no no no
okay so that's uh
all over there all right
[Music]
can you not i need to go there
no no
who calls me a [\h__\h] excuse me what's
with you
side story
fallen guy oh no did you fall over that
thing
fight him i don't you can take him
really you think so
we haven't tried him
yet
oh god what the what is this creeper
i see a creeper just lying on the ground
hey there's a no napping zone why don't
you get up and move along look at his
face
in scrubs there was this this pain
scale with like pictures of
faces
how much pain they would be feeling
according to the scale it was just a
joke but
if you look at this guy's face you'll
see that he's in pain he's just napping
he's not just napping i mean look at him
look at those eyebrows and his mouth
angled downwards
you need that that uh scale from scubs
scrubs scrubs i can't talk oh my god
stop talking chihuahua
they say that's the seven
[Music]
six
i don't know
he's hurt oh no
did this guy get the snot kicked out of
him he's in so much pain he can't even
talk
medicine
i have to give my own medicine
ah i only have good ones i'll give you
one of these
here you go drink this
perfect perfect depiction of that
little side quest going on here you
alright hi
yes i'm feeling much better though thank
you
wanna tell me what happened why did you
get laid out
it's because i was chasing a dream
keep on chasing your dreams yes yes
sometimes you fall down on the way
on the path to the dream yeah yeah it
happens
it's my dream to boldly walk across you
well bridge what a dream is that
a grand old dream like walking across
this bridge sure does explain why i got
beat to an inch of your life
except not real
i mean come on it wouldn't take more
than a minute or two to just stroll
right across this bridge
but it's not that simple
why is that it's because of this
schedule i'm wearing then take it off
no you don't know what the station is
that's terrible you're not worth the
times at all so not cool
starting to shoot for a stadium's jumper
it's a jacket run by athletes at the
stadium
so they stay warm and limber overseas
they call these very varsity jackets but
here in japan it's studying all the way
i would just call it like a i don't know
baseball jacket or sports jacket or like
i don't know
i don't know what do you what do you
call these things varsity i've never
heard of varsity jacket
it's a good jacket though besides i mean
i don't really like what's in the back
but
oh yeah it does say
something about fight me in the back
why city jacket
huh
is that common
jersey
neat but why the what were you wearing
uh would you wearing a staging make it
so you couldn't cross that level bridge
well you put on the statue like this and
you pop the collar and suddenly everyone
thinks you're some kind of big shot all
the punks come charging out looking for
blood
does your read what yeah did you read
what the back of your jacket sends
but even dead it's not realistic
i've tried crossing eight times now when
every time goons show up and beat the
crap out of me before i can make
it's certainly um unique problem but
there's gotta be other dudes wearing
jackets like that right they aren't all
getting mauled by the riffraff
right i can't explain it but when i do
it i get so much heat does my face piss
people off or is it is this just my
destiny
ah this is an [\h__\h] if that's the case
but all right at least i get why i were
bleeding out on the pavement here
so here's a novel idea maybe take off
the statue
seems to me that's the search of all
your
but that defeats the purpose i love this
dungeon you wouldn't believe how much
trouble i went through to get this sweet
jacket i want the word loud and proud
that's that's my dream
that it's a free country so but i'd
wager you've got another beating coming
down the pipe if you go through with it
that's what complicates things
oh i'm sorry how rude of you my name is
suda
that chad why are you calling him
sulachan
if you don't might be saying you look
like a man who can wade into pearls and
walk away without their hair out of the
place
well i've got a hair tie but yeah i can
hold my own stop looking at my legs
creepy
i'm sorry if this starts with what do
you think you could help me make my
dream come true yeah okay i'll fight
those guys for you i'll pick i'll i'll
i'll um i'll hold those people
away from you you can just walk calmly
don't worry or i'll do it
sure
all right all right yes of course
yes yes no problem it's like an escort
quest yeah
i've
already had enough of these but if it's
just through this bridge then i can do
it
you didn't even see the back of the
jacket
i didn't even see what it says
you just saw the front side and you're
already mad
at
[Music]
okay
okay stop breakdancing
[Music]
anybody else oh we're still walking okay
so many of them
let's change my stuff
[\h__\h] can you guys get off of him
please
[Music]
i need to be more careful holy [\h__\h] is
there more coming oh god um
[Music]
breaker style
like if if i could uh cancel my
movements it would be no problem but
and let's do it again can we do it again
okay
yeah you got dude
how do we do it again
just talk to you
okay
yeah with the breaker you commit to a
long combo
yeah
like a beyblade
[Music]
spinning in front of him worked well for
me yeah i would i would reckon that
could work well
[Music]
maybe just yeah
now we're good we're good i'm gonna make
it this
[Music]
oh oh oh they don't come like after it
kills them they come after
and he walks the certain
oh
pop okay
okay but i'm doing well now
[Music]
cheese
he could walk a little fast and no he
wants to walk boldly
with with um with confidence yeah yeah
you need to walk slowly
do some aoe damage
ah
should i try with
the
wrong side
i tried with the slow
you to be fast and maybe break your
style again but
only do a few hits each
[Music]
yeah a breaker at the end once they're
too many
why was that so fast
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i'm already down
look at them in the back
oh
yeah i think it may count how far i am
as well i i may have triggered it
i need aoe
[Music]
protect the civilian let's go
pretty
okay
[Music]
please
they're kind of missing a lot
i almost got it
[Music]
yes i finally did it i made it the way
across the evo bridge while wearing my
beloved statue yeah good for you
you made my dream come true i'd like you
to have this this is the best i can oh
do i get used to
encounter finder
i don't think i've ever been this happy
i'll never forget what you did for me
today what's an encounter finder
can i find where i can fight people if
i'm really really really desperate to
get
money and exp
cruising around in a jacket is that big
a deal to y'all you're an odd dude
i know i don't think most people would
understand how much this meant to me but
still it was my dream
i guess that's the true of most dreams
ah you can't find mr shakedown uh-huh
okay
thanks thanks i guess
you're hungry okay bye-bye
next time maybe just swim under the
bridge
although
you gotta be a really good swimmer to
handle that one
surgeon's pretty weird but his
philosophy is right on there is a real
man
he got
caught up in something again is that
is that part two
of the side quest
uh
no no it's just happening again he just
went right back
why would you do that stay on this side
for now
look at that woman
she was getting stuck and running like
crazy and then finally reached her
boyfriend again
you see that
look at her go
she was zooming
okay
i wonder
oh there's a weapon in armor shop here
wait a second i want to check that out
let me look at that oh in here
well are you a side quest
looks like a side quest to me
oh no equipment search results
oh that was uh
[Music]
aha i remember that all nipples
you shouldn't went reasonably well why
is this so dramatic
stealing iron
and i got a recipe for a metal bat
[Music]
and a dagger
uh okay
that was the first time we um finished
one of those here you can receive the
equipment item recipes parts or assets
found by your agent equipment is
immediately ready for use recipes enable
you to craft equipment provided you have
all necessary parts enough money to pay
the fee uh
if the name of an item is not shown in
the crafting menu it means you have not
yet discovered the parts or equipment
required to make it
dispatch agents to various locations to
obtain many different types of parts
once you obtain a new piece of equipment
it also becomes available for purchase
in the shop crafting it will be cheaper
than buying
okay
can we send you guys off again right
away
thank
so you can get new weapons i personally
didn't use it
yeah it seems like weapons don't really
matter in this game i
i expected there to be more like that
because of like a dragon i was used to
that one
you better move
you better dance
this is the night
you gonna remember
wow
whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
wow
oh eggs
eggs
i got a lot of eggs here
eggs show yourself
i want eggs
i remember that
she wanted him to get eggs
they kicked me out
wonder how fei who and long who are
doing i'll drop in to see them later
go back in
now
oh
uh
did i just talk to people 100 times
let's go once you become more familiar
you waste welcome
consider part of my service
[Music]
would also recommend that you work at
helping your bad skills holding
[Music]
you could perform with a bat that simply
wouldn't be possible using other weapons
[Music]
baller
playing cash
[Music]
i'm gonna play catch
okay okay i was just wondering wait if i
have a recipe like can i ah
no
wait
if i have a recipe who's where can i
make it what can i create
new dispatch destination
okay uh there we go craft equipment but
also uh equipment search
where can we go
oh
[Music]
we can't go to europe
oh we can go to italy
that sounds a lot like italy sicilian
and napolitano
uh
all right it's not that expensive
[Music]
you can see what you can get there oh
mail and shirt
what chain mail or just mail like the
letter
hammer nunchuck
and mail
handgun shotgun jacket
a yo
whole spare mail
kinda wanna send him to one of these
[Music]
shotgun right it could be pretty good
oh
[Music]
lucky find stun gun amulet handgun
equipment rate
[Music]
i don't know who i should go live
but they cost a little ah she's the most
expensive
guaranteed fine
[Music]
main is a pcb
which one should i get the best one i
mean i have the money for it but
who are these people
that's real people
okay
[Music]
oh extra funds
8.5 million
damn
is this gonna be worth it
airplane bye bye
okay and let's try
crafting
um
we can make
both of them
but will i use them
no i don't care i don't need it right
now
only if i have better better recipes
he was leaving on the javelin yeah
which color
which category is here you mean
ah didn't say that thank you
uh a hunt dagger butterfly knife oh
metal bat oh
oh
it may be a bat
ah
why not
okay bye-bye
thank you as well
that has some aoe so that's good
oh guys are you still not over that song
still not over it oh
also i have a pager
thingy what's what's up
dragon tiger and come guess i'll swing
by if i can where
dragon tiger what does that mean swing
by where
that's a side quest thingy
anyway
should i try them should i try killing
him wait i want to try can i i'll save
before there's a saving point right here
[Music]
of his lifetime
uh which style i wonder mm-hmm
oh i can't get pretty close to you
without starting a fight you with the
ipad yeah yeah yeah give me your money
sorry i don't want to read it
i just want to fight
can you talk so much
alright
bad start
[Music]
we can do this
nice
[Music]
get out of here get out of here
oh
[Music]
ring man
yeah i wanted to use the heat action
i was like [\h__\h] it she's going to use
the heat action but no
don't let me do it again wait don't save
is it going to save don't save it's not
going to safe right
how did i close the game
uh
how do i close the game
[Music]
close game
now i want to get him once
i was i was i was going to be fine
i was going to be just fine
it's going to disappear no
i'm not the king crushed i'm new
no really
sega it's so bright this screen i heal
my eyes
okay
here's the finder i guess so but like i
did it because it was so close by
[Music]
yeah sega needs dark mode
that light mode is way too bright on my
eyes
how do you look at the is it like can i
already see it
like here
no
it's not
valuables
hearts
no equipment
and by the way let's put on a
weapon
okay
so now i should ah there he is right
over there uh here
maybe he has different amount of money
now
i still have my money right okay
okay eight million i don't know how much
he had before but let's do this
blazer
no not now
come on
my game crashed i'm sorry about that
let's do it again
okay i'm not gonna make the same
mistakes again
holy [\h__\h] that hurts so much
i don't wanna
that move
i need to
be careful about that move
[Music]
oh
there we go there we go there we go
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
oh my god
ah
you can look for the settings uh
whatever it's okay
it's okay
game is so unstable don't buy the ps5
guys it's
no no no it's so unstable they really
need to fix it
then you can buy it
maybe wait for a ps5 uh
update or a second ps5 yeah
[Laughter]
even if you want you want you lost money
anyway
yeah
but don't i get all the money back also
when i win and get his money
yeah
is it that worth it yeah the ps5 pro i'm
waiting for the ps5 pro
is it's not worth it
don't get hit yes you do there you go
we're going to make it worth it
wait where is he now if he's too far
away no he's right there if he's too far
away i would have just ignored it but
now you're really
oh he's he still has the same amount
i guess that doesn't change i really
really i really really really really
really really want to fight you
so [\h__\h] me and i like you and you give
me your money
break his boys
oh
[Music]
i wanna use my i wanna use my
heat
[Music]
this is like [\h__\h] elven ring
oh
it's not fair it's not fair
um
he's still there
he's always there
he doesn't even change his position at
all would prefer to not fight here like
we had more space
in the first bite
can you like come over here
to the middle
now oh he's turning around oh i really
come over here
a little bit faster
yeah come on
come on
and now he walks faster come come come
come come come come come
okay
let's do this
what
call me a [\h__\h] you're a [\h__\h]
don't talk too much
all right all right we're in the middle
of the street
it's looking fine
[Music]
you never did that before but that
didn't really do any damage
okay
that one i got one down
one paper that's pretty good now he's on
the ground i want to do that second
heather
i can't he won't let me do it
i want to do that one when he's on the
ground okay don't do it get out of here
get out of here
nope
believe
[Music]
he couldn't fear me with certain with a
certain attack you could probably even
kill me with that amount of hp but we're
not gonna let it happen
[Music]
there
please
don't get too impatient no it's not
patient it's just
i feel like he gets stronger in his
second face
just like [\h__\h] album ring
see you there
oh what
hold away with it you know what [\h__\h] you
another time
another time but i'm gonna take care of
you guys indeed
[Music]
let out my anger
what do you want what do you want what
do you want
don't get too close to me
ow my god
in his life to teach him i mean
yakuza yeah but did they really play
baseball
in their free time i kind of doubt it
all right
aura
wait
no no no ah we're not supposed to go for
taxi
how about we're supposed to take the
taxes somewhere oh
we need to go
[Music]
here
okay
kj in clan office
enter the building
i'm gonna be snacking today on some
swedish snacks
by the way
from yesterday
do i want chips or chocolate
i don't want chocolate i'm
sonic
[Music]
you're gonna have to take it up with me
why [\h__\h]
[Music]
is that how the yeah
aren't you guys proud of how fair you
guys are
wow
that scream woke me up well good [\h__\h]
morning [\h__\h]
oh my god
she shoots me in the back look at yakuza
yeah
oh god
oh my god
i'm using a baseball bat that's not a
knife or uh
gun
good morning
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
hey we should be thankful for them
talking to us otherwise we may have had
to do even more damage to them
all right billy can guys a detective who
can get me into the can to see
nishitani hangs out on bishop and bridge
the guy said it's worth a look
what's up
dragon tiger oh oh i guess uh my
delivery is here is that what it means
can i spend some money on breaker
uh close
at 2 million
[Music]
perform an invasive move and attack
after the enemy breaks for your guard
okay
and this one this one this one
what about slugger
oh wait i also i have nothing and thug
what's up
oh my god
triangle
okay
and health gosh splashes around naruto
need to invest more yeah i kind of
forgot about that on management side i
guess
uh
that bridge over there okay
oh and get look who's there look who's
over there
so you're kind of suck
can you wait can she join mine
because i'm looking for cute girls to
join right
hey
cookie cookie
pink suit can i take that off of you
oh i thought i was doing the heat move
on the other guy all right
gets pretty loud huh
let me try to can i adjust
only that is there a way to adjust only
that
i can't adjust the music
[Applause]
i can't
[Music]
what did you say i was saying that it
gets pretty loud only when i'm fighting
i'm sorry about that
i think it's fine really i'll just made
it a little bit a little bit more quiet
than on my side generally
yeah there was no audio settings what
the hell
so anyway can you join my club
you're looking like you're ready for it
that's a cute dress
yes that's what i'm thinking majima
yatoy masho
but she looks like she already has a job
in that area
what a covering club if you gave me a
present i'll think about it i have
tissues a purse oh
designer purse
uh really
where
where are we gonna buy that
sega
uh shot bar
casino
oh wait no it should be one of those
important brands maybe
or
um
donkey what this sometimes has pretty
not sometimes actually always has pretty
good ones oh they're march okay well
then
that was that one right yeah okay okay
okay
a gucci bag for the gucci girl
no problem i'll do anything
because um i don't want to try that
minigame again
a little bit today
maybe right after we
recruit her
um i think
that could be fun yeah
yeah
that's another side quest you're telling
you we're sold out blah blah please well
there's got to be a way look you can
wear all you want but so that is sold
out please
no oh no oh no
what am i going to do sniffle
okay not now
i need to buy a gucci bag
oh
oh they got those gucci bags
oh i like these ones
they look like a louis vuitton
[Music]
i don't have a louis vuitton bag though
i'm just saying because i've been
looking
at their bags a lot
and there are other things so i i know
the look but i don't own
any louis vuitton
there's a ring here just a single ring
the wall
the wall is asking me to marry it
maybe i should cup it on the wall
thank you so much for
asking
wall
you're beautiful you're so
hard and wide and
stiff
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry i need a bag
uh
french handbag or italian shoulder bag
does it matter guys
[Music]
that's only in disguise oh [\h__\h]
it might be
yeah it might be
oh she was literally like camouflaging
herself into a wall holding a ring out
there waiting for me
to accept her
because i i already i already told her i
know what she says in indonesian when
she when she asks people to marry her so
i told her that it's not gonna work on
me
anyway does it matter
a handbag specifically okay
[Music]
yeah
no
[Music]
camouflaging
wait do i say it wrong oh come on
if anything i said correctly i would say
how how the is it a french word
originally
it sounds like a french word i think i'm
saying it correctly
don't say the e
i'm not saying e
i said camouflage
but i said camouflaging
like a verb in that case so that might
may have
sounded like camouflage
no no no no
wait i'm supposed to say the e
wait am i supposed to say it
oh camouflagey
wait which one is it
no
i sell it right okay okay
well
i live i live in a country that's uh
close to france you know so
i got that stuff down perfectly you know
it's kind of almost in my blood not
really it's just in my air because it's
close enough
um
but that means because the air goes into
my body so the air also touches my blood
so somehow i do have some french blood
in my body
i'm just saying i don't want to flex or
anything
but yeah it's pretty cool i know
yeah
um will it because
this one you know it's just it comes
natural to me
um
flexing flexing the european and me
i recruited her she's silver
that still means i can't um
make her
uh
do a do a makeover right she needs to be
golden or what was it
where is my place
where is that place again
this is not it right i do it somewhere
else i do it
uh
here
yeah sunshine
makeup is just the story ones oh okay
well i want to go and try it again but
we gotta
apparently go to the
um
you know what uncle i'll go down this
bread chicken
i have to beat the bosses at the cover
right bro
she probably runs you get platinum
hospital sub story et cetera ah okay
single plants we will baguette
from
oh there's another one of those ladies
do you also want a bag or something else
you got you girls really stand out
why are you wearing that dress if you
don't really already have a job like
that
a high-end accessory
a high-end accessory wait is that all
you said
a ring a necklace or a bracelet
okay it could be any of those things
well while we're at it
bracelet or a ring
[Music]
all right
she said
a ring a
necklace necklace is
cheap
or a bracelet
i'll buy you the bracelet it suits your
address
and there goes my money again
excuse me not applicable what are you
saying there what are you trying to say
huh
yeah it fits her look
that's what i'm thinking
you know that's just once again the
french fashionista in my blood
that knows exactly what to do
here there you go
bronze okay the other one was better
but welcome welcome
also while we're here okonomiyaki please
no oh he doesn't even
it doesn't even sound okonomiyaki
what's here
outdoor ultra moo oh no
show me player is here huh yeah
i don't know how to play shogi
my game
is
[Music]
all right i'm gonna make my way now to
the bridge i wonder
[Music]
did
the donkey hope they have some medicine
too because i i feel like i want to
stock up again
otherwise
i only see convenience stores
of course the drugstore is really far
away again
yeah ah
okay okay okay
i don't know what happens on the bridge
so i wanna get the medicine before
beforehand
also gonna save here
no reason to buy anything other than
royale
but i'd like to buy a mix of of two
different ones
okay
don't by to get your weapons ah you mean
you pick up my stuff uh that was that
was uh here dragon tiger yeah
you're right with that
did you page me
noise
[Music]
whoa crazy unbelievable success mission
went swimmingly and treasure was found
double action revolver
we got two recipes we got parts
and
silver shellies
what is that
i got a gun
send you
off again i guess
wait how much money do i have
not much
ah you know what not now
when i have more money
it's a cup
a goblet a fancy cup
is it just for selling
it doesn't say what effect it has it
just says it's fancy
[Music]
yeah
oh can i sell it to you
oh only at one specific place i can sell
it
is that close by
because i want to get that out of my
inventory
where's the pawn shop
oh it should be one of the
yellow ones
temple
ah it's down there again
[Applause]
oh remind me to go there
stupid child again
remind me to go there sometime
soon
or i guess i could put it in my item
books
yeah i should do that
after the drugstore
one thing after another
how much is it worth i wonder
where is uh here
you guys can see you for all these
things
okay we need
[Music]
oh
now we have a full inventory
[Music]
i'm out of here bye-bye
you can sell directly from your item box
whenever you're near a pawn shop next
what
oh oh you mean if it's in my item box i
can sell
whatever is in my item box on something
okay
i want to save and put something in my
item box
what is that
how's it going thanks for calling me
right away that's as clunky as back it's
like it's a phone it's a mobile phone
it's the newest invention
wow
shoulder bag phone
it's the future
new iphone looking hot
why doesn't anyone appreciate the
awesomeness of backlinks
they should appreciate it
[Music]
we're just chatting on the phone for
that chunky bag you got hold on
we
win
pretty wild
no it's a real phone
backbone who put the phone in the bag
yeah
you don't know this is all the rage now
it's a fully transportable mobile
telephone made possible for the
state-of-the-art technology
now people will be able to carry
telephones with them all the time you'll
be able to connect with anyone anytime
anywhere
it does begins the addiction to mobile
phones
in humanity
the start of the ending
of humanity
no more chit chat no more personal
face to face conversations
no more letters
no no
none of that [\h__\h]
[Music]
i'll stick to the payphones of the rest
of the peasants
were you just about to enter a phone
booth yes i was
so i see you
very well i shall let you use the
cutting edge of technology my back phone
the place you call
thank you
i want everyone to experience the future
today you need to understand just what
the backbone represents aren't i
generous a bad phone ah guy says it's
state of the art do i want to see what
it's all about
i guess
wait there's another cute lady in the
back
oh she's staring at me she wants me she
wants me bad
she's down bad i love that red dress
you're rocking girl
let me call
music
i ain't hearing anything yeah you gotta
push the numbers majima
uh-huh
is it not working
you kidding me are you just acting
oh man the battery must have died i
probably used it all when i took that
call from my body
and they want batteries
eight hours yeah for the night i'm gonna
charge it for the night
that's more like a hassle than it's
worth well seeing as how your marvel of
technology has gone silent i guess i'll
have to pass on your offer thanks
you can't just give up on your chance to
cross the frontier of progress just
because it's out of power doesn't mean
we can't get it back
just told me it'll take eight hours i
think that got i ain't got that kind of
time man
don't hold that okay
batteries
okay well i'll use the phone anyway
though
sorry dude
here
and i guess we'll save while we're here
[\h__\h]
hello everybody
thank you for coming
i probably won't
never mind i don't know i don't know yet
about reading super chats cause like
i gotta prepare some things for
tomorrow's stream
legs
but i might just do that tomorrow i
don't know
might be fine
cabaret club
leopard print any any lip part
print clothes would be great but it has
to be designer brand name
uh-huh okay
well not right now
not right now
ramen
[Music]
ramen wait a second i'm not full health
i want some ramen now
right now
hmm
you don't say
yakuza don't scare me
don't scare me like that
er cha chu ramen
maxima is a strong man who needs strong
food
spoopy super chat backlog
oh no
oh is it you
i'm gonna have to take that back
um
[Music]
is
that's a cool boat
can we just jump down there
nice boat nice boat
nice boat nice board a nice boat
[Music]
um
and another one
had my controller on my on my lap
and it vibrated suddenly
oh yeah
oh
this is cool
[Music]
[Laughter]
of course she took me somewhere else
[Applause]
this feels familiar
wow
[Applause]
there's no cute girls
where are the cute girls
man where's the teacher lady the english
teacher
[Applause]
who is
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
do you want me to do it
um
[Applause]
what does that do for you
maybe he's hoping i'll die
[Applause]
oh i'm eating so many potato chips
is this a tough one i wonder
hmm
i'll just do my kikity kick and then we
could oh i don't have to go down
top for me maybe
yeah
[Applause]
um
orange juice
[Music]
foreign
looks like joker or something
[Music]
crimes are unspeakable i don't really
have
any unspeakable crimes
god he's a freak
point like that
[Music]
it sounds really familiar
okay
um
he got a knife
he's got enough
but i got it back
[Applause]
hey ginger chapman
i'll make orange juice out of you get up
[Applause]
he barely does any damage
easy
[Applause]
orange juice is ready who wants a cup um
[Music]
i can't fight
give me [\h__\h] flashbacks stop it
let's go
okay
oh okay without that he would be
he would be so lost and useless i'm
telling you
wow
oops [\h__\h] i want to activate that heat
move
whatever
get him to the ground
i'm done
okay buddy
but his movements really look lame like
he doesn't have much experience
fighting
good dropkick though but that's
partially on me because i made a mistake
[Applause]
and another one
we got him on the ground and that's the
end for you but don't worry majima
doesn't kill people
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
in one sentence is this kelly from a
different dimension
is this kelly's spirit animal dad
dead puncher
that's my line
[Applause]
oh
yeah okay he doesn't have much coins
that's good
yeah nice
[Applause]
yeah run into my into my choreography
and another one oh he has quite the key
though
bring it on
[Music]
[Applause]
you got me there you got me there
i'll give you that
[Applause]
i thought you were done
i'll heal a little bit just a little bit
i was healing okay
he got me out of my groove
what's that man
you might need to be faster
guys change my style
now we're good
that one i cannot
resist
he moves fast
a few more punches
[Music]
haven't been
[Applause]
stylish
victory
[Applause]
[Music]
tony i'm coming
he will hopefully be very happy to see
me
[Music]
foreign
huh
the girl was his
daughter because he built that place
why
okay
allu hodor
one more time
and maybe get some ramen again
i'm hungry
[Music]
i'm super hungry today
good stuff
i completed your ramen oh i got a cp for
that oh
gosh
yum yum yum
okay and you guys say buy more medicine
do i really need some um
[Music]
i have three
free slots three free slots
get it guys
freeze
three free months you hear what i'm
saying
oh let's help this guy
free free [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
into the river you go
overkill absolutely overkill
oh what was that
oh i felt good
that felt good
the slugger
on magima is so much more fun than on
kiryu
a gold plate
can i also sell that
for good
money where was that place again
wait where was the drugstore
oh here i went into the wrong direction
[Music]
oh batteries at don quixote uh
[Applause]
[Music]
sell this one to it everything
all right maybe we'll go to the pawn
shop first
[Music]
but he's still alive
okay this one's gone
his name was oda
but that's a different oda it's okay
it's okay
and there you go
there you go
okay um so wait where the hell is the
pawn shop it's over there right
there okay and i gotta go go there to
get a leopard brick print
something something
[Music]
i'm gonna take a cab
what happened to oda
nothing it's okay he's fine i'll protect
oda
okay
i wanna go
here
also big big ben well the money is over
there as well
i don't wanna
i'm not in the mood to encounter him
right now i think
uh
over there oh he's gone now anyway
oh wait there's a lady here i forgot did
i forget the red dress i didn't know i
didn't but while i'm here is it even
worth it recruiting so many girls
at this stage
she has okay hair though
what do you want what do you want [\h__\h] i
didn't listen
i always wanted to design a brand name
code or scav okay
coat or scarf and something with a
leopard print
which will wait won't that fill up my
inventory as well only for the moment
though we need to go
let's go to the pawn shop
the more good horses do you have the
better okay but it won't help me much if
i suck at the game
sell items so
i'm gonna sell
the plate and
i thought i could sell the thing ah here
there it is
22 million
[Music]
wow
indeed wow
holy wow
that's some good morning cartoon cutting
do you hear it guys i can hear it it's
like the angels are singing but with the
sound of money
okay
excuse me i'm here again yeah it's kind
of suspicious that i'm coming here so
often buying so many expensive women's
presents
okay we need uh this one and
uh [\h__\h] what was the other one
uh a scarf
i think she said scarf
she didn't specify which one right scarf
and something else
but a code or scuff okay we get the
french scarf
and the other thing
because those are cheaper ones a guy
yeah i have i have many material girls
ettola
foreign
and i am a material girl
okay
i want to use that on him
[Music]
where was that girl she was somewhere
over there right one of one of the girls
that i saw wait no wrong side
no she's over there
where's she wait no she's over there why
am i here ah
i found out what's going on over the
bridge but i just went back
[Music]
now there's people there again i don't
want them i don't wanna i don't wanna no
no no no no no no i just fought you
myself
well
the problem is i don't run away from
fights so even if it takes time
i gotta do it but look at my money
the money is agreeing with me
[Applause]
hmm
just one sec please
we should play some elevator music
whenever i'm in one of these fights
[Music]
please hold
please hold the line
please press number one
if you would like to stay in the line to
continue watching the stream please
press number two
if you want to leave but you're not
given the choice
please press number three if you'll do
anything for takanasi kiwawa where's the
girl
wait where is she
wasn't she here
i was pretty sure she was um
no she was here
thank you
it was the wrong side after all yeah
funny once you got it
i shouldn't be talking to too many girls
at once
i'm trying to tell you i got confused
what ah there she is
that's her
okay
french scarf
be happy now
silver
okay
and now
we go
to here where the red girl is and then
we
can still buy some medicine
and then go to the quest okay okay okay
that sounds
sounds perfect
free thank you
actually never mind we wanted to do the
game with the girls too
oh you you were here wait what what what
was that quest about
[Music]
the again fund
i don't know
that sounds complicated
what is
um
[Music]
will you take some of the funds money
it's your choice
you know why you would want me to put up
cash but you're saying you'd invest in
my business too of course but it ain't
like it's our money we'd be handing out
it would be from one of the investors
mutual investment trust
when we pair up clients so whether you
contribute or withdraws it's always
coming from or going from the same to
the same person but
[Music]
headhurt
do we need to understand this
real estate guy in kamurocho
when that certain someone in camera to
invest some cash it comes to you here in
southampton
wait
is that supposed to be keep you
and it swaps the cash between
kirill and majima
[Music]
ah there it is okay
ah
wait
oh
is this what kirin did i already invest
something on kitty's side i don't recall
that
did you just give this to me as a
present
shared item box huh okay no no i'm good
i'm good i'm good
i'm good
but okay now we have that option to do
that that's cool
a skirt and there you go i recently told
you guys i don't really like clothes
with that with that kind of print on it
i feel like it's so tacky
um
bronze not a huddle
okay now now
now i want to give that game another try
it's
down
down here down here okay oh
but before that
i'm buying some more medicine
[Music]
it was popular in the time yeah
yeah yeah yeah it was
still it reminds me of
what was her name that show of the girl
that was kind of like a maid to that
rich guy's family flan fletcher or fran
fletcher or something like that
she was always wearing leopard prints
and stuff like that
always
and nanny yeah
they were playing that in our tv in
german as well i remember that
yeah i watched it sometimes
sometimes randomly
okay and now
next stop is
sunshine bar or whatever it was
[Music]
foreign
never mind
maybe you should be carrying a bigger
weapon where you're not so
easily
missing
everything in front of you hey
me
stupid fight
sorry i'm late no problem welcome we
didn't do that much main story yet
so
it's been going pretty slow so far
because i have to run from one side of
the city to the other side of the city
the whole time
[\h__\h] hole again
i missed it again
i'm sorry
i'm sorry to the store owner i'm sorry
smacking smacking real good
stop
[Music]
left right left right left right
have these guys never heard of credit
cards so was that not a thing back then
they're all carrying so much cash with
them
i can change direction during that move
why don't you then
i'm going here
but i think i want some food here as
well
i guess japan doesn't use that
card the cards as much as
we do maybe
this place looks fancy
or shiny young
what can i get here sushi
yeah holy [\h__\h] completing all of that is
kind of tough
soup of the day
anymore i'm gonna burst you kidding me
it's just a soap
oh
okay
they have vodka
huh
i want the soup though
majima
[Applause]
someone recommend you no it was just on
my map
that's a surprise
why
just that we don't often get young
customers young
young people always want to try new
things and this fast food is so trendy
nowadays
it's not about being trendy it's about
being cheap
and the taste
the the taste of fast food
it's just so addictive
majima is just 24.
he's just a little itty bitty baby boy
majima
i'll come back
beginning of a friendship with the
komian chef interacting with him we're
going to remember
we've never had a completed friendship
before in this game i wonder what
will happen
will he give me free food
[Music]
time for sunshine
batteries yeah
batteries
hello
i'm i won't get anywhere today at this
pacing
[Music]
there's no
there's no batteries i got there
i can't carry can i sell you much
weather
i'll give away my tissues
[Music]
dun dun
oh by the way did we do this on kitty's
side yeah but we didn't do it on
majima's side yet right let's see what
do we got how much i don't have much cp
on
on his side but we can already
uh buy some things
oh yes
i need to sneeze
oh
new one boy
oh but we can't do this one yet i don't
know
that's so
fast um
by the valley when you're
giving agents extra funds what
ah
um
we got the card watcher
i'll close reopen the menu oh
oh
hello is this a platinum girl
can we restyle her
it's good that we went here first oh
hello akina
can i work at your club yes you're hired
you're hired
welcome
gold i thought she was going to be
blasting them
god damn it yes you can style him i
can't
no i can't ride it's only there's only
plants in them
another one
[Laughter]
wow
you look old
okay
silver
oh my god we have so many of them now
they keep on multiplying
oh my god
[Music]
okay
that's okay for now
uh
ah i was going i was going there i was
going there
ah
what's it now
what do you want now
huh
it's great little sace tax you wanted to
pay attention every time you buy
something
of course it's just taxes
some [\h__\h] idiots
just suck it up for [\h__\h] sake it's no
reason to get mad over that
huh
i'll take care of those another time
this one's good
really
[Music]
i'm not gonna read the whole thing
though
[Music]
you want to use it's a new tags you're
going to start wait they
it hasn't been around for that long
every time you buy something they're
going to judge you three percent more
attacks
that's how i do people that's how it
don't mean
it's a [\h__\h]
eh my my chill
being this guy to a pulp isn't going to
make the sales sense yeah exactly
and tell the government without beating
up people who can't do anything about it
um wanna take out for this mosquito and
we'll show you about
everyone blowing up
okay
i guess i'm fighting you
right i wanna do
i'm sorry bye-bye okay
that's what you get
thank you so much
i'm tayo matsuzako tayo is in the sun
what a coincidence um i drink yeah okay
um please
mm-hmm i need a drink i came to
tottenham for a conference on taxation
policy but i wasn't prepared to face the
public about it
even here we're going to
you're trying to make this country a
better place to live right you got to
take some pride in that do you think so
i knew people would be unhappy with the
new tax but only on the logical level
when i saw how emotional people get
about it
if they get mad about everything
they get about literally everything you
try to implement
it's just you can't you can't make
everyone happy
even if it's a good thing
that you're trying to implement you just
can't get them happy if they find out at
the same time there's only on the tip of
the iceberg and there are more taxes on
the way i hate to think how the people
really
do
[Music]
many more effective ways of generating
revenue streams
[Music]
come
on but
yo i'm telling you taxes are lower in
japan than they are in austria so
at least i at least
certain taxes
certain taxes at least i don't know
about everything i don't know everything
in detail
yeah
okay i want to get your views on
taxation my views
maybe majima should become politician
[Music]
you see i just had this idea perhaps
someone is completely who is completely
ignorant of taxation can offer an
entirely different perspective
i mean
yeah aren't
politicians supposed to like
you know
poll people and get the opinion of
people in general anyway
isn't that what you're supposed to do
anyway
[Music]
okay let's talk about taxes
oh we're going down there oh gonna be so
far away again
where are we hey
where are we you better bring me back to
where we just where
is he hoping to try gold in the copper
mine yeah
isn't this the place where i just had my
bag you
do you know why the government collects
taxes from the people oh it's a quiz um
to provide
public services
i think
yes okay wonderful
education medicare medical care police
blah blah blah build roads and bridges
reunions
if you were in the position of
collecting taxes from the people what
would you tax
what's satosan what
what
what does that mean who is got
who is that
huh
well i would attack some
cigarettes
that makes people more healthy too
because maybe they'll think it's too
expensive now don't buy it anymore
three years ago there actually have been
a small tax on tobacco products
i don't really really want to pay tax on
them but i suppose they're non-essential
mm-hmm maybe you're gonna jack up taxes
it's the non-essential stuff that you
start with people might be even more
likely to understand tax and smokes
right
yeah
yeah um
it packs around 200 yen now people [\h__\h]
and moan but i think that they'd still
fork over for anything
yeah yeah perhaps yeah
oh i think
about
each pack being worth it yeah yeah
about five minutes and probably quit
cold turkey
oh
was he already planning on increasing
that to 500 holy [\h__\h] i think something
that's closely tied to everyday living
would have the best potential uh-huh
air
castle
gasoline is all ready i i don't drive a
car but from what i know it's already
[\h__\h] expensive everywhere
pets
the pets themselves are you saying that
or we're always saying the the
like food
and
liter litter and all that that comes
with that or just the
having them
no we want to give smart ideas not
stupid ideas guys guys guys guys
yeah
the price of gas is dependent on the
cost of petroleum so people have
experienced price hikes before they
should be used to price creep actually
there's also provisional sheriff and
guys
[Music]
that's a fantastic idea
anything else yeah
i was thinking about that sales tax
those goofballs were all riled up about
next year we got to start paying three
percent on top of everything we buy
right
why stop at three percent sure you can
go in at that rate but wouldn't you get
more if you bumped it up
it wasn't matuma
when he hurt three percent
really pissed and shocked himself just a
moment ago and now he says oh how about
we make it even higher
that would be impossible you saw what
happened just the three percent tax
caused so much outrage people wanted to
tear me apart yeah
taiyo chan you ain't thinking people are
pissed because you sprang a new thing on
them and you have to turtle up you gotta
think about the long game
familiarity is a scary thing my friend
people are bitching and moaning about
this shiny new tags but once it becomes
a regular part of life they'll move on
to the next thing to be to moan about
and that's when you start gradually
turning the screws
every time you hike it up a little you
get some more blubbering but they won't
be screaming bloody murder like the
first time you introduce attacks wanna
know why because they'll be used to
getting screwed
if something they've already accepted
gets a little worse it's just the facts
of life doing what they do
yeah i guess so
please uh don't vote for majima
he just understands it too well um
are you even off this earth
want to know
mazuma is an alien
if the sales tax were to be raised how
high do we think we should go
five percent
yeah
[Music]
it's probably
how high is it now i wonder probably
like higher than that actually
eight percent or so
um uh
ashwood just what really
you [\h__\h] politicians have so much
money and you just give me some wood
oh [\h__\h] you
ten percent
consumption tax in japan
wow
really he probably just ripped apart one
of those chairs while he was on the
toilet it gave me one piece of wood from
that chair
thought i wouldn't know this huh
if texas got up isn't my fault no no no
no no
agata
see we're back here
come on okay we're going down to
sunshine
down to sunshine we go
and then we focus on the goddamn cyclist
hey main quest i mean
well i hear sound issues
elgato
there we go
okay
this is how majima crashed the japanese
economy oh god look who's here uh uh i
just wanna just
sunshine
okay
one sec one second
okay i'll probably be really [\h__\h] at
this but
i was so stressed out last time already
yeah i guess so
new girl has joined many new girls have
joined
prepare to open
all right so hostas list
huh
look at her
yahoo
oh look we have a lot of the i love
these ones down here
bronze
ah a lot of bronze girls silver
okay we definitely have to add the
golden one how do we
how do we add them
ah cast on duty one second
[Music]
so we have
sexy and beauty
we want to cover certain things right
now we add uh this chick she's beauty
and cute
and we need someone funny
i guess
who's the funniest
you
funny and cute
okay
so if someone wants sexy if i just try
to remember this i'll know what to do
but can i add more oh wait i can add
more oh yeah right okay uh then i guess
you because you're silver
thank you
should i just fill it all up
just for the sake of it
um
[Music]
yeah okay
nice music
[Music]
has to be part of it
okay she's just an all-arounder but
she's basically [\h__\h] at everything
oh god i won't be able to remember that
but okay i'll try to remember jesus free
uh
yuki is sexy and beauty akina is beauty
and cute
and hyoko is cute and funny
oh god i won't be able to remember that
oh
cute and funny the girl with the
fringe
and the straight hair
short hair cute girl with earrings but
everybody has earrings side swept bangs
to the right side is
beauty and cute i can't remember this
[\h__\h]
okay
uh what was special training again
i got talking
all right let's get to know each other a
little better yuki not that i care but
why don't you tell me about what kind of
guy you
okay
well my bad so tell me about your type
already
um
what's what's a prince here
a prince
a horse
i think she wants me
yeah it sounds just like me
wait i shouldn't have said that probably
wait
we need to pick smart answers
yeah
don't say it like that
oh sorry you could tell maybe your ideal
man but i can't be your princess why are
you saying that my team i have
confidence
she's happy though
what's that on this next that was not a
joke that was not a joke
no no joda no no
[Music]
this chick is so [\h__\h] rude she's so
such a [\h__\h] but she doesn't realize it
it's the eye patch isn't it
huh
on it
surprised you're such a dreamer
yuki-chan
i don't even know of any old girls
schools in my
country
so i grew up surrounded by girls at your
schools i'm starting to see why it's
tough being around men
yeah i guess you can't really get used
to talking to
guys in that case that is
pretty realistic
huh
why are you saying sorry
no you're actually the best one in the
whole club so
don't worry about it but also a club
needs variety i guess
i guess that's the more motivating thing
to say
a good club needs a ride with variety of
a variety wide variety of girls actually
i mean sure it would be nice to have
someone who could actually talk to the
customers but some guys prefer girls who
come up like they don't buy into the
whole nightlife business oh yeah i guess
so
you know it's a good argument
see a girl like you adds appeal to the
club as a whole yuki town we can cater
to all walks of life that way
shut up
what are you talking about
what kind of guy you take me for next
question
i know it's probably a ways out but i
wonder what you'll be like when you do
get yourself a boyfriend yuki down
wink wink wink
that was her name right
uh
that's this job though it is
you figure it out probably
or do a horseback date
i shouldn't figure it out
she probably will like the answer about
the horseback date though because you'll
she'll probably find it funny
[Music]
but yeah you'll figure it out
let's go with that one
if you liked him you'd make the effort
though
i think i could really fall asleep in
that club
now
the next question if we get that down
can we get her to level up
you know you're an odd girl yukitan
in one breath you're saying you'd want
to date a prince and then next you're
saying it'll be a hassle you're like a
grumpy old man in the body of a romantic
young lady
[Music]
don't say that now it's close to a level
up come on
so grumpy in middle age is fine as long
as you're a woman
well maybe this is a bad time to bring
it up but have you ever actually gone
out with someone you could send i get
the feeling you've never dated are we
gonna go on a date someday
sorry
um
i yield
oh you should prove me wrong you've got
quite a bit of dating experience you
could john
no
you kind of figured but you know it
ain't no bad some of our guests actually
like inexperienced girls better cheer up
oh no
where are the hearts where the hearts no
normal lesson
[\h__\h]
ah
you done goofed
both of those answers were kind of weird
man
but okay we gotta level up
nice
okay now uh let's go
uh
i guess
they can call in for absences what
okay this will be so bad this will be so
bad this will be so bad ah
i don't know what i'm doing i don't i
don't remember call
what button yeah
[Music]
i prefer sexy okay i have uh
this
this girl
have fun
okay okay so far so good
[Music]
we're sexy
there you go
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's go let's go let's go why is he
angry
you have to do something
reverse beauty long session but also
poor beauty beauty beauty here
[Music]
remember
what's his problem she's sexy
[Music]
sexy
huh
[Music]
help okay hi
what's your problem
[Music]
he's giving you a signal what is the
signal
power okay
did he sweat on you i'm so sorry
[Music]
very sexy once that long session poor
uh namito can go again
[Music]
it's actually going better than the
first time thankfully
i have way more girls to choose from so
okay check please travel
a gift gift bye bye
i just give everyone a gift
why is he not happy with namiko
what's your problem
uh
[Music]
i don't want to give my best girl to you
why
[Music]
what do you want
funny funny funny funny
you're not saying
[Music]
always extend okay
i wish it would count for that guy too
[Music]
my first bunny short session
i don't have one
anyone who is particularly funny anymore
i'll give you how to meeting
well gracious stand up give girl
everywhere
[Music]
never had these options before i don't
know what to do
[Music]
ignore what the customer wants yeah
gracious send them
praise
we want
so she recovers oh okay
okay
[Music]
what's happening what's happening
what's happening
[Music]
[Applause]
okay praise the girl good job
the pgm slaps
fancy funky time is over though
what does that sign mean
how do i remember what that means the
menu ah okay open the menu that's that
kind of
that kind of movement okay
how would i know
check please
uh how about you extend your session
have fun
get yourself to get get get you get to
know her a little bit better but it
ended already fun well i got a little
bit more money today
three million and it's not that much i
spent too much on gifts
but that's okay
[Music]
wow
we didn't even have that many
customers
profit is profit
true it do be like that can i go again
i can do it right away again
can i just continue this forever and
ever and ever oh [\h__\h] oopsie
are they
healed though or do they have like oh
some of them are not feeling so happy
how do i make them feel happier
look at the last super chat first
attention to running look at the
customer's face when selecting a girl
and just make them as happy as you can
nowhere
oh
okay
oh my god your wrap down
give get them to rest okay
[Music]
so i just removed them from my lineup or
at least at least this girl
and i can get a different one and
yeah
the other ones maybe i'll keep
[Music]
okay
we didn't even use our our joker because
i was waiting for someone who could
spend more money
okay open for business let's do it one
more time
a special training oh can i do it again
oh oh no no wait wait wait wait i guess
no wait i didn't
i was again special training okay
[Music]
i'm here to teach you some things again
about
talking to guys
hey
kinda cold today huh saw this neck
something like this there
i thought everybody was saying you were
cold
acting cold
oh god great start
i can tell you've been getting better
with the customers lately but you're
still having trouble keeping
conversations rolling
on
girl we went through this the first time
you can talk about anything even
something small the weather current
events keep casual
you can even throw out something you've
been trying to get off of your chest
[Music]
anyway so today let's try putting the
burden of conversation on you yuki
best trick to start a conversation is to
just ask a question think of me as a
guest and fire away anything
so what you're going to ask
i don't
[Music]
egg
yes egg sushi
of course egg i'm all about time ago
i knew she would like it i knew she
would like to tell my girl
tamago is key
it's true it's to be true
based on my experience
[Music]
hi
imagine is very young still you know
but check this out you could join your
brother question on the left field but
the conversation went fine didn't it
you ask a question the other person
answers easy huh
if you're having trouble carrying a
conversation just ask the customer a
question and let them ramble it will
turn into a conversation lickety-split
okay
next question
i don't have a wife don't ask me that
kind of question yeah
no wife to get mad at me in the first
place i live alone as a free man more or
less free man you might you're stuck in
this city literally
do i look like a chef
yes i do
i just do whatever
that would be amazing
oh yummy please yes
oh
she wants to cook for me
[Music]
by the way they say meat and potatoes
but they actually mean a japanese
um meal called nikujaga it's
it's pretty simple but i really liked it
when i ate it in japan usually when
when uh usually it was something more
homely nothing you would really get at
the restaurant but something that a host
family would make for me for example
you read that in the book or something
did you actually read books like that
you could tell
my lips are sealed
you can open them up though
i can tell you're getting better at this
talking thing you're making good
progress
what what i mean i can open them up over
the crowbars and this isn't that what a
crowbar usually
is used for like opening up things
[Laughter]
i didn't mean by kissing or anything
just this with the crowbar
gently
what do you mean
by
chill guys gently
oh
i think she will be happy about i'll
request you
i think she'll think that's funny
then i'll request you as a customer
yukichang
i carry a conversation just violence me
right all i gotta do then is come in
here and request you over and over
for me
it's a joke man
who's been so casting you're gonna learn
to tell when someone's joking
um
it worked anyway
that's not like a hostess who knows your
jam
hey look at the time any last questions
you want to ask me forget about the
training for a sec anything goes
[Music]
that's a pretty vague question
i should probably say she's working
hard because your cute is just too
shallow
working hard
[Music]
what's important is how hard you're
trying to be better
oh
besides you ain't great at talking to
guys yet here you are toughing it out to
overcome your weakness that's something
to be proud of if you ask me oh
huh
what creep did she just call me creepy
[Laughter]
she has a way with words oh yes oh yes
this [\h__\h] girl
let's call it a wrap this must have been
better than the last one
okay okay
but how
how do you get
the perfect score what the hell
hi
[Music]
level 8 hmm go level 9.
bam
okay
she's far ahead of everyone else holy
[\h__\h]
let's do open for business
okay i'm feeling good about it
[Music]
let's do this girls
okay so i'm gonna look at the face
apparently it changes her first cute
though
[Music]
okay i was just looking at
who has that skill that that attribute
okay
[Music]
spend that money yeah yeah yeah
make it rain make it rain
for sexy
[Music]
okay
it's not even that sexy but okay
help okay what's up
towel that's a towel
i learned that
before before the game told me that
looked like a towel movement indeed okay
okay okay
[Music]
he doesn't really like any of the girls
well then
go with her
please okay how about an extension
declined
[Music]
did i still get the money
uh
what's that ladies glass maybe
tell me before i give you the wrong
thing yes you always get the money
wait what did you just send i looked
away for one second guest bus
[Music]
okay okay
okay
[Music]
fine with me
what just happened ah r1 is possible i
don't want to do it now maybe we'll get
one more customer
why they're all poor
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
no thank you okay goodbye
rip battery what battery
battery
[Music]
oh it will be fun
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
there you go
[Music]
oh wait we can do it again
wow
[Music]
i'm learning
[Applause]
[Music]
i have 50 million in the bank guys 50
million
nice
500 fans oh we did it
i bet hino's not a happy camper right
now
but it is hino so he's not going to
stand for this i'm sure he'll try
something for sure he might try barging
in here again that would be bad do you
think we should keep the doors locked
the donkey done
how are your how are you our customers
gonna get in all right and then what are
we going to do don't worry about it i'll
[\h__\h] him up
why don't we go and check out club mars
huh
go to pop mars
we're going up against him it might be a
good chance to research what kind of man
he knows and what club mars is like that
ain't a half bad idea yoda chan let's go
and take a look for ourselves
okay
donkey dong
i guess we can go now
is it gonna be dangerous
can i somebody said i can save in here
is that right
where is the
where could i
what save that a lie also you could tell
how are you doing
backstage
ah
sure there was a backstage room i forgot
about that one oh yeah
i like this place
okay steve because i don't know what
will happen if we go to club mars
yeah i love the jazz
so jazzy
why are they covering up the mirror
weird with a curtain
getting ready for a fight
i knew it i knew that would be a fight
let's go
marsh so this is hino's club mars
okay
looks kind of run down
around it it's really flashy
it's a damn eye so it hurts to look at
it hey someone's coming
oh the girl is cute
oh my god
we're gonna get her for our club aren't
we
she's wearing such a cute dress like an
idol dress kind of
um
i'll be back as soon as i can make it
italian
wonderful i'll be waiting for you
oh she's platinum
yeah why did the dad be the favor and
send eye to his table but he didn't
spend jack
what the hell does he think he is
reading i like that she's the number one
girl of club mars
i i don't want you dealing with
cheapskates like that laos anymore got
it
loose
but tabata son is a long time regular
and he mentioned his finances were tight
this month
crimea river oh crabby river
oh grammy river
oh crummy river
i want you to uh i want you serving the
fat cats because you know what makes the
world go around money money money and
more money
listen up maggot we'll be tired we clear
in the club and let's pimp out the
interior use gold leaf or something
yes yes
he's got another thing coming if he's
fixated on cash you know thinks money
can solve anything
as as if he wouldn't notice that we're
standing here
including how to run club mars as a
business so he spends as much as he
thinks he needs to get more customers
and and become a popular club
he's actually spent a small fortune to
attract girls from the other clubs
that's why the quality of his town
really sets the bar
but the girl who's undisputed number one
at club mars is i who's been working
here for a long time
well she's modeled after a real person
huh
she's another one at club martian did he
not drag her in along a gold paper route
too
no she seems to be the lone exception
apparently she simply wanted to work at
a cabaret club and just applied
the girl who walks in off the street
winds up making more money than the
girls who spend tons of money to recruit
the irony of it all
that's par for the course you can't
expect girls who'd portray their clubs
for cold hard cash to provide excellent
customer service but that girl she seems
so nice she's so cute too i wish a girl
like that would come to work for us
we'll go get her go get it
what's going on there
do you know them sir
no just two buzzing flies who need to be
sweating
here's another job for you go
exterminate them
um are we having an issue with bugs in
the club
yes yes
we need to
fix them go get a programmer go get
kokuchan to fix the bugs
oh it's that
ah her name sounds familiar
yeah the music
well i have some hot chicks
as my fans too
i've got some cute freaking girls too
[Music]
some cute cosplay girls
are you okay i'm okay
that was
easy you know from club mods one of the
five stars he ain't gonna be easy to get
rid of
i want the girl i want to restyle her
maybe i should just play sims uh
okay we really need to get going on the
main story
it's been three hours and we haven't
gotten anywhere so far
[Music]
oh we have the battery here
[\h__\h] i should put it in the item box oh
well um
we gotta go all the way up there
no
this way
yeah it's been three hours
i've been trying to do a lot of things
but
oh yeah i need to um my abilities i have
50 million
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i love my sims content
oh yeah i i was i'm gonna
play
sims one
sometime soon
i've been planning on that
can i um there we go
yeah it's such a classic and it's
actually
way more difficult than
sims 4.
back then sims was really really hard
mode
and i just want to do it for the
nostalgia as well
are you guys hearing me
or is it too loud
get into the superstar one oh for sims
one one i want all the extensions man oh
[\h__\h]
i need to go that
way
okay
hi guys
what are you guys again some side quests
look at them dancing
where was the skin
oh i'm glad you could make it
where is this again
break yourself sanji ah
[Music]
i fight you you teach me something or
what um real fights
breaking bad
they're posing
they're taking me to evil bridge
actually for this one time
i'm glad about that
do i have to fight in breaker style as
well
i suppose so
i think i'm winning i think i'm winning
wait
i'm looking the wrong way
[Music]
oh
i got 1
i i feel million the blue one gives me
the least amount of money
[Music]
yeah this one gives me twenty thousand
the red one gives me fifty thousand but
he keeps on interrupting my move no way
he also gives me thirty thousand
[Music]
oh
yes yes yes yes yes
skit
we're back here damn it
all right i was trying to hold back but
i landed a few head crackers
i'll survive
wasn't counting on any tips at all so i
figured we did pretty damn good
once we put a bit of polish on things we
might make some real green
here this is this is your cut
what
i deserve a full 2 million
excuse me huh
yeah
seems a little short dude
huh yes you're 20
huh you [\h__\h] bastard
i don't want to put you in the pool
house or anything but you do know who
was doing the real work out there don't
you
uh-huh
come on man don't beat me dead sure we
we're putting on a show but it's still
there's like help so be on the other end
of those kicks of yours
yeah you gotta pay your medical bills
but still
you were asking for it
this was part of the show
huh he's buying a boombox he's not even
using it for medical bills
compresses uh-huh
you're gonna be buying corn purses
oh yeah
[Music]
oh
i thought they would teach me a new move
they didn't even teach me a new move
huh
and i didn't even get healed
okay
okay well if i ah
if i talk to them well anyway uh okay uh
uh first i forgot once again i need to
spend my money
[Music]
i definitely want to spend some money on
slugger but also on breaker
oh damn
oh
boost the headcount of the batman
chuckles oh
i can i can afford that one
or boost some health
we could almost do both
i do use that a lot i do yeah
let's do it
more
crumble
with the bat yeah that one that goes
like left right
although in moments where i would like
to stop the combo it's going on even
longer would actually be a little bit of
a problem
okay once we have two million again i'm
gonna spend it on the health
damn it i spent nothing on here
[\h__\h] i spent it all on slugger
oops yeah it's a bit one-sided right now
we spent 70 000 on slugger and then 5.2
and 6.8 here
damn it
slugger opie i feel so too
um for for kirito i feel more like
switching around here and there for but
for majima it feels the safest to just
slug everything away
most of the time
all right
wait let me stay before
ah
you wanna feel my new power
what he's not doing
oh isn't that a new move
that's the new move that i just learned
right
there we go
and how do i change her out there we go
i don't know how i did it but i did it
damn it
slap
on your knees
kneel before
oh i'll take your kneecap
[Music]
beautiful okay i just it's your fault
you picked the fight with me i just
wanted to go to the safe
saving thingy oh i can do it wait i can
do i can give him the batteries
and i'm also
no never mind oh that's okay
uh yeah then let me give him the
batteries first
i got four million oh okay okay
here hand over the battery
blade blah blah
i'm fine please don't mind me
now is the time for you to experience
modest technology today
it's my shoulder it hurts
i can't very well put state-of-the-art
technology on the dirty ground can i oh
my shoulder it hurts
do you need a massage now
i'll be the one massaging him
look at the one standing behind me the
police guy to take this guy
he's just like dude when are you ever
gonna do the main quest
dude
dude you're wasting so much time
i'm waiting for you
i've been waiting so long
yeah i showed you my fight club please
respond
what you want a healing drink like
well i gotta give him one one of the the
good ones i only have good ones now i
think
okay
here
you're welcome
better be worth it
uh what's next
now we're gonna find these guys
is the reward gonna be that i'm gonna be
able to use his phone wherever i want
maybe
that i can save wherever i want you know
what that would actually be worth it
that would actually be amazing
it would make sense as a reward it's not
that yeah
beautiful
beautiful oh i got an untouchable bonus
because they didn't touch me
can't touch this
dada dada
you happy now
now give me your phone who am i even
calling
it still doesn't work
huh i'm pretty sure it was just you
[\h__\h] idiot
maybe when the ghoul fell out on your
ass this thing got circuit knocked loose
or something ah being at the cutting
edge is it is delicately constructed oh
no
my beautiful backbone
this is personal now
you heard me out when everyone else
mocked me you're even kind enough to buy
me battery in the medicine uh-huh i
can't let you walk away disappointed
after everything you've done for me
uh-huh
please come to the m store and chill for
your waste a little later i promise you
will finally get to make a collins state
of the art experience
okay
anyway uh
i know i would spend it i said i would
spend it on slugger but i didn't spend
[\h__\h] here
i can't really afford anything now
anyway though so so we're gonna get some
health
very good
and now um
sorry
i'm good to take you to the holding
cells whenever you ready now
let's go
listen
[Music]
i forgot to say
fine
i forgot to heal too
[Music]
we'll be fine
i was gonna save after the quest
oh well we'll be fine we'll always be
fine we until now we only died once like
a few times by the same guy
the the money shakedown guy
besides that we never died in this game
did we
no maybe we did but we were able to redo
the battle right
yeah
i always love these nice cutscenes it
gives me time to snack
i love games to have a good voiceover
jj corruption
[Music]
oh thank you
oh wait it's not for me i thought he was
talking too much why do i now get in
youtube
you crazy [\h__\h]
no need for you guys to get up
oh
no yeah
is that like his crew
no
i came to see you
i'm trying to prove my love to you
oh
[Music]
foreign
um
cigarette
titty
oh thank you
[Music]
be
wait
he said
i find this interesting
talks about yo somebody with in a white
suit took
makoto away isn't there a chance because
everybody knows kiryu as well that
nishitani would misunderstand it um that
kilio took makoto away which is
partially true anyway
and then maybe he um thinks oh that must
have been kirill so i'm gonna let majima
find kiryu but then majima meets kitty
and he's like
that's not him that's not the guy he
wears a white suit but that's not the
guy that i mean it's a different guy
okay here's a that's that's a different
uh
different uh
um route that we could go but the game
is probably not gonna take us there
i don't know
but it wouldn't have been funny
maybe
it would have been a reason to make the
two people mean
from both sides
nishitani doesn't know kenya
i feel like they all know
the
don't
don't don't you dare use the floor as
your ashtray guys gotta keep the cells
clean
you're not a big guy i feel like in
tokyo in tokyo he was well known
all right okay i take it back okay
[Music]
m
foreign
[Music]
uh which style should i go for
i last time i think i thought him in
breaker style but
my slugger style is the strongest right
now i think
oh holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
good start
there we go on your knees nishitani i
know you like it but you're not supposed
to enjoy it
[Music]
oh
get up
[Music]
nice move what is that that's funny
that was fun though
i know i know what that is you can't get
me with that no no no no no
we good
[Music]
get that combo in break it boys
once he's on the floor she'll hit him as
much as possible now wait until he's
done
with his funny moves
[Music]
remember the buttons remember the
buttons remember the buttons
[Music]
i'm not playing with you
um
do i need a heel
now i need the heel now i need to heal
up
[Music]
now i need a heel
oh god
no no
stop it
damn it
[Music]
he's wasting my heat
closer get closer get
[Music]
he closer on doing that
no come on
no
let me try this
the dance legends we dancing
it's a dance battle come on come on
[Music]
okay
he's annoying
oh
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes
now
[Music]
i hate that i hate that
oh my god
it's a slow annoying battle but we
almost got him
gone
yeah my thug isn't very uh upgraded
stop it don't fall in love with me
[Laughter]
did you just say
um
foreign
[Music]
m
then we
foreign
you just want to be close to me
and get some accidental cycles
um
she will probably get hurt after
[Music]
legendary hero are you [\h__\h]
spoilering you better not be spoiling
this
that better not be a spoiler
if that's a spoiler
then
you gotta leave
that's not cool
trying to enjoy the game here
hmm
foreign
um
if it wasn't a spoiler and just a joke
then it's okay but i don't know what a
spoiler is in this case because i don't
know what the story goes like
[Music]
is
me
i was just about to say he needs more
body movements when he talks like that
you're just gonna walk out like that
aren't you
then we gotta break the door i guess
just
open it
[Music]
oh
he's probably pissed he doesn't want to
do this anymore
guys
you're bad at aiming dude
is the stomach better than the heart
a heart should be it no congenital well
this is probably also pretty damn
bad
um
[Music]
oh
yeah cuz that to be a little bit too
nebula though
making it so dramatic
[Music]
revive
hey
[Music]
forgive me
yo there is no more bullets in your gun
[Music]
what is happening how does he even have
still power to stand
oh
chapter 11 is done
oh dear
that's quite some money
but i told you i didn't need to save i'm
fine
oh man
oh man cheer willpower
now
yeah i was i was starting to like
nishitani is funny
chapter 12 then of desires
my forehead hurts from frowning
can someone make me stop frowning when
i'm sad
headhurt
chill your eyebrows
[Music]
foreign
like he doesn't have any real fighting
skills
payback [\h__\h] i want [\h__\h] payback
um
he just loves me
now he's dead
um
there must be a place where
a lot of
um
abused girls are being brought to you
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you okay
[\h__\h] you
i want to bonk into you
i can't
there you go
already kind of saved
how's my inventory looking oh wait i can
buy abilities again
all right let's spend some money
let's do this
and let's do
this
let's do
and i think i'll keep the rest
mm-hmm
cabaret
we've already spent so much time on
inside stuff
big mission coming
[Music]
really big long mission
but even if we do the the game then it
will probably
not get me more than 10 million or so
can't get healing item during it be
prepared oh
let me find you let me find you
what are you talking about meaning money
how did you know
how oh how did you know i'm on fire i'm
on fire
no more of that no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
uh what should i do i mean i should
definitely fill up my inventory with
items i get that
what is that by the way telephone card
um
we have some extra um weapons so that's
good
um
i mean i guess we could do around
one round in the sunshine get some armor
um yeah
uh
and where was that in the pawn shop or
okay
i think you guys told me it's in the
pawn shop
shut up
[\h__\h] you
no i'm not listening to you
you're the worst person on this whole
wide earth
really disgusting
wait uh should we go to uh which one for
sunshine first
reminds me i need to go to the pawn shop
i wonder how much money i need though
sunshine
around us for style if you're interested
but this is sort of end game territory
i'm in endgame territory
should i go to the
pawn shop now
i'll take this first i need money
we need money
we need money money money
uh how's it looking like
i'm gonna do a quick special training
session because i have to
we gotta continue the yukidon story
[Music]
previously that it's cold
looking cute
what's up the giggles i'm trying to talk
to you like a customer wouldn't
i need some healing right now my um my
new friend just died man
at least they're doing okay when it's me
we are practicing with oh
honestly
that's good
good to hear that your job should be fun
um i seem to recall he always was bonsai
i remember
i've been listening to you
that's a big one
of course i remember
wow
that's professional
you practically practically got a case
file on your customers i have that too
next question
wait what
the clubs can come quite a long way
hasn't it and you've been here since the
beginning to see it all change
them
remember when this place had three girls
in it including you
so tell me something why is a girl like
you working in a club like this anyway
didn't we talk about this before
last time i said climbed up just like
this maybe it's time you cleared the air
oh
uh
please burn my case file no no no no
no no no no i got it all
several copies of it too
in this day and age companies are
practically hiring bums off the street
and you couldn't get a bite
what did you even
can i see
girls like this if they are done with
this and want to do a different job what
are they going gonna write on their
resume
because i i have i have the same problem
man
um
[Music]
were clueless honesty is a talent
what should i
public relations social relations which
one should i
do ah
they both sound good
but probably there is one that's extra
good
honesty
coolest
circle
honesty clueless which one don't you
know
honesty
i'd say being unable to tell is actually
a pretty positive quality yukichan yeah
like me in the job injury or or
um in the
in the health inspection
for the flight attendant job
i was also too honest
and therefore didn't get the job after
all
look around dad's the times we're living
everybody's dressed to the nines and
lies in vanity trying to one up the
competition but you don't do that you
just put yourself out there the way you
are honest almost to a fault
i want to work with people i can believe
and i'd hire an awkward girl who can't
tell a lie over a bunch of smooth
talking
suck cubie any day of the week
the other one might have been
um
if we have two more questions then we
might get maximum if we do it right
i'm glad i got rejected too if you
weren't here at the club who knows what
would have happened
[Music]
no
if you could get a normal day job now
would you still want to do that instead
of the cabaret club
that's really depressing toodle
from what i've seen in japan office jobs
are mostly really depressing
and you don't even make much money so
hmm
[Music]
triangle maybe
i
i guess you could network i guess
triangle i think i would prob probably
that's like the other ones are kinda
um
or a circle
i'll do
circle
but that sounds so weird i will work you
hard that sounds like
it needs some some better phrasing to be
done
triangle good advice
yeah [\h__\h] it i'll go with my gut
you never know one of your clients could
turn out to be a corporate manager
if he likes yeah he might offer you a
job right here on the spot
you know what better not accept a job
like that because if he comes here and
then gives you tries to give you a job
he probably just wants you to be
uh closer to him at like in his everyday
life as well
in the office
so just that he can always look at you
and maybe grab your butt every once in a
while so i have a bad feeling about it
i have a bad feeling
forget that story it's a forget forget
about it forget about it don't do it
[Music]
on her first day at a shady bar
did we not get
nothing nothing from that not even a
little bit
was that the worst dancer
you gotta get sexier would have been
better or what what or was there two
wrong answers
oh yeah
what you're getting enough sleep at
night you get down
two good answers and one one of them
being even better than the other
and one answer that doesn't give you
anything
oh sexy would have made you lose hot oh
okay we never had that happen before so
i didn't even know it exists ah
eh unexpected guest
is it a cat for the window
circle sounds like a
tsundere like like majima is jealous or
something
a lady needs sleep
nothing nothing just get your beauty
sleep you could tell
[Applause]
bad for the skin double bad if you fall
asleep on the job
okay okay we got a little bit
a little bit extra
nothing wrong with going out for a night
in the town just don't overdo it
it's just she's not going to tell us
probably just a cat or a cockroach or
something like that
sleep because there was a cockroach
running around in the apartment i get
that understandable relatable
normal lesson okay
wow
all right is everybody feeling okay no
your kitchen is not feeling good and
yuki
baby
okay wait uh
uh i'll hear this one should i still
bring her in
[Music]
i replace her
let her rest
okay
then our lineup is looking a little bit
weak
okay
we'll be fine we'll be fine
open for business can we go
nowhere else okay so mars
let's go
i know how to do this now
[Music]
let's go
[Applause]
make some money money money
[Music]
he really likes her
which girl is your favorite guys huh
and why is
[Music]
what
oh you get like more recovery if i get
it really early before the game tells me
oh that was ice i think yeah
okay okay okay okay okay okay
good job
[Music]
okay we got a good girl for you as well
i'm learning i'm learning i'm learning
[Music]
hi
oh [\h__\h] uh yeah oh sorry
go with
akina
[Music]
can't get distracted in this game for
even a second
[Music]
short session ah okay
uh
that
is ice
[Music]
i'll give her a reward
and check over here on this side too
oh
akina deserves a reward yeah yeah yeah
bgm is so good but no it's already over
help help help what is it
oh
that is ashtray
because i've never seen it before
okay
[Music]
man i still remember the first session
was so chaotic but i
i grasped it rather quickly i would say
oh that is
ladies
[Music]
that is that is ice
ah they're all bad okay
[Music]
sorry to work your butt off so much
oh okay
she helped me
[Music]
because the other one wanted the long
one this one was the short one damn it
[Music]
um another one and then we're so popular
does this ever get even more stressful i
wonder
can we get more tables
[Music]
it gets faster later on no more tables
but more customers okay
that's okay
i have some
headspace right now yo you gotta know
you guys
[Music]
oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
baking bank making bank making making
making bank making bank making ban
making making making banks
[Music]
i'll offer it just just because
okay 5.3 million
our best girl wasn't even here today so
that's that's okay that's okay
[Music]
all right
you can fever doing fever what
what
yes another round we're doing this
forever today
ah
sorry guys i hope it's not too boring um
should we still talk to
our girl yuki-chan
i guess yeah
date
let's change things up and practice a
date for a customer
you have that kind of service
wait why does she she's not styled up
she's not wearing the hairstyle i got
her what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
is that a bug
sometimes you go on dates with customers
then come into the club together you got
to be able to have a good time so today
we're going to practice with kinda okay
well i'm i'm in for that but why does
she look so different
i guess because she's off work
she goes to the default yeah
[Music]
she better make herself pretty for me
now for the date
she didn't
unbelievable
three times shine i'll feel awkward
singing in front of people so i'd really
help it would really help if you chant
into
uh
is this like the other karaoke games
make
okay
[Music]
can i handle lively interjections i'll
try
it
that's why it's sunshine
go
go go
hi
[Music]
hey
hi
[Music]
oh my god
hey
[Music]
she's cute i could barely focus on the
back
that was tough but but the fact that we
got the cutscene means that we must have
reached a certain minimum
she did she did
it's because you help me it will come my
stage ride would you mind singing next
to me
hell yeah baby
i'll show you what a true idol is
24 hour cinderella baby
best song
so now
[Music]
oh
yes
[Music]
going pretty well so far
hi
[Music]
me
i mean
i mean you must give me a better rating
than bozo for that one
you better 87
i tried my best i got some combos in the
first half of the song i think mm-hmm i
went without a mistake for quite some
time but then i [\h__\h] up
thank you
[Music]
do we still have to talk
oh it comes with a good lesson
[Music]
that was fun that was worth it
all right level 13 almost 14.
and we got some
some nice kadaoka i missed karaoke in
this game
not too shabby she says you're a pro
right thank you
yeah
oh i sang
i sang
songs before
but yeah we gotta sing more at some
point all right let's change the lineup
uh
wait wrong one one uh here
uh switch this one out
there we go so it's just one out
there we go
no wait that was the wrong one
let's switch this one out
we have
no one left uh should i just kick her
out completely or should i just keep her
in the lineup
or
[Music]
i guess i should just remove her
completely both of them
yeah
should be okay
we should be fine
need even more girls yeah
it's gonna drop the extras
[Music]
is looking fabulous again
i would like to get some rich people
there we go
please tell me you like yuki johnny yes
okay okay
[Music]
thank you finally someone who's not poor
i was waiting for this chance
rad all right all right another average
one on it
oh he doesn't like the girls though
[Music]
that's too bad that's too bad
well you got to deal with it
it's not my fault
not my fault
party
okay
enjoy
[Music]
oh a fourth one coming in
uh he doesn't like the girls either
[Music]
yuki-chan
look he's like a prince going down on
the knees
so politely
she's like get out of here i'm busy
i'm running out of girls now what the
[\h__\h]
so much for uh what was that so much for
only getting free tables you have it
some people need to leave now um
okay that's good that's good wait what
was that what was that i saw something
happening
[Music]
that's what it was
okay
i mean actually that's better for me
because i might need her now
long session prefers funny
okay
sorry you gotta continue working
[Music]
please
menu
[Music]
okay okay i'm such a busy manager
another one
[Music]
please go
let's go
[Music]
the timing is good like when someone new
comes and that's when they want uh
uh to leave thankfully
[Music]
give her a reward so she's ready for the
next guy
[Music]
wait one second
i have to give him someone he doesn't
like
um
sorry
[Music]
but you're still gonna pay right
okay good good good maybe we can switch
someone out
yeah
yeah yeah
[Applause]
oh another
[Music]
here we one there we go there we go
let's see if we can switch
[Music]
this is a bit better
okay
[Music]
keep that paper
going look at that bar at the at the
bottom of the money bar
[Music]
thank you yukitan you're the best
oh okay favor is over
[Music]
club sales have reached 10 million
sorry
maybe it was like latest glass huh
damn it
[Music]
what does the ashtray look like damn it
what is that what
[Music]
index fingers and thumbs
okay
yes
that's pretty damn good oh rank e
trophy talk about town i earned a trophy
that's some good management
see this is me um training to become a
future whole life manager
uh
from club mars area
hi so we can move on to another area
not yet
um
is it the girl
wait the sound is weird
let's check it out what's happening
oh there she is
your eye for me those clubs
i'm gonna scare you out of all right
money that asshole's club you're gonna
do something about it
what can i really do i mean if you're
going to play okay oh yeah play play
play you've got the pain
shut my wife took the kids and left me
because of that damn club you're part of
the problem yeah
no
no no no no doesn't work like that
if you're alive laughing with the kids
because you're going to the club then
the problem was you going to the club
not the girl who was working at the club
logical problems
okay we're gonna save her by bringing
her to our club
let me let me get her she'll be happy
with me cause i'm gonna give her a new
look
she's gonna be so inspired because i'm
saving her now
he's gonna be like ah that guy
he's so cool
[Music]
yeah
i like to call that move
eternal beating
[Music]
certified
batman
that was underwhelming
no maji masan you're just too strong but
why did you
why was all that noise what on earth
happened
who are these people have you been
beating people up again majima song
why'd you always gonna assume it's me
i'm guilty as charged in santo these
bozos were making a racket in front of
the club so i figured i'd do something
about it
huh you beat them up just for that much
my son you can be such a monster
i was trying to impress this girl
no no that's not true
she said me
leave you who might you be [\h__\h]
happy birthday alain yoshida happy
birthday happy birthday happy birthday
congratulations
celebrate yourself
what are we going to do majima son she's
from club mars
calm down we're gonna hire her
you knew and you still helped her what
if she's an enemy spy and this is all
for her plot
no no chill
chew yuki
all right i had a message from hinosan
for you
i've allowed you to exist out of the
kindness of my heart until now but i
grew tired of your buzzing in seconds if
you're challenging the five stars there
will be no mercy it's high time i
destroyed you let the tears of defeat
begin to fall
that is so true and evil
that's the message
ain't that classy i guess that's his
declaration for fine if he's got a death
wish i'd be happy to grant it
that sounds great watching my son let's
show he know that we won't bow down to
the five stars
okay
what's the matter you get down you're
shivering are you scared
i'm just [\h__\h] cold let me go back
inside
that's not what i'm doing
that's so great
what are you laughing at you're making
fun of me
oh no i'm sorry i don't know it's just
fun
it's fun like
yeah everyone in the club sunshine
actually gets along with each other
you think so we don't get along at all
actually i hate this guy
it's a nice change of pace from where i
work it's all
all the girls at club mars are wound up
tight and hinosan doesn't really treat
us like people
the way you free talk to each other i'm
really jealous
there's nothing to be jealous about
majima makes fun of me all the time yo
girl you are way ruder to me than i am
to you
way more
she's been saying so many mean things to
me i want to call my mom about it
um
she's thinking about joining us join the
revolution
right
why did you help me even though you knew
i was your enemy you know my enemy the
club is my enemy exactly
yes
that's what i'm saying you and me were
just one of a kind man mind your mom
your mom
besides i ain't jaded enough to let a
girl get attacked right in front of me
just twiddle my thumbs
i see
maji masana truly wish you the best help
for me again
she wishes as well i guess so that's why
she's number one at club mars she's cute
i wish she was my daughter
oh okay
that's right maple leaf that's right
my eyes sparkle too see look
i'm getting a new girl who doesn't make
fun of me but looks up to me instead
so do we have to go and fight him
wait how do we fight hinosan are we not
gonna fight him
i guess we'll just run the camera right
club one more time
one more down one more time one more
time since we're already here like what
the [\h__\h]
this is gonna be a long stream man
i guess we're not reading super chats
because it's just gonna be that long
because i want to finish the chapter too
[Music]
it's happening soon enough okay
wait you said 17 chapters or 18 sorry
i'm asking it again and right now we're
in the in the 12th
oh no we're in the 13th chapter i think
so that means
next one
uh 1415 is gonna be
gideo
and then
but didn't you guys say i could switch
maybe i'll maybe now we're gonna be
switching soon
we're getting so close to the ending
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
would be a long one
17 is both only in chapter 17 i can
switch oh okay
after the story is complete oh can i
still do some stuff after the story but
you know that like what what am i doing
it for in that case
[Music]
i skipped a lot of side stuff yeah but
like
[Music]
it's okay
for me it's okay
uh
yeah
there's more makeover stuff but yuki
looks perfect the way she is now and i
don't want to waste any money now
unless there's a new girl that i can
dress up
um
and we already got her a lot of
expensive things previously
but okay let's do special training
wait dancing
did i see a dancing icon
are we going dancing we're going to the
disco they're forcing me to go to the
disco
[Music]
they
she doesn't care which one
i don't want to risk it too much
it's been a while
[Music]
ah whatever let's do it
i have to win
against her
oh god
[Applause]
[Music]
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god oh
god oh god
[Music]
i don't remember
she's probably bad at dancing anyway
isn't she
[Music]
wait how do i activate it
[Applause]
[Music]
is
i lost my focus
[Music]
[Applause]
that was
uh normal lesson
of it oh well at least i won against you
[Music]
oh my god
okay let's look at our cast
wow
switch out
these ones
and
uh she works and
the silver girl
yeah
perfect
everybody is in a pretty good mood
and
yeah
i think we can open for business one
last time
one last time
[Music]
can we drink
yes
[Music]
uh with good deep pockets
towel is easy
[Music]
let me try to
tell you a story while i'm at it uh
[Music]
yeah
you may have seen the pre-chat but my
doctor's visit
went
okay
it could have definitely been better
because first of all
i was ubering
and i would have been there on time
[Music]
uh
that i was like kind of like on a on a
time pressure
but we would have been there on time
but then suddenly he makes a turn into a
side alley
thinking that
it would help maybe which wasn't even
necessary
oh there ah that's not
[Music]
good the moment the moment he turned
into the side alley
uh there was a huge
trash truck
somewhere in the front so it was
um
not good
we were stuck there for like 10 [\h__\h]
minutes which ended up in me being
late to my appointment first of all
which
i was the moment i got out of the car i
ran like
insane like
i ran
to the to the building and then i ran up
the stairs
and i i got a [\h__\h] asthma attack
and then i
in in
while breathing like this
[Laughter]
i apologize a million times to the
reception people
and i also apologized a million times to
the doctor once i walked into her office
and i understand that she would
first tell me you know
we
not good
we don't like people being late
but it was more than that she was like
really
oh [\h__\h] i should have done enough we
wanted a short session anyway
okay
she was like really really aggressively
telling me like
here you can't do it kind of stuff we're
gonna kick people out immediately i was
so close to kicking you out
i was about to go down and tell them to
kick you out and all that so you must
remember and she repeated herself
several times i kept saying i'm sorry
sir i know i know normally i'm not late
like i'm so sorry
[Music]
but she kept on complaining and
complaining and complaining and and and
yeah being mad at me
yeah
i already fought and she she 100 notice
that i was out of breath and i was like
really
i was still breathing like
still at this point
yeah but she was really mad and at some
point she finally stopped um
at some point she finally stopped but
but then um yeah she started asking me
what my problem is so i gave her some
documents that i had and i started
explaining while she was asking
questions and i i tried really to give
really clear and short answers um
because i know how doctors are at this
point
um
but i was still having a little bit of
problems breathing
and
um
i was still having some problems
breathing and and
therefore my answers were kind of like
um i guess
they sounded
like i was uh what's the right word
excited in a bad way i was kind of like
sounding
i don't know upset no not upset but
[Music]
on edge maybe
and
but still i was still getting correct
clear obvious answers agitated yeah
maybe i sounded agitated
but but not really i don't know i
thought i was
being fine and
i was doing my best okay to
give her
clear answers
i was just stressed out and then
and then she suddenly
snaps and she
like she asked me this question
she asked um right now the time is not
running right we're fine right i don't
see that
just in case let me do this
um she asks me
so
uh
is your pain stronger in the morning or
in the evening or or yeah when is it
stronger when is it the strongest and i
said
it's
always the same i just said
yeah oh it's always the same
and then
and then she snaps at me
she says
[Music]
she said excuse me quinoa we need some
serious energy i need you to take this
seriously i don't have time for like
unclear answers i need you to give me
clear answers and also calm the hell
down like okay she didn't say the hell
but she was like really aggressively
telling me to calm down
and to give her clear answers and
because she doesn't have time for this
and i'm like
and that's the moment where i start
getting tears in my eyes because i'm
like it's the truth it's the [\h__\h]
truth this is why i hate these people i
just said the truth and i gave you a
clear short answer and actually i was in
the middle of continuing and explaining
um that i'm always in pain but um
i um like the the time of the day
doesn't matter but i feel even more pain
when i'm trying to sit still or whatever
but she like stop stop before talking
she interrupted me
um
yeah so and then got really mad at me
and she kept on going and going and
going and i was trying really hard not
to start crying
i had tears in my eyes but i tried to
for the next couple of minutes i tried
to control myself really
yeah um
but she was not
not cool
[Music]
i don't
get it i apologized a million times i
was out of breath i was trying myself my
best to get clear answers and i was just
saying saying the truth she might have
thought that i was exaggerating when i
say always but i'm not lying it's the
truth it's always
it's always
[Music]
i don't know what to tell you women
i don't know what to tell you afterwards
after a while of talking and talking and
talking
um
because i was really scared to piss her
off again i got i i
we both calmed down i guess and it was
fine in the end but
i don't understand what i did
to
um
be talked at like that i honestly don't
think i did anything wrong besides being
late but we um
cleared that in the beginning of the
session so
um
okay
[Music]
anyway
yeah she um
was a female doctor at least she then um
um
started prescribing me a bunch of like
things which i'm also like kind of like
not so
excited about but i'll tell you later
um
all kinds of all kinds of therapy
sessions like different ones but
i told her that i just got out of a
physical therapy
uh like last month
but uh
she basically is prescribing me two
extra physical therapies
one no fairly normal one but not
one-on-one like i had before this one
will be like in a group which i'm not so
excited about but okay
um and will be
done in two weeks though because i'll be
going there
i think four times a week or so
[Music]
and then after that
uh
i have to do
a different
therapy
which is not quite physical therapy
but more like
um i don't know what the name for it is
in in english
but yeah i could cancel them but i won't
really be
doing much with that doctor anyway
anymore it's okay it's okay i'm gonna go
there um yeah it's like uh
like they're gonna combine things like
uh
um
physio physical stuff and and psychic
stuff
um
uh
no not psychic but psychological
wait what's up
uh
ah that was the name
[Music]
that was the name um is there no english
name for this
[Music]
there's a wikipedia page but there's no
english page for it
multi
module pain therapy
something like that
uh
[Music]
which is
basically
a physiotherapy and psychological
like
mix
with
movement and and
[Music]
i don't know
relaxing technique
techniques and
medical treatment as well
which um she
also prescribed me because of the
mention that
i have fibromyalgia although we both
agreed on this one at least that five
like someone saying i have fibromyalgia
is pretty [\h__\h] because that's like a
um
um something you
assess when you don't know what else the
patient could have
um we agreed on this one
um
but yeah this one however
that will be a long therapy
um first originally she said like
there's two options like one option is
me going there um
like like a rehability i'll be there
uh
every day
the whole day from morning to night time
i think i wouldn't be sleeping there i
think that's what she was saying she
didn't mention that but it would be the
whole day
um for like two weeks or something i
think but i said i can't do that
i can't do that and then there's another
option where i can kind of
um
do it over the course of
more weeks but uh
not be there all day
yeah it sounds super excessive and i was
like a bit like what
what
um
this is sounding like a
pretty big commitment
but okay
um
no
yeah i i still have to do
i i'm basically i am getting a second
opinion because
the way the way they work there they
need me to also
have
um
an interview with the
psychological doctor
person
um and then she said that the final
decision on how they're treating me
is on that person
so she's gonna assess my pain in a
psychological way oh i'm so excited that
she's gonna tell me i have daddy issues
yeah yeah that's that's why it's a
multi-module
like uh they combine several
fields um several
tech techniques
yeah
yeah i can still turn it down
um
if i want to but yeah um i'm gonna
definitely i guess
do that stupid physiotherapy again i
don't honestly
at this point
i feel like the other therapy okay uh
that makes more sense because it's not a
physical therapy it's something else but
i literally just came out of physical
therapy and i know that
everything they're gonna teach me there
i've been to physical therapy a million
times now everything they're gonna teach
me there is the same things that i've
already learned somewhere else they all
do the same [\h__\h] they all the same [\h__\h]
there and this is not even one-on-one
this is not even a one-on-one session so
it makes me feel uncomfortable
i don't
i don't really want to turn it down
because
it's kind of connected with the other
thing
uh because i got the blood test a while
ago right and um
and i didn't get it yet i didn't get the
results yet but that lady over there
for the
um
room romantic
thingy they want to figure out if i have
that
dad illness
uh they were like you gotta go there
while you wait for the
results of the blood test and because we
can't give you an early appointment
anyway
so you make an appointment over there
and then like months later you're gonna
come back to us
with the results of what you did in that
therapy over there
uh
well you know they are basically they
they need me to go there and do all of
that [\h__\h] just in case
that it wasn't
very much
[Music]
i don't know how to pronounce it
because that saves time and that i guess
makes sense in case it wasn't that i
would have already started doing therapy
in for for the pain
uh
somewhere else
kind of like
i'm trying to kill two birds with one
stone
um
because i got a back got i got to go
back to the first place
sometime in june or something because
they couldn't give me an early
appointment
roy matic
[Music]
i don't know which one there's a million
types of romantic
illnesses diseases
and
they were are testing my blood on that
and other things but they
didn't send me any results yet
anyway
and there's so many
so many things now so many
i i'm gonna do it but i just don't think
that that the two-week physical therapy
is gonna do anything because i'm doing
that stuff at home anyway
it's not gonna make a difference
but okay i guess while i'm waiting for
the other therapy to start i guess i'll
do that it just will make me even busier
than i'm than i already am
yeah
but then if i cancel that one and then
but still go to the others then maybe
the doctors will be like well
well you didn't go to the
to the physical therapy so
of course it won't have such a great
effect you don't you didn't even try
um
i don't want to be like
no
i don't want them to be like smarty
pants on me
yeah
no
i don't know
yeah i'll i'll think about it i have to
go first to that
psychological assessment anyway first
that comes first anyway so
no
i can honestly with confidence tell you
that they're just gonna teach me the
same [\h__\h] that i already learned a
million times so
really it's just on me doing it at home
it's
it will not make a difference if i go to
their therapy
it will just waste my time basically and
be stressful for me
[Music]
physical therapy is all the same they
all do the same [\h__\h]
but okay maybe i can go to one session
and then if i say if i figure out oh
it's the same [\h__\h] then i don't go to
the to the other sessions maybe
i don't know
anyway
but what are we doing
here
that was
an urgent tangent
[Music]
urgent tangent
and the pgm wasn't very suitable
[Music]
for
oh favorite time is over oh no
[Music]
but you don't want to pay much
okay
finally i got that one right
[Music]
that sounds like a you problem
sorry almost almost missed it
astray aspirin
short sessions actually extend more what
does that mean i tried extending short
ones they never say yeah
[Music]
that's right everyone everybody wants to
ask her it's really stinky in here
stinks like cigarettes
[Music]
no i i understand the doctor was pissed
at first
but then later the way she snapped was
so unnecessary
[Music]
i tried
because i was 100
i swear to god i was getting clear
answers and i was giving
them actually besides me being a little
bit out of breath besides that i was
giving them calmly and clearly
i don't know what a [\h__\h] problem
i was being nice and polite as
[Music]
well you guys i agree i was rude
okay
[Music]
well we're back up to 30 million
so you guys told me
that
in the next section
i won't be able to buy items
for a while
right
so i'm gonna fill up my inventory and
then upgrade with the money that i have
or should i keep the money
i will definitely fill up my inventory
though should i should i
keep some money though for some reason
so i don't regret it later
upgrade and buy healing okay okay
having a bad day taking it out on me
i don't even think it's that
in my opinion
doctors are just
always like that at this point like
they don't listen
they don't let me talk
they interrupt me
now
sucks
my last physical therapist was really
great um
yeah
i liked her
and thanks to it being a one-on-one
session that was also way way way less
stressful because the previous physical
therapies that i had before that were
also group sessions
and
i
first of all i don't see how
that um
is better than a one-on-one session like
a one-on-one session is always better
because you can focus on on the person
and
yeah their individual problems
on that day especially
so
if it was another one-on-one session i i
may i may be more
positively thinking about it but
in this case
hmm
[Music]
is it a cosplay no it's just
um it depends on the
institution it depends on the
the
their whatever they are offering and and
what's available
or what they think is necessary for that
patient but sometimes they don't just
don't have one-on-one sessions and
sometimes they just don't have group
sessions
or whatever um
[Music]
oh the one thing though
that
um she i generally think she took my
pain seriously she just was rude and
didn't listen to me but also like uh
um i did bring up my asthma because for
some reason it was like uh
it made sense for some question that she
asked me
and um
she asked me like if who
if i have that diagnose and i said no
because
the doctor so far didn't care about it
and she was like okay okay okay uh
remind me that at the end of the session
that i'm gonna i have to uh prescribe
you or not prescribe you send you to
like give you one of those things to
send you to uh
um
to a
long
professional list doctor thingy
and problem was at the end we both
forgot it
at referral
yeah
she told me to remind her and then i
forgot so we both forgot
[Laughter]
but yeah next time i'm going there for
the other the other doctor session i
i'll ask about it
um
recover
[Music]
first of all hp
ah 50 million
this is the amount the heat cost
i don't have that much ah which one
should i focus on i barely use [\h__\h] if
anything are you slugger or breaker
ah docile
post some quick stuff the heat guns will
rise when you definitely evade
a 2 million only let's go
okay
sticky notes would have been helpful
yeah
[Music]
you want everything don't be nice
doesn't always mean they're very good
too
sometimes you can smell some sour grapes
huh
yeah i mean i said i'll go back
get all the two million ones
crystal oh i still have two million ones
this is the power of the regular attacks
okay
yeah yeah
it goes will rise when you perform a
jumping flourish near an enemy
well i'll never do that i won't remember
that because there's something else
however
l one
and l
do i need to push l down
and then press
x i'm never gonna do that
this one maybe
this one i wanna do but in case i get
that one i need to get this one
l one and l
and then x
oh boy
this one i can remember
l one while moving oh i don't have to
push l down is that what they're saying
l1 and then x
i don't want an x while i'm running
while i'm running
you're asking for a lot here
we have two million ones here as well
15 million
no i don't think i do
i can't ah no i can't get this one
polaris an enemy carrying a weapon then
take the weapon from them
oh is that a heat move
an enemy weapon
dagger or bat
that's
cool that's that's good one that's a
good one
i think that one i will end up using
yokado okay
um
will get this one i think or
yeah
i will get this one after being knocked
down triangles
after i'm being knocked down triangle
seven million can i get anything with
seven million
oh wait maybe uh that one two million
unleash a surprising attack when
switching to slugger style
the moment i switch
right side from from another style 30 oh
so if i uh if i am at the third heat bar
and then switch to slugger style
because that's on the right side
then it will automatically
do a surprising attack okay
um
okay
wait when you switch
does the heat bar reset no right so what
if i'm on in slugger
and m at the third heat bar quickly
switch to something else and then
quickly switch back to slugger does that
work
but why would i do that just for this
i probably wouldn't do it on purpose
like that um but okay
um
it would work
it's not worth it yeah
okay ah there wait there's one more oh
nice nice nice nice
xl
all right number one thanks myself let's
go i didn't see these i didn't realize i
could go there
okay okay okay perfect
good we boosted our health
quite a lot
did i miss any others but now i'm down
to 1.2 million okay in that case
i'm gonna save
um
because i think i got all ah wait we
wanted to buy i want to buy armor but i
didn't i don't have any money left
[\h__\h]
you guys think i'm gonna be fine
am i gonna be okay
i'm gonna be fine
beat up mr shaytan
okay i'm stronger now does he get
stronger too i wonder he doesn't get
stronger right
i need some money quickly
this is so endless like
i need to do this i need to do that i
need to do this and i need to do that
and now
okay let's try to beat him
but
i will probably need
more healing items afterwards again as
well
you
not me
i ain't got time for side quests now
what
let's hear it and what i'm trying to say
is you like my shoes
you're my boyfriend huh
huh
you like the side story yeah dude okay
let's do it
maybe a couple yeah
i want to have a boyfriend
the heck is with this little lady went
up to a man on the street demanding that
i would be her boyfriend what the hell
i'll get it together can't let her know
she got under my skin
she got under your skin
nani
a strong answer
like don't even think you've won little
lady
i
this implies something else
though uh
sorry darling i got no interest in woman
but
that means i'm interested in fighting
could you set aside your preferences and
just be my boyfriend for today oh only
one day
yeah you left out some details i needed
to pretend to be my boyfriend not
actually be my boyfriend yeah that's
important that is important
yes you see my father is visiting from
back home and he's demanding to meet my
boyfriend
for several years now he's been hounding
me to meet swedish
sweets
sweeters
sweet sweeters sweet toys
sweet
suits it suits you suit suitors suitors
there we go he's arranged for me
took me a moment
he was getting some resistance and i
finally got fed up and told him i
already have a boyfriend so back up
suitors like hooters yeah
i also told him my boyfriend is finn
wears an eyepatch a cool point
that's me
the [\h__\h] as if she was planning it
what i am
i want you giving so many details
why did you describe me down to the
buttons
i never thought i'd have to introduce
him to my father so i just kind of made
up as i went no [\h__\h] way
she's just a
she's a fan of mine
i have to see if this boyfriend is
worthy of marrying you so here i am and
i've got a big problem
uh-huh
no problem okay let's do it
all right
what a coincidence that's totally
coincidence
we're gonna marry some guy they don't
even know and end up spending the rest
of their life with him fine you painted
yourself in this corner but i feel your
pain i'll pretend to be your boyfriend
uh my name is cocoa that's a cute name
please call me poketan uh sorry i didn't
catch your name
you and her boyfriend accept it now
let's just pretend we're in a romantic
relationship we can't be so formal with
each other
okay
okay let's go
come on jackie but we're going to the
restaurant where we meet my dad for
dinner okay
okay okay maybe she'll give me some
armor
that would be helpful
what's your dad like
probably some [\h__\h] weirdo
[Music]
let's go over my boyfriend's backstory
backstory we've been going on for six
months you are a dentist who likes going
out on drives and watching movies a
dentist that looks like that
no [\h__\h] way
your favorite food is the omr that i
make okay well that sounds realistic
i had to give my dad some details about
my boyfriend so i made up some stuff if
he gets curious can you make sure you've
got it memorized oh [\h__\h] uh
half a year
dentist
and
omar dyson that's all i remember
six months dentist drives and watching
movies or more daiso okay drives and
watching movies
okay okay
i can do this
that's your dad
looks so young
hello
hello you have such a jpeg face man
it's it's so like pasted onto your face
uh please to me is
this one um
what's it i understand my daughter looks
to you for i'm surprised she told him so
many details about me like visuals and
what i do and all that but she did not
tell him a fake name so i could keep my
own name
like wouldn't that be like one of the
first things the father would ask for
what the name of my boyfriend is
support oh no in fact that's quite the
opposite of what's understood by me at
every turn
how could courteous of you something
that gets to me these days is the
erosion of courtesy in today's view
that's why i'm going to tell them it's
not like those are stereotypical men
okay
i know that described you as a man who
was telling uh you didn't believe me i
would exist right i wouldn't believe it
either
i never imagined such a man could
actually exist yet here you are in the
flesh
see that i told you i wasn't lying my
boyfriend's right here in front of you
i figured he was another figment of your
overactive imagination so i'm actually
quite sure
yeah
don't make up things that that
i don't make up things that often do i
my line of work i'm a dentist
good job
i'm glad i remember too
i was wondering how did you come to meet
cocoa
oh [\h__\h] we didn't talk about that
well i'll just make up something then
that is
an anime answer uh well even a second on
the third one
i think the second one maybe
even though the third one is funny
free
i hear back on me dying in the
background you guys hear it
yes
[Music]
are you guys trolling me telling me to
go for number three
she likes movies she mentioned that
dummy down there
oh yeah driving and movies right okay
that's that makes sense
that's how we met i'm moving come to
think of it yeah
look look you guys are trolling me this
is the right answer
yes it makes a lot of sense
this girl might feel kind of like an
anime girl but we did not have a
ridiculous anime situation where she
runs uh for the streets with toast in
her mouth and i bump into her no that
did not happen
yes that that's how it went amazingly i
can't believe you came up with such i
mean remember it's like it was 15
minutes ago it was so romantic
mm-hmm
what is it about my daughter that you
find attractive huh
he's he wants to give me the blessing
for marriage that's what i need to ask
you about what about cook
what do you like
we didn't talk about that either
but what does that have to do with
it it is something she told me to say
but
does he mean like
but one is too simple
three is
creepy
i guess it is on my eyes
yeah you're probably gonna say it gives
her white food qualities
i must agree with your dad her omurice
still has a special quality to it i love
it too
if it's delicious delicious i want to
ask that you want you could just
i didn't like the answer
dad
tapping into coco chan's backstory
backfired from her dad's point of view
he wants a guy who appreciates his
daughter fully not just for her
yeah but wouldn't that be [\h__\h]
shallow if i said
because she's cute
that's that's so shallow that's like
nothing what the [\h__\h]
come on majima
give him a deep explanation
would you say excuse me i need to go
wash up
sure honey don't fall in it
awkward
majima kun
yes i have no idea who you really are
but thank you for playing along
does is this scripted does it
always does he always find out or is it
only because i got one question wrong
what what lie
i got no idea what you mean well i love
your daughter deeply
i'm just not pretending i knew this was
all an act from the moment i said that
okay he always knows okay
was it that obvious if you knew from the
start
because i make nice fried chicken i do
make nice fried chicken
what gave us away i could tell just by
the way my daughter was acting i wasn't
her father for all these years for
nothing i guess
coco is so desperate to convince me it's
my fault she tried stunt like this isn't
it yeah yeah you pressured her
you know your daughter well you saw it
right through her unless my wife and
coco was still an infant oh my eraser
alone oh music changed sad music
i tried to reinstate a while so no one
would look down on her for not having a
mother but i know i've been overly
protective of her i can see now that
she's capable of standing on her own two
feet i've got to stop telling my
daughter to do this or not no more
pushing her to meet potential swedish
suitors she's her own woman it's time i
learned to let her go
but the truth is there's another reason
i went along with your little cherry
someday my daughter is going to bring a
real boyfriend to meet me ah
he's practicing
thanks to you i got a good idea of what
to expect when the time comes i think
i'll manage
uh it still ain't a good feeling to
spend so much time lying to someone who
knew it from the start
but i gotta tell you i think avoiding a
an arranged marriage wasn't the only
reason kukuchan pulled this done
i think she was trying to show you that
you don't need to worry about her so
much
pretty plain to see that she's the
source of a bundle of your worries
i think she wanted to reassure you that
she's capable of looking after herself
she wanted to prove to you she can
manage her own face like getting married
welcome back
can we stop acting now
welcome back john listen your dad
actually knew ah he's still gonna
continue acting
majima kun
you've done well finding this man i had
nothing to worry about after all
i know right go to chances
so this means you'll try stop trying to
set me up yes
happy end
and i'm out of liquids
i need to get some water
after this
thank you
and now i'll see you never ever again
five pieces of floor cool
wow
[Music]
you forgot something he's going to tell
me something
there's one last thing i need to say
i'm glad i got to talk to you
you're good man yeah he is
i like it if you would be my daughter's
room
no
i have better things to do
no no no my girlfriend is going to be
makoto
no
no i'm not the ideal man
trust me
majima is not the guy you want to give
your daughter um to
because he's in so much trouble right
now and he could be dead
any
any morning you wake up he could be
lying dead somewhere on the streets
killed by someone
no no don't
no no
this is why i'm single
you'll just be really really sad
yeah
you don't want that so where the hell is
is he still there
he's not there anymore now he's
now he's there
you know young
do we really want to do is i have a
feeling it's going to be a pain in the
butt you know what i'm just going to go
i'm just gonna go
for it
um
i don't need any more money
i'll need it
no
i'm going to continue the story now it's
been
5 hours and 40 minutes
and this is gonna be a long
chapter apparently
[Music]
eh
what he said he would date me
i missed that
what
dude everybody's falling in love with me
mina majima nikoi's town
thank you
thank you gian mod it's okay
you weren't supposed to remind me i'm
supposed to remind myself
um okay
i took
um but
i'll go get water
you guys stay tuned
um
we're gonna
have to
play this a little while longer i'll be
right back i guess i'm gonna go on to an
idol meeting too
brb
guys do you mind if i made myself a
sandwich
i need to eat
the bread
today
because otherwise it's gonna be stiff
tomorrow
okay
i'll make it fast
hmm
[Music]
all right
kyoto
[Music]
huh
foreign
no poor girl
he's blind
yo cool lamb still
wow
[Music]
foreign
hmm
[Music]
hey you didn't see that coming
why does that always bonk me
is that when they block
oh when i push square a little bit too
often
whoa
you remember remember those lyrics
[Music]
oh
journey like a thousand years indeed
and this will probably feel
exactly the same
until we find muscle dog
it's gonna be a journey a thousand years
[Music]
pick up and die
the longer we went
get
anymore i haven't sung that song in a
million years
maybe i shouldn't do breaker style
because there's a lot of
[Music]
if they let me start
i need some
warm-up things you know when i dance
[Music]
i know which one is more effective
maybe not
i do enjoy break style
the
fighting style though
i do enjoy it
ah
[Music]
i gotta say
the interior design holy [\h__\h]
what a waste of a beautiful beautiful
building
turn this into a
hotel
a normal [\h__\h] hotel and i would i
would love it i would love sitting
there there's no word for us to cut your
scene
we'll make it ourselves and make
memories yay
oh god
[Music]
forever
um
i mean
i'm saying it's a waste because of the
purpose of what they're using this place
for
[Music]
let
ah
[Music]
a normal hotel
doesn't have
a million employees that can fight like
that
there's someone there with a lot of hp
cool
you
that's cool
yes
[Applause]
get down
oh he has a different mask oh [\h__\h] i
missed my chance
[Music]
travel 50 kilometers on foot
traveling running inside of battle
counts as well i didn't realize that
[Music]
and he is bigger
okay time for a
for another bite
[Music]
nice
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
wait i can use the doors as a weapon
i don't need it
i'm good
[Music]
i want to get my money's well
um i'm fighting the air don't mind me
yeah ladies
let's go
[Music]
i'll give you some time off work
by
killing you
it's called freedom
yeah reminds me because i was watching
this show right um upload
and i forgot to ask you guys i wanted to
ask you guys
if
if you were given a chance
to upload your consciousness
and therefore basically kind of live
forever or have the chance of living
forever would you do it
or would you just want a normal
normal end of life
because you might think
yes no yes yes yes no no
you might think that that's like such a
super awesome thing but not necessarily
oh they're bullying me
[Music]
and while i think upload i'm in the
second season now has some
kind of ridiculous
parts to it
um
[Music]
it shows it shows some ways how that
kind of stuff could be very corrupted
like i like how
there's like this like big internet
company horizon
which kind of controls
uh a big market of like the whole
uploading thing
and
yeah it's it's there are some [\h__\h] up
parts about it and also then there's
still like
uh
experimenting how to get someone's body
back like like a download in this case
they call it download
and while they're experimenting they're
failing and ended up killing someone
damn it
so
that's pretty
funny can you guys stop what the [\h__\h] is
the matter
need to watch the playful of so much why
do i need to watch a play-through
because i don't want to play it on
myself by myself is it a horror game
it's not a four game i feel like i heard
of it
[Music]
does it have a similar theme
one more interesting aspect
to that whole story
i think was
like
imagine that was actually possible and
there were some big companies
offering like services for that
um
i think it makes sense to imagine as it
is also the same in the show
that
um
you know it's gonna not be
necessarily something that everybody can
afford since you're not doing it for
free
so then there's all these
people who have an average
uh income
and uh or no income at all and they're
gonna be like yo this is not fair
why do these rich people only get to
get a chance for uploading
their consciousness and live forever
while we even though we work so [\h__\h]
hard
we don't get [\h__\h]
huh
and that creates a big beast
you see that coming
that creates a big
um problem issue
of course
yeah
so
there's also
like a movement
in the show
where
they're basically uh
trying to
make
an option for free to let people upload
for free
and even though it's a kind of a stupid
comedy show
it has some valid points and interesting
interesting theories to it and and not
theories but like
how how things maybe could be in the
future
also like completely automatic cars
are like pretty normal
um and everything has an ai but then the
ai kind of like bugs out so often and
and
uh then people die because
the [\h__\h] cars just don't do what
they're supposed to do someone hacks
into
a car sorry i'm kind of like spoiling
something so if you want to watch the
show maybe don't listen too closely what
i'm saying
um
yeah
by hacking the car you can like kill
someone but people are like oh ai cannot
fail so this must i don't know this
cannot be explained there's no way ai
would fail
[Music]
would i do it though
i don't need to do it i'm an eternal
phoenix so obviously yeah
you don't even need to ask me that
question
[Music]
wait one sec dude i need to take a bite
hmm
[Music]
huh is it is someone behind me though
oh then look for a second
how dare you i'll [\h__\h] you
let me heal myself
we already got some items thankfully to
fill up our inventory again very very
kind of them
what are you doing
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no [\h__\h]
no no no no no no no no
wish he could go closer but okay okay
when they're aggressive and want to
fight back
they do come closer to try to hit me
in the middle of me attacking them so
that's a bad choice for them
[Music]
in yours
all right who's next
oh item
toughness toughness
that only it fills up something
might help quite a bit i'll take that
and then i can pick up only one of the
items oh well
[Music]
there's one thing i'll at least send it
to my item box
okay
[Music]
oh
time to take a bite
makoto
um
oh
foreign
[Music]
i'm eating a sandwich but it's the last
bite
[Music]
um
that has already been proven a million
times
uh which style do you guys recommend me
for him i'm probably gonna go with this
one anyway
hit me hit me try to hit me
right
whichever [\h__\h] or slugger okay
[Music]
i'm so stupid right now but okay he's
easy
okay okay okay okay
hope you're into feet
because you'll be tasting a lot of it
today
stinky stinky imagine my feet
[Music]
little bit slower
i shouldn't be wasting so much time
because my heat runs out
good good good good good good good good
good good good good good
thank god i'm not failing those prompts
anymore holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
you need a rhythm for this man
i [\h__\h] ran him
[Music]
i think yeah we got one health bar of
him down
get up
[Music]
i'm so nice waiting for him to get up
but honestly it's just the lack of loops
that work when he's on the floor
it's not me being polite not really
[Music]
uh
this is fine
wait wait he's on his way to his
deathbed anyway okay well that was too
easy
actual
no i can't just stand next to him calmly
sometimes it doesn't even pop up when
i'm like next to him
no he attacks me
enemy
you guys scared me saying this would be
tough this place
real estate real estate
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
he might be more
useful in tokyo
what you gonna do with that give it to
me
thanks dude
for me
oh that's very dramatic
[Music]
[\h__\h]
huh
holy [\h__\h] no you're a big [\h__\h] not just
a little one
well if he's not alive anymore to
protect her then i guess i gotta go yeah
hi
oh i thought it was way longer
that did feel like the ending of it yeah
you guys made me feel like it's way
longer that was so short
oh
[Music]
you know what we will not watch
the
beginning of the next chapter we will
not watch the cutscene when watched in
the beginning of the next stream because
i feel like
uh
that will
give us a good opening to it
um
yeah
nice yeah i was just that was a walk in
the park
i want to know what happens next well
you'll have to come to the next stream
next week we'll do two two yakuza
streams next week
uh probably gonna finish the game
or i drag it out a bit more
and try to do
some more side stuff but i don't know
we'll see how i feel next time
you're doing really well with the game
thank you
yeah
i always opened pretty decent recently
i mean
more dancing yeah
um
thank you thank you guys thank you
yakuza once again has lifted my mood i'm
okay um
yeah
um it's already 10 pm though so
i don't know if we're gonna get into the
super chat reading um
uh
yeah probably not
done
there's 17 chapters i keep on forgetting
if it's 17 or 18 i think it was 17 yeah
17. um so
13 14 15 16.
it might even be smart to drag it out to
three episodes
uh
to do one episode with like
one
more side stuff and an extra chapter
and then the other episodes of two
chapters each
probably yeah i might do that yeah
yeah
i know
[Music]
i didn't do bowling yet no wait on which
side was that majima okay to you because
people told me about the bowling the
bowling the bowling the bowling and i'm
like huh where the hell can you even
bowl
um we've been already so fast i honestly
thought this would go on longer kitty
aside okay then remind me to bowl next
time if if i forget about it
remind me to bowl
yeah
okay
in tokyo
best manager in the game are for for
that investment game
not interested in the classic style
games oh i mean we can check them out um
i guess they're like probably kind of
similar to how they were in like a
dragon probably
i'm drinking some more water
i'm tired
i just joined what's going on ah we just
finished chapter 12.
after uh a long long long long
roundabout doing side stuff
you did very well at that management
then again
are you talking about the management
minigame and like a dragon cause the one
here with kirill i still don't fully
understand so you must be lying
you have to do the cult sub story ah
didn't we already start that one anyway
okay wait wait i think we started it but
we didn't continue it
yakuza seven yeah and yakuza seven one
was fine um
yeah there's a lot of side quests that i
encountered but didn't uh really
properly continue
uh
a little bit head hurt and tired uh
well six and a half hours of this game
kind of kind of drained me
but it was fun
[Music]
today
yeah
i was just saying like because someone
in the comments was talking about
a son of a guy like he doesn't look
scary but he's such a piece of [\h__\h] like
his character is so
so evil
and
like
uh
ew the way he treated majima and still
treats manchemo
is the worst i've ever seen also
including like a dragon
saga is my least favorite character now
i think
[Music]
pure evil yeah doesn't even look evil
looks like a really good guy
did i
say when we first met sagawa oh he looks
like a good guy because i said that
about a lot of people
what about kuma worse than kumar kula is
just like
a coward that's just like
pathetic a pathetic coward but sagala is
just
pure evil
for no [\h__\h] reason so far like
there's nothing that
that really
gives him any good reason to do what
he's doing
he's just evil what the [\h__\h]
um
i hate him i hate him so much
every time he shows up even though he
doesn't look scary
because he intimidates majima so much
every time i see him
gives me shivers gives me like ah my
heart stops for majimo for to say the
sake of majima my heart [\h__\h] stops
every time he shows up somewhere
and he's like
i want to protect majima
i want to protect majima who protects
makoto
um
[Music]
yeah
horrible horrible guy
and i guess
i wonder like if sagava you guys
shouldn't spoil me but i wonder if saga
was like
gonna continue
controlling majima like that and and
that he's like partially definitely
definitely partially the reason
why he ends up
being so crazy in later series
i i mean
definitely must be part of the reason
but i wonder if saga will be around much
longer to ruin
my boy much more
um okay i'm not gonna look at the chat
too closely i'm not looking i'm looking
not looking
um yeah um
will will i will i find out
like will i see
i won't see crazy majima within this
game yet right
he still
is still going to take a couple years
right until majima goes crazy becomes
the person that he
he
becomes no comment okay
i will find out
oh well i'll find out
will i find out
okay i'll not ask
[Music]
so
tomorrow is gonna be an interesting
stream from my side i still haven't had
much time to think
through it so i'm a little bit nervous
so i just have like a rough idea of what
i'm going to be doing happy
you'll be
um
don't get your hopes up too much
i'm worried i'm scared
but i'll do my best it will probably
just be a relatively short stream an
hour or so
and
so
uh please come and check it out uh
because i prepared something special and
then later on in the middle of the night
we'll have
um a stream on gooda's channel gorda has
been preparing a lot for it
um
yeah she's been really really excited
and had some a lot of different ideas
so
it should be fun i'm i'm i i've been
leaning back and letting guda do her
thing
uh that i don't have to do a thing
thankfully um i think she will take the
lead
during that stream so i'm just gonna
chill and let it happen
yeah i i've
seen some of the things that she's been
preparing but i don't know everything so
i'm excited to see
what she's been working on yeah she's
really excited about it really motivated
i've never seen her so on top of
something before
yeah because this is really something
that she's been
focused on
normally normally she's not this like
super super on top of something
super chats super chats i don't even
know if i can if i will read them
tomorrow
worst case ah
i think um i i will be able
i know it's gonna be unarchived uh i'll
probably read them on monday yeah i'm
sorry
i might do a
depending on how much it is i might do a
super chat reading stream
uh otherwise i'll just um add it onto
something else
yeah let's uh save the game
don't don't look at anything
a german eight times a high-end
streaming color
save data
save it
yeah
oh no i was going to take monday off i
think sneeze sneezing coming no no no no
no no
no
no no no no no we're not going to look
at this
i am curious but
as long as i don't even see a second of
it i can handle with uh okay i can
handle not looking at it once i see one
second of it i want to see the whole
thing
thank you guys bless you too bless all
of you and let me bonk you let me bonk
you
come here ted come here chad
you ready you ready
book
a book
how does it feel
huh it should feel good it's like a
massage
oh i don't die what no
come back
knob
reverse mirrors have you erased it guys
i know with you
you're feeling better now sorry i
thought that would feel better
uh
i can help you
should be okay now
revive revive
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you guys um watching for so long
for six and a half hours thank you very
much i appreciate it and
sorry for the rent uh in between and um
i'm good though i'll do i'll do the
thing i'll go i'll go to the doctor
don't worry about it um
yeah um
i'm gonna go
chill a little bit and then eat food and
then sleep and then
wake up and then prepare the stream
but i still gotta i gotta make the
thumbnail before
yeah
should i spoiler what it is in the
thumbnail i would make it more
interesting
if i if i do show what it is but if i
don't show that maybe it's also more
mysterious i don't know
[Music]
i'll i'll i'll have spoiler it
[Laughter]
don't spoil censor don't show it keep it
secret keep it for surprise okay i'll
i'll partially i'll partially
show what it is partially partially
and then maybe make a second
thumbnail for later to switch it up
maybe
okay
please watch tomorrow
and in german we say
um
say it say it say it
auf wiedersehen
yes that's right thank you guys
it was fun today
we got a lot of things done i think
um
yeah
thank you
for watching love you guys
thank you thank you thank you
yes
bye
[Music]
do
wait guys
should i show you that
mommy sent me something
[Music]
ah should i unlock
i'ma jump in my body
[Music]
wow
i'll show you
[Music]
ah
just just a little bit
i think
no it's not the thing for tomorrow
[Music]
wait one second
one second
[Music]
oh
okay
only a little bit
this is uh um just
totally me um
[Music]
right
ready
oh
[Music]
okay
that's all you're gonna get
[Music]
wow
that's with the suit
[Music]
i'm gonna
we're gonna get that too
it's gonna take a while but i'm gonna
get it and then we can do streams like
this from home
show it again
okay
[Music]
ignore the ears
cute
i like the pose
[Music]
thanks america