[Music]
[Applause]
five five
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
Hickory King
okay muted we just started and I just
unmuted it what are you talking about
what are you talking about
[Music]
literally one the second the second I
what
[Music]
did you just wake up well more or less I
mean I had breakfast
and but I woke up really late and then I
wanted to cuddle whips movie because she
was being really cute
and then I almost fell asleep but I
didn't
I almost fell asleep but we she was so
soft
and I was like she was sleeping when I
had my hand on her belly
her family
[Music]
we would have understood thank you I
wish I could have just slept right there
you thought this is a pizza stream what
are you talking about you're so confused
a nice relaxing Sunday yeah I'm in a
blanket now even
oh
[Music]
blanket Wawa
uh
[Music]
no
no I don't have an energy drink today we
can't let that be a normal thing after
all
I'm good
microphone why is there so much hair on
you huh
why is there so much on you
with you on you
foreign
[Music]
no not funny that's not funny
that's not funny what's so really cute
not funny
yeah yeah it's okay let's cover up but
it's so cool
her legs look funny
with those huge boots
uh this is funny
but um
still very
mmm showing
showing us the goodies
oh man
but that choker is covering up
the
corridor
perfectly for some reason
no matter how much you move
it's covering up the corridor
the vine corridor
uh it's funny though I like the weapon
too although I saw someone on Twitter
drawing how like it makes absolutely no
sense because it's a shotgun
apparently and if you try to shoot with
it normally you hold it with two hands
and you will cut yourself because
there's a knife for the bottom of it
it's very impractical it's just for
style points uh
but but but but
yeah it's a cool outfit
but that's her default hair right I
compared it
it looks like her default hair to be
it's nice though don't always need a new
hairstyle
sometimes default hair is just fine
I didn't even think about that like oh
new outfit I should take the chance for
it for new hair one all kinds of hairs
well if used wishes for personal
costumes
oh yeah well
I think she originally had a different
wish but then it was a wish that in the
end everybody else eventually would get
anyway
you know what was it some figurines or
so
and then she changed it
um
those buttons holding her shirt oh
crying oh yeah there's there's a couple
of new outfits these days major standby
money and Sam bye
um I like my new samples very much too
is
um
outfit kind of like inspires me
because like she has
two shirt variations like sometimes
some some girls do this and I never
think of it when I plan my outfits
that I maybe could do that but I don't
know if I really could it really depends
like you have to sacrifice
um certain things if you want certain
things because you can't we can't have
everything you know
resources and all that so
you know
yeah
if you want
a hairstyle or two if you want two
hairstyles then you have to like
you know then you can't have this and
that blue
um
alive
well I mean if you count unofficial ones
yeah
but there's
if you count official ones then I mean
then
surely it's a Japanese member by now
because they just are in there longer
the anniversary yeah
anyway thank you
[Music]
so
random new hairstyles there's no such
thing as random new hairstyles what are
you talking about
there's like I can ask for a new
hairstyle or something else like a new
jacket or something like that for uh
like a birthday or anniversary
occasion
um
yeah and then yeah it's not random it
has to have a special occasion and you
have to plan it a long time ahead and
otherwise it's gonna be late
random to us view is no current occasion
how's it random though
or maybe maybe some girls don't
advertise it as it being for that
specific original reason but it's
supposed to be
for some specific original reason
oh don't worry I already did
ask for the
you know shirt to be removed and that's
gonna you know take up a little bit of a
wish a part of my one of my like
birthday wish for example
oh yeah
not too much though I think I can still
add something
um
I'll think about it I have to think
about it anyway Let's Play Fire Emblem I
didn't have time oh God 64 hours what
the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] I didn't have time to you
know move on and and do something
oh my brain oh my God wake up wake up
wake up okay okay
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah
um
yay
there's something no then I would have
to get up and make some tea I don't
wanna
oh
[Music]
because I almost fell asleep and I
stopped myself from it now I'm extra
tired
but
uh yeah
just like Maple referral that thing down
there
like me that's how I feel
and hopefully I wake up also I've been
feeling kind of cold
I'm in my apartment because I turned off
the heating
because I feel like
when I turn it on then I get too hot at
night
also it gets really dry
and it's like not that
terribly cold
anymore
these days although now April started so
April weather April weather is being a
thing again
you
uh
so it's come in my cat were like you
might even snow who knows in April you
never know it might suddenly snow
please don't tell me I have to do this
okay I did them all
[Music]
there's some
yeah so now I'm just in a blanket Erica
who's even wearing my clothes she shows
up sometimes looks really fluffy ones
that's my twin brother Ephraim
sorry if he surprised you but he's
impressed with you too
[Music]
not a piggy in a blanket but a chicken
in a blanket
I feel like we had that
come up before
don't even I only said that because it
sounds cuter than Phoenix in a blanket
um
awesome
[Music]
look I have a cat in my a cat hair in my
mouth
your ring was entrusted to my kingdom
Roy
so brodia will be relying on your power
I hope this day would come
after chapter 23 okay I'm gonna trap to
20 now and I went out with the pacing
that we're at it probably can only do
two today
always only do two
um
[Music]
anyway
sorry guys I'll wake up eventually
I'm awake I'm awake
pick up
oh this is empty all right can we just
go
I wonder if we can just go without
thinking
and do I have to buy something wait did
I eat I didn't eat I probably didn't eat
let's just do that
oh that's the one thing I always do
[Music]
I picked up everything already last time
yeah
[Music]
good
baby
up
um yeah
herbs
where sour cream clonji is that like
it's like a soup right
I'm gonna go all out
okay
huh
what a disaster hey it's just [\h__\h] up
but she's still happy about it I did not
know pain was a flavor
pain flavor oh my God
that's even worse than f
completely burnt sour cream candy
oh my God
please do not give me a bentle of that
wait did she
what at least no minus because last time
I did something that was F
and I got minus points but isn't G below
f a b c d e f g
and G didn't give me any minus what
maybe the extra ingredients I put in
there like kind of fixed it or so
she is too burnt to even try it maybe
they just don't eat it okay well that
makes sense like I said it stays neutral
then the f
F from G because you don't get minus
points because they don't even try to
eat it
[Laughter]
well thank God
oh thank God
oh
um
concerning yunaka you need to learn how
to cook otherwise you're not gonna
survive in this world
should we just like give it a try just
move on
let's see do I have some stuff to refine
something
what could I refine
[Music]
what could I look forward to find
I know daggers are great and all but you
know
that's gold Mary right she needs a spare
plus why but
dude has a square plus one I should just
give her that one because I'm not using
Louie anymore sadly
spare I really like using the spare
I feel like I use it a lot but wait she
needs to like an upgrade too but she has
a javelin plus one but that's it
let's give her plus one on the Red Cross
yeah spare feels really a spear
versatile
shut up then woke up just a moment ago
okay
[Music]
sour cream rice thingy okay
that was the funds for this one
right it's good right
but I'll go with this one and then maybe
the spare two if I can
spear
spear spear snowing let me upgrade this
one
oh it's cheap
I mean silver
oh yeah just watch it
because I use gold memory still so I'm
okay with that
um
see
a swap
with uh this one yeah
foreign
[Music]
she's normally a sword user that's her
only spare eyeliner should be a good one
okay
[Music]
um
Engravings I don't really think I did
hmm I don't know it uses up too much
brain capacity I don't know how that
works
what even is that again I don't
um
I don't know when would I be engraving
on
[Music]
this one's so funny
oh are we up to 1.46 wow
well
I never even checked because it's just
it doesn't show like the detailed
numbers and then I don't even care
because it's yeah it's just suddenly
happens
oh oh
[Music]
they should make a list they should make
me able to sort it by most used
for real for real
maybe volcanone or foreign
what do these things stand for again
what does MT stand for
I thought
[Music]
Mike
does that even matter for magic users
though
I don't know like for other games it's
like attack often doesn't matter only
intelligence or so it matters and a lot
of other games
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm just you know a lot of
games logic mixes up in my mind
it's true though
it's Justin Trudeau
um so I don't know if I engrave it with
something can I not use that emblems
engravement
uh anywhere else
[Music]
surely I can right
sacred is really good thank you I love
you
Secret
[Music]
ah because I like your logic too your
explanation because most enemies can't
attack
from a free range anyway so me losing a
void and Dodge
for the sake of hit and crit is good
[Music]
what um
mine's 20 to them
damn
yeah but yeah okay
why not sure gotta be careful though to
only use four and one far away
oh okay
um
we can upgrade to
should I use it wait the granola is one
to two range though
um
this one has only upsides
what's up dog
[Music]
I don't know how to use that joke
was upside
[Music]
what's what about me
um
[Music]
what on Earth
Zach
[Music]
why
why do you even
why do you even think about it such a
thing number one question
why do you even why are you even
concerned with such a thing
uh
what I'm good yeah it's too early for
this
then number two
even if you're concerned with it why do
you commented
publicly
and then number three
I can tell you there's no corn coming
out of my butt
oh
so far
and I mean
how would that even work
I bite into the coin I don't just
swallow the corn as it is
oh my God
[Music]
I don't understand
I want to understand too
I want to understand
[Laughter]
wow wow
uh
uh what's W Alice wait right
[Music]
um
so honestly the top row would be nice is
there anything it makes the range big or
not
[Music]
blazing
blazing seems fine too
thank you
[Music]
oh damn wow that's four this one's four
up and only one
that's worse which is what the [\h__\h] only
wait
[Music]
ing for a low hit time empty weapons
home
[Music]
yeah a hit and speed for all that okay
okay
wait pretty important
[Music]
that's okay
at least I'm engraving something
um
well that should I engrave
Liberation has engraved
something
um I have so many Bond fragment points
like we can engrave everything
[Music]
low WT equals better chance to double
hit or not beat about it
someone says Celine doesn't double
anyone
so apparently that's fine
blazing on panette killing acts oh
amazing
okay
you want her to crit even more guys are
you insane
[Music]
it's crazy
oh maybe maybe engrave a bow from our
Chris
um the Longbow or the killer Bowl
we can do both
[Music]
we can do blazing on the killer boat
till no
also great okay
yeah he already is amazing gonna make
him even more amazing kinda want to put
something on this Longbow maybe too
I don't know because I think I use a
longbow a lot as well
eh only one weapon can have an
ingredient what
one weapon per person
I mean
oh
okay
ah no you mean no no no no no not one
weapon per not one effect per character
but you mean one effect per emblem after
all the thing that I kind of wanted to
know before
if only
ah
and then what do we put on the killer ax
after all
[Music]
wait did that make me waste my bond
points
[Music]
still blessing
I mean
[Music]
there's also this one
Fates
gives her uh 30 extra credit
that's even better kind of
wouldn't it
oh
hey see we can share
you'll have to take it away again
okay okay
[Music]
don't you want to hit though well yeah
it'll be fine it'll be fine she always
seems to create anyway I think so too
but I mean
they say crit
so I shall do it
um
[Music]
yeah the 11th sword
she already has something engraved now
though
thanks for the membership
[Music]
sure that's so like one of the weapons
I've kept the longest
and used the most
um
[Music]
which one
yo this with DLC
you get so much more options here that's
really really overpowered rivalry I was
looking at that one too
[Music]
no but I want your guys's advice so I'm
gonna do it now
hmm
to someone I think it said something
about that
what
you died
[Music]
um
the killer lens
from home
[Music]
what
thank you
enough heart is not even hard
with flex
I'm more fun I don't need more bone
fragments I'm good
[Music]
foreign
moving on because I can't make decisions
I guess I'll save
I do have some pizza for later if I get
hungry
I'll just throw on the oven and then
throw in one of my pizza pieces
if I get really hungry because I think I
might
yeah already warmed up pizza yesterday
because you know of course the pizza
went cold really fast
but oh my God it was so good y'all
it was so good
um
I think I enjoyed the
um pineapple one the most
um
[Music]
prizingly
I liked them all though
and honestly like maybe everything was a
little bit
um
when I you know it looks a little bit
like everything was swimming on top of
it when I took it out right but I mean
that's really just the first moment when
it comes fresh out of the oven
where's the story here
and uh yeah it wasn't like that at all
like it didn't feel like things were
swimming I was totally fine lots of
ingredients so yummy yummy yummy
yummy yummy
is this where we go
chapter 20.
I think this is the one
okay
picking
this is a [\h__\h] of War map huh
and Little Caesars they should
they need to have me as their like
advisor
what you let them take two of our rings
I apologize see we we figured if we
stole a couple rings you'd be proud of
us there's no point stealing theirs if
we keep losing morons I'm sorry okay but
will understand where his favorites
after all he's not gonna scold us for
losing a couple rings
Marnie um
yes
[Music]
I should have done as I ordered no more
and no less I cannot protect you this
time
[Music]
was it on her butt or on her cheek I was
following lady vale's orders do you mean
to suggest she is at fault
I will not make excuses if punishment is
due give it to me you Marnie was merely
seeking your praise
I am to blame I should have stopped her
what a selfless display
see you show care for a fellow Hound
I'm touched
or perhaps you fear what I'll do to Lady
Veil if I'm angry
alas
spell what you promised to wait until
our return I meant to I really did but
then the defect awoke I had no choice
and don't speak to me of promises you
have broken your vow to Lord zombie
head of this
family my children when they misbehave
punish what are you gonna do Marnie run
I don't think so
um
look at that personal chancla now the
fire
painful too
cold salivating you have work to do and
I'm leaving what should I do with them
oh they'll come crawling back they have
nowhere to be but at my side I trust you
won't be distracted from the task I gave
you even as they inflict pain upon you
pay attention there mustn't be the
slightest down yeah but this lady is
insane I've got to see if that loser is
Lord sombron's kid
this lady is insane
[Music]
here we are
and lose your Castle is likely within
those walls
fail too yes
it's really nice with the mountains
there's a chance she'll face us as an
enemy not a friend be vigilant
at the first sign of danger we should
retreat
what's wrong
those words
they're Mars that's what he told me at
the senia Cathedral before
before I lost him still haven't
recovered from our defeat that day
what if it happens again it won't we're
stronger than ever before confidence
guys literally stepped into your role of
divinity
you really think so yes that's why I
know we'll get the emblems back that's
the highest praise you could give me
easy peasy
let's go
is the Lucia Castle usually this quiet
no
I would at least expect Royal soldiers
to be standing guard Maybe sombron
dealt with them you mean turn them into
the corrupted
who needs those boring soldiers when you
can have me
Chris been a wild Divine One welcome I
would love a one-on-one after that long
journey oh and look the long-lost
princess
got home sick huh I gotta hand it to you
two more rings in your pocket
not bad
but for the complete set you'll need
more like this one the Ring of the
caring princess
it's the real deal too is your new one
right we didn't have yet
I'll give her back
all you gotta do is beat me what is this
nothing what you think Lord sombron's
gonna show up it's won against many
we'll Crush you hmm you know just what
to say relax no one's coming if I'm
wrong I'll bite off my tongue and choke
on my blood what is this about you want
answers you'll have to whack them out of
me fine
get ready Chris
we'll make you give back that ring I
will whack you talking make me dragon
dear me lim oh limb all right I will do
that don't complain afterwards
I just realized I don't have the I need
to use them
the ring fingers I want to put up some
ring fingers
[Music]
where is the folder
let me check
[Music]
where am I
one of my fingers
[Music]
here it is
um
mmm interesting guys
chapter
16 and then there's this like a jump and
then there's chapter 22.
maybe I'll just take chapter 16 then
download
chicken fingers
take note of the
damage reflecting Skillet Chris has I
learned this the hard way yesterday oh
okay did you just play it yesterday
part where I am at all right thanks for
the
notice oh shh
let me bring up my hands really quick
[Music]
this is funny
what look
I'm the one's reacting to
ah
my mouth I think
blah blah
one one
cute
that's just where it spawned by default
okay like this is probably fine
oh are they a little bit small
they're attached to my boobies no that's
I think it looks better when it was
attached to something else on machine
mmm
[Music]
yeah but it doesn't really
because this one's fine
[Music]
yeah okay wait it doesn't fit my outfit
oh well
whatever whatever
you can't really tell
it's like I'm wearing my default outfit
with my Empress hairstyle
um
okay it's a pretty straightforward room
with seemingly not many enemies which
means he's probably gonna spot no never
mind they're in the dark probably
oh yeah
haven't had a map like this in a while
but yeah
cool treasure chests here two Treasures
there
oh
no get the torch out Port I don't
remember how that works do I give one
character a torch or I mean yunaka can
see anyway so we'll have yunaka with us
for sure
[Music]
already there
um
I'll take her too I think I don't know
we don't need Freemasons
oh the Chloe Maybe
[Music]
Maybe
what do you mean low battery
oh
I have a charger right here
and my switch is right there and I'm
reached
okay we're good should be charging I
think
illume stuff I'll probably have one
but when I use the staff does it
only does it it doesn't light up the
whole map right only life is like an
area
I feel like I won't even use
all done that much but okay I'll give
someone
maybe you
um no
there's Adam
rescue
ah I don't have one
I would have picked up one somewhere
before
I can still buy one right
nice
bring me Kyle
place you're not going to every corner
of the pre-deployment squares and use it
to see all the enemies are close to you
how would I place her in every corner
when I only have one yunaka
what
of the pre-deployment squares what
[Music]
Oh you mean before it's starting
with Mikaya user extends
and then the Hortensia is best of Mikaya
according to someone else oh my God
okay well
well well well well well
[Music]
shall we switch it with
maybe with the elixir
um yeah
okay
and then
um
emblem rings
she currently has sovereign
[Music]
yeah
siren works on Ivy OH Ivy Veronica she
has Veronica right now
Veronica's the one that spawns
gotcha
I don't mind switching I have too many
glims now
Soarin of course
hmm
I wanna switch up Hector
because
I think
wait look
no
I want to switch out Ike I think
or I don't know
[Music]
because
great Aether I feel like
I don't know
it's cool when it hits
but it's risky
[Music]
okay
it takes time you know
[Music]
okay
I'll keep it I guess
hmm
okay space wise uh so Yuna can see some
stuff right
I mean like you mean you would want me
to switch out like uh
I don't understand what you what you
wanted me to do here
I understand so blah blah blah blah blah
although
I know
why are all the Flyers on that side
there
but only one Archer but I don't really
see flying units
yep
so we'll have
sword sword
ax
slams
Magic
[Music]
and then we'll split
yeah one magic user on each side
one no wait but this doesn't work again
because of the two
about like this
yeah
and then
something like that who is you oh
and why did you see though
is this how you do it when you manage
your KFC employee's work schedules
I don't manage your work schedules it
just so happens that my own schedule is
your schedule
okay
all right I think I'm happy with with
this more or less
I know you canceled
[Music]
let's keep the fun going
I'm gonna make you work for it thank you
he vanished
Chris must be using Emblem celica's
Power she probably hiding in the shadows
be careful everyone I I don't know about
the DLC maybe not
I don't know probably not
oh
we'll see
[Music]
all right here we go
let's go
uh why why are you so little damaged but
at least we break him
mm-hmm
[Music]
I just got with the killing is
broken no crit though all right
no parallels today no I wanted to do one
part privately but
yeah I want to finish this game next
week you know
I'm ready to move on
[Music]
mmm really really
that doesn't kill you
really
I am shook
[Music]
high level war is a walls of meat is
that what that one is
my God
hmm
there's a 25 crit chance
[Music]
pretty good help
was that yeah
25 Christmas was that on the on the
Chain attack or on the on the IV attack
[Music]
uh wait
uh
go ahead
you finish
and just by her walking I can see the
what's behind the Shadows right but I
mean
okay so far I don't see much
a little different
[Music]
in the middle of this round
thank you guys for the memberships with
killing Edge your name's killing Edge
don't I have a weapon that's called that
what's that look like a good level up
yeah yo cool say the word
fan the word
and I shall kill or maybe not
with the javelin it's not too bad and he
only has 56 percent
could miss
[Music]
I think I'll do it
she has good magic resistance
[Music]
what
wasn't he just up there
[Music]
what
none
did I miss him teleporting
when did he do that isn't this the first
round
did he do it before it started
because
the intro okay I'm too tired
it doesn't ever turn
so he's just gonna but wait does it take
up a move for him to teleport
because can he just attack me and then
teleport away that would be just so
overpowered mean
[Music]
oh
it does it after it gives it is a whack
a moment
I'm not enriched though [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
Charming okay
can't I'll do my best where do I send
kiwawa
maybe left one of them is not attacking
anyway aka the dancer
I'll send her left
all right we can break this one
[Music]
break it until you make it
oh
wow that's really low percentage
hoping
hoping for the 67 percent to hit
[Music]
if you're killing this turn he will stop
walking around the map yeah that would
be nice man is where he warps is it
scripted
I wonder
yes
I'll protect you happen thank you
it's scripted okay so he always starts
down there
Longbow
not too much damage
we don't have to keep the distance
because it's already broken so let's go
with the steel bow I think
[Music]
yeah simple or
or hope for some luck of the Kettlebell
but I mean I still have other units who
can help so I'll just grab the two bro
[Music]
oh maybe there's like a couple of
choices
and uh yeah maybe like free choices
that are scripted and it just goes with
that whatever
[Music]
you sure
so far I don't feel like using the staff
yet maybe next turn we'll see
choice is yours
When You Reach
there okay
kiwama go here
could then make dance and move more
[Music]
should I
why not
that helps
ah yeah I could have gone in
I was thinking the moment I did that
yeah what if I would bring him to the
right side
dance for Ivy attack boss
is that worth it
yeah I always have more than enough
rewinds
you go this side after all
that's for Ivy baby
thank you Ivy does no damage to him
[Music]
I mean yeah I guess we wouldn't kill him
but I mean it would have been nice to do
something of course you did some damage
look at that and uh
or orc would kill him you know
some decent damage and he can't attack
back
[Music]
kill the horse
all those kills because they might
double kill someone
true
okay
fine fine fine
rest now yeah
yeah she had 22 crit on that
okay
let's see who does he go for probably
yeah
Chloe so what's the plan you're gonna
stab me mash me shred me to ribbons
is it gonna kill us
it'll surprise
I won't be much use in this state I'd
better head to the rear lines to rest
great start
again where did it go
uh except or undo
oh
[Music]
Southport Please Subscribe when you kill
him once again I already know
um
that would mean I either have to
like get into
I don't know
um
I would have to move her and that brings
me back quite a bit
meow
all right
[Music]
try to send that layer
but now I still don't see him though but
yeah yeah yeah yeah
isn't Chloe the only one without counter
because otherwise I would say attack and
then go away
she's the only one who doesn't have
cancer yet
[Music]
she'll survive if she has full HP
m
thank you
[Music]
let me move this part first
for 29 so full oh
okay
[Music]
that's dangerous too I'll stand here
okay and then what did I how did I
just should I take this one down
two
[Music]
twenty three
all right
let's see Japanese or American never
I am Austrian
I speak German is my mother tongue but I
also speak fluent Japanese and English
[Music]
have a mixed audience so sometimes I mix
in some Japanese
[Music]
I can't believe I did that
Miss World once clearly she's a talent
yeah because I made such a amazing pizza
yesterday
foreign
one could think
Italiano
[Music]
how does the staff work
oh I use it at the spot
seven space radiant that's [\h__\h] like
like I feel like I even don't I don't
even need to use it because like man
wasting a turn for that
I'll just move on and let's see
well maybe uh maybe next time
oh with Mikaya engage okay okay thank
you for reminding me
I shall possibly do it next time
now the question is do I still want to
bring the dancer to like
IV and so on
what if I dance
Ivy now then
[Music]
she can always start attacking this one
and then maybe when I attack with Chloe
it'll be a kill without her getting
damaged
or I dance I try to dance Pinette
that's best okay I'm like going with Ivy
first
and yeah okay
great help
[Music]
but I have to consider Chloe can only go
this far and she can't attack from here
she so I have to leave a spot there but
he can counter away anyway or she can
just go here
[Music]
wait she also takes a [\h__\h] ton of damage
from that
not like this okay not like this
should work that should work because 7
HP Chloe can do seven HP just fun
what do we go here
[Music]
foreign
I'm doing this for you you better
survive after this
I'm counting on you
I rewinded a lot for you hi
and then we have Chihuahua
[Music]
all right
hey we know
but I don't know about her resistance
um 44 damage okay
[Music]
where did it go oh
oh
[Music]
now I'm enjoying the game I mean it's
been very long
but I'm enjoying it
it's been a little while
now
surprised Ivy didn't get Ambush I mean
like in this position yeah
[Music]
all right show me what you got gold Mary
what's the point
wow critical breaker
you're cute
give me some EXT
[Music]
ENT agent of shield are you hating on my
are you hating on my gold Mary
it's been rocking this okay
it's dangerous but maybe okay in a
pillar
what do you say guys no
no
no no
right
you were beautiful while you lasted
[Applause]
I just realized my chat is really
uh zoomed up made it bigger looks kind
of weird oh well easy to read maybe
um
I think I want a heel of Ivy
not lose
I will go as far as I can
um I mean
she has no maybe not because she has a
um
and then
just throw some foreign at this little
discount
not bad bug
[Music]
load here God anyways are you insulting
her are you pissing her I don't
understand
we not understand memes
now sea down is now not in reach of
anyone great
horsey though
it's gonna be lagging behind
okay maybe now it's time to illuminate
engage
[Music]
oh yeah it's a great sacrifice
hi
what is there to see
don't forget the guy in the back there
what
oh oh
forget that one
that'll go
okay
but is she still alive when she's the
one she's in that form because she's not
on on the horse
I thought well now this is not it's just
still considered flyer
um
wait I what oh
[Music]
okay maybe
oh
anyway I can take care of this one with
piwawa
thankfully
oh
is that even any kind of bear damn
okay
what does that mean
I wish
what's lying light up surrounded you
have that too
well it's already lit in here
I could engage
try to shoot Chris from here
but I also kind of want to focus on on
this one I don't think
[Music]
okay
oh
wow
maybe better make doubles
doubles
bubbles
my double person is someone else so who
knows the doubles again
if what was it was it Lynn
okay well then no problem
I'll call it double hell yeah I'll call
the doubles
[Music]
oh yeah okay this is fine probably let's
see
[Music]
yes
what no
did you just okay
Mara what the [\h__\h]
Tamara I got kidnapped
yeah bye
okay okay Coolio
doubles are so overpowered
Laura they're killing all my doubles
straight away
stop and they're gone okay but that was
so worth it
[Music]
no
23 shoot the Buns
oh my God
you're right
oh
Tamara rip
I don't think I want to rewind them
I mean it's not even my fault they
teleported her there sorry
I've got him
[Music]
yeah I'll keep it like this
we're just gonna do it maybe we'll
teleport someone else
[Music]
don't say the thing that we're all
thinking okay
I like her
so Grace is gone again where the [\h__\h] is
he now
[Applause]
um
a good night
[Music]
that Mage is is that Mage gonna do that
more often
that's really upsetting we only have two
enemies over here okay
[Music]
here
we will get a crate trust me
no we didn't
no I blew it we're done with a crap
unbelievable
oh it's science
what
you little [\h__\h]
can you believe that
okay the Stiletto if we're lucky Chris
okay
fine I'll take some damage hmm nailed it
all right what happened well we lost one
unit and we're accepting it we lost
Tamara that's okay
it's all right probably
just play with a little bit of a
handicap
I think I might heal
before I attacked again
as long as we don't lose our Wawa I'm
fine with it oh you're being extra
Charming today huh right away
come let's let's see those rings
I mean
wait did I use
did I use Revenge before or did I use
killer ax
because I felt like I had over 70
percent at least
a hit chance
did I just use the handbag panda
[Music]
I know I know to range yeah yeah but
we can break him anyway if we hit
so I wanna do big damage
something lady kill I don't know how
that would work
you just killing so much is just a
better good life
okay
RNG is re uh set anyway but at this
point I think
hmm
okay
no crit is okay
it's all right
let's see
you're done now if she hits now I can't
believe he's still alive but I can
finish with Chloe or with panette even
foreign
thank you kindly
I'll go up here
take him down
we're done
Pinette gets exp even though she didn't
lift the finger great
um
wait there
[Music]
only here still no Christmas sign all
right now to this side
it's making me a bit nervous decide
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't one hit that one can I
what what's going on
I must engage and hold but all for one
wasn't that the one that attacks with um
[Applause]
uh chain attacks like
depending on how many are close to you
come on
how do I get the most kills
I mean chihuahua can finish off two of
them or can do half damage to him
can
[Music]
you can call doubles again
oh wait what yeah that was again
no doubles again
I didn't realize you can see doubles
again
[Music]
okay that means that this one will go
for the double
[Music]
surely
emblem engage
is that a waste
because I could just normally kill the
one below me
oh let me just do rainbow
I must stay focused
oh yeah we're reset her level
[Music]
okay
I do not want to be wait I wonder if the
maze could
go for one of the doubles for
teleporting them to themselves
that would be ideal if they want to
teleport anyone please let it be
double
ah there you go this works however it
would take a lot of damage
this works
I don't think it can I mean if they can
attack them then they can also surely
teleport them
we'll see
especially if no one else is in range
and looking juicy
oh
kiwama has skill that makes her move
again what I forgot
Ricky was that
oh that was raining storm
[Music]
oh genius
because I have barely used raging Storm
I mostly use the
the other two I think
yo how these are taxes so powerful
Fire Emblem free houses ring overpowered
so overpowered
foreign
Ty was to open
all right we cleaned all of that up
I did
oh
Chris
okay but they anyway focus on the
doubles thank God
that would have been things
I mean if the meteor comes down so
slowly yeah that's dodgeball
immortality
[Music]
genius
okay
I would like to see what's up
just standing there I guess I could
Dragon man
nothing yeah
nothing goes by
what what's this area all about
[Music]
oh
it's boring where am I supposed to
attack
[Music]
yeah
they're a little bit too far to help out
[Music]
please
big help
[Music]
dance
I mean but what if I send someone over
there but next we need help over here
after all
barbecue thank you
FC cute
I had so much like I had a good time
yesterday even though I was freaking out
and was exhausting but I'm so happy with
the new camera
hope we can do cool things with it in
general I'm happy I finally got like a
proper camera
for myself
it's really nice
yeah
I watched the archive and I think I mean
I only saw you guys screenshots from the
live stream
but I feel like
the quality was better in the VOD of
course
a little bit better
[Music]
yeah and uh
I think with lighting I think I think it
was good that it wasn't Overexposed and
all that
but you guys are saying
you want it to be brighter and maybe
that'll look a bit better but I don't
want to overexpose over exposure I think
it's nice to have
the colors be like you know realistic
and not blinding
especially with cooking
so you can see realistic colors
but my room was pretty dark thank you
my room was pretty dark
[Music]
sorry that was a legit accident and I'm
not gonna rewind because of that
I was gonna go one more down and then go
up to dance
I know I know
I didn't wanna
not worth rewinding though
I'm scared I could go further but I'm
scared what if Chris is there
[Music]
ah
poly Ergo you can also buy a fake
brother which is a better power cables
we can with better no no
um I I know there's a better way to do
it I was just not you know I just bought
the camera
I wasn't
like you know able to get all that
working just yet but there's a way that
you can use it as like many people who
use it as a stream camera too so
um yeah don't worry I know how to make
it work without dying on me next time
[Music]
trust me it'll be fine
oh it was never done okay let's clean up
here
[Music]
did I use the great sacrifice before
the machine dies on me because no wait
but then it's not really a good exchange
is it because they're not
they're not that low and healthy that's
not a good exchange never mind I'm just
gonna waste it
it's all right
all right
[Music]
it's just because it runs out next round
and I kind of want to use
things before they run out
[Music]
noise
oh hot 21.
[Music]
doesn't kill unless critch
um
[Music]
ah
six days only believe
um
which one though they're all good
maybe maybe I also believe in my 12
percent
[Music]
Rest In Pieces I don't think I have a
brave sword I don't know
well he's dead that's good
[Music]
that's a long bow
what about
steel ball kills
your stupid little [\h__\h] I look
you killed my Tamara Because of You
Tamara died
no more of that
you will be a little game until no one
can beat me
what let's get level up
I'll Chris and trap oh is that what they
used for that oh could I do that
couldn't use it on on Grizz
no no
[Music]
um
we have
two more here ideally
oh wait no these are illusion oh God oh
I still got two left over
then let's get this
25-25
[Music]
I'm not afraid anymore oh no worries
about being late welcome oh did you guys
get fooled by anyone on April Fool's
I
I haven't
actually
I didn't get fooled by anyone but I like
I was I saw something that was real that
I thought was fake but you know
ah gen four yeah that was confusing to
me because normally we know ahead of
time and stuff like that gets announced
so I was like what
what
I can't be
so I didn't really believe it but it was
I was confused like did I miss something
I don't think so
like why would they already I don't know
seems a bit too early I don't know even
it's not even early though because it
doesn't didn't we'll just have our one
year anniversary and I'm like what one
year anniversary
today
I only bought Tesla for retaliation
for Expos trying to purchase Activision
what
Sony bought Tesla and retaliation for
Xbox
is that now that that really happen or
did that not happen
fake anime announcements oh
that's sad for some people who are
really excited for something
[Music]
oh that was fake okay
so is third gen ID really already there
for one whole year
that's crazy
[Music]
that's just crazy talk
um no for real like one year how how
also the teacher's Grit
can it already be one year
man what you got
[Music]
yo the vein of fog in combination with
the pillars holy [\h__\h]
plus 60 I need to occupy all of that
oh God I can't though
uh well I can't move Chloe even though
it doesn't help her
I know it doesn't help her but I don't
want anyone else to occupy it oh but the
phone goes away by that time
no no no no no no no I have to protect
it
you were reverse fooled by Kelly
oh so yeah that was what I was saying I
mean I knew it was real but that was
what I was saying on Twitter like
April Fool's no way that she's really
revealing an outfit share without fit
even ah
[Music]
well she did she do
why is the right side so boring
wow what's what
I could
I couldn't dance connect or I could
dance gold marrying I think I'll dance
gold Mary because she can break the dude
um
[Music]
because Pinette and Ivy clean the right
side
[Music]
um he's on the pillar true
oh you know collapse almost funny really
I was sleeping
you know there's some cute art for the
for the girls yeah
[Music]
I mean it wasn't a bad time for me but I
I feel like
I was fine with not participating
because
um I already turned old before
and when I turned young before and you
know that also didn't go so well at the
old old was fine but I don't know I
don't want to repeat my joke from last
year you know already time traveled last
year
so
I'm okay
[Music]
you're too kind
but I would have loved to get some
Ina art of small blah blah blah so I'm
sad I missed out on that
[Music]
Poncho
a fake Kaioken stream why would you lie
about a karaoke stream
what how is that even
wait I just noticed there's a heart on
the map
[Music]
why do I see a heart
why is my view apart
[Music]
the collab could have used an angry Baba
but
you mean old Wawa
[Music]
yeah look there's a heart where I'm
standing
on the map on the small it's even more
invisible
is her moving a heart
[Music]
yeah you didn't notice that I don't feel
so bad for noticing not noticing until
now
um
well Chloe doesn't seem to be able to do
much damage but
at least she doesn't get any damage back
[Music]
she's kind of low on health and that
feels kind of dangerous too I think I
want to hear she does she only has a
mend
and she should stay in the back on this
Lane
[Music]
unless I engage her maybe that would be
nice too
let me see you
[Music]
I'll take it if something goes wrong we
can rewind now it's my turn
yeah
oh really
I knew that
oh I knew that
I knew that that's why that was such a
big brain move of me huh
I knew that
I totally knew that
[Laughter]
oh
um what's wrong
yeah yeah
ah what is this one mob doing there man
hold nothing back
[Music]
can't even do that
really
what's with this Bob
I have an idea
because I need to charge her
anyway
illusion I want to charge
I had a pillar I just wanted to go here
afterwards
she may be lagging behind a little bit
but that's okay
now
am I
gonna have the courage to
go ahead or should I stay together
because they already moved on to the
next
[Music]
should be fine yeah maybe just like
Scout with Guam there's surely some
enemies there they can't have no enemies
at all in this one
[Music]
he's probably standing in that pillar
ah Chris was there they kept it all
empty for Grace against Pinette oh 24 I
should survive
okay I think I can kill him like get one
HP bar down though because like I have
the full team there no no other enemies
to focus on
he got himself into more difficult
position no way did he teleport away
again so then that's a problem [\h__\h] yeah
well I have to find him
going all the way up to the top of the
map
teleport down you
down here routine
that's so annoying gonna nah they
wouldn't make my whole team run down to
the bottom again
you did it for me all right okay we'll
see
yeah
that would be so annoying
[Music]
um
mmm
well he would always come for my team
yeah and then teleport away though so
that sucks I want to find him
and now he just teleported here and then
teleported away so I don't think he
would just be in this area so close to
me
uh lamb
lamb
[Music]
leg
give me strong foes
[Music]
this map is lame
this is so lame there's a lack of
enemies
I can't believe I'm complaining about
that
[Applause]
um
what a lovely sea
fine by me
[Music]
anyway one of the reasons why I didn't
want to do something like
too much like oh haha funny I fooled you
for this year's April fools because I'm
I'm kind of
I I didn't feel like it
I thought my pizza thing was more fun
I I mean even if I try to fool you
nobody's gonna believe [\h__\h] anyway like
I don't know
like whoa is that even worth the effort
trying to fool you with something that
you're not gonna that we all know is not
true
then I could just you know make a fun
pizza
I just felt like I'm too old for her
doing April fools or I just I just don't
find April Fool's entertaining
it's just I look at jokes and I'm like
funny on April Fool's oh funny
I don't know pizza was more fun
to me
too old
I mean if if you can
um
if you can
it's the word
simply wonderful
you can I don't know the word if you can
manage to actually fool people
if you manage to do it so well
and then respect but I feel like yeah
nothing fooled me this year really so
I lost interest and stuff as well
and not just me
most I just look at this cool thing that
we aren't actually doing yeah
I mean some cute things come out of it
but then
could do that anytime it doesn't have to
be April fools then
I have
I might have something
coming up
that could have been an April Fool's
thing
but no need to do it on April Fools
if we just dance panette but I'm too
scared to attack with her
genius
got it
that should look
anyone
stay here
[Applause]
the return of maybe a frog oh no
hold on it's been a while since frog you
wow
[Music]
our return
yeah this is so I don't know I don't
like the the odds of this why don't you
get it to attack twice
week not a whole week just one stream if
I didn't
froggy wow for April Fools well are you
calling for Angie Wawa a joke
how insulting
panette
why you make it so difficult for me
whatever
hold up
[Music]
no
I blew it
says
I am speechless
absolutely speechless
thank you
64 is incredibly High
[Music]
64 because of my
uh engraving huh
there you go
and no what
I found that was gonna be a prick
and I can't even move back to the thingy
[Music]
and I can't even move it to the pillar
ah
64 is zero percent
oh oh god he's a terrible position now
no
oh my God yeah that's that's them that's
not good that's not good that's not good
that's not good
um
no
I'll do the raging Storm again so that I
can clean up a little bit and protect
alcreased
is that okay
you just saw someone missing and 90
s okay that's it 97 crit chance missed
that is that is not okay that is quickly
just lie
this is it
that your defeat was inevitable
oh it uses a free turns wait a game
[Music]
I can't even really reach oh wait but
afterwards right afterwards after moving
no I'm okay
should I go put left one for the right
one
I think I look for the right one
that was maybe good
oh
pesh cats with weapon is that
your defeat was inevitable
a bad girl
intended for close Comet poisons hit
foes well that sounds normal okay
killing Edge
oh cool okay that one is going to
unically holy [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
I sense danger here
[Music]
I fear one death
that's where all the foes are yeah
danger danger danger
fall back well now it's too late only
kilow could fall back but even then
even then she's still in range then I'd
rather off of myself as a choice of uh
enemy instead of a crisp take me yeah
bye
um
survived
he does survive what what caused ah but
the others might hit him to death yeah
tired of playing hide and seek oh okay
eventually he just stays there when he's
sick of it okay thank god oh wow Chris
I might keep it
fresh at the end and there's barely any
never mind
I'm sorry what
[Music]
I'm okay with losing one now or two yeah
that was an unlucky crit man
nice
[Music]
I could still rush for the boss
I think but no
I won't even say it's like the position
she was at
hmm
[Music]
but okay
should we really go back this far
full turn
foreign
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
you shouldn't have that one equipped
okay I just don't attack and I just move
away
retribution is due
I'll do the same thing
that needs healing
hmm
but if we keep Chloe up there all alone
and surely she's gonna be the one to die
I don't want to break him
foreign
changing that
yeah
wow I would sacrifice her
as long as I don't lose two units
so
I mean this far back should be fine
right where was she standing like here
originally
here she's probably fine
paint
go back and dance all right how far does
he go
should have got one more bag and I'm
gonna dance
[\h__\h]
again I can dance for panette but we we
saw how that didn't really help us out
much
[Music]
I don't know
now I'm like super out of confidence
I love condensed oh
oh I read that this is one second lane
um I forgot yeah
[Music]
um
so faster
and sentence then sends the honors of
her
I mean I'm not gonna dance panette with
him
because I I wasn't gonna do that anyways
but I might as well just dance her okay
I might as well do that
wow they're getting in such a big
dancing mood
I'm gonna do it
you gotta do it
allow me to demonstrate
Conga yeah
I know I didn't dance either with that
but I mean free versus one you know
I just
barely even then I I really can't do
much but this looks good
wanna wanna hope for a crit
IC that could be a crit with 59
percentage what the [\h__\h]
maybe move on
if it doesn't if it doesn't hey it's an
hour rewind
and then I don't know go for it okay
come on come on come on come on come on
and then we'll also see what's going on
on the other side I think a little bit
oh yes
overpowered the 59 percent
yeah
okay
now what do we see
let's see something
see one enemy
I will fall back a little bit
Tim
he's seeing him
I'm stupid
can't damage him anyways no I would have
stayed there in an attacked with someone
else now I can't attack because I can't
see
it's good you're leaving ago yeah I was
thinking I mean I could fog up here
we're here
because otherwise I'm fogging up the
enemies
he was there
Chloe will definitely be a target of
Interest
I'm ready
[Music]
I wasn't even expecting or hoping for
that
you okay
what did I do up here
how Chris died right so we want to
prevent that
'll stay behind a bit
oh
God I should have put him at least now
even even if I would have put him in a
position where he didn't can charge
afterwards that's not good because then
he's gonna
tease all the enemies
let's take it slow
although I would like a kill out of this
[Music]
I
will see
I won't forget you
I believe in Yuki Wawa
[Music]
oh
yeah Chloe
I don't have high hopes for Chloe
oh
[Music]
shoot the hell hole that is this
Darkness
has yet to activate and griss is also
still rooming around
for Christmas so you know in the mix
let's
why did the PGM changed so much
okay
um
our foes are strong
[Music]
okay right here
hurry
it's such a mood chain victory is mine
didn't attack one because we went back
to normal
ize silver blade
hi
how you doing
[Music]
nothing to attack now
it's
uh seven space plus one right so eight
okay maybe I'll do them again
[Music]
thank you
okay now I see them
I was feeling more confident when I
wasn't seeing them
hmm
I know I know the pillow doesn't help me
I just want to stand here
tactical decision
[Music]
um not worth baiting Maybe
why am I such a scaredy cat now
[Music]
we gotta take one of them out
I can't though less quick
[Music]
not good
yeah I should have engaged
[Music]
I'm getting hungry
hungry Chloe yeah because the last meal
we didn't even eat
oosh
maybe I shouldn't have been so passive
on the left side maybe I should have
just gone all in
[Music]
ah I still have rewinds it's good
should I Endure I don't think I can
endure I feel I think that'll kill me
I want to attack it and move away
[Music]
I was hoping for crit
I don't want a dragon vein I also kind
of want to finish that dude
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] right you can't wait
she will die
[Music]
but Let's go ask
uh dance Ivy or dance peanut
[Music]
Maybe
oh where do I want to help out though I
can help at the top
[Music]
I can't kill I'm not gonna crib
please
[Music]
need help
where are the chords when you need them
[Music]
I know I know she needs to heal too
she doesn't have cancer I really need to
get Chloe cancer
I can also go for this one sure but you
know
which one's more worth it
[Music]
no we want to use the wrap here because
this one no I don't know
doesn't matter Celine would have been
really useful for healing here
um
[Music]
oh how Gallant
now and in return
okay
please nobody else
trying to get her
no
it might though okay I'll accept that I
think once it was okay
foreign
okay
please leave for that alone
poor seat out
ah
there's no losses
okay I can't reach Chris yet
[Music]
avoid will he stay there
and I am
maybe if I use like a one of those
attacks it pushes him off of it
um
full heel now yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah on the right side means
it
[Music]
uh maybe at the end of the turn [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
like at least after moving the left side
oh well
sorry
all right
it's okay Kiwa won't even take damage
look
Dream well they're all like the enemies
over here are so dead
so
hmm
[Music]
pretty nice they won't even
in that case
I mean
25 credit is kind of low but we've seen
Miracles before
[Music]
oh
no my no curl now no Miracle now
hi I'm sorry
[Music]
my side is done and as you can see now
about damage
oh
all right we have four enemies to deal
with here
this is a one hit kill
I say is worth it
unless someone else can do that one too
whatever you ask
[Music]
foreign
serves you right
yeah he'll attack us all right
Annette has full HP and she survived
before she'll survive now
I think I might use her down here
I can always dance too
Unforgivable
yeah still haven't used her engaged
meant
what was Corn's engagement again
emblem
ah the flooding
ah
maybe against the boss
oh no
yeah
okay then I'll keep that one
wow
that's not fair
oh let me go back here
they are so strong
emblem
are you ready
and now I think I should be able to
somehow finish that one enemy
with some other
helpers
now it's Checkmate oh I did finish
watching Queen's Gambit by the way the
whole time I was watching Quinn's Gambit
I was always expecting for there to be a
like oh oh now now there must be like a
really dark Twisted Stern that's gonna
make me cry really hard or so
and I mean there were there was like
maybe one turn that was really sad
because it really wasn't overall so bad
I expected this to be really like
defeating for the main character in the
show
but
she seemed
like they didn't throw that much
[\h__\h] at her as I thought they would it's
an actual show yeah a really good one
really good
eh the strength plus four is that only
for that turn
or or do they keep it for the whole map
it's about chest yeah one turn oh okay
okay
kind of want to go here to charge
a bit far
[Music]
allow me but the whole time they were
playing chess blew it okay even though I
didn't
um I can't believe I lost I don't know I
never understood what was going on on
the on the boards because it was
happening so fast
well it was still really uncertaining so
even if you don't know chess well they
they did a great job that makes that
proves you that they did a great job
because they made it enjoyable
even if you can't follow
but oh man it must be even more
enjoyable
if you if you know a lot about Chess
yeah you could feel the tension it was
really badass it was real cool
mmm
well one of our hardest hitters is gone
sadly
I'm a dancer
so she can get a bit closer
protect ourselves now
oh you can break them wait let me just I
just want to see how this works
what no we can't no we can't because we
can't do damage
I agree wanted to change RNG
there's like only one enemy left and
Chris
he got plenty
give me some time I'll be right there
I had no choice but to win
Queen's Gambit is kind of on
one of my favorite shows now but like
um
it's also hard
not top five but in my maybe top 15.
it was really good
actress was really cute too
um
even though the show is really not
straight edge
concerningly little straight edge I
alright I wanted to
do the engagement
Quick Change
yeah you should give it a launch right I
don't know why I waited so long I think
there was like I started watching it
a long time ago just like the first
episode
uh first five minutes or so
I watched it until the part where she
ran down
being late for her match and then I
stopped watching for some reason I was
like I I'm actually not in the mood for
this right now I'll I'll start this show
another time and then I didn't start for
like
over a year
I ended up not
I ended up not watching it after that
for some reason
foreign
because I think
it looked kind of dark to me
in those first couple minutes it was it
concerned me
an AI chatbot
that sounds really basic
find my lack of knowledge don't worry I
didn't know it even until my viewers
told me
I might miss
[Music]
it means when someone doesn't do any
kind of substances and no alcohol no
smoking and all that
foreign
isn't here
[Laughter]
this feels good yay I'm gonna kill you
all of you
try me
nice I'm so happy for Chloe because I
feel like she hasn't been doing oh
silica oh I feel like she hasn't been
doing many like really impressive moves
recently so
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I was
intimidated by the show and it wasn't
just feeling the mood at that point
and then I forgot about it for a long
time
but it really wasn't as dark as I
thought it would be oh bolting oh yeah
not so good though
let me see
oh that's so close
it's a good start though
Chris has me note 13 crits on her side
yeah
[Music]
should I dance one of these to me
well I wonder if I would dance uh gold
Mary if he could even reach
no she couldn't
who does the biggest damage well Chloe's
damaged me pretty good now
good for poison people
find that argument
double form but then Ivy also take so
much damage from it I prefer to do some
first some chipping damage
and then finish that HP bar with ivy
oh dear
that's not something weird at all
wait she would she would keep too much
she actually survived some of these and
maybe he misses
the four the 56 one maybe we can go for
that one
I Will Survive
Mini case
well he didn't miss but I'm okay with
this
foreign
yeah now he's poisoned
and there's already some damage there
okay
mediocre
A rad
I can still do this
yeah well this is it
sorry yunaka
Xenoblade or so
[Music]
what's that engagement it looks so
futuristic
kind of crazy looking
okay
[Music]
um
who wants to finish it because if I
engage QR she could get she can attack
from a distance
the others can't reach anymore
I could also give it to Ivy
[Music]
and I'll try double pouring
why why are you guys so
why would I do double porn when I can do
single L fire
hi
this has free range what do I I don't
care about that he's dying this turn
away
now I don't care
I'm just contemplating who to give the
kill to I think I'll give some exp to
Chloe
oh but she'd die
unless I do this one
I'll just give some exp for her
[Music]
um
do you want some EXP
can you take it oh yeah he can he would
even break him
yeah
good for you sit down
oh yeah
wow wow wow
[Applause]
wow
emblem engage I'll give it to kilawa I
think
all right
that's it how do you like to be heard
Divine one I'm a speaker pleaser wow
that's like the perfect boyfriend oh
hand over the ring Chris
ignoring me seems very considerate it's
my feeling
I'll give you
the film
oh
so intense
[Music]
oh
good stuff right
oh my God
oh my gosh
Excalibur
[Music]
wow
that she did quite well
[Music]
took longer than it was necessary though
but you know it do be like that always
the ring we got it back
was what I could have
what are you laughing at hmm me not even
nothing because that was awesome
thing and all that and preparing
gasp
I thank you
it's such a relief to have you back
again oh this is so why is this so
dramatic
crazy
[Laughter]
oh man
ain't this whole thing just a laugh Riot
Sofia
that little hunch of yours was so dead
on
I think it's clear you've lost your mind
look at you acting oh high and mighty
it's clear you've lost your mind yeah
that's cute
the real question is have you lost yours
you're playing up this whole thing like
you're a God but you're fighting on the
wrong side
why are you staring at me with that
stupid look on your face you think
you're a Divine Dragon let me set you
straight you are the child of the fell
dragon
no but how
okay how dare you utter such slander
such lies if the dragon doesn't remember
it how the hell would you know anything
were you there a thousand years ago hmm
I'll tell you how I figured it out
Divine and fell dragons can both summon
emblems right but they don't do it the
same way Divine dragons pray
Bell dragons though
they use invocations
that's how you summon Celica that's how
you've done it all along isn't it which
means you're
say it with me the fell dragon's child
but then
he's so kind to explain to me like that
why did Mother call me her child how
should I know you'll have to ask her
oh wait you placard
Sticks and Stones what's that mean
anyway now I've got what I came for
too bad it cost me a ring but I was told
to buy time and I did Lord sombron and
Lady Vale should be long gone by now you
mean
you were here after all whoops very very
old slip out oh well your Divine dragons
are fraud take your time falling apart
will you scatter to the winds cut each
other's throats
so many options
he'll continue supporting me
all dragon they all will follow me
blindly
and be divided by the enemy
calm
sambron isn't here may have been another
attempt to mislead us let's look around
and make sure it doesn't matter in the
end
if you use your powers in a good way
even if they came from Evil this place
is well and truly deserted then it's
okay
sombron is no longer in the castle what
should we do now
ah if what Chris said is true
I should leave what do you mean girl the
night mother died I had a nightmare
where I was surrounded by Flames my hair
and eyes were red
now I see
it wasn't a nightmare it was a memory
one bad dream doesn't prove anything
maybe not
but this will emblem cigarette I am here
you knew me a thousand years ago didn't
you
answer this
was Chris telling the truth
am I the fell dragon's child
you are wait why did he not care to
correct her ever until now though I
apologize
with your memories lost we thought you
could be happy living this way this is
what Lumera and I agreed upon the day
you will walk why did okay mother call
me her child
sambron had turned his back on you your
life was in danger both you and the
mirror wished above all else to be a
family that is the fullness of my
knowledge
plenty sigard
I'm sorry everyone you spit out you
drink you need a refund for that Divine
dragon
I never was you have nothing to
only a Divine Dragon could imprison
Sombra on his mother is there a Divine
Dragon what chance do we have now of
surviving this war
without such power there's no hope of
stopping sombron
the power of a Divine dragon
you have failed Dragon Blood yes but you
forget your own abilities
report when my ring was returned and you
summoned me
I used an invocation emblem summoned
through a fell dragon's power cannot
communicate
think back upon emblem summoned with the
fell dragon's power
speak no
when I called out to them they didn't
answer please explain further sir
circuit a fell dragon's invocation robs
an emblem of their free will their
service is compulsory with a prayer the
emblem keeps their free will a Divine
Dragon would wish nothing less you use
both invocation and prayer
I do have the power of a Divine Dragon
your hair and eyes proved the fact
eloquently
at one time
both were red the blues proof that
through lumaris alone you have inherited
a Divine dragon's experience your
explanation for that Colgate hair could
succeed her as the Divine Dragon mother
we emblems fight alongside you of our
own volition we could only deepen our
bonds with you because you have the
power of a Divine Dragon you are the one
intended to carry on lumaris Legacy will
you still leave after hearing this
is that your wish
no I want to stay I can't change that
I'm the fell dragon's child I know that
but
I would like to continue on cast The
Divine dragon
[Music]
if he will have me of course we will
alright sure first we came to you
because we needed your help but now I
care about you fell or Divine or
whatever else is he hating on me
so no more talk about leaving us we'd
never have made it this far without you
I will follow Wherever You Lead if you
have only half of your power so be it
we'll make up for the other half what
matters to me isn't how you were born
do it the life you're given if you
choose to live as a Divine Dragon simply
then that's what you are conflicted okay
I am made Resolute by the terror
understandable
to me you are the Divine Dragon I'm just
that stunning I'm leaving would not
change that Bond everyone agrees after
all you are what connects them
and always shall be
the Divine Dragon
Phoenix there's much why do they keep on
saying it wrong I may have made choices
in the past that I can't take back but
for now
I'll continue on this journey with you
we emblems will follow you
have our own free will
fifty thousand military fans let's go
that's some good money
um
you little shits in the chat
[Music]
all right
daddy hold on I don't know what this is
you know I mean hmm
I know
look maybe
I've I've been I've been influenced
about what to think about the story
but people saying
they don't like it
or do I just generally I'm just not not
that impressed
I don't know which one it is
[Music]
just I've been I've been spoiled by free
houses
that's the problem
[Music]
don't Vandal didn't play this
not as bad as Fates
Divine Dragon
mavier it's you I overheard your
conversation about being Lord Sombra
going crazy if that is true then I urge
you to help lady Vale what
you're not here to stop
us all this time lady Vale has been
sustained by a desire to meet her
sibling if she sees you she will be
saved I know it I'd like to support her
like my friends here have supported me
hmm fail the true Veil has been a friend
to us
but we don't know where she is she is
traveling with Lord sombron to the land
of lethos lethos
sibling
what do you think or a full sub let's go
with him
and remember that extra lie I was
bothered by idle guard
full okay
I mean but yeah okay maybe she was like
a little bit problematic here and there
but
the whole like war and all that was set
up so cool
I don't know
those characters were cool
I didn't even like unless it was your
fourth choice other wives you mean
choosing someone for wife you know
that's an important decision that's
different than liking someone as a
person or you know for the story and all
that
like you know the lore yeah the plot was
more
satisfying I think when all this is over
what do you plan to do
I guess that myself
to travel the world and also read and
sleep a lot I'd like it if you were by
my side as well I'll be sure to consider
your kind invitation as we hasten our
way to your days of Tranquility my God
can you speak like a normal person
foreign
well
you cannot blame me for putting idle
guard forth as a wife choice
when there's so many great choices for
rifles
it's difficult
you can't blame me
it's rough
it's all it's not that easy
[Music]
huh
oh pretty Pebble not forced
maneuverworms
wow wow wow
we shall jump straight into the next one
even though I'm lacking energy by the
way I'm not streaming tomorrow
I have two recordings tomorrow
starting at freaking 6 00 A.M
oh
for official Channel
one of them was the one that I was
questioning if I should really do it
I started
often you know the office for this
come in in like doubles they're like do
you want to be in this in this program
and then I say yeah and then turns out
they're always like being recorded back
to back
um so they start kind of early I mean
not early if you live in Japan
but early for me
well it's summertime now it's a little
bit better
yeah
of course there's been other em members
in official programs
of course
Cali is in a couple
I feel like
bills baby baby yeah Iris probably too
yeah Iris too
um
[Music]
I mean they choose Japanese speaking
members because the programs are in
Japanese
so it has to be members that have some
decent Japanese conversation skills and
that's yeah that's Bales Iris me and
Cali
oh they could no they could do enough
has Ina been in a program before because
he knows Japanese is I would say
sufficient
for that purpose
depending on the program
I think she did it's good to see you
would you care to join me
sorry I didn't take you on the last trip
but
it was kind of a weird fight anyway
[Music]
no
Emperor's Miss what the [\h__\h]
for them
[Music]
Christmas oh wait
wait that sounds like
oh that sounds like a
that is that
like I just want to say English
translate
the explanation is exactly that what
have you guys ever heard of Emperor's
mess
I told you guys before about kaisersman
but have you ever heard about is that a
thing in English have you ever heard
about it no
they put an off strand
[Music]
in here
that's really good that's good effects
yeah
[\h__\h] I never thought of that the
translation before and purpose but it's
a direct translation yeah oh my God but
I'm so hyped about this bite-sized
pieces of fried pancakes love it and
melted butter on top of powdered sugar
yes yes
I'm so happy about this
stop
don't [\h__\h] it up Celine I know a few
things about cooking
know
[Music]
this should make for a lot yeah
yeah
on the plate the sauce that he leaded
with lovely aroma
oh Celine
D with all of that it's okay though
I knew I love you I knew it
[Music]
incredible
cooking
my country's food now I really want to
eat that
I miss that dessert so much
it's so good it sounds so simple right
but it's like
um
yeah
I can't believe they included an
Austrian dessert
what
could you cook it in a hand can stream
Maybe
it's it's not that like
mind-blowing though it's just you need
to taste it to understand
[Music]
I don't think it would be so interesting
as a stream because it's it's
really actually quite simple
and it doesn't even look that like
impressive
hmm
[Music]
I think I'm gonna bring over some potato
chips let me
I want a snack
the Bears
[Music]
ah hi
what are you guys doing here
you guys doing here
okay
[Music]
we found one movie now ah it's the one
that I was into
that one is Canada oh
just engaging
hello my dear
uh
um
[Music]
I'm eating pumpkin and no one is here to
stop me
that creature behind me oh [\h__\h] I'm
playing dead so just so that can
surprise me and then make me be red for
real that's for real
[Music]
yeah junkers are sleeping
chunkers will not be the one to stop me
from eating good
no not bomb bam
I'm eating pumpkin
potato chips
or have you ever had
damn
[Music]
yeah the chips mmm
homo bears
all right speaking of Pullman
[Music]
can you [\h__\h] believe it
the Uno
never working out
ah
[Music]
too funny
but I think
I think it was plenty fun
and that was one and a half hours of not
playing a game
hmm
Ubisoft what the hell
[Music]
um
do you not want people to play Uno
is it a whole conspiracy theory so you
get people to play like the real Uno and
person again
is it a conspiracy theory I think so
hmm
I will never
never try to play Uno with people again
at least not without like taking a whole
day beforehand to test it out but
um
I mean the thing is
[Music]
like I asked beforehand hey
which soft which platform are we gonna
do Uno with because I've heard I noticed
that a while ago some young girls had an
UNO collab and they were like I just
skipped through it because it didn't
concern me but
um I saw them
like discussing on Discord hey
Uno this and that problem this and that
because Ubisoft account this and that
blue I saw they were struggling with it
because apparently some things changed
so I mentioned that to the girls too
like oh I don't know exactly what the
issue is but apparently
there's been like
you know some changes in Illinois now
it's even more difficult to play it so
we should decide which platform
to play on but yeah
in the end both of them were [\h__\h]
yeah oh yeah the only Uno that is
playable really without issues
I guess would be the clubhouse one
which isn't officially unum
but you know
yeah
forgot about that one
mm-hmm
[Music]
no I will send friend requests whenever
I have a collab that needs um
me to be friends or someone on switch
again
it's okay for now
I'll be a loner for now
no no not Super Chat reading camera
continue
William
Monopoly is broken on all platforms
[Music]
they're fun
um
bankrupted for waiting too long that was
her fault
because you can even see a countdown
you just have to read
[Music]
I know it's stressful but you know
um
she was all tapped well still
with Monopoly
and Uno if you plan to have a collab
with these games you have to expect to
be [\h__\h] over by it somehow in some way
[Music]
several times
do not
underestimate Uno and Monopoly
that is the lesson to be learned
[Music]
okay
hmm
should I
we're friends on warm
[Music]
oh wait I got like a new weapon
several is this one worth using it
should be right
okay option
instead of which one though I wonder I
will
bring it to plus two maybe is this is a
good one right you said equivalent
[Music]
okay
and then we also had
the Excalibur but it's another wind tone
so I don't know it's just really
worth investing in
it sounds powerful
useful against magic flies
[Music]
you got a bracelet didn't somebody ask
about a brave foot was it something else
like a brave something something
someone's like why does your character
not have a brave something something
what was that about
I forgot though it's a brave lens
confusion
a brave sword for color too
I'll be here crunchy sound is good
[Music]
to get yourself some potato chips too
wait
do you sell that
[Music]
you do don't you
break so hard instead of uh you guys are
like kind of hating my Steel weapons
aren't sure even though they're not that
bad
[Music]
dong
parenting attacking twice at least it's
gonna take up to four times
[Music]
foreign
here you go
[Music]
anything else that's interesting in here
anything new
well
[Music]
um
they also sell a patch cuts and a card I
never heard of that one
[Music]
um
okay
take care now I'll upgrade the brave
sword and then I don't know we could
already go
I don't know how much more difficult the
next map will be
the leveling
[Music]
I'll be here
don't forget to eat I already ate I ate
the emperors
oh
what
um how can okay
I'm gonna go to the arena I think I
forgot that one last time
oh card sword in Hungarian oh
[Music]
we have to wait
the problem with Chloe wasn't I think
that she didn't uh get cancer yet I just
couldn't buy it for her yet but she has
that uh
the the closeness of cigarettes I think
we just didn't have the points I think
thanks for stopping by to uh I am here
yeah you know what I mean oh
55 chance only come on Hortensia
wrecker oh
small Sisters still losing to big sister
oh man
at least you got to level up
prepare to be awestruck will she get I'm
Lynn get ready
this tree is yours Glenn won't lose next
time I'm sorry that you stood no chance
did I
choose by accident
you can randomly get emblems
what
and then does this ever happened to me
before
[Music]
I will act as your opponent today
Clan 33rd Steward of the Divine Drive I
forgot you exist sorry dude I've had my
eye on you
he's got an elephant do my best now and
in the matches to come
I didn't help him though
damn Chloe
okay
[Music]
ah
it's finally Chloe
finally I'm sorry you had to wait so
long
um
there it is
finally
um
now everybody
[Music]
doesn't have cancer
college alone control
yep
did I
[Music]
was there a point issue
now everybody has cancer
[Music]
really go on sit down
okay
I'm Sea Dog famed dancer of song
I am singer of house Chelsea you guys
know those cookies
um why were they called again
those cookies
oh my God
well-earned victory
you know those cookies that um
what are they called again that are like
kind of um cinnamon taste kind of
um that you get often to coffee and tea
and yeah yeah no uh what wait
hmm
yeah Lotus cookies
McDonald's has a Lotus ice cream right
now so I tried at least in our country
and give it a try
[Music]
it was okay
I feel like I should have added some
sauce because I didn't add those
it was only the it was it is you can
easily recreate that at home all it was
was basically a Lotus cookie crumbled
over basic
vanilla ice cream
it's yummy but nothing special at all I
was surprisingly disappointed maybe also
just because I was so hyped by the
chicken nuggets
the chicken nuggets can you believe it I
got ten
can you guys ever get more chicken
nuggets than you ordered
yeah it's really it
that's all there is without ice cream
[Music]
it happens quite often
um
I think I've seen plenty of people who
say it happened to them once
between my luck
we know chicken nuggets okay
[Music]
um
we got 10 anyways America
oh
oh yours not 6 9 and 12 hours or 16 and
12 I think
[Music]
6 10 20.
oh my God
I mean
nobody orders that alone right
and then if you want to like eat it with
somebody together right
because like
I mean you could fill your stomach with
20 chicken nuggets but why would you get
20 chicken nuggets and not just like a
burger and then some chicken nuggets but
not 20. you'll find
it twice I mean yeah it's a whole meal
but that's like what are you guys wow
what
share
yeah that's no no I'm not saying it's
too much I'm just wondering like why
would you feel your whole stomach go to
any chicken nuggets when you could have
like I don't know six chicken nuggets or
and then a burger
they're good yeah but what
what I'm not knocking shaving
I know
wow so I guess that sells surprisingly
well the 20 combo
damn that's America baby I usually do
share with my family
yeah
[Music]
shocking that is shocking to me
20 is like damn do they have a box that
fits 20
we don't even have chicken nuggets boxes
that big I think
[Music]
because our biggest is just um
12.
they don't just give you like
two different boxes
two small ones I mean
um
[Music]
when apparently we have 20 nuggets too
what what what
McDonald's
[Music]
chicken
oh yeah we do
[Laughter]
you want to ordering that that's why I'm
like wait wait wait wait I know that's
the in the English box though
yeah chicken nuggets
wait don't wait oh
[Music]
let me go on the Austrian McDonald's
website
chicken and fish
why is it so slow
[Music]
for wait ah
what poor we have a minimum of four
we have four six nine there's no twelve
I was confused
what
all right
yeah sometimes I do only order four
six nine and twenty
feel like sometimes I eat four
maybe not no maybe not
don't say Happy Meal but
[Music]
I would never order 20. I feel like 12
would make more sense alone
20 only if you would like share
why won't you eat so many chicken
nuggets
says the one who in the beginning of my
time I'm stuck on the qawwa said how
many do I eat per day like what 1670
are you Lord
[Music]
43 44 days 53 a day yeah yeah 53.
hey well
[Music]
but not all at once I eat one every half
hour
one and a half every half hour
[Music]
right
sorry I mean uh two two and a half every
half hour
while I sleep yet
[Music]
that's difficult map yo
I mean I I don't sleep while eating I
wake up and then I take um and then I
sleep again you know it's like you know
the the thing that some people found out
is pretty cool in sleeping in intervals
so there's you can do that for eating as
well
um
no anyway
whatever
moving on
to get nuggies administered
intravenously no no need for that no no
I want the texture
I want all of that
properly
of experience it
[Music]
yeah yeah it's playing with the spiders
they just the nuggets they just fall
into your mouth while you're sleeping
you won't even notice but I want to know
this so I wake up for it
anyway
you better
[Music]
foreign
just get fresh ones
you're probably stocking up for the in
for the case of an apocalypse right
right right right right that was the
only reason you did that right right
right right or like a a pandemic right
right right right right right right
apocalypse or pandemic right right right
right right right or like when you get
really sick and you can't leave the
house for five months right right right
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah
oh funny
don't worry I'm not Naggy shaming you
because I understand
why can't we just be hungry no no no
this is a different issue I am doubting
that they taste good after freezing them
and then reheating them
I doubt it
but I mean
prove me wrong I guess
but then again just why not buy them
fresh to you maybe you live really far
from the McDonald's and you don't get
you don't want to like drive out that
often maybe I guess
possibly that would make like a little
bit of sense
[Music]
clearly you don't I do want an air fryer
though
it's gonna go now
[Music]
is that where we're going
I guess so
chapter 21 Having learned the harsh
truth From Grace the party pursues the
fell Dragon to life his castle
[Music]
begin
this is a double chapter oh [\h__\h] heart
chapter oh no
why'd you not
why don't you not tell me to prepare
more am I okay am I gonna be okay
I'm not gonna be fine
our ship is docked here
[Music]
you told me too late
thank you for escorting us
already like you asked feel free to tell
me how great I am wait a minute what's
the Divine Dragon doing here
Marnie
you want we don't have any more Rings
there are circumstances get your [\h__\h]
together travel together times are
changing Divine dragon
after Marnie and I lost the Rings zephia
disciplined us chapter 22 is easy to an
unjustice game
so On My Honor I will not betray you
once at sea I will deliver you safely to
lethos will you trust me I will
take us to lithos
the Divine Dragon should meet with Lady
Vale
have no reason to fight as long as
you will hear details again if that is
unsatisfactory then you may remain here
let us go Divine Dragon good luck
go there
the Lord sombron's child what what yes
so that means you're the sibling lady
veil has been looking for all along
that's why we're headed to lead those
hang on does Chris know about this he's
the one who told me
Chris picked a fight to DeLucia Castle
to verify the truth even surrendering a
ring to do so
going to lithos
it's about gradlon the fell Dragon's
land lost under the sea intends to
restore it to restore that Unholy land
my word what more do you know about this
vendor
gradlon sank beneath the waves one
thousand years ago
I will make everyone my friends was a
wicked place
[Music]
to raise and revive it sombron needs to
destroy the Divine Dragon shard in
lethos that Shard is what chains grablon
beneath the waves Lord sombron finds it
problematic so you're saying that
sombron's greatest desire is to restore
Christ far from it I think I did if
the word is fitting for Lord sombron
to invade other worlds other worlds the
continent of Elios is only a stepping
stone he plans to extend himself
everywhere there are other worlds who
wants to rule them all made their shirt
how is that even possible I'm well
beyond what I know for certain Lord
sombron has shared little of this with
me I can say lady Veil is a pawn in
service of his greater Ambitions please
tell me anything more you know
I've heard that Bale's called a defect
what does that even mean well as a start
Dragon royalty should be able to summon
emblems
she cannot what Lord sombron learned
this recently soon after his Revival
when reunited with Lady Vale
his children all fought in the War but
she is youngest
never saw battle
or any implants she told me we met once
all that time ago you were among her
many siblings
they all in time died fighting in the
war all
save for you
then sombron was imprisoned and Lady
vale's mother died leaving her alone she
could find no friends in an age when it
was rumored to last fell Dragon child
had survived lady Vale lived in hiding
knowing that where she discovered
she would be killed a thousand years
living like that
[Music]
all alone that whole time not exactly a
few centuries ago she came into contact
with worshipers of the feldragon in
their care she slept in a hidden temple
until Lord sombron's release
she had been long ago close with those
in that Temple
but when she recently awoke they were
all dead weren't they
so lady veil was relieved even Overjoyed
to find herself reunited with Lord
sombron he detested her and proclaimed
her a defect lacking a fell dragon's
abilities and character
sombron required her obedience however
so he ordered zephia to tamper with her
nature lady Vale may have thought she
was no longer alone
but she's never been more so
ever Mafia is such a
chance is it the waves are you seasick
cry but obviously
ville's life was
the one with the tragic story
and maybe even nicer to her
probably you have never told me of your
past Marnie
I mean you know happens all the time I
was just abandoned by my mom that's all
I had a lot a lot of brothers and she
decided she didn't need a girl
which is weird since I was way Superior
to those useless jerks even back then I
mean I was better at helping her but she
never said Thank you or a good job
or anything the first time we went for a
walk just us so she could find somewhere
to dump me imagine my hand and hers and
we're strolling from place to place
she left me at a church finally bearable
believe it when she tells like this the
priest was nice long as I helped free
Lord finally Down to Earth but thank you
eventually I met zephia enjoying pounds
see Lady vale's story is so much sadder
zephia filled out the four hounds with
devout followers of the fell Dragon did
that include you Javier
yes I was there at the Hidden Temple
where lady Vale slept
she awoke I was there to speak with her
she a royal Dragon asked me to be her
friend I said it was impossible lady
Vale then asked if I could offer my
service to her as a knight
big deal to be hand-picked like that by
royalty who would have thought you made
her night that's just cool I mean that
mavier that's really cool should you
wish I'm sure lady there would also
accept you as her Knight what no way I
don't want to work with you that much no
praise no thank yous I hate you wow so
slides I already belong somewhere I need
to get back to zephia
since you're helping the Divine Dragon
you're probably gonna get kicked out of
the hounds
I expect this much yeah well I like
being one of the four hounds
as soon as we're off this boat we're
enemies you do hate me after all so
surely you'll be happier all right so uh
yes
I'm done talking myself
[Music]
Javier
thank you for telling us all of that
when we find Veil
I hope you will do what you think is
best for her even if that means we'll
cross blades again
I shall
hmm
I liked how she became so human like
normal now
the land it's Fallen to rot and ruin a
sure sign of gradlon's return or that
our foes are now destroying the Divine
Dragon shard
[Music]
it's in the castle
Queen lumera's home who would have
thought we'd return here to see
everything
come to this
[Music]
Sam's nice to be home normally
I can almost understand
show yourself
ah the Divine dragon has arrived should
I call you the Divine imposter
Nani you've arrived earlier than
expected
how did you know where to find us
my other two children haven't even
caught up to us yet I assume you mean us
hmm
why are you with them
you just brought them here
and betrayed us
unbelievable
you have it wrong wrong
looks pretty clear to me this is my
doing I want Lady Vale to meet with the
Divine Dragon I might have even forced
them to come but it wasn't necessary
Marnie had no part in this mavier return
to the hounds Marney
go now
[Music]
you sent your dad but mavier what will
we do with you
[Music]
I'm willing to forgive and forget if you
can explain yourself
We are family after all what nonsense I
know you're going to punish me but lady
Vale will see the Divine Dragon
you rude self-serving
oh I don't mind
I was just thinking I'd like to talk to
the Divine Dragon mice it was evil Vale
it sounds like evil Vale
evale
what's happened to you
it's good to see you again
what did you do to Lady fail
I told you about Lord sombron's
Enchanted helmet the helmet doesn't even
look that stupid down there has now
truly taken hold
fail
do you know who I am oh her outfit why
you're my dear long-lost sister
what a happy reunion
this is what you've been trying to do to
her
and the other lady they'll return no
never not as long as that helmet remains
attached and intact that other side of
her is dead
dad oh please you should be delighted
you don't have to talk to the defect
anymore
Sophia I know about vale's past
do you
you were alive way back then what I mean
I didn't know
when I helped you with all these awful
things lady Vale was all alone for so
long
and she was so excited to see her family
[Music]
now she never will
it's all so terrible what is this Marnie
Sofia I loved it when you gave me praise
I loved it when you said we were family
I love belonging somewhere
I loved the four hounds but this has
gone too far I have to do I know what's
right praise or no praise
Marnie I'm going to free lady Vale oh
I'm going to break that helmet to Pieces
really no
love it when game characters are like
stop and then don't move
oh
she tried oh that was simply pathetic
respected I couldn't put a scratch on
father's gift this is cool strength and
it did nothing I take it you were trying
to free me fool that you are but as it
turns out you have failed in your
attempt no no
I ordered you to stop did I not
such a bath girl
[\h__\h]
you are a very naughty child
no yeah
no I was just starting to like her
[Music]
sorry I tried to save her but in the end
I guess
I wasn't strong enough
if she's ever her old self again
will you tell her something for me
please tell her that
she's done
oh well
man no what [\h__\h] that's sad please
Barney no
you'll see
where did she dance
how very tragic and finally a plot list
that I did not expect nothing
[Music]
yes Revenge
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
money was just trying to restore Veil
and all this
I will never stand by you again Sofia
save for the moment my blade pierces
your heart Divine Dragon I beg of you
allow me to fight at your side to avenge
Marnie to save lady fail Mafia
I don't know if I'll put you in my
actual team but sure betray me
leave me sad and lonely again and you
sister
I thought you'd be happy to be reunited
with me after
so long you are not our Veil this must
be about my new look
then you're not going to like this look
either hmm
oh Martha his fellow emblems stolen away
you turned your back on him oh
lonely thing just like me ah hello
Raiders
[Music]
spoilers no
had I known I had a sibling who survived
the years
I would have killed you I'd like to make
sure I'm my father's one and only child
you want to be alone forever yes that's
right
I have no need for this sort of family
or friendships or bonds of loyalty I do
appreciate you bringing the Rings to me
but that's where our relationship ends
now
goodbye
sis well let's just talk come on
talk it out let's talk it out no more
violence
Marty did
the martini didn't deserve to die she
was just like ah changing herself
to become a better person
that's so sad
she was good at heart
but maybe he also didn't expect that
zephia would go that far
I didn't expect it
don't blame him blame him
super SSG he probably also already
blames himself and just like beating
himself up about it
[Music]
will die when they are killed yeah
hmm
[Music]
oh man all right what are we dealing
with why are there such big circles oh
there's this Dragon thingies again
worms
one is behind me one is on the side
okay we'll take care of them first who
are strong
what's strong against the worms
it was just one was it connect and it
was really strong Maybe
against them
some normal mobs
Annette Whoever has Erica
oh
while engaged also without being engaged
and Chris
you may want to rush lots of
reinforcements
[Music]
oh the few who can deal with them at all
yeah I wish I had to because now they're
like at both sides
go up as fast as possible should I
ignore these
or should I just have panette be at the
bottom
deal with
them but have them follow me
I ignored them
[Music]
it's right here for me so I'll sleep
okay go now thank you
thank you
stuck to one side and worked out but
okay because silent charge
besides you mean don't go middle go left
or right
because the charging thingies are on the
on the sides too
[Music]
thank you
definitely do not go middle
oh
and are they not gonna come for me
anyway though
[Music]
ah they don't spawn until I reach a
certain point okay then I could still
take care of the bottom do these ones I
think I'll just go right side for now
uh and
[Music]
kick
I tried to deal the reinforcements it
didn't go well
I bring my whole team on the right side
really is that really necessary there's
not even that many enemies here but I
guess they're coming later
[Music]
okay connect
and go right there
okay
at the same time oh okay
unit selection I don't think I'm
bringing this lady here but I do want to
bring Celine again because she made me
one of my favorite dishes ever and I
will not forget that
she made me the emperor's mess
I will forever remember that the rest of
the team seems fine this is like my to
go team now
I forgot about fogado
okay
should I change some rings
who has
Chloe is Erica
so she can move uh deal well with
the worms as well
yeah I forgot it with rainy and bow can
be pretty good
why we could just if right and go to
of course
[Music]
do that should we
actually or is there a reason why it
should go on avocado
Sega could help Secret
because of why
ah more magic for the ball
override
okay
and then maybe ends up uh oh see maybe
inside of Tamara
I'll bring fogado
I could do that
[Music]
there's not even like flyers in this map
though
but okay if you guys think that's
helpful
forgot about it on tomorrow
yeah he's still keeping up level uh wise
I would say so cute
okay
switch those siblings those sibbies
ouch
and then give fogado which ring
[Music]
we have silica cigarette Roy empty and
Veronica
or magic
you're sure
and then what should we put cigarette on
we
yeah
who has lips ring
no one no see though
so he can dance to a boat map what how
would that
[Music]
oh
put on Celine
[Music]
six thank you oh get well soon thank you
Patsy thank you we're slowly getting
there slowly
hmm if I look better when someone who's
not see though
let's see they'll come get refreshed
oh yeah yeah Violet was on someone else
anyway
if I do this then
I want to give ticket to someone
I think
it's so good
be kind on her anymore
is that weird
o
sit down
[Music]
who's that
a good investment
cheeky I'll do my best
[Music]
ah because the heel yeah maybe I'll need
that
um
foreign
[Music]
who should I go for
foreign
[Music]
who can attack well
cidel can attack
but
not well and ideally he should be
dancing
the skill she passes on are good
okay cool Roy I'm with you
please
[Music]
not going to use Celine yeah I will
I will
[Music]
I don't know if I want to give him Tiki
I mean he could give at least he could
give the um
the second HP bar to people that's
that could be kind of noise
[Music]
oh did I not get
um
[Music]
I'm just gonna look at the inventory
anyway
he danced if he's Transformers I don't
know
you can still dance
you can do the HP bar thing and still
dance in those turns
still dance with a dragon
oh okay I guess we'll do that then um
and we have a brave box we have a lot of
chop oh we do have a boy bags we'll just
take it
fine thank you
let's look at my all my characters you
have one spot empty there
[Music]
we could give her
some healing stuff maybe
a physique
I think I'll I'll give her a physic
maybe a fresh one
Excalibur
but she has a Windows floor
[Music]
we don't use it much but
lollipop lollipop
following Ivory alone heels might want
to check on that okay you
[Music]
know she has a rubber
brake lines and Javelin maybe something
else to add on to the
spare
foreign
[Music]
or
a Rider's Bane
vocabulary
for your oh wait no I'm not bringing it
never mind yeah okay
that makes me think
can Chloe make good use of the Brave
lands too
[Music]
maybe instead of one of the others
have I been using the iron lens
revenge is a Knuckles oh okay
Brave over iron
maybe not only
it looks like
an overall good Improvement
cruelly
[Music]
you've heard the other one too
do I have more elixirs
all those stupid stories I do I do
[Music]
uh ah I was gonna give her uh
it's gonna give her that dagger
hash cats
[Music]
no way didn't you just gotta stay over
the Stiletto
[Music]
should I keep the steel backer
kind of oh yeah really
[Music]
okay
um
no more illum necessary
I also heard this is maybe in this
expression up
freshman
ah I don't really have a freshman
to buy one
[Music]
or I'll just add a physic
hahaha
and then honestly
she has plenty of ways of healing
yeah she's good
she's like always good
[Music]
teleport
yeah I mean she only has two books
and I almost never used what ranges uh
Excalibur
ah
well she can't use the Excalibur
[Music]
you can't use the bulgar known in the
foreign
[Music]
okay
we for beautiful
um wait let me let me go through
um vulneri I guess
[Music]
all kinds of bows
and Alex here
oh Blood Gang
wow German
y
sword
Alex here
[Music]
ever give her another stick or give her
a proper healing item for herself
I have a double elixir
what's up pure water again all right
relax
priority of school foreign
if you think that's a good idea okay
scroll cake
you know what you should have done
because he can he can also eat it it's a
healing item too
oh
yummy
somebody eat that before it's not good
anymore I've been keeping it in the
fridge fridge for a couple days now
and I think I
[Music]
quit
not cancer
but instead of
um
[Music]
maybe it's
um
um maybe one
okay
[Music]
of course I didn't wait what
hold my ring doesn't got the counter yet
[Music]
Chloe maybe I should give cigarettes to
goldberry
[Music]
no
what did that change
I don't know if I like the changes that
just happened because I don't see what
happened
she didn't have those staffs before this
year
my plan
the physical I I feel like she could
keep but I guess it was a javelin before
[Music]
she had a mend
really
I think this is fun
um
[Music]
okay I think I'm ready
Chloe has cancer I think so yeah
I think I equipped it on her
[Music]
yep
okay and uh sorry now the only thing I
want to check is the position
[Music]
thank you
if I go right that this dude will follow
me 100 right
[Music]
it'll be on my ass
won't hit
Mario will jump to I am right oh yeah
yeah yeah
I wish I could give him a ring I have so
many left over
[Music]
five
I'm gonna down and first to Chinese
if it's gonna attack me anywhere maybe I
should go left side
so Mafia can access is he oh he's Lance
[Music]
because he need it
urgently
how do I even do that
[Music]
Lance instead
ah story
[Music]
foreign
one I am with you from this day forward
thank you welcome
[Music]
welcome
you don't even have to defeat the other
ones
yeah I wonder if you can just skip them
and go straight to Vail
it comes with the flame lens okay nice
and really this dude oh wait I don't
know
well I'll go right outside right side is
good
I trust
she's so strong
maybe we'll get a credit
we'll have to heal her and back up
though
okay sorry you had to see that
you can just focus on the boss
anyway
[Music]
s guys
I'm so lame
right away
everybody behind here
is this really the way
[Music]
won't be laying for long okay
Mommy I can heal her ah oh perfect
that's just a little bit though hmm
save me
it's the threat it's supposed to help
you survive okay
all right
you have to remember by the way since
this is a two two chapter thingy right
ideally
I would want to play one more chapter
after this
but I do have to get up early tomorrow
hmm
[Music]
come anyway aren't they
scary
the stage is mine
[Music]
thank you
I can
and it ended pretty fast if I go for the
bus only
[Music]
let's see
yes
so far so good shall we
I got them out of range too
my will is firm
where too
although I don't think I can somebody
face me
all right all right I hear you
and I'll say say the word glowing around
boy
no no not after the double chapter just
double tap here
hey
oh the PGM is kind of cool here
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah they're they're
surprising me from the back though I
don't like that either being ambushed
like that what am I supposed to do
continue running away
I feel like I have to face them
[Music]
let's fight them let them come to you
um
[Music]
let's begin
he's got a tomahawk
[Music]
maybe I'll go for some
for something
[Music]
no fire do you also have a tomahawk they
all have a tomahawk
they all have a tomahunk
[Music]
can I be out there there's two arches
I am fine
it's fine
I am engaging immediately
tap area what it's across
is it the cross
[Music]
hmm
not a cross
I had it right the first time really
[Music]
ah
okay yeah that seems pretty decent but
it doesn't oh damage on the ones in the
back
[Music]
I will win them down
hmm
[Music]
I would go with Celine
pretty good
[Music]
oh 47 for him
I mean he does still attack with the
tomahawk but
47.
he's likely to miss
we have all those retards next to yeah
yeah if I can kill with a one hit then I
I won't do that but
[Music]
all flowers eventually Wilt scam
scam
[Music]
I'll kill I'll kill the Archer
so that less danger for Ivy and coal
Dream well
at least I found him
okay
let's see can I do something here
I will not lose
[Music]
I I might use him to heal
wait today
not have a spear or something like that
right
but it will leave one HP
no
really one HP
really
it's lame I'm so lame
[Music]
like Chihuahua is there now
itadakimasu
just joined a team and gets a really
sick weapon good for him
you can't kill everyone on the center
you could just focus on that let the
ones come to you
[Music]
I'm a dummy
wait
I want to see how far I get on this side
too oh
[Music]
Pig Sia
deserves it yeah
he finally realized what side he should
really be on
[Music]
okay maybe the other Archer
take him down
[Music]
Mamma Mia
who hates me everywhere so much
[\h__\h]
[Music]
if I may
I'll apologize later
I don't know about that
I might dance someone to kill that one
Archer because
[Music]
I cannot
take him down on my own
[Music]
um
yeah yeah I just said that about you
know like two seconds ago
now I regret getting going to the lower
path with Chloe because now she can't do
anything here average she has a she has
a healing thing you know
it was rearranged
because yeah she only had it because of
the rearrangement
[Music]
port
don't judge me okay wait you could also
take something out of the combo now if
we really wanted to
ah
[Music]
it's a card
but I don't know which one do we get rid
of though
we're gonna mend or if you think
[Music]
okay
I really confused me I had it all right
before that but then I accidentally did
the optimization which is not really
optimizing it at all you know
what's the issue really
oh well now I'm stuck here so
guys I want to waste Demand on that
little HP
how many is that
5 HP
no I will not
[Music]
maybe not attack and just create a
dragon vein here for safety
[Music]
Gordon Ramsay what pizza did he make
certainly not
as good as a pizza as I made
[Music]
get on to my level Gordon Ramsay
gotcha
wanna play gotcha
[Music]
wait when they summoned the hero right
in front of him right
[Music]
let's see if we can get really lucky
like last time I doubt it though
[Music]
he can also dance
yo
uh what color was good
wait ax land sword hmm
or neither
I think last time we used ax
[Music]
exercise
you can't move up the contract
ah if
call us Richie aren't you
okay let's try
[Music]
it
I'm blowing on my on my
license
okay almost died first Hospital fourth
time on one side will be too often
but really weak here
really weak right now
what do they have even as a weapon they
only have one weapon
oh my God
maybe keep them for later where they're
actually useful I don't know
no way don't they
what about here
[Laughter]
excellent bait can use a decoy
okay hello
hello attack me
[Music]
you just wouldn't attack I was wondering
that too I should
but hey
poisoned now
the Archer is poisoned now thanks to the
dagger hey dads that's the cool thing at
least
[Music]
okay now I will dance someone to kill
the goddamn Archer
[Music]
but who can take that
only
Ivy probably
[Music]
but she might take some damage herself
before the killing ivy can read
[Music]
thank you
oh you want two of three poisonous
snacks eh what I thought that worked
differently
[Music]
uh I don't want I don't want to
understand so
frontal
[Music]
fluff
she can't kill
[Music]
yikes
thank you
yikes 19 crit
ER
oh I should have engaged
[Music]
I will let me undo it
better work though
[Music]
it doesn't really
I mean it's kind of good too though that
much damage I like it though
oh
yeah okay
[Music]
I mean the airway would have been cold
too but I want we want the Archer to be
gone
gently right hi
I'll leave her here
oh my God Mary is still here
gold Mary doesn't have cancer though so
I want to be kind of careful
just wait
[Music]
verily
oh
my peanut also doesn't move yet
[Music]
and I should have used gold Mary I
bought gold Mary was my last one
um
[Music]
yeah
I'm stupid did I go I just wanted this
one crit 34 crit 69.
it is hard to tell somehow because of
the fog probably
[Music]
okay
what about it
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
not
damn it
one more
decoy they missed again
okay okay okay but it kept us quite safe
from these two remaining ones
lucky
almost
I don't play nothing oh my goodness
okay good good
[Music]
now what they're already coming should I
move on
foreign
[Music]
I just I will just like move up like
this straight
kind of almost all of them
[Music]
wow you can really dance
what does that mean
[Music]
good
sleep now
[Music]
Aya
fogado and Veronica
[Music]
cannot even kill this little baby
corrupted who's basically dead
looks pretty though
[Music]
well I mean I have to move all them up
and they can barely attack people while
doing that anyway
I wanna I wanna kill the one on the left
here though
nice
Celine yeah this is again why I love her
so much look at her
oh I can't get him down to 40 but then I
only have uh level six
42 42 this is the best
[Music]
good art
[Applause]
games
[Music]
fire M scam
that's what this game is called
[Music]
hell
man
retribution is due
[Music]
kind of running ahead of everybody but
okay
[Music]
that one has a bowl though
the free bowls so he's gonna go to the
right side
[Music]
should be a front line for the boat
she's on the right side though I mean
[Music]
give me strong foes
well I think I know I know one thing
no one thing to do fortunate
I'll get to look so different with this
look damn
different character
so I want to
outboard them I'm sorry
or call Donald
[Music]
I don't know maybe I'll call doubles
we're not that that much in a clock
clutch moment right now
[Music]
do you think they will hit them really
hard if he stands there
why not shoot the boss
could I even make it
yes probably is
[Music]
he's got a physic right
wait so
[Music]
now it shows only across
so this is only across
remember that she's flying yeah I'll
move her away after
we're getting ready as a dancer out of
there
and the whole thing is like boys
[Music]
thank you
next to Ike it's only a free degree of a
ignizer
oh that's why that oh
that is very confusing to me
okay at least we got one kill
[Music]
my units are safe
wait what what
she missed
huh
[Music]
hey yo
it was 42 percent
ah see yeah that's no that's why
generally I don't really want to skip
anyway because then yeah I know I know I
missed this kind of stuff I was
confident I didn't look you guys said
bolting well then look
and look
look
who to dance
or give HP bar and don't dance at all
I'm not sure
[Music]
wait who do we have we have
movie or else
okay
oh no
[Music]
I believe I am in the right
okay
I think they'll take him as a bait
they won't
they'll say comic because that's fun
that's fine
so popular
thank you
hello
[Music]
I love getting more and more interesting
not a little
oh
damn
another kill for me
that's reinforcements I'll stay here
unfortunatia I'll just heal
[Music]
I can't even mend her
I was creating when it doesn't matter
yeah today is
something something weird is going on
[Music]
foreign
I'm sorry you had to see that
I'm happy I had to see that
but that I'm sorry I had to see that
level up that was kind of [\h__\h]
final fight
[Music]
food
not enough to reach connect okay one
second one chick
couldn't just hold the line
how much damage do you do to Celine
probably too much
nothing oh yeah he doesn't have a like a
was it a handful
[Music]
foreign
okay I think I'll just stay here
[Music]
my God I am so powerful
one
[Music]
doing well
today we're so smart to equip those ax
guys with tomahawks but they couldn't
spend a short bow on these archers on
horses
damn
[Music]
Chris
fold nothing back
foreign
well if this is an indie Army
what's the major Army then are we we
aren't the major Army even though are we
[Music]
the only two units that I would be in
not without Chris
[Music]
Savion
what's Revelations and radiant done
[Music]
yeah okay I have a major Army okay okay
if you guys say so
congratulations
[Music]
I could even try to hit them from here
huh
try
67 ain't even that bad
[Music]
other FB games oh
I maybe want to dance with somebody
but I don't know
I wanna dance with
[Music]
me
I gotta make my skin I'll make my
schedule tomorrow by the way oh oh yeah
wait my brother is also coming tomorrow
again
um he's staying over for another night
because he's gotta go check out an
apartment
[Music]
magician's not good for movie years
okay
interesting choice
[Music]
sounds like a busy tomorrow well what
I'm hoping for is that I can take a nap
after the recording because there's no
way I can get a good amount of sleep
so I wanna sleep afterwards I hope my
brother doesn't disturb me thank you
oh but also he's gonna help me this time
installed Sims because last time we
wanted to do that but then it got so
late after building all that furniture
[Music]
ah the Ally can act but can't move so
like for example they could use a staff
or so for example is that what that is
or I could like make a dance or dance
again to the person right next to them
[Music]
I might as well do that
you don't get someone to heal someone
can't make a dance dance I tried oh okay
can you do anything but move
Chloe Chloe has a staff now all right
she's a staff now right I give her a
stop now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh oh yeah right she has a men
well I mean take it
I'm learning I'm learning and I didn't
know about this in the first place so
by the way he can also heal
[Music]
there we go there we go we're looking
pretty good now in terms of health my
good friend
and killed enemies
yes
[Music]
doesn't matter to me hi Chris do you
have a ring did you not get any new
rings
potential wasted
he doesn't have a ring huh
only ring left is bails oh for real I
took them all now oh damn
[Music]
nothing personal I'm merely following
lady Veil don't talk to the devil
they're just a double
he doesn't get it she was deceived
April Fools
20. oh
the way it moves is so cute
oh yeah
bye
this is
and also my right team is like kind of
all too far
but
[Music]
it's pretty decent
it's Excalibur range only two
let's see how much damage I would do
though
oh not really
[Music]
was that a crit
is that a crit
[Music]
she mad oh
I'm already taking SHP bar from the
sidelines
[Music]
yeah I think I'll do that
oh
what do you mean we're cigarette
well did I I didn't give anyone secret I
think or did I
think I ended up not
because we couldn't decide on who to
give it to
Selena's cigarette
Celine so in so far guys
[Music]
but I don't know I don't know how to get
it around that if I dance then she would
probably still not be able to get around
them I mean maybe around the left
ah from here
[Music]
they lined up so nicely this is the
first time it works really well for me
[Music]
raise your sword
Killswitch first why
[Music]
would lemon sort of been much much much
much better I mean this is fine too she
broke a lot of them too
I remember when
who was it who was it we've used that
all the time on me
much better work worth going back in
time for maybe because this map is small
should I
[Music]
ah An Elegant okay
do you want me to finish first off so I
thought I see why I see why
uh please
foreign
thinking it's all so funny
where is she oh here
that also helps with her catching up on
the team so that's really good please
thank God as well
[Music]
I mean the ride is being kills the mage
it's not that much better
also the writer's been breaks two of
them guys
[Music]
while I get no kills with 11 sword
no no we're at this bed is better huh
[Music]
but at least I'm getting more damage on
on the other on the grace
pliers and yeah a little bit more but
they're not broken and they're still
alive I think
I was maybe this will go for the Riders
vein yeah look I need to kill and broken
helps me more I think
[Music]
this was worth it
okay
beautiful
[Music]
ah that was satisfying
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay
oh wait what Grace already so dead
again
rest
but the Mage I think I want to go for
the mage
somebody else can finish Grace
[Music]
oh
that's okay for me
I'm sorry
he's dead he's so done
[Music]
I'm a bit scared of this boy
but he can't move that fast it's okay
it's okay
just a scratch oh wait they have so many
Flyers oh and I have a Crest I wish I
was a writer's Bane for for both so that
I could just shoot straight through them
in a line as well another round has been
override would be cool
hmm
it does
ah the steel boat does
[Music]
excuse me
if you didn't I had no choice
[Music]
what
a bit scared of all the other flyers
ah where's fogado
they're okay
who do you choose wait wait can finish
that one let's see
what can you do
huh
come and face me
[Music]
ah maybe I'll
dance alchrist
s oh true
[Music]
damage
nice thank you
wait that was it
I already had her down so many HP bars
I thought she was gonna have one more
okay
[Music]
so we only have Veil left
my God
[Music]
and we have one more double illusion or
a double standing around as well
attack Snappy with Chris
and Grace with mavier oh it's too late
now
I took the opportunity
[Music]
hard to stand
Chris ah Your Grace is still there ah
wait with who what did she say oh he was
basically dead he should be dead
with Mommy yeah okay okay fine bye bye
bye
yeah but look
he could also kill this one oh wait I
don't want her hair
[Music]
um
I can see this is how I would use
hurry for the best results
dialogue over optimal play
now
look at the dialogue and then rewind yay
optimal place okay
dialogue I don't really care it's not
gonna be that special is it
oh
see that too I don't know
okay
maybe I'll dance more beer
we can talk about that
traitor don't worry
dare you speak her name I will kill you
quickly you'll be buried before you feel
any pain
[Music]
feel worth it
death means no more pain
and who needs that
I oh I know it's never that wimp it guys
it never is
oh okay
that's not even worth dancing for
I'm not a cheerleader man
not your personal cheerleader
oh I think that I found myself
I'll apologize later
good stuff though
good stuff
[Music]
I'm sorry eh
okay I thought you apologize for missing
Maybe
please do not miss
wait I haven't even
[Music]
I can't go back now but it's okay we
already killed two bosses we're good
[Music]
wrote In fact
yeah yeah those are
maybe worth it maybe
[Music]
well now I don't have a optimal play for
her but oh well
[Music]
I guess I'll just try catching up here
maybe do a dragon vein for whatever
reason
ah it can't even fit me in
so sad
[Music]
God damn it
nah I should have danced with bilaf
after all
ah
should have danced
well at least one of them will go for
the illusionary double
thank you
[Music]
fine I really thought yeah I think I'm
good too I mean it's almost over
oh I'm up there
oh
kill this one
[Music]
need help
okay I'm in I left one wanted to pull
God or maybe yeah bye
[Applause]
for you oh Chris incoming oh
can you have a double crit
when you hit twice is that possible
worth it worth it worth it worth it
taking all that time bye bye fogado
thanks though thank you
I'm not Invincible it's possible I
wouldn't say that
I never saw that happening I think
Moana
even more okay I will now rush to Dale
I hope I I don't think I can you can't
reach probably
um
[Music]
oh I can reach that Thief though
does this thing give them some extra
Powers oh yeah
[Music]
I feel and avoid
do it yeah okay
guys
not good
oh she only missed one
[Music]
hmm
you're a little way here
[Music]
oh Celine
is it worth it taking him on right now
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
Celine is moving down
kill the feet and counter out
[Music]
I am sorry
eleven
yeah I will be the bait we don't want
kiwava to be the only bait
um
[Music]
I had no choice but to win
thank you question mark
foreign
I think vamos means
let's go
right
I got it I can speak Espanol
[Music]
should have danced
I kind of want to dance
I want to dance like uh four people
I just need to get them in a cross shape
[Music]
my chemo she will go and stand here
perhaps
so someone here someone here
um Chloe Chloe will be doing
[Music]
what Chloe
those should be healing
[Music]
cut
what do you mean I'm one square short
I mean
short of what
I can't reach she can't reach
oh okay I'll put someone else there
it's okay
so
[Music]
oh
and see though
I could
I be on this side
[Music]
or uh no yeah yeah um
meat Shield
[Music]
contemplative uh-huh
but yeah I'm just that's just you know
that's just humans being humans
[Music]
I can like dance for example Hortensia
move on with her already
now
and then one now
wait I can move see though
here but it's never end result the same
as well I'll just can't see it all to
dance someone but I just might as well
isn't this like the same results
[Music]
answer after she dances
oh
[Music]
my God
where's Celine
this is Celine red okay okay
[Music]
yeah I'm still not sure if I should go
for the FIFA Selena for the
big big
ugly monster on the right side
[Music]
I will go for the monsters
because sounds fun
okay one down and we get a cool song
wow wow
oh yeah she is they're all pretty
they're all pretty
[Music]
foreign
how far does fire breath go
probably far enough
[Music]
but quick maybe quick maybe quick maybe
quick
no quick maybe not
[Music]
the more I move the strong I go oh
who's here
[Music]
and I still don't use tea man
okay
baby
[Music]
we're almost done
oh last but not least
oh
ah 54.
54.
[Music]
oh how I wanted to find you oh how I
want it but good dialogue that we want
to see Mira's pet
the whimpering pathetic worm
you are not
mine and you're not mine
Veil is
give her back no you know you Veil and
I'll prove it here and now by destroying
you
[Music]
it's 72 close to arrest damage 72
I think we have to rewind
um
[Music]
I guess we'll see what happens because
you know that was the last move
There Is No Escape
effective damage the Dragon
okay
maybe hopefully she doesn't go for
kiwawa because just chihuahua cannot die
[Music]
zero damage hero hit zero crit good job
dude last decision
oh
okay bye-bye I'll Crush you
should have given me
maybe instead of dancing meat should I
just give myself the
[Music]
um
the HP storm just in case and she can
kill someone else I don't care
um
[Music]
where did it happen she held down to him
I'll do that
emblem
koala
at all costs you must survive
for the greater Goods please
[Music]
ah where did she stand
it doesn't really matter I guess
[Music]
protection there we go
now what will happen now
Unforgettable
this is my Redemption
have I made a difference
anymore
my time with the four hounds is behind
me what a deal two for one protect you
same as ever mavier you won't
acknowledge me
you won't even say my name well don't
worry I haven't forgotten your reward
how about a swift death I will sacrifice
anything everything to save lady fail
from you give me strength when a hero
when a white knight literally oh my God
I love him yeah he's not even gonna die
I think
a percentage chance on him damn
he even survived that too oh
I thought it was over for him
he's a definition of a tank wow
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay okay okay okay okay okay oh is that
really necessary thank you
putting a lot of pressure on me here
okay what's really effective against
bail
[Music]
what is
that review again
ah directional Roar
nah okay
does it have range note
who are you looking at the me in front
of you or the me from before
I've made my choices
that's good
for now
um
ideally
we have to take her down in one turn
I'll protect you
[Music]
of course
he's easy I can
turn Max but I want to do it in One
Direction
[Music]
oh she only has a 48 hit chance
wow okay
[Music]
but wait is it the same dialogue as what
we had before
DreamWorks probably right
same one okay
I will stand here
who can do some cool stuff let's see
engage
like
Twin Strike
all right all right all right dance with
Chihuahua
I mean dance boy that's yeah yeah I
wanted to do that
cool
I'm gonna do that right away
mine
where's my dancer
he's my dancer
my dancer
are we humans
ah this one see though oh we dancers
are we dragons
oh are we dancers
oh my hands are cold and I'm on my knees
begging for the arms that will combined
with twin strikes I will take another HP
bar
are we human
or are we dancing oh I think that was
even a crit in there because her oh and
then I mean
I mean guess I could could somebody
dance me again
who's the one who can give me an action
without me uh you know but but without
me moving I'll just stand right here
so I can buy love
I can't reach
yeah okay that's fine
the Twin Strike was gonna be us I think
yeah that's no that's kind of always
wait wait wait wait that's kind of
always
doesn't do that much damage so I think
I'll go with him
I'll apologize
mm-hmm
and that's it one last HP bar of course
now checkmate
[Music]
could do it
but wait then can kind of really do it
yeah yeah he could at 100
okay if we have that guarantee then I
wanna get some other exp here yes
[Music]
oh
brother he would die
I'm waiting
ah um
oh great sacrifice gives the
stream yeah
that's okay
it's trying to get a little bit
here and there and everywhere
full level damn
[Music]
let's see
that would be a beautiful line but oh
well
all flowers eventually wilt
nice
[Music]
see this kind of stuff this is important
too
this is important too
oh I can't even know that
to make sure not to fill the box right
away don't get too eager how awful
is the second seal oh okay
Celine means the second field remind me
remind me about that
[Music]
six hours no five hours 40 minutes so
far this will feel that long yet to me
but it's already what's 8 30 damn
how do I turn these things off again
how did I turn them on
thank you
all right here we go
I
okay Bill
[Music]
y
victory is mine oh only only seven turns
but the map was kind of small but it had
three bosses yo
[Music]
what
it's like a punched her in her eye why
are you here oh
which is that's normal
oh fail
it's really you isn't it this doesn't
make sense her changing back wasn't
supposed to be possible
up the enchanted helmet
it's correct marnie's attack worked
Marnie
such bravery
Castle you've been under zephia's
control
her mind you have to die really bad
and
wait a second
what am I hearing
and where did I get this ring what a
cute fit though
this is yours right
I remember we were near the cathedral
you said it was important to you here
please thank you
I will not allow it
oh
[Music]
you need me well though defective
daughter of mine
Papa
Michael is so close I can taste it the
apple does fall really far from the
Train sometimes
no
no and reclaim my emblem rings at once
they don't look alike
the [\h__\h] well then there is nothing more
you can do for me so pretty
and I have never been in the habit
of keeping that which has no value
foolish child
twice now I have struck you down
but I promise you
no amount of sleep will bring you back
well I got to play Veil now instead this
time your defeat is final
oh
I did what I had to do to keep you out
of Harm's Way I meant I'm into two
groups like me for a while
completely wrong I wasn't there for you
so sorry Phil for all those awful things
I don't care I don't care that
don't be all right there's still so much
I have to do
because I'll not die until I've told you
everything
there's still too much left
I'm here
and she dies exactly right before that
word that one word she couldn't get it
out yeah
huh
Chihuahua no you can't
leave me
don't leave me
now there is nothing to stand in my way
the Divine dragon is
let's see this day
but how how could this
dragon from Whole Life Ian will be now
replaced by Veil hope you're happy guys
why would
swaywood creatures another of my
children the one you've been searching
for all this time your sister
huh
the Divine Dragon took the traitor
enough in the events of the last war
thus the fool did survive
no child of mine should live as a Divine
Dragon death was this one's inexorable
fate
break
time you're my sister I
heard you I finally found you
oh I don't understand why you would
sacrifice yourself because she is your
sister you dumb dumb
[Music]
all 12 of the Rings are finally in my
possession
no those Rings belong to my sister their
friends
[Music]
together their power is so great
granted once every thousand years and
now that unrivaled power is mine
good um cutscene
Subs were a little bit delayed there
[Music]
and it may see no work memories
he should put the rings on his little
nails there
oh you're such a big boy but they grow
up so fast
Daddy
peace
please know
oh how big you gonna get
okay
oh he's been casted for a Game of
Thrones now he's out of here
as you know has a dragon
bye bye
good for you guys have one second
holy [\h__\h]
oh
that wait if you're gonna remind
shouldn't we rewind so far back that
where he doesn't have the ring
or are we gonna be lame and go to a
point after he got the Rings
[Music]
because we wanted to be more difficult
for us
wait the game's not ending right after
what's coming now possible
great long restored
where are you going
you've destroyed everything
you killed your own child this is what
you were going to tell you looks like
it's over for you all when the game was
plenty long Cynthia lady defect
you survived here only because of all
those who came to your Aid what a shame
four more because now it's time
[Music]
farewell
lady fail
I don't come on I heard it happened
wrong but Marnie broke the helmet oh
Mario Simple Mario
it was only cracked that's certainly
weakened it but with Lord sombron's
elevation to power the helmet Works far
better than before
lady Veil come on out
join us if you would
no resist
you must resist
[Laughter]
girl father
how far does it take a hat off
finally done it I wanted to kill the
Divine Dragon myself
but oh well lady Vale
Lord sombron will gladly Listen
to You Back would have had to cure you
can resist any kind of strong magic
return to father
of course
yeah I figured you'd say that
we all know
as for all of you
death is inevitable maybe she's like but
I'd like this mess dealt with now
mail
clean this up you're not faking it you
just so quickly crank back into evil
yeah
[Music]
they'd be useless to you the Divine
Dragon
none of you have the ability to summon
emblems
the end we have no way out so who wants
to die first there's no need for any of
you to squirm or struggle you're all
about to join your beloved Divine dragon
we all going to die here
there must be something we can do
talking to me I'm dead guy dude
dead
I'm dead hello
why are you still asking a dead body for
help
more cutscene let's go
you need to strike me down
yo she's got a super smart look
oh
even as evil mama
more or less evil like she looks evil
Mommy why are you here all by yourself
the war is finally over mother
you
[Music]
treacherous well my God this game is
kind of brittle sometimes
so pretty Phil dragons have to die in
the end
but I wanted to be
good dragon
[Music]
you will
someday life will return to you
that beautiful day shut down
I will give you a birthday gift that
suits you perfectly
thank you mother
I see that day
maybe your turn dressing white the
gleaming sword at my side
OptiFine Dragon like you oh God
this costume is so good the emotions
here oh
[Music]
that was a really good cutscene
emotional damage
face cracking top notch
it was a memory
where am I
Wawa
Welcome to the
usual room
oh
I must have died protecting Veil there's
no waking up again this time
I had dreamed I would awaken as a hero
only now I realize
that did happen
but
it's too late I wonder if I'll be able
to find mother here
mother
Mommy
fail
why are you here Papa used the Rings to
raise gradline
the helmet reactivated
my head began to swim
and then
I was here things didn't go how I wanted
them to
and now it seems I've died
you're my big sister
you gave your life to protect me I'm so
sorry
you should have let me die don't say
that
are rewinding forget you have a link
back home there's still a chance for you
no
no more
I tried so hard
I wanted Papa to look at me and not see
a defect I wanted him to forget about
the other worlds and just be with me I'd
always think
if only I tried harder but it never
mattered
I kept getting crushed over and over
seems outside that will ruin my weekend
and fail once more I'd rather it just
end here
with you hey
why don't we fall asleep
together
the world will end with or without us
and
I feel happy because I finally found you
maybe the others will join us eventually
really perhaps really well then except
hmm
I'm not ready to give up
I want to save our world
and everyone I care about fail [\h__\h] the
world LOL
and I understand why you feel the way
you do
you do but please don't give up
not before you experience the life you
deserve I don't care anymore
even if I returned and survived all of
it I can't stop Papa because I can't
summon emblems all I can do is create
the corrupted
a fallibility befitting a fell Dragon
corrupted fail
there is something you can do
revive me as one of the corrupted
to King hyacinth
it was as if he'd come back to life
return to himself perhaps I could go
back y'all are going crazy now maybe but
you aren't thinking this through don't
bet hate they're gonna look so ugly
terrify you now you want to be one
we do that
we'll never be able to change better
this way
at least you died as yourself
would you really want to die as one of
them I'll sacrifice more than that if it
saves everyone
how I die doesn't matter but do I get
like my own character design please end
this war like a skin whatever I can
Chihuahua corrupted skin please don't
give up fail at least come on if we
don't just put me in a [\h__\h] bunny to me
this is the only way forward
prevail
what do you live for that is so weird
my friends told me it doesn't matter
where you're from
important
it's how you live how you live and what
you do shapes your future
who do you want to become I've never
thought about that
but if it were possible for me to change
now I suppose
I'd want to be like you
I'd want to become a dragon who saves
the world
they really are siblings
I
a long time ago let's go back and save
our world
together all right I'll give it one last
try
I hope to see you soon
Mr you're my dear sister okay okay I
trust you get her out of here now
[Laughter]
stop stop
lady fail please come back to us oh you
miss her mavier then I'll kill you first
maybe you'll find what you're after on
the other side
huh
lady fail he's giving birth
do you
right oh I'm not going quietly
[Music]
not herself exactly
the true lady Veil she's fighting back
I know that my sister believed in me
so I I believe in myself
shut your mouth you are nothing but a
defense like Gollum mark my words you
quivering little baby you're gonna be
dead
wait there's already a crack in it I'll
break it I can't be me again you
[Music]
oh oh it's still coming he doesn't care
it's time now Time to Say Goodbye
made out of style before I'm just like
Loveless
oh
finally
it was about to oh Chihuahua dead on the
ground
[Music]
it's all right I messed up again
I wish
I'd have done something
I'm so sorry but you did it all on your
own I put you're wrong about me doing it
alone
my sister helped me
[Music]
the Divine Dragon they're managing to
get me a little bit hyped here
good job
[Music]
Guardians of the underworld
cast aside the rules
[Music]
right
I'm just normal
I imagine normal that's boring
you can't leave
I'm just normal
it's a no difference
[Music]
Divine one has become corrupted
not even like a below right
please everyone what was this
questioning if she could fight me
there's nothing to fear
it won't hurt you I asked Veil to revive
me as one of the corrupted You Must
Believe Me
but are you really you yes
I'm the same person who took this
journey with you the Divine Dragon
whatever form I take but what makes her
what makes her corrupted though
she just look what I found revived
normally one ring probably yeah one ring
and my DLC rings
a Slime by your side as though it wanted
to be with you the emblems in the 12
rings have played their roles
you're like the dream of power once
again I lost my [\h__\h] Rings
unbelievable so much today
now
it's my turn all right Martha
I've returned
I'm here for you
you're still showing on an emblem of
beginnings
[Applause]
nothing happened
no that's what makes her corruptive has
to work
I have so much to protect
ORS
join me once more I'll show you an
emblem of beginnings
[Music]
oh no he doesn't
he was on the toilet guys
so happy to see you
you can't speak because yeah
I used Val Dragon power to raise my
sister
using that same power to summon
wow
all right what happened
you're reacting to the emblem time is
short
need your help to summon all the emblems
again you don't have to trust me but
this is the only way you must stand
together and fight as one
yeah that was a good uh
continuation of many many cutscenes
finally you know a good amount of story
at once
[Music]
the rings are on this map
hmm
let me see I'm not sure if I'm gonna do
this
I'm going down
I'm not sure how long would this take
this looks like pretty big quite a lot
of effort at least like two hours
[Music]
judging by how long the other Maps take
me
shaft is a bit hard
let's say it's not long
easy map it's just for stories though
shortest and easiest map in the game
okay
okay I can do it but
since I have to get up so early tomorrow
that would mean I don't think I would
read Super Chat
um
Fuel and now I'll schedule a Super Chat
reading for the next week but I also
need to schedule I mean before I forget
you can already like
schedule like a image only so I don't
forget
you know one second let me just put it
into the
[Music]
found out for the story yeah I want to
see that too
me too me too
okay
Super Chat
and members okay it's in there oh also a
Boston anime Boston's next week
[Music]
okay
yeah
[Music]
Empire for members you mean what Star
Wars movie we can
yeah I'm doing I'm hosting if all goes
well I'm hosting a VR Easter stream
for
Easter
but I probably won't be the only one
streaming it
[Music]
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
I'm like I'm working on it
very nervous about it
hey I'm not sure as I have to like do it
so that it doesn't overlap with Anime
Boston I probably won't do it at like a
an a prime time even though it's really
[\h__\h] for me
and then sleep after and then go to
Anime Boston so probably like between
8th and 9th
that night time
do you have horse units why is it good
how's it look you just rushed to these
and then interact and then
[Music]
move on
for you and your friends yes
foreign
[Music]
oh that's the armor of the horse
suddenly zebra unit
fire and Zoo
let's just keep the same team that I had
before oh yeah
okay
I think I might switch up more of the
air sorry wait I can't I have to use the
same team all right
my main skill change
oh oh
okay well then the only thing I can
really do is change places
so
let me
do it like
[Music]
I guess and let me save did I say it I
probably already saved
we are officially over 70 hours of play
time
oh can I do that like now
is that a thing I can do now and on the
who anyway
what was I supposed to give it to
uh
[Music]
Celine
oh
[Music]
um
uh
oh
mind blowing oh
looking great as always
should I move some of my existing DLC
Rings over
should I get all am I getting all my
rings back here
or just some
do it okay
Wawa has Marv
I'll just have her keep Marv
[Music]
um
I don't know
we have idle guard even
middle card yeah
all of my ring was sorting again
can't believe you're making me do that
again
foreign
Hector
[Music]
Hector on cogitsu
I suppose Hector let's go let's go
it's just temporary
[Music]
I add the bond rings
for long
[Music]
ah wait I only have
what is the Titania titanium attack
speed
dude
gold marine
[Music]
so much
so much thinking required again
I just want magic unlock
speed luck oh I think I'll give that to
someone else
strength
look at that unicorn
speed luck yo
[Music]
yeah I am I'm also thanking my do I
really need to do this because we'll
just we'll just pick up those two rings
run away
[Music]
thank you
okay whatever
Oh I thought it stood for a captain but
no corrupted kiwawa
crap koala must stand
forever
hi hi okay is that all of my rings
why are they
the emblem rings have been stopped I
just dropped them please sister get
close to a ring and Trace why would he
why would that dude be so careless about
that did he not believe I could like
get them back
oh no no no no no
that's so careless
um
[Music]
yes
yeah
I feel like we're so zoomed out
I will protect everyone I have no choice
but to win oh crit
is back at it again
[Music]
verily
Connecticut
from Connecticut
[Music]
I hope this is really as short as you
guys said it was going to be
[Music]
a dragon right there running rich for me
and my Longbow perfect
[Music]
choice is yours
okay
[Music]
the dance
would be one to five hours for you
though no I'm gonna hurry I don't care I
don't care
no matter okay if I lose some units
whatevs give me strong foes
[Music]
okay Martin maybe I will not take down
that little dragon
[Music]
let the Carnage begin
sacrifice yes sacrifice yourselves for
the great quinoa which is now just a
corrupted but let's not tell them Bobby
you're reporting let's not tell them
because they probably
want to play with me otherwise Count On
Me
I'm just like you guys I'm corrupted now
I'm listening how could I even prove it
though
I look the same
no mistakes sadly
[Music]
what
the [\h__\h]
a lot of damage
I
[Music]
guess
I'll pull back for now
sorry horty for putting you into this
position
[Music]
damn gold Mary standing strong over
there oh
okay another reason to rewind
huh yeah
yep
I'll apologize later
oil Crystal did a good job all right all
right
okay another reason
was that the closest one the closest
Dragon there
Alfredo wow what's up
a new record
thank God I can still rewind
I go back all the way here sorry about
that so that was so unexpected a little
bit underestimated everything
[Music]
oh
might as well engage
emblem engage
morning good morning
guys
oh thank you giving awesome
Stones some pretty Stones Some Pebbles
once one
Chihuahua is fine I'll give one to
laughs
I want to make use of these very few
bracelets and things that I have right
now
[Music]
wait so what went wrong here is the is
Hortensia
right
oh yeah because I danced her and then I
went on to attack some of them
which wasn't as good as I thought it was
gonna be
[Music]
um
I could dance ivy
or
you knock out or just no one or more
beer
mmm
she could still die yeah
sure she could
so
I don't know how careful I gotta be
[Music]
a gold Mary gold Mary too
yeah but gold Mary
[Music]
unless I would have rewinded to
where she moved I don't think I can
really do much now
thank you
[Music]
see that I'll drop that to the dragon
the one down there the this one
okay
[Music]
a hide I go I have not even here even
here
I'll give it one more try
I'll take I'll take another step back
um
[Music]
oh I can help here
no kill though
better than nothing
from here I can't attack
right
missed
ah I'm worried
okay
[Music]
foreign
I love you but uh
[Music]
I just want to live in peace I rewind
again
hey
I have no choice but the right way to do
it
on this map
stick together move down the middle
[Music]
okay
series of battle for those battle
what
which one
[Music]
I don't understand though
tap one
[Music]
ah
okay
yeah I guess we'll just stay in one
group okay
ah because it's like two back to back so
that oh oh there okay that would have
reset
back to the other one too oh no
come on come on come on we have to do
this
this is already the way I put everything
together right
so I will go
foreign
I
think I'll protect you
go go right side
[Music]
come and face me
my will is firm
what are you doing
I hear you
[Music]
all right
where's my dancer
the stage is mine
we're too right away
um
I'll be here
of course and I'll be you
whatever you need this will take a
little while
[Music]
foreign
yeah I was just like no
I'll go straight for the middle
really stubborn
strategy
I work ready spaghetti Count On Me
[Music]
shut that no they're just falling asleep
just like me it's getting tired too
[Music]
just chilling
and guys what should I talk about ah
is there something to talk about
I'm at work I believe I am in the right
hope it's going well today
all right we heard you meet kobo's Mom
yeah when did you hear that
I did
she say that
I met her mom and her brother
I mean we didn't like talk much
at all
basically I shook hands
that's basically it I think ah well her
mom seems to be pretty up to date about
how things are
so and like what kind of person I am to
Kobo
so I said um
what'd they say something like yeah
[Music]
I guess she's my daughter now no no I
don't remember but something hinting at
that relationship
no it wasn't awkward I wouldn't say it
was awkward
your daughter calls me Mommy too
I didn't say that no no no maybe I
should have said no I don't know I
didn't want to like I want I don't know
what kind of person she was so I didn't
know if I could crack a joke but
all right
it all happened so fast
yes it is I was like preparing some data
collecting some data for
one of the oh official problems that I'm
doing
and I had to count how many countries
wow I visited so far
and because I couldn't think of all of
them on the top of my head so I went
through like a list where you can like
select every country that you've been to
but I've been to 17 countries holy [\h__\h]
I didn't think it was that much
seven
seventeen
I think that is if you include Vatican
City
which I'm not sure if you should be
including but you know
Ah that's a lot
I was surprised too
yo kiwawa misses worldwide
[Music]
no not as a flight
I had to stop you
right again counts really well it's
basically easily
fiddle of Rome it's so small I'm not
even I don't I don't think I would
normally count it when I say I've been
to Italy and I've been to Italy
I didn't even do much
didn't you just stay for that long but I
did not count was like countries that
I've stayed like
that I've you know been through because
of Transit
um
even the one where I stayed 24 hours in
transit
even that I did not count
[Music]
it's been like the 24 hours one you
could almost count though
foreign
couldn't I take that
let's be careful
indeed let's be careful
you have to stand on top of it
can you can I stand on top of it
has to do the first step
only quinoa as his approached first
[Music]
for every single one of them
like
[Music]
um
I'll apologize later
ah okay
[Music]
ah don't know if I wanna
have the ones from the left side come
over
[Music]
okay
I'll be waiting
yeah what else
um in terms of topics
what else what else is there
my brain is so empty
little brain
I need you girl I know what to say
we had fun
[Music]
I had fun
I don't know what to say about that and
unfortunately girls
I mean I met all of them
before except Pomo
um
[Music]
the members only
um
[Music]
illustration
the wallpaper
yeah I revealed that I
um I got hormones illustrator to do it
[Music]
I had that in the works
for a little while
[Music]
and it's simple enough themed after this
season
the beautiful beautiful
Sakura season so if I don't forget after
the stream I'll upload it otherwise I'll
upload it tomorrow
are you guys using the wallpapers at all
or not
[Music]
yeah you are oh thank you
I'm too good
using fiber and marching rotation right
now
[Music]
I'm glad it's getting some good use
nice soup
hmm
the hero that I summoned stays until it
dies
oh no until my thingy runs out right no
no wait a little bit more every next
turn
[Music]
I'm also using my wallpapers and my
members wallpapers as wallpapers by the
way because they're so pretty
[Music]
I really like them
oh this was not not the best
oh maybe now I should engage
maybe I'm good
[Music]
oh
should I go absolutely random I close my
eyes
you guys say stop say stop when you
wanted me to stop
he wants ax let's hope we're getting ax
stop
okay wait say it say it again
[Music]
I totally heard you saying stuff
some fun guys
oh sniper fabrication all right all
right all right okay a sniper against a
sniper here what
it's got a steel bow
all right
I was really lucky with that five star
wasn't I
[Music]
yeah but we can we can kill this guy
[Applause]
made a difference this sniper is
probably better than forgoto don't you
dare say that well did Pete hears you
um
oh
nice
mwah
well they're all coming I got that my
sniper's still alive
can shoot down one of the Griffins is
that a griffin
[Music]
okay Wawa
would you do us the honor huh
what
how does it work
or is it just that coincidentally her
reach is just not enough at waiting
[Music]
teach us emblem of the academy
leave a cross
all three of them Oh I thought you had
to stand right next to each single one
of them that would have been annoying
[Music]
but does that take up their whole move
yeah well then I'll prefer to First
clean up here maybe
yeah
foreign
I really like their new one I got really
hooked on it
[Music]
well
well they can still attack I think
release some others say no
I guess we'll test it out with one of
them with whom who do we have we have
Lynn and biliff and Lucina
oh
it doesn't matter for now
[Music]
it's too many rings anyway
what if I just leave them on the ground
I'll get them back anyway right
I ask that you joined
dot dot
one
the ones but I can't talk to another one
it
and what but I already picked up one
okay you can hold multiple but only use
the first one don't okay
[Music]
okay the ones who already have emblems
shall fight
[Music]
I'm sorry
um you're stuck with the one you picked
up okay
[Music]
I hear audio crackling
no maybe with panette will go here
otherwise it's gonna be a little bit
annoying oh and even look for index you
could do it
[Music]
um
I will take the killer axle if we're
lucky
[Music]
I'm sorry you had to see that
she is such a genius
[Music]
incredible she's like a
Miracle child
all right what do I do with you you
can't reach anywhere maybe I dance
although Seattle has no
not that he can read maybe he gets one
on the left side
[Music]
Prodigy yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's what she is
black
not really worth going over here
[Music]
Hector's uh
yeah that's that I don't like them ah
stupid
[Music]
oh wait wolf file is nice
in my mess too
[Music]
Mr marnell you are telling me lies
I am not playing so great so far
no no no
and then
[Music]
I wanted to give Lynn to Alquist
but right now
I think it's just important to optimize
anyways
[Music]
I just want to get them out of the way
everybody
you know what I'll give Lucina too no
she has Tiki
all these are can't recognize any of
them
foreign
[Music]
wait 75 is really good
that's pretty good
Gotta Throw Them from afar they'll be
like what the [\h__\h] where did that come
from
like a prank call Ivy the Prank Caller
the rain jazz
I
feel like I should have done it on this
one though
that was my ideal
outcome but hey wait but Vail doesn't
have cancer
and that's not a really safe position
there
[Music]
Selena however can't reach
and I already danced
[Music]
I hate this stuff okay
I shall take Lucina with Veil
[Music]
I know it makes no sense probably
ah what
I don't know
and then I'll pick up Lynn probably with
gold Mary
[Music]
gold married
most people agree this map is annoying
annoying
no no no
it's not very satisfying
[Music]
one damage wow
yeah you could use them right away
I think I could get behind that
idea and supported
yeah oh yeah one more thing I wanted to
do this week is let me put that else in
my um schedule Korean
Korean stream
Korean learning stream
because this coming week I don't have a
Korean lesson
it might be kind of a weird week next
week because I also oh my God look at
them I also want to take two weeks uh
two weeks off two days after five of
them so Monday because I'll be working
on Monday but I want a proper day off
too I mean I never really have proper
day offs but you know what I mean
[Music]
when does she do a square when she's
next to who
I go Hector or what
how many time for the weekend no no no
no no no no no no I'm streaming on the
weekend
Mike
do I have Ike right now I have a Hector
I don't think I have Ike
[Music]
not yet huh
I kiss
Ed huh
[Music]
I'll do the fire thing anyway now
are we down
foreign
[Music]
maybe I can only take one day off like
the Monday where I'll be working
[Music]
I can probably do Korean learning stream
on the same day as a member stream
one in the early in the day and the
members later in the day
I'll I'll figure something out
[Music]
foreign
let's do this first
[\h__\h]
sorry to trouble you after all you've
been you're mine just a little more all
right you're mine now Lynn
accepted I you can't say anything anyway
no complaints accepted
I am fine
are you really you don't seem so fine
[Music]
oh my God
I'll just take up this one and then take
my leaves
quietly
[Music]
after talking but you can't swing move
right away that's so annoying thing
like I can't even go that far back
I might create a vein of fog afterwards
that sounded like a huge wall of enemies
[Music]
Mamma Mia
doesn't matter
[Music]
so does that poison the one next awful
is that what it was called
a vein of poisoned
[Music]
the range the rage purple
Veil a veil of poison yeah yeah
[Music]
oh misunderstanding
I won't dance with someone who comes
from far behind
[Music]
but
look
[Music]
I need a group dance
wait
you've got bailiff
not buy love
if I dance here it was by love
I have a cross of people around me
[Music]
cup
s
[Music]
hey
oh that's just stupid
[Music]
I can quit you
so that was really worth me taking my
DLC stuff because those I can actually
use
[Music]
oh man
sorry I'm being really indecisive again
[Music]
are you here
what
[Music]
oh a fire right away
cool land maybe better can I go from
them
why not
[Music]
now
no distance
[Music]
or or
this way I got three of them
but
[Music]
one second
okay
[Music]
hmm
and the rest cannot do anything
basically
it's so sad
[Music]
I think Ivy could do something I think
Ivy could do something
Yahoo
she can kill this one
cook let her cook
speaking of cooking I'm gonna use all of
those
ingredients
from yesterday to make some tuna corn
pasta I know some people are gonna be
like eh weird on us are you not gonna
think that's weird if it's not a pizza
but it's just a pasta
tuna pasta maybe more acceptable than
tuna Pizza
for some reason
[Music]
let us see too oh it's not gonna be that
special
[Music]
yeah
I don't like tuna either way yeah that's
surprising because even someone like me
who oh dude
[Music]
doesn't like seafood
generally
love the tuna
did I tell you about my my favorite
frozen pizza changing its recipe Dream
well and now not tasting so good anymore
so I don't get it anymore
and the other pizzas also kind of all
change so now I never know what the
frozen pizza to buy and I'm buying less
frozen pizza which might be a good after
effect for my health
oh
and sweep
yeah yesterday
[Music]
or the day before yesterday I looked
something up about that
if they maybe you know we might consider
changing it back again because of other
people's opinions turns out I am
definitely not the only one with this
opinion there's like this huge drama oh
because this is a huge Pizza brand here
and people
all over Austria and Germany I'm really
pissed they're like tuna Pizza is
absolutely useless now it tastes so much
worse now please change it back and
that's already apparently like I've
noticed the pizza recipe flavor recipe
being changed like
maybe two free months ago I don't know
not so long ago but I saw a lot of this
criticism was already commented like a
year ago so apparently maybe in Germany
or so possibly they already changed it
earlier
so
and even though they only changed it so
early
they still
don't change it back even though I think
they all don't like it restaurant Dr
Edgar yeah
and then on their social media on
Twitter and so on
they are on it saying like oh sorry you
don't like the new flavor then you even
replied so they see it they acknowledge
it
Mia
you're making a big mistake
I wished I would change it back
[Music]
I can't even be for cost reasons because
they kind of added new things to the new
recipe rather than taking things away
see what
hello
this oh
because they added uh onions which in
theory if you go to normal
pizza restaurant or Pizzeria
then I would say
[Music]
hell yeah but for onions on the tuna
pizza that's quite normal that's quite
common
but
but but but but but
not on this one this one was so good the
way it was ah makes me so sad
here they are care for us emblem guys is
it worth to fight the ones that like
followed up in the back
like these ones these ones that kind of
have to kill right
the ones that are really close
onions and barbecue chicken spread yeah
onions are cheap yeah but I mean
characters
yeah I'm sure that even the employees
agree because like the pizza tasted so
good before
okay
they'll come to me though
who is this Celica and Mikaya
I will not lose
[Music]
I'm sorry you had to see that
should have bought 1K for your freezer
yeah like I was thinking back when I
changed the recipe and I tried the it
the first time I was like well this is
[\h__\h] should I like stop by
um more
for my freezer but I wouldn't even have
so much space in my freezer or should I
because they still have some old ones
probably somewhere in the beginning
I was thinking about considering should
I buy some of the old ones
if I could find them should I go look
for them
purposefully
well
well well well
I didn't because somewhere
of 86 you for real though
somewhere in my heart I think I was
hoping
that because I didn't like it and it was
obviously wrong
that they would change it back again but
they're not they're not changing
I don't get it why
why why why why why why why why why
all right
[Music]
so now I'm sad because I'll never ever
have that Godly flavor in my mouth ever
again I don't even know how you would
recreate that at home you know
that kind of pizza you can't recreate
because it's like a frozen pizza
how would you do that
bye people for making it home did you
watch my stream
oh by the way so uh
my pizza friend had a pizza party where
I wasn't even there but they tested
something out there last time they had
their pizza party apparently they tested
out using those frozen pizzas and baking
them in the pizza oven instead of the
normal oven and apparently
no I didn't forget to invite me I think
I was maybe in Japan
but apparently it tasted really
disgusting
so I think it's maybe something like you
know in in normal Pizza Oven it would
take like 12 minutes or so
in a normal oven and then the pizza oven
you have to take it out after like
maximum what four minutes or so because
they got an even stronger Pizza Oven
there than mine
otherwise it will turn black but
uh
[Music]
uh problem
is
if maybe something like if you don't let
it in there for long enough
then perhaps
the flavor cannot unfold how it's
supposed to be unfolding
yeah yeah it's designed to be baked on
our ovens
[Music]
the dough the dough is made to be baked
in that certain way and that's why
there's instructions on the on the
outside as well
oh I can
oh I can attack as long as I don't have
to move huh
wait so it does work but in this case it
doesn't help me do we get the XP for
that though
just a little bit
if someone is in range yeah
[Music]
okay
oh should I help up there
[Music]
one guy was right huh what
ah that one guy
[Music]
give me strong foes for one time only
the one guy
one guide me could have one guide me but
I didn't believe him the one time when
he would have been right
[Music]
can you believe it
oh
[Music]
I'm gonna get the right one guys
let's kill issue
[Music]
I'm hungry now I need something proper
nothing potato chips
[Music]
excuse me I would like to ah 45
I'm sorry
huh
oh yeah wait I don't have to make pasta
today
I have so much I have like four slices
of pizza no free maybe big slices for me
they're big enough I think for dinner
oh
you know I could have also eaten them
for lunch
but
we're not doing that apparently
but ain't nobody got time
[Music]
wow any adult no no after the stream we
made mom we made one more pizza
and just threw as much on there as
possible
Hawaii and tono
wait I didn't look at the person
you're sorry what score Lucia I was
ready to apologize
[Music]
I'm Peter
what do you mean Italian
of course
[Music]
oh my God I haven't watched Family Guy
in such a long time
I've been watching a lot of charms these
days
it's really cringe but it's fun
so having a good time
Overkill
absolute Overkill
[Music]
stop cringe in a fun way yeah
unforgiving I'm almost done with the
first season I think
you know what I did even though I bought
those DVDs I ended up buying like a
digital version anyway at least of the
[Music]
maybe almost all seasons whatever it was
there because it's more comfortable than
having to set up everything
okay who's left you oh
it's more comfortable that way just
having it digitally and I thought they
didn't have it digitally at first and
that's like when I first looked for it
everywhere she didn't have it
and then I found it in some
some like weird service where I had to
upgrade I think I have to upgrade my my
already existing right weird
subscription within Amazon Prime so
another subscription within a
subscription gave me access to be able
to watch charm digitally
I know do you guys have Amazon Prime we
watch stuff on Amazon
like digitally because they have like
all these weird
services
that have like a couple shows no no yeah
yeah
they have some good shows they have a
lot of good medieval history shows
that I was binge watching
um
you're cleaning up nicely
no problem
[Music]
don't want to watch something on Hulu I
have to subscribe your stuff yeah yeah I
had to subscribe to Stars too but I
don't get Hulu from that
I don't wanna do yeah I can't afford
reset the RNG
[Music]
the Bell really should not be there
no way
[Music]
I don't know
you're too kind
[Music]
of services are a scam
there's just too many now when
[Music]
these little marvelous Mrs Mabel maisel
coming out I think in May
[Music]
there's so many y'all
May
[Music]
foreign
like just me choosing something that you
can watch on Amazon Prime I think that
will happen again
probably happen again
did I reset the RNG now
is it reset just because I attacked with
someone else or maybe
Maybe
[Music]
yes it is right
yeah
if not then I'll accept it
I made a difference
[Music]
thank you
for real real
[Music]
and
all right I'm really brute forcing it I
shouldn't be needing so many different
units up there but what the hell
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
let's see how far I can get
today
[Music]
all right now oh my goodness how awful I
mean it's not
it's okay it's not that long we're
almost done surely surely
especially if people like connect are in
the group
taking this
so seriously
putting everything they got into it
with
[Music]
it
all flowers well what weapon does he
have do I get that
it's just
yeah
it looks cool powerful lands of Legend
can strike close or at range yo
looks nice
S rank Lance
yay
I've got you
knuckle
[Music]
was that too much
my panette is the most consistent
Berserker you've ever seen wow
what a compliment
for a Lucia
you messed up the spirit you made plus
five
what loud
the fire can hurt me too right if I
stand in it at the end of the round
[Music]
let's see I think I didn't need kiwawa
down there after all
I always
did that I had to stop you but at least
I'm being careful
[Music]
okay let's use a step
perfect position
cut my good fortune already and viable
by people oh good to know okay
[Music]
am I blind or are there no enemies left
for sure only one up there
which
bogado for once actually
legit things
super helpful
what in what world are we
foreign
[Music]
okay
that's only the ones at the bottom wow I
have to catch
the cats are fighting
[Music]
look wake up
good night
are you sleeping
are you going to sleep
[Music]
good night
a few more fun hopefully not from the
top because I'm leaving the top now
I'm leaving for the top
I'm leaving for the bottom
[Music]
easy kill
for the one and only
[Music]
hmm maybe Chris
here
's gonna be great of course thank you
thank you
[Music]
I will not quite in rings
oh I should use ivy again for some
far away damage
[Music]
is already unengaged okay it was nice
while we had it
Unforgivable
[Music]
hold nothing back
I don't want to waste my Alex here
because I barely have any I gotta go
shopping gotta use that money
I guess using a mend
it's kind of
in the end all the same I'm listening
all right
[Music]
I'm never gonna heal from the cross side
effects because I don't wanna
[Music]
it's Destiny me and Quasar were destined
to be together
thank you
[Music]
oh this is so far away
dangerous
that's it
whatever I'll accept it sorry sorry for
posting you there I was doubting it
while I was doing it I was really
doubting it
me I'm not moving my little pcs one more
step no no no almost maybe I will
[Music]
no I will not
foreign
[Music]
do the thing that you always do
oh sorry you had to see that
didn't get the crit right away but
poisoned the other one and
we lucky
we didn't get the damage come and face
me
[Music]
I just want this to end
your thoughts
it should end when I collect all the
emblems that's the one it should end
now we're getting close good story
though a lot of story progress really
feels like end game you guys are saying
there's only two screens are you guys
sure about that like it feels like
if I do one more stream I mean I mean
[Music]
really yeah no fun you know about that
almost certain
um okay and then we go we won't get to
finish next week though because I don't
think I can schedule two streams
hmm unfortunately
[Music]
Chloe finally gets a hit too wow wow wow
wow wow I mean a kill
simple enough
[Music]
um one extra panel for marriage I've
heard you guys gonna remind me of that
I mean if you guys would be okay with it
I would love to do the prayer that
parallelog off stream
save some time
to tell me which one
and don't worry for my marriage I'll
invite you guys
I'll do the marriage on stream
oh hello
what's that
why are you on an animal oh that looks
so weird to me
[Music]
that did not look like a horse to me
you'll bring the wedding cake really
that'll be a good one
[Music]
wow
I want um
a 10
10 floors
I mean I mean 10 levels
10 levels High
please
for the cake
all right no more you know what I'm
gonna go higher
and wait
for your memories
[Music]
here I'll come to you
he's also waiting for you because I'm
done down here
[Music]
all Mary waiting here
oh marrying inside a wedding cake
a Cake's so big that you can marry in it
oh you
you don't give me a funny idea
don't threaten me with a good time
[Music]
put it inside out
sounds like fun
[Music]
yeah
oh my God
he's gonna Excalibur
hey yo
more
that must be the last one right
surely those are the last ones
should I leave some people in the bottom
avoid that still emblems over here
Chihuahua make your way over there
[Music]
we'll switch your roof maybe no I'll
help her pick them up
maybe somebody comes from down there
after all and
makes me really tilt it
I'll take them up
two emblems is again
can you pick two up because if you still
can't just go to action afterwards
yeah he can pick you up
okay
yeah after this stream of kiwawa tired
today
even though I think I slept enough
the map didn't end until I grabbed them
all oh oh I guess they won't ah they
will only send reinforcements until you
have all the Rings and then they won't
send any more new ones but you still
have to kill all of them
wow that's so nice
[Music]
foreign
seems like they always come from the top
part of the map
[Music]
yes
why yes
[Music]
Laura Lucia
anyway
[Music]
you're gonna become
wedding cake baker you know what you
should beat a wedding cake
[Music]
wrap yourself in a wedding cake become
the wedding cake
[Music]
I tipped my castle to you
wait one HP I thought that leaves
style points though off the roof
I believe I am in the right
[Music]
no
you are wrong
[Music]
no rise up bear your face
and if I get Pinette to stand in the
middle she can talk to all of them
multiple
[Music]
people
no nice that's all of the Rings yeah
oops
huh
how did they just like remind me of my
mission oh
was it get the rings in the beginning
[Music]
strong enough for me to have her
always in my team in the following
battles to come
she's cute but
maybe we'll have to help her out a
little bit she is
we'll have to do something she's like
she's like five wow okay
I didn't check
I just have to land
Unforgettable okay yes he needs items
and
we'll see
did it
[Music]
story time
story I've summoned the emblems and
we've fended off our enemies
I think I better apologize
to both of you what for doubting what
you said
I thought this was all one of sombron's
Tricks a way to turn us against each
other but when we fought together I knew
it was you
our Ally our friend corrupted or not I
am glad you returned thank you all for
placing your trust in me
and thanks to Lady Vale we couldn't have
won without you yes resting back control
of yourself Reviving The Divine dragon
you did much today if not for your
efforts you'd probably be dead thank you
I did what I could now we're all
together again
what's the matter
I can't move
[Music]
what
no I'm Vanishing I knew this was a risk
but it wasn't supposed to happen so soon
oh [\h__\h] gave you all the power I could
it's a bit enough I must
oh no
summoning the emblems must have trained
you I didn't realize it's all right I'll
try again hang on Guardians of the
underworld
cast aside the rules that govern life
and death
your body is rejecting my power
can't take anymore Yabba thank you for
trying Veil
[Music]
but it seems my time has come
the 12 emblems are here with their help
I know you'll be able to stop something
no
you can't leave you said we'd save the
world together I'm sorry
you'll have to do that without me no it
was useful in the end
I can die knowing you're all safe
only I could fight to the end with you
got the Rings back
we're all together
we could have finished the mission
mother gave me
I could see the world come to peace
all I see is
oh
no
okay what that
what don't lock her with this child
you desire the power to fight
to the end
alongside everyone
[Music]
Dragon child you who fought bravely even
after death
would you rise once more
I want to fight
it can't end here she's literally a
phoenix guys
no matter how hard it may be
I have to continue until the world is
safe
must fight
like the emblems have I was right all
along
I have heard your wish
and thus
[Music]
our power is yours
wow
oh do you get like a final form too like
viola
please give me final form
no a new hair color
please
oh
you wear that
no yes
blue
I'm Blue
[Music]
this is my final form
12 emblems must have granted their power
[Music]
thank you she meant me right how did
this
[Music]
for yourself
I made you a promise
[Music]
I'd give you a birthday present oh it's
my armor why should I completely
perfectly again
I always knew that
wasn't the present that I would be like
white a very happy birthday to you
[Music]
I guess it came early this year
this room my armor looks the same has
become your emblem ring
lumero's power was held in that ring
you have restored the power of the
Divine Dragon well she must have known
this day would come
the day of your rebirth
[Music]
now look at me I feel
no
her eyes are fixed too your life was
saved by the combined power of 12 rings
making you
13th emblem
Fire Emblem
that's right
and that is your emblem ring what much
like the rings that house our Spirits
that's
that's only ever been spirits
never became a fire emblem unique Among
Us
and it's like I was never corrupted no
power as an emblem dwells in the ring
what
you do that tends to really beat a fire
emblems though you die you are now
reborn as an emblem with a new body but
wow someone used your power I am fine I
thought you could only Grant it once
every Thousand Years the 12 rings have
another Power
when we kept
Which Way someone said expired you're an
emblem we can finally reveal the truth
unable to perform the Miracle at any
time
to be together
agree on who who deserved the miracle so
that means I yes we all agreed we wish
to fight alongside you we could do this
once and never again
not in all the thousands of years ahead
what's more
will be the last
world
this took all of our future power
it was worth it to fight alongside you
now this is the first time we emblems
have shared the same wish
for this
for you everyone knew this was the only
way we could save you
no one returns from Death now being an
emblem is perhaps not what you desired
I hope we have done the right thing I've
died twice
I didn't expect to be back again so
thank you my friends and I will do our
best to protect this world
I'll make the most of what you've done
[Music]
I'm so glad to see you again I'm sorry
we were separated in hallucia
so long since then oh it was Bare barely
a blink
that your years of Slumber it's good to
see you my fellow emblem
[Music]
yeah okay the story has been picking up
here we have to have you back to find
one
crying again
I don't think I could survive losing you
a third time oh I prayed at the end to
be with you again
we all were and now for me it did here
we are
an emblem
I look forward to seeing what you can do
I'm sorry I worried you all I'm not
going anywhere ever again
I will always be together fail
without you I wouldn't be here oh thank
you no
saved my life too remember I should be
thanking you
[Music]
what is this an earthquake no
this is something far different
a greater force is in motion something
is happening
let's look
that was good
oh what in the world
what's up that in the middle of the sea
Redland
it's back
portal is opening in the sky
soon sambron will set out to invade
other worlds
we have to stop him I wish we could but
there's a barrier in the way
yes and it's covering the entire
continent
power that must have taken Papa doesn't
want us to interfere with his plans
how do we break through
we will need to destroy the feldragon
shards that are sustaining the barrier
I don't know where to find them
I can help you can I feel
I guess you'd call it a Vortex of bell
Dragon power with nothing grab one I
think there are two of them is that a
bug no
three
follow me we'll destroy the feldragon
shards and shatter the barrier
what
was it a dream
what the [\h__\h]
I can turn blue again in battle
oh
ah
so like when I engage
I just become the emblem I am the emblem
but I'm like
well that's a weird switch I did there
that's confusing okay I guess I am my
own emblem now
oh
yeah I want to stay blue
oh but okay so she's not only an emblem
she still keeps her physical normal body
I thought it was over for her
oh
my mother
[Music]
well it was interesting and
it's
end game now baby
last spurt last hospital
now try my best to finish it
we've been reasonable time AKA probably
not next week not the week after yeah
she's such a phoenix
there's so much for a Divine chicken
man
so fitting and what a fire mom has never
been like oh Fire Emblem until now
she literally after so many Fire Emblem
games the first Fire Emblem
because that's mind-breaking for me
having to play the other games but
except one
no
it was found lemon free houses what
who
who was the Flying bloom in free houses
don't tell me it was bailiff
crest of flames
okay but that isn't the same as Fire
Emblem saying it so clearly it just
doesn't hit the same way you can't say
roll the credits after that
that's just different
they should say fire emblem
wait so but it does that mean
what
wait what did all these ambulance that
I'm collecting in this game
also get called Fire Emblem at some
point in their own games
oh no
no
okay so I guess just the protagonists
but they never they became fire emblems
but they never
oh pilot turned into a DLC emblem
hello
personal plans Fire Emblem
in this game she's not called the fire
emblem I think
[Music]
because it was overlap
yeah well buy love wasn't that the okay
oh I guess ill guard was a DLC
it's usually an object
[Music]
okay I mean that was hype I'm a bit
confused but that was really hyped
nonetheless
[Music]
and you know the story I feel like more
convinced about it now
for the first time in 70 hours
[Music]
I feel like this was
y'all
good progress good story
good
um cutscenes the cutscenes were amazing
really good soundtracks throughout the
whole
mm-hmm eight hours today
all in all
yeah good good uh voice acting too
[Music]
good script also I mean the dialogue
we're fine I mean in the beginning of
today also they're like
now
we've got we've got to a good point
s
[Music]
where are you
oh she's got shoes on but she's got the
cutest outfit
[Music]
I'm so happy we can always be together
now yeah we she's cute
[Music]
story time no okay
there would do she would be there
to do some some bonding with her to take
a better look at her I'll do all of
these still off screen
oh my God it's too much
[Music]
yeah the hair oh my God it's like Anya's
hair
she must have her personal
hair combers
coupons very fast oh that's nice I guess
they did that because she joined so late
in the game and she's just really clingy
[Music]
best support paralog is now available oh
you gotta tell me which one exactly it
is I'm gonna end it here no wait
72 hours my God
I'm gonna eat the pizza now
and then hopefully um I'll throw in some
melatonini because it's already 11 p.m
[\h__\h]
look it up that's so early oh my God
it's
it's the exam
um ah which means I have to get up at
like what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] who followed this I feel like I've
said it before I don't want to do
recordings that early because when they
ask me they want to take part in it they
don't tell me the time yes
oh
you don't tell me the time at that point
you tell me after I accept
oh yeah I'll put like five melatonins on
my pizza
sorry guys can't read super chats I'll
after the recording tomorrow and maybe
after the nap
I will
make a schedule okay
[Music]
get some good Rhymes thank you good
night boss thank you thank you
and the one thing
I didn't get practice time to practice
for that either but I told them I don't
know [\h__\h] about it they were still like
oh please come anyway
laughs I'll I'll do my job as a comedian
and just write random things down
[Music]
it hit Divine Phoenix you mean yes yes
good luck on the recordings thank you
thank you very much
Alfie does it uh wish me luck that I can
sleep I my whole day I woke up I had
breakfast I cuddled 30 minutes with my
cat
I stream for eight hours and now I have
to go to sleep after eating dinner what
the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] bye bye
[Music]
foreign