​​​ ​1, 2.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear me?​ ​​
​​​ ​We've left the stage area​ ​​
​​ ​and are now in...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ta-da!​ ​​
​​​ ​The green room!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, timeout!​ ​​
​​​ ​Chama!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well?​ ​​
​​​ ​How are you feeling right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Please wait for​ ​​
​​ ​Sora-senpai to get changed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well?​ ​​
​​​ ​How are you feeling right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Words can't get through to her!​ ​​
​​​ ​What a problem child.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bad girls get punished.​ ​​
​​​ ​Go get her!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! I'm a founder here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, well, I'm half-angel, half-demon.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'm a badass!​ ​​
​​​ ​Argh! Argh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just accept your sentence!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, let's take a look at​ ​​
​​ ​our next green room.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, what's with the wind?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is this room so windy?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no! I'm gonna get blown away!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeet!​ ​​
​​​ ​I smell a case.​ ​​
​​​ ​The police will be right on it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Suspected Gale​ ​​
​​ ​in Green Room​ ​​
​​​ ​Suspect Sakura Miko Arrested​ ​​
​​​ ​It wasn't me! I didn't do anything!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hear me out, Senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why me too?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh,​ ​​
​​​ ​well, looks like they've​ ​​
​​ ​all been arrested.​ ​​
​​​ ​In this green room we have...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa, booze alert.​ ​​
​​​ ​Have a drink, pump yourself up.​ ​​
​​​ ​You won't accept the drink​ ​​
​​ ​I'm offering you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't drink any more...​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're drunk in the​ ​​
​​ ​middle of the concert.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yikes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ramen's the perfect capper.​ ​​
​​​ ​The owl stock adds​ ​​
​​ ​some nice flavor to it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't make stock out of me!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's missing the secret ingredient.​ ​​
​​​ ​And lacking spice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm, it needs more meat, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yikes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's hit up the next joint.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, missy,​ ​​
​​ ​you haven't paid your tab yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Gosh, that room reeks of booze.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move on to the next one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Something smells good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, this is really great.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why must you be so yummy?​ ​​
​​​ ​Eat up! I'll keep 'em coming!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're eating your kind.​ ​​
​​​ ​How does it make you feel?​ ​​
​​​ ​As long as everyone​ ​​
​​ ​appreciates the taste, it's fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa! This one's got a pepper in it!​ ​​
​​​ ​And mine had plum.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mine had Indonesia in it!​ ​​
​​​ ​This may be a​ ​​
​​ ​prime business opportunity.​ ​​
​​​ ​Enjoy all the different flavors.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, takoyaki parties are always a riot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move on.​ ​​
​​​ ​Locker room interview!​ ​​
​​​ ​Roboco-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh? You here for mods?​ ​​
​​​ ​I said interview, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh? You here to party?​ ​​
​​​ ​Interview, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​Er, um...​ ​​
​​​ ​No need to force a joke!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah. Well...​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you all listen to our song?​ ​​
​​​ ​Enjoy the rest of the show as well!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm really looking forward to it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, Okayu, you say something too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ngreeong.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​How's it feel?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? What do you mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​I was, like, told to​ ​​
​​ ​interview you guys, so...​ ​​
​​​ ​How's it feel?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, that mic's too close!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wassup?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's yer deal, lassie?​ ​​
​​​ ​How's it feel?​ ​​
​​​ ​You bugnoring us?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's yer problem?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me talk!​ ​​
​​​ ​And that's the story.​ ​​
​​​ ​Take it away!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll do the interviews next.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't mean that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Evening!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're here to do a​ ​​
​​ ​locker room interview!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​2023 is almost over, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​It really flew by!​ ​​
​​​ ​It'll be 2024 soon!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, what time zone is Indonesia in?​ ​​
​​​ ​2024 will hit Indonesia​ ​​
​​ ​two hours after Japan!​ ​​
​​​ ​We can celebrate twice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, I like that mindset.​ ​​
​​​ ​How much longer​ ​​
​​ ​until the countdown?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yikes, we need to move on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ookami Mio-senpai takes over​ ​​
​​ ​as interviewer now.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right! I've got this!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're hitting this room next.​ ​​
​​​ ​holo, holo, holo!​ ​​
​​​ ​We, holo no graffiti,​ ​​
​​ ​are taking over this show!​ ​​
​​​ ​Give it back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fix this!​ ​​
​​​ ​What did we ever do to you?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Quit whining! The year's about to end!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to welcome the new year​ ​​
​​ ​in this crazy place!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bwahaha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then try and stop us!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm closing the tab.​ ​​
​​​ ​Smash that dislike button.​ ​​
​​​ ​No lols.​ ​​
​​​ ​(＾ω＾≡＾ω＾) Hohoho.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wha?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why'd I have to get the crazy room?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks like we've run​ ​​
​​ ​into some difficulties,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I—Hoshimachi Suisei—​ ​​
​​ ​will be taking over!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sui-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​The Hakotaro dislocated her jaw!​ ​​
​​​ ​I gan't do da goundown lige dis!​ ​​
​​ ​(I can't do the countdown like this!)​ ​​
​​​ ​She needs facial reconstruction.​ ​​
​​​ ​And... why are you looking at me?​ ​​
​​​ ​We figured you wouldn't hold back.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come at me, bro!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, you asked for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fly, you fools.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, let's check out​ ​​
​​ ​the next green room.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nyonyonyonyo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Haha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Their funny bone's gone all funny​ ​​
​​ ​due to excess magic intake.​ ​​
​​​ ​You eat this, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha-ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too! Me three!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's too early for you, kid.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're just as much a kid as me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Takes one to know one!​ ​​
​​​ ​W-Watch out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pfft! Bwahahaha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bwahahaha!​ ​​
​​​ ​草草草草草​ ​​
​​​ ​Gah!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is boring!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm hitting up the next room!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hollo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! The baby's asleep!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm supposed to be the baby,​ ​​
​​ ​but I'm wakey.​ ​​
​​​ ​We should hit the hay too, honey.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who are you calling honey?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to sleep too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, man, fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​The great Towa will lull you to sleep.​ ​​
​​​ ​May I join you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Dear, who is this man?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I... I don't know! Please believe me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Phooey.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm tired of pwaying the baby.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mom'll take over on the mic, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's our next green room.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Graaagh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Korone-senpai spun around too much!​ ​​
​​ ​Now she can't stop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can't stop, won't stop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Woohoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stay!​ ​​
​​​ ​A-Anyway, I'm here for an interv—​ ​​
​​​ ​My mic!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is no time for an interview!​ ​​
​​​ ​Help us, Choco-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Great! I shall go to the​ ​​
​​ ​next room over, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ayame-sama!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stay and help!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, hey.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry I'm so not cute.​ ​​
​​ ​Sorry I'm always so gloomy.​ ​​
​​ ​Sorry I'm a shark.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry I'm so not cute.​ ​​
​​ ​Sorry I'm an alien.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're feeling the song's​ ​​
​​ ​withdrawal effects!​ ​​
​​​ ​We've still got performances to go,​ ​​
​​​ ​so quit getting all depressed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Pekora-senpai doesn't seem​ ​​
​​ ​to be affected, I daresay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry I'm so cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​This bunny...​ ​​
​​​ ​She's got so much self-esteem!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop that.​ ​​
​​ ​You're all cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sora-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway, all said and done...​ ​​
​​​ ​...we're only a few seconds away​ ​​
​​ ​from 2024!​ ​​
​​​ ​Man, that whole year​ ​​
​​ ​felt like it just flew by.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll keep going next year!​ ​​
​​​ ​Together with everyone!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone to the roof!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eeeeeh?!​ ​​
​​​ ​0!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please support hololive in the new year.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you liked this, please subscribe for more!​ ​​