a while ago me and Jemma went to have
some cute Instagram aesthetic afternoon
tea together it's in a cafe Naka Migo
called Ur it was a roseen berry theme
they had mostly sweet stuff but also a
few Savory things and you were
surrounded by an insane amount of fake
flowers in a pretty narrow and small
room here's the menu by the way let's
start with this jelly strawberry ly
thing normally I don't like jelly but
this was bomb we had this little pasta
too but it was so cold when we arrived
so I had them warm it up the sandwich of
ham and pear was great here's some Puda
on potato salad and there was some
Savory soup below too but of course the
sweet stuff is the Highlight like this
Berry puffet yeah this raspberry mousse
was a delight oh and look at this
raspberry cream brlee cheesecake wow
this raspberry M blah doesn't only look
cute but also tastes cute oh and by the
way you get all you can drink tea in
super dolly cups they had these selfie
sticks and lights on the table for you
to use I swear every other person
besides us in the cafe was 90% taking
pictures and 10% eating