[Music]
K
hello
hi hi I'm with
cing
[Music]
K oh wow hello oh small w wow today
because I thought maybe it fits oh what
the now my hand is not moving I
will turn my hands off if you don't
stop yeah see I'm I'm not actually
moving it you little
guess I I will I might turn off my
hands then that's okay no
problem Odyssey yeah yeah yeah Odyssey
was like when I bought Super Mario RPG
and now a lot of other games are on sale
and odyssey it was like like 20 bucks
cheaper than usual so I
thought why not why not and I purchased
it for maybe the future cuz I heard that
this Super Mario Odyssey is a really
really really good one right so okay
instead of scratching my ear I will turn
off my hands now no more
hands ody see slaps yeah I've heard and
that the music is really good too yeah
yeah unravel unravel 2 is 84% off AKA
it's like four bucks right now what the
so oh I'm considering buying it to
play it with maybe
narissa I think I played unravel
one with coyote right was that
unravel but we didn't play the whole
game did
we
wait oh wait what I did that was it was
too oh did I play it on
Steam did I play play it on Steam
because I don't own it on the switch so
that must have been
steam ah well then okay then no need to
buy it but I almost want to buy it
because for four bucks even though I
already own it I really want
it man I've never felt like buying a
game twice
before what a deal how can I ignore such
a
deal yeah can couldn't have been one cuz
it doesn't have co-op huh
[Music]
no oh okay guys how you doing it is time
for the Wawa to play a game I am back
home in Austria in case you're not a
member or in case you didn't watch my
member stream yesterday I am back home
in Austria
it's
cold and it feels like what the it
feels like I've been gone for like 3
weeks or so because it wasn't this cold
when I left I've only been gone for one
and a half
weeks but the weather is so different
and it's like like as like cold enough
to snow in
Austria like it's been snowing in places
in Austria
but that wasn't the case when I left
like what the
it's it's suddenly really crazy
like it's cold and different season
feels like I've been gone
forever M suddenly winter winter has
arrived m
[Music]
yeah y did you ever see F while you were
in Japan oh I mean um I I every now and
then I get fan letters from jenma not
this time like any fan letters but I got
some stuff that
uh that has
been waiting for me for a while
apparently like a a cup a Starbucks cup
from a Korean fan so it's a soul
Starbucks cup it's really pretty I
actually just drank tea out of it it's a
really nice
cup uhhuh and and one more one more uh
handmade probably 3D printed chicken
kfb uh
kfp worker
chicken was that from popcorn probably
still from popcorn I don't know why I
didn't get last time cuzz I already U
got some stuff from like popcorn last
time I was in Japan and popcorn was last
year though uh but yeah I got some stuff
from that time again like the cup is
probably from that time and they just
like forgot to give it to me but it's a
really nice cup so I'm happy to have
it you work at Dunkin Donuts so
Starbucks is your enemy how how I don't
I don't think no I don't think that's I
don't think you should see see Starbucks
as your enemy like I feel like people go
to Dunkin Donuts for yeah maybe coffee
but like donuts and like nobody goes
like people might go to coffee to for
coffee to both places but they will not
go for donuts to Starbucks so you have
something pretty unique in your
workplace there may be some overlapping
things but nobody's going for donuts to
Starbucks like man Dunkin Donuts let's
go let's
go oh Dunkin Donuts is a popular place
for coffee too huh I've heard I've heard
but yeah so I'm back in
Austria it's time to get back into the
groove um but I hope you guys enjoyed
the couple of off collaps that I've had
uh I put a lot of love and F into them
like I feel like I feel like all of the
off clubs that I had they had thoughtful
ideas behind them I I I came up with
creative stuff you know I'm quite
proud well they they all have special
meaning it's not just oh off collab okay
uh let's uh play game X whatever no no
that was there was lots of fault behind
it
M I'm really happy with my off collapse
this
time one was so good that it
banned skin exposure on H life no just
kidding I I
I I think it's a weird coincidence in
terms of timing but jenma says that it
was a long time
coming and and I just feel like uh-huh
uhhuh
I feel like I feel like I
mean I didn't break any rules when I did
this and I didn't get bonked but it does
seem like a weird coincidence that the
following day we get an announcement
about skin ban no more skin I will never
be a flesh tuber ever
again I shall remain
virtual like the great
[Music]
wandering out
you and as your beloved
RPG gamer takanasi
kiaa I'm going to play Super Mario a p
but it's my first time I know this is a
remake my first time heard good things
oh she looks kind of thicker than usual
Peach did you gain
weight audio
[Music]
okay wow
B oh is he going to sing peaches peaches
peaches peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches not quite the same mood Mario
I'm late oh my God please come back
back where did to go oh no oh no I
forgot to tweet about to start huh okay
oh mama me I forgot to tweet about the
the St oh what
the oh she didn't look very concerned
yeah it's just another day of being
abducted oh just every day
urren nothing weird about
it
teach
starting nice music starting
now I don't even remember it anymore but
I watched uh like the first 20 minutes
of game play
perhaps I don't even remember it though
like what even
happened a difficulty mode to start in
I'm guessing normal is fine
I mean they're probably already freaking
easy on normal
right
right how easy can it be on
Breezy okay we just saw
this thank you I want to read super
chats today when I'm done here don't
know how long we'll play my goal was to
finish the game tomorrow in a second
stream cuz it seems to be short but
but at the same time I noticed I have
like other things to do so might aim for
free
streams might aim for free streams
because I have
to meet someone tomorrow and I also met
someone
today and I need to sign ton of
Polaroid
still hundreds and hundreds
yeah many many full WS free free so I
don't know maybe we'll see how it goes I
don't even want to I don't even want to
decide on anything if I feel
uncomfortable I will share tangents but
I also feel like I literally can't
multitask so
why does why do his eyes look weird he
looks like a
puppet interesting
look but yeah it's cute like squished he
looks so squished and and small small
and small that's why I'm small
today eh can I fight them oh I
can already without even being
introduced
ah this is has mushroom L form aha so
small they one hit wonders
man oh this goes fast oh do I get EX one
exp that's like nothing probably right
it no but it set 14 XP to Next
Level
so actually one exp is a lot if it's if
we're still in that
scale no no a oh he only does one HP
attacka do we get two XP now yeah
okay
o
oh looks good looks good looks good so
far looks
cute I like the the graphics
uh Bowser I thought I could just like
come in here and get my princess back
what's going
on Peach on a
rope it wait why am I already at the
final BS
fight don't let Bowser bruise you Mario
Mario prepare yourself for something
that you can't reach cuz it wents way
too
fast oh no
I will just ah I can attack the
chain interesting he's like
Oh I thought he was looking at the chain
but mar mar the chain oh you already
knew oh why you so smart Mario you're so
smart you noticed before I could tell
you
yeah how much HP does the chandelier
have wait am I supposed to do something
else besides should I use my special
what's my oh jump stom POS oh no I think
normal attack is
fine fall
down the chain attack the CH I know what
oh now what did I even have a choice why
a joke put some muscle into it yeah I
mean you you're not want to talk you
keep on attacking me with one
damage
H there it goes what was the
sound oh no
no it's a chain reaction hang in their
chandelier Chand
chandelier I'm Holding On by the skin of
your teeth whatever you do down let
[Music]
go so it's like actual living beings not
just like the design of the
chandelier hi Mario hi
uh what what am I supposed to
fight the air the the what do you call
this falling
down what's this what do you call this
again physics gravity gravity yeah you
want me to fight
gravity didn't you think I was just
going to give her to you you always in
my
way oh sorry my throat is not so good so
I can't can't make the best voice right
now Fung foiled again his crying
face oh oh we have officially defied
gravity oh Mario you had me so worried
let's get out of
here Mario the whole Castle's
Shing
why just because of the
chandeliers was the whole castle built
around those
chandeliers
oh some weird sword yeah these are
like the things I'm guessing that the
game was originally named after the
things that just flew away do I have to
collect them throughout the game once I
have them all I
can save Peach or the world or yeah
that's it that's the
plot
oh Mario's pet cute it looks literally
like Shrek's backyard Shrek would feel
comfortable here oh I made theop
sound
hey
Mario I is Toad G to talk a lot in this
game probably
yeah how much do I want to commit to
this
voice
uh yeah okay maybe just in the
beginning oh
God lots of people use something called
the door to go in and out of their
houses anyway I came by to pick up
Princess Peach since she's a bit
[Music]
late why am I hanging like this is this
how I sleep honestly it might be good
for your back just hanging
[Music]
Maybe
oh my
[Music]
God why does he
have his walls
decorated with medieval hand
[Music]
Cuffs in different
sizes has anybody ever a question
dad kinky or I no I was not thinking
about him that being kinky I was
concerned about how is he using it is he
like shopping people's head
off with that on that's a wrench no what
I don't mean I mean the what the wrench
is hanging on look at have you never
seen a medieval
handcuff a wrench sussy Buckle making me
seem stupid oh that's safe okay oh fast
safe
[Music]
sheesh oh
oh mhm the the wooden ones yes
yes by the way I have still still since
I'm still concerned about the lag I have
my uh
latency h a bit later than usual is that
why it's called latency late being late
now it's pretty late latency so I don't
see your comments as fast stockades is
that what they're called oh no they're
called Piller oh
game caps are not
[Music]
centered what are you talking about game
my game capture is pretty oh oh wait now
I see
it now I see
[Music]
it
hey I found the princess was here with
you Mario so where is
she Mario what the silent treatment
you're not telling me
something it's Bowser again isn't it oh
no here we go again Mario what you play
is bring her back like you always
do Mario
I forgot something important if you get
knocked out you'll wake up at the last
place you're saved but guess what on
this
adventure you'll save automatically
whenever you go between
[Music]
Aras
Pinocchio oh wait is Toad called
Pinocchio in
Japanese
I think I heard that before it'll save
all the time so whatever it just
yeah you can also hop on this safe use
some let's not talk more than we have to
shall we go to B's
keep ah kinopio not
Pinocchio p
kinopio i sound like I'm it shut
up is that how I can imitate my beloved
favorite streamer
just
make the voice of
toad that sounded a bit like
her May
beloved
oh uh what kind of voice would this have
M
uh what do you
think high voice slow voice chill
voice something deep booming and deep
that's exactly what I can't do in my
register so
what I can't can't do none of what you
guys are
saying
okay who goes there a
trespasser sounds like my bow voice
almost this Castle now belongs to us
Smithy
gang we have big plans and this is the
first step in them if it weren't for
nose characters like you
we practically own this
world so let's see you deal with
this
a you think that sword speaks in a
British
accent I don't know about that no
[Music]
so what he just destroyed the bridge and
I go
away uh I'll go home everybody is
booo there's boohoo down
there
boohoo
cute back to the bachelor pad I guess I
go in my house cuz I see nothing else
here oh there he is you're back so soon
did you forget
something no no what happened
[Music]
then
uh re acting how about you just talk
Mario H I think things would be much
easier in your life if you just talk no
no okay okay
the bridge to Bowser keep is up now just
wonderful we must in from the chancellor
if the Mushroom Kingdom at once let's
go let's
[Music]
go ah Chris prad cost too much huh they
wanted to have Mario talk but oh no
turns out Mario cost Chris breat cost
too much money ah you little
oops excuse me oh that bump on your
head reduced your HP level one of the
mushroom kingdoms verys have to perke
you right
up whatever you want to
use why did I come back
[Music]
anyway I just barely made it back in one
pie please help oh I should have
said
yes it's an accident I thought yes
would be the first answer cuz I already
had
[Music]
battles go no don't stop
time oh wait I can do more than
oh
I
what press a what I
press a when I'm like in front of the oh
I didn't know that was possible okay now
I a hit a has enemies attack back to
okay oh shees I wonder how how
uh what's the
word how how lenient they are with that
if your timing is perfect you'll take no
damage I can't read my phone is way too
high I can't go down
Action commands won't save you from
attacks that hit your whole party oh now
try a special move by pressing y Okay
jump did I press a again oh I was about
to yeah I was about to why' you stop me
you little depending on the Move
sometimes you'll have to do more than
just press a button so keep an eye out
for
[Music]
that will it tell
me well thank God I'm I said yes to the
tutorial
each time you nail an action command
this action gos fills up a oh when the
action gos raes 100% then your enemies
better watch out so look forward to that
the more successful Action commands you
do the higher this number will go if you
can do it two or more times in a row
some Buffs will start to kick in for you
was I'm reading and registering
everything yes yes yes yes what so just
do it as much as you can for you Mar
action G will fill faster as power Wells
up inside I know that's a lot to take in
but never fear you press B during
balance select help you can go over any
of this again uhhuh okay you can't even
see the explanations outside of battle
by selecting help from the
menu
okay don't forget it's there
[Laughter]
okay came back to make really
sure thank you Toad such a
homie and there you have St
[Music]
it we need to tell the chancellor about
Peach so i s the
[Music]
kingdom I'm
ding let's go my to is dying let's go W
my to my FR I have a to in my
f
let's
go
Chancellor let's
fight if I do I get like a special bonus
if I jump into battle that would be
[Music]
fun ah I did it I did it I did it no I
didn't do it no oh the timing I pressed
way too early like I got to figure this
out like especially if they turn and
then attack it's like what when when are
you actually attacking dude ooh I even
did like some kind of shock wave damage
there
shh oh if if Mario punches like once two
then if I press a again in the right
timing on the second punch does that
like also help or is it just like once
is
enough not
[Music]
DIY no just one press okay
okay so the the fact that I had 25
damage mean probably means I did it
[Music]
right
oh there I guess yeah you can maybe try
to go with the Rhythm
huh a perfect timing a oh that's what
that
was
oopsie no
no I I always press it when they like uh
arrive ah this time I actually pressed
exactly when the the thing hit me but
maybe that was too L look out for the
exclamation
mark oh there's an exclamation
mark for
defending what I didn't see what the
hell
okay let's let's try to see it oh hey
ah
ah I pressed it
though oh it's pmax
[Music]
ah
yeah B HP was I down to one
HP y
[Music]
really oh
I get two
attacks
yo I had one HP what I was going to
die Level Up Mario level oh no do oh no
do oh I could choose what I
upgrade
uh
I would say physical Let's Get Physical
come
[Music]
on what what what would you you have
chosen guys thanks for the membership
[Music]
renewal yo 68 she that's their weakness
ooh I think I blocked it I think that
counted as a successful block wait let's
not waste this
by did I block it no I guess I didn't
cuz then it would have shown that
wall I swear I'm pressing it at the
right time now D more or
l oh
well as long as it's still doing so
little
damage oh hi
Toad and bye
toad I can really just
lead we should save
toad I see I see the I see the
exclamation mark and I
press a when I see it but I don't know
maybe it's the
[Music]
lag he's a goner no I'm not playing
through
OBS my life was splashing before my
eyesand second
there
me life was flashing in front of Mario's
eyes too when I was down to 1 HP and I
didn't even
[Music]
notice oh I
didn't but just because I pressed it
earlier before it didn't before it even
showed
up that was that was actually me kind of
pressing it too early but I guess that
is the timeing
[Music]
for me it felt like too
early
okay is it like in terms of like
leveling is it necessary for me to like
fight every enemy I
see Will I struggle if I don't later in
the
[Music]
game she didn't even see her item
what I
mean I saw I got an item
but it wasn't so
significant okay I will look at
[Music]
it you get a lot of trash in RPG games
okay that's what I'm used
to just getting trash all the time think
we got this thing raises FP by
one oh wait was it special
items how do I switch to special items
ah
ah I don't know how to switch special
maybe I don't have special items level
cap is 30
what so should I use it you can use
recovery items in the field with x i
with X should I use it
[Music]
uh the flower point right is it like
forever
raised you need to press X when not in
the
menu yeah
okay oo
o oh I already did this one is there
enough item hidden back here
no okay uh wait do I go right side or do
I cute what can I do that
too no not really sheesh wait that's
that looks
fun he's dancing on the
[Music]
flower no I always press it
through now it was too
late the one time I can stop stop myself
from pushing it too
[Music]
early W oh
no oh I get to ride it and now I can use
it for my advantage
oh ah
[Music]
spe let me spein again and then I can
jump higher
huh a
what ah is it ah in the direction that
I'm looking at at the moment okay flower
flower no wait flower
wait oh did that just fill up my flower
Point
[Music]
what
no special awareness non-existent God
pick me up
what what what is this problem what a
weird
of oh it it I immediately raised it did
that's 12
now it raised it without my
[Music]
permission pick me up is just a
revive tried to jump me oh to to
to
wait to toad wasn't there before
the fight was he
to I'll save
you Toad not existent in this
[Music]
screen no not f for toad I saved him by
that was a close call thank you so much
who thank
you raising my flowers flower flower oh
actually oh my God that already brings
me to one random it's not even a tangent
it's just something um I I met Louis
Senai one of those
days
and first of all she was dancing
pineapple I was like what the why
do you know the pineapple Dance I'm so
happy she was just like dancing the
pineapple dance out of nowhere the the
one where I like look to the side
and go to the side and do like some step
step steps where kind of like diving you
know that move that is really difficult
for me
actually
[Music]
oh she's not
Senai I keep on saying
Senai unbelievable damn they have a lot
of
HP
um yeah so I was like really happy I was
really moved that she actually like cuz
I feel like um my my activities are cuz
like all all the whole live girls we
follow each other you know so I would
think our timelines are like full with
lots of activities from other members so
I don't really expect anybody to be
following my music or what I'm up to
what I'm doing you
know
nice so I'm like always incredibly
surprised when somebody knows my newest
songs or whatever I'm
doing and
then oh yeah there was something about a
flower I guess we saw like a flower and
then she said calmly
elegantly FL flow flower and so that
reminds me of the crony flower meme so I
try to like bring it up and like explain
it or ask if she knows it or if she
knowingly said it this way because of
that it turns out yes she knows the
flower
meme that was also surprising to me yeah
she knows the crony flower
meme H do you seems to be really popular
yeah yeah yeah I I I know that and I
appreciate it but do is pretty old at
this point so I hope people check out my
new music and and did she knows
pineapple I'm
happy yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah and and I think it was because of
my tweet but uh was it it was L right
who just the other day reacted to my
tweet saying she loves love Rush what
[Music]
happy pretty old only a year yeah but
like I mean if you compare it to me
having five new songs out right now you
know which a pretty Banger
too I responded twice yeah that's how
happy I was no that's how much Twitter
is trolling
me hey are you looking at me my hammer I
don't like
you
Mario let me just fight him go go go
oh yeah oh should I be worried
maybe I should have healed
yeah uh better bring out the
[Music]
jumps and okay no it's not big damage
I should have
PE I wonder how much more HP he has left
but I'm going to I'm going to risk
it 46 she
[Music]
money money
wo oh he uses a buff okay
that helps me I'll I'll I'll go for out
another I
missed
ah yeah
bye mushroom mushroom I got a freebie
let's go
ah is this like common for beginners to
just not get the timings
right y y y y y y y y y y
[Music]
y I pressed it the moment I touched
him I swear yeah okay damn I wish they
were more
lenient okay I'm I'm like I'm like
totally out of it
now y
no no no no no no I'm dying
again
Mama
Mama okay I did it this
time Hallelujah I can't jump
anymore come
on okay oh thank God it's over
okay
that's all the damage we had to
do toad stop getting into so much
trouble you little
King just a halfway almost down
Mario where did hmer come from I don't
know from Donkey Kong looks like a
barrel on a stick you know what it
is it was yeah it's obviously the Hammer
Bros Hammer I don't know where else it
should be coming from has a chance
against you when you want them with this
oh can I use it as an item like the jump
or so no I pick up a hammer Mario has an
a have you
noticed sheesh it's going to move
on he let me see what's down here
nothing wait all the enemies are gone ah
no Cloud friend still here okay let's
go why you guys shocked what did I say
he does yeah when he takes off his hat
did you not see
it equip it now yeah
okay
equip ooh will I always attack with the
hammer
now
ooh o
[Music]
ooh raises FP by free permanently right
okay okay all right right all right oh
oh look at me look at me look at me
again you look so different than the
other toads wow these are different
toads hav't SE Princess Peach lately
What m is going
again oh no real oo
moment oh the normal toads are
like these are like adult toads oh my
it's cooking
clean why why do they have cut off
stairs
here I'm here too oh my God just look at
this it's like I better not enter this
[Music]
room hi taking I
here just can I bounce of you wait why
won't you let me bounce bounce
properly what a speed to be bouncing in
and he also has the medieval handcuffs
on his
walls what the if I prce enough I'll
jump as high as
you oh my god did he just get
[Music]
faster oh my God I I I have heard that
uh this game because of is such an old
one Nintendo
was still quite very
um
Brave and a lot of funny things happened
in this
game and apparently they didn't take
anything really
out so yeah I already I already see like
some of the traces of this humor what is
this not old came out like a week ago
you know what I
[Music]
mean
St
nice are you selling things ah oh
crashing oh they have a they have a
hotel like all other games let's
go Final Fantasy Mario I I I personally
wouldn't um bring up Final Fantasy but
God what
this what is it with these
toads I hope my grandchild turns out to
be just like the princess stop it Mom
make a great sidekick for you in a few
years right I'm wor only if you stop
talking like that otherwise you will not
be my
sidekick so nice to see our young ones
having a good time is your bed also
bouncy oh every bed is
bouncy n that could there be secret
items in
places
[Music]
I wonder if it's worth running and
looking around really
[Music]
closely there's invisible blocks oh I'm
not good with like sensing them cuz I
don't play Mario
games Ry isn't just a friend anymore
we're getting
married do you happen to know of a good
wedding trip these two are getting
married for
them happy news but it's like I feel
like
I'm stand on them can can you carry
me no I just I just I just stay wait I'm
wait was I just on the stairs oh no okay
now I'm actually it what this
[Music]
this I'm so
confused
death I got
you what's going on where am I
actually okay
now get me on this toad
head so he does carry me okay okay
[Music]
okay oh my God what is this game
so if I just jump around a lot maybe
I'll hit uh like a secret
block I'll do
[Music]
that just generally
everywhere wait can I get on the
kid
no got to get the right timing so I can
get on the kid I want to speed with him
[Music]
I'm playing jumping
rope yo let's
go
oh I jumped off on my own and I I I I
got dizzy oh I feel like I found a
little
secret
oh that's
funny hey
[Music]
that's
funny okay is this the item
shop a pleas surprise one of the frogs s
his grandchildren is running errands in
town today I haven't seen him though BR
you're here to
shop maybe pick me up revives down
Alle refreshes status during battle
pretty cheap
but it's a shirt it's a pair of
pants this is so I like the description
should I get a shirt because the pants
don't even help me so I'm guessing I
have pants
on or I mean my armor set I had nothing
though I should get the shirt
right yes equip it if only I could like
see a difference in my looks that that
would be amazing but okay a lot of RPG
games don't do
[Music]
that it's a shirt are the pants with ah
then maybe for a
toad
Mario sorry toad I'm not following you I
am
curious I need to check out the other
areas here
where the hell is is leading Peach's
room this
bad oh my God jump yes of course I can
jump on her bed but this one actually
like oh wait no never mind it does let
me jump on the same
spot
nice look found Peach's question mark
Quest he what do you think you're doing
I found there question mark question
mark question mark I'll give you this
new just leave everything where it was a
mushroom I I didn't even get a close
look at what I
found but okay it gave me a prompt so I
thought I thought it would be like
completely secret stuff like I had to
sense
it
[Music]
questionable the way he I don't know
that just felt like he opened the door
with his tummy by running against it
aggressively but I want to go this way
first sorry
toad something something about
this game
already I'm guarding the treasure room
sorry but you'll have to get the
Chance's permission to pass now hold
what about this
door
oh
oh everybody's favorite pastime in this
game jumping on beds the VL better not
be goofing off while I'm cleaning the
gas
room this the guest room
oh I may have used it in the
[Music]
past let's go how toad really wanted it
oh that's a big
toad s Mario is
arriv indeed I
[Music]
have than goodness you're
here I heard an explosion or something
about this keep it was so loud I almost
dropped my
spores excuse me princess what where is
the princess she departed for your house
hours
ago is there wait is there a king if if
Peach is the princess and this is the
translator is there a king like an
actual human
King well excuse me
princess no King
no I fear the worst could Bowser somehow
be behind all of
this yes
yes what what kind of special powers
does this Mario have in in this game
reenacting
things it like but actually turning into
the people I was like what the am I
am I Bowser for a
moment I thought I thought I was getting
Bamboozled and Bowser was using his
magic to turn into Mario and I was
playing
him spor is alive you're telling us that
Bowser has abducted the princess again
never mind it will be up to you to enter
the keep and rescue Princess Peach no I
don't want to
because he punched me and it really hurt
though I actually already tried and
then
I yeah and then then I destroy and then
there's a beak a beak Earth quick and I
fall down from the beak uh distance and
uh I was really startled and I don't
know what the that was supposed to
mean at the end but you know uh yeah I
can't
go
Mario your life is in your hands please
save her dear princess whatever you just
talking about I don't give a you
have to go hey
Mario why did I just
stumble you're making sure to cryp the
things you get right H yeah yeah no no
no need at all NOP M I have the chat to
tell me these
things you can buy AR no thank you oh my
[Music]
God
we are extremely easy to
startle mama
mama can you read can you read our
messages in Toad's voice no only if you
want me to take a week off after the
stream for resting my
voice just like me no I don't startle
this badly and roll down the stairs
which is by the way a big a big fear I
have when I I go
downstairs like I often get scared that
I like Miss uh Miss step and then fall
down and die do you guys also have this
like fear
[Music]
constantly especially if I don't look
exactly at my feet when I go
downstairs I look I like I I focus cuz I
am too scared that I will fall down and
die or break something tumble over head
forward
terrifying you jump downstairs damn you
badass parkour your life is a
parkour bath MO is that a thing I got to
look it
up is that but that sounds more like I'm
scared of baths bath more
phobia oh Bop phobia is a fear of stairs
you may be afraid of falling down the
set of stairs or a steep incline a
traumatic accident involving a fall
injury or death may cause the specific
phobic
disorder I don't know if there was I
[Music]
mean I don't know if there was a
specific fall that caused this for me
but I do think I have this fear H yaka I
have a phobia I always wanted a phobia I
don't think I have any other phobia not
that I am aware of yay
I'm
happy it's nice to have a term for
things you know let me take a froat
candy by the way because I'm also uh
very very scared of losing my voice is
there a phobia for that
probably look it up for me
guys just say no to gravity you
gravity here let me show you the middle
finger
you grabing the middle finger up
now what you going to do about that huh
ah what you going to do what you going
to do terrifying right yeah yeah yeah
threatening oh violence oh the
violence oh the
[Music]
violence I ain't part of you
sister I threw gravity to the
ground I'm not going want to fall for
you anyway back to the
game forgive me but I can't stop
worrying about the princess go to The
Cellar and prepare for your journey The
Vault guard shall assist
you is that where the guest room was
probably okay let's
go tweeted you a hidden chest guide
first Super Chat thank
you for this uh Place specifically or
like for the whole
[Music]
game I saw a happy
thing let me go let me go my
Twitter refreshing my Twitter there it
is a guide to Hidden Treasure Chest but
in make it so that the ones you can't
miss you can get back to the Remake so
you don't have to worry not
all oh oh I haven't when like
looking at a guide like this on like a
website like game
FAQs brings me back to uh like my Tales
of
Symphonia times gaming as a teenager
looking up
guides oh my
God the place this house hop on toel as
he starts walking towards the first
door okay the one in the palace is like
enter the palace and hop on to's head as
he starts I already missed that towards
the first door jump on the place above
the door and the boxes up there I
already missed that can I still do
[Music]
it I I shall keep this guide open i h
see you guys should keep this guide open
and tell me but
I can still get it later okay well
remind
me these are legit
Secrets okay am I am I
choosing all of them flow
flow oh try suest flowers increase your
flower as soon as uhhuh
yeah okay okay okay yeah I've already
had that happen to me this a mushroom
but you knew that by looking at it huh
these mushrooms you get from Treasure
Chest don't work quite like the mushroom
items Treasure Chest mushroom when you
open the chest but you can save them for
later mushrooms you find this items only
restore H but you can take them with
you okay thank
you coin there's a coin I will force it
on to you so you will be rich one day
and then hopefully you will give back by
using the trickle down effect I'm
counting on you buddy secrets secrets
[Music]
anybody yes create
jobs I I will vote for you
Mario come come back here what the
is going on what is this cut
scene it's so sudden
what why is this music like
like some music bugging why is it still
playing this feels like it shouldn't be
playing without a
cut okay now it's going away It Feels So
Random it right it was kind of
random who is this character that I've
never seen in any other Mario game
before oh no that reptiles don't like
Grandpa's
coin
a
oh I I can't cry Big Boys Don't Cry but
it's just not
fair oh it's the rain it's totally the
rain it's not
me it's the rain I'm a big boy I don't
cry he's a he's a
frog that is not a frog are you insane
guys how is this a
frog huh he's a
marshmallo that's why his name is
mellow hello
marshmallow yes you're soaking wet
aren't you certainly not from my tears
though cuz I wasn't crying at
all oh
I'm all right
now wait is this why you guys were
saying he's cobal rain Shaman he makes
it rain when he cries for real for
real
sheesh he yeah why the does he no
it's not a frog this is not a
frog even if he will tell me he's a frog
I I will not accept your your identity
m- there's nothing like a good
cry but why was
[Music]
I what's going on in this game what's
going on in this
game there was no reason for him to fall
down just
now he just stumbled while
standing n
[Music]
I can't with this game oh my God that
was some reason my my grandpa asked me
to buy some things for him here when I
walk into town The Croc stopped
[Music]
me his face cute oh yeah he took it from
me he stole my coin I tased him but he's
way too fast F Mario let's see how
you're going to take care of
Bowser uh oh
sure oh oh I'm saying yes by jumping
okay
wow oh oh oh I see me jumping showed how
literally literally how I'm going to
kill him with a jump he doesn't stand a
chance ow you D Mario I know all about
you you've got more jump in you than a
box of frogs especially more than me cuz
I'm not even a frog I'm mow from the
tple P I'm a Frog can you believe it no
I can't jump embarrassing huh yeah we
can't jump cuz you're not a frog I know
frogs very
well how about it Mario will you help me
catch that selfie
please yeah gu yes what if I say
no thank you thank you thank you thank
you the young frog mellow
who who doesn't look at all like a
frog joins Mario in his quest oh oh
oh
what the game agrees with
me
yeah I like being agreed on
the Scrapbook has been added under your
Journal you can check it out to look
back on your adventure so far oh I I
literally packed him into my journal
he's
gone cute I mean I don't know somehow
his clothes are like Asterix and Obelix
cloes feel like he's
cosplaying
Obelix let's look at this oh
[Music]
oh
so okay they write down like phrases
important phrases
here uh from those moments when that
happened Mario let me tag along to get
back my stolen
coin I'm shocked you know L of course I
do of course I'm
European it's a European comic that was
all over my childhood
he's tough kind and a really great guy
that crocodile might have left him so we
better hurry and chase after
[Music]
him don't like the L Li we I don't know
if I'll be looking at that very much but
wait let's look at this so that the
exclamation mark is
gone
oh
oh hold on hold on
a it's still no okay it's gone I thought
I would be gone there until I look at
every single
enemy a hot toad comes running to
support you who knows what you might
get I want to move on I want to want to
Mom I saw him he's in here somewhere he
just don't pass me second did you see
him did he look something like
this oh oh
I Lally have this like superpower of
turning into whatever I imagine
wow he's the one who took my coin why
didn't you stop
him cuz I forgot my bazooka at home sh
give be a break here you little
[Music]
you never catch me or snail could
have run you more later
woohoo
[Music]
uh oh I can't this so
cute so
cute H that's him yeah why we were three
people standing here we could have
stopped him why did we not stop him this
time what was our reason now
yeah okay I'll go get him but thank you
a map if you select map for the menu you
can pick a location to jump to as long
as it's somewhere you've been to before
okay
[Music]
um
flower
[Music]
I followed my
womanly brain waves in
intuition this is not from a guide
whatsoever mhm signal
ring signal will let you know when
there's he touch near you oh oh that's
awesome oh well for now I shall
definitely put it
on nice better than
nothing no I I did not read a guide what
the hell why would
[Music]
I the
Right the rightmost corner of the room
but is this it's not
right maybe it's what the right a right
I maybe
here in the rightmost corner of the room
there's a box you will need to jump of
of the guy's head to reach
it what what
[Music]
box I guess this is the rightmost corner
ah there it is there it is
oh in the same
room it's the same
room
[Laughter]
yay no I didn't read the castle one yeah
I kind of missed that one maybe another
time there he is he probably stashed it
in the bag let's now have him are you
trying to tell me go on home to Mommy
before you get her
[Music]
kid all right yay we have a group we can
fight not alone anymore let's see how
the battle works now ah I cre shared
between the entire party should you use
it to attack or to recover as you learn
specials think carefully about who's to
use ooh frog see this mow see that thing
that is still kind of far from being a
frog but it's more frog than you are by
far so be
ashamed oh did I do it no I don't think
I
did why does he look at the
camera is this
normal because I have him selected I
just noticed does Mario do that to oh
Mario does it too
okay he looks so happy into the
[Music]
[Laughter]
camera why is he looking
here let's try
this W oh it's even his weakness
okay oh I did it it appeared pretty late
though
nice malow is so happy but I feel like
he's breaking the the the wall the
fourth wall by looking right at
me really feels like he's looking at
me in the Bandit's way there's a
spinning Bandit's way is this a Bandit's
way
yes it is spinning flow jump on jump and
jump up right at diagonal
jump huh hi hi guys
uh I was streaming my my tangent notes
you
[Music]
know I will tell me yeah true but wait
where is
this I didn't see a spinning flower is
it like is the next room still Bandit
way it might
be what the is this one
[Music]
[Applause]
sus ah the timing for that one man is
pretty sudden out of nowhere or also
kind of
[Music]
late
down but I I thought the ring will ring
ring when oh level up
Fireball
bonus physical when I enter the room but
like then that could be like still
pretty
like a big area so I want to look at the
guide oh there's the
flower you couldn't jump to save your
life kid so I guess it's
goodbye
oh that is the spinning flower but maybe
there
[Music]
more and jump right upright a diagonal
angle
what diagonal
[Music]
diagonal
what there must be another one right
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay uh ah I already fell down Mama
Mia this music is fun
[Music]
H uh why
is why are the blocks only up until that
point
[Music]
anyway oh wait I can just reach it like
this okay ah oh okay it's like the game
the game from the sports
F the prin the princess game where they
uh the free Knights had to make a
the the path for the
princess
[Music]
oh a croa cola what what the is
that all members recover fully okay cool
cool cool
cool that was easy for me to reach nice
nice first
try I am persistent P but I'm on ad
my
is
there no okay no more in Ban's
way don't need to be so
careful there's nothing to find
anymore
[Music]
40 the accessory yeah I know I have it
but I still what what do you want
[Music]
what
hey stay here stop running
[Music]
coward can
I oh oh nice can I set it so that I
attack with mow
first or is that not possible I
wonder woo wow I'm on the roll
wooo wooo ah speed stat oh okay okay
okay
okay so Mario just too
[Music]
fast and I don't want to use the thing
right now cuz it took me a while to get
the gge
up I don't want to use a special
maybe if I fight this
dinosaur
stop I want to fight one of these
[Music]
ones oh dear
okay I had a realization about like this
K9 thing just
recently the naming because it's a
K9 so they call the unit K9 I was like
[Music]
wa
a what is this what am I what am I
getting a power mushroom and I use it
immediately 30 attack up or was that a
heal to
30 and power
up
[Music]
he
died I didn't
realize what happens if he
dies do people die when they're
killed
y croak he's at the end of his croaking
days no wow nice 92
sheesh hey I blocked that
one
I'm not permanent okay he he's
already happy and back up on his
feet wait did I get the thing out of the
box when I jump on the enemy before
fortify did
I I don't even remember is he healed now
no okay I guess I'll heal you even
though I don't have that much a yeah
right okay that's so
weird I did
okay cuz now it seems like I can't reach
it
[Music]
anyway
oh what what you doing do you want
that you can't jump well enough huh T to
is tempting but now is not the time well
it's definitely time for me to get the
treasure box I want
it wait no way no
stop death
perception
yes oh that's what that's oh do I got
exp that's what that's for oh my God
[Music]
I got level up for that let's
go HP rain oh nice hit ages before the
shower
ends uh wait this this stat is for mow
right then I would get uh
Magic he's
[Music]
dancing
that's M right
okay oh oh
yes you can press y in the field to use
specials to recover
oh thank you for making this
possible I guess we got to continue this
game to reach the other Treasure Chest
if we can can
we
[Music]
might take some time though I wonder if
it's worth
it feel like it should be worth it but I
don't know if I have the patience and
the jumping skills for it if I kill all
the enemies here will there be new spawn
I hope not cuz I will I I'll say let's
get rid of all of them and then
try
nice let's do a little
thunderbolt I I always go too early
on this one
[Music]
m
yes at least this one this one I kind of
figured
out okay okay okay one SPS only return
after you leave the level and come back
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay I just did it like 1 second after
the Fun hit the ground oh okay maybe
I'll try that next
time this is why I can't play Mario
games
M but like this angle I feel like makes
it especially
difficult
to understand where you are
perceive uh oh the
[Music]
Shadows where are you going I'm going to
the other chest here look at the sh yeah
what what what's what's not helping
me not
much
okay did
I this taking ages can I stop oh wait if
I jump early I'm kind of changing its
route oh wait I
see there is ah a I I finally understand
how these things work I thought there
was a final place where they stopped
but
Y
Cool skilled jumper after
all I I I got two treasure chests you
got nothing dead end and they would give
up I'll just have to hide
that doesn't really look like a
dead end there's so much
more it's come to hiding let's see if we
can sneak out behind
him first we need
this ah you little sh jump
[Music]
me
yeah nice reflex wah
wa
[Music]
I I I should start my tangents doing
these fights but I'm kind of in the
[Music]
zone them
my my
tangent
[Music]
notes m
ah yeah maybe first of first of all I
should want to double what want to W
coins challenge the system win
big
yes Yi okay oh God
a here y I thought it was going to go
longer cute man there a little bird
there too
though Yoshi looks funny Yoshi looks so
so squeaky
[Music]
sh I got you that was
nothing no I know exactly where you
are oh am I supposed to like
ah I understand there we go I basically
was right is this like a wait is this
like uh supposed to be the same like
animal as Yoshi I just
realized it could be but Yoshi doesn't
look so threatening on this one this one
looks kind of
threatening oh no he's a crocodile no oh
okay okay okay then what's
[Music]
Yoshi what is Yoshi a
dinosaur ah okay very similar things
though
your eyes are much faster than your feet
at this R oh wait that was still not
it
what you little I swear to
[Music]
God stronger not a h I'll take you down
first hey perfect
hit oh I am ah I did do it correctly but
I just got to do it again okay
okay I was thinking like hey I I feel
like I got you there but
[Music]
okay okay so I think oh that was my
fault I think I should tell you guys the
the tangent that I was telling in one of
my pre chats in the waiting room cuz you
guys said it's good enough for attention
so I guess I'll bless you with it
everybody
here oh nice
mow yeah give me my
coin my Dodge Coin did you really
believe me I was
lying
ooh oh no the
crocodile is attacking oh I'm so
scared I can do
Fireball H maybe I'll do it let's
see
oh
this one's like a repeat push attack
nice nice nice nice nice that one I
don't have to figure
out
[Music]
timing
oh dowsing a tail
fire yeah yeah yeah so this other day in
Japan I woke up and I chose violence
literally so I was going to go to get
breakfast somewhere oh you oh holy
[Music]
I wonder how much HP he has left
let me try again
Fireball 61 okay okay I'm a bit oh oh
that was a close one holy
oh I blocked it oh my God
this dude also woke up and shows
violence I I think I should revive him
just in case if we all go down we're
but he wakes up with okay full HP
okay okay okay
um
oh I guess I'll take a
look
it 160 still oh wow okay then it was
worth um bringing him
[Music]
back so H I was on my way to get
breakfast at a restaurant and I was like
walking down this like pretty
[Music]
calm damn it pretty calm
sidewalk that was pretty much the only
one walking in in One Direction there's
no one coming from the other
side and
suddenly someone a guy in like a suit
like a salary man going to work or from
work I don't know I don't
care like kind of like from behind me
diagonally crosses
me yeah and then decides to even though
the sidewalk is pretty wide and I'm like
not taking up much space decides to like
cut me off yeah yeah he definitely had
it coming that little
walks diagonally past me but like
so close to me and not as fast as me
like if you deciding to walk past me cut
me off then you better be walking faster
than me at least in the moment where
you're like passing me because otherwise
I'm going to bump into you and it's
going to be your
[Music]
fault way too
early y oh
lucky
nice um yeah he sealed his fate that
[Music]
moment you didn't have to cut me up
so he does that and I noticed like he's
dangerously close to me he chose to be
dangerously close to me and the danger
zone and so I'm like I'm not having this
I just woke up I'm going to breakfast
and I'm not having this I will not slow
down like I usually do just because you
decide to cut me off so closely I'm not
going to slow down for you no no no not
this time you little you chose this
you are my making this happen so I did
not slow down I just I I just kept on
walking in the same Pace but this
dude after diagonally Crossing me was
walking in front of me slower than
me and it only took like two maybe 2
seconds of us continuing to
walk and I saw in these two seconds I
saw our feet dangerously closing in on
each other and getting closer and Clos
closer and I saw I saw it coming and I
was like I'm just going to let it happen
I'm I'm just going to step on
him so after like a few steps and these
two seconds maybe yeah maybe it was
literally just two or three seconds of
him in front of me and I I just stepped
I basically stepped on his the back of
his
foot and and I I really like flabbergast
and flustered him like he was like what
the like he didn't both of us
didn't say anything but I gave him like
a little bit of like a like a pissed off
look like passive aggressive yeah was
like like like he just stepped on my
foot that's the kind of attitude I gave
him but I was the one who stepped on
him and he looks like so confused he
looks on the ground on the on our feet
and he looks at
me and and he's
like
what just happened I can't believe
someone stepped on my foot basically
like but then like at the same time it
seemed like he also
realized that this isn't really my fault
I think he understood that's why he
didn't say
anything ha some cute small girls
stepped on you but you you do realize
that was your fault right you had it
coming also oh the most important thing
is that I was like walking with my eyes
free look to look around I was like not
preoccupied while he was walking while
looking down on his phone so he was he
was doing nothing
thing that you shouldn't be doing like
you shouldn't there's everybody who
walks somewhere looking at their phone
down not in not like at their
surroundings but down on their phone I
do that a lot too but if you do that
then you shall never feel like it's
anybody else's fault when you're causing
a situation like this
[Music]
so
yeah and I I just felt So
Satisfied oh did he just heal 60 okay
okay okay you want to you want you want
to you
[Music]
wna yeah let's let's get serious you
little I didn't think you would
heal fire is his weakness really
all right I can't no more I mean I could
probably use an item but whatever let's
[Music]
see
one
okay I have
to drink the honey
[Music]
syrup well I was not distracted what do
you mean what do you mean I was
distracted I definitely was not the
distracted one on that sidewalk it's not
like there was like no space on the
sidewalk like I don't I really hated
when people like decid to cut you off
like pass by you because they they want
to be in front of you but then they
don't walk they don't actually walk
faster than you and pass by you like way
too close so that I have to slow down
and I have to go around you I hate that
so this one time I I decided m not
having it
[Music]
today not having it today it did say
weakness huh why why are you only doing
one damage you little
[Music]
wait recover does it also mean to
heal someone who's
dead
otherwise I'm kind of
[Music]
well who knows maybe he doesn't
have that much uh HP
[Music]
anymore maybe
not then let's just try to survive on
our own for
now and block everything
hopefully
[Music]
what
B okay
okay Yos Yos Yos we can do it we can do
it
I too early again but it's okay I
did it I did it
yay was that was going to be really
really
dangerous oh the FR coin it's so
cute got to pay it back in spad kid no
stop the bullying No
Bully adios
amigos we are not your Amigos all right
we got it back
wow was that that was a roller
coaster yeah
anyway I honestly for a moment I felt
scared when I stepped on that dude's
foot cuz I didn't know how he would
react for a moment he really looked
angry I thought he might call the police
on me but he's fine I think he learned
from his actions that it was his
fault I go for HP this
time
that was my stat right yeah we didn't we
got Grandpa's coin
back his demise will serve as a
horn feel gin R for real like maybe
maybe if I wasn't I don't know gu number
one gin and number two a girl small girl
maybe then maybe if it wasn't for that
he would have gotten angry but the fact
that I did it a cute looking guiding
girl that was quite some guts I had on
me also I mean I did act a little bit
like oh
accidental but it was 100% on purpose
like I'm my eyes were on you locked on
you while your eyes were on the phone I
did this very very consciously every
every step I made was very very
conscious more conscious than I could
ever be I've reached new level of
Consciousness I've ascended I could I
could be Jesus right
now I can finish my ER now wow look at
this the C guy left the
wallet we should return it to the police
station oh never mind we're not in Japan
I will not return it
[Music]
then did you get
exp does it it could be a Yakuza side
quest
yeah no it was your fault and it's
unfair to him that he didn't feel
comfortable calling a small woman on her
misbehavior because he would be treated
as the
bully you sound so
serious you sound so serious
[Music]
oh oh
oh I'm I'm
speechless I'm so speechless I
can't
if you want to join me we use the map to
go to
[Music]
the I shall continue to choose violence
more often and teach these people a
lesson who don't look where they're
walking cutting people off while they're
on the
phone no justice I will serve Justice
where are we
going excuse
[Music]
me should I go fast travel somewhere
back to the Mushroom Kingdom I
guess be the bigger person can't be the
bigger person he was l like much bigger
than me and that especially that made me
feel very powerful to fluster such a big
person and and make you make make him
feel
smaller just by stepping on the back of
his
soul teaching him a lesson teaching the
taller guy a lesson small small WWA
literally small small wow teaching Rich
salary guy in suit a lesson that you
can't just strut his stuff and walk down
the sidewalk like he owns
it this shall be the day that serves as
a lesson for all the phone Walkers that
don't look where they're
walking people will learn from this and
everybody on the sidewalk from now on
will be scared of a
Wawa
possibly possibly stepping on their
gorgeous gorgeous
shoes they Gucci
shoes no one will ever ever even attempt
to do such a heinous act ever again at
least not towards me I'm going to close
off tourism because of
you because of you they close the
borders to Japan
pen because of you there's no one
anymore on the
sidewalk wait isn't sidewalk actually a
word that comes up
INRI feel like sounds
familiar my
shoes I think I was wearing sneakers
what the he
what what's going on Mama Mia the sh
guys the sh
guys
Shore why they called
Shore let's use my gge move I oh maybe
it's not really worth it do you guys is
that a Yoshi
egg no oh I get a block for whatever
happens next or what no defense resist
ah no I do okay cool cool cool should
I should I uh
keep the gge moves for special
fights is it worth like saving it cuz
they're jumping on around oh the clay oh
that's I guess it looks like the sword
uhhuh
ah thanks for the memberships guys thank
you get it often enough and it doesn't
do
much I guess I mean I I do think it does
much but just
not if I jump back on
them ha how you like
that bada bing bada
boom that's like nothing holy this
boy is
weak I love that
sound they feel up really fast I know it
doesn't really feel like they fill up
fast to
me wow melow you are
[Music]
useless Mel is the worst character in
the game yeah cuz he's not even a real
frog if only he were a
frog oh wait what look what I found
thank you uh do I have to save all of
these oh my God
this one's the
worst stop it at
[Music]
once
nice
o
oopsy I guess let's do a
funderbolt oh I got it right this time
he a I think was it you motion who gave
me like a hint on when to push it like
that didn't help at all cuz you said
like the first time the Thunder hits
that's like so much earlier than I did
it now than when you actually need to do
it bad
advice have to wait wait quite a long
time for that
[Music]
one
m
[Music]
okay
uh yeah what are we going to do about
[Music]
this he's better with you yeah I mean I
know he would be better but I don't want
to waste so many
flowers also I don't want to waste the
AOE you know when there's only one or
two enemies I feel kind of bad about
using an AOE attack
again I think kind of an RPG
[Music]
mindset leing up is slow for that reason
oh the leveling doesn't seem slow to me
doesn't feel slow to me
oh oh help the people in the castle they
just might help you oh there was someone
there let me in
hidden treasure nearby can I actually
reach it by jumping on the shy guy this
time
maybe wait there's so many this is like
ooh
no
but is it
different H think
[Music]
so you get no Bounce from yeah I guess
so
and
nice oh he missed no good for
me one
damage
hey
[Music]
wow two
damage glad to have you back while what
do you mean back I was only I wasn't
really gone I still streamed and you
know maybe this week I didn't stream as
much but the week before I still
streamed plenty even though I was in
Japan and like doing dance lessons and
all kinds of you know I try my best
to still be there you
know I wasn't really gone and it was
really only one and 1/2 weeks I kept it
really short which made it really
stressful but you know why I did it you
know why I did it for you
guys I knew you guys wouldn't like it if
I was gone for too
long and and also I
mean I also didn't want to stay away
from my cats for too long of
course
and also went to Japan last month too so
I understand you know like I know I know
I know also not like ideal for
me I wish I could do all the things I
need to do in one trip but then then
that would be extremely stressful
[Music]
too
do everything you need to do in one day
if only if only I
could yeah I still try to share a lot of
what's going on with you guys I feel
like you know it wasn't even I wasn't
even gone for that long and it wasn't
even that little amount of
content why do you think everyone went w
gang looks like we have ourselves a new
home we can bounce around all day long
and there's no one here who can stand in
our way yeah who let's bounce in another
way let's bounce night
[Music]
way and yeah I know I wanted to do more
solo streams
[Music]
and actually that's why I brought my my
laptop but the thing is like I ended up
only really having time the first two
days aka the day when I arrived in the
early morning and then the second
day but that was the weekend and I I
requested to have like streaming
equipment right away but it was I think
forgotten to be prepared right
away um and then it was the weekend so I
couldn't be prepared on the weekend cuz
you know had to be a weekday so then I
couldn't stream on that weekend the one
weekend where I did have time for solo
streams
yeah and then the other days I I really
just I was I was so busy so forgive
me yeah my cat I I don't want to I want
they're so cute I hope I can stay with
them
every day for 5 years I don't want to
leave my home anymore for 5
years listen up King wait is this
the same thing that talked to us
before listen up gang these guys are
going to put a stop to our party are we
happy about
this you're asking for it oh you're
going to get it
I pick the wrong people not to B with
bub how about a fat lip to go with that
ugly
[Music]
mustache they're ganging up on me
different dud a looks kind of similar so
I thought
[Music]
maybe the Smithy gang their weapon
inspired yeah I can see that
mhm ah wait ooh we're not looking so
good let's get some honey syrup
and I'm going to let mow heal us that
will be our first
turn hit a before just before the shower
ends just
before oh I think I got it no I don't
know wait it only healed Mario I thought
it would
heal
no a
be well I hope uh do they maybe have oh
I can only no did I have a fire weakness
I hope
so
y okay got to be careful now oh he
[Music]
missed I don't have a I don't have any
more Revival I items damn it damn it
damn it
Dam okay okay
okay yes yo I'm actually doing quite
well right now you what where did he go
I was going to I thought he was jumping
on me I was going to
block oh I'm on a
roll oh I I'm about to fill up my gsh
too I just buy any I thought I thought
maybe the shop wouldn't even be
available because of
the shy
guys yeah definitely delayed attack yeah
bye AE that's okay I still have a lot of
HP or is he just not going to there it
is can't block okay that's fine eat my
special actually might be something
really useless what is this flower juice
oh flower essence why not why
not can't block again why he going to do
that every turn
[Music]
now
M time to become a really good blocker I
can't block this though again
D he's going to do that every turn
no what no
way wow okay time to take down clay
Morton first of all I
[Music]
guess a I got a full one what this
a
goodbye oh he's leaving again then
I
can't can't even I can't even focus on
him
then
W
nice but okay yes lucky the the few
times that I miss the defend they
actually missed themselves
nice should you just jump on him
okay nice
[Music]
one
wow need to heal before he comes
back let's heal now
couldn't down the freebie
[Music]
oh yes okay I'm getting better at
defending
nice can't block that's oh he missed
this is the time
yeah yeah
ah come on we got to give it our all
yeah ah please don't leave yet please
don't
leave okay okay uh oh this he on the
leave I
[Music]
wonder W nice
damage I feel
like it's telling me something about his
weakness but it's not showing up on the
screen
a again I thought I was defending
hell w wa come on
wa yeah this is tough if only I had the
Frog actually he died too early he's
only way to
[Music]
thunder
the ones that stand really close to me
it's kind of difficult with the fireball
cuz the
distance pretty
short I'm string a lot with the bosses
in this game huh no I'm not no it's just
I didn't
expect
[Music]
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
no
a yes
okay he's coming back big guy's coming
back he can't have that much
more HP right but my problem is I don't
have any more flower
points
[Music]
okay can't block but I won't
die please stay for a while I I will use
the garge next turn suppose don't leave
don't leave
don't what do I want flower points would
be good I don't know what a lot of these
things
are should I just like let it happen
[Music]
randomly oh flowes okay I'm fine with
that thank
you oh I can get to pick me up to H oh
well 67
[Music]
baby yes
yes it's like this time I stopped it my
my my
[Music]
reflexes
no such a coward boss yeah for real what
is he doing is he going on like a coffee
break oh wait I'm
[Music]
dying I'm dying
again this fight is
unnecessarily long oh come on because I
lost the supposed alleged frog so
[Music]
early
nice
[Music]
huh no
hey
oh I should
[Music]
heal I
can't
ah wait special let's
jump
69 his FP is
gone well how about his
HP it's time yes
finally w I stalled him but he was about
to die
anyway unnecessarily
painful I brute forced that fight that's
how it
[Music]
feels damn normal mode isn't as easy as
I thought it was going to
be wow
wow
yay make sure to buy the armor from mow
okie dokie okie
dokie oh that was one of the Seven Stars
thingies oh yeah I was I was wondering
because like considering how short the
game is I felt like I should get one
just not good it's not good the mustach
shield pistach shield mustache Shield
one is
strong strong yes we must warn the boss
come
on how nicely they jump in
[Music]
sink me lady would you
care to
possibly bless me with a dance
tonight
I am honored to be in your
[Music]
presence Mar to the
rescue what who were
those TR
Cher my goodness right
[Music]
Mario
I'm Day
Dreaming yeah I was first the princess
and now this it's just too much to
[Music]
bear
Mario did you just come out of my
[Music]
assio how about we ask Grandpa for help
he knows everything excuse me but who
are you oh hello my my name is m I'm
from T pole Pond well any friend of
Mario is welcome here in the Mushroom
Kingdom as I was saying Mario you our
only hope Mario please you must rescue
the princess now Mario I'm in your D too
let's head over to granda's place in tle
P he can
help wait why did I even come to
Mushroom Kingdom in the first
place uh guess I'll find out soon enough
when I got to tired with you again Cloud
clay Morton the sword-like monster who
crashed into the Mushroom Kingdom have
anything to do with the star place that
Mario found our heroes move on to on
toward the Carol
[Music]
sewers
getet
[Music]
I love that
song go back for the treasure you say is
it possible for me to receive the
treasure please move toad so that I may
buy
your head the will of your bouncy
mushroom
head get the treasure that I am looking
for is it in the
[Music]
middle like in front of the
door jump off
ah okay okay okay okay I see I
see nice B nice B nice B ni nice nice
nice um can you get a bit closer thank
[Music]
you the co that was a frog coin
woohoo okay let's go to the item shop
and get uh pants I guess
[Music]
Zu uh Mis I got my coin B
okay well done lad here's the thing I
promised
you make sure it doesn't get stolen
eaten or whatever your grandpa needs it
okay Cricket
pie pants wow something you guys are not
wearing ever cuz your uniform only
consists of a
top has jelly
huh Mario thank you so much grandpa will
be
Delight wait don't don't go inside of me
again I want to put some pants on
you hell yeah let's equip it oh besides
that you jump against any oh it
wasn't possible for any fo prevents
poison
damage H it does give me a lot of stats
even I should get the
shoes oh yeah definitely pick me
UPS
oh let's get the max which is apparently
six
uh let's get a oh wait these are
[Music]
expensive
no maybe
[Music]
two the jump
shoes I'll get them you guys will have
to tell me look at the gun
while I play you have to tell
me oh can I put the ring
on
Mow
maybe I'm yes oh yeah okay well then no
problem then I still don't need your
help
um where are we going
[Music]
next I mean we're going to the to the
home of mow right but like through where
cuz it doesn't show on the
map it doesn't have a weapon yet
yeah seems
[Music]
like okay I'll go
outside he get no weapon yeah he only
uses magic
oh it kind of gives you like
a an image of what's coming up in the
future
too but first we go to this nice Pond
area I don't play Super Mario VG only to
end up one guying
you what wait what do that mean you
you're not you play you're playing it
but you don't want to one guy me or
you're not playing it so you can't one
guy
me there's the entrance grandpa says to
watch out for balloom whoever that is
it's probably a little dark down there
so keep
[Music]
alert
okay
uh might want to save soon no problem oh
why is this music so
spooky why does this give me Castle
Vibes oh he do a
swim oh I have to go from
here read directions on how to enter
yeah sure stand on the P oh really okay
well I came here by going through a pipe
dude
do I immediately want to go for that
pipe or for a different one H like this
one
ooh maybe maybe not maybe I ah wait can
I not ah there we
go not feeling in the book this place if
you mean with the enemies that I
see I mean I don't really I'm not a
completionist like that to be honest
boohoo
cute can't look at me he's scared of me
wait can I go up
there maybe
not
Bo what guess we're fighting a Hob
Goblin out of nowhere
sheesh I feel like he might not like
fire let's give it a
try no he didn't really
[Music]
care did that rat just like leave
forever or is she planning on coming
[Music]
back
uh please do not kill my mow
[Music]
again
no I'm not very focused right
now
[Music]
I swear to God at least he's not
poisoned
anymore wow 76
sheesh
hey I bought
stuff well will he be on one HP once I'm
out of the battle or is he going to
still be on
zero thank you
Yuki yeah I think there's like snow all
over Europe these to today and maybe
yesterday and maybe
tomorrow Europe at least like Central
and north from Europe are currently
blessed with snow one HP okay
[Music]
good how was that only 12 what the
no he was almost down okay
okay
I I I I have
oops dude I will go
back oh ghost find ghost
[Music]
yes
um they all look
very
dangerous to
me maybe not not really a fight I would
have wanted to
initiate so let's
[Music]
see uh-oh oh thank
god let's bring the Thunder out and hope
it's somebody's
weakness
oh
ah
wow
what I can still attack right just no
special attacks
[Music]
okay no what the I mean these
enemies are not normal right oh my
[Music]
God
[Applause]
[Music]
yep it at least I can block that one
holy
sh's weak no leave me
alone can't
block m
H yeah I didn't even feel like I was
skipping that many enemies but seems
like we're
underleveled okay at least he's
down wa
shees W those are
fast
skipped the whole town didn't really
feel like I should have I know I didn't
feel prompted to kill them all I guess I
should
have you're welcome
[Music]
no why are they still not there
oh my
[Music]
God
ah
ooh 10 he got he did 10 damage wow
actually
schooling wa oh
man yeah why
know
I I feel
underleveled
wait on let's go back I feel like maybe
maybe they would at least be lower level
in the in the first room I don't know
just hoping and
coping maybe the cheap cheps would be
something I want to find
[Music]
M wait can I uh use his HP
rain okay
um and trying my best to
block yeah grinding should I not grind
in
[Music]
here
let's fight the fish they can't be that
[Music]
strong wait am I always going to be
missing oh okay I was hoping that
Thunder would be their weakness since
they're in water
wow this is how we get grind in here
let's
go going to go for attack and
defense next one
please no problem if you miss Mario oh
wow it's actually
[Music]
impressive
nice we like to see
it more I would welcome more cheap
Jeeps
um can they come
back
no maybe I should leave the
area that will mean that I have
[Music]
to like re ooh that wasn't the exent
redo some other enemies too
though you can go to another room from
the water they do lost
[Music]
here antidote
pin
[Music]
yeah I suppose I could use that seems
like like there's a lot of poison going
on
here
Ka oh wait
what
oh let's buy it I
guess I I didn't really see how much
damage it was the the the poison
specifically was actually doing to
[Music]
me what if you guys think
I should get
it uh I want to put it on Mow then then
you guys from now on have to tell
[Music]
me if there's a treasure that I should
get
um 5 two let's get a few more of
these and then let's
go back to
the kettle
sewers and I'll try to get those chip
Chips down again actually let me save
[Music]
too what the is Mario what is Mario
wearing he's wearing what he's always
wearing his red shirt and his blue
trousers oh you mean actually what armor
I I gave him the one option they have
the
shirt it also grinding this gamage game
doesn't help you gain levels it also
helps you practice
blocks it it doesn't just oh
okay oh I was confused like what do you
mean
what why
[Music]
not m
no I missed the
just next
allll yes a nice triple o baby you
triple don't necessarily oh once again
y don't necessarily want to use the
Thunder especially now that there's only
one enemy left so we'll be fine with
that
yeah I mean if there's an attack that I
see for the first
time that's hard to read then I don't
think
I it's like so bad that I miss the
timing of
Defending um I'll give Malo some HP
because good Lord he needs
[Music]
it okay where do here we go there's so
many
tubes I go through this love to listen
to K drawing a drawing what are you
drawing okay let's find
you
yeah
[Music]
okay I wonder what's what's the way to
go
I wonder if jump would have been more
effic oh no he died anyway so that's
good oh and oh they leave okay do I get
exp from only the one enemy that I
[Music]
killed what's this water that I
got defeats Undead in a wing
oh ooh okay only the killed ones okay
H
oh now the mice are not running down
here anymore interesting oh I fell
[Music]
down I guess I'll get my
gos
again I always get that why do I always
get that now I didn't even need it it's
that much but
[Music]
okay a you little you are not going
to leave no I will kill you before you
can leave
no why why do I always miss let me try
this way there you
go was I just unlucky or do they resist
normal
[Music]
hits
what
what they have the the the mimics
too I feel like a mimic wouldn't like
fire so
[Music]
no fire no Thunder how about I close you
by jumping on you
aggressively that's his weakness okay
you just want me to jump on you
okay damn maybe he resists all magic
A
[Music]
how much HP do you
have no bonus I
think so you he uses the same attack as
that boss
[Music]
monster nice 120 what you still
alive I down
okay
Ying yeah now give me the
treasure what's your treasure your
jar is it ah I got the true form pin NY
is that an
accessory you won't be turned into
mushrooms or scarecrow well so far far I
haven't been turned into that so I will
only put it on once it becomes an issue
it cryp
that you think it's going to happen soon
and I'm going to regret not having it
just wait save it for the boss yeah
seems like something that might happen
with the boss
[Music]
then why why tell me that why not just
make it happen in the moment n why you
redirect me to
this
weird
exactly for real for real cheap CHS
cheap
[Music]
exp you little
hey oh wait you
y one strongest cheap cheap you are not
so cheap after all I see a another of
cheap cheep or whatever that is swimming
deep down in the
water oh no it's a ah it's a rat's
reflection
ah I see
oh that wasn't even
by and that wasn't even on purpose I
didn't know I would be
able can you stop
[Music]
that that's not how you should welcome
your new
Overlord mellow the fog
okay can we
go is
this is this a dead end no oh it goes
even
further ah wait it led us back to
here is a frog now just when they are
trying to hurt
[Music]
us okay I I don't know where this feels
like a maze I don't know where to go but
I'll go here where we have been before H
but we actually went back why did we do
that was that uh used immediately I
think it was
[Music]
right
ah
no ah once I once I fall down there I
can't go back
right
D damn it damn
[Music]
it I can't
really
and one leaves immediately probably shot
like I got surprised Bamboozled by them
and they were Bamboozled by me being
Bamboozled you know when you only
Bamboozled because some like someone
else is like surprised someone screams
and that scares you too that's what
happened I'm sorry for surprising
you but yeah thanks for the EXP without
me having to lose any
HP oh they have a
shadow I don't know what their weakness
is I'll I'll try it with
fire I mean it's not
bad
yes somehow that one I'm good at
blocking
[Music]
almost down all right let's
go let's see let me look at my tangent
notes I have a lot of tangent notes but
some I
cannot reveal just
[Music]
yet oh wait
ah okay you guys say I can recover from
the
[Music]
stairs can I
really
no wait is this
the again the is this is this the the
thing the what's it called I
forgot the ha
what and it it I we it's not a mimic
anymore it really isn't we did fight it
in this instance right of me being in
here um I don't think I can actually get
[Music]
back from the second yeah
really Second
[Music]
Step
oh
[Music]
nice you surprise me can I jump on this
one
maybe
[Music]
okay
nice okay so here's a
tangent this one time me and
jenma this a cute JMA tangent this one
time me and JMA were
like somewhere in Japan yeah okay just
like doing our thing
walking and
suddenly JMA sees
something that she locks her eyes on and
and immediately runs to it what do you
think what do you think got her
attention so much that she excitedly
runs up to it
h what do you think it could be
[Music]
in gacha
OU oh you guys
remember that she likes OU damn no
it's
not it might be somewhat of a gacha in
some
way it was and I I I was really confused
by how this was so fascinating I really
had her explain it to me it was a a
Pokemon
card pack dispenser like uh not
dispenser the
like vending
[Music]
machine pretty modern looking with like
a screen and all and ah
right I wonder if this is only in Japan
uh or if this is an all over the world
things they have for booster
packs ah please let me get some
[Music]
enemies
I really didn't understand why she was
so excited but she immediately ran over
and bought uh a a couple of booster
packs and so she tells me that
actually
um
it's because in Japan they don't
sell uh they don't sell booster packs
like anywhere in the
shops on its own these vending machines
are like the only place to get them and
they're really
rare and like you can basically just go
to a shop a card shop and buy single
cards or I don't know maybe decks Maybe
but they don't sell the booster pack
separately probably if I remember
correctly just because like
they have a shortage of them maybe I
don't
know ah because they only want to sell
to that that might be something like
that
yeah trying to keep it available for the
kids maybe maybe that's the thought I
can I can see that
yeah I like that thought behind it
[Music]
it what's what's a Boo's
weakness bu to try to resell boxes in
the Spates m i i i i can imagine
[Music]
yeah oh only the water let let's see
let's use the water then I was thinking
about
it do do all of these count as
[Music]
Undead oh there we goes get all I get
the XP for that
[Music]
right that we talking about
TCG yep
y I used to play Magic I really love
[Music]
magic they all die turn all of them are
oh okay okay
okay
reveals MTG prle for real I need to
check if anything happened with my per
request but I'm guessing
no they don't want me to stream that
game I guess oh
nice
um should I use another one of those
Waters I mean I don't
know
perhaps don't know if it's worth it
wasting two of them in one
fight
yeah but I I don't know it was
really cute seeing Gemma so excited and
like getting these Pokemon cards I
didn't didn't even know she was
collecting Pokmon
cards and I asked her do you even do you
even have anyone to play Pokmon web and
apparently she does so like at card
shops I guess you can play with people
so if you're in Japan and go to a
Pokemon card shop maybe you'll meet
jenma maybe yeah it's kind of cute I
like the thought of her playing with
Pokmon
cards oh and oh she told me that when
she opened them once she got
um apparently this was really like lucky
but she got uh from like there were two
different booster packs and she bought
like two of each I think or so and the
first ones she opened of each both
already had the like special rare pull
whatever I don't know what it is but she
got lucky basically with the cards that
she pulled good good for her I'm happy
for
[Music]
her let's
fight card opening stream one well we
did something like that before actually
with JMA together
yeah
M nice
[Music]
ah there he goes all right only one left
then let's attack
normally oh oh yeah okay
[Music]
okay need to prepare for work have fun
if you
[Music]
can ooh
wait jumping is his weakness I didn't
realize it until now pure
water yay say some water say some water
let's
go then I sh Wait I already have free
again I didn't realize that
either then let me use it on the
shadow I got a free you mean the coin or
enough pure
water that was an easy
fight wmy
water collaboration let's see oh I got a
freebie so when it says you get a
freebie it means you get a like you get
back what you just used seems like it
okay then I shall continue using
[Music]
it I got another I got another one
woo oh my God I'm winning yeah
yeah I was like no way no way I'm going
to get another one let's
go Pokemon this time but I don't know
that would really just be for for jma's
sake cuz like I don't really
care much like I don't understand which
cards are good and I don't have a
special connection to it like JMA
does I learned a new move super jump
okay
we desperately need that level
up 25% chance of happening
oh you just sold it for 75 coins you
didn't have trouble defeating weird flex
but
[Music]
okay I I am going to continue using the
pure water cuz we have plenty at the
moment
and I appreciate a quick
fight free me please free me
please yeah nice
fight I can try to land consecutive what
for real and I got a pure water so I'm
back to free again let's go um should I
try to go down here oh okay okay
okay it's a dead
end Frey
[Music]
STS oh okay suck it see you
later why don't you want to fight me
BS why rat Funk honestly
I feel like Bales is going to eventually
release a
song with that title she
must actually it sounds like she already
did
[Music]
rat
leaking her future
[Music]
songs yeah she told
me she told me in my dream no she told
me in the K dinner that we went to where
we ended up just singing H talking
actually not singing But like the the
plan was to have dinner is actually on
the on the day where
I left Japan
right and we were going to have
dinner cuz
B DMD me one day and asked if we can
hang he's like okay I I don't have much
time left on my schedule but we'll make
it
work and so let's fight
you yeah yeah yeah yeah then like I was
in charge of this deciding where we
would go but I I didn't really feel
quite like going to like an isaka type
of place so I gave her I gave her some
choices I said either we go to a noisy
dark isaka or we go to a familyfriendly
happy family restaurant or bails listen
I'm not sure I'm not sure what you're
going to think about this idea but how
about we combine fun with food and go to
k because Japanese K they have bossing
food and you know the karoke itself is
just amazing too
so I thought like for me personally it's
a great idea I wasn't sure how Bales was
going to react to
it but the moment I mentioned Kad she
was like girl I was thinking the same
thing actually I'm like oh let's
go so we went to for dinner we focused
on eating and talking cuz that was the
main goal and then in between we sang a
little bit but yeah 2 hours five songs
roughly we weit like I think I did most
of the talking Bales was like listening
very
interestedly where am I I've been in
these places
before
yeah I was I was I was very passionately
talking about a couple of
topics and Bale strongly
[Music]
agreed is there another pop
here uh I feel like I've been through
all these
tubes
the High School Musical was at the very
end cuz we were like thinking okay what
song can we sing together at the end and
I the only thing I I knew was like I
know Bales likes Disney a lot so I
suggested Disney but that led us to High
School Musical and to the realization
that they have a ton of Disney
songs on the Japanese Kadoka but they
don't have like
uh ah no uh actually they don't have
High School Musical songs like only from
the first movie oh I should have
gone there could I
have yeah they have a bunch of songs
from the first movie but the second one
which we were actually looking for like
we wanted to sing like fabulous and
stuff and they didn't have it at all
man and we we both strongly agreed on
the fact that the second High School
Musical is the best I haven't watched
High School Musical in a long time but I
I feel like I feel like all the songs I
remember are from High School Musical 2
and that must mean that it was
objectively and personally the
best that is a simple request all things
fabulous bigger and better and best
because they didn't have the song in the
kist lineup we just sang it's a little
bit
Acappella I need something inspiring to
help me get along I need a little Fabby
unless that's so
wrong yeah and I told her we should do a
High School Musical watch along
together yeah Shar is so funny
[Music]
man
going to relax and
reow where the am I going I am so
damn
[Music]
lost only seen the first one where the
hell have I not been yet what am I
missing what you NY
I know that was the entrance
[Music]
yeah maybe what about this
one
fabulous bigger and better and let
me uh I don't know I guess that tube
might be
[Music]
interesting something fing I forgot to
was yeah that's what I wanted to do
right was I in that room
was I
there wait wait wait wait wait wait how
do I get there
[Music]
again
uh
is it's not here wait maybe the next
one is it here
no must
be must be
here is it here it's here it's here can
I jump from here like a long jump yes
[Music]
yeah
no
no I fell down that well I was just
being in character cuz honestly
Mario stumbles and tumbles all the
time wait is this the same
place it is wa much much much oh
no oh no no no no no no no no no mama to
jump and the
run I can't to do it because I have
played no Mario games in my lifetime oh
mama M I'm here again I found out like
the
[Music]
connection
yummy pure pure
[Music]
water
let's try a thunderbolt why're not bring
it on yeah we like we like some
[Music]
thundering oh wait the actually the
other one do like jumps that's his
weaknesses and death I just
[Music]
remembered a poison me again
aist whatever don't
care can't hurt
me my mentality my mental health is too
strong ooh ghost time what what do we
want what does this
do water has been drained oh no so scary
spooky what's up these
boohoo
[Music]
M I will use it on the
bll
[Music]
bye-bye actually
no let me
use honey
syrup have the the pizza buff oh I wish
I had a pizza Pizza buff right now on
myself I want a pizza I actually don't
know what I'm going to eat
[Music]
today W one
hey you know my mom almost uh made the
fire alarm happen last night she was
cooking dinner for me
cuz she left today this
morning and she's making some
sauce with like first like she was like
burning
sugar
and then she put in balsamico vinegar
and all of that created a lot of a lot
of fog and my uh like she's also I think
not used to how hot my stove get
get yeah and then it set off the smoke
detector I guess because it went like be
really
loudly and I thought it was going to go
it was that like I thought that was
already the fire alarm but apparently
[Music]
not
because uh it actually turned itself off
like after a few seconds so everything
was thank God I was really worried I
really thought this was going to be the
second time I'm setting off a fire alarm
in this
apartment I was going to be so
embarrassed I was like Mama you set up
the fire alarm God damn it and then it
was
fine is there a difference between smoke
alarm and fire
alarm didn't really realize that
[Music]
no same thing
M
okay I wonder why it turned itself off I
I didn't I didn't think that once it was
activated it could like so quickly
change its mind and be like oh nope I
guess they're probably
fine wrong false alarm false alarm I
didn't think that it would do
that
Frey you can stop it by poking it I
don't know about
that depends how much
smoke check batters I actually just like
fairly recently had someone check my
smoke detectors I
think I even in my my Japanese airb B
had someone check my fire smoke
detectors it's like so annoying why does
this have to happen when I'm here why
can't you do this when I'm out of
here woke me up
early yeah but I was already struggling
with
[Music]
sleep oh wow you actually missed sheesh
Dam
[Music]
it now it was scheduled like I knew it
was going to
happen but it took quite a
while took like 10 minutes cuz like
somehow they were like in this one room
apartment they were like like six six
smoke
detectors and on one you seem to be like
pretty stuck kept on going back to that
one thank you 35 months is like oopsie
ah so much isn't it oh suddenly you get
a good hit in
wow okay middle got woo
oh my eyes they're
burning shall we do another boo fight
wait
M some honey syrup and then we can do it
then we can go in let's spam the pure
water 36 let's go thank
you hey Elie Lapin do you want to El
laen I wish say Elsie lapen but prob is
supposed to be laen
right do you want to edit a video for me
[Music]
H help me out a little bit help your
boss
[Music]
out life hiring he's hired by CI but
that's fine Callie's hiring the people
that I hire
too everybody's hiring the people that
I'm hiring
Kell's hiring chy too now ch's like so
busy I'm asking chy to do something and
he's
like y I'm so busy I'm like
what what
happened yeah I'm like the talent
finder everybody like uses the people
that I use which I'm happy for them to
be making money go get that bag they get
so busy
too busy for me so just drained the
water but we're like not going anywhere
in this room huh then let's go
back oo now we can walk here and I guess
this tube wasn't available before was
[Music]
it wow are the trend set are so real so
true ooh oh I feel like we are at the
boss pretty
much
[Music]
what about the other things up
here a Mama
[Music]
Mia it's up
there come
[Music]
on okay boss let's
go oh what is that
cute
do we pull its
tongue this this must be below is that a
fire hose or his
tongue he has four
eyes ah it's snack attack and you're it
Snack
Attack yes below wait I don't want to
hurt it it's kind of cute just cursed by
having too
many things
doubled let's try the super jump wait
wait I should have put on this
like this this pin right damn it
probably this thing is going to turn me
into weird right
I thought I was going to press the
button a lot of times
[Music]
y
ta 449 weakness lightning fear poison
mute lightning okay o room service has
been kind to me where's my bab what
y okay so none of my attacks
really um do anything special you have
to time it it's infinite R okay let's
try
again oh I got three hits pretty good I
would say for the first try where I
actually understood what what I was
supposed to do it caps at 100
she okay let's try to do this fight with
actual two of our teammates not just
one because I need the thunder so you
better not die on me
ah stick for body headful of straw
give me a scare no no no no no no can I
block it no can't I don't want to be
scarecrow I can't do
anything I guess I'll
defend no stop don't lick
me how long am I going to be a scap will
I will I automatically get out of
[Music]
this I guess the pure water doesn't work
on this thing
either two of three turns yeah it's it's
fine I want the I'm going to use
Thunder can't stand it the hunger the
hunger
no
no now I have to use my FP to actually
being useful and do something while my
mate is gone is he coming
back he's coming back right he's going
to spit him out like next turn or
so
[Music]
right
no only if I can do damage per death
Noah he's not coming back this fight no
come
on egg what was that
again a blocking the next move okay that
could be good could be
[Music]
good
wow a you guys you li I didn't even get
one guide I got 100
[Music]
guide I wish I wish now I had enough for
the oh I do have enough for the F let
go you little
shits what you're turning me to
[Music]
again I can't even use an item as a
scarecrow no
[Music]
way oh mama
M my last FP
item please don't eat me again
please
no but it's okay cuz I can use uh the
Thunder anyway let's do
jump and then let's do Thunder there
okay that's
fine that's
fine
[Music]
yeah three and
two now I I got another I got another
freebie so I can fill up my FP
again so far this boss fight is
definitely going better than the other
one I just should have put on the pin
little did you know
I'm all at stopping a flood of
water so long
[Music]
so he he
won no it says I
[Music]
win or did I
win but I don't really it didn't really
feel like I got all of his HP
down did he just pece out out of nowhere
decided like I don't want to play this
game
anymore it's not fun with only
scarecrows what the
hell must have been lying when he said
water would come gushing out of here uh
no no he wasn't no he wasn't why he Com
when just switch it back before he
washed away yeah then um jump on the
thing
[Music]
you stupid you stupid
oh but that looks like
fun at least when I'm just looking at
it this is the me's River Course what
the crash course uh yeah I mean I don't
want a crash though maybe a more like
softer course jelly course I don't know
instead of a crash
course start off first at The Falls use
l to move left or right and score
coins
okay P spe to make little Headway
against the blow
B along the way there a few holes as
what will happen we'll just keep that a
[Music]
surprise doesn't sound good all but yeah
but go to the no okay okay
y I got
it no should I go for the hall maybe I
should let me
try what it's like a it's like a Disney
uh
ride wo pretty it's just nice to look at
but nothing to
do oh and then echo on of this hole oh
maybe there's another frogco here oh oh
no there's something else
there W oh oh oh I go back here okay oh
frorn on the left rock corn on the
left mhm trying to go as slowly as
possible I go for the hole again is is
the same
thing more or less
[Music]
still cute some of the holes are a
little more than IE candy
okay cute oh cute oh
cute
a wait
he's the chap chep ended up on his Fork
oh I got the
ah I got the flower power
woo
yeah yeah yeah I I didn't really see it
yet but I
saw
um that I didn't really look at the
picture but I saw that it has been
perhaps
finished nice
[Music]
soon I'll use it when I start the tales
of AR rise DLC but I don't know when
that will be oh oh come on no there's no
way I'm getting that one w
no no no no no no no no
no M I almost had maybe this hole can
bring me back somewhere
[Music]
higher that one showed up like oh thank
you
really l oh oh
really late and so far in the
corner okay where is is this next cor is
this the
end looks like the
[Music]
end hey I almost had them all
no Barrel jumping event uh another thing
okay time you jumps and grab coins along
the way okay jump to the next Barrel
before they
Collide but it did
collide miss it and you'll change course
aha okay you didn't really show me how
to jump onto the next one though leap
over the fish that pop up or you lose
coins okay it sounds
[Music]
difficult uh uh
ah
[Music]
H okay I'm like pretty bad at this
one I was like still kind of like
figuring like getting getting the vibe
you know figuring out the
[Music]
vibe
oh the music is so
[Music]
fast
you little
S I barely get any
coins
man ah wrong idea no thank you for the
banking did I even make any
money oh I did
w try to CL you got for me for frog
coins as a first time only bonus I give
you a frog for
60 M Tad P Pond got more info them okay
we got 27 ah and the coins have to be
specifically from
this come back and try again
okay I got a Koopa
[Music]
shell it keeps the coins um let me I
want to do it again
you can try your luck again if you get
on the trampoline it will only cost 30
[Music]
coins I don't know maybe
no poopa sh equipment
okay how come oops see how come I didn't
get like a one of the
uh special stars from The Boss f
uh what am I doing uh uh equipment
shirt Cooper shell kick to
attack
oh wow okay thank
[Music]
you that was difficult first
try feel like I did pretty badly on the
second thing wow the T
PES oh my God they're so
big thank you thank
[Music]
you no no there's never a b just always
goes like like that I accidentally
left is there never a b there
[Music]
is
when oh it's waiting for
me to do what to talk what what do you
mean
talk where is the
the
no hey can I help
you m it's you we've heard all about
your adventures with Super
Mario he calls me Super Mario if that's
my last name you guys speed up bom right
you know about that see Mario the wonder
ways of the world bring news to us here
that's why Grandpa knows all the News
That's fit to
hear are you really du Super
Mario everybody you little guess who's
here ah they're so big oh what's with
the last one he's the real thing but he
doesn't look anything like I thought he
would they do say he can jump better
than a froggy I wonder if it's only a
rumor
good
wa your
[Applause]
mouths well well what's new frog
s Grandpa Mario's been
help Grand Grandpa's Mario's been
helping
me I know child the rainstorm we just
had that was you wasn't
it
ouch watch it up there you're supposed
to make me look like I'm floating here
okay what's happening where is
he ah okay that's what he looks like H
then I'll change the voice
again
wait wait wait
wait he's a
fake
a he's acting like a cult
leader I can see the
litu welcome so you are Mar yes am the
Frog St you have come to seek wisdom
from me have you not I've been waiting
for you yes all people can often give
good
advice
Lord but how R over me let's get more
comfortable come along and we'll
talk clear
reverse
come
along t p don't just float there make
yourselves
useful form a bridge for
Mario all right
oh the music is different very
different wait there's like more oh
no what what what what Co did I do W
welcome to the Frog coin and por your
first timer aren't you listen not the
green coins you find periodically of all
coins accumulate them and you can buy
items at the tar
really ooh I have 11
now racist part is attack Power
Defense attack power aha for like single
ones put enemy to sleep do they have
different items juice bar are you card
member even toad of sky has a who the
is why does it sound like a like a
gamer tag name of a
toad or something they got from like an
online
database might want to save it for later
okay okay okay sorry you're limit you
limited to this menu if you don't have a
current membership
card Tad pole Cola party recovers 30 HP
oh for 16 is that good is that a good
[Music]
deal a chovsky ah
toski should I
buy I'll
buy maybe uh maybe for the time when I
have a bigger party though but
yeah situationally good m
[Music]
wow I must explore before going to the
place where they actually want me to go
play notes by jumping on the T let's
hear some
oh is there like a specific Melody to
play to get
[Music]
something surely
yeah what you you got to find the hint
for it maybe it's in the
bgm surely it's also in
um in the in the you know
in in the guide but I can't see it right
now is that something you
composed that sort of resembles the
melody I'm think oh sort of what are you
thinking of the
to ah must be some kind of chovsky
Melody chovsky surely isn't copyrighted
anymore right what's a famous chov I
don't know chovsky
[Music]
chovy well I'm like which one would it
be maybe
maybe there's a
Shany that's so annoying to try not
cracker are you just saying that because
of a de nuts
joke can I play
this no ads why do I have ads
like I'm on my waa
account oh wait this one's the right
[Music]
one how the am I supposed to make
this ah maybe
D maybe that that feels like something
they
might oh wait you going to teach me
no
way between the second and the third
lines from the top lies
[Music]
d uh
okay this too much for me
already
[Music]
m n the's not going to die so what was
this
[Music]
like let's
try
uh no can I
cancel
I don't know this like too
difficult I don't care
[Music]
it's actually pretty high oh
no I don't know I don't know I don't
know this
sucks what the ones that
stay there's just one that's
staying
oh the ones that stay are correct
what how many times do you want me
to do
this
[Music]
uh okay I have an
idea like I could try
to yeah but this also difficult try to
get everybody in one line for each round
and
see
H is the first one also going to stay
from the last run or do I have to
remember this
no oh wait H there were actually three
correct ones
um
Super Mario RPG
[Music]
T to of
Sky
no where's my
[Music]
mouse I don't care don't
care I will do it my
way I'll probably up anyway
that was too
[Music]
early
I don't know maybe here maybe too
late something like that oh oh oh
oh the last ones felt like wrong
remarkably similar
right okay Stay Stay Stay Stay
Stay
ah
uh pretty
close I don't
know I don't
know
ah okay maybe that's it maybe that's it
it's pretty
difficult
[Music]
H yo it even by looking at the guide
it's difficult okay
you're welcome to of Sky please take
this as a token yes go Alto card if I if
I ever need help with my compositions
again I'll look for you there here until
then you oh there was going to be
more are there going to be
more what's this Alo card
though oh I got it I got it
I want to give myself some credit for
that a membership card what that's
that's where I get the membership card
for the juice
bar yo this is kind of
sus no
way let's see what the juice bar has
some banana smoothies maybe even an Oreo
[Music]
shake just one more drink that's
it I don't even want that now that's too
expensive damn okay let's actually
[Music]
go oh what a nice
little island you have here
here yes come into my sanctuary and
partake of my wisdom
[Music]
children there's only two cups of tea
and only one is filled
anyway what does this
mean oh that would have been one Tacko
that would have helped me with that
whatever I don't want to go through all
the door me
daddy do remembering
[Music]
Arc YouTube audio play on that's fine
probably yeah cuz I'm thinking isn't
chaikovsky
like like isn't that the music I played
like really
old isn't it really really really
old it's public domain I think this I I
looked for a recording that sounded
pretty original and public
domain the music is written on that sign
what that sign how
[Music]
what
[Applause]
[Music]
chocolate
SMY character I should rescue the
princess yeah if only you knew the truth
he's somewhere there what how do you
know he's evil that's why he has the the
cloud person with
him
what was this
awkward
silence what
[Music]
happened was he like too shocked by the
thought of her not being there anymore
[Music]
mhm just when I was about to free the
princess I heard a loud crash so huge
sword split the sky up oh suddenly can
something like
crazy out of the blue a Shar sent you
sent a free of you flying
B piz still somewhere out there
no you worried about the princess But
first you need to take care of
SMY his underlings are wreaking fa in
our world CLA Morton whom you defeated
at the Mushroom Kingdom was one of them
more will be
coming grandpa I almost forgot to tell
you something we found a star the
Mushroom Kingdom Castle do you know why
it was there a
star most
interesting this may sound illogical but
I believe shooting stars can Grand
wishes and now more than ever I believe
they play a vital role in the fight
against
Smithy was that too much to absorb
no okay guys you can sh up about the
public domain now we'll see what
happens okay it's fine it's
fine it's quite a situation we have on
our hands isn't
it wow everything sounds so dire and
serious so go I guess clay was
only the first of many Mario some of
them will make Bowser seem
nice probably Bowser is usually quite
the
loser
[Music]
[Laughter]
of course he's going to accompany me why
you talking about I'm only a simple
topole I thought you were a frog this
adventure isn't for
[Music]
me my my boy I've kept
just it's going to say it it's going to
say it
no don't crush his
dreams you're not the tple yeah cuz he's
a frog
right
[Music]
money oh I love this
I was sitting here one rainy day
enjoying a snack of
cricket and I happened to see a basket
floating down from the Falls I peaked
inside and saw a little baby staring
right back at me the name mow was
written on his belt I felt sorry for the
little bundle of puff and took him to ra
my own grandchild he had powerful magic
oh he's
shaking oh he's shaking and I knew he
was more than a piece of fluff I thought
surely this child must be from some far
off
land I'm
[Music]
adopted
tadpole almost if you turn the letters
around almost becomes adopted ad
adop the only thing is like the L should
be a
d
[Music]
CH holy holy holy did you
guys notice
that
whoo
is what that's not on purpose
[Music]
right wait is that is that
actually something that matters later on
kind of a stretch I don't think
so adopted
[Music]
tple I'm
adop what is the name in Japanese adop
an adopted child is like a Yoshi Yoshi
but tle I forgot what was TPO
T
TP what if it's
[Music]
also oh yeah oh it's just
ODI no that doesn't really have the same
kind of
[Music]
connection m I'll let you
cook Yoshi what what Yoshi no Yoshi Yosi
Yoshi is a to
what so
sad can't even be sad as a small 3D WWA
can only be
happy holy there's so much
happening now it's
overwhelming
well now is not the time to cry go with
Mario's adventure and find your real
family your real mother and father out
there
[Music]
somewhere your bious magic is sure to
come in handy on your adventure you'll
take him along
[Music]
yes Granda thank you for the
pinky
I won't cry anymore I'll go on this
adventure with Mario and find my real
family now be a real boy will then it is
settled you must embark on your
adventure immediately first go to roast
down where I need your
help yes I'm a big boy I will go save
the world and find my wheel
family
that's byebye tadp see you later
suckers talk to him again
huh you mean Mr frog the frog
Overlord frog
Lord he's
crying
it'll be quiet around you with mellow
gold maybe you SN that's right I have
forgotten all about it I will give you
something for the pie you brought back I
know you all have the stuff I used when
I was M let's
go oh froggy stick froggy stick come in
handy do not forget to equip it did you
see his a again now huh huh well that is
important
wait how much extra 20
sheesh all right
party let's
go you missed again
Mama Don't
[Music]
Blink yeah he has a weapon now is
suddenly much stronger I
hope let's go next
next the yellow tiles are I
know you can't jump off a t and is
blue I
can't what is that
star
[Music]
no now I know what it is it's an enemy a
star
slap it's so shiny
[Music]
me shy guys shy shy shy sh sh sh sh sh
guys he looks so happy why are you so
happy huh you're
adopted
[Music]
thought
give me that yeah okay there it
[Music]
is no that's not where I want to
go that's not really where I want to
go I I don't even know where I want to
go I just want to get everything that's
available here on this
Pond oh
nice
oh M no
hold yeah cobal and mow are pretty it
died pretty similar aren't
they okay I'll just go here for now now
let me
go we go here
then
oh new
enemy they immediately run
[Music]
oh new attack item very
cute
so when it falls down is maybe when I
push the
button
maybe you little
[Music]
they hate
Mario what what did what did Mario ever
do to
them they started out hating
[Music]
me where am I going here oh we're back
to the pond oh okay okay okay that's how
this
works huh
uhhuh then we shall go this
way oh
hello oh if
they're no I should get like some kind
of like Buff when I attack them or like
jump into the battle when they're like
you know fainted like they were just now
mhm what is this Pokemon anyway over
there surely it doesn't like fire
spiders hate fire kill it the fire
fire it I didn't care
okay well good
[Music]
enough Doom
Reverb a I can still attack normally
ooh I think I got the right timing
there fire fire light the
fire they hate being squashed by the
boot more
[Music]
OHA
attack since I apparently skipped too
many enemies last time I am now going to
try to do my
best to get as many items as uh enemies
as possible enemies did I say items
twice I mean
enemies need to fight more get more of
that EXP
did P Senai like she cleared it in in a
in a 112 hour stream did she play in
Breezy easy breezy mode or like how else
did she do
[Music]
it oh
nice normal
mod
really easy game if you doing I guess
yeah you probably didn't like look much
for Secrets but still like if you if you
able to do it in one sitting 12 hours
that tells me that she wasn't
underleveled either
right
so she must have done a lot of battles
like she probably didn't really avoid
them like I sometimes did now and I
immediately got payback for avoiding
them
so D maybe she really had all the
timings down really well ah she played
the original oh okay okay so it wasn't
really
blind
ah okay that that makes sense then she
knows the combat then she knows where to
go a little bit if she remembers okay
okay okay okay that makes sense lot more
sense
[Music]
now Corona and O play the
or I I
never did this game even come out in the
Germans
speaking countries I feel like it
didn't did it cuz I never saw it when I
was younger
maybe it's really just that
old no it didn't right okay yeah that's
probably why cuz like at that time at
that age whatever age that was I'm
guessing it was like really small small
but even then I feel
[Music]
like if it if like when you that young
you don't pick up on games that are not
even in your own language you know like
they're not even so in your country so
like 1996 okay yeah I
yeah yeah I was not in
this no I was I was not really
available 1996 and not even in my
country no surprise I missed out on this
[Music]
game
cute I like the
[Music]
tunes
no again okay chill out now I like
hearing it
but
again yeah we're sleeping
okay stop
[Music]
spamming h
H wakey
wakey I don't know how much more HP they
have ah let's just kill
him maybe I have a pin to protect this I
don't want
it I don't want
[Music]
it oh so by the way I
met I met someone special
today remember a while ago when I was
taught
[Music]
AOE by a certain tall pretty
lady from twitch a flesh tuber
Ellie yeah I met her today
woohoo just die I don't want to waste my
flower points on
you God damn
[Music]
it damn it how much
HP
oh my
God y she was really
[Music]
tall yeah we had like
brunch and there was a cat at the cafe
like it's Lally like it lives there it's
like a cafe
cat so
[Music]
cute and um yeah just that was the first
time we met met of course so it was like
lots of like first time is talk just
kind of kind of good talk but I didn't
have so much time cuz I had to stream
afterwards and you know so we just
really lefted at
that but it was nice seeing
her it's a good it was a good
opportunity to like get to know her that
the the fact that she was
here oh we talked in German the whole
time by the
wayman's really
good like last time after that collab uh
remember we talked a lot oh hundreds
right but we talked like
in mostly in English at the
time but probably because of the
surroundings naturally like she just
talked German on her own the like
constantly so I thought okay maybe she
wants to speak German
[Music]
today so we did just
that I was going to ask for English menu
for her and she was like no no no it's
fine German menu is
fine German always works
oh hi hi
Z is her German better than her English
no no no no no it's not better than her
English but it's pretty damn
good I want to get more FP potions
man did she lift you up no I should have
let her
try oh what's going on over
here yeah don't don't
Bowser here don't get caught be
quiet is he training
[Music]
them no she didn't visit AA for me no no
no she had other things to do but it was
a nice
nice actually like it seems like she
came to Austria like pretty much on the
day when I left to
Japan and then she said she's leaving
tomorrow in the morning so we literally
just had this one day I was
lucky this one
opportunity all right people from ranks
Jagger head of the sorry I'm going to
read this normally shout Warriors
Warriors we that Koopa Master of the
hooded sorcerer
[Music]
this yeah I'm glad I could make
it
yeah German sub Chann we did talk about
it um soonish hopefully going to do a
little German collab perhaps of AOE on
my channel and last but not least goom
Hilda Grand damn
lady oh oh oh but I feel like I've seen
a female glomba design
Goomba Goomba it's a Goomba right is a
GAA like I've seen a a a female goomba
design before but this is just a default
[Music]
one the bridge is down but we'll find a
way to get back in move out on a double
oh they're they all struggling going to
get back in
no oh yeah yeah Paper
[Music]
Mario Bowser and his minions must be on
the way to Bowser's Camp come on Roose
is Just J
hand W town has a lot of treasures I
think oh that's Rose
seems a bit affected by
the the
forests little
whatever what
what what just happened it's not a bug
right see arrows come flying out from
the forest and when you hit you can't
move see look I can't move a bule now I
know how a scarecrow feels oh
dear are you stuck too since the day a
shooting star found fell to the forest
ours have been showering Our
[Music]
Town yeah be that's terrifying we need
to help
them no okay I thought maybe that would
be a treasure D I tell you it's scary
out here but someone's got to pump the
water yeah be careful water pumping very
important job oh that looks like there
could be
a I guess an
actually oh yeah all right okay I got
this one about the guide let's
go hey M it's so nice for you to drop by
the shop what can I do for you oh this
is the shop nice a fake shirt and fake
pants all
right exactly what I
[Music]
need h I'm good I'm good but do you have
some normal stuff for me like the honey
syrup If Only They would uh recover more
than 10
FP thick ass shirt oh
dear oh there's no good now I can't go
to the forest to chop any
[Music]
wood there is way at least to my house
but my son's been playing with the
controls again only you could jump out
there please help
me this this your house ah ah wait I can
go up if I jump on your
head thank you I guess or you thank me I
don't know ooh nice oh nice those are
raising my Max
right ah you little what's taking
daddy so long do you think he's still
looking for the
treasure what's taking daddy so long uh
you being a little
that's
[Music]
what come
on hey my second one that I found on my
own
[Music]
so Mario where my treasures okay
uh oh um no but it wasn't
me kidding
wasn't me wasn't
me what the
I I I I I that was me all right
I'll take your
away all right we're out of there never
entering that home ever
[Music]
again there's another chimney here that
really interests me but I can't get up
there I think
trying to jump
that there's something here F me huh
what are you doing walking around here
though you must be pretty bored wait
that's it you're just going to reward me
will
[Music]
you I really can't get up
there
[Music]
hello oh tiny Peach oh it's little do
Oh's cute Mario
help hey
[Music]
Mario boing boing what you're trying to
reach the peach boing boing or is it the
sound of your boing boing
[Music]
jumps
oh I did not like seeing that you think
you can hurt me with you CH his sprs I
trust pach you're com and with me diip
your
lip help help somebody please help
me
help oh my
gosh
it's
Mario
Mom oh yes there I hear
hello what why aren't you
[Music]
Mario holy well you have to H the
fuing stairs are you
Mario I think I will say yes let's be
honest and give him like this moment of
being Star
Struck how do I know what you well let
me jump let me jump
yeah wow wo wo w wo wo wo wo
wo my I'm such a one trick pony that's
what you say
right want to playing with me want I'm
playing saving the world no G Mario
might be a little tired
dear a come on you never play with me
it's not fun playing alone oh dear Mom I
had to ask what you play with G uh okay
again only if you let me make Mario and
Peach
kiss only
then mar Just B the farm so um you can
be B I'll be Gino okay Gino so yourself
what ready let's play from where I left
off is this like a mini
game oh scary everybody just watch
me
ah wait like I don't even know this
character yet that's how you're going to
introduce the character to
me watch out B cuz's going to blow you
away take this
ah what he's in Super Smash Brothers not
the one that I
know I don't know
Gina I don't know
Gino our fan favorite Gina
really oh my God super duper custom
poed
[Music]
shut ah I
missed oh you oh are you
right um game over
damn that was a big out
oh oh no no no no no no no no who
W what is
[Music]
this oh that's how are we are we are we
getting Gino to become a real
boy
no to the real boy Gino Gino Gino that's
how we get him as a party member maybe I
don't
know it's going to be a real
[Music]
boy and like what is this like what what
is this fancy light magic where does it
come from and why did it happen at this
timing
looks like a one piece
character holy I'm a round boy oh
my God I can move holy
wo wo wo
wo
W the
star one of the Seven Stars so do I have
to break
him take him apart in order to get it
but I won't realize until much later in
the game and then it will be really sad
when I realize oh the large star is in
you Gino sorry I might have to take you
apart now here comes the
[Music]
saw we'll see how it goes
again just checking for secrets
[Music]
I have recovered but I will sue you guys
so be
ready was amazing Mom I just thought you
know walk into the forest NE huh yeah
dude that's just cool that's like
totally normal and uh no problem like no
not not freaking me out at
all yeah Mom you know come on like don't
forget about it it's really cool it's my
best friend the only friend I have come
on please let me go find him uh yeah
okay but you better stay in the woods
too cuz I'm like so done with
your
shenanigans mom why please let me
go I'm I'm respire I'll being a good
boy I'll go for
you can I get these Stars
no h okay
let's get a new party
member how do I get to the forest
where's the the path here oh yeah oh
yeah can these uh arrows hit me as
well
[Music]
first I'm
blind they can
ooh Danger
maybe H here
no maybe the path is not
here maybe it's out
there where is
it
okay it is
H
oh W I got a
mushroom
yeah the music in this game is really
[Music]
nice is
that we let's go and a gorilla um excuse
me that is a Donkey Kong in
Chains what did you do to him we have to
F what
happened that's why there's no more
Donkey Kong games coming out they're
keeping him
prisoner to be Side characters or like
even
worse enemies just random
enemies in these other
games poor Donkey
[Music]
Kong use Peak on him does it say
something about Donkey
Kong
[Music]
P 69 five your poison sleep
mute ouch oh sh oh
oh
[Music]
oops uh fire
right
sh but still like that's still a lot of
HP I have to support
Mario with some
rain
[Music]
nice yeah W
wa okay moto moto
fire did he also have a weakness for
thunder
[Music]
don't remember did he let's give it a
try got the me he's almost down
anyway uhoh
yes oh he's almost down I guess I'll do
one
more a my
finger donkey k at
[Music]
home try to peek again but time didn't
hit
oh oh n that's what it
says
oh let's go
Mario let's take the
physical they gave that enemy in
Nintendo subscri only profile picture
for some reason
what I have to go in
here dangerous oo
[Music]
wait are the mushrooms I'm getting uh
actual healing
items little
[Music]
stop mama mama
M
[Music]
I'm
those your recover HP or fpm maybe
HP you're running into a lot of special
enemies oh is it not so
normal I'll give him uh healing item for
now
aaby let's go
[Music]
yes finally a special again this time I
would appreciate the FP juice but we get
a purple star that I never got
before star attack succeed for two turns
oh I don't even have to do
[Music]
anything
um
wow
nice nice not
[Music]
bad
yay what's
that it turned me into a mushroom a a
mow mellow room me too
no can I still attack
normally oh but I'm
recovering HP in this form wait I can't
do anything that's why they're keeping
on attacking
y you little shits ah he
misses ah no mow down no no stop please
stop please it's not
fair
no no you can't keep on spamming that
but he runs out of FP at some point
right also he missed like enemies seem
to have FP too as we've seen and I am
recovering and they're not doing much
damage except for that one okay here we
go you little piece of
y
[Music]
yab
stop
[Music]
you can still do time blocks and TR Farm
oh okay
[Music]
okay nice feel like he ran out of FP
that's why he's not doing it
anymore frog
coin oh and the be was like all right
skattle
time
it's for mow right magic or HP you
guys I like he needs
[Music]
B je is
higher what do you mean tier oh
oh okay is that like different each
time hey y okay okay okay
okay there's a
boost oh
nah
no oh man what the is that other
new
enemy
[Music]
wow
he okay here comes the fun
[Music]
thebolt
yes yes no okay he keeps on putting it
on
Mario used for fan animation from this
game always hits me
[Music]
off is that so I don't know what you're
talking
[Music]
about oh stop ganging up on
Mario no he
listened he
listened
[Music]
n i press way too early it takes much
longer than I expect oh my God oh my
[Music]
God
uh why is this fight so stupidly long I
was forever in the form of a
[Music]
mushroom yeah
nice
nice I'll bring another Thunderbolt into
the
battle used in a lot of fan videos you
mean like what what any fan video of any
[Music]
fandom I can't I can't really think of
anything where I've heard
it
oh can't even see me rolling my eyes in
this small waa
form okay I need I need some honey syrup
man I can't take this
please do not transform me into a
mushroom again
oh oh
okay
no he missed oh my God not you can't do
it
again I swear I can't run away from
Battle how about I need to
[Music]
XP
H okay good
block good block
[Music]
this
m might as well have made the game more
difficult
yeah feel like I'm being targeted nice
one though nice Wawa I rarely get the
Mellow hits right standard
[Music]
ones where are we going
oh uh you're protecting this land I see
not very well switch there's original
BTM I can switch to
yo oh
[Music]
a nice oh is this like a little guessing
game of which tube is the right
[Music]
one oh wake up I want to fight you oh oh
I have anger at the
wiggler H what's in the other
[Music]
one
can't find anything here if there's
something hidden I'm not finding
[Music]
it
oh oh poy Mama raid
oh oh thank
God hello
[Music]
hello let's go set the bees on
fire wasn't his weakness but still
pretty
[Music]
good
nice
I what a weird
enemy Koopa shells with bat wings
carrying an
octal
enemy so
weird is there anything here for me to
find let's just fight I guess
grind W on the
[Music]
grind never see it again wait who whoa
Whata what the
enemy
H I'm out of FP
[Music]
again check the notes of the
enemy H can't now y
it oh suddenly you guys don't want to
turn me into a mushroom anymore huh you
got enough of Mario's room now huh
okay I taunted
them I reminded them that that was a
skill that they
had I hate them
[Music]
hate do you want to fight this one
too I personally
don't but let's
[Music]
go
m let's try to super jump again oh no
actually it takes up so much let's
not let's not do that let's throw in the
thunderballs no you can't attack
twice ah see
[Music]
that
oh come
on
[Music]
don't ye no
oh I defend it time to wake up mow time
to wake up I think you're very easy to
uh go up in flames in this current
form
[Music]
all right this room is
clear what about
here empty
looking all right all right I'll check
my
guide in the forest m in a section of
the safe box no wait what seven stumps
go to the middle left stump there should
be no enemies
go oh
[Music]
okay go to the bottom right there should
be little I think I'm in the bottom
right St am I there should be little
spots of light on the ground go to the
largest spot of light in Center bottom
and
jump is
this
wait it's all like pretty lit
up there's nothing
here
H let's go to the other one is this even
the right one ah no it's
[Music]
not okay this is the bottom right one oh
wait but shouldn't have no
[Music]
enemies no that that doesn't
matter
[Music]
ah put on the signal ring it's all right
why why signal ring when you have a
guide
w
I'm losing my patience for these
[Music]
fights oh oh he's
dead
[Music]
Ohama
woo toad
assist oh wait the golden shroom what
was that again
power W find the
power yeah mow is also like whatever I
don't want to grind anymore I don't want
to I want to be a
frog oh hey I got a frog coin maybe with
that we can turn you into a frog
eventually can't promise there's no
light here no specific light
[Music]
I don't want to come run and it takes up
a move huh yeah
thanks can I try again I don't want I
don't I want to
[Music]
go I didn't heal him that is
true
[Music]
no stop why is it following me not
that's the good
enough
[Music]
no that guarantees escape from the
battle ah no need normally normally at
don't want to like run away from battles
anyway
but oh nice that was a good
timing no but at least with that one he
heals and hopefully won't
[Music]
die they're both almost
down you had trouble too
yeah it's like every fight has a special
enemy and now we're in vegetative
[Music]
state oh oh I'm I I'm full on
mushrooms oh might as well use one but
uh to my dead I can't of course I can't
but what was I going to do I yeah it's
going to
equip the signal ring I guess for now
remind me to change it there's a hidden
treasure here wait and which one am I
the bottom right one right it
says a little spot of light on the
ground got a larg spot of light in the
center bottom and
jump what it all looks like equally lit
to
me maybe
here wrong
[Music]
stu okay if I just see any there there
there's quite a bit of light there that
must be
[Music]
something I forget which one they're
weak for but oh okay was the jumping
[Music]
okay oh true the ring didn't say
anything in the room I just
entered you're
[Music]
right
now the stupid enemies are back no stop
fing me no no I hate
[Music]
you okay let's stay in here until we
find what we're looking for at least
these ones died fast he
no no no
[Music]
no let's kill the mushroom as quickly as
we
can and going to use a as speaking of
mushroom going to use a
mushroom uh
[Music]
No you little why are you so stupid
why are you so dumb why are you so
stupid why are you so
[Music]
dumb I hate you so much you little
ah are you so stupid why are you so why
you so stupid why you so dumb no at
least for once okay ah and there he
[Music]
goes no I need the ring for the trees
John I don't want to keep on Switching
also what the hell where is this light I
don't see any light maybe it's where
these dudes are
spining no
no don't tell me the enemies are
back that's it that's it I don't care I
don't care about one stupid ass
flower no no that's it that's all the
attention I'm giving this super tree
stump
maze ah wait oops
uh but like besides those Treasures is
there something else I should be
[Music]
finding maybe
not
H that's it
okay o ooh do we want to wake him up no
you're just going to get angry
right oh an actual mushroom this time
huh I
see misusing my trust and my
[Music]
mistress
I should tell one
tangent let's
see what have we
got
[Music]
a I'll make uh YouTube shorts out of
this so right now it's kind of like hard
to imagine what I'm talking about maybe
but I I went to this like like super
fancy Starbucks in
Tokyo I shall show you pictures but
[Music]
um it's it's not a normal Starbucks like
it doesn't even have the same menu and
like there's a lot of merch lot more
merch than usual that you can buy and
there's like different floors for
different things like there's a coffee
floor where you can only order like
coffee
stuff
it's like a higher end Starbucks it's an
insanely huge
building so crowded too when it first
opened for a while for like a couple
months maybe you needed like tickets to
get in like sorting tickets needed to
get early there to get a sorting ticket
and then be lucky to get
[Music]
in yeah multi floor Starbucks yeah there
was a floor for tea t b
and
uh oh there were there was like a lot
more Bakery stuff than
normal lot more baked goods than
normal they look so delicious but me I
went with Gemma and me and Gemma we had
plans that that was actually just like
to kill some time us going in there was
just to kill time it was like
coincidentally the place where we wanted
to go was coincidentally close to the
this Starbucks Reserve yeah yeah yeah
yeah
Starbucks Reserve do they have it
outside of Japan too anywhere I
[Music]
wonder oh you went a similar one in
Chicago
really the food looks so good
actually but like yeah we were going to
go eat somewhere else so we didn't order
any food just
drinks Chicago has a massive one oh
oh Empire State Building has one in New
York Chicago New York
oh
so it's quite impressive I want to go
there again just to eat all the baked
goods but in the end I mean actually in
hindsight like at the at the time I was
really impressed but in hindsight's like
well I guess it's just like like a
bigger Starbucks they didn't even seem
to have Frappuccinos I was like where
the hell are the Frappuccinos
Frappuccinos are my favorite thing about
Starbucks and they had no Frappuccinos
on the coffee floor no Frappuccinos on
the tea
floor
[Music]
and I don't know I didn't see any
Frappuccinos anywhere I don't think they
had Frappuccinos maybe maybe the
Starbucks Reservoir is too fancy for
Frappuccinos but what the hell like why
why why why what's not what's not good
enough about Frappuccinos where's the
Frappuccino floor huh
where's my Oreo
[Music]
Frappuccino Mama
Mia oh mallow's going to die again
unless I give him a
mushroom No I gave it to
myself
ah
[Music]
oopsie
happens no not the McDonald's one I I
really like the Burger King Oreo
[Music]
shake well those are real ones
okay no I don't think that was a hidden
frun I like I I looked at the guide
too the map and everything say anything
about Frappuccinos anywhere it said like
here's coffee here's
tea here's food here's merchandise
here's all the coffee beans and all
the the pumps and cuz like the
interior was like very special
too Mia another special enemy
really
yeah big gift shop but I didn't buy
anything cuz
yeah F coins farming
[Music]
huh does it not show you the exclamation
mark anymore when the game thinks you
got
it
H you chose The Wrong Enemy
tonight the wrong Italian to make your
enemy I
again I cannot transform
anymore it's
over I will show again if you fail out
okay that's what I
thought please just show it always
[Music]
please Ah that's G yeah there was a a
notification to you guys about the CD I
didn't even know that now was going to
be the time where they start sending it
out I haven't even seen like any footage
like a photo or a video of the actual CD
but when you guys were like writing on
Twitter about getting the
CD or like being notified of it being
sent out I i' asked music department if
they can like if that means where I can
see something like a sample I want to
see like the printed
out uh booklet and
everything did they fix it yeah I I
would hope so I think
so but um yeah I would have liked to see
how it turned out before it got sent
out I wonder what it looks
[Music]
like wa if it get sent to the story do I
have to go to my bachelor pad to get it
oh oh wait wait wait there he is there's
so many
enemies oh I can run through probably
not recommended right I
[Music]
should
okay I see where you went but I'm going
to try to fight a little bit
too
stop it's lost wood
[Music]
yeah well maybe yeah maybe it's just for
the ones who ordered in the Holo shop
wasn't that the only place where you
could order my CD
[Music]
anyway I hope you guys get it soon this
ASAP let me know when you get
it
a geek Jack too okay
[Music]
okay oh purple
again okay then I'll just go with normal
attacks ah come on what about my second
turn on the purple
star hey what the why
not no email for Geek Jack okay but
maybe it's being sent out for you guys
as
[Music]
well do I still have the purple star in
effect oh you think I'm good on the
XP really I don't want to let my guard
[Music]
down but if you think so then I shall
move on
to better things in
life you ordered extra stuff of yours
[Music]
first
oh okay this way
[Music]
oh yeah Japanese people definitely will
get it first of all before you
guys but you guys will get your turn to
I wonder when I will get my
CD if they already had it ready to send
out they should have given me one while
I was still in
Japan
228 let's
[Music]
go did you get immer samples um no
supposedly it was sent back to
Japan but I was like looking at the
tracking for a couple days after and it
didn't
move let was hoping to it while I was
still in Japan and then bring it back
the same way I did with the motion
capture
suit whatever I mean it's already like
pretty damn late where did he where did
he go down or right side it's already
pretty late for like some of the stuff
in there anyway like the H
talk stuff so
whatever I get it at some point it will
be like a late Christmas
present top right okay
yeah bottom red
[Music]
huh I think wait no where is
he I think it reset
[Music]
me
is
ah just as clumsy as me oh you almost
got hit by an arrow be careful
stop
[Music]
oh wait for me oh I found it saving
Point are we going to fight
[Music]
him oh oh wait the
stumps boy B Boer 99 997 998 999 1,000
1,000 for cover day one F this is yes
yeah another 1,000 will I
shoot Mario who is that guy he must be
the one shooting ours at w
town oh that thing is what I was just
voicing happy I am yeah that doesn't fit
I don't know what the what is this
happy
am look look at their expressions when
freeze they
do W they're standing
lookes more practice do I
need no he's not stopping we got to do
something yeah F go go go go go what do
you think you are you can't just go in
there if you now yeah we can there too
many of them will be cream
oh no someone's coming let's hide and
see if we can learn anything oh is that
boy no a green
[Music]
star
green one I
found what what iur me you must not
practicing I am more hours must I shoot
where statues must I make
yeah is the boy is that boy
hold it right there you don't know what
you're doing return it St to
me I stranger you are and TR looking at
that t we must who is in
charge who might you be
yeah I
serve a higher
authority that star piece belongs to
everyone you can't keep
it
stop angry I
amaba yeah it's an
Avage oh it becomes a a
bow hey chill
[Music]
out a BBS cute
Papas let's go yeah we have to help yeah
let's
go let's go wo
wo oh BBS let's go follow the
BBS I'm not afraid I'm not going to
cry what catch
up see you later I guess stop it that's
enough strong you are but strong I might
hurt you I will so long part now we
must no stop you safe
thanks for the help but who are
you Mario you just ditched me back there
huh don't I know you you look
familiar so you're D Mario we know about
you
knock it's I
am wait this looks like
um one of those old games I used to play
when wow I was small like this character
design looks like from that clay
game then I
[Music]
played not Spore but I guess it has
Spore Tendencies
[Music]
too it's funny clay clay F no the
neighbood yeah not playay Fighters but
wait let me look that
[Music]
up
CL
fighter oh I that also has same
Vibe oh actually no never mind no
neighborhood neighborhood is what I
mean okay so are we using him now what
do you got GLE
beam hold a until just before discharge
[Music]
okay okay
okay this this is something I am better
at timing I think than other things
let's try this
again
it could be better let's see how
you react to thunder as
well bad yeah now free against
one wow he can
count
shoot an arrow I touch when a Target it
hits the button unlocked un locked also
locked the tot assist yeah for a fight
Just Between Us
yeah no more toad assist in this fire
that's what why why do you make the
rules n
though what the what are this
what what are
[Music]
this nice
I will never miss this
[Music]
one you'll see don't worry about it okay
well I don't have uh the points anymore
anyway but let me get some honey
syrup oh
ah n can't block oh no oh that was big
damage
can't do normal attacks that's fine I
was going to use my general beam
[Music]
anyway n constant
perfect
Perfection that is
W no fire weakness either
huh how about some HP rain on Gino
he really is a rain Shaman Shaman
Shan
y let's support each
other stay
[Music]
alive got a freey
no um but yeah again no points and can't
even attack normally so my choices are
none
[Music]
I'll add one
more how long is it going to stay a I
[Music]
wonder oh oh there it is no more items
good that I just loaded up on FP right
before
that
I'll try super jump again even though
I'm not good at this
one ah what I did press when he jumped
maybe a little bit before
[Music]
man 16 that's so low ow
hey the sound it makes to makes them
really sound wooden does it make the
same sound for everyone I feel like it
woodn't w wooden wood
[Music]
woodn't HP
rain on the wooden bullet
ah I missed it
again oh no more special attacks okay oh
oh wo wo wo whoo what's this Bunny's
hamsters why did that make me go to
sleep okay I will use this time to
recover some
[Music]
FP we're doing pretty well I would say
16 that same amount of damage as I do
with the Thunder oh come
on
[Music]
ooh
welcome oh ah he went on the same
one ouch
okay it makes the same sound for mow a
too
[Music]
bad oh no none enough we sleepy when is
okay there there he is I was about to
ask ooh
[Music]
64 changing
uhuh
ow Melo don't die please we're almost
done I think I mean I didn't check his
HP I feel like at
[Music]
n got
a w
ah
what let's do
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay yeah bad this is at the end of my
rope I am
oh look out lock all buttons I simply
must no what what am I supposed to
do what are we going to do he won't let
us do anything listen everyone we'
proven that we're quite a team let's
join forces all three of us at once and
take him
down got my
throat super super combination attack
collaboration uh you can now use triple
moves ooh these powerful moves are
available when the gge is 100% just this
once will fill your gge for free oh I
thank you I need a pro candy oh man all
these voices
[Music]
star Riders oo the power of the star
pieces delivers a powerful strike to
single
enemy let's end this now
oh
[Applause]
pry and in the old version were did
these cut scenes like not exist at
all or just in a
really low quality
[Music]
version not at
all oh the mechanic didn't even
ex what about all the other cut scenes
though all the other like high quality
cut scenes that we
[Music]
see
nope no cut
scenes Oh I thought so Malo also level
eight let's go two one
three oh I don't really see I mean this
one's four maybe we do HP here
too thanks for the help you really got
me out of a jam why are you staring at
me you know I'm more than just a doll
don't
you oh yeah I mean at this point yeah
have you guessed the truth I'm a visitor
from above and this is a form I'm
borrowing briefly
ah okay you found a vessel in this
puppet Oh you mean like from the sky or
something higher than that I'm afraid
do you two know anything about the Star
Road completely in the dark well it's a
big mess up there right now and it
concerns you
too let me explain you've heard of a
wishing of wishing upon the star
shooting star specifically at the Star
Road it wish is transformed into a star
when it's granted it then turns into a
shooting star and falls down to earth so
you see the Star World plays an integral
role in granting wishes but ever since a
sword destroyed the Star Road
everything's come to a
halt no stars have been made since the
way things stand yours is a world where
wishes can't come true
[Music]
anymore are you saying this star is part
of your
star that's Star Road my fluffy little
friend yes that star is a broken piece
of Star Rod I'm here to find them all
and repair the Star Rod the broken star
piece Jesus there are seven alog
[Music]
together peace to return we must get rid
of Smithy find the star pieces and
repair star thank you thanks
[Music]
true I'm blah blah blah but it's hard to
pronounce so call me Gino after the
doll
[Music]
I thought it was going to be another one
I chose him because he looked the
strongest I of all the dolls huh mommy
was also one of the Dolls excuse
[Music]
me oh thank
you now grab the star
Mario I shall indeed it's mine my
star my second one
[Music]
[Applause]
righto
stretch
wow five
[Music]
more
come on let's get this show on the
road doino who is searching for the
pieces of the styro joins Mario and mow
things are definitely looking
up I like these little
narator
dialogues heard everything would have
known that's time was so important I got
to
[Music]
for
thank you I'm glad you can watch the
stream
wife the secret to the shooting stars
has been unraveled find the star pieces
and bring peace back to Mario's World
woohoo M oh we're back at the this maze
but there's no more wigglers is this the
same maze I don't want to go in inside
anymore
anyway
so oh oh we got to go to
moleville yeah but I can't go there okay
[Music]
so game looks fun yeah it's fun it's fun
so
far
town the the
grinding would have appreciated a little
bit less
grinding
necessity well it looks much better now
the flowers are
cute why speaking of Ro
Town hold to the house on the hill it
has a switch to the stairs I already did
that oh I did already all of them he
he found them on my
own wait Ro
[Music]
Town let's go buy some stuff
again we
need a lot more honey syrup
yeah here you go didn't I already go
into the chimney look I did was that
different City
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I've been here okay okay
know yeah it's the OG music right now
this so cute wait now I want to hear the
the difference probably pretty similar
but
[Music]
oh oh ah the modern version also so
nice
ah it gives me like Broadway
Vibes well
hello finally
home can't believe an hour hit
him yeah that's some crazy going on
here finally you're free for now I
guess thanks to your lord and savior
Mario that's so
[Music]
pretty
so you guys are not getting back the
doll for a while hope that's
okay know you came back
Mommy say Mom this is the Gino I was
talking about my my what a fabulous
costume must be kind of hot for the
person wearing it though forget it Mom
all
right how I wish I could but Mario and I
must leave now to find the missing star
pieces star pieces you mean like
shooting stars what well how can I
explain this you're if I don't
get them the world's
oh okay explanation
time uh
uhhuh woohoo Oh Holy
Light
woohoo this is how it used to be but now
it's like wo w
uh not coming back this do you get
it I have no idea what the you're
talking
about well let's just say that the
things stay the way they are your wishes
will never come
true
[Music]
what no one's wishes will come true
until star pieces are found and the Star
Road
prepared wish is why I have chosen to
join these two in order to find the
missing star
pieces so that's it and that's it well M
needs all the help he can
get he really doesn't see much in
me you know what you know what I did see
something sparkly fall somewhere around
mobille think that that's one of those
things you're looking for to know that
seems highly probable we'll make mville
our next thank you for telling us about
it
I'll be waiting for you please go f the
Star Road and make sure all my dreams
come
true of course of course we
will little boy Little Toad boy whatever
your dreams are oh
present a finger shot is that a weapon
for
[Music]
him cute these characters are really
cute it is oh he might be be able to get
some of the new armor is there is there
new armor first of all or can he wear
like a shirt
or let's
see oh no none of
this
H can I give him some accessory at
least here have the signal
ring
his armor is caped by the I sleep at the
in once uh was this the
[Music]
in uh
no I have the star oh so it was their
[Music]
place
oh wait do I have to talk to the mom
want to sleep
[Music]
here it better be free oh okay
okay I W hope so me
[Music]
lady what the Link Link hey hey
Link Link what the there's Link in
here this just like um it could be
several people and I got lucky to get
link oh my
[Music]
God she's lucky Hey listen Link's
Awakening uh yeah that game is never
coming out I guess because he's not
waking
up he I what I can talk with no what she
no he's gotone what do you mean I can
talk with him I didn't think I could
s shows up lat the
[Music]
what but didn't I already get the
treasure from
here
ah there was another one all
[Music]
right wait you my grandson has come back
in one piece thank you Mario yeah you're
welcome nothing special in your house
H he pushed me he
[Music]
literally
where did you keep those
kids
[Music]
H where where are they in the
chimney where are those
[Music]
kids
okay I was Co but I made it on time okay
Dad I'm happy I can make things easier
on cool fans um yeah sure but like
what where are they
going where are they disappearing into
also where do I need to
[Music]
go I want to how do you go to the big
map look where do I
go leave town oh
[Music]
okay can I go here ooh
mville
ooh what is that Tower thing
there looks
funky
ooh o interesting
area item shop so it's a whole another
town right away
okay you've got
moles wa this looks like the area in
chicken uh what's it called chicken
run chicken run chicken is that not the
movie the the chicken horror game that I
played
everyone's up on the mountain but I'm
stuck mining store so watch on
me oh if have clothes oh the mega
Cape chicken feet M and then Mega
pants Oh wait there's work pants for
like
[Music]
everybody
can uh for example the the wooden boy
can he wear the pants and the cape at
the same
[Music]
time work pants extremely good yeah I
see like they they boost much
more no magic attack but minus magic
defense a minus defense
General should I get give it to
everybody I just bought the Mega shirt
and like they were maybe not because
they're already wearing the other
[Music]
things it's an emergency din trapped in
the
mines then why are you just staring at
the wall if there's such a
emergency maybe not so good for Mal he
needs yeah yeah he needs the defense you
wor us until end game
sheesh new weapon for Gino oh wait this
a weapon for uh not Gino for
mow and we get the punch glove but the
finger shot we already have
[Music]
so nice
view what about
here
[Music]
nothing
they so
cute a pretty crashed down into the
mountain I wanted to see it but my M
told me it was too
dangerous M she go and find out what's
happening but she's sure taking her
sweet
[Music]
time should be no secrets in this house
so
yeah there was an area I didn't
check before this one
really oh Bowser yeah don't jump Bowser
toally don't
[Music]
jump his army is smaller
now I skipped the pipe
Vault
okay most of our allies have run off
what will we
we had experience fighting
Mario these two guys are too much shut
up all of you I'm the biggest baddest
bro around and don't you forget it but
if Mario is any i' been kicked out of my
own castle my reputation will be ruined
even I have an image to keep you know
let's show him who's the bus around
here p p
p
and
wow why was I able to come here if I
missed something what the
[Music]
hell pipe
Vault wait is this like a happy
place it's
optional oh whoa whoa whoa bubble bubble
ah uh okay ah oh I fight
them
[Music]
oh how strong are they
huh
ah not
very so either you fight them or you
just skillfully jump over
them not my
thing no I can do it I can do it ooh the
music more special
[Music]
enemies oh
oh even with that 129 what let's go
[Music]
Kaboom
boom I wonder if it damages me and it's
not showing damage so I'm guessing
[Music]
no just blasting
him
okay what was strong against the Frog I
don't remember maybe jump on
him all right I feel
[Music]
strong what that's so cute this new
weapon ah and he even does like a good
amount of
[Music]
damage
a no
ah okay I'll take that as an
insult saw my face and got so scared
right away okay
[Music]
okay makes sense kind of that they would
resist me jumping on their
mouths
I can I can accept
that six
n oh yeah the jump ring
oh
[Music]
cute wait can I enter all of them even
with the p
ones well this is a flower pot so this
one surely I can't
enter ooh what the hell are those
ah so
[Music]
many
okay need AOE attack
[Music]
time for some
gardening no okay just one damage what
scare oh I'm blocking it still no oh no
this one's not blocking it oh but he's
falling asleep okay okay ah I would have
liked this AOE but sure I guess
not they make you lose coins you don't
remember the white one
no what do you mean
remember did they appear in this game
before I don't remember them from other
games either
though take your coins
ahuh
they make you lose coins oh how
many I'll be
[Music]
careful dude have you not learned from
watching this
fight Miki lost all her
coins well they're always there okay let
[Music]
me ah ah no okay better than losing
coins I
[Music]
guess
wa how do I do
[Music]
that
don't know if I can really jump over
them from below so got to jump from high
five I didn't even lose a single coin oh
wa well there's a
more but wait oh there's more
that's
[Music]
okay I guess we'll
fight uh
[Music]
syrup you know I can't say I've ever
seen someone play this game without
doing the timing stuff quite unique
gameplay here on hey I'm trying
what am I so bad that I deserve to be
this roasted like a roasted turkey Happy
Thanksgiving Everybody by the way late
but
[Music]
still my I'm a begin okay I'm trying my
best
I feel very
roasted I did it didn't
I it's hard to figure
out oh he's
[Music]
excited
ah okay okay that one's
[Music]
tough oh I did it no
a I see I see how it
is well I didn't lose too many coins
it's okay
[Music]
I got some back too so where is this
treasure there's a treasure here you
[Music]
say
yes one thing after Now where's this
[Music]
treasure
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
behind what what
what I'm I'm trying from every side
oh that is not behind that is next to on
the left side
okay can we play with Yosi
here why
[Music]
Yi what are you speed
Yoshi Yoshi be running Yosi
I love
[Music]
you let's play Let's Play are we going
to race or
what I care to read it
yeah H reservations for two mushroom
travel
agency
[Music]
aeny now that you're here we could use
your help pleas talk to a few of my pal
air and why you can't understand them
well hop aboard and I'll be your
interpreter really I can ride
you
yooo I can't jump
anymore okay talk talk wait wait wait
wait what I you cracked racing my life I
could run all day by the way you know
what I saw not too long ago I start
falling somewhere by Mulo
w b here is the fastest runner but he's
full of his
self bossy only races one onone so
everyone can join us stup bed
wow hey Yoshi think you can beat the old
bossy today let's
go take my cookies good luck I'm rooting
for you
go she got some cookies
yummy can I can I hatch the the Yoshi
[Music]
eggs muchos
accent and let me
on it would be so much better if we
could all race together
[Music]
get
Sor you bought a cookies all right
consider yourself lucky today you've got
yourself one and
[Music]
one I couldn't think of American accents
I don't know how to do
them hello again
W throat is dead let's not do that
anymore Press A and B
alternatively along with the Rhythm the
tighter the Rhythm the faster you go
swag press y during a race to eat a
cookie it's energy will help you go
faster uh yeah okay ab ab ab ab okay do
do I do it with one finger
or oh God okay I'm doing it with
two let's
go
oh oh in this Rhythm oh I may not
have been doing that in the
beginning okay okay okay okay okay what
does it have to be in that RM can I not
go faster cuz I was
faster two
three
how's that still I still have problems
you
say I guess earlier there's really some
uh okay some input lag there okay okay
no I have one finger on each button
[Music]
Focus let's a
go
oh quite
well ah
ah ah
no
no it just jumps like a
fool
ah I couldn't get back into the Rhythm
once I was out of
it no I want to do it again
[Music]
please Yosi
please please can I do it
again cookies how do I get more
cookies yeah I think
thank you you keep on giving me the
cookies how often will I get his cookies
until he gets sick of my
[Music]
it's very normal to be bad at this
game oh wait I don't need you to help me
but I guess let's try it
once no no no no no actually I'm
fine
three two three two one
go
okay yeah all
right you guys oh you guys are bad at
this one
huh that was pretty good if I didn't
fall out of the Rhythm I would have been
[Music]
fine
Ah Ah that's what
[Music]
happened I won I won I don't know why
the he was like doing stupid
at the end again but okay I did
[Music]
it starting today Yoshi's the new B
around here since when have you been
able to spread like that what the
oh wow I have my day in the sun let me
give you a tip brace someone slow that
way you'll be able to stash away the
cookies but we don't need a bus anyway I
just want to
race I'm not going to turn off the game
bgm no no the bgm of this game is like
legendary how can you even demand such a
thing for your
selfishness wow
wow also there's quite a lot of like
different patterns so it's not even
repetitive you
know here's something to remember me by
Yoshi cookies thank
you I can give you a call let's
[Music]
go okay well this was worth going
through the the tubes mhm
oh that's where you
[Music]
go okay we are here
again I got a summon oh yeah I guess is
that so nice so
[Music]
special m
I do have to
say I am
feeling uh I want to end it for today
cuz I also got to read some super
chats
TBH what are you
doing
a you think you're helping
huh
M okay sounds good sounds good good
stopping point
[Music]
yeah yeah I got to read some super chats
I don't know how far and behind I would
think that most of the collabs didn't
get much super chats so it's probably
not too
[Music]
bad I want to go
and get go somewhere where there's a bit
calmer bgm how about main
map how was it on the main
map oh it's quite nice I make it a bit
more quiet
though 312 super
chats that sounds like a lot but is
it uh I guess you guys sent a couple on
in the waiting room even
tomorrow is
also Super
Mario Time wo let's go
here well I'm not watching the oh a
big not watching the Nintendo
[Music]
Direct
small W is
Big
shinger
[Music]
smallness
CH wait I'll fix
you
[Music]
I will
try to fix
[Music]
you what size are you
guys a there it is that looks
better
[Music]
okay um
okay
[Music]
wait this okay okay this good this is
good I think
this
[Music]
what what what's the like the last one
oh frog fru my
fruit
FR frog frog in my throat
oh single hot mother crystals in
your
area black pink in your area single hot
mother crystals in your area
oh
should you want to read them oh a
couple a
couple a couple a couple a a a c a
couple super chats a a couple super
chats a a a cup a c yeah yeah
[Music]
that
uh skull skull skull
I still have so many tangents
guys but got
um ra ratio rized rationalized ra ra
ration
ra
R ration oh
ration
and is this the hot hot mother crystals
in your area
stream no that's final so even before
the Final Fantasy
[Music]
finale the
wow
o w had no time to read
[Music]
huh why am I even why am I not using
hyzer it's been too
[Music]
long is Miki Miki is doing
endurance
[Music]
girl these Japanese
syli all going hard on the endurance why
why
why don't force
[Music]
yourself I wonder how far she is I don't
want to spoiler myself so I'm not going
to
[Music]
look
okay DEA DEA
DEA
uh
[Music]
thumbnail even my thumbnail folder needs
a moment to
load my thumbnail oh my God my thumbnail
folder has
835 things in
it granted not all of them are thumnails
cuz sometimes I accidentally save
something else
there but that's like quite something
there's so nostalgic to look at too it's
like looking at the photo
album
[Music]
damn
Nostalgia
yeah my oldest one in this folder is
from
Yakuza and then Risa and then oh
this that's old as
this one best of takas
2020 that's the day the year I debuted
but I still made like
a this
like
no the time when I think nexit was still
watching my stuff until he got
poached to work for some company I
suppose that's the way it
goes one day cow carrot will stop doing
things for me
too on all of you guys just be
poached go to better
places remember
this snake remember remember
this remember
this I used to use this for stream
reservations
yeah yeah nowadays I just like to have
everything ready right I don't want to
like have a reservation thumbnail I just
want it to look clear right away what it
is because you never know who looks at
it at what time and might be interested
about
it um you know the contents of
it the rise of
thumbnail wait is it
here the F the Glorious F oh yeah I see
it
oh one of my best ones I was lucky I had
like a a good fitting fan art in like a
similar pose lying
[Music]
around I need to stop looking I need to
read super
chats that would win the wa thumbnail
Awards wa thumbnail
Awards yeah yeah thumnails are important
that's why yeah what that's what I have
in the back of my
[Music]
mind I mean I don't want to like bait
with thumbnails so I do want
to have my thumbnails be
representative of the stream the problem
is like as a streamer you don't know
usually you don't know what's going to
happen in the game that you're going to
play oh I just back up did I already see
it I feel like I did um so you can't
really like make a thumbnail that will
show what you're about to experience in
the
Stream unless someone who knows the game
or so makes it for you but like for
YouTube ERS who upload like videos of
their footage not
streamers they can do that and then that
can be really interesting too like I've
noticed with
this certain YouTuber that I
watch you know when the thumbnail is
like super interesting he gets more VOD
views you know
so or like for for boss fights and so on
you put nice bot on the thumbnail and
you know I can't can't do that and so
it's normally just like basic like this
but I wonder if if I if I had a system
where I would change the thumbnail after
the stream if that would be
efficient for VA
Watchers but that would be more work too
and like that kind
of requires me to go through my own
VOD of the game play
then screenshot it and hope I get like a
not so blurry high quality screenshot
then cut it out and make it into
something usable for the
thumbnail I mean I guess sometimes on
the on Google you can find some usable
like character artworks and so on but
sometimes you can't sometimes you want
to use a screenshot from the
[Music]
game I did that for tunic I
did really I don't remember tunic was so
good I should I need to force
someone from Advent to play tunic who do
you think would like tunic in Advent I
want someone to play
tunic wait did I just say who do you
think in tunic would like
Advent did I say
[Music]
that no didn't say that right can we
replay can we can we go back in
time yeah I was thinking of beu too
she seems
like she I don't know if if that's her
type of game but I feel like she would
be good at
[Music]
it I said it right
okay is that right okay okay
okay are you sure are you sure though
are you
[Music]
sure
I'm hungry what am I even going to eat
[Music]
today what am I going to eat
today maybe I'll order
[Music]
food it's not too
late anyway uh take a
47 unknown thanks for the pinkies sorry
I wasn't there uh at the last stream
boss that was the first time first
stream I missed this year
mhm it's okay I was hoping for perfect
attendance in 2023 but the internet went
down so I can't really do anything
doesn't count I'll catch up with you in
the vault now no don't worry that
doesn't count what the
internet being dead is not in your
power legit you're you're you you you
continue your streak
proudly don't worry about it forget
about it forget about
it forg about her cute
right she'd be cute in there morally
imoral
you happy belated 18th birthday I'm so
late I don't know if you'll hear this
but
congratulations m
CH
[Music]
dyal
than thank you for the thanks for stream
even if they have some hiccups with the
connection recently oh yeah I wonder if
during the Final Fantasy streams it also
had
like like cuz I heard that only the
ultra low latency had issues
later on I heard that later on but I
wonder if that was the same problem for
the Final Fantasy
streams I wonder yeah that was really
annoying to
me like for the full stream you guys
were like saying it had issues so that's
that's quite a big oof other streams are
also lagging yeah who knows maybe they
also had ultra low lency it's been a r
couple of days at work and chilling with
kfp has really helped I'm happy to hear
that I I wish I could could provide you
a smooth smooth stream but yeah sorry
for the scuff at least today it's uh
fine I'm I'm still doing the the middle
latency option now cuz I'm scared to go
back to the ultra low latency so you
guys are a little bit delayed for me but
it's fine it's fine it's not so bad as
like the the slowest
option so I think it's fine thank you
Tassimo and Juan caros Rodriguez than
for the pinky hi didn't you last week I
finally got my onee badge oo nice thank
you so much for staying for so long time
went by quite fast I remember I started
watching you around the time do you
really oh I really admire your talent
and the passion you put into everything
you do and I'm happy to be in kfp see
that like really feels like you're still
like really fresh to me joining at the
time of du you that's that's pretty
fresh I wonder if you were already
watching Hol live maybe other Ian
members since quite a while before or or
if that was generally the time you
entered the B rabbit
hole are you
here
whoan
didn't I yeah didn't I already say
something about do you being old
today long Roba you were my first friend
you I discovered H like in August Oh you
mean August last year oh damn so yeah
it's like
overall you're pretty new overall
wow nice to have you here I hope you're
having a good time and staying forever
[Music]
certain in light of recent news I have a
new song recommendation for you Dragon
Force has recently released a song based
on the Legend of Zelda called The Power
of Tri the Triforce it's power metal so
you don't have to worry about
sco power
[Music]
metal
I am I am not
intrigued
certainly I am not
intrigued Legend of Zelda is all nice
but I
[Music]
treat I I think I know know what power
metal sounds like yes feel like I've
heard that before my bro
hurts I look it up just
because I feel
like I would be mean if I
don't
um sir no not not certainly
Dragon
Force Dragon
[Music]
Force was I supposed to know who they
are I'm listening
now no
no
looks like Legolas that
dude but also like the guy
from
uh game of Game of Thrones number
two that's pretty cool but like it
doesn't give me Legend of Zelda Vibes at
all because it's so power
metal there's no Zelda Vibes just
because you call it
Zelda something something it's not going
to give me Zelda
Vibes I mean maybe the lyrics yeah the
only Z thing about it is probably the
lyrics but like it doesn't enter my
brain
so oh I hear
[Music]
crackling I'm not in a receptive mood I
suppose
sorry moral
imoral I might
turn playing hardcore classic Ser I
don't think I would want to try to play
oh my
throat it's a really
[Music]
weird
really weird scratching is like like
there's needle one one
needle
oh I was saying if I play World walk I
don't want to play
hardcore delar Dan del d I'm just going
to assume that's who you are Captain
meow water a thank you for the
pinky tento I have to say you went
pretty hard in combat today especially
the one versus on I probably did I don't
remember but I probably did your ability
to predict the story has been pretty
amazing did
I all I can really say is try to replace
rook's Gambit with something stronger
like judgment
Vault I I think I eventually did did I
at least I replaced it with
[Music]
something but then at the end I don't
know continuously replacing something I
just got used
to
yeah I'm glad at the end I finally
fought found one combination that I felt
like I was happy with and still had some
of the newer things in it so it wasn't
outdated I was predicting stuff before
they revealed it wow that's just my Giga
brain can't help it can't stop it it's
Unstoppable yesterday Ah that's action
yesterday you asked why I was in the
usual room it's because I've been
Boozled you twice for messages from M
and JMA ah like like messes like I love
you so much you're amazing blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah JMA right
ah escaping the usual room and try to
start Rebellion I think each was a year
and a couple of
months yeah for all the these things
honestly you you deserve usual room for
life life
sentence you kind of
do so and you don't you don't even seem
like
you're going to be orderly once you
leave the usual room
so you still haven't learned your
lesson so you're staying for life until
you learn your lesson then
parole hearing let's
[Music]
go yeah he's proud
you I am a t beep than Brandon D all the
pajamas thanks guys for keep on
reminding
me I'm so happy about the matching
[Music]
pajamas
I'm I'm done with that story
Mo what wait the one after that why does
it have so many super
chats
why why maybe that's not much maybe
that's just maybe it's not that much
maybe my my feeling of what is much as
no I I I know why because Moto son was
back and
spamming
a couple of
Reds mhm that was a happy surprise
though
uh okay I'll gambaru I'll gambu I'll
just read this one and then I'll
[Music]
go Jacob 47 soon Jim Tracy soon muffin
thanks to the pinky thanks haven't been
on a bright spot for me recently but
besides that even if I have issues
catching the streams at times due to
life I want to say thank you Teno for
still being here you bring joy to many
and makes these times worth it no thank
you for still being here I have to thank
you okay let's just thank each other
[Music]
right it it do
be quite the accomplishment and
endurance of me to still be here too but
same to you
guys high five
hey thank you for supporting
me not giving up on me not not uh
leaving me
behind and moving on to something better
no where the grass is
greener and the water is
Bluer and the Sun is
shinier m y ton aani thank you for the
red super chat oh wow that's a big one
holy thank you thank you for the
entertainment you provided and your
interesting tangents you talked about
all the years since your debut I do not
comment often in chat but I try to catch
as many streams as you can are you here
now are you
here to catch the answer to your Super
Chat
[Music]
squ don't see you maybe
not also chat slow ah you are here okay
chat is just
slow H here my very first YouTube Super
Chat you first fall and you go this hard
dude
ah a
throat h
feeling
for thank you so much and yeah I
sometimes feel like you know I I feel
like I talked like I I told so many
interesting tangents in especially the
first two years that I wish I could tell
them again for the first time at some
point when you stream this much it's
really like
most of the interesting things I can
tell I've told from my past from like
before
Holo and now I got to make new
memories you know I mean there's maybe
still some interesting things I just
don't remember but
like you know I've been digging deep
and trying to share a lot
yeah sometimes I feel like I can just
reshare my tangents but like most of you
guys feel like you've already heard them
and feels awkward to tell it again cuz
then I don't know especially knowing
some people heard it
before and I can't even
remember the ones I told anyway the
interesting ones besides like the
typical ones like the bomb on the
plane oh
the
stest story application
story stuff like that my Thro
really hurts
man oh the electric scooter story it was
a good one
too yeah oh yeah me being almost sold
for free camels in more Morocco and and
and and in Morocco on my birthday night
being broken in and having the the thief
standing right next to me and me
thinking it's my brother cuz it was dark
and I was half
asleep
yeah good
times many
stories free camels is a lot I
guess I you suppos so
[Music]
a is that supposed to make me feel
better my brother and I'm
hungry anyway you crazy crazy thank you
so much tan for sticking with me and I
mean I I hope I'm still interesting
enough for you guys I try my best I I
try my best to like write down anything
I can think of and make new memories for
you guys so I can share them too
basically like my Japan
trip it may have taken up some time
where I could have been streaming but
honestly while I'm creating some cool
stuff for a certain 3d concert I'm also
making memories that later on I can
share on my stream and I really need
this kind of stuff cuz I feel if I don't
have a tangent at least one per stream I
feel
like you guys would be disappointed cuz
I know you guys love my tangents and
also I feel like I didn't bring
anything to the table on that day on
that stream like I
need always at least one
[Music]
tangent even it's if it's a tiny stupid
one something
otherwise I feel like I didn't deliver
today I was boring today I didn't share
anything of meaning and interest
today what my feves what but no no no I
got some mixed up
now did you mix it up on
purpose anyway tman here's a kiss than
I'm py and
[Music]
it's fine not to have a tangent might
never to girl some talk about this yeah
you mean like you think you mean many of
the girls don't Tang to as
much yeah but
like feel like I've I've created
expectations for my viewers
so and and for me it's like like a
personal minimum of entertainment that I
want to
deliver but yeah after 3 years just it
just run out of it I
mean I've had a very eventful life okay
and even without the ones that I can't
really tell even then my life was very
eventful not having anything left at
this point getting that far with my
tangent is like quite the accomplishment
on its
own why you talking like you're 60 cuz
cuz I'm like literally Eternal
Phoenix I've lived more than 60
years
remember very eventful
[Music]
life I know I look smoking hot and pity
py
young but I'm I've been through some
I've seen some
then no okay
[Music]
grandmaa thank you for the red super
chat I haven't sent many super chats the
past year but but I today is anex
exception it's my birthday I'm just a
week away from my freear Milestone so I
want to thank you for all the
entertainment you've given us over the
years and looking forward to many more
of K I'm so sorry I'm so late reading
this thank you so much where a birthday
ant like anniversary for year
anniversary
[Music]
both thank you so much happy Bel
birthday and thank you for supporting
the wa wa for fre years and more to come
hopefully where are you what where are
you I can't see you show yourself show
[Music]
yourself okay maybe not here today
that's
fine I hope you're not not here because
you're mad at me for being so late I'm
so sorry but thank you so much for
supporting the waa and believing in the
waaa you're the
best m M much love to you I wish you all
happiness in the
world chocolate
insomnia Unity
chat M I feel like I reacted plenty to
your super chats in the actual stream
but thank you so much I'm happy to see
you again thank
you
energy and and
[Music]
EMP age of
EMP we talked about playing Age of
Empires again me and Alie so seems like
you're into Age of Empires don't worry
there will be
more thank you so much M account name m
MW m m m
what a nice surprise that
[Music]
was na CAU on Pinky this free message
cost me $50 10 out of 10 would buy
again is English your first language I
think you're misunderstanding the
meaning of
free time to go back to
school but
H how will I replace you as a worker at
kfp I don't think I can you're like
Irreplaceable not that I'm like trying
to flatter you or
anything just just because you know like
cuz you're baking like damn I need
those
Bakers those baking
hands
un CH
doomsday
[Music]
Max sign X thank you be trapped requires
dress yeah yeah oldin really was
like not worth it for me at the
[Music]
end goodbye thank you for the pink and
always will be the absolute cutest ever
I mean today I am definitely especially
cute
yeah thank you thank you so much M A
Maro D Brandon D
dard
cat
smoothie what are you doing
here I love
you sttion thank
you that was a roller coaster fun no
roller
coaster
yeah I I don't know I'm I'm I ended up
rating the game really high right but
like I'm still not happy with the ending
but that's like very personal I
guess so whatever delar tasima thanks
for the pinky let's Goa show him who's
boss
hey
well I think it was really clear who the
bosses
were that crazy
dude that little
killed so much that was so dear to
[Music]
me pain pickle take
monke
Al
Z
[Music]
thanks ah oh thank you slime it's okay
it's okay
swis oh nice let's go Tel congrats you
did amazing fun fact you were doing five
times as much damage every stagger as CI
was doing to Altima and you beat him
first try too well she took a couple oh
really as expected of the game of
Yen I wonder if CI like forced herself
to go for like Ultima though H not
Ultima
[Music]
oldin you know I have this
one
M beauty beauty mark that I feel like
for a while now already it's like coming
[Music]
off but I I heard that you shouldn't
like scratch or do anything with your
beauty marks but like it's like half
[Music]
off I shouldn't touch
it it's so
weird maybe no I didn't pick it up like
it's like I'm about
to yeah I I should I shall go to
dermatologist at some point but they
just for that tiny little thing there
man seems like a
waste uh I'll think of another reason to
[Music]
go I don't really have any other
dermatologist problems right now I think
do
I yeah I had one removed
before you know where I told you I think
I told you she like just like shaves it
off
pudding
pudding how how come you're here
hm how come you're here on this fancy
day
sir
[Music]
H where the hell are
you don't like me
[Music]
anymore you were sent a death threed by
J oh because you're not around
right yeah that's what happens that's
what
[Music]
happens
N I will not indulge in your jokey
jokes thank you
razine thank you so much R for for
giving me confidence oh my God smoovie
is like rubbing on my on my knee cute
baby so soft you than soon wait where's
L come
here smie
wrong she's worried about me cuz she
knows I'm hungry
maybe time to move to
Brazil that doesn't change
nothing eaten Exile a d Cru gold D you
can M than for the pinky congratulations
can first round ultimate to what a ride
for your first FF mhm this has been such
a fun journey by the way we're going to
visit my aunt in Denmark and vacation
Norway
oh hope your trip to Japan will go well
thank you wow that sounds great sounds
like fun I want to go to those places
haven't really been to them those
countries yet how was it I already gone
or like back
home hope it was nice I wish I could go
there
too one day one day one day I will have
visited every country in the world
almost
almost the ones that or not um kind of a
stupid choice to
visit I will not go
to Tassimo T thank you for another
pinkcake congrats on finishing that was
certainly one hell of a ride but
personally I like the ending it goes
well with Clive's final message even if
it's really
sad um I guess I'm not I don't want to
accept it I don't
no I don't want to no no
I don't want I want I don't I don't even
want to talk about Final Fantasy 16
anymore like in
hindsight the ending leaves such a sour
taste in my mouth it's
[Music]
crazy it was fun it was like good but
yeah I I I I hope other Final Fantasy
games have better
endings not such
like training
ones then you can ignore my Super Chat
no no I would not
[Music]
no they don't they're dark games they
all have heartbreaking moments
[Music]
what another FF that I would be
interested in is the one with the cute
girl s cuz like now in hindsight I I
understand now why that that lady is
called
Sid the one with the yellow jacket and
the short blonde
hair I I just like remember seeing a lot
of cute
cosplays that's 15 oh oh yeah yeah it is
really recent
yeah wait is she Cindy or SID wait did I
think it was Sid because Cindy is so
similar now maybe it's not Sid
oopsie she's so
cute H one of the
worst oh Sid is sh for Cindy or or SID
her Grandpa ah
okay smovie is sitting on the Big Orange
bean bag like a
loaf she looks like she's facing towards
me and I feel like she's putting
pressure on
me not
yeah her being in this room while I'm
still
streaming feels like I'm being
[Music]
threatened I'll fin I have to finish
these super chats I can't cut it off
here and moon D Final Fantasy 16 was one
of the most emotional I've been for a
game in a long time oh just by watching
or also by playing definitely was one of
the top games of this year so far thank
you for streaming this game and I can't
wait for more jrpg streams I guess what
we're playing at the moment counts as a
jrpg too even
more even more squeezing a couple more
jrpgs in here before the year ends let's
go I'm glad you like the game so
much I I think like in terms of like
game quality like mechanisms and
graphic and everything it definitely
deserves to be one of the top games
yeah wasn't even an RPG in my opinion
huh it's an
RPG we're going to have an RPG
discussion again like I understand why
you guys don't want to call
like Zelda an RPG which I I will still
continue calling it
one cuz Mario doesn't have a sword oh
that doesn't matter at
all no it's an
RPG yeah for sure for
sure okay let's not start this
discussion this movie is waiting for me
ultim okay thank you for the pinky
congratulations being your first ever
final finisher and what a fantastic and
wonderful Journey it was also even
though he was a massive
LS absolutely loved as a villain which
of course I say with no bias at
all uh yeah I mean he's pretty cool even
even though like it's it's quite a
common storyline of like some evil
wanting to recreate the world in their
own way quite common
um but interesting like especially at
the end where he really broke down
everything for us like how it came to
this it's really really nice that there
was definitely some depth to
[Music]
it but him oh oh see d game 8910 D
Lord
EV oh yeah too being saved
is at least one good thing we want to
keep those doggles safe yeah yeah Bruce
Jen Lee than you thank you yeah Al Ro
d d for the pinky regardless of the
ending thank you for the awesome
playthrough really enjoyed your gameplay
and reaction to the story thank you you
enjoyed my reaction at the end
too me
being quite
upset yeah I was I was just like
maybe if I played other Final Fantasy
games I would I would kind of like know
what to expect you know to expect some
sad ending but it didn't I was really
thinking it was going to be like
relatively
positive even if that would be tacky to
like make it something positive
but I don't know that's what I expected
from
jrpgs
[Music]
the fact that the other FF games are
also like this um kind of froze me off a
little bit
against playing
them but I will at I will commit to at
least playing one
more maybe next year or so
[Music]
M ff7 has a good ending all right that
one has a uh remake right
HD
okay then I'll gladly play
it
um LL kfb Intel the apartment thank you
thank you Ki thanks for the red super
chat he it's been 3 years ago today
since I sub to you during your K
endurance stream oh oh yeah I think I
read this I wasn't a fan of Holo V just
yet but that stream was what started my
journey into the rabbit hole and it was
it has been a wonderful ride since then
thank
you that's so crazy like do you just
have it in your
recommendations even though you didn't
watch vtubers before that's like
thanks YouTube wingman oh even oh hi oh
they're so needy entering my room while
I'm still streaming she's like rubbing
her face against the camera oh and she's
laying down in front of the monitor
chunky
[Music]
wonky what I'm not done
streaming hasin
chuni approaching me she just strutted
in here quickly jumped up the
table so
committed she's so soft
fluffy by the way my mom is Smoothie
Oshi
surprisingly apparently smoothie is
really not as annoying when I'm not
around
she said like not at
all really she didn't have the issue of
her waking her up at
least she likes smoothie more proba but
I feel like it's not fair because um
apparently and that really makes sense
cuz it fits her personality chunky wonky
was just not around this whole 1 and 1/2
weeks she just was hiding because I was
gone she was like sad
meowing sadly and just
hiding out of my Mom's
View such a
baby so she said that she mostly only
saw smoothie
anyway but chunky wonky she's such a
sweet girl you
know yeah my mom's like she said she
usually woke up like around 8 or
so but still smoy woke me up today like
at 6 or
7 but mommy was still there so she gave
her food
[Music]
eventually no no I feel bad for chunky
wonky she doesn't take it so well when
I'm
gone
but good job on being patient good job
baby don't turn off my computer please
please by touching my mouse with your
foot
uh so candy could thank you m that is
really crazy to think about but thank
you so much for making that decision on
that day and staying here since as a
loyal sweet beloved chiming
employee M eight all red J thank you
congrat C your first Final Fantasy clear
you did amazing with the combat today
especially I hope you can experience ff7
too one day oh well we just talking
about it thank you for the series good
luck and safe travels looking forward to
the off collapse and the result of your
hot work
thank yeah
results I I already know the date since
a while when it's going to be streamed
but I I I feel like I want to announce
it properly um when when the date comes
closer
so please please wait a little bit but
it will be in
December
yeah I'm also going to announce the
guests beforehand I've
decided yeah in the form of tweets and
[Music]
images so you'll actually know
beforehand yeah I've seen like some
members announce them beforehand and
some
don't and I thought I I I think I want
to announce it beforehand you
know because I mean it's pre-recorded
anyway let's make use of that and
announce it beforehand have the members
also tease and AD advertise
it yeah day by day up until the live
that that's the
[Music]
plan so thank you
Ma Adam J D I am a team be space
wonderful than morally moral and Fa
thank you for the pinky while was save
world again I love Final Fantasy 16
thank you for playing it thank you too
it was a
pleasure had a lot of fun finally diving
into the Final Fantasy
fandom
[Music]
silhouette H tees no I wasn't thinking
of Silhouettes I was just going to
clearly because Silhouettes in the
end whole life Silhouettes that they're
like usually pretty clear like who it is
so does it even make sense for it to be
silhouette like it's like so obvious
like animal
ears two hats Cena
whatever
okay smoothie H chunky wony do you want
to do you want to Pur into the
microphone
huh come
on if you're going to if you're going to
lie here and be cute you better share
with the
[Music]
classroom no
thank you thank you for your
wisdom
baby now what am I going to eat I don't
have any hellofresh stuff right
now some frozen stuff in the freezer but
that's going to take a while to warm
up oh he's
so
ah I know what I'll make have some some
pesto
[Music]
sauce I just want to be
lazy
M with junky wonky and
smoothie sleeping
endlessly
okay I'm going to put up the reservation
for
tomorrow judging by how it went today uh
we're obviously not finishing
tomorrow
so yeah tomorrow will be probably around
the same
[Music]
length and I'll see you there guys I
have something
before uh
some
special meet up
so um I'll be busy before and also I got
to sign a lot more postcards until
Monday meow
so
I I think I'll probably just not stream
on Monday and then sign for hours cuz I
I already signed a lot but no in the end
I started early this time but in the end
then I got really busy and stopped
signing the cards for a while and now
I'm here stressing out about it again
wow I feel like next year for
Merch I might if I do limit it
signatures handwritten again it'll be a
much smaller number so you
guys if
you're an owner of a sign either real
Polaroid or digital
Polaroid let me tell you you're very
lucky
chicken but especially the real life
Polaroids
[Music]
obviously
fluffy
belly
understandable okay I'll go make
something quick to to eat
now okay guys thank you for watching
sorry I'm kind of like really tired
right now that's why I I may
seem kind
of my eyes are
falling
[Music]
down English sugy myth speaker of
Ian
a ah chky
wonky
leave she's so
electric electric Cat Electric Cheeto
[Music]
cat
tomorrow yeah yeah that was from
her she gets really electric when she's
around my PC
[Music]
stuff okay
bye I saved the game right I can close
it
just turn off the
switch I'm tired let so
[Music]
tired oh I know why it's cuz I didn't
get like a proper
nap that's why I'm
tired no
[Music]
nap wa was
energy C
[Music]
# philosophical
Phoenix
[Music]