[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
happy birthday Japanese bro
[Music]
thank you
we got the we got the walkie-talkies to
work guys hello
oh hi everybody hello
uh so today we're doing it with really
bad walkie-talkie quality to get more
you know immersion everyone
oh God you're you're ready sounds sound
even better in walkie-talkie quality
uh so uh yeah we're playing this game
again this is part two uh you guys
better watch both point of views uh
because otherwise you'll get confused uh
probably more confused than we even are
but both me and AMA are ready to
embarrass ourselves today once again
[Music]
uh and uh we uh ended it last time I
think at chapter six uh I don't think we
can finish it today we're not even gonna
uh hoop hope to finish it
um we're probably gonna do three hours
maximum because uh I have the convention
that Ahmed was on yesterday I have that
today the same convention so I gotta be
there in time yeah
yeah AFP represents
uh teammates represent
I saw some really cute anime cosplays
there yesterday what was one of them
actually you
um I don't think so uh I was cosplaying
um a different grade streamer yeah
ah okay anyway oh uh oh what what the
hell what
that is no toy
[Music]
she probably doesn't hear me now right
because I can't activate the
walkie-talkie
[Music]
what
don't rain and let's go
what's going on
you guys hear it as well
Eternal I'm a tunnel
okay
I mean that was super creepy are you
still alive
oh uh I just was in a cut scene and I
think we're on the wrong chapter
you mean we're too late to to to to too
advanced
yeah because the last time we were
playing we're doing the alchemy One oh
we switched places I think we did yeah
because I think I see the thing now that
you saw before
how did we do that time traveling
huh copy that copy what copy what
I don't know
um I think yeah I think we we have to
what did you do what did you do I mean
oh is this the thing you did last time
no we're not gonna do that [\h__\h] again
are we nope nope nope nope nope okay
exit to the lobby okay I exit bye bye
[Music]
I'll hide the screen because I don't
know what it will show
[Music]
I'm hiding the uh your partner left you
to die oh my God
I
I I'm hiding the screen uh I guess you
can open the lobby again
I am thank you
she left me to it says she left me to
die on my screen partner disconnected
don't make it so dramatic
oh you got it
um it says I can only go up to chapter
six but I think the one we just tried
was chapter six no
did it not
did it not save
our progress
but we finished the part that we just
landed in I I don't remember how we did
that
I found that
I found this game Auto Sales
yeah I thought I did too I think it
maybe it just didn't uh it didn't save
it properly oh my God okay
um oh I see a room
wait is that are you in your room
uh I'll say right okay
[Music]
I guess we have to do it again
no then I will remember how to do it
remember I remember
oh dear yeah we'll speed run it we'll
get it on the first try okay
[Music]
wait
um
[Music]
I don't know I don't know we'll see
we'll see oh okay
[Music]
then I press ready let's go
let's go
oh
uh game okay there we go
oh God I don't want to do that [\h__\h]
again
is she laughing does she hear me
where are we now
okay yep uh I'm in a different place now
that's for sure
what I'm in the
uh
am I going to ratley
is this where I came from
ah okay yeah I'm getting the same
cutsceness from
before I guess this is almond
finally another Soul here to save
Captain is a hellish Castle foreign ages
now listen there is a way for us I need
your help
arthritis over there
get it to work and retrieve the stone
with him I'll explain later
okay
cutscene ovals
I hate this I hate this this is giving
me bad Deja Boos
is this your time Loop Ahmed did you
create this time Loop
maybe oh God okay
um
blue to orange green to Red what blue
blue
two ah blue blue blue to orange green
I don't know
maybe maybe
um you know what maybe I'll open my my
stream uh from back in the day
or or someone from the viewers can open
it and tell me what is to the right side
of that and to the left so I can can the
chat help me please
um I'm just gonna I'm just gonna rely on
chat okay I'm in
all right kfp get to work please help me
please help me what's let's go let's
just go in the right side order can we
just go that way this way
can I use Panic who's super effective
might be different each time eh no this
looks the same this is the same that's
for sure bad idea
is
it
I believe
I have so many windows open please don't
please don't make me open my own stream
from back in the day tell her to college
but I'm do you do you remember the order
I think so okay
um
but do you remember the order as it was
like
on my screen like
do you do you know what's next to the
one that's orange and green
red
red red
or red only
just read okay so that I'm gonna put
that to the
one on like there's two two thingies
where I can put it the one on the right
side and the one on the left side
connecting but I guess it no it's only I
don't know
um
so red only either connects to blue blue
or blue green
oh
right only blue blue and blue green
[Laughter]
[Music]
blue blue I don't have blue green so
I'll get testing
okay I think that's working and it stops
oh okay I think I think that works um
continuing please
that did not work okay that did not work
it looked like it was working to me
well it started differently from last
time so it started at blue blue and it
went to red and then it went to orange
green yeah and it stopped
yeah yeah because I don't have all of
them in there yet
right what comes out the orange green
do you know
uh if we're going opposite
then no I didn't know
um
uh
um what colors could be connected with
orange green on your on your thingy
yes there's a blue green there's blue
and then there's just Orange
I think chat was saying that it should
be blue green
I I don't have blue green
is that orange one of them okay so it's
either only orange or only blue
okay testing
at least we kind of like okay yeah I
think that works no at least we kind of
know the basics oh it worked it worked
until there so I need I need to know
what's connected with red and blue
the only option is blue orange blue
orange
but I don't have
one what
that is weird because I don't have a
blue orange I only have orange orange
and blue
um
[Music]
I don't understand
okay uh or just a single blue okay okay
I will try it
okay
trial and error trial never guys
shut down
okay let's see
connect connect
[Music]
and connection oh
yeah okay that was not it
that's okay because uh we could just try
again and it'll be the same I guess when
you like start a new chapter when you
start again from the beginning that it
randomizes so it's not the same as last
time oh no
but so now what
um I don't think it randomized again
probably right probably now it's still
the same as the previous try
probably hopefully
yeah yeah it'll be the same as the one
we just tried so it doesn't work on the
end where like
um it goes
I don't know my mood doesn't work after
orange so maybe it has to be a different
one because uh yeah to go after that
wait okay so uh
what what was connected with uh with uh
orange green again sorry
either orange blue or blue green orange
blue orange blue a blue green I don't
know
I don't know okay orange but what did I
use the first time
and what was connected to Blue only
uh just orange sorry just Red Green
so does that mean that this would go
here
I mean is this what I just did before
I guess I could also go to single orange
okay uh I'm testing
it looks like up until there it's
working
so what connects one more time uh with
uh orange and green
uh either single red blue green
or a single Orange
so last time I did orange I think I know
it worked right
no let me see
uh testing
it has to connect to two things yeah I
know I know okay but this is working I
just need to figure out this one and not
die again okay I think until that point
it worked again
uh the last time I put in uh
the remaining
which one did I put in white connects to
red and blue red blue
uh blue blue or blue orange okay and I
used blue blue and I died so but I don't
have the other one that you said
so what the hell
I think that I died I think I was the
one who died because I was standing in
the water over here when it uh went oh
oh
okay you mean that was a timeout okay
does she mean that did I really want to
have time okay testing testing it didn't
look like it was that close to the
ground though
okay
then that was really bad timing
no what do we what do we get come on
oh
yay
that was fairly fast thankfully
that's because of our two big brains put
together which will now disappear and
become a no-brainer
which actually shouldn't not be
something good
we gotta make a concoction here I think
Watson concoction
oh God this looks complicated
and we we stopped here last time
oh you know what I think it is is
because this technically isn't part of a
new chapter it's like part of the same
chapter yeah probably
where do I go
is there a toy here at least we're not
in a time limit now I'm gonna describe
what I see in front of me
um I see uh what is it ah oh wait a
second I'm still uh exploring oh okay
almost there
uh like a maze and I also see she was
stuck uh something to mix potions
explosions
is I gotta go through this door oh
is that her
is
no game is like yeah every time when a
new area loads it lags a little bit
sorry but it will
what's it called a
Soul Stone
now I need you to find all the pieces
one of them is in here in the greenhouse
is she seeing us cutscene too but you're
done don't fight me in the high
Alchemist quarters oh like a different
one
you talking to me
talking
she sees a different one okay hello I am
back
um I just saw a cutscene
hey that sword is like your sword well I
have a sword but it kind of looks like
your sword
pick it up pick it up
I have it but it's broken
okay well I I'm in a room that has a
free big barrels tattoo and
um
a lot of tubes
tubes maybe many tubes
okay
uh where should we start
good question
ah
um
pipes I mean pipes I see a lot of pipes
that are
um they have like buttons underneath
[Music]
and oh a few numbers as well
and uh oh they I have two letters two
levers that are next to the pipes one is
orange one is blue
uh
okay
I found some uh pieces of pipes
me too me too
uh I have I have uh three uh ah free
free pieces of pipes I has
oh wait four
um yeah okay
and
um
looks like you can can you can collect
all the pipes
Pokemon
yeah yeah I got the I got the pipes I
post uh um I pulled the the yellow
leather and now I have some yellow fire
running through the pipes
but
it stops
somewhere
uh so I found a book here to make like
different uh potions or something and it
looks like uh it's got some instructions
here that each bag turns into
uh oh there's like a powder that you can
mix with the liquid that makes like a
different fruit it looks like so we're
trying to make a fruit that's uh kind of
looks like a mushroom and a pineapple
put together and the way we make it is
by mixing green bucket liquid with
yellow cup liquid to make green big
bucket cup liquid
yeah
oh
okay
uh hey I see like yellow smoke coming I
I don't know if that's you yeah yeah
that's my my smoke I think my fire my
guess yes guys guys I turned it on I can
also turn on the blue one and there's
the barrels I guess the yellow one
kind of is connected to the barrels I
guess they all are connected to the
barrels
and the barrels have some colors on them
though one is a purple one is orange and
one is green
does that say anything to you
no
okay good
um
uh what are these numbers what do the
numbers mean what do the numbers mean
one
ready
two one
two goes to four
and also two five
Mason what do the numbers mean what do
they mean
uh
do you did you just change something
over there
uh copy that I did oh uh wait I can
place them
why would I want to place that where
which one do I want to place
two of those
uh
[Music]
what exactly did you change over there
uh I'm messing with the pipes the pipe
connectors and I I think this is uh I
don't know it's like some sort of gas
that I'm trying to ignite within all
these pipes and have different
connectors so I'm just trying to make
sure that it's working
oh
aha
I should change something again I guess
okay
does that would move over there but like
that doesn't go anywhere so I would say
if anything I would have to overtake it
again
oh but wait
ah why does it still come out of two
but it does connect all the way over
here
kind of so if I were to put another one
oh
no wait it comes from above and what if
I go this way
oh now it goes all the way over here
but it doesn't do anything
um
yummy
oh my God I see you some red red fire
now do you have a
did you did you activate some red fire
uh yes I did
ah
it was like no now we changed back to
Yellow
just doing stuff she's doing stuff over
there now it's all yellow
turn on the the red one again
okay copy that
oh
where is it
did you turn oh there it is okay I see
the the gas the red gas now
um
is this a I think we need cups do you
have any cups Cups
I I have no cups no
I only have a tubes
me too
I don't understand
I don't get it is anything happening on
your screen a mess not real like I say
like the general color of the gas is now
our Orange
not red
and I try I'm trying to connect it
that's that it goes to the the barrels
because like the tubes the pipes they
are kind of connected to the barrels
and but yeah I think I have to try
around a little bit to make it
connect properly I guess
what if I put this here okay and uh
or um
I guess wait well if I what if I put
oh wait
ah wait what if I pulled this one
here
and then
there's one here
and it turned orange again but it
doesn't
really do anything here
I think you gotta mix colors
because this is orange this is green
this is purple and I have yellow one
blue
and she has red do you have any other
color than red don't activate it but do
you have anything besides red
that I messed it up uh no I only have a
red and yellow but I'm gonna try to fix
my parts
okay
wait what do I need to make purple red
and blue ready for green
uh
uh yellow and
wait a second
go a little bit yellow and blue for
green really was that it
smells like something it wouldn't work
eh what what excuse me what
I made an orange yeah I made orange too
um
can I put a straight one here why is it
like flowing out of there
can I put that here oh no no it's gone
don't even
do I even need this part it just has to
go over there what the hell
one
two
um how about this
I don't understand I feel like it's like
everywhere connected
properly that's what it looks like to me
maybe not
Maybe
maybe this one was right
[Music]
and then
here we put
almond maybe almonds looks like
something oh it's leaking my gas leaking
that's not good is it that can never be
good
oh should I make this one this one first
try to make that one first
I am now activating blue I'm just gonna
try the blue first I'm gonna turn yellow
off
can you uh keep red activated
is red on right now yes it's on right
now
okay that comes from there so
I'm gonna put that there now it's purple
nice oh it's purple yeah oh yeah it
should be purple again if I do this
I can't talk at the same time on the mic
like on the uh
yeah sorry uh
should be purple purple it is purple but
there's something something I am doing
wrong it is but something I am not doing
correctly one second
all right so maybe if I describe what
the area I'm in looks like it might help
you so I have a red lever in the wall uh
connected to some pipes and there's one
two three four five six seven pipes
which are each respectively by their
numbers
I have I have those numbers as well
okay and then um I also can see a flame
so there's like a flame and that
represents the color I think you
probably have something similar to
a flame that represents the color
well yeah those yeah yeah yeah right now
it's purple
yeah mine too I think
um
this represents like a liquid so there
should there should be like a container
that you it's all can pick up
foreign
[Music]
one moment please
yeah
I'll be my update I found some juice
juice
[Music]
motion blur
motion blonde motion blur motion blur
motion blur motion
to Bloom as well
turn this one is nice though we can join
it all
doesn't really do much difference
okay
um
yeah okay I guess uh I guess I guess it
isn't it shouldn't be leaking but I
can't put anything in there
I found cups and I filled them with
juice
uh-huh
oh okay okay you do you
it's better oh thank God okay
um now focus on the riddle kfb my dear
chickens combine your brain cells please
I drank the juice
[Music]
don't drink it on me that's that's
probably really bad uh concoction that
is expired go backwards
was that um some magical juice perhaps
well anyway let me try to figure this
out okay
um
What if I
no that has to stay connected that has
to be
it has to be this way
otherwise it's not purple
what what does this site look like when
I um
what if it's not that one
maybe maybe it's
um
maybe this one
oh no that just goes upwards
that God that goes nowhere
no it has to be the straight one
I conclude it has to be the straight one
um but this one is made now but there's
frame coming out and here
there's one coming out oh wait now
there's two coming up
what if
put this like these
so
blue goes that way
um
[Music]
no no it's just red oh
and trying to
recombine it so it's purple again but in
a different way because I think the
first way was not correct
what number is blue going into
uh
free
tell me
what did you do something there
did she change something
and I want another one of those three
part ones but
can I put no
but it's purple
game
comes out of the three on Amazon is on
the wrong riddle
you have to tell Emma the numbers with
which numbers all right besides the
pipes uh what else what else do you have
nothing only pipes
needs less leaks I mean there's one leak
um
I add three barrels yes barrels and
pipes barrels and pipes free Barons that
have free colors one of them is purple
one of those orange and one of them is
green and I'm currently creating a
purple flame
uh that should
I'll wait a second
no oh yeah that it should it should go
it should connect to the barrel and then
fill it up I suppose but
uh I have I have a leak somewhere I
think
okay do you think the leak could be on
my end since I also
uh yeah maybe I have a leak at number
one I guess
after that I'm on my way okay
can she connect that
[Music]
oh and actually I don't really care oh
hmm that changed everything to Blue and
I still have the link
because you turned the left yellow level
oh
okay I made it I mean I turned it in ah
I turned I turned green a yellow one now
it created something green but now it's
now it's gone again what did you press
no it's now it's green again
okay but so now I don't really have any
leaks anymore uh
uh wait does that mean the leak is okay
if it's there because how would I have
my purple
um uh
okay never mind let me let me test out a
little bit
let's try to make green I guess
what
if uh
shouldn't then in that case
because I don't need two Blues
that is
wait a second what do we have here two
I don't understand
drunk yeah
no
what did you drink again
juice is there no more pipe
because she drunk pipes aren't connected
to the barrel if you're looking at this
one Vehicles here
seven
[Music]
why does it stop there oh
uh did what did you just do
um I connected my flames
okay keep them that way maybe I'll test
it out
can you describe again what uh what you
have in front of you
um I have all those numbers that you
said I have them as well they're on on
below and on top of
um big big big pipes
and that I have single pieces of pipes
which with which I can connect the pipes
and there's like gas coming out of the
pipes
um and I can turn the pipes
so that pipes get connected in in the
right way I guess
and uh
then
in some way at some point they should
lead up to the barrels and fill the
barrels up
and also I have the two levers with
yellow and blue
does that make sense okay so can we
confirm like if we fill it with a
certain color like if we
um contain all the leaks if it uh fills
the barrel with like a certain color
liquid so that we can test because I
have juice on my side
juice
uh yeah for example when it was all
purple
um I was hoping for it to fill up the
purple Barrel but it's
um
didn't fill up because I guess something
is leaking
what is your way to identify the leaks
and maybe we could try again and then uh
press the lever and maybe that'll do
something
um
my way to identify them is well I just
see it leaking
anything I've been pressing about no
no
okay
oh no
um
you turned on red I think
okay I will
I will try again to make purple by by
turning off Yellow by by turning off
yellow
which gives me a link though but
otherwise how am I supposed to make
purple if if yellow is on I need for
purple I need red and blue and you
activated red so I activated blue
and not yet now it's purple
let me just try over I'm just okay one
second I'm gonna try it all over I'm
gonna remove all the pieces
okay okay copy that
what if what if it's not supposed to go
straight
maybe that was the issue
uh what if it's supposed to go like no
that makes no sense no it has to go
straight
that makes no sense otherwise
okay so what if
I sent this one didn't I do that already
I've said I sent this one uh oh wait
does it what if I send it downwards
oh
let's see it
well it comes from below when it comes
from
from the left well how about this
sending it downward sends it to Ahmed
[Music]
why is it leaking from there did she do
something
let me remove that it comes from then I
come from above before
what about now
no and now it makes from above wait is
that because
well
wait a second it it comes from left
and below below is below comes from here
yeah okay that makes sense and from the
left it comes from
here but here we have the leak
I'm a ninja anywhere in your vicinity do
you have uh something that has gears
and Ladders
did that looks like a gear
[Music]
I can't pick it up or do anything with
it
um does it look important
no not really seems like decoration
there's a door that's locked so
yeah I really only have this room with
the barrels and the
the pipes
ah my chancellor has been saying you're
doing the wrong puzzle but I don't know
I mean I can't really tell
uh do you have do you have a pipe that's
connected to one be honest I have
barrels which I can get juice from I
have this uh Contraption which looks
like it might affect affect the pipes
but uh this has a bunch of
um Cog wheels on it that are movable and
then one two three four five ladder uh
icons on it I don't know what they
represent I don't know what it's
supposed to mean but there's two red
um gears like cogs on it and then I also
have one Contraption which looks like
it's to mix
um which uh I can close and it mixes
something and then I have another
Contraption which kind of looks like a
fryer where I can put the cups of juice
and if nothing happens when I do that
then I have two books which describe
some recipes and then I have those seven
pipes with a ton of uh pieces she has so
many things okay
um do you have the pipes do you have
anything that's connected with number
one
well then I gotta get there one second
okay
okay she's on the wrong part oh God
yeah the recipe part is like I don't
know the numbers the numbers that suits
my whatever I'm doing here
um
[Music]
all right uh I'm at number one and I
have a four piece connector pipe uh
which is connecting in all four
directions oh
okay did you like insert that somewhere
or is that like already in place
I inserted it
you inserted that and ah can you get rid
of that
okay got it okay
uh what do you have
so uh is that
it's still leaking
and like put that four piece connector
put it at number five maybe
uh so at number five
um it just shows like where the flame
would be if it were connecting earlier
on but at the moment there's no uh
Flames coming through to number five and
there's no place to connect it the only
places I can connect pipes is between
six and seven six and seven pipe three
which connects to two and then at pipe
one
aha
um
[Music]
maybe six and seven because like
whenever I had the color right
then it still wouldn't go through maybe
put that one at six and seven
but I'm missing red now okay over copy
well actually another question did you
turn off red or was that connection
connected with the four piece thingy so
if you take that off I have no more red
I just turned it off the red is
controllable via liver please turn red
on
happy okay
so when red turns on it comes from
you need you just need to color right
with high enough pressure to fill the
Bears remove leaks to increase pressure
uh-huh
you mean that that thingy has to be on
the very left the right or left
but I'm not getting red I'm not getting
red did she do it
the red isn't connected I'm still not
getting red
um
oh it's because I don't have a pipe in
number one oh oh oh okay
um put it put it there again I guess
yeah thank you
I went but then I wait now I don't have
a leak though now I don't have the leak
okay keep it keep it like that
um
let's try this one
come on come on
hey what just happened why is it why is
it coming from above now ah
tomato
how about this
come on come on now it's leaking here
progress I don't see any progress man
it's the same [\h__\h] all over again
um
oh by the way it's almost it moved it
was in the middle before
um I see one change and that is oh wait
ah you said you have six to seven and
number three as well right oh can you
put something at number three one of you
cubes thingies
because I have all this video uh on my
way
okay I don't know which pieces she has
though uh yes ah
ah that changed the color back to Blue
I just removed the pipe
um so there's like a
all right so the weight looks like is
that the number two pipe is coming from
you whereas for me the number one pipe
is now connected to Red which means it's
feeding into three and two which mixes
it
can you the the the piece that you put
into six and seven can you put that into
three
it's a four piece connector I think copy
that which that was a four piece
connector right
yes okay now this now now I have that uh
what if I what do I do
have normal links
but it's not filling up I have no more
leaks which is I think a progress
but please wait please hold on
she has these do you want to deliver
something that you can turn the barrel
juice into a different color
uh yeah but um I need I need it to be
purple right now
no connection to the barrel ah do we
have any other piece that you can put
into the the last six seven connection
yes I got a uh I got an L shape two
connector or I guess the one connector
but it's like you know two ways oh can
you put that in there
I think that will uh yeah put that one
one way connector in there I think that
will do it because I guess it's like
this part right well there's nothing
there's nothing coming out of oh
of this one
there's no flame at four five six or
seven oh oh okay then I think
you will need to put
any piece
at four
uh I can only put pieces between six and
seven at three and at one
[Music]
I just it is a flame though there
wait a second here we have are you okay
we don't want do you do you have leaks
anywhere
[Music]
technically no but uh I am missing a
flame at number one because I put third
piece connector instead of the four
piece connector we do have a little hold
on I'm just I'll fix it on my end okay
okay
um
yeah it stops
here and it goes up to three
ah and then it's only blue oh wait ah
yeah now now it's generally only blue
oh my God
why is almost already an hour ah now
it's red nothing purple nothing
connected okay
um now I always again ah now it's purple
oh
you
know of course I no longer have any
leaks from one to three and I now have
Flames coming in from four to seven they
just disappeared probably based off
something you did yeah yeah probably
um
how about this
um so now I have the same leak as I have
before but I I'm not sure if that is
actually a problem
oh
yeah uh what what and now it's only blue
everywhere maybe there's something else
we're missing
yeah now now it's back to only blue
color I think you removed the red one
yes
um
kind of map or like uh some sort of
symbol somewhere because I have this
piece that I think is important with the
gears and stuff and I I'm not sure what
to do with it ears
is it what does it look like only gear
is on it or
uh so it's kind of like a it's a it's a
hexagon and it has
um different
uh circles connected with dots where
within the circles and dots oh sorry uh
different dots connected between each
other and in those connections I can
move gears uh throughout like the puzzle
I did not understand that okay chat is
saying it's just the pipes we just focus
on the pipes okay okay
um
let me think
[Music]
my
foreign
guys comes from one and from six seven
and from Ah that's purple again
and from free right
but
uh
doesn't matter if there's leaks okay
it seems like the problem is weeks okay
make signals
um
can you
stop the gas
that comes from number one
is going in a circle
uh
see I'm drinking tea but it's already
warm lukewarm God damn it
oh we're just chat you both know what to
do and not what to do
remove your plants okay I will remove
all my pipes again
okay
um
uh okay so right now I have only
blue that goes
from like into it's trying to go to pipe
too anyways uh can you turn red on again
[Music]
please go
bread please
it's not coming though
uh
uh can you send your red flame to six
and seven is that a thing you can do
all my pipes disconnected
[Music]
okay I See Fire
um
over there the thing is I'm the flame
that I get from you
um wait can you I get the number two
from you the uh type number two feeds in
from you and then so does four
five six and seven four five six and
seven
but she also has control over these
right
uh yeah
um I I uh
don't know what to say
um
uh all that I'm thinking
uh can you get the some can you get some
red fire going through number three
ah
how about this
but I need now I don't have red anymore
[Music]
we're not giving up we're not giving up
purple okay uh oh wait I just had purple
there for a moment that looked good yeah
what about this
no
um
now it's blue
now it's purple
um
keep it like that
let me try this but I feel like I did
this already before
[Music]
well
how about this
no how about this
okay I think we got it really oh never
mind whatever you had before
okay I turned it back to before
for one more before
this one
yeah leave it like there okay
lagging here by the way yeah hold on one
second
this is this might Remove Your Flames
let me check something yeah I have some
other leaks now
aside from the source work your way
through the pipe all right hold on one
second
plug the holes as you told out going I'm
drunk I drink too much juice
what
oh my God there's a lot of red
all right can you mess with the
connection the connector that comes from
two or three or one one of those yes
wait
all right wait oh okay just leave it can
you put the four piece connector into
the last one yes
ah
no oh
what
the four piece connect oh no never mind
dad ignore me
but I think I need gas from one
mom
friends
I currently do not have any leaks
that's good I guess
well I don't know someone in chat said
then so I just told her what the chat
says because you guys seem to be smarter
than me
forget it
everything on my end looks good the
colors are mixed and also there's no
leaks
yeah the colors are definitely good but
now I have a
a connection that is not working I will
I will I will test around some things
[Music]
did I have that before
oh my god did she do something
[Laughter]
yeah she's doing something she's doing
something
foreign
[Music]
what do we have here apparently four
four
three how about this uh
um
I am
maybe we should start from the beginning
hold on I'm messing around with it
okay so I think what it is like
obviously whatever you're changing also
changes the yeah
to figure out the way
um where neither of us have any leaks
[Music]
all right
um
can we start from the beginning
all right
um let's just go to the first part
copy that let's let's do one pipe at a
time so I think the first one I'm
putting actually has to be correct
so I just sent blue over to the next
pipe
um
I guess what do you what what are your
options here at the first thing whatever
you have
all right so I have red coming in from
the left connector which can be
connected to the three other connectors
and uh at the bottom connector it would
ignite One Flame at the top connector it
ignites two Flames but it still comes
out on the right connector that makes no
sense when I first don't see it and when
I don't see it that makes no sense to me
[Music]
um
all right comments and hype number three
I can connect uh what did you there's a
red I mean red gas coming out of the
left connector and the blue gas coming
out of the top connector
uh can you
um make it so that it doesn't go through
number one
please I'm so lost but I think yeah okay
yes
um but I still need red I just don't
want it to go for number one
okay but uh this creates a leak on my
side
um
yeah I mean I also I also have a look
because we're not done
uh I think I think that's okay
um but please uh
can you somewhere except for another one
somewhere else makes blue and red
I wish I at least I could see what she's
doing I need a camera extra camera right
here please
ah okay nice now I have purple
and no leak on that side I think this is
uh good
so maybe let's keep it there
um
no
okay next
okay I'm gonna send yeah I'm gonna send
the purple one
uh to
number five I guess so I don't
understand this where does it even
ah to
um what is this just connected to four
four tubes
what what happens what happened now in
your place
I don't know actually okay
um
[Music]
I don't get it I don't get it
[Applause]
[Music]
um I don't I I don't I don't understand
okay I'll describe uh so four and five
both come out uh individually from the
floor for me and they both need their
each flame ignited and then there's one
in the middle so I don't know if if one
comes out of four it might ignite five
and then go to six and seven
[Music]
nope
ah
um what happened
oh
okay now it's blue
is my connection correct I have take
Knight three on my side but um
I don't know how to do that without uh I
have a leak I don't know if it matters
I saw this okay
there's two more times
is she still doing something
oh yeah doing something
[Music]
use the tea now what
I'm not touching it anymore no taxi no
taxi no Taxi
only cats tattoo
while I'm here let me look at this you
understand it the next time
no I don't understand it
hold the line I'm holding the line
let's sip some tea
uh
tell Ahmed what numbers she needs to
connect but I don't even know
even like how do I know but now there's
a leak so isn't that perfect
um how would I know
how would I know
does this have a meaning because this
one is like I don't know darker and this
one is brighter
why is it like that is that is there any
meaning behind that that is the only one
that's so bright behind I guess it's
probably not no connection to a four
pipe I have a pipe so yeah but like I
have only three places to put it in so
there will always be one pipe left over
that's just Graphics okay
[Music]
how's it going Kiara
oh
I think like on my side
um there's no leaks
and everything is purple
now now I have a link
or it's not gonna hear noises
four is not gonna like does that mean on
my side it's not gonna so do it you guys
said no taxi though I'm not doing touch
Itachi
Minecraft okay
now I'm doing tachitachi
even though you guys told me to not tell
dachitachi but now I'm supposed to do
tattoos what if I do this no I'm free I
don't know foreign
do you do you have any leaks now
uh
I do not but uh number one flame and
number three flame are not ignited
but Chad says that I they said that I
had the right pipe connector so I don't
know
um
sorry I do have a leak between six and
seven at the bottom
oh okay
um
so you have more leaks now
uh hold on
one second
I hate riddle games I'll never play them
ever again
wait is this should I change this again
because you guys had no taxes it wasn't
correct should I do this changes again
and put the L shape one again and didn't
work
it was right before it was right before
put it back
but but
oh
she changed the pipe
um
I'm gonna take a four-way pipe and six
and seven uh-huh
can you take out the the four-way pipe
from six and seven
already did
thank you
so what did I do
wait
one moment please
is this how it's supposed to be we only
situation before
how about this
that was red why is it red now
I don't think she's mate
why am I so stupid
[Music]
um
look at the pressure yeah it's like a
little bit oh now it's in the middle now
it's a bit more do we need to be on
green just just help me with that does
it have to be on green or in red does it
have to be on evil the very most of one
side
does anyone know
it has to be
tell Emma not to feed you for
I'm standing for one again okay
it has to be on green okay
ah
oh I should turn something off
um what did she turn off
uh did you just turn on the number one
yes
um
please no no feeding from number one
please
thank you
um
[Laughter]
can you send
uh red from
before three four
one of those right you have control on
one of them right
six seven one she has six seven and one
ah
[Music]
like that
oh yeah probably I think
foreign
[Music]
without any leaks I I think we want no
leaks and we want my I have this
pressure thingy pressure
meter on my side and I have it I need it
to be on the very
um right side
um
uh and right now it's a little bit of uh
uh in the middle sorry okay I start
again
I have a pressure meter and
um now it's in the middle now it's going
below the middle now it's changed to
below the middle I need it to be higher
I needed to be at the maximum now it's
like at the middle now
uh now it's at the middle
so I need it to be at maximum pressure
um
then it will fill up the barrels if I
understand correctly I think I do so
and
um
uh there is a leak at one again
um and the the red one that you sent
through
tree
um I think
can you send the red one only for one
and three right
only three one and three
do you have any other way to send the
red one besides through one and three
I can't get it to three because if I
send it only two well yes
oh my God
foreign
okay now it's completely off
when I was one again
as I I at least right now finally
understood the fact that since she's
above me
it's coming through here
I didn't quite understand like where she
is and where she's sending it from where
it's coming from but okay I think I
understand it's like coming from here
and from here
but are these the only places where she
can send something from
all right going to one and three
uh the free is fine but the one I don't
want the number one I don't need that
uh okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
uh keep it like that for a moment
okay
no oh purple
what now
how's the pressure yeah the pressure is
higher now so that's good but it's not
at maximum yet
um
[Music]
okay I sent I sent the purple flame up
to number three can you send that
to the next place
uh nope there's no way for me to connect
three and four four just comes out from
the ground
is there any way for you to fix any
leaks you have except like uh don't
don't make it come out of number one
[Music]
yeah
now it's coming out of number one now it
stopped
eh yeah now now is now is uh
not coming for number one so that's okay
but can you connect number three to
number four
[Music]
I don't think so
please wait
foreign
[Music]
do you have a purple coming through ah
wait keep it that way
uh okay
um
one second one second please please hold
the line
okay
where is it like where is it wrong where
where is it wrong
do you have a leak
yes I have one where where is that leak
in which one
[Music]
Nike
calm calm
uh if you turn off number two is it
possible for you to turn off number two
then I won't have a leak number two
turn off number two
uh
um
[Music]
no
uh I can't turn it off
it just comes through the ground I don't
have anything any way to turn it off
I think
or
uh I can I can try to not send it to
number three or I can try
to not send it
to
number six
[Music]
or number five
don't send me number three one moment
please
wait is there any red right now oh yeah
look
ah
[Music]
where's where's Red there it is
we will never get this done
we will never get this done yay
[Music]
oh purple
Hallelujah purple low pressure
[Music]
low pressure
big pressure
can you what did you just do something
can you undo whatever you want whatever
you just did
ah no that was probably not it
for a moment for a little moment when I
put something in I think at the same
time you put something in there to
change something before a moment it went
almost to maximum pressure it was look
on the way to maximum pressure I think
did you guys see that it wasn't changing
anything really I had it set on like one
thing for like a 30 seconds hmm
okay
um
well
uh
why am I on why not why should I not
take you guys told me to not take this
one
but like I needed
the purple
beautiful it's purple oh
it's higher pressure now
um
can you
do you
you have
at this very moment
[Music]
I'll leak
yes I have a leak uh where it says
number three there's a flame coming out
of three yeah and there's also a flame
coming out of two and two is leaking but
three is connected to the uh pipe that
leads to one
[Music]
um
I
understand
nothing
I know nothing
ah
what's what's
um
uh so I think
um like when you said the pressure
changed to maximum there was a flame
coming through one from your end
it's the only change I saw
um
[Music]
foreign
my side is correct
[Music]
I have leaks coming from number three
can you stop that
oh
I hate this right now I hate it
okay
now
uh I have a
I have purple so that's good
but now I have leaks here and you guys
said it's fine but these links are
coming from me now
[Music]
it's working it's working it's working
whatever you did now was correct
foreign
okay let's take out all the pipes
and make uh Orange
so I belong today blue and I will turn
I'm turning on yellow uh you can keep on
red
um but I guess it will have to come
through a different place we'll figure
that out let's start from the beginning
um the Wayne yes
I think that is already something good
whatever you did
I have orange flowing through number one
and that one goes for me to
um wait what did you just do did you
just do something
oh
wait
it is orange but but wait wait wait wait
[Music]
okay
um I currently
um have
uh I have it going through I have orange
going through five now but now it's
yellow again
um
can you
uh while you place the pipes
can you tell me exactly what where
you're placing them
okay
um I just connected red to Yellow which
was a red exit flame thank you to number
one which uh seemed to turn your flame
orange yes moment there's nothing else
coming out of anywhere else
okay
uh
um where where does it
um where does it stop for you now
[Music]
um all I have from you is um yellow
coming from number one
hello I also have some coming out of six
and seven okay can you connect that
somehow
now
um I have Flames that are going to four
and five and I have one coming out of
three that I can connect to two if you
like
um I'll test it out
do I need oh
like maybe
um
[Music]
does that make any sense
how's the pressure
uh it's like a tiny bit above middle
and I think
uh the two doesn't really lead anywhere
for me so the two is unnecessary yeah
yeah
mmm
I want to put a tea one here
[Music]
um I put I put the
connector
that sends it to five
and six
and uh
I understand now I have almost almost
maximum pressure
okay I do have a leak um
where
it doesn't help if I send it through two
because then it makes it leak on your
side
yes and it's less pressure
now it's even less now it's more
[Music]
now it's less pressure
it filled up
yes we got the orange one yeah how did
we do that I think that was lucky very
lucky
I guess we we really should follow the
the pressure meter and organize by doing
that by looking at that okay
uh green is made by
yellow
and blue
so I'm standing blue
uh you can stop actually you can stop
red now
hey I I already had a feeling that this
had some kind of meaning but now I got
the definite yes that when it's at
maximum
it works so blue I'm gonna send the blue
one
this way
uh ah she's sending yellow too wait how
do I need to send my yellow then because
I guess you you are you can send uh
yellow as well
are you are you able to send yellow too
or do you only have red
one second or is that no she only has
red okay okay
ah oh okay whatever you did now well I
think it's it needs to stay like that
wait does that mean does that mean only
I am making green
okay we're sending we're sending green
and two I will send green to number
three
um
I see wait now it's not green anymore
yeah one one second she only has yeah
but she has to like help me connect it
right even though she can't make the
color
so
[Music]
um
oh no okay now it's green again
and uh
[Music]
oh wait let me take that
foreign
[Music]
do you have do you have leaks right now
if yes where
where
uh on number one because my my uh pipe
when I send it to where it connects to
number two it uh Loops back around and
leaks into my one area connected here
oh isn't that where her red comes from
um okay something you did changed it
back to Yellow now so something that you
disconnected now I think some at least
somewhere yeah now now it's green again
somewhere it has to be connected so that
my blue and my yellow mixes to
um green because like both colors come
from my side
both yellow and blue
so yeah uh well I still have a week so
well then I'm a mess now a little bit
okay okay I went down on pressure just
so you know
good green
pressure is higher now and it's green
again
well I'll connect something
[Music]
um
but which one
oh now it went down
well I mean it has
I think it has to be that one though um
like you have to send it through three
um I can try to not send it for free one
second
oh wait a second send it to
here
and then try well this one
oh it's very low
uh
is it still going for free oh wait maybe
it is
good night place it this way uh there
okay
okay I'm holding on I'm holding on
holding on
I thought I sent it downwards I wanted I
didn't want to send it upwards
I wanted to send it down one second I'm
gonna change it really quick so now it
comes from here
but I also have it coming through for
why do I have it coming from four four
is like
I guess for for always we'll send it
what if okay I'm I'm also changing
something to test it out what if I put
the
this one
like this
oh
that's too much I still have a leak
where is it
uh it's coming from one
coming from one one second uh
when you send yellow through three
um can you like if you send it through
three maybe and and not send it through
one is that possible
oh we'll we'll check we'll check
send it for free
don't set sending it for sending it for
free now
um we'll try to
um
there's no way to send uh yellow through
three
ah
ah yellow two free uh
wait maybe one second what if I uh What
if I
uh I mean for example
for example would this send it to free
uh wait
this way it should send it to free right
is it coming for free now the yellow
yeah okay okay okay okay okay
I have no more leaks
uh
[Music]
yeah oh oh oh oh sorry actually I need
to change something because it's
definitely not going to connect to the
barrels the way I have it now okay
um
well one second what if I look at this
and I put
she wants but then I have no yellow I
have no yellow
um
this is how I had it before now
no that's that's not it
I understand
and
well
my blue
needs to go to four
and then go come back here is this where
I'm mixing the colors
well
yeah yeah we'll keep it keep it like
this
okay
come on
no no
if I think logically that's it though oh
there's something leaking here can you
stop it coming from free
or do I have no more green then
uh
one second I just gotta change some
stuff
oh
[Music]
wow that took us wait too long oh my God
yeah definitely a little bit faster like
if we had known about the pressure
thingy
my door has opened uh I'm in a new room
I see a big big plant that looks like
the piranha plant from Super Mario
Sunshine
oh it's moving and I see papers that
show me like plants and potions
I have some juice bars with orange green
and purple
okay
I have plants
[Music]
um
seed
seed packets I guess
[Music]
and I have on the other side of the room
I have
a big container
with some signs
okay that could be useful so um I'm
gonna describe again the thing that I
have it's a hexagon with uh gears inside
of it that can be moved uh which are
connected in some places and and it has
five ladder icons
[Music]
okay uh I am on the ladder right now
foreign
[Music]
what signs do you see
okay so there's a like a north
um so it's kind of like a compass on top
of the hexagon like there's an arrow
pointing up yeah
I have a clumps too I have a compass too
okay uh and then I have some gears which
are movable inside of the hexagon and it
looks like
so it's a hexagon right so it's got one
two three four it has got six sides this
might be um parallel to like the shape
of your room maybe because there's
ladders in uh two of the north corners
and
um one of ladders ladders uh West
Corners uh down by the south and then
one by the East and the bottom
what uh
uh um well I have also six signs
like astronomical signs
uh around the compass and also around
the whole room I'm in I'm in like a big
hole in the ground with a ladder and and
the signs are are around the ladder as
well like for example they're on the
fourth piece of the ladder I have like a
planet on the sixth piece of the ladder
I have stars on the seventh piece of the
ladder I have Sun
the eighth one is a Sparkle and the
ninth the last one is the the tenth one
is a moon
okay I'm gonna move around some stuff
see if anything changes for you
[Music]
it's changing currently
stream facts
door what door
what toy
under me
Xbox
I opened something
oh the signs are all moving now
uh it's turning
a lot of stuff is turning
I think I just turned on water
yeah I think we're on a timer now so oh
God no
not again okay
um well uh
what do you see what what can you move
can you move something okay hold on
oh oh oh my ladder pieces are like not
aligned anymore
so I guess we have to move them back so
that I get back up
I'm gonna climb up anymore
yeah no I can't it I can't I can't climb
up right now because the ladder piece is
yeah gone and uh water is like halfway
um like under my elbows
the line piece with the planet
it has to be moved
one second I'm messing around with it I
might be able
I can die a few times I'm a phoenix
doesn't matter
it's okay this is fine this is fine
yeah I guess I'm yeah I moved a ladder
by opening it up like I said activated
it oh God
um water is around
um
my breast
and I'm I'm hanging on to the ladder
right now
in a few seconds it's okay though chill
try to figure out whatever is going on
there
ah
[Music]
the the the the the first symbol the
planet symbol is by the way uh
Northwest and now I'm drowning
this is fine
this is fine I like I like water
okay I'm bye-bye it's turning black
slowly
um
I guess I'll die
okay we'll figure out on the next one
yeah we will we will
we surely will
okay
I just said
okay I'll go into the I'll go into the
Container again
foreign
are we on the moon or something because
the way I jump is like so so soft like a
feather
going down
and go going down right now and uh
should I immediately turn on the water
or
[Music]
one moment okay
what emote bunk chickens add that and or
that around before your mode and it
should work what for real those
so that's the beginning of your message
[Music]
everyone test it out right now
okay so before when uh the room was
filling up is it like you could climb to
One ladder and then the next ladder and
then the next ladder or
um uh I was able to climb up three
pieces of ladder and the fourth one was
gone the fourth one was the planet that
is uh also aligned to North West in the
compass
whoa
it's working okay uh if you turn it on I
think it should move
yes I'm turning it on and the latter
piece moved
and yes the ladder piece
they are gone and water is filling up
okay the liner trees is currently two
steps away from being back in place the
first one
I think I think two two steps
uh one second
let me up
I'm supposed to fly
that's that's enough wait a second
oh yes no Northwest right knee on the
Sci-Fi version
it's a bit difficult I always have to
say it in German in order to figure it
out I can't do it in English
but that's Northwest I think
um I mean the the this one this one this
one
um and finish
oh
I'll climb up
that should ah okay move um move move
keep on moving yes yes yes yes yes yes
stop it there
okay okay okay going up going up next
piece is sparkles sparkles that are I
don't know if that helps you but there
are the
uh
at West
uh there's a what is the what is the
compass direction of it West
I think you know
West West Sparkles are West and it's
like one step away from being in front
of me the latter piece
where the hell did she do that
it was pretty fast she figured it out
pretty fast smart
as expected from a detective
spring sparkles
as one of my favorite emojis oh oh
you're turning the one below me but I
guess that doesn't matter anymore
because I'm already on the one above
yeah should be fine it doesn't kick me
down anymore nice it doesn't all have to
be a line
[Music]
she just screams doesn't suit like
walkie-talkie that's it are you okay
yes yes
[Laughter]
put me back please I'll tell you when to
stop
um
uh yeah stop now
okay okay next one is the Sun and that
is aligned to
um Northeast
at least I don't have to do so much
thinking in this one
thank God did you sleep oh we didn't
talk about that now we have to talk
yes yes I have a lot of time
I'm timeless
um yeah I took that thing yesterday I
was already super tired it was always
super late so I fell asleep immediately
um I feel
I guess a little bit
um a little bit less
tense today but I mean I obviously still
have the the pain in my shoulder and my
neck
but I I guess I probably
I'm not sure to be honest but that's
probably what the medicine
did uh relaxing my muscles so the
general oh
one more roundabout because I'm I'm one
way one one piece away from the ladder
yeah
[Music]
and stop please
perfect perfect next one is uh the star
shaped one
um and that one is at North Side
no uh
uh Southwest
you know what I'm saying in German as a
child this is one of the things
Southwest Southeast one of the things
that you get yeah hold on uh Todd uh to
remember the the the directions
um
um it's a it's a phrase I say never wash
your hands without soap
knee and for Norm
Austin East
uh f sipher is soap for self
and Vashon is wash for West yes Russian
is washing it dreaming and that's West
you know you know what I'm trying to say
oh yeah it's like no soggy waffles I
guess yeah yeah we say don't wash your
hands without soap me on the side for
Russians
oh
no I heard it moving there's not I don't
see anything maybe she's moving the one
below me
and that wasn't working uh
something else is moving but I don't see
which one nothing wait where am I no
you're moving something below me I think
oh okay I see
I assuming this free Sparkles one
never eat stale wheat what what is that
I just remember wheat because we never
got North from southwell last match I
know always have to tell myself that
that sentence otherwise I don't
quite
get it takes me a while
her puzzle involves clicking like crazy
oh dear she must be stressed out
we we
said East
no what I mean
uh is there any way I can help you
uh no I'm just okay
okay
uh
so anyway
yeah um probably because I was already
tired and fell asleep fast I couldn't
really notice the effect of the medicine
and I woke up and I felt like a little
bit more relaxed oh yes the thing about
me is moving uh yes yes yes and stop
stop stop this yes yes yes yes okay last
one uh Moon shaped one is
in east east
please save me I am going to drown like
a fish oh no not like a fish I guess
fish Don't Drown um
foreign
[Applause]
oh like a gouda without floaties
you know the the woman at the pharmacy
who gave me the medicine she was like
really dramatic about the medicine
I close to the ladder to go up but you
have to turn it around one more time
I'm on the last piece
okay okay
we don't have any more time to talk now
but yeah the pharmacy lighting was too
direct dramatic
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm in your brain power so
strong
thank you
wow okay ah wait I guess the the water
it goes for like uh I guess we needed
that water to go up to the
eye goes all the way up to my planting
area
oh now there's like water coming through
the for some um shower thingies and they
put water on the on the uh uh uh uh
uh
uh what's it called
soil soil
sprinklers making water go pew pew pew
on the soil okay
oh I can take this
I'm I can take
seed packets uh
um what do you have over there
uh so nothing new has opened up to me I
still have um I have like a little mixer
uh or it's like a fryer or something and
then I also have a mixer and I also have
two books with two different a few
different recipes which I can read out
too if you'd like
oh yes I also have some recipes uh but
yes please do
all right so I got one recipe book that
has the triple eggplant packet and it
says plus the red juice equals a red
eggplant plant and then it's the blue uh
egg plus the yellow juice makes the blue
eggplant and the uh tentacle of the taco
plant uh plus the purple juice makes the
sorry Taco seeds plus purple juice makes
Taco plant and uh
weird shaped banana plus a green mixed
banana banana
oh okay
um
um some of the things you mentioned I
think
are on my recipes as well but I have
different recipes I have recipes that
make for example
uh two fruits combined turn into one red
juice then I have underneath I have one
combination that makes the the white
juice white potion and one that makes a
light blue potion one that makes a light
green potion and one it makes that
combines the red the blue and the green
one to turn it into a black one
with a deadbeat on top of it
copy that
um
and the the fruits that are uh necessary
to make the potions I have like seed
packets of them I guess I can plant them
let me plant some of them
plants plants
oh
oh okay I already have some plants
growing
up
some funny looking ones
Farmville bird
but I couldn't plan on gonna send some
juice over
but you're sending juice to me
I don't know
oh I just found Minecarts I got
Minecarts here
cards yeah and I gotta lever unless I
can send something to you as well
oh
but I don't know what uh okay uh
um let's see I'll just try to start by
making
the red potion first so I'm gonna make
two fruits
and one that is like a
alien green apple and one that is like
free aubergines
that's probably not the right name in
English
um
uh so I have a book here that uh it has
like a pineapple mushroom and it has
like a weird face on it sort of and it
says
uh yeah it's just in the book and it
says if you mix it with yellow it makes
red potion
what
uh red potion
mixes for you with a juice and a fruit
foreign
yes but wait is there something like is
there a goal like maybe we can figure
out the goal because we can mix all this
stuff but we don't know what we're
supposed to be making
no well all of these potions lead to the
black potion
uh the the black deadly potion I think
they want us to kill the
the big plants in my room
the Super Mario Sunshine blend
okay
and so I need the red the blue and the
green potion so I want to start with the
red one
and
and the red one
needs
yeah two plants but wait wait plans but
do I have them let me see
this room is really really big what did
I plant here
wait uh like the juice that you made
earlier with the pipes that doesn't
affect anything
uh
I didn't make any juice yet
I mean
the pipes that's just the
which pipe do you mean
uh don't worry about it then okay okay
um okay so I'm gonna make the the plants
that I need for the first portion
but it was this one okay I have a
recipes for plants here if you need it
oh yeah can you tell me do you know how
to
make the
the one that looks like
um
does that look like
uh it's like a greenish one
and it has
um some some some
suck sake suck suck knobs
here are uh triple eggplant blue egg
with the wings uh takodachi with green
tentacles and a moldy banana
[Music]
the the triple eggplant yes yes I I I
have a package for that and I need that
one for the red potion but the other one
I need for the red portion is
uh a yellow yellow green
plant then I cannot find the seed packet
for
uh so you have a recipe to make that
plant or
wait a second maybe uh sort of it says
uh yellow the multi banana one plus
green juice equals the plant so I think
you need to have the packet already and
I don't have anything to make the packet
ah okay
I plant here I don't know it's not
growing though
oh here's another one but can I only use
them once
one
moment please
oh so uh on my other book there's a like
a mushroom pineapple looking face fruit
and it says if you uh mix that with the
yellow it makes the red potion and also
there's a green juice in a bucket and if
I mix that with my yellow because I have
access to Yellow drink so if you need
yellow drink maybe I could somehow get
it to you
oh yeah I only have orange green and
purple
cake is that the one I'm
at this is or is this a mushroom
pineapple mushroom s
maybe if I does she have
do you have Minecarts I'm sending some
over there right now
uh I do not have any mine cards because
if I cannot go through here okay they
should arrived in a moment they're
coming
[Music]
well what have I put
oh
take it
but yeah I need to hear your voice
please
um I love you too umek
I'm here I'm here don't worry don't
worry I just collected some juices the
ones that I have though the orange green
and the purple one I just put them in
some buckets
okay don't be scared on it don't be
scared
where's the minecart
what did they not arrive
not that I know oh I see it I found them
okay I'm gonna send you back some juice
and do anything yes please do please
please and then do anything I I lost my
purple stuff
huh wait why can I not add why can't I
only add it to that one but only one
color of juice to only specifically once
uh I was trying to add some of my colors
to my plants uh to my plants but uh it
didn't do anything
you have infinite stuff I lost
connection on the last half of that ah I
added
um purple juice to one of my plants to
make it grow but it didn't grow so that
was not the right thing
oh what the hell oh I only got the top
part oh wait oh never mind never mind
sorry sorry I have the first plant uh
that I needed it just looked different
when it was growing but now that I take
it I already that's the one I was
looking for okay I have the the weird
I think you call it pineapple mushroom
mushroom pineapple
yes now let me plant the free eggplant
one
but how do I get how do I get rid of
these ones
I don't want to grow those
I want to grow
these ones
or the juice
sorry one
um I sent you some juice juice juice
juice juice juice uh
currently the one that I'm making right
now needs no juice I think
okay
thing
okay that was the free eggplant one
right but it's not growing
uh any can you just send me whatever
juice you have there right over
uh copy that already on the way already
arrived no oh nice
super speed delivery yes indeed it has a
raft I can confirm
that's a lot wait I can drink it I'm not
gonna drink that she got drunk from that
didn't she
can I put that there this was it right
nope that was not it what about this I
cannot and wait do you have any any
other juices besides the yellow one
uh negative yeah
why does that one not grow this one
uh do you have any clue over there on
why the eggplant is not growing
does it not like one it looks like here
the eggplant needs the red juice red
juice
do I have red oh do you have red juice
uh no I only have yellow juice
do I have to mix [\h__\h] again with
ranchers I'm worth making I'm making red
juice
and trying to make that one
um
[Music]
oh can you send me back any fruits
well I'll send you a couple wait I'll
send you the ones that I have that are
on the recipe
uh do I have this one okay
oh can you send me back actually uh one
second
I want this one do you have the
pineapple mushroom yes one second
can I plant that here does it grow
it doesn't grow
what have I got this
doesn't do [\h__\h]
okay uh let's plant here to plant uh
Center the pineapple
mushrooms hopefully
Cindy sending
and uh they don't grow new ones or what
doesn't add more oil
I think he's
um
I think this one we'll need
that one worked
yes plop
[Music]
you send me more of those
okay look at this one
take
let me put this there again
you can't yeah
why do I get more scenes
I have French juice orange juice red
it's red I have red oh please send back
to me oh no keep it maybe
because you're the mixer you will need
that eventually I think
ah there it is ah keep keep the keep the
red juice for now
after that I'm I'm making wait do you
still need more of that one fruit
uh yeah if I use that fruit I can make
the red juice
but you already have Rancho so you don't
need any more right
oh but what if you need it to grow your
fruit
ah no it doesn't look like it I need
orange later orange no you need orange
my orange um
you know what
send it over can't uh can't be uh
harmful but I'll send you one more fruit
first
um okay copy that
go go yeah
take it
sending you the fruit right now uh
please send me my order as well thank
you
okay it's on the way
yes Ah that's so fast that if this is so
fast it means that we're really close to
another as as if I could not just walk
through that tunnel and see you
could definitely do that okay so I'm
making the next fruit for
the next potion the I'm gonna try to
make the white one
and for the white one I need a long
banana let's call it banana banana with
orange juice
I do have orange juice and the banana
okay um where did I plant well
I you have the orange juice
um but if you the banana we need the
green juice and the green juice is made
I think you have to send me green juice
in a bucket and I mix it with yellow
juice and then it makes green juice in a
mug oh okay okay okay
maybe this one
I'll send her a orange
thank you somethings
red juice is not red potion thank you uh
I don't think I need the orange bucket
yeah I just added some extra things
you
uh wait where did I put the banana did I
put the bananas somewhere which one is
the freaking banana
if I do this what is this for if you
can't place anything in here
oh I don't know what it's for oh well I
guess we'll figure it out later all
right so let's put the green juice with
the yellow juice
add some yellow juice
what am I getting from them where's the
banana Where's the banana
banana bananas bananas
okay we remember we planted the banana
here and it's not growing because it's
stupid what about the salad juice with
the green juice
well that was not in it okay I wasted I
um I wasted both of the red and the
yellow potion I'm sorry
uh that's okay I have a green I want it
I'm setting it okay I wanted to use use
it to grow my plants but it didn't work
okay I'm gonna send you another red
juice
oh okay
[Music]
that was my own walkie-talkie my own
walkie-talkie scared me
um
[Music]
well I can go on top of his platforming
oh yeah
all right your delivery's on the way man
I'm polka standby
okay thank you
so
you said green juice goes on banana
uh one second let me confirm uh yes that
is correct green juice on The Moldy
banana it has worked
I have the banana
now I'm gonna put banana an orange thing
okay I'll send you the banana and orange
juice do we already have the orange
juice
I got it you can send me okay colors
because once you send me a bucket I have
it for forever
ah okay and she wants the other colors
oh wait what am I supposed to be doing
with the banana what are we what am I
supposed to add the banana I think you
have to mix it with the orange juice
uh the orange bucket the orange bucket
[Music]
copy that
and I'll send you purple and the other
color as well
just for later
okay uh scratch that I do not get
forever
oh okay okay should I send you one more
orange as well because I just sent over
the other stuff
uh no that's all right I I have I have
it okay okay
wait why am I mixing the banana with the
orange uh because that makes a white
potion
and I need the white potion later to mix
it with a tentacle plant
to make green potion
oh okay
[Music]
this was this is way easier than the
stupid [\h__\h] we did before that
not that one all right your delivery's
on the way man thank you
I'll tip you later after the Stream
okay okay I got the white juice
um so next up
huh next I will make the I will make the
plants that are necessary for the blue
potion which is two blue plants one with
like a ball of tentacles and the other
one is a holy egg
that blue with some
shapes around the egg
I see it uh from it says on my recipe to
grow that one you just need the yellow
juice which I sent you a bunch of oh for
the for the holy blue holy egg I need
yellow juice
and the other one I already have it says
yellow mixed with the seed packet for
the egg where was the plant okay nice
because the other plant I already have
anyway okay I'll make that plant BRB
holy egg
that's not you
uh holy eagle
ah there it is okay uh let's plant it
here and put the yellow juice on it hey
oh my god it worked
I'm sending you holy egg and other thing
okay
please mix for next blue juice
uh sorry what am I mixing blue juice you
should get blue a blue potion out of
that
yeah but uh what what two things about
mixing up the things that I just sent
you those two only no juice extra
[Music]
I wanted pure I want the pure flesh from
those fruits
family of mine no no no I don't know any
toys blue books no no you need anything
else
ah oh yeah well I guess for the next
potion
um did this one work the blue one
yeah it's in the cart ready to go but
I'm just trying to see if you need
anything else oh I would need uh
a white white juice I have but I need
one more plant that I'm gonna make next
I don't know if it needs juice it looks
like the the takodachi I guess it's the
taco Dashi one
yeah I have that in my book
um it says purple juice for that one so
you should be covered
oh okay
wait hold on let me double check that
it's uh one second okay
okay that one goes there yeah purple
juice straight from the bucket worked
okay ah
bucket which one
uh what the hell the plant you're trying
to keep this one all right your delivery
has landed oh thank you I made the plant
successfully
it looks beautiful
hey okay I got this thank you so what am
I making next
let me check my recipe so we have we
have the
we have the white potion we have the
blue potion we also have the red potion
right
uh I think you have to send it all back
to me because I have a thing to mix it
all together like a oh yeah so that I
can put ah yeah I'll send you the white
juice and the the takodachi plant to
make green juice
[Music]
okay got it
um
okay the things that are arriving now
you have to mix that together
oh to make a green potion yeah that is
necessary for the green one
and then we have
blue
but we're missing red on it what did I
do
with the red potion
I only got that I only got that last
part
am I making juice or potion ah now
you're making potion uh green potion by
combining the takodashi with the white
potion
never made red I guess I didn't
and then we have to make the red one
again because that one was I think juice
but I need a potion
I guess I think we made the wrong thing
in the beginning
[Music]
yeah I have I have the the one in the
mug can we turn that into potion into
your place
uh uh well if you need red juice I just
need the pineapple mushroom okay
pineapple mushroom
this one I sent the green juice okay I
think you can probably keep that one
that all those juices but okay I'll take
it for now send it back I'll send you
back uh
um I like the the plant first and then
I'll send you the the the other potions
that I have because I think you have to
mix them into the black one
which one was it okay which one was it
a steak all that
and because they're all I took all the
fruit from that ones anyway
yeah the triple
do you need to you need the triple
eggplant too though right the mushroom
and eggplant
uh
unless you have a recipe that says I
need that uh to make
um
and my recipe says for the red one you
need the triple eggplant and the
mushroom pineapple
uh to make the red potion oh yes yes he
has the red potion
happy okay one second
um
[Music]
this one uh put that here but in order
to grow this this one grows put the
eggplant ah for that one I needed red
juice right wait uh let me ask for the
Triple eggplant which juice was
necessary again to grow in
red juice okay oh yeah that's what I
needed that for okay okay I'll send you
those two fruits
maybe they're vegetables
yeah probably
okay what I'm sending you now combined
will make a red potion
and with that
uh when you sent me back the Minecarts I
will send you the the blue and the green
potion and then you can mix the red blue
and green into a black one I think
that's it
copy that oh my God that ones are on the
way
oh I got it
why is that why is this one going so
much
uh okay
okay sanding blue and green
yo
might have time for one more riddle then
after this
I want to end at the latest in one hour
at the very latest
yeah this is like
this is more obvious I don't know it's
like way more obvious than the stupid
pipe thing you know
I mean the communication was very much
off anyway in the other room but it was
also just like I I think we both were
unsure what exactly we need to
communicate I mean I was trying to
communicate
until her all right I'm sending you the
death uh Ray okay
okay I think we're both lacking critical
information
oh my God uh
oh dear okay I'll kill the plant I guess
good luck die
it just it doesn't look very dangerous
but it did the trick
[Music]
that was so so anti-climatic what the
hell man oh my door opened again okay
I'm going to the dorm we can do one more
riddle I think
okay
okay this is where I'm supposed to go
is the door up there open now there was
a door up there I think or no
I I went to here that's not open
upstairs was this closed before
am I just going upstairs thank you guys
no no no I actually looked up how far we
are in the game and I know that there's
no freaking way that we'll clear it
today
uh
is this is this where I'm supposed to go
that's a long way
oh
God see
nice room looks cozy
oh I got caught we are nearing the end
my friend uh-huh I'm certain the final
piece and the way to create the song can
you not whisper into my left ear
Somewhere In This Very chamber I hate
that now hurry find It Go
so close so close
oh [\h__\h] what
crazy stranger as I'm like yeah what the
hell man
I cut scene over
nope
is she still watching
okay is my stream laggy right now
because of the loading I think hello
now did you also see the weird cutscene
uh it wasn't that weird I just have a
sword that's like rebuilding itself it
kind of looks like a diamond sword from
Minecraft
cool stuff I'm in a really messy room
right now
uh me too there's a ton of like uh
different things I'm gonna go ahead and
describe my room first and then you go
okay there's a bunch of paintings around
the room uh that are mixes of different
animals there's also let me see what
else I can interact with
uh there's uh paintings with patterns
[Music]
I have those things too
I also have uh this Jewel that I can
try to turn on but it does not turn on
and also I can remove the paintings on
the wall so maybe
oh okay
um
I
I cannot remove them
but I was able to move something on the
flower on the flower pattern
uh painting thingy
like a puzzle
okay you can move the flower paintings
yeah I'm going upstairs and upstairs I
have
I have a desk and I have a world so cute
uh
thing and I have more paintings I have
more of that uh flower pattern thing
that I can operate I have a little box
little chest treasure chest I can't
interact with most of these things
though I have a shelf
I have and not so much up here except
for that those paintings until
I found
the book and the book
I can't I can't inspect the book and it
shows me
uh the the
thing oh God okay sorry I'm I'm gonna
try to describe this it looks like
[Music]
um
looks like a clock but with no clock
inside but on top of it is a ball
okay I have something like that and I
have a book that like shows directions
for it but I don't really understand it
at the moment
um
we should uh try with the paintings like
uh try something with those
okay
I can't do anything with them though
uh describe like the general shape of
your room like on my room I have a
fireplace on the bottom floor do you
have that
yes I do
oh do you have a painting above the
fireplace
no I don't
oh okay oh I was able to take uh
I was able to take an item uh pick it up
from I picked it up from the chair next
to the fireplace it's a the sand clock
thingy that you can turn around
oh an hourglass yes yes
I can barely pick up anythings but yeah
actually
after I picked that thing up oh I
started getting
uh
like sparkly things
in some places
like
um
I can place the items that I picked up
only in those sparkly places
like it's telling me to place it there
but I have a bunch one two three
four five
six seven
eight nine ten eleven eleven
eleven I have 11 places where I can
place those tiny items
but I don't even have 11 items
um but anyway Let's uh you wanted to do
the
paintings right you were able to pick
them up
[Music]
so I also have a uh can candle thingy
that has one two three four it has uh
seven candles on it
and the candles on and on
I have them too but I cannot turn them
on or off
but which ones are on for you
[Music]
I can turn them on and off so maybe I
should match them with yours so starting
from left to right tell me if it's on a
run or one through seven
left to right okay my left to right is
are we looking at it from the same angle
though
uh
I'm looking at it towards the fireplace
like okay
it's behind it okay then from left to
right from that angle is the first one
is on the second one is off
the third one is on the fourth one is
off the fifth one is off the sixth one
sixth one is on and the last one is on
uh something happened I heard something
no I heard that too I've been hearing
some noises for a while now
it's kind of scary what the hell
uh
are you doing something with the with
the candles
uh yeah I I got it and I when I uh
reached what uh when I reached them like
all the correct thingies some something
I heard a sound of something like
my draw opened and there's a book inside
there
so I took that I took the book
yeah I got a book mine has the letter i
on it yeah I have the same one
okay so I guess that one is uh that
candle thing is done
okay
um how about let's try the paintings you
said you could do stuff with the
painting no I can't but you you're able
to move them around right
yeah
oh uh do you have any paintings like on
your staircase
yeah I got the okay staircase is
well one of them is the the one with the
movable flowers
and next to it above it is uh
an animal that is free animals one of
the animals is a a lion one of them is a
camel looking thingy one of them is a
bird that's eating its own tail and it's
got bird feed as well
okay uh can we start from the paintings
on the bottom of the staircase like what
is your painting on the bottom of the
staircase I have no painting
okay uh the second painting he said was
the flowers yeah the middle one is the
flower thing that you can move the third
one is uh that one that I just described
of the Lion's name like it has a snake
tongue and a bird that eats its own tail
and the Llama is like one animal that's
three animals
kimara
okay also for the flower paintings I
can't move those
yeah I can I can
okay so maybe maybe we have to uh do
something with those two if you can move
them but I can't
yeah okay
what does it look like on your side
it's difficult to describe though it's
just flowers one second
[Music]
uh okay you already described the flower
painting my circuit yeah if you want to
do that one first yeah
um
I can turn four pieces it's like divided
by four
oh okay so on the bottom there's like a
rose bush it connects like a rose bush
uh on the very bottom gross
does she mean that that's not really
roses though
uh wait which one does she mean
I don't see any roses
uh
uh on on the bottom row you see a rose
bush
yeah so on the very bottom like touching
the frame of the painting is a rose bush
and then
uh sorry sorry on on the left side right
the left piece or the right one as well
uh both the bottom pieces on the inside
corners on the bottom it's a rose bush
on the outside corners on the bottom
it's um sunflower
ah okay yes okay I have that aligned and
about the top one
at the top the top
um okay for the top row the bottom
corners of the top row are both
sunflowers
a bottom bottom middle or bottom right
bottom edges
a bottom bottom middle
ah okay then
in theory that should be correct
I think but there's more I have more of
those paintings
I have one that's upstairs
um if you go upstairs and then go right
do you have it there as well
yeah
um I have one above a chest and the
candles yeah yeah I have that one too it
has a little bit of a different flower
pattern
this one is really difficult to describe
I think
two in the outside corners is a plow
three petals only
uh I I didn't get the first part of the
sentence because I was also talking can
you repeat please
on the bottom row on the outside corners
on each of the outside quarters for the
bottom row is a flower with three red
petals
three red petals
this one
my dental isn't correct I think I think
I got it can you do the top row
is that cool all right the top row is
the same thing but flipped so for the
top row the top outside corners are both
um the three red petal flower
uh
no
and now it's
wait I got the wrong one here
oh well so doesn't mean it just becomes
one perfectly aligned picture
for this one yes yeah I'll put this one
true yeah the other one didn't okay
let's go downstairs
okay the one next to the clock
okay for the bottom row the inside
bottom corners for the bottom row is
like one big petal
one big without uh hold on this is
confusing because there's another one
that's kind of a one big pedal hold on
yeah
these two well there's one that's bigger
than the other
okay
um on the bottom row the top inside
Corners which connect to the middle are
the ones which look like a bird's feet
[Music]
which one will look like bird feet
you mean several bird feet
yeah okay so the big one they'll be
yeah okay yeah I think I got that one so
that means
the middle bottom is a somewhat big
petal with two green leaves sticking out
yes okay okay now we've got that one uh
top row
on the top row the bird feet flower is
both of the bird feet flowers are on the
outside top corners
[Music]
um but the other ones didn't open up
does that mean we have them incorrectly
but I got a book out of that
maybe if we get all of them right that's
the one that's supposed to open ah okay
okay then uh I guess okay next thing we
can do the the one with the clock that
has a book inside too the one it has a
book that says p
the clock it's not really a clock it's
like a
Circle tank and a and a
um ball on top of it that's like purple
blue color
what it's on the first floor behind the
behind the um candles
yeah I see the orb huh yeah yeah the orb
one so for that I have a book that uh
says
it shows me some some crystals and it
says no touchy touchy
put it on the next page it says if you
do touch Itachi then the orb uh lights
up and then the crystal also lights up
and that will make something out of the
uh uh Circle orb thingy pop out
[Music]
sorry for that amazingly easy
explanation
I have the same book and um oh I think
it has the same diagram
but I don't really understand it well
did we see those Crystal fingers around
in the room
yeah there's about four or five of them
there's one on the top floor there's one
in the bottom towards the door
there's one by the
paintings
that I don't think I have them
okay uh how about we do the how about we
do the paintings um the animal page oh
okay okay okay
um should we start at all the staircase
yeah I got the uh I got the I think I
have the okay yeah just yeah let's start
the staircase okay
um next to the flower painting that we
aligned
um diagonally
above it right above it like right side
above it but not directly above it
diagonally above it
uh is the one that I described before
this it's a chimera that it has a bird
eating its tail and a little camel
thingy and a lion with a snake uh tongue
and Bird's feet they're standing on it's
one animal standing on bird feet
uh with a bird
with a beak eating its own neck which is
the tail of the animal
uh okay got it now the one next to it
okay next to it that is where the
staircase is already ending and you're
on the second floor the the first
footstep
uh so that is an animal that's a bunny
with angel wings White Wings bunny feet
and a bird that eats its own tail again
with the tail being the neck as well at
the same time
foreign
Birds angel wings bird feet bird eating
neck
does it have a snail shell on its head
no snail shell only bunny ears pickle
[Music]
where's what the hell
am I being weird oh I've got another
item
am I being rude then I will apologize
was I rude to her
I don't want to be rude to her
why do I need a Snickers
was I rude to you guys
when was I was it
nah okay okay
all right uh let's go to the flower
um that's above the chest and the top
floor they're painting to the left of it
yes it is the same thing but with a
snail shell
okay
I'm fine okay
for enjoying your descriptions nice
they look they look very cute
that's what I like the most Maybe
look at those PN eyes you say PN
pin
the stupid clock freaks me out man
it's a nice room though I would I
wouldn't mind like living in here
I have one more one more painting on
that floor
oh she talked sorry I have one more
painting on that floor
okay uh it's next to the Bookshelf
on on and next to the other one other
bunny that was without a snail shell
and so the position you got it
uh yes okay so there we have
um it has a snail shell it has long bird
feet and it is just a bird in general
with PN eyes
next painting oh you got this one
yeah let's go oh a painting to the left
of the stairs when you're on the first
floor
ah
left of the stairs do you mean like in
front of the windows
yeah yeah okay it's the same thing but
with two beaks
the painting looks like any other
paintings but like above the fireplace
ah I have one painting that's really
weird it's above it's next to the door
the entrance door it's just a dude and
it says nepias
I think that's the last one
uh where next to the entrance Door uh to
the left side of it or like looking from
yeah well there's an empty space
probably for you next to the entrance
Door
I got it I got one more I guess above
the fireplace oh no above the fireplace
I have no painting
okay wherever your next painting is then
[Music]
um
ah sorry uh there's one more
um on the floor next in front of the
window
it's really dark
[Music]
it's with a snail shell and I can barely
see it it's really dark but it's like a
uh
[Music]
oh wait that worked something opened
what opened
do you know where it opened
no I don't know
it made a noise somewhere somewhere is
another book
is there okay ah okay I found it
all right
um
yeah then shall we now do the the last
thing the I think it's the last thing
I don't see any other books here
go to the clock
oh there's another book here yeah yeah
okay
foreign
to the right side of the clock
um do you see like something that you
could move or something like that
ah
yes I see some buttons
when I move the buttons the
um
the thingy the the thing comes out of
the clock
okay so on my clock I have a three big
circles with a different amount of like
uh strikes on it so I can tell you the
numbers so like for the first one it's
four
uh as if it were 9 10 11 12 1.
okay that made the pp keep up thing come
out
uh so I have four strikes where it would
be like 10
11 and one on the clock
what
sorry is that on the is that on wait you
said you had three
free knobs
but yeah there are three knobs on the
clock and then on the very top one
there's four strikes which are in the 10
11 12 and one spots as if the circle of
the top knob was a clock
how many do you have on the other two
[Music]
uh six on the bottom which are in from
places uh eight two if it's a four
o'clock
[Music]
six on the bottom
and on the third one
uh three as if it were 11 12 1.
okay okay okay
when I moved them uh the time actually
[Music]
oh
the one on in the middle makes the time
uh the seconds go faster
yeah the time goes faster
is there anything
sorry sorry can you say that again
is there anything on the very bottom
uh it's like a reset button
I think let me test it out
oh
I can't post it anymore
I pressed it once and oh oh you press it
too
no I can't press it I can only look at
it
uh one after I press it once
something slightly moves and then I
can't
and I can't immediately press it again
but I think if I I think it's supposed
to like at the end um uh open up the
the door for the book
yes I guess we just have to get it
correctly
[Music]
okay
oh okay okay uh sorry I kind of
I really uh don't wanna interrupt right
now but I really need to go to an island
meeting
oh okay okay I'll be fast I'll be fast I
promise sorry
[Music]
foreign
I don't know
[Music]
foreign
okay
Daddy I'm back
no problem
okay okay where were we uh clock
yeah so I figured out I figured out
where I went wrong so on the second knob
uh it's actually uh six marks from nine
to two
okay uh when can you can't move them can
you
nah they just have the marks that I just
read off to you when I move mine
does anything change at you please
no probably not till you press the
button at the end and we got it right
oh okay okay
uh
oh wait
[Music]
um
what does that change
this one changed the speed
[Music]
this one changes the
just what makes the top one come out
[Music]
what's this one do
I'm trying to figure out what each knob
does my middle one changes the the speed
of the
the clock I guess
the lower the lowest one makes the
um birds at the top come out
I'm not sure what the top one does
though
I don't think it matters what they do as
long as we have the like the marks I
have as long as I give them to you
correctly
okay okay
uh okay so I'll read them off again from
the top on the very okay
there's um four marks in the 10 11 12
and one spot yes
okay and then in the second one there's
six marks in the nine ten eleven twelve
one two spot
okay
and then in the last one there's three
marks in the eleven twelve and one spots
[Music]
um okay
press the button
wait wait wait yeah
huh wait did I do it wrong
look at the three ways to do something
else
ah
wait I'm not sure if I did something
wrong one second uh
wait does that change the ways
I think it does
not sure
slightly
[Music]
ah
I have a
lot of our dials
at the top
one two three four five
one two three four five six at the
middle one and three dials
in the uh Below in the lowest one
um
it changes
the sound of the
clock
no one of them
oh maybe we're just supposed to get it
to the right time
oh
[Music]
what is the right time the time doesn't
change at the top it always stays the
same
oh
it only changes the
um the big circle thing in the middle
that goes from left to right
does that one move for you
uh it looks like it's just moving
normally on my side
what's normally
I see I can make that go faster but when
I do that on my side does it make it
faster on your side as well
no
okay can you exactly this is a rhythm
game maybe can you exactly tell me at
what Rhythm like just uh imitate it
[Music]
one two one two one two one two okay I
got that one I got that one I think
uh
do you have ways behind that
like behind that clock that's moving
[Music]
oh
what
[Music]
um behind the clock that we just like
the um adjusted the ribbon
what is that called pendulum chimes
Chimes yeah
um in what position are those is that
the left one higher than the middle one
or something like that
okay uh hold on let me find it let me
think of a good way to describe it one
second
because I can change the position of
those
pretty greatly middle okay so the uh our
right one is higher than the middle and
the left one but the left one is higher
than the middle
okay then I think I got that one too
um
one does the the lowest knob makes the
bird come out right but I have three of
different sounds so when your bird comes
out what sound does it make
okay
[Music]
sounds
excited I had to freed up on sounds they
are different but they are very similar
so you cook
um
sounds like all of them
[Music]
oh my dude they look different too what
does it look like yours
uh it's a jester
what's I think all of my free are
gestures but they have different poses
one has the arms like asserting
dominance one has them on the bench it's
sitting on
and
wait do that again uh the one and mine
is sitting
okay
almost sitting what is the middle one
let's do something else okay then it's
the last one
okay okay testing
[Music]
oh my God
nice work oh my God
I like that one that one's nice
I am motivated
and did you get the book
yeah I got it
okay then I think now it's really only
the
the orb thingy left
ah so I was thinking of the orb is is
your uh round orb glowing no no
is anything glowing for you yeah oh now
the orb is glowing
that's it now it's not glowing anymore
I said oh actually never mind that's
probably not the last one I still have
items that I have to place everywhere
but we can do the orb thingy now it's
glowing glowing glowing
it's also glowing now now it's not
glowing
one second okay
okay so when it's going then I'll touch
I'll touch one
okay okay
I keep telling you it's not glowing
still not glowing
[Music]
here's my stuff
what is
wait how does that help
[Music]
something just moved
I think
it's going it's going it's going fast
fast glow well
something came out of it something came
out of the some um
um knob came out of the thing
okay still like
it's not glowing but I think the first
thing you did was correct now it's
glowing
uh but honestly I know now the first
thing is went back in
the bolts the I have like I have uh I
think five bolts
that can came out of Cam can't come out
of it
the first one went back inside though
yeah I have the same orb and I see it
pop out I just need to know when it's
like actually going because then I press
the thingy okay
the glowing
[Music]
it's it was glowing very softly now it's
blowing very fast and very brightly
but the knob is not coming out I just
hear a lot of noises I think that you're
activating them now it's blowing fast
fast going
slow glowing
fast flowing very fast slow glowing
the channel the items are real I think
I don't know I don't
that one is with the bull guy thing
[Music]
it's fast not glowing was just glowing
fast blowing fast flowing
oh knob came out so I think fast flowing
is better than slow glowing
yeah so when I get closer to like
different crystals around the area for
me it's either fast or slow and I guess
the fastest one is the one I should
attach to tell me whenever it's going
fast okay okay it's not going now
a slow glowing slow slow fast
yes snob came out yes yes yes
okay
well slow glowing slow fast fast fast
yeah fast fast fast yes snap came out
number three fast glowing fast glowing
fast glowing fast loan yes number four
you got it you got it on me good job
what a detective Sasuke
are they are books fell
oh they spell something
but I still have something on it I still
have a lot of objects I think I have to
place them around the room because I
have the glowing spots
all over the room
okay
X
sorry can you say that again
what are the objects oh I have um I'm
not sure if I have all of them but I
have
um
um a a cube I have a sand an hour sand
clock thingy
like oh
okay the cube place it next to the uh
orb machine word machine Rhino left
uh right
okay one second guys guys what do I call
this thing again in English
well they call that okay I have a
I also have the the a globe a globe
okay let's do the uh hourglass I want
you on the desk uh on the bottom floor
across from the fireplace with the scale
on it and place it on the right corner
okay
done uh now I have I have the cube and I
have a box that's open with a key
need more items okay the Box place it on
the fireplace mantle on the right side
okay okay
wait that box you place you said it's
open it has like turning knob thingy it
has a key inside and yeah on this on the
right side it's a turning thingy yes
it's not a record player
oh wait maybe it is
is that a record ah wait is that a key I
guess it's yeah that's probably a record
players it's a music box yeah
okay so what is it that you have left uh
a globe a standing Globe not the one
that's next to the desk
um in the ground floor that's a
different globe
but does it look like it it looks very
similar but it has like a longer like a
single singular foot to stand on
because the other the other Globes have
like four to five uh legs to stand on
it's like a mini globe
on the top floor on the second floor
um on the bookshelf put it on the second
bookshelf on the left side on the inside
corner this one
I had to open up something
there's a chest behind you
daddy
find me
on the second floor
chest
wait sorry where did you find that one
uh on the staircase
um on the second floor there's a chest
underneath the flower painting
ah here okay okay got it
so
is there another rainbow noise down in
it I think that's it
why don't we do with these books
I don't know place them on the bookshelf
or I don't think so I can't I don't have
like an option to place them anywhere
like put them down
[Music]
let's try to find
some spot where it can be inserted or so
I mean it must be somewhere
must be somewhere
look at the letters uh
n s p e oh is that is that code one more
chest that looks like it can be opened I
don't know if you see it it's next to a
broken door to the left of it uh by the
clock
oh
uh if you mean the same chest I cannot
open that one can you
uh no but okay I found the place to put
the books uh next to the fireplace
there's a little bookshelf underneath a
small painting
ah okay
[Music]
wait I'm showing I'm sure we're supposed
to spell out something and that's
probably somewhere in the room hidden is
it near us
nah what yeah okay you know that that
weird painting we put next to the door
that has some graffiti on it it says
n-e-p-i-a-s and that's exactly the
letters that we have
ah good point but my on the top row it
says ESP so maybe we connect it like
your top row goes in front of my top row
or something
oh oh
okay never mind I'll just I'll just
place it what my painting says okay okay
I heard said something else I thought it
says the same thing
oh I got mine
we're going through here next
Galaxy
that was weird that the letter is they
look familiar to me
because I have the exact same letter uh
maybe we should swap our words
okay uh like you mean I spelled the
thing out that you have over there or
uh yeah I'll read it out to you
um on my painting it says ESP
oh wait I A N
e
s
p
dot e s p or t
you have a t i I don't
now I was wondering if you have the same
books now but okay so e-s-p-i-a
yes e-s-p-i-a-n
okay I I didn't sell
it was
uh okay for you it's n-e-p
-i-a-s
-n-e-p-i-a-s near pias
foreign
[Music]
yeah but uh I don't know if it'll save
here
wait at least go okay just go into the
door
yes yes I am inside
um
well even if it doesn't save I think
if we don't play it like five months
later we can kind of remember what we
did
oh yeah yeah it'll be we'll speed run it
the next time
ah okay
wait right right soon does that get me
to the next uh level wait but that door
is closed
okay well then
uh I guess that's it for today
yeah
that was um I think in the beginning we
had to warm up our brains that was why
that was so frustrating
yeah I think so too and let's turn on
Discord instead of this crappy wonky
talking
watch that over
I still have a push to talk in Discord
as well though because we wanted to be
push to talk and Discord first but then
it actually worked today in the game it
didn't last time
I great detective work yo thank you you
did a really good job too I think with
our communication skills are pretty uh
on point I was amazed by you know doing
the the ladder thingy because I I was
basically doing nothing while I was on
the ladder it was all you
oh yeah I just needed the directions
yeah I could like visualize it in my
head based off of what you told me
though
yeah that was that was fun my least
favorite one was the freaking tubes
pipes thing
yeah
I think of like a
probably if we were swapped I probably
would have missed the pressure meter too
[Music]
uh as a game changer once we found out
the pressure thing I also I think it was
confusing because you were already able
to go to the like other riddles that
came after that even though I was stuck
in that room and I only had the the gas
but you were able to see other things
like that is so confusing you won't know
like what to start with what what
matters and what doesn't matter
yelling at me they're like no I mean do
that later
yeah but can't blame you if I were in
that position I would probably try to
figure out maybe the other things matter
as well I don't know oh yeah so we we
both had our uh
moments I think but
all in all we both tried our best so
what the heck yeah I think we did a good
job you know once we got the ball
rolling our brains were like firing away
no no the last room with all the small
Windows was good I think because they
were not too too complicated
yeah yeah
[Music]
do you have any advice for the
convention you were there yesterday I'm
gonna be there in like half an hour
yes
um you know wants to do wave so you know
just make it happen wait did you get one
no no no no no I'll do it again I did it
last time I'll do it again I'm excited
yeah I just I I feel like it's it's kind
of difficult for me to ask the audience
like all right guys everybody we're
gonna stand up now even though you were
waiting outside for three hours you know
what wait that's fun they love food kind
of stuff
and it's hard for me to Hype them up I
think you definitely do it better
um okay I'll do my best
and what what kind of what kind of
questions did you get this time oh it's
kind of cool because like uh they asked
uh me and Inna both questions at the
same time so we could like answer
questions about each other and stuff
like that so I think it'll be cool
but questions about each other you don't
mean like couple questions like what
what kind of uh juice does the other
person like to drink the most no no not
like that just like uh oh like uh how
did your initial impression of them
change you know from now until then that
sort of thing oh
this last in the last convention where
both both of us were we were separately
alone on one day and then at this
convention yesterday was you and Ina and
today is me and you know so it's it's
cool that they ask like questions for
both of us that's nice of them yeah yeah
cool so maybe I get some taco taco
questions
employee like last time what the same
no I'm just saying I hope there's a KFC
I
think they're there they might be there
on the cover they might try to hide
their chicken feathers because it's a
bit a bit like you know you stand out in
the public
yeah but I thought yesterday
oh my I saw what you did with photoshop
on Twitter and put you put like yourself
in Cosplay there it's so cute
oh yeah there was like a and there's
like an empty space there you know it
felt like unbalanced without you okay
ah man you looked so good with orange
hair and and uh you also put in some
highlights in your hair and all that it
looks so good oh thank you
it looks like you oh
man
Charming you are very Charming
oh well I I hope I hope uh I can
um make a good impression on everyone
today yeah it's gonna be fun you know I
think you're really good at hyping up a
grass yeah it's gonna go great
you're very good at that too though
you know that
[Music]
you are yes you are
yeah very much so I'll take it oh thank
you
also you are at all like we have this
tour of five conventions right and
you're at all of them
yeah yeah I wanted to do all of them
because uh I don't know it's fun
now I kind of low-key I low-key regret
not selecting all of them like you but
at the same time I felt like it's gonna
be too stressful and honestly it already
is so
yeah especially because like uh well we
had a break between this one and the
first one but like the already the next
convention is like this coming weekend
but then after that there's like a month
break I think because it's like October
yeah but the next one is next weekend on
our anniversary so yeah
wait am I on that one I don't even I'm
not even sure
I don't think so I think I think it's
Cali and
maybe okay yeah that's probably why I
don't have it in my calendar oh okay
that's good then because I'm busy with
other stuff like that lower eyes
releasing let's go oh yeah I've been
waiting for that for ages is there any
game that you're waiting for at the
moment to release oh this month I think
it's this month it's a DLC for uh outer
Wilds which is a
space game I think I saw Anya playing
that today yeah yeah she she's I think
she's on like part eight or nine we've
been playing it for a while now it's
really fun did you play it already on
your Channel
yeah I beat it whoa you're gonna play
the DLC too
yeah I'm gonna play it like uh like one
week after it comes out because then the
chat will be like
and I can't watch um
yeah but you know what if you you
um you should you don't like backseaters
do you if you play it one way and then
they'll tell you how to play it you
should play it on the first yeah so they
don't know how to play
that's true I guess I could always watch
it later after they play it yeah yeah
yeah I I'm always like if there's a game
coming out that I was waiting for I I
would not be able to wait a whole week
to play it never
oh yeah some people spoil it that's a
good point yeah but anyway however you
want to do it you do you
um I'm gonna check it out too because it
sounds interesting very interesting
okay
uh because it's like a puzzle
exploration game and you have to like
put all of this together and you also
get to fly a spaceship and yeah I like
the spaceship idea but I don't like the
puzzles about that
yeah it's pretty it's a pretty big brain
game is it as big brain as this game
um
I wouldn't say the puzzles are his big
brain but just like the whole mystery
and stuff like just solving it because
you kind of like have to solve a mystery
so yeah I would say this oh okay you
could do it it's a lot of reading I like
reading
wait my chat's gonna say okay you can
read what
they did that before and I sent them to
the usual room so they better oh they're
Xing they're asking gotta punish them I
will you guys I'm writing down all of
your names all of you every single one
of you
rude oh my God is your chat ever like
doubting what you say as well oh all the
time yeah they're always like I mean
you're wrong I mean you're wrong and
sometimes I'm wrong but most of the time
I'm right and then I get to rub it in
their faces but dude that's nice but do
they doubt like your skills like when
you say I can do this and that like I
can go I can jump from a 20 meter uh you
know those those jumpings things in
swimming pools
oh yeah yeah probably yeah would they
doubt you if you say that
yeah they'd be like uh but you you would
be the best in that ground pounding the
water
oh yeah I've seen like a video like that
where it's like super high up and it's
like a challenge like to jump I wouldn't
I wouldn't I would do it but I
definitely hesitate because I kind of
like that feeling of like oh God am I
gonna do this I don't know really does
your butt ever hurt from ground pounding
um yeah yeah sometimes my tailbone
because like you know when I sit on it
weird yeah yeah yeah
yeah that happens yeah when I when I sit
in front of the PC for hours and hours
my butt will start hurting just from
sitting so I can't imagine how much it
must hurt from ground pounding so much
oh that reminds me that reminds me I
have to say it was not on purpose to
have my mom come to the Minecraft server
when you were on vacation that was not
on purpose
yeah I saw somebody was like um maybe
she's trying to avoid Amish
I love that logic that's Furious but no
actually she's coming back to the
Minecraft server next week and that'll
probably be the last time but we'll be
like building for probably like five to
six hours or so so you could you could
come by if you're awake you can't say
hello to my mom she's a bit scared of me
I'm gonna stop by I'll stop by okay what
charmer you know you definitely are but
she thought that maybe you're ground
pounding uh thing is serious and should
be taken seriously and I told him no no
no no it's just jokes don't worry about
that I wouldn't do that I'm very
respectful
yes I believe that
I believe in you amik
yeah that's one of those things chat is
like
again again here they go again
I think my mom wants to meet you she
just doesn't she's a little bit of a
Cinderella maybe she doesn't admit it
but she I'm sure she will be happy to me
she was very shy when gouda and Ina
suddenly showed up
um yeah but then afterwards she said she
was really happy and the girls were
really sweet so I think she would be
happy to meet you
she met Kelly already no no Cali was not
around either so I think yeah it was a
shitty time for her I think
yeah I thought maybe next time
sure oh you don't force yourself I think
it's gonna be a shitty time for you too
I'm awake at weird times okay that is
true all right um I'll get ready for the
convention and I'll talk to you soon and
we'll plan out the next session of this
stupid puzzle game
okay well yeah we're gonna beat it for
sure yes next time we'll be to um maybe
schedule some more time today we didn't
have so much time excuse me
we probably only have like two hours
left a bit
hope hopefully yes hopefully not so much
yes
yeah so what do you always say at the
end of your stream
no no no I mean yeah
um bye-bye wow
right
you know now you have a good opportunity
to come up with one because you know
it's gonna be a one year anniversary
Now's the Time to make up new things
yeah
I was trying to say I was trying to get
Aya like saying Aya so I was like saying
ayasami
I I
oh
I I asked me oh yeah
hmm
okay
[Laughter]
I think I think yeah has has potential
oh thank you thank you yeah all right uh
then you say I asked me and I say
I'll be dancing guys and in Germany
tomorrow in a mongoose and an archived
karaoke stream
I'm nodding but I won't be there but
have fun I'll go take care of these
shoes so you're doing like a German
anime yeah you're singing a lot of
German karaoke songs like there's
there's some um animes that were on
German TV with German openings so I'm
singing a bunch of those like Digimon
and Pokemon and
don't remain all that kind of stuff but
I'm also gonna be singing anime songs
who didn't get an official uh adaption
of German opening which is the fan made
one so I'll mix it up
ah that sounds really fun yeah so maybe
you can check it out if you have them I
I really like the color your your
rendition of Sparks
uh
disclaimer please do not start a fire
today uh at least not without me being
there okay
yeah mini print supervision yes yes I
will be the supervisor so I asked me I
asked me goodbye everybody thank you for
watching
see you next time
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]