[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
one hello
yay y
[Music]
y why do you guys have
clothes I'm so I got coins why not
sleepy yeah you get like 150 coins in
the beginning and one shirt costs 50
coins it's so expensive I have to
well the that's nothing look at the
other prices those are way more crazy
this is the cheapest
shirt you get like a little fart
emoj oh yeah it's so usess I'm gonna
click on okay well uh is it everyone's
first time playing the game
yeah yes can we introduce
ourselves no
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
from the player
order okay we can we can introduce
ourselves while doing the volume check
then yeah right right right
okay I'm not a cat I'm P
hello hello
yeah
sounds
good next one the one who says sounds
[Music]
good thanks for having
me did you just wake up oh no I'm just
sick she's sick
she she sounds a little bit like money
[Music]
oh my God sounds like okay and next uh
uh my lovely this running
bird which one uh
W yeah why why do you need to think so
long about that cuz you both are running
I was
choosing okay hi
k um I'm the kiaha I uh love ID girls
and I love Amed so this is like the best
party ever let's go let's
go oh my God you are
loud let's
[Music]
go next the one this yellow
bird yellow yellow bird yellow
bir um how to how to
introdu my soul there you go
introduction da
okay good good day man my name is
k from H third generation D my
soulong have you had brecky yet bre Brey
bre nice
Brey brecky done okay next uh Amy let's
go hello
[Music]
[Applause]
Watson we have a
detective we have ative and we have a
secret agent very nice
I'm I'm barely a secret agent
you barely the misunderstanding of why
am is here oh oh oh should we should we
talk about
it wait can can we talk about it yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah I I I reacted with an
emoji to the in of this because I was
like oh shoot that sounds like a cool
game so I put a little POG a little C
POG and I wasn't expecting to join but
I'm here and I'm happy to be here anyway
we're happy that you're here we're happy
that you're
[Music]
here didn't sign up but she's still here
even though she didn't sign
up she didn't sign up for this it was
really funny marer yeah it was really
funny cuz I was like uh react if you
want join and I was like I'm imp POG so
I was like let's
go
yeah okay uh
this re I'm H Ru
[Applause]
[Music]
yay next last but not least is our
sweepy sleepy
bird sleepy
bird oh did you just forget about
mea oh
[Music]
my sorry even I thought you did
Inu I'm
sorry attention please thank you for
your
[Laughter]
[Music]
attention okay now the real last but not
least
Ana hello it's Ana from Hol Live
ID
second um how do you change your color
can you change your I think we need to
change it
the oh no yeah yeah yeah you look good
perfect you look good yeah okay yeah it
looks it looks good okay
yeah you're good
okay okay since we don't have much time
I'm thinking we can do um two maybe one
uh one to two classic games yeah one to
two classic
games and then we can try other stuff
like um the hide and seek or The Killing
Spree one I think oo okay yeah there's
many
sounds good Sensei yes is this um is
this game like a certain impostor game
disc call oh yeah yeah something similar
but
duck and Goose quack yes wait which one
which one is the Imposter the duck or
the goose the duck the goose is the okay
the goose is the crew mate yeah okay
okay sorry uh I haven't very I think I
haven't played
either in the
title I haven't played either so yeah I
haven't played either I couldn't up my
alarm oops also this is also going to be
my
first sorry just in case I overslept
um yeah okay let's play I think it's
everyone's first time playing anyway so
let's
play
what go wrong okay three two
one it's
starting I'm a
lover okay what happens if I die
though
uhing uh the tutorial is really nice it
tells you what to do
guys pardon excuse
me
oh please do not kill
[Music]
meain I have so many
Engles
where oh
this I have so many booger on
me
what oh let's right
[Music]
here polish armor I think the armor was
somewhere
nearby
this yeah here it is I found
you it's getting
clean okay what it's spild doal like
actually I need the
gws or just for
prin there some more painting
again again
why wh why is the BTM like this it's
full of
suspense get
a get a
book I Amelia
Senai I bet you're the
impostor uh if I was how would I
tag oh you you'd press space I think
think I don't think I'm the impostor
oh but what if you're the impostor this
is a psychological
warfare what if I'm not
though hi hi hi
Ollie you're an impostor you're a D Duck
quack quack quack quack quack quack
quack
run so
ominous why do I need to keep
reassembling why do I have so many
duties it doesn't make sense yeah the
third when is it
ending stop
it huh I keep reassembling
[Music]
we were
lovers we were lovers was no one was no
one we were lovers okay okay we need the
wait did no one kill yet no one was just
trying to see what
yeah okay okay it's it's okay I think we
can make the task
longer task
longer I was looking for dead bodies
because I was the vulture I'm supposed
to eat dead bodies but there were no
dead my God what the heck so it's
four we do have it's four vers
four and
no like two ducks and then two two other
people on the duck
side wait was there four people I think
the roll for the uh um the duck side is
only two so oh wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait yeah only two only
two
a I I was I was a vulture which is not
the
duck wait who's the duck you're not a
duck but a duck is a are you guys
supposed to help the Ducks no
no no the vulture is kind of doing their
own thing they just they don't don't
even have to do task but they also don't
kill they just eat corpses and if they
get they're just in for the they're just
in for the win yeah just for the food
yeah just I mean dodo as well it's like
Jester if they get folded out they they
win alone yeah I thought that was
supposed to be like know the um cuz when
you're a duck you get these like unlock
this and that like sabotage unlock blah
blah blah do I but yeah I've been trying
to work that out but but I didn't get it
yeah you have to kill someone if you
want to
sabotage oh so it's
like okay I will bring Al sen P I was
searching for you we were
lovers oh you know you know what's crazy
the lovers role they didn't tell us who
the who the other partner is yeah yeah
so we have to look by ourselves is is is
it out where's my
lover
my one
more um my task I I I set the task list
to be larger so I think it should be
fine can everyone let's go press ready
ready up please
ready okay again let's
[Music]
go wow I can kill people
hi
hi not too close
please are you my lover you got another
lover get a PL oh I'll get the plunder
[Music]
from hi I bet W was something
here I am something but uh I think it's
a good
thing suspicious everyone is something
actually
right yeah maybe yeah I
something where are the
tasks din
oh was pouring tea what hello no no no
we were at the dinner table and we
didn't know that it means like
emergency
[Music]
okay okay
okay wait we can't skip we have to
vote okay literally skip ad moment okay
oh now we can't skip
ad the duck are
voting the duck
what what does that mean what does that
mean I don't know what that means
everyone is safe for now everyone
is oh the arrows are so
weird Al we can go to the dining
[Music]
room I well I mean I don't want how do
we
eat how do we eat the food I'm I'm so
scared sorry wait wait wait wait that's
the dinner bell oh I'm so sorry which
one is the
oh why are there and
you yum
yum collect the dishes how do we collect
the dishes though
oh here
why is it so hard to get the
dishes don't kill
me
oh guys guys guys
yeah
huh I didn't see
Ollie
yeah yeah you and Ollie went upstairs
right I went right and then I saw it
upstairs not upstairs beside it oh
IES Ella was with me okay so this is wa
where wait wait where were you can you
self report in this game yeah I don't
know I I think wait I it's
either Ollie and
Kyla H but it wasn't Kyla because she
just got into the
[Music]
room but I don't
but V how do you just pressed the name I
I think I just what what yeah I think I
press the
name oh my
God
who I think we don't know what we're
doing yeah say I think it we just need
to click
right H
suspicious supicious but time to collect
the dishes
again collecting oh it's a lot easier
now yeah what
happened okay let's wash the
dishes where do we wash the
dishes thees saing raining ooh hello a
lot of people here but it's okay could
be self report but if you keep it's okay
you can just keep going with raining so
if you die yeah okay okay okay okay yeah
we can separate but no don't
please only do you want to go with me oh
sure ah I'll protect you I look very S I
don't like this we can go we can go 3x3
or something yeah yeah 3x3 sounds safe
yeah or five by four to you Y where do
you guys got to go I don't
know oh unclock the
toilet
wait
yeah how do you
unclock I didn't
click click it I did
it wait what is
rainy hello you're good right
rain is going with Zeta right I I don't
know Ella if what I need to tell you
something what I'm a
sheriff then you can't K me right yeah
but a sheriff is not a duck I killed I
think from enemies to love you can kill
anyone right if you're why are you guys
always together you screaming that I can
kill
anyone you can kill anyone
just kill all of
us of us kill me kill me kill me kill me
kill anyone right no I'm a Sher I I only
I only kill
Ducks I think it's KY she keeps susing
everyone then can I kill KY yeah just
kill me okay everybody make some don't
don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't don't yes no
no witnessing yes and no yeah and
then I'm out of here I don't want to
take my
chances that's incredibly
suspicious
oh
um no one trust me I I trusted you I
said I said don't kill no one trust me
before she selfreported
I was staying ly the entire time
wait wa did you actually report or
because I was Canadian so like I self I
didn't report it's Auto
report don't kill the Canadian killed
the
Canadian I literally said that I saw wa
and rainy together before that happened
and but no one
Tri we didn't
hear I don't remember you saying it
yeah so wa I who was who who was the who
was the who got the L roll oh yeah I no
not me what the was it was it you no I'm
I'm lovers with you
oh spicy so we got it correct spicy oh
my sorry my alarm keeps ringing on okay
so turn it up girl turns out this is aot
faster than the other I'm trying I have
an larm I said an alarm every 5 minutes
uh I'll turn it off okay so are we ready
do you how about we switch it up with
different rules yeah
okay let's
see R grind Gamers I
think uh I think I think I
think we can do assassin so basically
it's uh you can kill during meetings by
correctly guessing a role or die
trying
your
yeah during meetings Okay M let's go
let's go let's go let
[Music]
go one one you scare me
womaning a I'm ready how that work
uh okay let's go save save
save
let's go I'm a
medum Okay cool so I would know who
died sounds like me
P oh my God you have p t too I'm also
pouring tea it's over
here yeah guys it's the anniversary of
royalty so we're pouring tea we're doing
pour pouring tea uh there's going to be
a special stream on Friday so be sure to
join the royalty when you
[Music]
can hi
Anya how would I know if people died
anyways
huh
huh oh why do I need fingerprints oh I
can look from right I forgot I had that
feature that would make things a lot
[Music]
easier there we go
and then we can just go to the
[Music]
kitchen
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
us might be
self-report no no no can can can you
explain the body where was the
body uh the body is in the laboratory in
the top
right
laat well me me and Ella we were we were
in the kitchen I'm in the kitchen I'm
trying to
find we were in The West Wing
yeah I think we can it was me SK it was
me I self-reported don't skip oh it was
you actually it was
me that's very s don't that's a very
s what if she's not s what if she what
she a doo
she's she's probably a doo
bird
that no so who who killed
wasn't
me you guys me so easily I was like oh
how do I make myself like if I want to
be kicked out as a doo bird then I
should just make people think that I'm
the sussy
one I skip I Ved
Watson
how many times did r s by got the duck
the good the the duck it's the duck I'm
voting you next yeah whatever happens
we're voting her out
first okay let's ready I'm ready again
again I was
[Music]
shopping
wow it's very fitting that I get
summoned
[Music]
here
oh oh we got
[Music]
these a are you it are are you
it no are you the
duck oh Za hell I have a compromise are
you
it
yeah I'm a vulture I want to eat
bodies me too I want to see
bodies so are you it or
[Music]
not
why are you not doing
tasks because I'm a vulture vulture have
fake
task oh okay I'm just finding okay let
me find
my o clear water pump clear water
pump
uh we don't know where it is
wait where is it oh it's still it's down
there will we make
it it's
outside I got it I got
it did you guys got it yes got oh I got
it I got
it does everybody have to do it I think
everybody has to do
it I did it wait I did already wait wait
wait I think
what blue with blue
liquid I want to be with
Wai what
what why do you want to be with r Senai
because she might kill I want to eat the
body that's kind of s oh oh hi you're
not doing anything I
see no I'm doing
death suspicious stop following
me no no it's for your safety if you die
I can just eat your
body no yum
yum no so you're not doing task you're
just running around I
am
stuck I'm just slacking up my
last hi hi oh I love this
task I love task it's putting the water
in oh you're cleaning no I'm putting the
putting the water in oh yeah you're
putting the water and then it's going to
be going to be wild here later
yeah
no
no no two people
gone two people
gone where is this in the I'm voting re
Senpai no matter what in the piano room
it's
reai she
became your
last because she's always
it nah it's just my luck previously
are we voting I I vot I
voted no no oh no what if she isn't
it no no no longer wanted that's so
sad
uhoh we're still
playing what if it's
not just want to eat bodies
man that's my vulture
cries
hi see I'm
innocent I never
trust R only died cuz she was a lover
with me I was killed and way died with
me so romantic
wait that's not true I murdered
you you did you did but Rea died with me
because you murdered
me yeah so you guys yeah their lives are
interin and I
died okay let's do something
really
stupid let's go stupid stupid stupid
something stupid something stupid
something
I what about so what
about I oh how about a detective
round what detective do detective you
can investigate players to see if they
have killed that round maybe it's too op
maybe too op okay never mind too op
okay I can we we can go with stalker
basically you can track one player
that's mine
okay again you scare me
woman I'm ready by the
[Music]
way and this
time
what if I just keep going emergency
meetings and then
like
suspicious stop I was innocent last time
H
suspicious only suspicious
ious no you are suspicious very
suspicious no you are suspicious no
Ollie what what did you why are you sick
what do you have I think is it cold yeah
it's a cold but I don't have a fever I'm
already are you getting better or worse
right now I'm getting better I don't
have a fever I only have like
a
[Music]
s
suspicious
very s okay
fine where where where do you want to go
I don't think you I want to go whoa so
many why do you want
to I would like to deduct a few
[Music]
things I think K might be a ER so she's
not a
duck what okay I'm I'm the stalker Ollie
and it's kind of useless oh never mind
you're calling her
useless useless what no no I'm saying
the stalker roll is kind of useless cuz
I like I don't get much from it I feel
like does it like do do you win if you
successfully stalk someone what do it do
olly ol why are you blaming me I'm
foring you
no no don't no she's protecting you I
was trying to no I was trying to
like nice
[Music]
deduction you want to sa for
now darn foiled
again suspicious
very suspicious you're doing your
task
suspicious me help
help very
suspicious you're not doing your task
Amelia
Senpai trying to run away from you but
you're not doing your task awfully
suspicious
it's you isn't it I'm doing my task now
I'm
cleaning not a speck of dust I see
suspicious don't touch me don't touch me
don't touch me don't touch
me oh my God oh my
God wait wait wait wait wait wait what
wait what what's
going what
I was cleaning a picture and Raina ran
past me and I heard her and then I was
done cleaning the picture I was going in
the same direction and Olie was going
with me and we both saw the body kind of
at the same time I was like what the
what what well one thing for sure it's
not Amelia
senpie is my true
love lovers that means it's
what why who where was everybody where
was everybody where were you
huh I was at where were you you tell me
right now Watson tell me where you
were I was with ol yeah she was with me
I was with Ollie I was with Ollie no no
before that I was with her the whole
time
for what's
happening oh [\h__\h] no you guys messed up
you messed up big
time you guys messed up big time why oh
no wait do I still have
does can
you you are so close you were so close
but you were telling the truth no Ollie
Olli fight I knew you were the doo you
were so fast
[Music]
sorry what does doo do again need
toed but but ol got the people right
though yeah she said on yeah but I still
wanted to win so I voted for
myself I see crazy that is so
sad you didn't win I'm so mad for
you it's
Tri okay so in kind of
unnecessary mm okay the stalker
roll um yeah this one instead of so I'm
exchanging the lover duck to um Hitman
duck and bodyguard Goose so the bodygard
gets a bonus for protecting a player wow
but the Hitman gets a bonus for killing
them I don't know what the bonus entails
though how to even protect the
same discussion time I feel like the
discussion time is a little bit too
short yeah to okay okay let's discussion
time that was 30 seconds how about um
how about uh 45
45 yeah okay what from 30 to 45 yeah the
options are only 30 45
60 60 okay 60 okay let's go
60 we have okay okay we need to write
this
down
mhm let's go okay so let's go instead of
mimic I'm using the detective so
detective can investigate players to see
if they have killed that round
okay we can try that one okay let's go
okay let's go byebye
bye
awesome hell
yeah oh wait no actually not awesome I
need to deduct
them
oh you know what rather than going by
these I think it's
better yeah
don't worry friend you'll be nice and
clean before you know
it there's one over there
also but I want to deduct some of
them oh it's over here
hello
there
who well well wow that's so fast that's
so
fast is
it is it like automatically
reporting no I report it it was at West
Wing It was at West went to West Wings
can you see the map oh you can actually
yeah you can see the map
oh well it wasn't wa Wawa is
safe thank you yeah why you I was right
there too so I'm
too the last time the last time I saw
someone M and the westling is actually
Ru yeah because
singaa and then I left I don't I don't
think it's it it's I was I was from
hway you're from hallway Ry is awfully
stud library and then hallway yeah it's
a long way from hallway to West Wing who
are you guys voting for Ling I'm
skipping you're very
quiet only kind
of she still she's still safe oh okay
okay
ooh I need more
clues where are thou Clues fluff
and how's it the
flo oh who's
that so I'm at the East Wing get away
from me you
murder what the [\h__\h]
okay aha the power's out I bet this is
they're doing they're going to get us
all over there and kill us I see where
this is going wait how do we get
there
oh is see I
see your little
tricks it's you see you
people what the heck we're trying to fix
the light I think oh oh oh it's
fixed almost stack kill I see I see how
it
is I Ollie might
[Music]
be what
huhuh oh now what you got to
do more
fingerprints suspicious awfully
suspicious I tell you and no one's doing
their job
we go to the
library this is the
library ah
you looking good Uncle
Ben sis get away get away no she's going
to kill me she's going to kill
me I was about to report that I can see
it I see W going around and there is
aai yeah the whole time no don't stick
it on me I'm the medium I can see the
dead bodies I was about to go back to
the dining room to report because I just
my Med like yes concrete Pro I have
a every once in a while I can press
shift and then I see how many ghosts
there are and for the longest time it
was just one the last round and now I
just after my task refreshed and I saw
two so I was in the studio doing the the
base or something stream connection and
then just around the corner is a dining
room where you can report right so I
don't know where the body is but I went
to the dining room to report going back
and forth that was I no no I saw you
going back and forth as well so don't
stick it on me now you you two were
together and you were
probably if I kill someone no I'm the
medium Bally
[Music]
is wants to be killed again
actually hey how good did I just explain
how
the going to be B okay I'm not
sure I'm hungry I swear me too it was
just around the corner the dinner why
would you do that why would you
die that was definitely raining
Andy no we sa
okay no I got nothing else to do I got
to haunt people where oh hello can you
hear me hi yeah what does medium do did
medium they can see the dead bodies or
they can see how many people
died oh but not who killed them right
yeah only oh someone
died oh that's very detailed Ella Ella I
I I was like my hun is selling me train
my Hunt is selling me in staining and
she did Kill
[Music]
[Applause]
Me are to
clever
almond I don't have the heart to lay a
finger on you me me you
me was it was so funny seeing all these
I ran away from
R youill me
anything out a little bit too late she
was
silent I'm
sorry oh
no okay uh I think
uh how about we try since it's been an
our help but we try different uh mode
yes okay we can
try okay what about this hoot and
seek hoot and seek the owl must blend in
with NPC to complete task to win the
game spotters and snipers work together
to identify and kill the owl to win I
don't know how many owls there
[Music]
is what about Goan Goose Goan might be
like better like hide and seek tag yeah
oh the tag go okay want to tryan
yeah okay let's
tryan pass to reduce the timer or choose
to hide oh okay okay there's a similar
mode in um in
uh Among Us I mean we can try runs
really fast can try the other
modes yeah I I think we can try the
goose hunt first and then we try a
different one after this yeah okay
should be a quick round let's
go
go but we don't know who the duck
imposter who's the duck
oh hello so you're not the duck who is
I'm not the
duck are you the duck oh no run
run the scream damn can you hear me yeah
oh you were the second I was the first
yeah I was like oh no oh no why is it
always it's so unfair cuz I literally
spawned where these two spawned
oh so unfair hi
am do task let's do tasks we can reduce
the timer oh okay all right we got to do
task I don't know go go go go go go go
go reduce the
timer continue doing tasks we can reduce
the timer still
with oh my God I knew it what she did
say
what very
nice very nice very nice very
nice
tasks okay okay let's do task let's do
task all
theas I was doing my task who's left how
do I cut I was doing my task
we can still do the task yeah we can
still do the task we can still do the
task do we have to do the task like that
that so hard I think so yes yes yes you
have to because
it difficult
though your
woman oh my God why did she keep getting
the I don't know the task is too much
the task was too much Tas is too much
the task is too much okay for this game
yeah also I spawned where arisu spawned
in the beginning so I
was
no what are the odds of spawning with
the killer man oh we can't adjust the
task it's like set I time K so the
moment Ru immediately came to chase us I
was like oh no don't don't
come Z is like what what is that like
not me no I wasn't talking
about I thought he was I thought it was
Zeta but then Zeta
died why I did
nothing okay um there's this one called
Trick and
Treat so villagers complete tasks to
call meetings and then vot out the
monster to win so it's like we're wolf
right the monster wins when when
everyone's been converted to a thr I
don't know what a throw is like vampire
I guess okay I
I okay basically we do task call meeting
vote out the SS one okay okay okay let's
try ready
[Music]
ready how come I never get the SS
ones how come I never get this
on it's not fair
okay okay we got to go fast we got to go
fast like
s what's
this oh oh you got to you got to oh like
that why are you with
me I'm doing the same task oh
okay you
[\h__\h]
well I guess I'll just turn everyone
into a
zombie
nice zombie
zombie W zombie
[Music]
zombie time oh my God what the what
the I don't know um the studio
restringing the
I've been
very I haven't seen anyone I haven't
seen anyone but wa wa but she was just I
think or Ru anywhere
either I'm going to
[Applause]
Ru
have an intervention about
bullying I
[Music]
know
rainy oh
rainy it was so hard to figure out I
didn't know what I was doing but I guess
I won
thank you my little vampire babies
you're welcome I was the one who
converted all of them well not all of
them but most of
them oh
wow that was fun that was
fun wait so what can the
do we can other villagers yeah con the
vampires turn into like zombies so
they're kind of like yeah like zombies
but even when I clicked like the Turning
thingy it didn't happen immediately it
takes a while I guess until they
turn oh did it happen immediately for
for the others for the ones for the fs
who converted other normal
people I don't know was happen let's
play let's let's play one
more last one whoever becomes the
vampire good luck just try pushing
everything
Viller this is bad how about I just
complete all the task and if I see
anyone I book it out okay down the
hallway oh there's one over
here one over
here no no get away from me
get away from
[Music]
me
okay no get away
from okay so what am I supposed to do as
a thrw do I just kill people
[Music]
Pik yo what the
[\h__\h] again okay I don't think it's I
don't think it's on either yeah I don't
think it's rainu so it's either
or I
vote I had enough being
voted I understand it's okay I I
wouldn't vote you either bullying is not
okay
I'm I'm going to be a bully today en
R you're
reget cuz you were you were talking
about spanking something spank that's my
job I
see well there she
goes
again hello
mistress
real
mistress now if I was rainy or Ana where
would I
be hello hello let's look
together we're both
zombies oh said
bias
yumy see see you got to trust me
I'm I don't know why it gave me vampire
again I told
you wa why spicy time I tried to stop
but it didn't work for some
reason you knew what was going
on was it's because I need to fluff the
pillow oh me too I had to do
[Music]
that for
blood one more please
please do do we still want to do the
previous one or new one new
try new okay what about this taste like
chicken social deduction Battle Royale
protect your team's chicken and kill
everyone else what do you mean social
deduction I don't know DED I don't the
duck duck duck like
P PVP Battle Royale try it I think yeah
I think it's like it's like Battle
Royale I think you're supposed to
protect yourself one one man for their
own okay okay okay protect your chicken
ready
up ready ready protect your chicken prot
the
chicken the
[Music]
chicken
chicken who's not ready let's see
everyone's ready am ready everyone's
ready ready start the game try again try
again are you
ready I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready are
you
ready
maybe here okay I up
again
ah maybe we need a minimum amount of
people to
St
[Music]
Maybe
we okay we can try the um we can try
this one this one who and seek maybe
okay okay let's try whatever this
is let's go we have to take down M even
though she's not here
yeah
M I can't start either I wonder why
that's so weird new room broken
wait un ready and then ready maybe we
ready and ready already um yeah me too
I'm ready now I also did
um
weird let me try again sorry let me try
again no
problem maybe if the room is restarted
worst case I think the only like you can
ready um if it's like plastic my button
lit up when it was classic but other
molds I don't think I
[Music]
can what do you guys want to try
draft Yeah so draft draft is like the
like classic but like you can pick your
rules now okay oh that's so
nice let's
go
okay okay so let's see
oh you get a gacha oh you get AA oh what
does this mean what what is
[Music]
this you get to choose
first okay you need to win vulture why
would you choose vulture out of all
things because
I I mean I'm I'm picking I'm
picking whatever this wa can we see what
the what the duck the goose the duck
also chooses
yeah I think we can choose we can choose
everything like we can see
everyone's but but I'm not a killer
OFA living the life of gacha show a fake
one maybe for the maybe it shows a fake
one it doesn't show people's names or
what player they are yeah it doesn't
show like I guess yeah I guess
technically we can just uh like guess
which one is which who which one a lot
of people picking random nice Shar I was
reading I was reading sheriff
sheriff damn it I wanted to be
Sheriff then
K no
no hello Ana hello don't don't kill me
please no I'm going to do my task oh
what are you are you waiting to kill me
no you see I'm uh I will only kill if
someone else is
dead
okay wait how do what yeah how how does
this one work wait what how does this
one work someone's dead someone
someone's dead someone's
dead someone closed the door on us olly
please stay with me okay don't worry I
got you you can do the barbecue I'll
I'll be on the lookout why are we locked
how do I do this I'm not sure it's the
one with the wood right yeah it's the
one with the loot and like you try to
light
up fire I guess and
like how how
how how do I do this
help oh this is the box but then it's
not it's not doing
anything oh there we go how do you do it
I need to be angry about it um you just
you just use it like how you with
[Music]
hi oh I didn't even see a body so I
don't know why it uh
oh then maybe it's a it's a I actually
don't know why is it so silent where
where was the body where's the body I
don't know I didn't see it I think it's
selfreported
I'm the sheriff so I can't oh you're the
sheriff the so the what role can so
where were you I'm in I was in the
hallway by the laboratory by the sun
okay I think Zeta Zeta came from above
from the hall and say hi was it you Z
yeah I
think yeah you was in the
west two people did of West Wing no way
you came to the kitchen there's only
there's only no I was in The West
Wing I was in The West Wing
at I came in no you said hi to us well
one thing for sure it's not Anna because
I was with her the whole time
yeah I was with Ollie the whole time so
wait wait tell me tell me tell
me little
strong I Ved
[Music]
myself
what did I
tell
me you should have not killed me I
actually don't remember saying
hi I gen don't remember saying hi you
should have not killed me Zeta I am your
helper
you my
helper didn't you hear a hi didn't you
hear someone saying hi saw Zeta I don't
remember you see Z I heard hi I mean I
said hi to
everybody she was singing weren't you
dead I was dead Zeta killed me yeah you
were dead yeah I killed my
helper yeah it wasn't you then if you
were dead cuz it was right before the
body was found I heard
[Music]
a oh yeah we that was fun though the was
fun can we do it again the okay yeah
let's do it let's do it again let's
go I I to God someone said hi Chad you
hurt
no I did I don't hear a
hi damn I was so close to kill she was
in front of my
eyes why would you pick
vulture that's so freaked up who picked
vulture you sick sick being God damn it
what those vulture do
again bodies dead bodies I like this
one then a party dead bodies you win
then that's you Zetta oh
no wow
Z what
does detective
nice what is
that
Batman we will never
know
oh
cute I oh no not
me why did I say
I why did I say
hi so
weird oh
no are you following
me oh go to the
studio boom boom boom
boom and then some
tea
so but if this is a party what does she
do hi
and then we
cook now I know how to do it thanks
son hi hi can you stay with
me okay yeah I'm going to serve dinner
okay
okay okay how do I oh I go to the dining
room instead of the
dinner there's a task that let's
just H together oh hello hello no h
wasn't together hi okay I'm
done
okay oh she's laughing oh God simp oh my
God hold up
together
for is
waiting where's
KY K was going to the upper side I think
without saying anything which I thought
was s by the way even though I said hi
to her I said hi to her but she didn't
answer me with hi back which
[Music]
was
you there you go KY where is
ky
hi
sure
oh she's spanking spanking good how do
you spank the pillow I have keeping I'm
going to
do don't worry I'm watching I'm watching
okay yeah my task was over here going
continue
you I need to
reassemble oh wait I got to do this one
okay
I H plunging I don't understand how it
works I've never gotten this one
before how does it
work fire fire fire let's get fired uh
fire
fire fire fire fired fire
not going to lie do we all have to do
it fire fire
[Music]
fire how do we do
this oh okay it's
done where's
Anya
everyone Ana's
gone gone yeah wait no where's any is
she dead hopefully
not where's
Ana okay eat oh food foodo
foodo are you guys done with your task
not yet not
yet have to do
bath that's the chest
I'm glad none of us
[Music]
died oh wait what you were talking to
me sorry were you talking to
me oh I lost sight of everyone an we
thought you were
dead no I'm still alive and well I think
rainy went this way rainy okay oh okay
so it's definitely not Holo right it's
not Hol it's not
Holo i
s hell
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah what the [\h__\h] you were a
vult was she was following you just in
Cas you di yeah I was hoping I was
hoping either of you guys was
get it was hard cuz everyone was
together the whole
time yeah I I think having only one
imposter is hard it's so difficult it's
so people just to be like together
I'm not making it better
[Laughter]
though accomp me
that's
yeah okay I actually you know what's
crazy I actually didn't know that party
was an imposter I thought party was just
like uh like the goose just like just
like a just like a useless oh I was like
it it only says something like you can
give someone high pitch sound during
meetings I was like sounds
cool what so you can high pitch voice
but also kill yeah you can
also I guess it would be hard for
villagers to like discuss with each
other about sound
yeah my Roes like if I'm not alone if I
have like at least I guess if I have at
least two people with me I can't get
killed so that's why I keep asking
people to accompany
me I was waiting for
someone H was together the whole time it
was so difficult okay okay I think we
could possibly end it here
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe again
sometime yeah let's play again
sometime yeah this is so fun thank you
for making the time to play
together
invting thank you it was a lot of fun
yeah thank
you I'm so excited to see all of you in
Japan soon for
[Applause]
FES
y then we can
party we can party for real party h
take care Everybody Take Care
everybody good
good
[Applause]
[Music]
byebye
[Applause]