[Music]
so
ah
[Music]
okay
hello good
evening
i'm here to let out
some aggressions
hello hello i'm very angry
many reasons to be angry
[Music]
well first of all welcome to the stream
uh
i was um i would today is my day off
but uh you know i i kinda it's not like
i miss you
or anything
[Music]
it's not like i missed you or anything
obviously i know
it's not like i was lonely or anything
it's not like i'm addicted or anything
no no no no no
no it's been a while since we play
mario kart i took um
so i'll stay i stay angry for the whole
stream by the way
uh i took a i took um a poll on twitter
asking you if you want me to play a
manga
or very card and it was a surprisingly
mixed like about the same thank you for
the super chats guys
[Music]
thank you and what do i have to do
online play right
okay let's go i'm ready to fight you
next time i want to play among us as
well again
i want to play mangas as well at some
point
what do we do what do we do a tournament
or how does this work again
i remember the last time i did a
tournament i wasn't able to get into my
own tournament
oh
is it is it global okay we can just try
to get into
but then i'll be with random people and
that's called tournament
uh oh yeah there we go i made some a
while ago okay the speed one is mine
and the kusa tori is something else that
i made with ina i think
so hmm are yours rules
okay no limit don't switch
what does don't switch mean
it's time to rate yeah flip those tables
i'm [\h__\h] done with those tables
stupid tables
is that all right i think we're all
right i don't know i'm going to join my
room
did that just say that i'm what
oh yeah whatever [\h__\h] join speed
split
let's get um last time i was uh
trying to figure out what is the best
combination you guys told me that bikes
are better
than the cards
uh which which one of these
which one of these should i choose
though
uh cause i don't know what's important
for me
acceleration maybe yeah whatever ah
there's not much difference let's take
this one whatever okay let's go
is that good is that a good combination
oh my god are these all people who just
wow you're so fast oh my god i couldn't
even decide i couldn't even vote
oh we're already starting this is speed
hi hi
thank god
[Music]
let's see who we have here today who is
ready
to uh cooperate with
the one and only tencho
[Music]
nitanto
oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
ignore it ignore my australian flag
ignore that okay
ignore that how do i do them
judas is in there uh how do i do the
speed up again
what but i think i had to i forgot it
again
[Music]
the other day i had to change it back
from japan to australia
because um because i had to make a
payment
and it wasn't so it's so stupid
like because my paypal account is set to
australia
so you know how to use items again
[Music]
[Laughter]
other people are having fun
i don't remember you being such a nice
driver
oh [\h__\h] again
you're waiting for me but still you're
still too far away from me to reach wait
students
there we go that's good that's not so
bad
[Music]
oh
hear my rage maybe it will scare them if
i scream a lot
no no i want those items
wow okay i need i need this bullet item
as much as possible because i'm just too
stupid to [\h__\h] grasp
never mind that of course i'm a good
rapper it's not like i need it
where there were a lot of people waiting
in front of the finish line
kind of weird what happened there
thank you
[Music]
they waited for me yeah that's how it's
supposed to be i don't
i don't know what those what those
people in the top six
were trying to do what they were trying
to pull oh yeah everyone please leave
after one game
please thank you please
i'm trying to manage my anger okay look
at the title
it's written there
why there are no new people coming in
are we gonna trap with only four people
it's probably my internet connection oh
you don't know my room color oh oh
oh how do i see my room code
wait i don't know what my room is
[Music]
okay i have to go back sorry guys you
can stay
okay
[Music]
okay here room code uh speed
uh there we go uh should i write it on
the on
on here
oh wait let me pin it let me just pin it
thank you judas i am surprised
that you didn't try to win okay so zero
don't go in now otherwise i won't be
able to go in zero nine eight seven
uh five nine four three
nine nine one five what
now let me in okay you better let me in
if you all fill up my tournament
then i will not be able to get in you
understand
[Music]
okay there we go okay
let's go again there's a possibility
that this tournament is now split up
into two lobbies if i understand it
correctly
oh whatever they have to figure out
themselves
[Music]
wait i'm not in this i have to watch
them do i have to watch them
goddammit goddammit
okay let me rewrite that while they're
driving
sit tight okey dokey there's a bunch of
npcs in there i guess it's uh
they didn't make it into the room on
time
five nine four three nine nine nine nine
one five
okay that's the that's the correct one
good luck trying to get in there
faster yo
drive for the kfb i know you can do it i
know you can
i'm not in it right now so give it your
best try to impressing me
bye oh wait how can i watch someone else
there you go travel trash nowhere
from australia my home home country
burger king
do you guys know what what the the pun
behind that is
it's a joke on uh
[Music]
like
i don't know what that what that is
supposed to mean but it's a pun on
amelia
good names i like these funny names you
guys are very um creative husker gamer
is not very creative i must say
and trash nora also not very creative
change your name guy
guys change your names
everyone a burberry king
wait burger king now i understand what
that's supposed to be
barbican is a it's a pun on on that
certain franchise i understand find
american i like your name that's
actually really funny boo boo king
i hope you win it looks like you're
winning you might have the best name
higher faster how dare you keep me
waiting oh my god
three out of three almost done
and you don't need to spam your question
i think
uh asking only one time is good enough
that number on the screen is the number
to get into the
tournament lobby yup and there we
are the the people who just
drove without me you can stay
there
[Music]
you like cheese everyone i actually only
want like normal cheese
and not that that that cheese that has
lots of green
and weird colored stuff on it
the one that's like moldy the moldy
cheese
ew but the normal cheese oh like
mmm or mozzarella
what's the good one called what's the
good one called again
what's the good cheese cheddar cheddar
cheddar cheese oh [\h__\h]
cheddar cheese i want to stuff you i
want to stuff myself
up with all of that yummy cheddar cheese
ignore my australian flag it doesn't i
just
i just randomly choose a random country
totally
oh it's animal oh it's animal crossing
map yay oh can i
would you guys wanna want me to um play
i don't know how to do this anymore
would you guys want me to play last
night on stream
i haven't played it since since like
half a year oh [\h__\h] a tree
you're in the way
yes you would but if i start
playing now you better all come visit my
empty village and then give me all your
items and your money
all right why why am i the last one
again
what is
why does no one realize what good driver
i am what
and why don't they follow the rules the
rule is
to keep
[Music]
oh
how do you even get that curfew if you
have the golden mushroom oh my god oh my
god oh my god
that was totally useless
what's in it i'm coming for you
i have no item give me some light if
someone give me to my name
[Music]
no
why was no one waiting for me uh watson
what's an achillea waited for me
i don't know how this shoe waited for me
but
you have to let me win
i took number one okay everyone out with
you you don't understand the rules
only one round thank you bye bye
thank you come on bring me the next
people in
and let me be let me be very clear
you don't want to anger
[Music]
the person who's employing you
crimson you gotta did you just join is
that your second round only one round
per person please
why didn't you we're the new people
are you guys trying to get in
he just joined okay i'm so alone with
him don't leave me alone with him
ah there we go yeah let's wait for new
players yeah very wise
very wise decision i don't think this is
a
whole team but is it it's just a full
team
let's see their names let's see there's
one with a really rich face
that one looks like dude do you guys
know doraemon
i guess at least i think it looks like
doraemon
yay which one is it huh didn't see
takana
okay so if that person wins it's
basically as if i won
another
[Music]
if that person wins please i'm counting
on you i'm counting on you
[Music]
oh
oh i think i've seen this bro for the
first time oh thank you crimson for
waiting what a good guy
what a chat
[Music]
thank you whoever gave that to me thank
you
give me your offering
[Music]
hey come on let me win nothing with evil
at me or that
way he or she leading
they better be leaning
come on i take the i take the the rear
and you take the front
how about that
[Music]
okay
i love you guys very much
how did you guys get these curves right
oh my last round oh my god
i can't i just [\h__\h] stupid for this
game
i'm trying to twist i'm trying the game
just doesn't work for me my game is like
bugged or something
[Music]
wait
it's catching up oh my god wait where's
the goal
come on fake wait no wait i'm sabotaging
myself
no oh wait that's okay it's always over
wait
[Music]
yes i got number
don't leave me don't leave me you're the
only one who can make me win please
no no no no no no don't leave me no
no you cannot no no
my only chance for victory
night
winning one time it tasted so so good
such a sweet victory and you're already
trying to give it away from
how about trying a different character
does that does that does it
change anything the character
does that do anything
i thought the character doesn't matter
it does but i want to be a pretty
princess
are the other princesses better but
there's a catfish what the hell cute
there's a cat beach wait i can't use my
bike
okay let's go with this one there's a
cat beach
why we're not enough people or are we
there's so many peco events
[Music]
it's so easy to
to figure out who are the peculiar fans
i watched that clip and when she was
trying to figure out
uh if it actually sounds like that and i
still have to say it does not sound like
almonds
it does not almost
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
no
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i have to say though my driving just now
was good now
did you see how much i was drifting
i was better was it because i turned
into a cat
are you winning i'm winning
i did great right it was it was pretty
decent right but i still was so bad
because they are so good
oh vegan when you made the name
congratulations you know what to do
you know what to do right
you know i think we both know
and what the hell why does he have that
kind of a head
that what's it called in english is it
it's probably not goomba in
in german it's goomba it's called akumba
we need more people come on welcome
thank you what what is that uh criticism
sorry for back cinema there's a thing
you can turn on called smart steering ah
[Music]
is that the thing that makes you like
automatically move
do i want that oh it is called goomba in
english
[Music]
now give me that no no no
i [\h__\h] hate that road so much
there's absolutely no way that i will be
anything besides
twelfth place there's no way that i'll
be anything besides twelve
[Music]
okay just aim for the stars kiala aim
for this time
because you are star wars number one
hello
wow whoa whoa just now be smart and
don't fall off yeah
then you can win because how do
[Music]
we were just all driving straight that
wasn't that's not
fair how did you do that
[Music]
your if you don't like your boss become
number one
and let at least just super cute
adorable cats
i hate this road so much
[Music]
you lost your job buddy congratulations
on losing your job
if that was the one who just uh
afterwards
fell down on purpose well yeah might be
i don't know
you even without a job or you did i
don't know whichever you prefer
i guess but i'm not hiring you back
that's for sure
[Music]
why aren't they so good at driving is it
because they have a license
do i need a license as well to be a good
driver in mario kart 29
it's already over
okay but at least i'm number 12. what
the [\h__\h] being a man
you're supposed to let me win not be one
above me
to flex probably you did it on purpose
and you did on purpose
like you didn't even want to be any any
higher than that you just want to be one
above me
[Music]
i hate that road so much no better with
my
that was my chance but it's gone
bye bye guys so unfair exactly that's
what i'm talking about
okay come in new people come in
xinjing koi
bye bye please no more rainbow road
please no more
happy
who the hell is that on the left side
what what face is that
what what the hell is that face that's
so scary
that is such a scary face
you should maybe wear a mask or
something to cover up whatever that is
[Music]
are we full no we're missing one person
i bet there's more people trying to get
in but it's just
some kind of internet issues
doctor disrespect what
[Music]
all those people who are uh peculiar
fans
who have some kind of peculiar reference
in their names i've seen them all
in her streams why
i started posting it too what the hell
is your problem
someone [\h__\h] up my card that's sure
who was it someone put some fried
chicken or something in my cart
in between the in between the wheels
[Music]
calm down use it wisely
okay can i focus on drifting if you
drift
you piece of [\h__\h] you did that on
purpose you waited until i was right in
front of you to shoot that
blue cell
i'm gonna kill you
my life's mission is now to destroy you
[Music]
i will never forgive you you destroyed
my career
you destroyed my driving career
i will kill you where are you where are
you i will follow you
i will follow you where the hell are you
come here
where is he i'm i'm wasting my stars so
i can get closer to gandalf
there he is
[Music]
you have challenged the phoenix that was
a very wrong very bad decision
wrong life choices let me teach you
something about wrong life choices
it's what you just made now give me a
legend
wait that's over
[Music]
[Applause]
get out of the room can do it before i
destroy you
bye-bye thank you thank you for playing
with me thank you
bye bye bye
next next people come in
[Music]
papa wants me to be in the top three
have you heard if you don't listen to me
then listen to
[Music]
out of respect all the works that he
brought to this wonderful world
all the masterpieces that he he has
brought into this world don't you don't
you want to give
pay him some respect for that
oh which one do i go for which one is
easy i don't know
this one maybe i don't know please oh
everyone's choosing that one
[Music]
[Laughter]
please i want to i want to
i want to be in the top free for my papa
i want to make my papa proud
you know what to do friends it's for my
papa it's not for me okay
i know you don't listen to me i know you
don't listen to what i say
but at least
[Music]
i didn't know what i was doing okay now
now you guys know what to do right just
drive slowly okay
we wanna be careful it's dangerous
anyway like think about your family and
stuff
like they're gonna miss you if you like
haven't
like like me if you fall off the [\h__\h]
road so many times
not the weight don't wait for me
to wait
[Music]
wait where am i going what the hell
where's oh there oh i found it
sorry i don't even know the road
i thought that was the right direction
just waiting for me
is there no chance for me to ever see
the light at the end of the tunnel
no no no no wait wait
wait oh there's someone nice waiting for
me
thank you for respecting the wish of my
father
thank you
[Music]
oh
i'm so far away from everyone else oh
there's plugging in
clark is a good man
thank you for giving me news to adam is
the only one who has
manners and respect
no no there's one passing
there we go my blue shell at least did
some effect they at least
hit them yep
[Music]
i'm not last yes
they're not listening to me
bye-bye next ones
we need takanashika to come back
to classic
[Music]
please come back come back to me
i don't think she's in here now big blue
what are these rounds i've never seen
them before
we're missing one we're missing one
papa
[Music]
this is because this is because um
there's some queen chiara ooh
it's because it's because i can't find a
reason
[Music]
okay this is the one i will get top
three
this is the one i will get into topper i
promise
[Music]
oh wait this is like one of these water
parks
oh that's so much fun and it's already
different now that there were no such
plants in those water parks what the
hell
it started so good
[Music]
drift peach perfect why can't you drift
oh this one's difficult many of these
are
my first times on these girls how many
rounds are there how many um
i guess how do you call them not really
how many are there in this game there's
so many i've never seen before
yes triple bunk let's go we're outside
hello oh i thought that could bump all
the way no no no
no wait
what is the meaning of that anyway i'll
drop slowly
if they wait i have an idea if they are
pass me by
then i am at the pill
did you just drive backwards
how nice if only all people could have
manners like that
[Music]
it's too late now i'm too far away but
what the hell was that fence i thought
if i'm
invincible like you can like eat so many
objects but that was alive
that was a [\h__\h] one
will i ever get better at driving
[Music]
we're here at the fence again stupid
fans
i will order it i will order after this
match
i will call the mario park department
and tell them
to remove all fences
and then your career is over as well as
offense
let's see what you will do after you're
done being offense i don't think you can
do much more
than being offense huh well that's what
you get
for [\h__\h] me over life after being
offense is just nothing
it's just nothingness
you might you might be able to get
recycled if you have a good record of
being a good fence but you were
bad you were really really really bad
fans
i don't know about your record honestly
i would personally
take your record and write lots of
stupid things in here
[Music]
number nine wow
wow
that is really offensive oh [\h__\h]
kiana took offense
fences are pretty offensive you guys
have been very funny ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha
[Music]
i give you guys one more chance
to make peace
with your ten tool distract the other
players
by showing your ties that's actually a
good idea
that that might be a good idea rainbow
road or hell no
if you guys choose rainbow road i'm
gonna be
i'm never gonna forgive you
today
okay look at this now you won't be able
to look
at the road anymore
what is it what is it which one is it
which one are we going for
there's only one two people who chose
rainbow road it better not be them
it better not beat them come on come on
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
why
[Music]
hello
how did i not fall down there no there
we go
please everyone start your counters
start your counters now
that's down the real rainbow with the
other thing i don't know what that was
this is a real wheel
here we go number one falling down
counter
number one
[Music]
i have no hope for this road absolutely
no hope
there we go number two that was not even
on purpose it might not look like it
though yep
countdowns haven't fallen down two
why is no one looking at my time
[Music]
it's going quite well don't you think
number seven okay whatever
i take it all back and falling down
three times
[Music]
how can you not fall down in this room
no who was that
who was it
who wants to be fired for life huh
[Music]
you'll get into piano prison in my
basement
i have a prison in my basement and
you'll be in there i don't know
you probably think that's something
kinky but hell no it's not
[Music]
it is not let me
let me promise you there's nothing fun
about
being in my prison basement
why not face because i'm trying to make
them think of something else for driving
but these people are just too
focused on [\h__\h] driving
i don't know how they do it if i see
ties like this
if i see callie's time in front of me i
would not be able to focus
on
[Music]
oh
i think it's seven i think we have
reached the number seven and
okay whatever
yeah three
three three
three
[Music]
this is not fair papa
wait wait let's let's do that one thing
uh what was it what was it how do i
how do i get to the wait the manual no
no i can't change my card anymore i
wanted to do the thing the thing that
you told me about the stairwelling or
whatever what that was
still wheeling oh wait i didn't choose
[Music]
what which one are we going for
your mom i'm gonna ground pound you
come on don't you guys feel sorry for me
there's one person in the chat who feels
sorry for me what about everyone else
you don't feel sorry for me
[Music]
okay how did he accelerate that fast
that dollar guy how did he do this
he must be cheating oh
finally i get a red shell i think that's
the first time today
that i get a ranch shell this whole game
is ring
it's made to make meals they don't like
birds
it's discrimination because they don't
like birds
but i'm not a normal bird no don't put
me into the same
bucket dropper or whatever why is that
person
invisible i mean that guy is obviously
cheating i mean hello
or was he just a ghost i'm a phoenix
[Music]
[Applause]
what did i buy a crew controller for
thank you
oh i can jump
that's right okay someone who
understands how to respect
a phoenix you guys have no idea what i
could do
with my fire if i unleash my true powers
if i get rid of my transformation belt
when my papa put a sign on it it says
don't use but if i could use it
i would burn you all to the ground are
you aware of that
don't don't make me
[Music]
hate
let me
[Music]
what
yes very very much
indeed a communication era has
has indeed occurred tuscany
communications
you guys don't listen to me
you don't let me win there's a problem
with communication here
i think everyone misunderstood what this
is all about
communication communications
let me in again and now follow the
goddamn rules
okay how do i turn on the that thing now
can i turn it on
is is that or is it this one
is it this one is it the y
is l ah
do i not need one i said two controls
is that tail controls
okay so now it should be fine okay
you got ben i did not get banned why
would i get banned
oh god what's happening here it's only
five people
gone in sky [\h__\h] for a nanny
how did everyone get kicked out and was
it not only me huh
[Music]
what do you mean i got kicked out thanks
for going backwards
but it's my tournament tournament it's
my rule
my tournament my room
hey we should only eat
no that's no no no no no that game
doesn't care right i mean it wouldn't
give me the option to go backwards if it
wouldn't allow me to go backwards
that's not a thing
[Music]
i didn't even win i always lost anyway
why would they ban me
what
go faster go faster higher
backwards driver i mean there was no one
behind me there's nothing dangerous if
there's no one behind me then
you can totally go backwards there's no
problem with that
let me drink something hydration jack
ah it is not really a thing though
is that really a thing because the game
won't end if you go
backwards forever but everyone else was
going for
more it would make sense if i was the
only driver and i would go backwards
because the game doesn't end but
and it just ends up though you're too
far away right
ben we're going 12
i didn't tries time this was supposed to
be a one hour stream
come on oh there we go there we go there
we go okay
no more communication era let me
communicate with all of you
there's a
almost looks like kiara because of the
hair
okay do we understand each other
everyone
the rule is the communication
wait we're not [\h__\h] no wait we're not
full
come on two people come on
oh wait we're missing one people okay
that's all right i guess
okay let me win let me at least get into
top three
please i beg you i beg you i beg you
okay let's go kfc beat cafe oh
come on
kfp is number one in the world
[Music]
let's go okay only positive vibes okay
only positive spots positive spine
let's go my friends can't be repaired
oh no go
get all that
[Music]
that is something you do not if you want
to be realistic here if you guys tell me
to not drive backwards because you don't
do that in real life either
well excuse me but you also don't bump
into the others and you don't throw
items at them
in real life either okay understand
if we want to be logical then let's be
logical for real
okay you don't only apply those rules to
certain things just as it pleases you
typical
you know the rules and so do i
[Music]
it's actually not going that bad i'm
sick
[Music]
hey i'm actually doing good well this is
road it's one of my favorite roads now
i know it's important to take your
vitamins but
don't you eat the outside of the banana
as well it has even more vitamins you
have to eat the whole banana
don't throw out the most important part
of the banana
cava mutable
these children who don't eat their
veggies and theirs
and their fruits and their vitamins
what's wrong about eating the whole
banana go
go blue shell hell yeah
oh why am i so small what is this lag
run away
come on
[Music]
this is all i can do papa this is all i
can do
this is all i can do
okay last round everyone last round
the goal is to get
into the top three for real i mean top
five honestly i'm proud of myself that's
pretty good i must say
top three here we go don't disappoint me
guys don't disappoint me this round was
pretty good
you were fair we played fair top five is
all right
papa said that it was close it was
indeed very close
are we full are we i don't full was that
a good choice
i don't know i don't really know this
rose that well i don't play this game
off stream
by the way i gotta practice just for
tomorrow
we're playing chess on amelia's channel
it's a rematch
we're playing chess uh so i'm gonna
after the stream i'm busy i gotta i
don't gotta practice
chess okay what do you mean oh no
what do you mean i know you all want it
i know you do don't hide your feelings
you just being sunday you everyone who
says
oh no i don't want chess you're coming
to the stream anyway i know and
i know you're all gonna be coming to the
stream and be like
oh this is so horrible then why the hell
are you watching it
if you really follow me with that bad
and you're not enjoying it
and it's really that painful then you
wouldn't be watching it okay this is
the typical logic of haters paying
attention to
whoever they claim that they don't like
okay then why are you
why are you bothering yourself with my
existence then
if you don't like me if you don't like
chess why are you watching it
huh the reality is you love me so much
and you just can't live without me or
chest whichever it is
you love me deep in your heart you love
me and you know you do
that's how it is spinning fast i know i
am
i know and i love you too
see at least it's not unrequited
feelings
[Music]
i know you all love me doing chess i
know you love it
you love we love singing amelia playing
chess
that's the best thing you could be
watching on a
wednesday or whatever afternoon or
whatever time that is for you i don't
know
hey we're actually grabbing what well
i'm talking about this
i'm not even focusing on writing talking
and talking
maybe i should just not think i should
just feel
wait i'm doing quite well
actually i think the reason why is
because i know that
[Music]
but what i was trying to say it was
going so well because this this
map i actually played a lot on the phone
so this is one i know
i feel like it's actually playing
smoother i'm not
falling down anymore is it because of
that
is it because of the settings that i
changed
i feel like i'm like not even trying
that hard
to not fall down wait was it always that
wasn't always just
oh come on
yeah it's the other ceiling huh i
thought that was actually good
hi
thank you everyone
thank you
[Music]
thank you everyone so much for driving
with me
[Music]
thank you for um not letting me win i
don't know when
when you will ever learn this is why
this is why we have problems here with
communication oh yeah but whatever i
have to
as i rearrange everything here
[Music]
i'm angry
okay everyone um i'm out of the game you
can continue playing if you want
with the kft crew i'll be reading
[Music]
but some honestly that i think the whole
time are you guys do you guys all use
uh the other steering is that why you
were always better than me
[Music]
yes
liars i don't believe that
of course you aren't guilty
you are using it
come on just even even if it's a lie
just tell me
if
super chat just asked me how many times
i reached number one
well one time i did oh wait is it double
oh god
oh god oh god
i forgot that i don't have to play it on
on my
outside anymore okay okay okay
no that was the real kiara the
the one that took number one that was
the real cattle why don't you believe me
it wasn't it obvious it said takanachi
and she had she had orange hair that was
obviously me
but i love how i was hoping for that
kiara
oh wait why don't i have super stickers
out i love how i was hoping for that
kiara to pick uh to get number one the
whole time
and she actually or he actually managed
to get number one that's like a miracle
that's like that was like really funny
okay i will read super chats from this
stream since we um
recently managed to pick up again so
catch up again so i only have to read
the ones from this stream so this should
be quick
why are you pressing x that was me how
could
how dare you doubt me how dare you drop
my words i'm always
i'm always faithful and honest to you
guys
i would never lie to you oh thank you
for the super chat
happy birthday happy birthday nishiki
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you you sent the red one so i'll sing
for you happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
every day it's someone's birthday mine
is still so far away
as a european i won't be able and that's
actually why i did the gorilla
uh because i wanted to stream at a good
time for europeans so where's my
europeans at
wasn't this a good decent decent time
for you
wasn't it acceptable for some europeans
where are my europeans
at yo yo yo basket up
here
thank you everyone for the super chance
thanks for watching the stream i'll read
super chat should be quick so if you
want to stay
that would make me very happy and
tomorrow collab with amelia on her
channel
uh if i feel like it i might do
a gorilla on my channel as well
oh we could do a mangas yeah
let's see let's see
i
[Music]
and on the day after the day after
tomorrow
there is an important announcement
from my side on my channel
[Music]
there's like a lot of actually it's more
than one thing that i'm announcing
and i have to say i've seen a lot of
people guessing what it could be and
pretty much all of you are getting it
wrong pretty much all of you are getting
it and you're wrong
pretty much all of you yep
but it is a pretty big deal for me and i
think also for you i think you guys will
be
pretty shook of what's coming
and also besides the announcement i will
um
show you some things that i prepared for
the talk show
so it's gonna be a very important stream
to show you some exciting things
okay
because there's also uh the talk show by
the way
has a name which i will also announce uh
on the announcement stream it has a name
it's not called talk show but i didn't
want to put it in my schedule yet
it does have a name it has a lot of
things a lot of things that i prepared i
want you all
to hype it up with me together if you
would like to
that would make me very happy i'm very
very excited for all these things i'm so
excited to share them all with you
[Music]
know
okay let's read super chats everyone
let's read a super chat
let us revel in this joyous occasion as
the kfp tries to be tender
for the grand prize of a race check your
cards man
i never heard of a race uh why why don't
you do it when you're
promising them behind my back is that
why they didn't listen to me when i told
them to let me win is it your fault
because you you promised them a race is
that why
didn't listen to me
i uh i think we need to have a
little talk after the stream okay come
to my office
florida to the cafe
jacqueline sanchez next is thank you
thank you for thank you for um like
putting all the small ones into a big
one thank you thank you
and my one super driver for today i have
nothing more to add but i paid 200 for
250 characters and i'm going to use them
all
wow which deep wise input
thank you very much thank you for your
support
packaging and thanks for driving against
me
and thanks for not listening to the
rules thank
[Music]
felt like forever since your last stream
right
i kind of i felt like streaming
yesterday as well i mean i streamed out
um
yesterday at like
in the night time
uh like after midnight but then the rest
of yesterday
that that actually that streaming i said
sorry that microphone i
found it the stream yesterday felt for
me like the day before yesterday because
i screamed at midnight
and it was before i slept if you
understand what i'm talking about
so it did uh it didn't feel like i had
the whole day off yesterday but yeah um
you know how i i for the karaoke stream
you know how i
changed my sleep schedule and like
usually up until now it was
for ages i i did this thing where i
would stay up
until 6 a.m and then sleep until
like 2 2 p.m or 1 p.m
for the longest time and i could not fix
it for this for
whatever it does didn't matter what how
how even if i tried to wake up earlier i
was never able to sleep earlier even if
i was tired i
just always have to be around five or
six a.m sometimes even seven a.m but for
the karaoke stream
i kind of managed to
stay awake until 2 p.m
i i don't i don't know how i did how i
did that i think i took like a small
nap in between and then suddenly i was
living
the american dream of an american est
time zone sleep schedule and i thought
that was gonna stay a while
like that but it didn't i actually went
backwards and
i fell asleep last night at seven or
eight a.m
and i will try actually i have to try to
sleep earlier today
because i have something to do before
the amelia stream which is at 12
so i have to at least wake up at like
10 am oh my god how how can i ever get
up at 10 am
that's way too early but i will try i
will try
i got something to do
[Music]
yay yeah 2 a.m is really for me if you
consider my sleep schedule
i mean i just i don't know why but i
just can't
i just can't fall asleep before
[Music]
before it gets light outside
why kiara why why
i wish i could fix it i just can't
oh i'm just thinking you're late too bad
but it's a short stream so you can watch
it afterwards
i would say you should you should you
should watch it afterwards
once the archive is ready okay let's
continue uh we're really excited for
this week and although it will mostly be
a midnight stream for me i'll just do a
kia on my sleep schedule on video
exactly that's how you how you do it
that's how you do it thank you for your
support thank you for coming to my
streams even if they kind of suck for
your schedule
uh i will i will put in more streams
that are fitting for gmt uh like
european time zones next week and uh
there's also i mean there might be a
gorilla tomorrow who knows
but i didn't realize while i was in that
american time zone i didn't realize
i wasn't able to sleep well because i
would i would go to sleep at like
2 2 p.m and try to sleep until
9 00 pm but i couldn't
it just my body was like waking me up
and
trying to tell me bill this is wrong
this is so wrong
it was bad it was really bad i couldn't
sleep during the whole day
so i'm back to the usual
okay thank you hang
i
[Music]
um
tomorrow oh my god ah cannot withdrawal
is real
i cried during your kiss recover you cry
did not kiss me connor was it so
romantic why did you cry
that was supposed to be a actually
that's a happy song that's not even a
sad song
why did you cry is it because
is it because you realized that i will
never kick you
but only my wife callie i know that
hurts i know that hurts
of course that hurts i'm sorry
i'm sorry but it's it's true
is that why you cried
i'm sorry i'm sorry
i'm sorry
[Music]
finally got membership thank you welcome
to kfp
peanut button
[Music]
rachel thank you navy bully duncan
one sentence many super chats to save
tantra's voice thank you
thank you but i will take a bet on when
penta will arrange i'm going to guess by
the end of the first
or second grade as i'm wrong
was that wrong or was that right did you
lose your pet
when did i start raging wasn't i raging
from the beginning because i had my
angry expression on
you lost did i rage later or earlier
i was raging from the beginning right
well
well you know what to expect next time
[Music]
foreign
papa
and that's because i fear for losing my
job i wonder if you participated
thank you for cheering for me thank you
for rooting for my success
as everyone should andre
i just wanted to be like my role model
pencil and play slow like you
[Music]
i really appreciate you accommodating us
can't be within this cat language stream
men's thank i really enjoyed it i'm
still a bit rusty so i'm gonna make sure
i practice for next time
no please don't please just don't
do that sorry for facts oh yeah i fixed
that thank you thank you for
letting me know about that
[Music]
rainbow road right i only fell fell down
one
i just quit my job because i want to
work for kfp oh
did i have the honor to work with you
i'll pay you
that's the spirit hell yeah i will send
you this the contract
uh via email okay just sign it and send
it over
that is the spirit i'm glad there's some
people
with common sense out there who
understand
how this world how this business how
this economy actually works
thank you thank you thank you and
welcome to kfp
moulder man thank you and chain brother
thank you on the paid carefully spirit
thank you
and i
thank
but he's done with the counting he was
counting how many times i was
falling off of the rainbow road
okay
thank you for the
[Music]
i like i like people who are kind
to me thank you thank you very much
thank you for your support
i know
twice
[Music]
for the old one i hope it makes you
laugh share a bird documentary is coming
along
oh thank you so much for being amazing
and fun i always look forward to your
ppp
thank you oh how where do i find that
reaction video send it to me on twitter
and i will take a look
i will refresh because i reached the top
i will refresh and then we should be
done soon
[Music]
thank you so much thanks my birthday
thank you playing i am very happy to
watch oscar
thank you happy birthday i think i think
i already sang for you but yeah
[Music]
happy birthday
i woke up at 5am just to get fired i
guess still a fun stream
thank you yeah just send the next
application
we don't really um if you're fired once
uh we don't really pay attention to
your actual um work uh
history so you can just join as many
times as you like actually
[Music]
well that's very nice of you to assume
that um my playing my driving is bad
because
i'm watching the game on obs and
it's giving me input lag and telling me
to buy a second monitor
that's very nice of you to assume that
that is the reason why i'm so bad
you guys do you guys agree
i mean there might be a little delay but
you agree really
but no no i i might buy a new
a second monitor once i'm back in in
australia
because i don't wanna i said that last
time about
buying a mixer and buying a uh and like
oven thingy but then yes actually
yesterday i ended up buying a mixer and
an
oven yeah but for the monitor i
i want to wait i don't need it i don't
need it that's urgently i don't feel
like i needed that originally it's just
too confusing for me to have too many
monitors
so i like a small oven like
the size of a microwave in japan in the
kitchen
it's usually the kitchens are really
small usually so they don't have a
proper oven
as you guys probably have in your home
and therefore there's like small
ovens in the size of a microwave which
often
have a microwave function as well but i
only had a microwave and it didn't have
the oven function
so i i wanted that so i got myself an
oven as well
like a small one and a mixer yeah you
can use just
two monitors right away wow
still i feel like um
i don't want to make too much waste when
i leave i don't wanna
have to throw away too many things and i
don't feel like i need it right away
it's not that much time left anyway
time is tickling it's crazy time is
really ticking
forward one from cali no i'm fine i'm
fine
actually i have a tv monitor that i
don't use but it's like huge
i couldn't use that one so it's too big
to fit
on my table
i do have a laptop
i wonder if i could if you can use a
laptop
as a second monitor if you connect it to
your pc
with an hdmi cable another thing that
works
you can how does that work
you can you can but most people say i
can
one person said i can't
depends on a laptop not easy but it can
interesting
okay but that's too complicated i don't
really need it
um although i do often feel like when
i'm streaming there's like
not enough space to put all the windows
everywhere like there's too many windows
on my screen
and uh i'm trying to
make space for everything a bit though a
bit small
everything but i'm usually the games
that i'm playing i'm usually playing
them
on on the small obs screen
which is not even full screen it's like
a tiny window
so i'm not getting the best i'm not
getting the most best
out of the games that i'm playing
ah it's okay it's not that bad
[Music]
have it so i'm not older you want to
give me your birthday thank you
i'll take it it's my birthday today
wait i didn't prepare anything for my
birthday i didn't prepare any
announcements
[Music]
oh thank you everyone thank you now the
aldi's happy birthday is that for you
they are for you
james mcphee thank you rez thank you
and you're gonna win next time kiara
regardless it was super fun thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed it can't wait for
the chess game tomorrow here
there is someone who is honest about
their feelings there we have one of
those people
definitely sanitary officer dan
[Music]
i'm saving money my money like you said
nothing over green for now oh no problem
i caught the archive i tried to watch
but i fell asleep at 45 minutes archival
of this stream what
a different one thank you though stay
awake next time
[Music]
should i happily
i'm curious to see who will destroy
amelia
it just would be me or will she destroy
me
she had more practice recently because
she played with cuda
and i have not played since our last uh
chess collab so
it will be interesting i will practice a
little bit with some npcs
[Music]
with you also thank you thank you for
singing the maori penguin jump opening
in your karaoke it's my favorite anime
oh your favorite good taste
it's a quite quite the old one now but
i really like that it was so long ago
that i don't even
really remember what it was about i just
remember it was amazing
it was amazing
this is my first super chat ever thank
you thank you thank you
thanks for letting us play with you i i
let you pass me and then oh
thank you what an angel thank you for
being such
a much needed positivity in my life and
i'm very happy to be part of the kfb
cruise
thank you welcome to the kfp
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
you enjoyed it
you're getting a wisdom tooth removed in
a couple hours oh my god that's
terrifying good luck
oh my god good luck with that that's
gonna be painful i can't imagine i never
had my
mind removed but that must be horrible
thank you the chess match will be like a
fever dream oh my god
that's true oh if you if you're like
under those like
wisdom tooth drugs i wonder if you even
remember to watch my stream
maybe you'll be like watch you'll be
like staring out of the window
thinking you're watching my stream and
you'll be like wow
wow kiara got so good at chess staring
outside the window
whoa oh no amelia oh amelia she's
killing piano
i can imagine that
i hope you catch it though night owl
and last refreshing
is this super chat reading all the mario
kart 8 super chat i want to remind you
that you didn't finish super chat from
after
eh
i did
[Music]
did you miss my last sakura stream i'm
pretty sure i cut i caught up
i'm pretty sure i
the the first sakura stream uh if i
remember correctly yes indeed i stopped
at some point
but uh dudes on the favorite dream
but the the second i didn't refresh
but where did i stop then
[Music]
okay i read that
it's kind of hard to tell oh
[Music]
ah
so after that after i finished
finished reading the super chats
i secretly without saying anything
turned them on again and started saying
my goodbyes
and no one noticed actually i i think i
even turned them back
on before i finished reading them but
nobody
sent super chats at that point because
nobody noticed
and i said goodbye and i finished
reading the super chats and then i
forgot
to completely end the stream
and then people noticed that the super
chats are back again
while the stream was already over it was
just not like not
turned off on youtube when people send a
bunch of stupid super chats
uh i see okay let me read those quickly
i'm not sure where exactly they started
though
[Music]
foreign
nicholas
mario kart
in
[Music]
oh i wanted you to know that i did not
only fall from the rabbit hole but only
fell for only chiara you are
you are no pickle or center but you are
close for me you are the best and unique
of all thank you for making my year
thank you that's very sweet of you
thank you thank you but there's many
other great great
awesome lovely girls in her life
i'm happy if you say i'm your number one
but check out the other girls as well
they are amazing
thank you for the fun stream also hi
also please continue to make more fun
noises
what do you mean fun noises what do you
mean
i'm not doing fun noises i'm i'm always
talking like an educated person
i don't know what you're talking about
okay can you guys stop sending super
chat
[Music]
champion did i what do you mean
are you saying uh are you saying
amelia is the undefeated whole life
champion
i doubt that i i strongly doubt that
you're wrong my friend
also i like how they did i i i didn't
unpin the message again i
retracted the message again
it's still there it's just hanging out
out there
it's a empty pinned message don't mind
it
okay last one after we after everything
that comes now
i will not read anymore
and small brain thank you everyone thank
you so much
for coming today to the gorilla
spontaneous gorilla stream
[Music]
i gave it my all driving against you
guys
hope you enjoyed it next time
next time let me win
let me win please
please
okay and at the end
i'm going to isolate this at the end in
german
we do say auf wiedersehen
auf wiedersehen bye-bye
thank you very much for coming today
and i'll see you tomorrow on amelia's
channel check out the schedule
if you want to see the time
[Music]
do
foreign