do
oh
hello hello
[Music]
just before you switch the screen i came
back from making popcorn right
oh did you spill it it's
no it's completely burnt i [\h__\h] up
it's completely burnt that one time that
i actually have
microwave popcorn at home and i'm really
really excited to make it for
a great movie i burned it completely
i was i noticed that we were talking
and and i heard it stopped popping but i
was like i will be fine
i'm in the middle of a conversation with
you now so i can't go and pick it up now
so i left a little bit too late and i
opened it up and i like also
inhaled like burning fumes really strong
in my nose
like directly and then
and i opened more and it was all black
no come here let me let me touch your
ears
you'll be fine you'll be fine you'll be
all right you missed out on that one now
i was trying to avoid it but okay
wow okay well you want to um introduce
yourself to chat i'm sure everyone knows
but
you know yeah i'm talking about
and my apartment now smells like burnt
popcorn
it's okay you're uh you're teleported to
uh my couch
no more no more popcorn yeah yeah i
don't know popcorn
why do you not have popcorn here you
know
boy it really stinks holy [\h__\h] it's like
really far away
but we're holding somewhere off the good
start
oh no open the window a little bit
yeah maybe introduce yourself okay
go go go go go go
okay on the scale on a scale of one to
ten how how easy it is to
burn microwavable popcorn
how is he
what do you think guys eleven
one is it that is it that easy to burn
it
not easy honestly
[Music]
i was just saying um on a scale of one
to ten
how cute is kiara today i heard
something like a kick in the key
no no you're imagining things i just
said i just said it
on a scale of one to ten i'll kill
esquire today they're giving like
ten elevens oh wow well i knew it no
i don't believe this i don't believe
this
what is this what does it say i'm
scrolling
[Music]
this is my couch this is my living room
we turned off the lights just for the
movie
it's nice in here
my kitchen is even like kind of smoky oh
you know what else is smokey my
smoking hot dog
oh okay i wonder do you go
through your art tag a lot uh yeah i
looked through it almost every day i
wonder does did anyone ever
draw you with a smoking hot body like
bowling balloon like that's kind of like
a
yes like a different kind of you know
yeah yeah how did it look they look we
ain't
oh like really boing boing or just a
little bit
the fine really boiling point like me i
think we're we're working on a different
scale of boing boing here
was it different from your normal self
i guess so yeah yeah yeah oh
i want to see that i wonder what you
would look like with like
really really nice h-shaped curves but
usually they
uh they reinforce the um
the bottom department a little more than
the top department
sometimes because of a a mistake i made
on the street
what did you do don't worry about it
did you show your blood and i don't know
make it no no
i just i don't wear butt implants
what
i don't know you don't explain it to me
so i have to imagine i know there's
stuff you put in your
ear your uh your you're like brawl
but um i don't know a butt implant
batting
did you wear padding only when i go
snowboarding
[Laughter]
because i fall down a lot maybe i should
have worn that too when i went to
hokkaido of cali
um did you hear that story would i
i think people would appreciate if we
just would talk and not watch the movie
i think they would like
the cats watching by the way
i'm holding me those are the two cats
should i change it to cats 2021
or 2021 there's only actually there's
two cats on the screen
well yeah anyways yeah
[Music]
yeah i have a very very weak spot for
cats i love cats
this is a good turn thank you i learned
from the bestest
it's like every time i tune into your
streams you're caspering on the
microphone
wow you you turned into my stream at
very specific times then
i know like sometimes i just like tune
in randomly just like
cat prairie i'm just like is this car or
is it her cat
you got you got a good timing oh yeah i
know
my cat sensors are very uh advanced
except the cats don't like me
when i went to like the um cat cafes in
japan
like i went with a couple of friends and
like all the cats were like you know
when you hold a snack
in there and their hands they like all
like swarm towards them and they're like
all like
give me snacks and then like and like
i'm like eagerly holding a cat like
snack where the cats and then like they
just avoid me
i don't think but that that's don't
don't
no no no that's not on you
that's not on you i'm not popular in cat
cafes evil
only my own cats love me i i considered
bringing some catnip just look at the
cats
[Laughter]
you can't bring your own stuff to the
cat because like no no no but what if
what if
what if i just wanted to pet the cat
you know what i have really friendly
cats um
they they would probably be nice to you
and so just come over to my place
okay say no more leave your fridge
not locked overnight please thank you
so it's about it's about the cats it's
not about the food you know
you're gonna love refrigerators or
teleportation devices
oh okay
i thought you were just hungry okay but
that's that's uh just a side effect
okay should we maybe um get started i
guess so
i i'm looking forward to this it can't
be as bad as everyone's saying those are
just
like weak babies uh exaggerating i'm
sure it's not that bad
we'll see you didn't watch it either
right so no i have not i have seen
trailers i have seen screenshots i have
not watched it
so i mean i i have to agree on the
screenshots it looked kind of creepy but
that doesn't say anything about the
quality of the movie so
i mean it might be just like a really
high budget
graphic oh movie you know animated movie
yeah they even got like taylor swift
right so it has to be
high budget and really well-made he got
18.
you like her tell her
too much so um me and you are watching
it on different places i'm watching on
amazon
so let's line up okay well um i paused
mine
you know when it goes
yeah i have that right now and then like
it like ends the music ends and you see
the entire
universal logo i popped it right there
[Music]
you stop it right there okay i'll give
you guys right yeah
like a minute to get it all sorted out
okay does it really not does the music
really not container did i stop it at
the right moment because i got
great rhythm feeling not sure as long as
you see a comcast
company okay then okay then you're fine
okay
hopefully the audio doesn't go through
if it does
uh everyone just ignore it i'll fix it
i tested it beforehand but you never
know if anything changed
anyways um if everyone's ready
ready i'm so ready
nice
[Laughter]
is already is such a low
level dad burn inna again that could be
better than that
a dad pun yeah
a dad probably a bad pun
[Laughter]
okay never mind my brain was uh
lagging a little there it it took damage
from being a bad pun part
about stinky news um
all right was watching okay my jokes
never land don't worry about it it
doesn't hurt me
[Laughter]
they do quite often no oh you know what
when everyone just like face pumps you
know
that's when your jokes land you
can we do one thing before wait okay
give me one second okay um before we
start
start the movie
i'm gonna give you one graphic can you
put it on the screen
uh okay is it burnt popcorn
maybe i should get that
and maybe my cat away so people won't be
like
[Music]
hold on okay let me uh
why this stuff eh we will see
you'll see
okay hold on you wanna put your cat away
yeah okay
all right what's this oh okay which
complete in the middle yeah
okay this is it yeah yeah we're telling
you
yeah we need to take our hands you have
three three hands
okay okay you know you're ready okay
um congratulations to both of us i'm one
million subscribers oh yeah
yeah swapping and shaking
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake
shake congratulations congratulations
[Laughter]
if it wasn't for your birthday we could
have kind of celebrated to give up but
the birthday kind of gave you a last
push like really
right before the end so yeah yeah we
couldn't do it
it's okay we're celebrating now by
torturing chat i mean
uh watching cats i'm glad we i'm glad we
both enjoyed these kind of things that's
nice
[Laughter]
all right okay okay everyone ready
the time has come
i'm gonna count down from five and we're
gonna go and go
okay you know that's a that's a pun
kiara
oh
[Laughter]
uh um uh a replacement for
a popcorn okay
okay countdown from five okay
and we're going on go okay five
four three two
one go okay
okay tell me if you if you guys hear the
movie on the stream if it
does i'm gonna pause but yeah
hopefully it's okay
well there is no sound from the movie
yet do you see uh
did you just see a logo that said amblin
entertainment
uh e.t oh
now yeah the moon okay okay the moon is
pretty
today okay okay oh
my god you're starting oh yeah it's a
musical right
okay all good okay good oh the egyptian
the rising sun oh it looks good
can cats drive cars
regret ewe
[Music]
can't hold it back anymore
wait transform oh my god what's
happening
oh god stray cats
oh yeah
is this how people see me now that i got
my own cat here cat ears
no no
question micah is taylor swift coming
out of this
wait is she actually a cat yeah
on the screen shots i think so gosh this
is creepy
oh that's not taylor
i mean the ears are pretty cute you
found who this
and that is taylor okay let me just let
me just
ignore their faces i'll just look at the
ears
oh
i mean the songs are really good right
it's a really popular like play
musical play chicken of the world
i'm always lost in the streets
i wonder if this is even creepier when i
listen to it in german
because there is a german version oh my
goodness
what's a jelly called i don't know i was
gonna ask you
is that like the jelly beans on the
cat's paws
ah maybe
what's the difference
there's a lot of like skeletal if you're
angelico
is that is that like the uh
the cat's version of a zoomer
rumor a zoomer a zuma oh
no if you weren't around the bug then
you're a zoomer
[Music]
wow wow those moves
jolly clothes the music is buffing
yeah i'm gonna look at the background
catnip fun casino
oh my goodness
oh yeah oh yeah
and that was a really high note
yeah sing it
oh i'm still confused
moriarty
what oh evil cat
this is like a city built by the cats or
are they living in like human
no i don't i think they're just straight
yet or they
but they just like imagining that
everything's about them maybe
i mean they're not imagining everything
is about the cats
the cat's eyes it's
it's in it's based in london london
according to the chat london looks quite
different from what i remember
what oh no
wait do they all have no only those had
shoes on
wait who gets to wear shoes and not
um who has who has necklaces no wait
maybe they do
oh someone's doing something
where's the phoenix cats
mystics
oh
[Music]
so where's the planet i'm supposed to
hate
did it come up already
i like the atmosphere though
um what accent is this
oh it's london so it's british of course
a british braz yeah i know how to speak
for ash melee day
huh
oh she's a cool cat
somehow i just had mr grinch play
through
my head why i don't know why
we're run run run for your life
what what's your name
i
another name what
you what might
oh it indeed is
yeah it was not easy i'll just choose
their names
they're different names mine mine do
have two different names or maybe
actually three
hmm it's true it's true you know
oh
oh my god there their tails have
emotions this is cool
it's like it's kind of like a true name
in like the fantasy stories where it's
like
if you know the true name oh
then you're gonna rule over that person
like
like like with jon snow
never mind that doesn't mean anything
you know
is that a word i don't know i was just
thinking that
you learned this language better than i
do
name your name
oh feel it feel it feel the name
what's your expression
okay can you imagine if you introduce
yourself like that every time you meet
someone
my name is dan
it's so dramatic
oh
oh my
clarinet wow
whoa
my name is it's so serious
what oh mister felix
does that stopped or said said
i forgot his name
something
same cute
those flowers are fake though
there's a ball for cats
okay they use that word so often i'm
gonna google it right now like i'm
going to
oh it's it's a made up word is it
follicle dogs or alcoquettes oh
jellicle cats means dear little cats
i guess a telico is a cat
like a jelly coat cat
oh i'll get it i guess so
feelings cat wait what if this is just
kfb
it has nothing to do with it this is how
you bring in new employees
you sing dance around them tell them
they need a new name
no really not really
oh is it let's be taylor swift
is it
a gumby cat no no what's the comment
here they're keeping me
away making them oh my
chubby cat huh
cute chubby cat cute
that's the ideal cat phone
oh my god
oh my god my eyes
cara you look like you're having fun
i'm having fun i love this
is that a tail why aren't you singing
into
because that's a nice detail
oh mice
it's only 15 minutes
oh
oh god
don't leave you weaklings watch the
movie until the end
okay be really the other thing in the
shower with your tail is your microphone
chiara
no because i'm not a real cat that's the
thing
i take these things off when i go into
the shower
if you want to know the details i can
show you pictures
are your plug-in type
as i said i can show you pictures
oh my god why are the cockroaches now oh
no
[Music]
oh that's eat cockroaches
oh
oh inspiring
she wants to change she wants to be a
bad
version of herself
looks like a yummy kink hmm
it's only been two minutes
this is this is a great movie nina
oh
i love their accent mate
you
[Music]
oh my
i was a curious cat but i don't want to
be one anymore
i love him
hmm
wait is that jason the roulette
[Music]
oh
i'm trying
okay maybe i'm getting used to it
[Music]
you can't feed cats like milk
they can't digest it well oh
yeah you can't keep them too much
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
oh yes food fetish
oh wow eat
aren't so unknowing
wait did they just teleport
i'm so confused what's this
oh my god
i'm so confused
oh
oh man the singing though
ah a boot wow
oh my goodness i'm so lucky
what is this what is this
victoria oh yeah
what to this
new phone hoodies
she got a little bit of a drip though
[Laughter]
probably preferably not when she's
singing
she's warning us about another cat
it's kind of like the uh the outlaw
she's warning them oh
this is jennifer hudson apparently
wait is she the one being bullied
the outcast or is she warning someone
she's thinking about herself oh cats
don't cry that's not really stink
do they really not cry i don't
but what about those pictures of crying
cats are they photoshopped
cats don't cry they can like maybe tear
a little bit if they got something in
their eye
yeah maybe cheers
ah they're bullying her what did she do
are you jealous of her trip
she was just too good
will you take her in enough
she's so sad
i'll pet you
is
[Music]
fluffy
wait that's that's um uh james um
wait what was his name
james corden
i love him
i honestly don't know that many actors
i love him i want to poke the belly
yeah the way he walks
hello
i don't watch tv
um i don't even but he's on i mean his
shows get uploaded on youtube
like there's a channel
huh
why is that not covered here
oh simple it is
what what
what what what's with those cats in the
background with the big hats
is that where he lives gorgeous house
oh he left again oh yes show us your
nice body
he got on his neck he got a um
a tuxedo a bull thing yeah
a tuxedo cat
it's like the type of cat that comes in
that goes my job here is done
but they didn't do anything look at the
monsters too i just noticed
oh no
mmm mint
he took off his clothes but not his
shoes
that must be good
but i got cat ears too now i need
shrimps
in one bite
that's not going to work is it
that's not a cat
[Music]
oh my god that stingy water
oh
um i'll be honest with you i have no
idea what happened
at all in the movie well they're
introducing
like the these groups of cats and the
particular cats
oh i think right now they're just
introducing everyone
is it gonna be in like an hour of
introducing cats
no i'm sure there will be story they're
building it up
um i'm starting to doubt
don't be so negative
okay it's about it's what cats eating
from the trash
well i'm in these strikeouts do they
have a choice
no i mean they're relatively well fed
despite being because
oh he running
he's booking it out of here splash
oh that's him okay that is the cavity
what does he do why are they so afraid
of him
hungry
trap that was totally not obvious
what
well they disappear like that
yeah with my friends do your faces look
familiar who are those two
hmm
who are they
team rockets
those actions oh my god
she's cute
they're what they're called cats
[Music]
my first cat in minecraft was a calico
cat
ah nico nomicon
rip
mongol cherry well that's something you
sound familiar mango jerry
oh no they're the type of cats to like
mess up the room
as soon as the owners leave ah
[Music]
everything is chaotic and gone oh
a toilet paper gone
what if they like make her steal all
this stuff and then blame her for it
oh no i can see it happening
there's a reason there's a reason
they're only putting it on her
not taking it
this is a nice place it's like it's like
in team
rocket that's like meowth
oh right there oh meow
what kind of salad is that
why is the meat oh oh there it is
yum kind of looks straight though i'll
be honest
i love this jazzy music
oh have you ever done something like
that right on the rails no
you know maybe oh
just down sideways though
that's gonna break oh
no no lateral damage
that bad looks so comfy
oh no
no gran there dark people
i hope not oh no i knew it
but but no it's i mean it's not their
phone she got stuck
see shrug and they're gone not even
they're the ones
i don't think he's very helpful i'll be
honest
[Music]
blah
is this a romantic moment uh
maybe it was a little bit a little bit
of a doki doki
moment
what's eating num
chips
that are a few days old
[Music]
oh yeah
wait didn't she then
i forgot their name make
like muffin
now
i'm you but strong
nah nah nah
he's seen things this is a
he is a sailor
doctor of
the times
[Music]
so many cats
ah covering for her oh
deuteronomy
time for another introduction
a really long time
oh oh is she the one that died
nine times oh the cat that dies nine
times
they have nine lives
they're already calling victoria queen
victorian they just met her
no they made her their queen oh my god
no i think i mean the actual queen
she also called queen victoria like
victor that cat is called victoria too
of england oh
[Laughter]
i mean i mean if you look at the movie
it looks like there aren't any real
people anyway
oh oh the queen's name is victoria oh
oh i only know her as the queen i mean
i was like which queen do you mean which
one was called victoria for what what
year
i see the old
that's queen mcdonald's no she's just
been around for a long time
since since the days of queen victoria
she looks more like a lion yes
that's a maine [\h__\h] that's supposed to
be the main [\h__\h] i'm sure of it
i know that immediately i love ming
cause that's like one of the
one of the only ones i know like maine
[\h__\h]
oh
they're big and fluffy
well maybe or maybe it's not a make-up i
don't know
maybe her because ming cones are long
long fur cats their feet doesn't have
that long hair on her legs
on her neck big big
the long cats but she's old so maybe she
shrank
what's torture no she does have long
hair on the
legs as well this is maine [\h__\h] oh
there's like a cat youtuber not not like
an actual cat that's a youtuber about it
a youtube channel that features a lot of
cats
they have really really cute maine [\h__\h]
oh is it a
is it a korean channel no
it's uh jun's kitchen
ah
tension
wait is that is that iron mckellen
gandalf it is
holy sh what okay this this movie
was already great and now it's even
greater
meow you fools i can't
i can't believe they got all these great
actors what
what what's happening
he shall not nyampa
[Music]
pass you shall
[Laughter]
that is a good one
wow
is this the ballroom or is it a circus
maybe can you go to a circus if your
entire life is a circus
can you go to the circus if you put a
senpai
she is the circus yeah
oh wow that's some
interesting curry
what's that what's going on oh because
she she came in because
of that and like really crashes because
of her
wait but she's on victoria was her name
she's the only one in the middle what's
happening
crying just came in too yeah but they
don't see her yet
but they feel it cats have that feeling
that sense
why is he wearing those pants
why is he the only one wearing pants
that would make everyone maybe a little
bit more comfortable you know
maybe it's because of a gandalf cat
it was like you shall not wear
nyan pantsu
okay that was a stretch
now the stretch
oh oh yeah
what does this feel like like the
magical moment at the end of the disney
movie where everyone's just dancing
happily
happily ever after because the movie is
about to end
but we're not we're just wait what oh
is jason the riddle back oh yeah
asparagus
did you see that
oh i like this beat
why would you describe this as a genre
um some sort of like
happy good music banger
like the 80s yeah the 80s or back in the
80s
it's like when you see those like really
really old like aerobic
videos they're like doing the exercises
with the music
one two three four
[Music]
those shoes though why
what are those where are those
now are you victoria dance
oh oh she's a ballerina
beautiful
oh
wow wow i could never dance like that
i can't even touch my tongue yourself i
can't even touch my toes here
just let the ancient ones control you or
your tentacles
they'll do it for you
[Music]
i'll teach you i know how to dance
actually during like
i think like junior high we were like
required to take dance class
as like an options class hmm
i don't i don't want to remember
i don't want to remember
it's like a ritual is this
this is what happens sundays at kfp
we have similar rituals i guess yeah
this is when when the employees gather
the dancing for that for them for that
wage increase every sunday
can we finally get a raise
yes but it's going to be paid out to me
yeah sure
oh oh
she wants to join the fun
who talk to her
lonely
oh lonely god
pain nico
you know you crying no okay
it's okay to cry you know
oh i'm sad all the time that's the
secret
[Laughter]
you got a tissue for her you know
so sad i'm looking for a pet
like everything will be okay oh
i'll say i think she's carrying the
movie
you minus gandalf
i can feel the emotion the pain just
from
her expressions in her voice
[Music]
hmm
oh the control in her voice is just
so good
she can't trust anyone
oh look how her ears are like
oh oh they're being watched
me trying to say hello to stray cats
let's see
[Music]
i just want to give you some love
oh
she's a beautiful voice
[Music]
oh
that was pretty
i don't know why but her voice is really
familiar
um she must be a famous actor too
some people said it in the chat but i
don't recognize the name
judy dench you know that name
oh sound the music
sound of music i don't know i watched
that with my members months ago
and james bond
not sound of music okay someone else
didn't know what they were talking about
hmm oh yeah i never watched
did you watch the james bond the recent
ones yes
i didn't watch any of the movies
whatever that means a generic choice
i have a feeling i watched something
else that was she was in though
gando what happened to you
gandalf no it's gus
me too
do you ever get is he gonna sing for us
i wanna hear gandalf sing
actually like a fancy bed yeah
comfy
the singing kind of
is fluffy
yummy
i will deny it i might if i had the
choice to
it might be an option
i believe that you know i always thought
whenever
one day when i get a cat i'm gonna name
them sensei
cats are very wise
it's named after nyanko sensei
his ears so
good at acting
like the small gestures that he does to
act out like an old cat
she likes it
ahead
it's oh
i didn't actually give them cat paws huh
disappointing no not remembering birds
with arms
[Music]
but you know one of the best things
about cats are their paws
chill the jelly beans
[Music]
oh
static
[Music]
[Applause]
oh that was good though i mean
he didn't have an amazing stunning voice
but
hey it's it's iron
oh no
oh
he won't fall no
[Music]
he's gonna get snapped away i knew it
it's that easy
they're really cool cat
watson
is that him
i love this the instruments oh my god
what's that instrument called the one in
the background
this one chat
help i don't know
harpist cord oh
is that my real cat
that's that's the name in english that
sounds made up
oh it's a thing i think
harpsichord
oh yeah he is a real boycott oh my god
that makes sense with him he's the
really okay
that's not mario he's the railway cat oh
god
captain cat ape japanese
i like how they mix in so many different
ways of dancing
that reminds me uh on the last day of
school
one of my teachers went up on the podium
and started tap dancing
to celebrate the end of the year
good times
so fast
[Laughter]
i just want to put like oranges beneath
their feet
or fresh orange juice
i'm dizzy now
wow
i wonder if all these cats are just like
talking about their lives as
cats like they still lived in the like
the train station
and gus lived in the theater
but what are they listening for
wait for it
london wow
have you ever been to london yeah once
it was cold as hell
did you see the big pen
oh actually
no not really weird
we did do quite uh um
besides quite a lot of sightseeing
though but not the big ben
yes i guess we can
[Laughter]
the thing where the queen lives the
thing where the queen
what's it called again the palace
apparently okay yes
yes
[Laughter]
you know that little house apartment
yeah
did you at least go to visit sherlock
holmes
museum no i had no interest in that but
we did
we did do like a like a harry potter
tour
where they showed us like the parts of
the city that had something to do with
harry potter
he's fine
what what is this magic
my cavity his cavities hurt
help him
[Music]
oh man this heels
and the drink um
is that taylor who are you that
seems to be taylor swift oh my god
nice entrance
hey
oh no not the catnip
she with my cavity i guess so
she's sprinkling catnip no not the
catnip
oh no can't control
yourself no oh
wow it's pretty happening
oh yeah
snake are you gonna do m snake
oh she got those nails hmm
oh my goodness she doesn't even have to
walk
sassy got taylor
not there
there's a lot of ginger cats in this
neighborhood
mm-hmm
yachts
oh and i'm ginger too
you just realized
that power walk though wow
i aspired to have that sassy attitude
like taylor the cat
hmm oh no
that's sprinkled with catnip
not there hey it's them
the one that stole the jewels
are helping her
oh they're all the same
they're all they all
oh what's the cavity
crime hello
who are you napoleon
oh no that's my cavity
[Laughter]
why he's got that shiny fur oh
yeah yeah yeah
your blessing
this is fun
yeah what's that what's my cavity's
actor's name out of interest just
wondering because i don't know who he is
but i'm
i bet he's famous too yeah
yeah oh okay
e3's elbow never heard of the
i twist itches
oh no they got the queen
he's the gatekeeper in four
oh yeah she has to choose one cat
oh he got rid of the competition so he
gets oh
i feel like victoria is also contestant
yeah
she saw her sing
calmed down no
because then she can't choose yeah stop
no you can't for sure
oh no
not the prank no
you can't do this someone save her
no
do something victoria
i thought she was the protagonist
they're lying
oh dude
what
victoria wow does she have a plan
oh no
he's not a good magician to lizzy
he's got the power of love
wait he looks familiar
my cat is doing something weird john
grace hey
hey hey now
she doesn't listen because that's not
her real name damn it
it's one of the our three games yeah
hey guys what are you doing
meow
oh my god the human hands just can't get
used to it
oh whoa whoa
that's a fake fork
oh big magic
i wonder if they can bring her back with
magic
i hope they do
must them have to
you can do it you can
chuckle nervously
laughs
oh he's starting to believe
ah
the music is changing he's starting to
believe
that's not kittens but pretty good
though
worth it with enough food
hey why haven't i heard this mentality
before oh
no still nothing
you're ready cleveland please you can do
it
you suck
keep trying
jason sing for us jason jarullo please
oh victoria
oh oh
wow
[Music]
is
magical mister mr
felice do you believe
ah oh yeah
well yeah
maybe someone else should try maybe
maybe someone else
well well well wish
ah where did you come from
he did he believed him
oh my god oh he didn't swim over here
[Music]
your wizard
everything's floating how are they doing
that magic
what oh
well i never was staring over
i got so close
[Music]
on the boat
is it gonna hit the speed
oh he did it wow i now kiss
oh my god
oh is she gonna be the chosen one in the
end hmm scary
what what
oh yeah stage outfit
what
that's
oh no oh yeah what are you gonna do with
the tap dancer tap dances towards you
menacingly wow
wow
sugoi
yeah is it gonna fall no
no way okay
no don't go
oh
[Music]
oh she's opening up to them
oh no cute
give her a chance give her a chance
hey cinderella
[Music]
give her a chance
it just needs a visit to the to the vets
to like you know
get some brushing up done
and she'll be pretty as you guys it's
already pretty though
sink
thanks chad
noting it down
and that's how i joined hollow life
[Music]
hi junkies
all live auditions are crazy
this movie is all just a big audition i
mean it's fitting there
it's a lot of cats in her life too so it
kind of says especially like fubuki
cat
what are you doing chocolates
[\h__\h]
[Music]
she dying no she's just
overflowing with emotions yeah
she's finally on the chance to talk
about it
oh you you oh i love you
did you hear that you know yes
the real cats movie is happening in my
office
oh
[Music]
no
this is happiness
oh
you are the chosen one
you know have you found the liking in
the movie yet
yeah i think if you could pass the first
part
it's pretty good
oh
she gets a second chance
[Music]
indeed
just going up
[Music]
oh
past the
the moon
[Music]
oh no
ah
[Music]
like a hot air building
shrimp
i think i was here when i was in london
oh
she's talking to us but have you heard
of the phoenix cat
i saw it
what's your proper name
hmm
just as a fox is not a cat
a dog that is very true
this movie is speaking the truth
a dress a cat
is that you yes me
that's me 50 years later
i see the resemblance
maybe
okay this is this is the future of kfp
[Laughter]
well will all my chickens turn into
this is what the you the one cow is
being sent to the usual room
but they were they're competing to go to
the usual room what's happening in the
future
they do that a lot so yeah they don't
want to go to the usual room like
like powder 50 of my employees want to
go and 50
don't want to go
his name meow
you know i thought the song was gonna be
over like two minutes ago
wow is it over and amazing okay the song
is over now
birds chirping that is that song
she looks beautiful in the sunlight
are you a jelly cook cat yes
i am oh there we go okay she's like
thank you for finally telling me what
the
[\h__\h] that was i was wondering for this
whole movie
i was just acting as if i understand
what i didn't
there she goes
so sparkly whoa and
so she's gonna go up in flames like a
phoenix huh
um
[Music]
oh that's too bad that it's over i want
to see more
i'm not sure i have enough right beside
me
[Laughter]
and that was great what the hell is
everyone i mean the only thing that i
kind of
like a little bit about was how they
how the humans look as cats that just
looks a bit i think
they're weird like like people if you
can get through like the first like
40 minutes i think it gets pretty good
but you start to understand what the
story is about kind of
in the first 40 minutes uh
yeah i think it was great it was great
music great
graphics great actors really great
actors
but i think i think the first 40 minutes
kind of gets you like
used to seeing the cats and then
and then it starts the story you know
the story builds up
and you're just like man stop
criticizing my new favorite movie you
know
you want to fight
you you give this movie a 10 out of 10
don't you yes she does
blink if you give this movie a 10 out of
10.
[Laughter]
there she goes she did it oh my goodness
also it was your favorite cat honestly i
really liked the um i forgot her name
the one that flew away in victoria oh
i love their songs i think saving
something
jennifer hudson yeah i think they
definitely made the movie for me
without them i don't think i would have
survived
[Music]
i think i think my favorite cats were um
james the james the fat james cat
and the the the chunky
um gentleman young cat what was in a
jenny nyanyang
oh you know what i'll think in my next
unlike
karaoke i'm going to sing a few cat
songs
music is good uh i'll have to listen to
it
and that's gonna trigger these people
some more because they're just
exaggerating
i mean there's a bit of a hurdle to get
over to enjoy the movie i think
nah what the hell that's just oh man
everyone's just meeting me this was a
good movie
if i'm being honest i want to go see the
musical
oh the brother are they dressed up like
this in the musical
they're not cg for sure so it's going to
look probably
worse oh i think it's
chad
uh i mean the musical is like really
really well loved which is why people
really look forward to the movie too but
oh they just couldn't get over the cg
cat
oh jason derula was also supposed to be
a maine [\h__\h]
huh come on
what this kind of reminds me of um one
time
um we got free tickets to go see a lion
king
like the musical it was like such a
fun fun experience so
i wish i could experience that again
i just found a picture of the musical
and yeah they look pretty good
i never i think i the only time i saw
like a proper
musical on stage was actually uh
in london the one time i was in london
i went to watch mama mia that was so
much fun
oh i watched i watched both
maybe maybe maybe we can watch another
musical sometime
i was i actually actually you know
we could make this uh running gag you
know cats and all that because
when i was looking on i was i was
checking my netflix because someone said
on netflix them
cats movie is on there but it wasn't
online netflix i guess it depends on the
country
but so i was looking for cats movies and
then
and then apparently i saw on netflix it
has um
the the the ghibli cats movie
maybe we can watch that one together i
think i already saw it
like yeah i don't really remember i mean
i i watched all these good
movies but they're always
no but i went to a ghibli
[Music]
always always like reserved and sold out
and you have to make
reservations maybe
maybe next time if we're all in japan we
can book in advance
oh yeah we have to plan and plan plan
ahead magical
we have to do so many things go to the
to disneyland yes
disneyland japan is on and i want to go
to what's in the
nintendo one mario dad opened up
while i was in japan and i was kind of
thinking of going i even talked to
matsuri senpai about it because
i don't know for some reason we talked
about going somewhere together
but i don't know it didn't really work
out and i think
it would have been a bit difficult to
get in there because it was right at the
opening and then
oh yeah yeah kind of left japan but yeah
we have to go there that's in osaka
while we're here because it's it's part
of the universal studios you can also
check out the other places like harry
potter
and everything else also there's the
places with
the the running dude right
is it the one that has his uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i've been there
before actually last time
i wasn't able to see that so i want to
go see it
that's in shinsaibashi one of my
favorite
places when i lived in osaka i'm gonna
go to kyoto again i love kyoto
you can probably eat way more stuff than
i did when i when i was with cali in
hokkaido i had to like
most of cali could eat most of the
things but i was like
uh no thank you food right
yeah i don't like seafood um i like like
if it's just normal fish then i like it
when it's grilled or so
but raw fish no and any kind of other
seafood that's not a lot of ours
i wish we could go to during lavender
season it was so
pretty when i went it was lavender
season
and then besides the farm that i went to
they had a melon farm
[Music]
the sweetest like cantaloupes
that i've ever eaten cali loops
tell
[Music]
yummy food oh you did you did quite a
bunch of things didn't you
yeah i'm not very good at like going
through places but i went with
uh another friend and she she knew all
the ins and outs of all the toys
right you mean you went with fubuki
santa wow
maybe maybe one day
but yeah there's so many really really
uh really really cute places like
like you know music box museum
yes someone in the chat
said someone drew us too
offensively already found it someone
drew a swing cat style
um i don't know how i feel about that
[Music]
thank you that is why that is um
you know you look so weird why
this is beautiful this is beautiful
why
is that the only thing or even more
there needs to be more there needs to be
more
no oh wait oh that one's cute
ah that one from nazi and dallas
that's cute
[Music]
no i'm going to retweet those yeah good
idea
that is cute that is adorable
all right um yeah by the way one more uh
speaking of cursed things
um did you
did you saw all those smith kids popping
up
no oh you didn't
were you not much on twitter yesterday
uh i don't think so
because it was everywhere i mean at
least on my timeline
and try try typing into the search bar
hashtag
myth kids uh-huh and then maybe set it
to photos
uh-huh we basically have like probably
over 100 children now
uh all of us all five of us
combinations of um
of well everyone there's a lot of
combinations with you and and other
girls from whole live english
yeah you are a very popular choice
especially like you and callie that is
i've seen a lot of you with county inna
mori inaudible
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah i think that's uh
fun cute what do you think
interesting question are you looking for
it no not right now you should hijack
myth kids
i'm scared too maybe after the stream
okay i'm surprised you didn't see
anything until now
what i did not start this i just i just
i just put some
some wood into the fire that's all i did
oh let me i want i want to find a proper
inaumori
let's see
[Music]
[Laughter]
so excited no actually i'm not it should
obviously
obviously be takamori and just is wrong
every
every other couple with cali is wrong
and
i normally would go mad about it but i
know everyone's just joking right they
they know that the real
real couple is takamori right
all right all right all right
thank you okay thank you
thank you for uh it really wasn't that
bad
i guess in the end it wasn't too bad
it was pretty i liked it
did you like it chad of course you did
of course you did oh they love it
that's not that choice they all sing yes
in the chat all of them
oh yeah yeah yeah that is 100 yes
i like how we all connected through this
movie we all
we all have one opinion it's like we
became one you know
wait this is where i add subtitles to my
to my uh
stream go inna
wow great moving i genuinely liked it
but i don't know why everyone's so bad
thank you for watching with me
thanks for watching
did you say i love you no i said thank
you
okay i mean excuse me you're the one
going about
oh come on
[Music]
i saw that wink
important
venus i'm gonna i'm gonna talk to you
after this team here
i would love to talk to you after this
stream let's talk let's talk about
stuff
looking forward to it
okay do you have another outfit
we i really really really
really really really like you
yeah i like how you
change from love to like i see how it is
so quick not even a minute
i'm going to misunderstand yeah yeah
yeah yeah
no no but only announcement really is
once again to go back to to connect this
hall to the beginning but
congratulations to both of us and one
million yeah all right i got the thing
yeah and i'm looking forward to your
original song
no i'm working on it
working on it okay okay okay okay
thanks for coming to watch everyone i
hope you guys enjoyed the movie
and our commentary that was very obvious
i did yeah
[Laughter]
all right um yeah i guess i guess
we'll open it up here yeah
let's collab again sometime we can play
game two
or we can draw together yeah whatever
you're up i'd collect
because now i got my cintiq 22 hd yeah
is that the one i got yes you got the
ponytail yes okay
[Laughter]
okay okay okay until next time kiara
thank you austria i'll feed us in
that's how i remember it i'll feed us in
oh
you pronounced it pretty well i'll feed
you soon
oh it's pretty good i'll feed us in
okay anything that's made out of
buffaloes
that's what i thought actually these are
following near my house and they were
like i was like
buffalos have wings
um okay okay bye-bye
[Music]
bye-bye
you