[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
forever
[Music]
his tails are so cute
oh God
[Music]
my arms
can you touch your toes
can someone like push my back okay
[Music]
thank you costume that we had to put on
hey
cute cats wait
come on
I should slap you
screaming
yes
[Music]
you know I should slap you something
funny
I got an email about this a viewer won a
special ticket to record a live stream
and performance yeah wow
you guys must have missed the memo what
the heck
I wasn't tagged I was not tagged I can
tell you that I checked my tags every
five minutes saw nothing maybe they
forgot to listen to you guys or
something hmm okay I'm not against it
whatever just behave yourself okay
leave yourself
yeah don't be weird
[Music]
say that again
what's your name
uh-huh that's a really complicated name
you got there beginning Chad is that
your name chat dad
what are you today
oh I guess I guess they're already
recording the stream so we're live
hi all right everyone hi it's like an
exclusive oh God
[Music]
cute
yeah Welcome to our backstage for our
live stream performance we're doing this
a lot of performance today
a little
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
special day
[Music]
I can't two two
okay
yeah
happy birthday
hold on a second girl I should slap you
there's always been a hentai Among Us
[Music]
shark
s
[Music]
because the chat we don't know where the
chat is looking at either
um
[Music]
you're special
you're special for being in here
[Music]
you should be grateful Head Pass from
Pinkie Pie something don't behave
okay
I'll kick you out door's right over
there
I'm the bouncer we're just Parts we're
just setting the boundaries here
I'm always beating up you guys
oh well
experiment
well my cat is in the backstage room as
well
um
excuse me
okay actually this person this is
Jefferson is the first person to see us
in these cute out fits right oh yeah
that actually scared me
I mean this is your selfie
we all got them check it
yeah I can't really do that normally so
now I can't
wow it feels nice oh I just noticed the
taco you got a little taco right there
you know
wow
[Laughter]
yeah I know yeah everyone knows
yeah everybody's got a little ones right
here
yeah cool wow
[Music]
enough
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
I wonder
yeah
I thought you were good you promised
some new moves yeah of course well uh
are we doing this in a circle so that
this track person can be in the middle I
think we'll be over here like in a line
and then you could be somewhere where we
can see you
oh sure
I see you I can see you over there okay
yeah okay
okay
[Music]
I don't wanna I don't want to just
practice dance moves though we should
make it into a game
making a new game for us sure as if as
if life is not already enough of a game
you want to play more games in here all
right well you know it is important for
gamers for yeah
it's only be cute but it's also
important to follow instructions
correctly are you able to get up girls
[Music]
sometimes
you should it should be always that's
the right answer always yes yes
[Music]
I have a little game
there's a game
Chihuahua says
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
the original is Chihuahua says Simon
says it's just you know a copy naturally
naturally I will do some poses and then
you girls
should uh copy them but only if I say
kiwawa says Okay
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah okay three two one kiwawa says put
your hands on your hips
uh-huh
okay I kind of wish you had music
oh yeah
turn on some music bass boosted
Chihuahua says Whoa and sway your hips
from left to the right left to right
left to right left to right
it can't be right to left yeah
I did not say cabbage
um
[Music]
questions
we have your right hand touch your head
oh we're still doing that okay
[Music]
with your left hand touch your head
oh okay mama says touch both of your
knees
wow
here we're here
touch your knees and stop swaying yeah
okay koala says
Put Your Hands Up In Me in the air yeah
[Music]
lift one leg the left leg lift left leg
put it down again
wait ah
Cali didn't
[Music]
that's it
come on
listen to our chat yeah
everyone's out
very fast
[Music]
turn around
nice
[Music]
thank you mama says uh move your butt
towards the chat
what the heck
that's a little [\h__\h] up Kiara okay
it's cute it's cute you always says turn
around with your upper body only your
upper body
oh
wait I can participate
[Music]
to France again
Chad is a little too blessed today
[Music]
yeah
hi I'm not cheating
[Music]
oh wait did wait what I didn't I'm in
here
all right all right I'll sit on the
couch then okay
[Music]
a dip
yeah yeah this is a dab right this is
what that looks like to the other side
your face with your hands
like this
yeah straight out your hands to the
front
um
[Music]
squat
oh Lord heck yeah though I love squats
stand up again
[Music]
sit down completely
oh God you're gonna [\h__\h] on my
calibration 3D
[Music]
looking for the trains and
yeah but if you score it like right here
[Music]
thank you
is this like your face
all right thank you
she wins because of her extraordinary
endurance why a plus Applause
[Music]
amazing thanks for supporting me thank
you for the win a workout I'm impressed
yeah
should I help you I'll help you oh yeah
yeah if you want to thanks man hold on
oh God I might just need this myself
let me just recalibrate myself
and I can actually actually lift your
Ribbon this is amazing
which means I can also lift your skirts
don't do that Kiara
dude
[Music]
let's go
oh God I don't want to see that
there's nothing important
I'd like if I could wait but I can't
I don't know uh
you're welcome yeah
[Music]
the floor
whoa oh God
[Music]
you can't do that
okay
it doesn't work
we're chasing her like a zombie we're
like uh
[Music]
Kiara
yeah
there's no bullying here in whole life
no no
[Music]
it says Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Binks
[Applause]
so look for the outside look at the
mirror
oh my God whoa we caught you all right
[Music]
yeah
without any function of your arms or
legs
I mean it's cool but at the same time
what can we do to them when they're in
there
force them to watch his Goons
foreign
is
[Music]
oh it's like a fish we swim and they eat
their own
um
[Music]
oh these are nostalgic
yes
[Music]
later
what is that
what is that thing okay
young lady
[Laughter]
you want to come a little closer and say
that here
you want some of this
okay
all right now be real quiet and don't
scream okay because really we really
can't have the police involved here okay
there you go see it doesn't hurt that
much
Ah that's cute
they look a little embarrassed you'll be
fine don't worry if your face starts
swelling and your lips get really big
like Kim Kardashian that's normal
it's like the Kim Kardashian challenge
but uneasy mode you know
get that Tick Tock Cloud you know good
luck again
[Music]
[Laughter]
needs the injection probably because I
I've been nerfed terribly please please
on nerve my butt all right you got it
thank me later oh
God never mind I'm putting it away geez
back to the freaking head how's my
button let's try this at home kids get a
chance
[Music]
just chill
oh she can reach I'm so small today
um why are you so small today
whoa you guys look weird
[Laughter]
maybe we should compare our highlight
could have said line up from Thomas
let's see yeah
[Music]
no no it's it's Canada
no it's not you're getting on your tippy
toes you stop that
yeah
but if we both were to say
[Music]
okay
thank you the Justice once I'll let it
go
excuse me anymore
you guys keep going I just gotta check
something
okay we're like we're like a rainbow
she's gone yeah
people are always surprised by like how
tall Ina actually is oh is that an inner
hug
O's not tall he's short what do you mean
she's decently tall
[Music]
look
yeah they're all pretty much the same
people you know
[Music]
you know they can do like ocean cameras
they can like clip oh yeah only they're
all she's into one video because if you
just watched it might be hard to find
you yeah like just like a game
all over the place
we're here now we're here now we're here
oh God
is so much more complicated Kiara
they're trying their best oh I'm not
here I'm not here
oh oh my God what is that password
oh look at that yeah
[Music]
oh wow that's a tomato hey
Dura tomato
oh I can't he just hits me
oh oh I'm playing around hello
I'm sure don't be a dick
entertain me
I live in such a small house Chad don't
you guys have anything no anything to
say for yourselves huh where's the money
oh they do this time
what didn't they do
all right
oh yeah what was that huh we talked
about it
is
decided to ignore me but I'll go ahead
and explain it again
[Music]
I'm just pulling your legs so this is an
idea that we had for a stream before
right and I'm just now remembering
oh
chicken legs
do you want to get beat up
oh God what are you doing over there
yeah
wow what take a shower stealing it's
sharks they're spitting in a chat oh no
hey
there it's truth or dare
no oh God can you please not get that on
me please girl yeah I found it wow first
Cali
but
[Music]
Take Me Out to the Ball Game if we don't
win I'll be everybody with this crowbar
and then you chat cause it's one two
three strikes you're out at the old wow
all right
I'm sorry did I hurt you are you okay I
really didn't die I'm sorry I just I'm a
Reaper so it's kind of you're still
alive
sorry about that
really but I hope you're okay
are you good see I just Pat you up a
little bit you'll be fine okay what a
treat
all right okay
[Music]
I choose
oh foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
pink
[Music]
uh because you were confess confess
that was a prank though it was a prank
no no it was real but if you're a sad
you didn't pick her
no it was real okay
never mind
it's hard to explain
is
quiet B Mori huh what you do
will you give me the honor of hold on
hold on you have to go on your knee
um
hold on I didn't sign up for a bonk hold
on a second
um will you do the honor
my Oshie
put a ring on it
it's not the same thing
yes I do
thank you
[Music]
thank you happiness
I'll get it
he's in Vegas yeah we gotta keep it a
secret no one else can family
yeah
everybody else you forget that or this
will return okay
we're good we're good
hey nice have to pick somebody of me
[Music]
okay
I think it should reset hopefully soon I
think it takes a little bit of time
maybe one two three four five okay
oh boy that's perfect promise
yeah okay right here oh yeah
all right let me see
all right let's get you over I mean time
to diagnose chat doctors is Chad going
to be okay
to say this
a severe detriment
yes please look at our x-rays over here
this is uh our nurse Cali who's gonna uh
this is Kelly here
all right so it looks like we've got um
this is the this is Chad
they have um accurate issue going on
right now I think they have a they have
a jelly body
the jelly buddy yeah
they've got non-existence let me see
that thing
um let me see that thing
and also their hands
okay we definitely have to get you
vaccinated okay just uh turn around
quickly for me
[Laughter]
you should yeah that does not look else
no joke no how how long do they have to
live doctor
you guys
until tomorrow
ever
today
[Music]
arriving in their Lane yeah
all right all right
[Music]
all right let's see what you got oh
but you don't have to
uh-huh can you reset it
nice
you just leave it there I'll pick it up
and then put it down
oh I don't need to water break
oh yeah stay hydrated guys oh yeah true
we'll do
it's still doctor oh nothing could reset
oh nice
to chat hello easy
[Music]
chat
um
okay well I didn't think I would say
this today but now you're making me say
you're just kind of I mean I don't I
didn't know
I didn't really want to do this while
everybody else was around it's kind of
weird you know I wanted this to be alone
maybe okay we can just think that we're
alone okay just just act as you and me
and me and you
um so actually for a while I've been
thinking that uh
they love you
I love you
oh go for kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
[Music]
oh my God what is that
what I didn't see anything they don't
see anything I saw it I saw Applejacks
[Music]
I'm sorry oh those are gross and they're
soggy yeah
cereal Applejacks dictionary now
oh yeah together with milk yeah there's
this more back here too it's all blank
if you guys want to step back here
there's another board some area to draw
hi oh by the way next
oh yeah it's gonna start I almost forgot
everybody
girls there is
put it back in first and then put it
back in first
all right maybe try taking it out now
oh cute oh
[Music]
yeah can you do it a little tricky guys
okay
you could squish I got you girl we are
oddly eye to please be my arms somebody
comes in my arms yes yes hello
I love
oops wait wait wait okay yes hello hello
Chad oh
I wish I was a challenge squishy where
you're so short yeah
oh you're so cute
[Music]
[Laughter]
their phone alarm their voicemail their
car is gonna say it now yeah they're
called their notifications
[Music]
oh
so what else did we do before we start
oh yeah our performance actually is is
gonna we have 15 minutes until
performance so
yeah I totally forgot
[Music]
please turn back for us
in that time
time I'll take her please
blue
[Music]
oh how should we practice that's a good
question uh
hmm do you have any ideas
well it looks like since we have no
music you're gonna have to sing acapella
for me oh no astute observation that's
true
who should go first yeah
oh I want to hear the singing chops of
uh musical Powerhouse Calliope Mori
yeah all right
so I think we'll stand back here and
Cali because you have the curtain back
there that's a good place for you okay
hold on but I'm missing something
I should have really quick but
[Music]
um
do you vocally warm up
yeah
yes are you supposed to
usually I sing the song like three times
before I record it and I do vocal
warm-ups so that it sounds its best but
okay here we go
steps
[Music]
if you find the note that you're bad
with you got to keep trying to hit it
do you have any requests for songs uh
rap
this is
fine
can't turn back time I'll always be a
prisoner till my ambition has pedals
I'll dance your tune but hold your
breath guest is running the show so come
alive now once again so I can chase you
down we have five seconds away from the
end it's come
from here on out it's only just me and
this Blood last I'd rather just fit away
[Applause]
[Music]
someone else go somebody else
who's gonna go next
something for this
like if somebody else
Google some lyrics up thank you
okay all right
ready to go yeah I'm relatively ready
well okay I mean my my thing these are
always wobbly but I'll try come out
there
[Music]
do do
do do do do do do do let's go back
[Music]
now
foreign
no no
yes
thank you
nice job thank you yeah
you know what I've noticed
three five with all those different
colors we could be like sailor Sailor
Moon Rangers
[Music]
yeah
you're just sailor Cali next
[Music]
Tuesday right next to me now with glue
sticks
I need lyrics
how about your own song
[Music]
yeah yeah
huh
[Music]
five minutes what the [\h__\h] it's enough
time lyrics
I'm gonna drink something no you're fine
that's okay we listen you probably had
to listen to your own voice when I have
to I also never remember my own songs
lyrics so that's why I chose
yeah it was like
[Music]
um
nothing
[Music]
okay
yeah yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
foreign
how many times
[Music]
that was fun yeah heck yeah it was
really fun good job ladies
every song but the one that we are going
to perform
[Music]
oh no
it's fine
we have one last thing images
[Music]
pick a memory that that really stood out
to you
so there's a lot of koala on here
I think it's pretty obvious though
what cute
I think it's pretty obvious our our off
color my favorite yeah that's the best
favorite one
and finally I see you guys
[Music]
oh you can pick them yeah that's a good
one yeah
[Music]
yeah everything
do we quickly talk about this one yeah
sure
yes what cute I chose this one because
um yeah I I wanted to do like a dance
school kind of thing because I thought
it would be fun to teach everyone some
choreographies because I I have so many
choreographies in my head and I just
need to let them out it's been so long
even though it was really exhausting and
a little bit scuffed I'm glad everyone
participated in although is that yeah
that's cool that's from like the that's
from the dance school right yeah yeah so
yeah
did I do two yeah yeah with all of us
thank you yeah
oh sorry
who wants to talk about their memories
I'll go next Circle
here I am
do you need someone to help you oh I'm
okay I'm good thank you
um I really like myth Retreat because I
really love writing songs with you guys
and hearing you guys's voices over
things that I wrote made me really happy
even if it was a silly a silly little
Halloween song it it made me really
happy it made me want to do more things
like that and seeing the 3D MV was so
cool too and and it isn't a dream come
true yeah so I hope you get to collab on
more creative stuff like this together
yeah yeah we like put together pretty
last minute too everyone just said oh
yes
[Laughter]
yeah
last minute
but sometimes it helps with the
creativity yeah
how about you mine is you know when we
finally all got to off collab you know I
remember I mean I had a little bit of a
waterfall you know in the uh the first
year collab and you know before the
second year we finally got to see
everyone it was really pretty memorable
yeah it was really cool yeah and we
could do it again
yeah that'd be cool yeah that's that's a
minus two because it was really fun and
I love this screenshot
this is a screen that started the back
Trend huh
um
[Laughter]
yeah what about you know legs
[Music]
yeah I think I don't know because this
was like the first biggest thing that we
did with Council as well
[Music]
I was one of the few people learned from
a shark
a sexy dance says the Frog will haunt my
neighbors forever and the rest of
Eternity oh my gosh no you're a cute
anime girl now come on
and
gorillas
[Music]
[Laughter]
friendship which smells like maybe not
friendship but it smells like something
and I Like It Whatever It Is
um memories
[Music]
now it's time for us to go to prayer for
the performance
okay are you guys excited you guys over
there
yeah
see you soon
[Music]
okay I gotta go bye
okay
[Music]
oh I went to the wrong door oh dear okay
stages this way
and
[Music]
let's go
together
[Music]
hey hey hey
everybody
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
take it away
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
you are
[Music]
thanks for supporting us with us thank
you
[Music]
seriously thank you so much
don't cry no I'm not tired wow
that's so nice
went by super fast like super super fast
crazy to look back it's already been two
years
[Music]
but I think it was fun like I think
I didn't think I would be like in the
beginning I didn't think I would stream
so much and I didn't think I would be
here for two years
I think I think I was like okay free
streams uh per week all right uh if I
think I can do that free streams and now
I'm doing like million streams per week
[Music]
every day is like you know it goes by in
an instant it's like a blink of an eye
and then next day next day and suddenly
yeah it was just one year anniversary
yesterday but suddenly today is three
year anniversary one yeah
when you're busy busy
yeah
we got to try a lot of new things
I'm sorry I should put my phone on
silent
that's okay
[Music]
I'll put it away I wonder if that means
it's time
uh these times
foreign
could it be
let me make sure let me just double
check that it's time to ask the
bartender
I wonder could it be what could it be
well everybody
I mean maybe I hope they expected it
I hope something good something good
always something you like it you're my
viewer if you don't know what to expect
with the merch could you really call
yourself that you should know by now
he be trained well by now aren't you why
are you moving up or am I moving down
[Music]
my back I'll be right back
uh which one who wants to take which one
we're doing these first yeah
this one
because yes
don't show don't show that one yet Kiara
maybe we should maybe we should go one
at a time
okay okay nice idea
presenting uh that one oh that one has
everything on it so I should go oh okay
that one first okay Ena goes first make
sure you show them okay and I'll show
the back
okay okay ready we're gonna go yeah yeah
go
okay
it's okay yeah no speed race Circle
attack
look we have our second year I don't
know if they can see it anniversary
Goods
[Music]
yeah
are we so cute
outfit same outfit
oh yeah they're going to be made into
also you can change the order
yeah you can change the order
yeah so you can put your Ocean Center
here yeah very cute oh she sent her
house
number one an idol theme this year
because and we want we want outfits like
that too right outfits oh
clearly
[Music]
yeah
could you get a little closer yeah a
little closer
I think that's good that's good here
also yeah
it's pretty good
thank you
thank you for the cute orange
why don't we get the big one first and
then we'll do the small ones
isn't the big one the one that has all
this one oh yeah this one has everything
so like cool right
should we bring it
yeah get the big one get the big one
okay
just I'll just leave it up here
I mean isn't the big one
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
[Music]
I don't know should we do it again
over here
read it what does it say I actually
can't read it I can't read where am I
let's see
uh acrylic small plushie small plushie
takanashi Kiara small plushie you know
my ears small plushie gargura and small
plushie Watson Amelia yay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh y'all
you can feed them
look at the ears
isn't it cute and I feel like everybody
was waiting for these they're like what
are we gonna see the small plushies
finally they're here
they're here
your dreams are coming true
you guys made it real
[Music]
them only the website to buy this links
to buy You're Gonna Be Live at the 30
Mark so in about 10 minutes you guys can
take a closer look at these and uh
purchase them even if you'd like so uh
make sure to check it out I think the
links will be down below in the video in
the description
foreign
I get it that's on the back of that one
is there anything on the back of that
one it should be um
[Music]
yeah
okay individual sales two nice
all right is that it get excited guys
yeah
I mean that's it for Merch
right
oh yeah
yeah
anyone else have any yes announcement I
I have one thing
ever before yeah I guess I don't know no
I mean we already know I can do
individual announcements first
yeah
a reminder I had my anniversary stream
yesterday so the people who watched that
already saw that but I have a new song
coming out this Sunday so I want to play
the trailer here if that's okay it's the
new song is called do you do you do you
do you want to see it yes yes yes I do
do you
[Music]
I think you guys might be in the way
oh here we go
I didn't see it is it playing somewhere
[Music]
super sneaky
I'm not in control of obese at the
moment it's out of control
but you guys can check it out do you
I've seen the well you know I've seen
some of it yeah yeah it's really cool
you guys should watch it yeah
it's coming out again which date I think
it's it's things it's the 18th it's
Sunday and the it's not perfect my first
ever 3D music video but it's not just
you know there's um a quite a lot of
special things about it you will notice
immediately when you watch it so look
forward to it cool
[Music]
heck yeah looking forward to it yeah
all right well
um I have a little announcement if you
guys didn't see I just uploaded a cover
to my channel I hope you guys will check
it out I seriously sing in that song
um and I tried my best so
thank you
Suzuki from a one-piece film red I hope
you guys will enjoy it if you'd like it
please check it out that's all I have to
say
[Music]
I'm celebrating
I'm celebrating my anniversary tomorrow
yeah
tomorrow yes so I'll help I'll help if
you guys are free you can come hang out
yeah
I'll be there I want to see you
good uh what about you put it down put
it down I'm trying I'm done
anniversary stream tomorrow as well and
I have a lot of pretty
well I have big announcements coming
this week it might be pretty big for
guambo so we're gonna Escape what I'll
announce it as we go baby wow
[Music]
my anniversary stream that's gonna be
the day after tomorrow uh and it's gonna
I have a small announcement it's not
anything big but just a small
announcement yeah so it's the day after
tomorrow
looking forward to it
anything else what yeah
no
except the other thing the other thing
well maybe I should just maybe I should
just press the button hope it works this
time
all right one more thing
yeah here we go
is it working
here
dance
[Music]
they don't know what that is but now I
see what I did wrong there we go
[Music]
you can't see [\h__\h]
okay okay
let's do it again okay again
foreign
[Music]
I think it's pretty red it's called
non-fiction look forward to it
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah can we play mine again yeah yeah
sure okay
[Music]
does that have any meaning am I gonna be
cloned is that like some kind of
sure
yeah
exciting who else do you do you know but
yeah thank you again
yeah okay that was yeah but more
important was was the other trailer
obviously I would be called they're both
important
yeah important and I hope you guys are
checking out yeah enjoy enjoy yes
musical stuff going on enjoy
yeah we are singers after well I mean
they got singers
I tried something close to Idols
we're something like Idols but uh thank
you for the many many incredible
supporting comments to our wonderful
fans all over the world you guys are the
best thank you so much love you thank
you
[Music]
another thing we do would be possible
without you guys so thank you thank you
yeah
[Music]
yeah thank you guys for trusting in me
it turns out looking pretty good
hopefully so thank you
and thank you so much to preach you as
well for the models
again
lightning fast
and you know things
for such an amazing year yeah yeah
let's have an even better here yeah yeah
I look forward to I think um
[Music]
third year is the charm I'm telling you
I swear
if not I'm gonna rage quit that's so
funny you too no don't break anything
this is please I'm gonna flip the
freaking table
out
there is something under the table
that's a nice relaxing music so we can
just relax
[Music]
a huge time crunch I think if you guys
just want to spend a few extra minutes
maybe answering some questions from chat
or something like that I'm just gonna
sit on the say goodbye I'm just gonna
sit on the air take a break yeah I'll
sit on the beach I was planning to sit
on the edge of the stage because it's
like close to the the oh [\h__\h] like
View
yeah oh and not here just just cover it
just cover it hi what'd you guys think
of the stream how was the 360 thing is
it is it a kind of cool to watch and
then I gotta fix something did it work
well
yeah did it works
I love your favorite member we're able
to look at them at all times yeah look
at your ocean here it's cool so cool
really okay
I can't wait to see it me too I can't
wait to watch the video look around
yeah I'm glad you I'm glad you can do
this
if you guys have any questions for us we
can read them out gonna has a chat I
have a chat I think Cali's yeah we can
also talk about some more of the
memories that we didn't talk about oh
yeah bring some bring some out that's a
nice idea so cool in VR oh yeah it's
immersive huh
the one of us
welcome oh
um hold on I'll go check
you too can be a kawaii Idol I believe
in you
promise me you will or if you don't want
to be an idol that's cool too just
promise me that you'll
supporting us yeah
hey Nina
no we work here
questions
hi oh my God I want to get a picture or
something hold on oh yeah
why it's nice
idle Tales getting in the way
a picture from my perspective
oh
man I just couldn't what all the bing
bang
oh yeah
God I want to sell the Rubik's Cube or
something a puzzle Rubik's Cube was it
is
yeah group is nice you're gonna pull
them apart okay sure they're just stick
them back together really that's not how
you're supposed to do it you can paint
them though you know modern problems
are even more complicated yeah it's true
oh yeah by the way guys uh so there will
be a HD re-upload of this stream if you
guys want to experience it in VR because
we're streaming so it's kind of like a
you know it's called the bitrate and it
gets a little fuzzy and a little crunchy
sometimes but it's gonna be uploaded it
was gonna be in 4k but uh I had an issue
with recordings but it is going to be in
2K so that I mean that's still pretty
good
yeah this feel really good
I mean half of 4K is still really nice
you know yeah yeah let's go yeah
definitely I'm looking forward
yeah but this will be difficult to top
next year
so yeah it's like brainstorming for
ideas I was like yeah this this is good
to top it but we make it really
difficult for ourselves yeah for
ourselves like this all right we just
gotta do um
yeah whole dance yeah we should do it in
Japan with our actual yeah actual
parties
it's like we're evolving like Pokemon
the first year this year we're low poly
models next year will be full 3d I hope
exactly
yeah and then in 4k obviously then in 4k
right right that's important
feedback time baby yes
that would be crazy some people do
something literature is coming
yeah wouldn't be surprised that is true
that's part of the reason why I wanted
to try this stream like it's something
that I don't think a lot of people have
tried like in terms of v-tubing see I
definitely thought it'd be good to
experiment a little bit even though it's
it's kind of scary because I was like
thinking uh maybe it's gonna fail maybe
it's gonna look like super shitty or
something but it seems like you guys
enjoyed it I hope anyways we had fun
right I think it was worth it for sure
oh I do yeah you do apparently you can
watch the stream on the switch and you
can like move around there
[Music]
on a 3DS what about a 3DS oh I don't
know does 3DS have motion controls like
you can move it around
surprisingly many things
like a technical chat and that's about
it that was the coolest thing when
picture chat came out
collab
online
I was just playing with myself I thought
it was the only one who drew
masterpieces on my own it's a local
thing but sometimes you can play with
randos
ah
come here our friends we should collab
with it sometime
can we just Boop people on the news
um
[Music]
right well I'm gonna put on your suit
like after you got out of it so I got to
smell like both of your smells combined
oh God
[Music]
you all saw me dancing for like 10 hours
you can just spray some Febreze of
perfume on it and then it's just it's
perfume with sweat
I put it in the washer it's it's yeah
it's clean now
my goodness for that
although like right after we did the
mocap stuff like we had to travel so it
was sitting in my room for a little
while and when I got home
[Music]
it's not your fault I should have washed
it sooner I'm just leaving it
growing a child in there so
what what nothing nothing they didn't
say anything let me get some water
yeah
let's answer some questions from the
chat but the chat is moving so fast I
don't really see too many questions or
you guys this passion is awesome
there's something funny
what does Ina smell like
Tina smells good you know smells good
because yeah there's a part where I just
want to help her get in the suit yeah
yeah no yeah
she just was sweating at one time
is like
the scent memory you guys have of me is
that I was thinking because I think it's
overwhelmingly you smell fine not for
the rest of the trip
yeah I mean it was pretty hot so it
can't be happening yeah
good I never was able to say
that or I think that you told me about
that the remaining hat was not my hat I
had all my hats with me when I came back
so no that was your test and no no it
wasn't I had all my hats what kind of
hat was it you gave it to me you were
like this hat is too small I bought it
and it was too small remember you were
like oh I went to the Target or whatever
and you like you you said you went to
the kids section
huh
yeah she's still in the merchandise now
oh yeah yeah
screen Chuck the merch truck buyer merch
the other um day when I was on a
vacation in Italy I saw like airplanes
flying by with advertisements
unfortunately this wasn't Italian but
I've never seen something like that
before like an airplane advertisement it
was like it happened
all over the world
what are the airplanes before
and then and then we all get on a
shinkansen like a shinkansen Holo Ian
print or something like that
for the bullet trains
Hello Kitty and then the inside is theme
too with all of us and the chairs are
different colors I don't know we sell
sweets related to Holy hands
yeah yeah that's it okay yeah that works
probably all scene so far like
um fans putting us on like buses
full like it's been two years but still
like when I hear stuff like that really
you saw one today
in person with all of us
um
[Music]
thank you it's in the attacks actually
you should be able to find it I was able
to [\h__\h] it yeah
which tags nice
the r tag yeah I think oh yeah all of
our ice cream cones
I think it was an artist
[Music]
recently there was like they made like
tuk-tuks with with my advertisement you
know what tuk-tuks are they're like
they're kind of like friends yeah
I thought you were saying like don't
talk weird or something
it made you a special place
give me that damn thing
algorithm
oh yeah because I know because those
yeah yeah kiddo was sitting on the couch
like browsing on Instagram
the superior algorithm
yeah yeah cause I remember you telling
me like your algorithm you see like
weird animal stuff I don't see stuff
like that when I'm scrolling I see cute
videos I see a lot of this ones I get a
lot of fashion
[Music]
that's a good idea how do we even get
like hard data like how do we even show
that on stream
[Music]
yeah no thanks
that happens one thing that's in
everybody's algorithms is good as a
Japanese Duolingo streams
to this day
the legendary
pushing it hard YouTube there's a few
streams like that that I always see like
recommended yeah
I feel like one of my asmr's in there
yeah oh yeah yeah
[Music]
the spa isn't even a good ASMR spa day
ASMR yeah
ASMR I mean yeah the algorithm YouTube
does it
that's funny I wonder why
[Music]
because the viewers that lucky is
somebody
ah what if we did a oh this is kind of
like ASMR because you see what's gonna
happen is on the re-upload guys there's
gonna be like spatial audio so uh this
is the front so you're looking towards
the front so this is gonna be on your
right and this is the left so when you
guys are re-watching this upload you
know will be
cloudy
hi can you hear me
and then I'll be in the front yay front
audio
thank goodness
um
[Music]
you should go to yourself yeah oh yeah
you should replace somebody's head here
I'll do it for you wait oh oh God I
can't reach
come back there
where are you I'm right here
oh lordy
hello
grow up big face
yeah yeah
your head is
very little
yeah it's a little on my skirt hold on
this is a bit hard to it's on the larger
size all right it's fine yeah Monument
oh sorry I grew grounded by accident I
wasn't trying to it's just
um
okay that Ted's gonna be like where is
where is this version of the merch
this is the one they really won I just
stand up because if I sit extra big
anime
oh you're there my head
[Laughter]
I think
oh no now it now it's not worse now
we're not in the scene
that's a good try okay
yeah
I like this movement
what do you guys uh
uh after this I already ate I ate pizza
and now I'm gonna go sleep oh yeah
[Music]
I should get a salad
Pepsi yeah
Pepsi Pepsi Zero whatever it's called
gonna get some sleep first sleep is
important yeah sleep is good sleep is
good
[Music]
can I do it
it's pretty urgent but yeah okay thank
you yeah because I I recorded like two
others three other things I think so my
voice is a little good taking that first
rest it yeah yeah I'll get it done
though
yeah we'll do what it could be so
urgent well you know as we said before
myth always seems to do things last
minute but it always turns out pretty
good yes
that's true that's a good point
yeah
okay can you can we can we make one
promise to each other for the coming
year to get our [\h__\h] together and do
things a bit earlier than we should than
we've done so yes
yes that will save not only us from a
lot of stress but also the staff members
that we work with the producers
everybody everybody will be very
thankful to us if we just decide to make
up our minds earlier
[Music]
other people
sometimes the thing that we can do is
that we try to improve ourselves and
because if we don't then why would other
people approve themselves you know
that's a good point let's work hard
let's work hard fight God
[Music]
yeah like she's a dinosaur
[Laughter]
or maybe you could do like one of those
things where we're like we're on the
floor and then somebody gets like on
tapio like on like something on my bag
[Music]
I'm comfy
the family picture right here
yeah yeah
let me get rid of that though
yeah oh we're gonna put the song in the
background
get rid of that
should get rid of that clean background
I'll put the uh
it's gonna be pretty good yeah it goes
nice nice
[Music]
looking good
yay oh leg
Yeah I love it
kick it girl
nice I feel like I was gonna say
something but no I can't remember what
the heck uh pizza
sounds good right now food yeah I have
some leftover pizza
[Music]
like the one from last year you know
like some so they can take the uh
legendary screenshot
which what did we do last year anything
oh we should just nothing the same thing
but it was just a cute group picture
okay in comparison
yeah we can evolve yeah
besides that dance
that might be the best we can get from
Kira for now
it's all good so if someone will get a
fantastic screenshot yeah yeah
the balance because I'm a bit of
perfectionist when it comes to this
maybe could I can't come like closer she
looks so tiny
so small closer seeing is believing
um
[Music]
[Applause]
all right closing thoughts cheers
thank you everybody thanks for
everything thank you you're
[Music]
really close
okay
[Music]
yeah this is good all right everybody
thank you for watching for watching
stream I hope you hope you guys enjoyed
it somewhat and the HD version will be
uploaded yeah
promise you look forward to it yeah and
all the announcements that we had today
and not only that but you know going on
to our third year now I hope you guys
continue to look forward to it because
we still have a lot of memories to make
and a lot of games to play and songs to
cover and sing so we still have a lot
left in us and yeah it's all because of
you guys thank you thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]