[Music]
so
do
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow a good morning afternoon evening
good morning
hello
do you want to do an introduction while
checking if everybody's audio is
balanced
sounds good okay let's start with i
don't know
let's start from the top to bottom in in
discord
i'mma hugo amma's not streaming though
hello everybody yes i'm just uh here
playing with everybody in the morning
you know having fun anyway so my name is
amelia watson probably whole life myth
you guys know probably but hello you
sounded really motivated let's go
there i am i thought you were gonna like
quickly transition into some kind of
like
like um
reporting
stance or reporting the
uh the battle
oh kiara's going coming in first oh my
god i'm behind her right behind her oh
no oh my god what's she gonna do right
now
she has a red shell oh no but then in
the very very very back you know has a
blue shell so that's even worse oh my
god fono doesn't even know what to be
number one right now
you'd be pretty good at it too kiara oh
no no i can't only maybe in german in
english i can't think of words so fast
and in german
can we have a preview
yeah
maybe maybe while we're driving then
okay we have something to talk about
then
toronto
german driver
okay so amma's audio was fine i think
next uh fauna
or california today no kawasaki
oh hi
i'm from hollow council and i'm
happy to be here today i haven't played
mario kart in a long time i think we're
all a little rusty yeah
it's been a long time
very rusty yes it always runs in a
little bit
oh wait wait so can you say one more
word i didn't even check the audio yes
one more one oh okay
okay
that should do the trick
next
good morning afternoon
evening oh am i muted uh
no no um on my stream on my sheet okay
there you go hi wait were you muted the
whole time
no it's just just to my end um not on
discord
it's
cause i'm moving my my audio setup so a
wonky i need to set everything back to
normal
hi hi hi live
you know my innerness from how live
english
hey
nice to meet you safe traveler stay
driving
i'm taking that as a promise i'm writing
that down you heard it here nina's gonna
be safe driving
driving yeah it doesn't mean i'll be
slow
yeah hopefully limit
[Music]
hello this is my voice i'm always [\h__\h]
at mario kart hopefully
the
advantage of
you know all the roads being
new will be a disadvantage to all of us
yeah i've never i've never played the uh
new uh yeah did anyone anybody kiss them
did someone test someone no
i don't even know what they are to be
honest
okay
uh also sorry last time we wanted to
stream this
had a little incident but here we are
thank you thank you girls for
rescheduling
[Music]
you know phoenix sometimes catches on
fire it's just everyday and stuff yeah
uh watch out for the hair you know
look even in the world here you are
having so much distance from me because
you're scared that i'll catch on fire
again
i don't like the heat
sorry
it reminds me of the time off during the
off cliff camera
was that on fire i guess
when we were waiting for uh
the ride and then it says no smoking
else
[Laughter]
i don't smoke what do you mean
and she just repeats herself no smoking
piano i'm like okay it's so so what what
i don't smoke creamy
i couldn't i couldn't get myself to
finish you know finish looking hot
smoking
you lick your finger and you put it on
them and you go it's
oh
oh you should have done that
oh yeah
how do we how do we i think wait it's
it's funny that's right
yeah yeah are we ready to go yeah so
everyone who wants to join us so that so
just so that you know like after an hour
you know will leave us but that's where
you guys can join us
do we want computers
yes yes
hard computers yes yes
how do i turn on tilt controls
you have the wheel
did they even have that for the switch
a wheel i don't think so oh
oh
okay so is this the new stuff
oh is there only four new tracks or
no it's gonna be like
already in the previous one
is it i think snow land or
oh my god
are we supposed to pick the same one i
think ice cream as long as it's like
woman
we think alike
i like the penguin
i was gonna go for the penguin but then
i saw the ice cream
i'm done we're gonna have enough time to
try them all i'm sure
um
yeah
is this one like a oh is it just like
sweets themed there's like a diner
yeah oh that's so cute
let me remember how to play this
let's go
oh the track map itself looks simple
oh there was an item there
oh it's a helicopter landing
what the [\h__\h]
oh
oh this is rough
yeah if you hit the rail in the middle
of the stairs it like
oozes
[Music]
what no
oh
chocolate wait
[Music]
oh it is yeah
nice
[Music]
okay it's okay i can make it ring
i'm too bad i have to turn my stream off
i can't be documenting i'm coming for
you
oh who's the other bullet
are we fine
get out of the way
i don't want to hurt you
yeah don't worry i'm going oh
[Music]
it's a bit misleading there isn't it
oh there we go
it's okay guys i beat the cpu
oh no you're already finished
[Music]
don't worry guys
all
look at julina winning
the [\h__\h]
yeah it's muscle memory
practiced too much
in like long time ago it's just in your
hands i've had this long time too
me and fun i really want the penguin
[Music]
[Applause]
no no
no no no no no no no no no no
somebody remade that video with um
my with my chicken mascots you know
it's so funny
[Music]
so dramatic then maybe i if you know the
new meme video
you know what i'm talking about
hello
what's it from is it pink
yeah yeah it's like a children's show
yeah it's like stock
yeah it is stop-motion
oh it's clear
here
when i was a child i watched that
me too
ow
the penguins hurt ice ice places are my
territory
i feel right at home hi kara hi
[Applause]
you shot that at me didn't you
no just saying hi oh hey what happened
what do you mean
[Music]
what have you girls been doing today so
far
uh
moving furniture yeah you're not busy
how's it going yeah did you break some
fingers yet or get some splinters yet
i've been like bumping my head
everywhere oh no oh
can't be helped
[Music]
[Applause]
holy mother
so what were the others doing
sleeping probably
yeah
[Music]
i did a lot of stuff today too
oh what to do ah
all kinds of things a secret top secret
oh
that just makes me wanna know even more
[Music]
he doesn't deserve it
oh i did not practice mario kart all day
no no no no time for that
ah god damn it okay but better than
before better than nine for whatever
okay
i wanna go visit
bales
let's go to
australia i want new york have you guys
ever been to australia
no no no oh man
it is far it is foreign
i guess it depends where you are it's a
long flight it's far from like
everywhere yeah
so isolated
[Music]
it feels like it should be close to
japan
yeah like the same time zone or like
summer time zones only like yeah
an hour or so
but i know that a lot of japanese
students when they go on
like a school
trip a special one a lot of the um
schools choose
australia because it's relatively close
until
yeah it's really popular
for school trips oh no that's pretty in
here oh it's like in the horizon
that's on your horizon
bouncy house
oh
oh no
recycle your bananas guys
mistakes
inside i'm assuming you guys fell on my
banana i fell on any banana was it your
banana
perhaps
did did your character make the happy
noise like someone fell on their banana
[Applause]
[Music]
what power would you have
um
teleportation for inya
yeah
teleportation so it's easy to get to
places to australia yeah
yeah teleportation will be great
fun i love how you want to fly
i'm in with supplies
oh that's a good one for them
um
but i don't think i really want to talk
to my cats
does it feel like
my cats
what if your cat says something weird to
you though and it changes your
relationship
on no forever just tell me they love me
and i'll tell them i love them
on your food what flying is now flying
is going to pee
i feel like fine won't be scary what if
you like
bump into birds
like elijah and minecraft you wouldn't
want to bump into me huh
yeah kiara you're on fire you know fire
in the sky you know what
no noise
normally causing traffic air traffic
you know problems
i'll take videos of you and post it as a
ufo if you're like is that a bird is
that a plant oh it is bird
i fly with my cape like uh oh okay like
a superhero
yeah
oh i don't know what i should have
like i i like the idea of flying which i
can totally already do but
hmm
since i'm already got that i gotta
choose something else what's a cool
skill to have
mind reading yeah
i was just thinking of
a friendship ever again yeah that's the
thing like like
with greg park who's great
responsibility and being able to read
minds
will isolate you
more than ever yeah i don't think i want
that it's like is the difference between
can you control or can you not control
it though it's like trolling is also bad
though
it's like
you you get tempted but
you're always hearing how many like this
like so many people talk i think like
you'll go crazy
[Music]
that's what usually happens in ironies
yeah like edward cullen from twilight
say
i never watched one you guys watched try
on it another one i read the book i did
oh
yeah i read the books
i don't think i watched all the movies
were you girls like really i watched the
movies because my sister your sister
so this is what sydney looks like oh you
heard my cat
um
[Music]
before i thought you're gonna pay for
that
i'm sorry i'm not
not trying to start anything here really
really
i feel like you are
no challenging
challenging me
have a nice drift
where did my double items go what the
[\h__\h]
game is rigged
[Music]
not the bush all right before the end
[Laughter]
yeah i thought it was over too
yeah that was my nina suck it
i swear
i was gonna be first that was the third
place
i was me
i got i got bumped so hard the game
crashed you know
or the communication
i think i think everyone yeah we have to
redo this match
can maybe animate the room because she
doesn't stream anyway so she doesn't
have to worry about the what's being
shown come on on me how do how do i do
it yeah wait
okay i see yeah
yeah
on yeah we need to revive her
okay you guys can join me nice
i'm trying
[Music]
yeah did you guys watch charmed do you
know the show oh yeah i feel like i've
heard about it it was my favorite show
when i was younger it was a it's a show
about three witches and and and one of
them had the power of healing one of
them had the power of like moving
things one of them had the power of i
think teleportation yeah
yeah i wanted to be like them
i wanted to feel like though i want to
be a wish
but parts of the show were kind of
cringy because there was like this one
one of the girls had like this hot
affair throughout the whole series with
this hot demon
spicy spicy very spicy indeed yeah
what's it
they all have names starting with
crew pipers
books or something like
always in the library there's like five
billion of them oh yeah they have books
too yeah
yeah just so there's three of them and
all their names start with p yeah phoebe
piper
there used to be only three but then at
some point uh one got like replaced in
the show
so that's why those four names
yeah
yeah hot hot witches um
is that what you're watching right now
no but i bought like the box set the
whole box set of all
yeah because they there's no way of
watching it's anywhere online like no no
no service shows it
streams it so i was forced to
buy dvds in this day and age
i don't even have like
playstation playstation playstations
playstation i haven't even
that's what i'll be using
that's true
it's like like my dvds and blu-rays but
i like rarely watch them these days
i like that i have it and i own it i can
watch it anytime i want yeah then i
don't
yeah
the only blu-ray that i have is from uh
i think the second or the third
hula fest
because they sent it to me
oh yeah that's true
i don't know where anything is anymore
because everything is in boxes
uh-huh i know how it is it's gonna take
you a while huh to get all of that yeah
outside okay cause i got i got my family
they'll make sure that i don't
oh i don't blaze off and that's not for
months yeah last time i moved it took me
like
six months or so until i finally
had
most of my boxes empty but then there
was still like two or three boxes
who which were still like boxes after a
year
yeah
which shows you how much you actually
need what's in there so
throw it away
i don't need
much like i literally just have like a
temporary mattress behind me that's what
i've been sleeping
but other than that i've been i've been
living pretty fun and honestly like as
long as you know you can cook for
yourself and there's a roof and
how dead is phone actually she says we
can go on she doesn't know when it's
coming back
yeah i feel like maybe her internet just
died died
how long
should we just do a race right now like
one run race yeah let's do another race
maybe maybe
maybe she'll come back maybe it'll come
back we'll summon her with our driving
skills
i guess
he and law is very strong as usual
it's
down to myth members only now okay
all right you got the wheel okay i
started it
wait wait what is this
uh 150cc
[Music]
why are there teams i see teams no teams
i didn't put teams on i disabled it
oh
yes i'm using tail controls
it turned teams off i thought you had
one job amen
can we still change it
i didn't think so okay
this should be fine
it's just the friendly race
one car new york these two existed
before i know they mixed in
they mixed
the into the cups did they mix old rices
and new maces races
because i see a luigi pinball with
calamari dessert wasn't done there
before
oh no i've never seen them before oh
really yeah
all four on you
pinball
all right
[Music]
steal flags
you'll see the flags behind everyone's
cars but we don't steal them right like
steel
it's like it's like it adds up the
points of each team i love luigi pinball
i think i played that before on gamecube
maybe
on ds
was that you yeah
i was stuck
i was just trying not to hit the wall
it wasn't the end
yeah but today and today i'll bring it
to the gamecube too because then i play
them again
pinball machines so we don't like
literally out run the fall or like
oh
oh no
you guys remember
oh my god oh no
oh come on do you guys remember
the pinball game from windows
oh yeah yeah
pinball
i used to play that a lot did you know
they um don't have it in newer windows
versions nowadays because there were
some troubles with the
permissions with the developer i think
or something like that
real world
i watched this whole
like 20 30 40 minute documentation about
why
the windows pinball game is not in
windows anymore
oh it's so sad
we need you guys ever played the elf
bowling
elf bowling boy
oh yeah i think it was like a it's not
an early laptops it's like this really
shitty 3d elf bowling game oh like elf
elf yeah like like little santa elves oh
oh
maybe if i saw a picture
i'm so bad at this map what the [\h__\h]
what no
the [\h__\h] paintballs
all right i can still make wait all the
blue tea are at the front what
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
where are you ami first place no no i'm
in the second place now the npcs are
doing the hard lifting for ame
i mean i mean
what do you mean
what do you mean what do you mean
[Applause]
can't see the screen
have you guys seen ollie's new outfit
today it's crazy
oh i didn't see it because i just woke
up before the stream oh my god you're
missing out on like a legendary i know
the silhouette looks so cool
she is like a
holy [\h__\h] like i can't even describe
like oh she's dripping she's dripping so
hard
[Laughter]
looks like a pimp or something yeah yeah
yeah
she even has like a lollipop and it
moves with her mouth
[Music]
i didn't expect that like by the drill
hair
you know because of a certain i guess i
don't think that's certainly
[Music]
but no
no no
very unexpected
also those fishnets oh oh yeah
so cool
so good man
i can't wait to see the other whole live
idea second gen outfit
yeah yeah yeah that's i think reynes
oh reina cat i think that was her
silhouette right i am it
i am hi
hi yummy
[Music]
it's not tomorrow i don't know when it's
happening is it tomorrow somebody in the
chat says it's tomorrow tomorrow
i knew that was cold
[Music]
oh you ran into it raining in two days
wait wait don't wait what the
new york why are your roots so confusing
mamma mia
it's not my fault
yeah where does cats take place is it in
new york probably not
new york new york
yeah i think it is in new york
[Music]
we're in cat's territory are the girls
haven't watched a garfield movie
no
not sure if i'm interested
i heard it's really good
it's amazing is it yeah
it's a cat's movie right all cat related
movies are legendary
ten out of ten worth a watch worth two
watches
no i know someone stole my iron oh no
okay it's fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine don't panic enough
okay
i took a shortcut
[Music]
in here
right on the finish line are you guys
first again wow where's ahmed are there
no we're tied we're tired i'm and i are
tired
i want to be tied with um
[Music]
[Laughter]
what i choose this time
is mario circuit really not
it does there is there is a circuit but
different ones
tokyo
is
because um the the ones from the first
dlc are already played but we can play
them too
yeah that was from before it was from
somewhere
i haven't played the first one either
oh there's two waves
and then
i mean so far
none then we're gonna have more and more
i'm wondering when like when if we ever
do like a
whole live english in a d
mario kart or even like you know with
japan japanese members again you know
mario kart tournament
how we would have to
like limit the
the tracks that we would be using
because i i don't think i want to
practice how many are there now
especially if we do it at the end of the
year then there will be
all the dlcs out all of the waves
they come out by then yeah they say by
the end of the year that's the promise
from nintendo and you know nintendo
keeps their promises right
[Music]
so
maybe dlc only tournament
would be fun possible too yeah because
then we don't i mean we've all seen the
the already existing tracks a million
times
so i think pfc only sounds fun
yeah that makes sense
yeah
by the way this track was on the
i think for the first time on the phone
the phone mario cart
ah i put the wrong turn oh no no no i
played that before it was actually
pretty fun
we'll take
oh no i thought it got at me but it
wasn't it wasn't enough
i was holding a shell
[Music]
okay that's fine
oh she's on my team oh that's why i
couldn't for the show
oh
[Music]
stupid stupid isabel undermining my
coolness
all right then i guess i'm gonna play
this mario circuit man
i want to see how is it different is
this looks like this the thumbnail looks
like well i've already played before
i mean there's like which one mario
circuit but like
different my circle that's right
oh yeah i guess so
wait what are you guys picking
my
circuitry from
one of the dlc ones
i can't find it
it's like the third
okay okay yeah okay well you didn't have
to it's okay
[Music]
which one is gonna which
okay
let's go
i feel like fauna is not coming back huh
okay we can pray
maybe maybe a baton ton pass to her that
means when inna leaves after the one
hour then it's the one with being happy
[Music]
i thought we were on the team [\h__\h]
what you're not on my team no uh isabel
uh
either belle would you have a fitting
name for you i feel like a man
what would be a cute name for you isabel
[Music]
maybe a little bit too sophisticated for
you
now anything would be lovely on you ami
isabelle
she just she just compromised my run
if she does that all the time we should
ban her for why did i get hit with the
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it wasn't me but i'm laughing anyway i
was like in fifth place
oh it's cause you're the first of the
blue probably maybe
my team sucks
it's a bill
so
picky i'll get you for that no come get
me come get me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
focus focus comfort don't throw don't
bro
[Music]
i think it doesn't win
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're the same team
i'm colorblind okay phoenixes are
colorblind
is typing
wow
wow we win
[Music]
she's not coming back sorry chad
sorry you have to deal with myth only
hope that's
okay i hope we're good enough for you
chad
he's still with us in spirit
[Music]
and then we at least got to play like
a couple couple weeks definitely
yeah let's play mine
before has to go
okay
the teams don't matter i think we can
just leave that setting yeah
oh wait okay i can turn it off i turned
it off okay okay okay okay
now you can put us all in one team
that's that's fine
oh so we don't hurt each other do it
no teams
not teams
[Music]
right so i guess that did feel like a
different
mario circuit i guess so
kind of hard
i like that one
i didn't play it i feel like i played a
different version of that
okay now you just reminded me of what
that even means oh
calamari
oh is that
character supposed uh some kind of view
is that character or calamari
what
what i got the boost why are you faster
because of the cart or something like
that
[Music]
i didn't get the boost it's fine it's
fine
it's a technical question
but
honestly i just threw my my cart and
stuff together without really knowing
[Music]
what's i mean
there is this one cart that's like you
know the best car that everybody uses
in the tournament
but i still don't have that i got all
the other [\h__\h]
but i'm not getting that one for some
reason
oh [\h__\h]
i hit you with the boomerang you hit me
oh man
i love you on me
that was a close one
there's a train
hitting me i'm alive though
is the strap always here i feel like i
died for a second though
ah
really bad i'm really bad at the rail
tracks
never played on this map i think
uh i'm fine
eat them eat them eat them eat them
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was trying to go straight but i guess
i'm european
thanks ahmed for laughing at
[Music]
why is he not always first what the [\h__\h]
she's she's cheating
you're cheating
[Music]
no comment
can't hear you over this first place
trophy
[Laughter]
okay wait which ride
right now we tried every one of the new
ones
the ninja hideaway yeah
that was fun but very confusing
that's like my life
ninja
oh yes it's chocolate
wait ina would look great in a ninja
outfit if we ever do like a whole live
holo myth whole life
full of english carnival
i think inna would look cool in a ninja
outfit yeah you won't see me because
i'll be i'll be ninja oh cool
in every tentacle
oh
oh this is the cartwheel and all my
enemies are dead
i didn't get the
boost i got it
maybe i'm the better ninja
i show up i at least have some
experience well this is really confusing
yeah
it is
i know your dojo better than you know
yours
oh i like the music
it's so cool though this place is so
cool
some kind of
version of gotcha [\h__\h]
let me imagine
the music is so cool
since we can't go into japan normally i
guess this is all we'll get
so
oops that's okay
oh oh there's a bottom part oh i didn't
know that mm-hmm
what the [\h__\h]
music's popping
the shaman said down
[Music]
this one's so tough
oh
what's that anyway what the hell
i should have waited for a second
throwing those
come back soon oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
my comeback is coming
back
i hear i hear the shell where is it
going
i have no shell
a bump against every wall man
yeah the corners are so sharp
no driving on the tatami mats please
shine guys
okay [\h__\h] you then
oh there's the finish line it's like on
the roof yeah it's like it's like the
edge of the roof it's weird
oh that was close come on
[Music]
that was [\h__\h]
how the [\h__\h] did you get one again ninja
how does she do it
you can focus in
focus enough i mean focus yeah
um oh this one looks good
oh coconut mall or choco mountain choco
mountain looks yummy
hmm
i don't mind
anything's fun i'm feeling coconut okay
that was a popular one
they had this really good lemonade today
it was like a coconut pineapple lemonade
and it was so good it does sound yummy
oh it's expensive
it's those premium lemonades
these fancy bottles i had an ice cream
puffy today with strawberries oh
i love
this time i was not
terrorized by a bee actually was a wasp
last time
i like how you were like oh it's a bee
but then someone's like uh i don't think
that
everybody oh my god like ninety percent
of the replies to that tweet were uh um
i think that's a wasp
don't you know what the bee looks like
and what it was looks like
no i don't apparently
feel like stupid
okay now i know now i know
yes like me too much
that backfired on you i had a bomb
you hit the bomb oh
did a good job at crx
well yeah
yeah she didn't like the dance moves are
legit
so cute man i saw a photo of her being
beheaded though
oh you see that no i am not
um
what happened there
wow
i think uh
oh yeah
i think she was just taking a break you
know
oh so that's how
that's how she thinks
yeah she's like a lego man where you can
take the
yeah yeah i didn't know that does that
mean that she was having a headache
and someone works like that too
oh this is a different version of small
me so
probably not what the [\h__\h] i just did
donuts in the middle of the road
did you see the kfp food though
yeah oh i didn't see the food itself but
i saw the menu
oh yeah oh
i think it's funny you became like an
actual fast food manager yeah
finally man i've been waiting for that
for so long
oh why did it change now
and at the same time like in
korea there is this this added plus
collaboration too right and right now
my curry my chihuahua curry with fr uh
with
it
chicken on top so there's a lot of kfp
food right now in this world and it
makes me really happy
[Music]
so much fun yeah that's cool dude how
you avoid it what's that
ah
donut it got me wow
wow really really really i could use a
donut honestly
i should have gotten some donuts
donuts why donut why do not
because the car was doing a donut huh
yeah a car when a car does a circle like
this
ah
what you call that a donut what yeah
because if you look from the from the
top higher marks they're kind of
huh
it leaves behind and then usually like
if somebody's doing then you'd say you'd
use it a sentence like somebody's doing
doughnuts in the parking lot
if you don't do not worry about it that
sounds way too cute to describe
something so bad that's cool
you need a better word for that
but what you're thinking whatever
whatever you want
not random because it could pick a old
one
oh
okay
let's talk about it that kind of looks
like a what's it a moogle
that looks like oh
oh
really liked your bag in hollow bags
review
oh yeah sorry
it was so funny because it stood out so
much and everybody said oh that was
really like i mean like it had
personality
yeah you know the whole nuts but but the
question was uh what movie did you watch
with the pretty
the goggles
oh it's for um
it was like around christmas time and i
went to that the the people that kick up
their legs really high
what
belay
[Music]
you call that
oh
yeah they had a three oh nice question
nice shot me uh-huh continue what they
did but aren't they
people
yeah it's real people but they had like
a little 3d it was really dumb it was
really little
it was like it was like the intro for
santa claus and santa was in 3d and then
he appeared
for santa claus oh
that's
nice
and inna's bag was so clean and
obvious oh yeah i didn't even have to
blur it like it was so obviously inya i
tried to you know make people think oh
maybe it's eofy maybe it's i don't know
marine or whoever draws
you put that thing in your bag
hold my backpack yeah oh she didn't
specify what kind of bag so i just took
off my backpack
with her when she was with us she had
her
her ipad for drawing
oh my god
i could win this
i think not so fast
oh that wasn't even
come on give me something good
[Music]
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
you did well
in my heart i'm first
you know are we like in this place so
like right before the end what the hell
i had triple mushrooms and i uh i zoomed
in
thank you guys for playing
thank you
[Music]
thanks for watching chat cook check out
uh who's streaming i am the only one
yeah okay
i will gladly adopt everybody come here
yeah take care i'll see you guys next
[Music]
good week
don't get splinters
oh wait i can still be in here while i
end the stream
wait let me let me end things
everyone to your stream oh wait are you
doing the the raiding thing i never used
that yeah if i can i i i've used it once
but let's see
i don't even know how you do that
where is the option for that
direct other channel
where where do you do that
it's in the settings uh
oh really yeah
right be right back
oh there it is redirect
oh
should i make a tournament
um yeah
uh we can use a tournament that i've
made before and i'll just give you the
number and then you enter that one
oh
because yeah they stay open kind of
let me hide my screen then and i'll
look for my tournament
um how about
this one
uh-huh
that should work okay i'm gonna
write you on the emma
[Music]
should i write you a lotion
it'd be nice
i could try
there it is i sent you
okay i go now
oh wow
bye
okay opening tournament
that's only you and me
i'm scared
don't be scared i'm still gonna move you
closer to me hello
somebody's already in here and i guess
that i would be using that quick on my
quick i'm a fast what it says
uh yes okay
okay i'm joining i'm joining okay
and then and then uh let me show the
viewers the code i'm gonna pin it as a
comment
i have several tournaments and they just
guessed it's one of those
i think you can only have four so they
yeah they just guessed correctly
you are you coming in i already posted
it [\h__\h]
oh yeah yeah
just searching for players but i already
joined i think
i'm in a minute
and another kiara that one's not me
oh okay so guys the rule is try to
choose um if you see one try to choose
one of the new ones how about that
let me write that again uh
leave after one race uh choose new track
if you see one oh it's still hidden okay
one sec
okay so here it is
pop comment pinned
and
screen is
back on the right moment what do we have
we have sydney again oh
oh rainbow row come on why are you gonna
trigger me like rainbow road
oh there's a better kiana did you see
that yeah there's a better it's not
possible now they call thank you they
call themselves better kiara
little [\h__\h]
that that helmet is cool from the person
in front of me
it's a yellow helmet i
wow there's so much going on on this
track holy [\h__\h] oh i'm getting dizzy
oh my god
[Music]
oh i fell off
um start the counter chat
[Music]
oh my god
so ama did you ever feed any squirrels
with those nuts
yeah i did i fed a lot of squirrels
that came in naturally okay that was one
natural opportunity for me to say that
okay i'm gonna make use of it
there was uh i was at the park and i was
feeding the squirrels
whoa
and there was like a old gentleman that
was watching the squirrels oh [\h__\h]
and
i gave him a nut
why not yeah
oh well i don't know i thought he wanted
to feed this girl so i just gave him one
and i wanted to save them so i could
feed them wanted to save the the
squirrels or the nuts
yeah i saved the nuts to feed to the
squirrels and then the old man
when i gave him the nut he looked like
like he smelled it he was like
oh for me to eat
he was confused
yeah i was like no it's uh you could eat
it if you can feed the squirrels yeah
you're dead hungry
yes it's straight out of ammo's bag but
if you don't mind that
[Laughter]
he just he seemed really interested in
the squirrels so i wanted to
see if maybe he wanted to feed them
i hope i hope no squirrel was trying to
bite you
oh no oh but i did see like a completely
black squirrel is really cool what i've
never seen a black squirrel before
oh
it was cute dude there all the other
squirrels were bullying him
bam
i think those girls are just fighting in
general mean girls
[Music]
unbelievable
even the squirrels can't get a break
oh my god that ufo looks like a squid
oh cool cool i wanted to look at it
yeah this map is really cool because
we're in space yeah
it's like the the the small um small
myth video
[Music]
no no i'm just you know i want to see
that i'm 12. don't worry about me
no i was in 11th place so i think you
were oh oh
i'm really far though yeah
um
uh
oh i was gonna watch some netflix and
then probably laugh and eat
i want it's also you do like after
streams
yes always
i was i watched your your um
what was it called um
what's it called what's it called what's
what was it called that game scott oh
skye what what
oh city skyline yes this is skylines
that wants to the whole vod i liked what
you did
oh thank you
what did you do in yours i didn't see it
uh oh that was members only because we
can start with members only by the way
if you need something for me but i was
told that you plan out like bumps ahead
for your members
yeah cause we have like a a voting like
a voting war oh well where yeah
everybody all the members decide what we
what we're gonna do for like the next
four or five streams
[Music]
so
advertise your membership now
what are you doing the next four streams
oh yeah uh wait i think it's tomorrow i
said i'd play like a members only horror
game because i was checking and like
apparently there's a like a horror game
that we can do oh that's uh members only
oh i wanted to um
um suggest you there was one um
there's actually so many new members
only games that we can play finally
hallelujah
and there was one that i tried in my
members it's k-o k-a-o
it's a platform a 3d platform and i
thought maybe you
you would want to you know give it a try
it's pretty good
a-o-k-a-o yeah ko it's a kangaroo that's
called ko oh
yeah yeah i saw it in the update oh
yeah yeah
it is it's played it already since
[Music]
you played it already yeah i played
before one stream it's pretty fun
platformer it's like uh
apparently it's um a remake of a really
really old game
i hate this map
and it's from poland
poland oh
polish game look
so the voice acting is really funny in
that one
because it's polished voice accents only
even though the theme is that it's an
australian kangaroo
oh my god i'm killing them all let's go
are you winning
[Music]
there's a
game genre right that's called beat em
up games no
oh yeah uh-huh where are those again
like the the
the fifth fight oh is it like the one i
think so i think it's something else
that what is it
what are you doing after the horror game
uh like just in general or
like uh members yeah the members have a
different members oh i'm curious
what the hell did i do
i think i said i was gonna do like some
and i don't remember oh drawing maybe
i'm not enough
okay
i need to ask my members
hi what are you doing after the stream
after this stream oh it's actually
pretty late so i got to eat dinner and
then sleep boo
what's for dinner
sandwiches because i think that's the
only thing i have in the fridge but i
like sandwiches
do you like uh when you toast your bread
do you ever like toast it in the pan
with some butter no
no no you just do like something good or
something maybe i should do that i mean
this one is just a overall sandwich from
the
supermarket well maybe i should toast it
yeah just uh
you could just plop it in a pan and then
like flip it oh
maybe i'll do that i'm still a little
bit uh scared to use
my kitchen but
did you say what happened like what
exactly it was
yeah yeah i explained you know frying
pan
i guess i guess you don't know the full
story
right oh
yeah
so
basically
um
i
i had a new frying pan okay
didn't come with a lid important note
so
i started um preparing everything like i
cut the ingredients i was i already put
like uh sweet potato
um
slices in the oven
yeah yeah i was pretty far and then i
was about to grill the meat so i put oil
in the pan and then
i quick quickly went away to check
something but then i underestimated how
how quickly it would um
go
and become hot and then i came back and
then it was already like smoking it's
walking smoking smoking it was not on
fire yet but it was smoking type of oil
did you use like olive oil it was
sunflower oil
oh can i see face yeah some oils have
like a lower smoking point
compared to like a vegetable oil or
something i was surprised too man but
yeah so i was really smoking really
strongly and i was like [\h__\h] that's
nothing like that's already pretty bad
so i take it off of the
um stove
and the moment i take it off while i'm
holding it it catches fire
eh and i start panicking and screaming
like what the [\h__\h] and it quickly gets
pretty big
and
um
i'm like panicking trying to think
what's the best thing to do right now
and already at the like before
before i took the
frying pan off of the stove before it
started fire
catching on fire
um
it's
the the the the alarm already went off
and was so loud it was like
piercing through my ears you know so
that made me even more stressed and
panicky
[Music]
and so i was thinking
while
absolutely panicked that i should
probably not put water on it so that was
smart
i did not put water on it
that's good yeah yeah that was that was
one good decision that i i like to
praise myself for because i could have
done something really stupid there
oh yeah and then i was thinking yeah
well i want to like put something on it
to like smother
the fire but i i i was like worried that
if i put like a normal blanket on it
then it would catch on fire too like you
know it's the first time that i would do
something like this like in in real life
like i had training for such situations
at work before but that's the first time
that it ever happened we had to deal
with it yeah like if it's in a
controlled environment like
with somebody who teaches you how to
deal with it you're not nervous you're
not panicking there's no alarm going off
so there's no need to like panic too
much about it right
then it happens in reality and you're
like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] what
do i do
[Music]
so i'm i'm i'm like
panicking in my apartment
alarmist
and fire in my face
and uh so what i start doing while
thinking if there's no better way to do
it because there was no lid okay i could
have just put the lid on top but there
was no lid
so i started blowing at it like crazy
hyper ventilating blowing like
like really strongly i was like [\h__\h] how
could i have my whole kitchen on fire if
i don't do something and then the
unbelievable happened
after like
a minute or two of really strong blowing
i blew the fire out
really yeah yeah
it was
glad it worked yeah got those idle lungs
yeah
oh there's a there's a um
a pokemon uh dude what's his name again
in english magmar magmar
are we seeing different things never
mind
uh what there's the the rocco he's
called aqua in german
oh
bro oh he's just broken english you
don't see him uh oh yeah yeah
oh oh yeah yeah
and there's a famous
famous
uh
mario kart challenger that likes
ah
he's always he's in every
every single mario kart stream that any
whole life member does
really yeah yeah really he always has an
eye out for any um mario kart streamers
because he challenges everybody he
always makes it in oh it's really good
be careful of that dude
okay it's called
i don't know if you've been in mine
why we're in this map again
oh okay so anyway since i'm gonna suck
at this road anyway let me finish the
story
yeah
so i blew it out but alarm was still
going smoke wasn't everywhere in my
whole apartment so i first of all i
opened all the windows
and then i looked outside the hallway
because you know it was really loud i
think all the apartments heard it
and then there was one neighbor
who um calmed me down while i was
waiting because of the alarm like it
automatically alerts um
like some
headquarter whatever oh to come over
check
yeah so i was like really worried about
that and i felt so embarrassed and
ashamed but then my neighbor she like
calmed me down and talked to me through
the whole thing like 30 minutes
and and and she changed topics to
something unrelated thinking that it
would get my mind off of it so sweet
and then afterwards you know the some
dude came to check my
my
alarm thingy turned it off i was like oh
good no worries and
and then
i was like oh man i'm never gonna use my
kitchen ever again but i'm hungry what
do i do
and the neighbor she gives me one of her
leftover pokeballs you know what those
are
pokeballs yeah pokeballs the food you
know what that is
i'm pokeball [\h__\h]
you know
you know yeah yeah yeah um cause some
boomers don't know
oh
so i got food for free it was really
sweet and on the next day
i bought some chocolate pralines and
left them in front of the door of the
neighbor
oh that's nice yeah
just the same thing you could like
without her i would have like
fallen apart in that moment
yeah
um
and then a few hours later i had a
post-it note on my door saying thank you
oh i said thank you she said thank you
circle
cute you know
did something like that ever happened to
you
oh uh well my mom at one because she
likes frying stuff
so there was one time where yeah it
caught on fire
and then
um
yeah it caught on fire and then uh
i think she put a wet towel on it oh
yeah that works too i heard now yeah oh
and it was like smoking a lot and so we
picked it up and we put it in the middle
of the kitchen floor
oh
i remember why but did the
towel not work
yeah it worked it worked it was just
really smokey
oh
damn yeah i didn't think of that i
didn't know about that one i knew that i
had to
you know
get rid of the oxygen
but at the same time i was blowing at it
but it kind of helped yeah
you don't blow out oxygen oh well you
blow out some amount of oxygen but
um
yeah people usually blow on fire to like
get it started like when it starts
sparking yeah yeah
i started a fire on that day
yeah there are a lot of jokes oh yeah
and then on twitter oh so it was because
we canceled the collab but like the way
we kind of did it made it sound like a
like a really really dangerous emergency
or something so i tried to make light of
this situation but then afterwards it
kind of looked like oh yeah yeah i
burned or something but i didn't mean it
like that
and then afterwards i told you to
exercise but it's just because
it's because i have a amt or sorry not
emt uh emt cousin
and they said that when they're working
like really hard in stressful situations
you know
oh like emergency medical
thingy oh
well they like a paramedic now
yeah they said it really helps uh when
adrenaline builds up it starts to like
get stored in your body and uh working
out burns all the extra stress yeah
like after adrenaline inducing
situations
oh i did work out on the next day
i'm done
i was too traumatized and like ashamed
to do anything
i just cried myself to sleep for being
stupid
no it happens um oh just don't let it
happen again and i feel like if i
wouldn't have been living alone then
maybe i have you know had someone there
right there while it was happening and
and could have done could have made
better decisions on how to act
but
i was just panicking it was the first
time if it ever happens again
then i think i will react better
so
come at me bro come at me fire
do you think in those situations you
usually like panic
like just uh
of course yes
huh how could i not panic i always panic
i don't know like for me when something
happens like an emergency i'm always
really calm
i wish i had that skill
oh
can't remain calm always panic panic
from panic come panic are you in 12th
place i'm going to test you yeah i was i
was like fifth or something and suddenly
now that you asked me i'm tenth
magic oh there you are bye
hi
they're wrecking us amen what do we do
oh get good eat good
will you throw me a mushroom no
no
no mushroom appeared like in front of me
[Music]
oh that was short and didn't do [\h__\h]
yeah i like the animal crossing map yeah
i want to play animal crossing but it's
so much to like get your
island set up again like it takes
forever
what i did for animal crossing streams
is contractually just um
looking at other people's
maps because they have some uh maps
islands why am i not driving
because yeah
they they make some really impressive
islands and looking at oh fun
yeah it does sound cool also i want to
say i'm playing on handheld so if i have
my pro controller it'd be way better
sure
[Music]
so yeah here you go with the excuses
again
it's true
if you guys choose rainbow road again
i'm going to mold and moored and mag
everything all that and what
i think i feel like all of those mean
different things i think they
all have similar meanings
in my brain
no
did you see juggled
with the shirt
oh yeah i saw it
recently i feel like
yago
is getting more and more hip
yeah maybe uh he's going through
midnight
i didn't want to say it i didn't want to
say it
and there's a kobold and this is the
name mommy quinoa
it looks like cool cute
now riago's cute like uh yeah
yeah i mean like a you know like a
cute old man or something you know
old oh
he doesn't know he's not
that old to me did you know that he goes
running every morning
oh
yeah he told me in whole talk
mm-hmm that's good yeah every morning he
goes for even though you you can't
imagine how freaking busy he is right
and they [\h__\h] chose rainbow road
these [\h__\h] it's the other rainbow
yeah that's better i guess
no well yeah maybe
a little bit
oh yeah i heard like even
uh
like a lot of the
presidents for united states and stuff
they also make time in their schedule to
work out like every day oh
this is healthy yeah it keeps you
mentally healthy
and body beats physically
oh my god there we go here we go
start the counter i'm surprised i didn't
fall off until now oh number two there
we go
ah
i can't i can't i can't
so oh yeah wasn't
yaku was sitting
in the audience during mine and inna's
panel
oh really yeah
i saw him walking in because they showed
us um the camera while people were
walking around yeah yeah but we were
already audible so when i saw him
walking in i wanted to react to him
let it know that oh my god he just
walked in but i couldn't say it like
clearly because i didn't want to start
you know a whole
locomotion
yeah yeah because i thought if the
audience knew that he just walked in
everybody's going to be like oh my god
yeah
[Applause]
nobody nobody noticed stay in the old
notice afterwards or like maybe some
even loki noticed like during the panel
but they kept quiet
yeah but since he was facing
a back his back to everybody it was
mostly fun and then afterwards people
immediately all went up to him to ask
for pictures and autographs and he took
so many pictures with people
really
constantly yeah staff told me that they
took a million pictures for
people to take pictures of the apple
so popular
yeah
that's a i wonder if
he usually gets stuff like that or maybe
it's just here also i wonder
oh
people
maybe they saw him but they were like is
that really yago they were like in
disbelief like no why would y'all go
over here yago cosplayers too right and
then yeah there's one dude that actually
really no way no way it can't be yago
what the [\h__\h] no
yeah it was it was weird seeing pictures
of yago like at crunchyroll expo because
uh it didn't look like a like a real
yaga i was like what is that somebody
looks like that looks like a real yakult
you've seen so many fake yeah you don't
even know the real one anymore oh
communication era [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
did you get kicked out too
yeah okay
that's fine
i'll i'll open uh
a different room
um
[Music]
they're gonna try to guess again which
one it is wait
don't go in yet guys don't
yeah don't stop
keep some space for um and me
wait i gotta join
[Laughter]
yes yes yes i've sent
the number no i'm waiting
but it's so long it takes a while to go
yeah don't worry i didn't i didn't show
the chat yet
okay okay there's already people in here
they have all of them saved
maybe oh cause maybe it's like one of
the recently joined ones for them
but but uh
it's only four people maximum so you
should still have space
come on okay
i mean i mean i think i don't see you
yet
it's joining
i think the first race will be
uh
empty hey you're not here you're not
here i'm gonna race you're spectating it
says i'm spectating oh okay maybe you're
spectating the oh the race that other
people who are waiting
ah let's see if you can join
the next one
but it's gonna take too long
if you're spectating now
then you yeah
they always have like two
tournaments going on at once
uh-huh
so even though it's one tournament
there's always like two it's like two
different dimensions
so you probably would be joining
the other one that's going on probably
well i'm watching you race though or i
don't know maybe
you know what while while i'm racing
here do you want to make a new
tournament that people don't know
okay
the settings are
there's many settings but most things
just stay the same i think
okay i'll make one if you have any
questions
ask me
how i've made
chats with me my favorite place here are
way higher because there's only four
people
i should oh that's good
it's hard to tell sometimes certain
objects if you bump into them they give
you like a boost
and some
don't
oh yeah like some mess you up and ruin
you
oh and i know
oh [\h__\h]
that was unnecessary
did you guys watch hold on for summer i
only saw screenshots but holy moly
those poses that i saw in the
screenshots did you see them i guess you
didn't see that one either because you
also just woke up
yeah i missed everything when i go to
sleep there was a lot going on when you
were asleep
well live summer is back
oh
how is it
um they all have like kind of the same
swimsuit but like um
with like just like the idol outfit
certain details are in their image color
and they're very short so you see
much leg
yeah
and uh i saw a lot of butt shots [\h__\h]
hell what's going on
lack of bad shots
i'm gonna go check on twitter yeah cause
i sent you code for when you're done
with the link
i'm gonna try to end this asap
it's already free and free
the banjo music is going high speed
[Music]
[Laughter]
this was the one where i was actually
doing pretty good in the tournament
um
the one with the i think it was with the
japanese girls
i was pretty doing pretty well in this
one
okay sorry guys we're not doing this
tournament i'm joining this one
[Music]
hiding the screen
ah wait can i not just join uh
yours i don't do i have to enter your
number
oh yeah
under friends it doesn't show that
you're doing a tournament okay
using a code
there we go okay
oh i'm so hungry let's do like one more
half hour and then
we end it
okay what are you gonna eat what's
what's that sandwiches all right
that's it
yeah chips
no no i don't have chips
oh
no more chips well maybe
maybe i'll toast it like you told me too
no canned soup
okay i have no no
don't get canned soup i recently cleaned
out like my kitchen print all right
actually i might have some
some instant soup somewhere
wait are you in the lobby thingy i'm
coming right now
oh okay
i already told them the number now but
i'm faster i'm faster than them i'm
faster and faster faster
i'm i'm in oh is that you yes
oh and there's two two of the new
let's tracks let's see how fast the
people can come in
ice cream
i see you scream give me that give me an
i'll choose it already
come on in faster come on guys show me
your entertainment number skills
what's our race
oh there they are
oh yeah it just takes a while
okay
um
what's your favorite ice cream
chocolate
chocolate that's it yeah just regular
chocolate that's good it's good
yeah i like some more chocolate
sometimes
what's your favorite though
well it depends like if it's in in
baskin robbins in japan and my favorite
is uh love potion 31 and they did not
have that one in america so sad
i think it's seasonal like probably
around valentine's day they have that
yeah they could have been around
valentine's in japan they have it
throughout the whole year
oh yeah
and then
if it's like a brand ice cream in the
supermarket i love
guys oh maybe magnum a different name
overseas do you have magnum
i think so yeah it's like the bar yeah
oh i like the orange one
oh
it's nuts
almonds it's a vanilla chocolate covered
cream vanilla cream chocolate covered in
milk chocolate and uh almonds yum yum
yum yum so good
oh so good it does sound tasty
yeah
and um if it's just normal chocolate
from like the ice cream place uh
i think
i like strazzatella and vanilla and
lemon nutella
no lemon strata
oh lemon and um and
amarena cherry
i like them all but not chocolate not
mint chocolate chip
chicken no
i like that one it's refreshing yeah
yeah
i don't need to have ice cold
uh
toothpaste in my mouth no thank you
it's usually not that it's like more of
a subtle mint flavor
okay so
[Music]
strawberry good too
now
[Music]
do you know this song
yes
i sang that the other day in my karaoke
maybe you can use that for singing it
with me
sometime
oh yeah i haven't done that in a while
you should check
sing along
with me
yeah i'll do that
[Music]
yeah i don't know the rest of the song i
just know that one
i think
you gotta
learn it or you'll leave it to chihuahua
oh the helicopter looks funny
i feel like i'm doing so well how am i
still 12 what the [\h__\h] what [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h]
these people all practiced probably
beforehand
yeah and they don't have to worry about
uh you know reading chat or whatever so
australian baskin robbins says love
potion really
ah
oh my god
oh wait
oh i didn't do the i didn't pin oopsie
doodles thanks guys
thank you
i didn't pin the new one
[Music]
i wonder if the korean baskin robbins
has it because i'm going to hurry up
this week
that sounds really cool exciting yeah my
first time i'm gonna meet your mommy
i'm gonna meet your mommy before you
meet your mommy
what the heck
i'm gonna hang out with her every day
probably everything yeah
gonna steal your mommy
did these people not understand the
rules ninja is still pretty new we
should choose that one guys
oh
okay look at its face
we're picking mumu because of fauna
yeah
fona mood on twitter
so now everything's about
cow fauna
counter
when she leave us oh it's random
ah god damn it
i mean i like that road but
mata
[Music]
i'm nervous about hanging out with your
mommy the whole time though oh
yeah why
because
because what if she
if she
doesn't like me
because it's different like you know
being
together for a whole day in real life
than just doing a collab on on discord
for two hours or so
that's just like you
i hope so
i need to i need to be cool
so i i try first you guys will be doing
fun things so you know not just i hope
so i mean seoul is currently
flooded but
one of the parts only parts of it
apparently so
i hope we can still do fun things
but yeah
i'll try to not let my nervousness be to
nervously be too noticeable so then i
look cool to her
how do i impress your mom
um
i think if you if you laugh a lot
happy mama
mama likes to laugh so if you guys laugh
together yeah she does laugh a lot
uh-huh
you know what she wanted the way to her
heart me she wanted to do um um partner
look at uh um school outfits
she wanted to wear like school uniforms
and kind of look with me because like
that's actually
um in korea they like like when girls
are like friend friendly together
they like to do that they go like to
disneyland together in school uniforms
even though they're not students anymore
oh yeah interesting is it like a rp
thing like let's pretend we're no no no
no no pretending
oh just wearing it because it's cute
and because it's a simple thing to work
together i guess
oh
in japan they like to do that too
they call it uh seifuku disney
the uniform disney it's like oh that's
that's still let's do it you're not from
disney together this weekend yeah let's
go okay i'll wear my old uniform let's
go actually i mean normal students
actual students do it too i hate myself
yeah
it doesn't sound cute it seems like
it'll be fun yes maybe one day you can
do the same with navi
yeah i don't know if i'll wear
a school uniform i don't know
oh man you passed right in front of me
i fell down otherwise i would have been
before you damn it every single race i'm
like at fourth place like ah and then i
get hit by four red shells
yeah you guys suck stop hurting us
let us win
it gets our way to the end
[Music]
oh coconut mall
coconuts
what
maybe it's to get students discount no
no no no really no no no no it's quite
common
maybe in asian countries in general
because also school uniforms are more
common in asian countries
than yeah yeah at least i don't know
in europe we don't really we don't
really do school uniforms at least in
austria
oh they have there's a lot of places
here but they're like private schools
like religious schools they have the
uniforms but oh i didn't go to school in
like a place where
it was like the state law or whatever
thing yeah the uniforms that man
no no no it was a school dress code oh
what was the dress code
you had to wear a collared shirt
and you had to wear
that's kind of like
khaki pack yes that is beautiful but
okay i guess you can at least like
somehow get your own pants on your own
shirt but it ends up being pretty much
the same
yeah yeah
[Music]
but you can accessorize it right you can
wear like a cute
ribbon or something
oh yeah i think it's only as it's not on
the clothes it was fun
oh
wow that sounds hmm
we don't even
have
like
i mean we probably have one or two but
they don't really
stand out we don't have private schools
i've never seen a private school in my
country before
i only have public schools can i hit you
maybe it's okay
[Music]
no private schools no uniform set
said
so when i was younger
i would just at home
wear japanese
uniforms
[Laughter]
japanese school uniforms at home alone
in my room
you could wear
you wouldn't wear it to school
no of course not they wouldn't think i
was [\h__\h] cringe the only time when i
did something like that was um during
our um carnival called fashion
uh
um i wore a japanese made outfit
oh cute
yeah
[Music]
yeah and actually i had yeah i think
they liked it because that was an art
school and then the people there were
more chill about stuff like that and i
actually had several made outfits so i
gave um
i gave one of my friends a made out pit
as well and then another friend of mine
i gave her some other cute
japanese themed outfit i think yeah i
feel like a collector
yeah i had all the all the outfits yeah
i was really into mates like i really
wanted to
um work at a maid cafe
i wanted to move to japan and work at
the maid cafe but
never happened and now now that i've
visited several main cafes i'm like kind
of over it
you don't want to do it anymore no
no not really
it's not i still want to wear cute maid
outfits though because they're cute
oh
i want to see i made a cute made out of
pizza
i may have tried one on at some point it
was like a costume
oh but i haven't actually worn one
holy [\h__\h] how am i four
i
i'm fourth
you did it
absolutely amazing
and i was tangenting the whole time guys
is this map
good map good map cracked
[Music]
why there's so oh let's do a mushroom
george gorge george gorge
yeah yeah
the onion meat looked really good by the
way
korean viewer onion
oh
i saw them
on
i mean you're really popular in korea
you know that
yeah surprising
i feel like you're kind of the reason
why um whole life got a
little head start in korea
thank you thanks for yeah bringing us to
korea
i'm a famous detective after all world
renown
in the news known globally
[Music]
famous paladin's announcer emilia
all these [\h__\h] npcs man
stop picking random
goddammit but those are empties why do
they all are the same yeah they're npcs
i think
what do you mean because um
i don't know the game uh filled our
lobby with npcs because they're like the
others didn't make it in
okay we'll get a mushroom at least
hi
alrighty
yeah look at them they don't even have a
name ah except for the player such a
player
also why are there two
why are the two french toasts
pot they do that paint pearl
i love french toast
okay goes up let's go have you ever
eaten bread with mold on it
um
i hope not but i'm always really worried
because it's really hard to see like
when it starts molding just slightly
was uh-huh uh
yeah with like a toast bread for example
why
you you're saying that i think i i heard
you just
uh recently talking about eating
moldy bread
yeah did you talk about that in city
skylines
yes
that's why i remember
well i always thought that you could
just take off the moldy part and then
like eat the rest
[Laughter]
once you see bread molding it's too late
okay remember for next time
oh
i know you don't want to waste happen i
didn't get sick well probably because it
was just a small part but still i don't
think it's a
good good
[Music]
do i need choice come over there to make
you eat proper food
i eat i
good okay
so shouldn't you not be eating bread at
all i wasn't was it uh non-gluten bread
yeah okay okay i'm just making sure that
my almond doesn't eat the gluten
no gluten for um
i always eat for breakfast the
egg with yolk like cooked with the yolk
still runny and then some rice
i have this tub of like seaweed salad oh
come on i try to get another veggie and
then a fruit
nice i'm going pretty smoothly
i was doing okay
until i always fall off on the green
mushroom
oh
the bouncy ones it means
yeah
but the green one isn't bouncy
oh
i never tried that one okay thank you
for letting me know i'll never jump on
that one the blue one makes you fly so
try to aim for the blue one
oh it's too late
i would've been higher uh if not for the
last moment
um it's and i'm glad you know we're
having some one-on-one time here
[Music]
wasn't even that long ago like uh when
was it we were here
oh
last one
yeah whatever i wanna go back to ahmed
next time
maybe next year i don't know i've
already been traveling like every
[\h__\h] month recently like i feel bad
about being inactive
yeah but you still handle streaming and
traveling i try i try but
i've been traveling so much so i should
after this after this korea trip i'm
gonna
try to
wait
wait for a while
it's stressful traveling and working and
then you're like traveling so you don't
feel like you can take a break even
though it's like stressful to travel and
stuff yeah it is you you want you want
traveling
like a vacation at least you want it to
be
taking the stress away from you but it
often ends up being actually stressful
too and
you should uh take like pictures or
something and then you could pose a
dirty kiwa kiwawa nam yes
you mean in korea
yeah wherever you go yeah i want to
i should
also
you need to help me figure out on which
on which laptop we took that one video
that i mentioned to you oh
i feel like it was
i think it was on yours did you check
i don't think i
like could i could it even have been
online when i didn't have the the
software installed
yeah because i think
i was installing it
i don't remember
and we recorded some kind of 3d video
[\h__\h] post for me to use later on and i'm
looking for it so that i can upload it
during my career trip but i can't find
it yeah we had like three laptops at the
time because we had
nina's like oh no well i guess
technically for because gooda also had
her laptop although i didn't think it
was in the same area maybe it could have
also been inya's because i feel like we
were using it um
around that time oh yeah because she
already had the thing installed
yeah
the software
once when i'm thinking
maybe i'll hit her up after the stream
get some really funny video
and fairy
too much going on here
oh my god
you guys are all too close
except for ahmed i'm we can get closer
give me nine please
oh ame you should play tunic
oh yeah yeah i saw it looks cool you
said it's only like six hours long or
something no it's like 12 to 20 but
that's like you know compare everything
to only
no
even if you don't get everything but
i recommend it if you want to
play like any kind of rpg or adventure
game but you're not
like you're staying away from it because
they're too long because this one you
can at least finish in like three
streams or so
and
if you need a code
the publishers
have
uh offered me to give codes to everybody
in her life so
i would play at some point but probably
not like in the next few weeks i think
oh really um
that's really good like honestly it's in
my top 10
games of all time now
and i didn't even finish it yet
oh
oh next race last week try i want to try
it last race
wait quick yeah time goes by
yeah
it's on game pass but for everybody who
doesn't have a game pass they offered me
to give everybody keys because i i
i i was talking so much about the game
on twitter and praising you so much and
then they were like wow thank you
if they need an official ambassador
[Laughter]
they also offered me
to send me like a like a pr
uh
like a
gift box kind of
yeah for their playstation release
that's coming up and they're gonna send
it to to cover in japan and then they're
gonna send it to me yeah cool yeah it's
so sweet i'm happy because i mean by
that time i'll be done with the game but
it's nice very sweet of them yeah
they know i haven't finished it yet
ah
yeah i'm i'm like
i would i would need one more stream
but i i think i need to play i need to
finish after korea
uh that's no more time so now there's
gonna be a little bit of a break
it's so good amen and it's made by one
person
that's crazy yeah
it's so good it's like a
stardew valley
[Music]
i didn't play valencia i can't tell
oh i think that's also a game that's
made by like one person really what
i know yeah they did i think they did
the music and
everything
i don't remember i don't know wait chat
gonna
you guys corroborate the details
yeah i said yes
what
that's impressive
oh i think it took them a pretty long
time
i think tunic also was like four years
or so i heard
turn around
oh what is that what's that i thought
maybe that's a secret [\h__\h]
that looked like a secret didn't it
also tunic has a million secrets on it
and normally you know like with with
mario games and [\h__\h] i'm like really bad
at finding secrets i'm also i'm [\h__\h] at
mario games in general
oh and you know mario mario's kind of
more or less easy and tuning is way more
difficult but i'm way better at tuning
than than i am at mario games explain
that to me
have you played mario odyssey
no and that's what people have been
telling me that mario odyssey is easier
and i should play that one
oh yeah why i started backwards with the
mario streams or mario games
so i played odyssey first and then
uh
because it's easier
it's easier to like uh use the controls
and stuff oh i think i think it did help
me going backwards really
yeah
now okay if i ever play
a mario game again
then i'll consider mario odyssey next
did i still finish before you no no i
didn't okay i saw you like
like lagging and glitching in the back
oh
yeah how did i go from first to 12 man
okay let's leave the lobby
okay
thank you guys for participating
[Music]
yeah
oh uh it's just me left so
you can do racing of them if you want
oh no that's okay
take a break
oh thank you ama for staying with me
until the end everybody else left
they couldn't you know it was
unavoidable yeah
it's okay i got some one-on-one chit
chat time with emma that was nice
yeah
let's play paladins again sometime
okay the one fps game that i play
yeah you were pretty good at it
we should get a full paladin's team
you mean of other whole life members
yeah oh i would totally do it
i would totally do it i wonder if
anybody else would want to play oh i'm
totally in at least i have the famous
paladins announcer pack yeah you're the
only one
that should tell you how much i love you
more than everybody else
[Laughter]
actually recently they added you know
ruby like rw
what like a 3d anime
two paladins
uh yeah they added skins for like some
of the champions or the heroes
damn
that's cool i'm gonna look at that
they have some cool skins
okay i'm sure we can get a team together
how big are the teams
five
five hmm
we could even go full myth but i don't
know if they all you know i don't want
to force them don't want to force them
into it
we just ask everybody like maybe
somebody and i do want to play or
something yeah
yeah yeah
pound and steam sometimes it's a free
game so
i mean why not
yeah play overwatch already
so you saw me playing paladins do you
think i would be good at overwatch too
uh i feel like paladins is easier to
play if you're a new player
um
uh i mean you should try overwatch yeah
i'd like i'd be that'd be funny to see
you have to carry me
i think you'd like it though i think i
don't know why i think you like
reinhardt why not
yeah he's like this big tank guy and he
swings this giant hammer and he's like
ah reinhardt have you not learned
anything about me in the past
two years that is cool i wanna play a
cute girl man with a cute butt
uh okay then you're probably like a diva
i know her with the doritos
yeah and mercy i complained because
actually i uh when when i was really
into mmorpgs back in the day i always
played the healer
yeah healer's really uh good for new
players to start out with don't you get
like a lot of [\h__\h] and like for for not
healing enough
yeah so just heal
just heal just can't give a [\h__\h] say
come on stupid healer heal me come on
why are you not healing more and faster
well the good thing is at least if it's
not in overwatch 2 because in overwatch
2 there's only five players oh oh i
think there's still two healing slots uh
yeah so usually there's two healers
oh and i don't have to blame it all on
one person
yeah
just heal
i need healing
feelings
healing
at least that's what i know from mmorpgs
maybe that's not so much an issue and
yeah it's like a meme for
fps or for like uh hero shooters too
like i need healing i need healing
because you can spam it oh
oh
well in mmorpg games you have to scale
your intelligence and all that to be
able to bring out the heels faster
at the fastest possible interval of
1.0.9 milliseconds or whatever and then
the animation will get faster the
healing animation will get faster the
more intelligence you have and stuff
like that
oh i want to play mmorpgs man
maybe that might be fun yeah
it's i mean i guess then it has no
nostalgic vibe for you but for me it's
like the most nostalgic thing ever
because when i was like i don't know how
old must i have been 10 or whatever
played it with my whole family we were
in the same guild and we played world of
warcraft together
my mom my brother my sister everybody uh
it was really cute yeah
i have played wow like once so
oh
swans i think i only did the tutorial or
whatever oh does it cost money oh yeah
oh well okay
thank you everybody for watching i think
we can end it here i'm gonna eat
something now
watching yeah
thanks for watching yeah thanks for
coming on me coming oh thank you for
staying down uh in the in the lower
rankings of me
i just i don't want you to feel lonely
i think that was very sweet and
considerate of you you know how to read
the air
oh yeah thank you guys and in german we
say
she loves it
[Music]
oh my god
i'm gonna
i'm gonna teach you german someday
bye-bye ending screen let's go
[Music]
wow
that was for you kfp
[Music]
or was it