[Music]
okay
english collaboration
[Music]
wonderful i hear a lot of motivated me
crewmates only crewmates of course
it doesn't matter if you hide behind
that blue you can't see me i am just
i just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little uh
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then uh after a little while we had no
reports which was kind of just so fanna
did an emergency meeting um just to you
know because she was obviously scared
and which i was too
um
she reported okay she did an emergency
meeting and then what do we see free
deaths
of course she's not with us because she
made the meeting but turns out she was
the imposter how reckless is that
not to mention that she kills
people so easily
and she got voted out in the first
yeah
your stream hasn't started yet
[Music]
oh
yet
um
all right then um so i would like to get
some introductions from everyone and
every stream up yet
does everyone show you
are you ready
mermaid are you all ready yes
yeah okay i have a stream going okay
okay i hear you guys all around me
it's like binary
hollow like follow me oh [\h__\h] loud
self introduction can you all go girls
give me a reason why you are not sus
today starting from emilia go
oh why i'm not fresh today um
um hello everybody i'm amelia watson
hello live english miss number one
detective and um i'm not wearing pants
that's why you know
this is
so next up
your introduction please
[Music]
representing chaos everybody how you
doing
because we have to follow in order to
hear you
sorry okay i'm not sucks because um i
got a cute pet look at my pet oh yeah
i saw the hamster thing and i was like i
gotta i gotta
um
wow that's kind of kind of weird what
what interesting
all right
yeah
definitely not says callie
all right um so yeah um death is real
sus but guess what everyone i'm not
death i'm the sheriff around these parts
and because i'm the sheriff the sheriff
is never suss the sheriff obviously
didn't do it um some people may say i i
shot the sheriff but i did not shoot the
deputy meaning uh i don't know what that
means it just has something to do with
the sheriff and i'm not sure i'm not
suspect so there you go how can you be
the real show whatever
definitely
my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
you
a poisonous spotted plant no no no no no
i am a non-poisonous variety poisoning
you've already killed enough people for
today so your deed is done
exactly performers
no no no plant has never killed anyone
a little shock of horrors
here what's up everybody
oh i am not such because
um
[Music]
likely story i don't believe in such
you're sounding like us he practices
all right
hi
it's iris live english project hub video
singer
uh
i am very excited i
am 100
say so i would never lie which is why i
would never recess
i thought sorry yes
that explains everything i would never i
would never
don't trust virus
[Music]
a very very um
good self-introduction while other
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
is
[Applause]
your introduction
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro
from
the council
and
i am blue
yeah
oh
okay don't look at the color objectively
look at the color that's inside all of
us oh
my god
and flesh
wait did cronie say why she's nuts
oh right i'm not sucks because look at
this i'm wearing a mask i am doing my uh
part
in this situation don't get close to me
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not suns because i'm doing my part in
the society
and
i'm an upholding
oh no
saplings were all alone
the room was closed due to an activity
oh no
um
i'm sure there will be another
code
here all i'm using discord maybe we're
talking
you know we had a problem with the
servers last time right like during the
test oh
yeah that's true
this is just because of our inactivity
it's not a server problem don't worry
it's all good
it says could not find a room is what it
says
oh wait i mistyped
[Music]
in the middle of the stream or is it too
late even if they stopped
[Music]
okay
time is always on time
wait no no no no no what uh
please introduction and why you're not
says
i am the guardian of civilization and i
am an apex predator of the sky and i
could kill you if i wanted to
that's right that's right moving
interesting that is not hell that is
that that is the most nonsense
introduction ever yes
but i don't want to so i won't
okay
oh my god
so peaceful
like those berry bushes sweet i think
i take it back i take it back um
i i might not right no taxi back seat i
think it's a crap
[Music]
hello i
illness from am
of english um
the uh
priestess of the ancient ones
i think
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh
i am not sauce because i'm already dead
look at the the halo above my hands
[Music]
that chorus of o's was wonderful
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next up sanna is not streaming but she's
here so
[Applause]
[Music]
english council
uh it's been a while hello guys
if anybody thinks i'm sauce i'm going to
take it off and take all of you down
with me
we're just going to really reassure you
go back into back into the space where
you belong right or i can't you're a
part of the migrant right you should be
fine you should be fine if you get
kicked out i have no i have no reason to
oh um well
i'm very happy to have you here
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you
[Music]
return
and
i am the one organizing this and i'm
really happy that we could all get
together 11 people is a lot but we're
going to have a lot of fun today so
let's get right into it are you girls
ready to be
thank you
[Applause]
i don't want to be impostor first round
please not impossible
[Music]
all right let's go i'm the crewmate oh
dear what
okay i don't know if everyone else is
going to be talking to their chat i'm
not looking at chat obviously because
i'll be cheating but if i run into
someone and i'm talking to myself what
they think i'm um
oh hi
hi were you talking to your chat
oh your stairs oh
what
maybe this is what i deserve in the
first round i did kill everyone i didn't
thank you oh my gosh i was not prepared
all right well i guess i can read chat
again
hi guys
oh my gosh
first one it is what i deserve i killed
him
boom boom boom boom boom
you can haunt them by the way so she can
hear me and i'm just annoying her
forever
for killing me this is my revenge maybe
i can make her laugh
oh my god
again
[Music]
i'll try fixing it but maybe i don't
know maybe reinstall among us or
something like that because you had that
before yeah
we can restart we can restart we can't
restart who should we
can't vote
is
i was by myself it was the room with the
folder on the table oh records okay iris
ordered you spawn
uh where did i spawn let me look at the
map real quick
i
do not i've never really played this map
um i think somewhere like in the main
hall
okay well me sana and cronie all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vitamix
ring down there and
then two people were already yeah they
were already fauna and cali were already
dead so whoever spawned with them
about the beginning right okay
i appreciate it
all right iris for throwing me a bone
movement
you guys are making the wrong decision
you guys
[Applause]
we're all haunting watson
no there are no burgers to be made here
are you guys yeah hi ris hi rhys
i thought we could do a double kill
this is why the relationship does not
work okay what no you can't we're here
wait no i don't think she can hear us
yeah only thank you scream louder
can hear us we have to go haunt bay and
make her laugh in front of other people
yeah
i'm gonna go home
oh my god that makes sense
where is she where is she where is she i
have to do those i'm gonna do other
tasks oh yes
i have to be a good ghost still
and do my tasks
um
wait can i do this okay oh i mean thank
god
your partner
we were actually a thing
in this in this round
oh we don't know that this is why he was
killed
i don't know i'm i'm wondering right now
if we should
close the trail is strong um test it out
again
hi
hi hi bae what is this hi bae
it's absolutely ridiculous
[Music]
how annoying will that be
if i just keep doing that
to get important stuff yeah obviously i
need to i mean i need to
convey something i learned oh
clean up clean up
everybody do you share
i haven't done a lot of the tasks
on this map
wow this is so nice
i want a
just
doing the among us tasks
i
made fun there's something very nice
about doing
easy
menial tasks
that anyone can do
you feel accomplished just from
switching
flipping a switch
we will find the second imposter quickly
let's just find the snake
spy on people it feels wrong to spy on
people when they're talking to their
chats
i feel like oh my gosh wait this is like
what people say they will do when they
get
wait
oh you have to oh my gosh you have to
lift it up i didn't know
like when you're invisible what do you
do you go
spy on a cute girl
cute senpai
oh
um
i'll spy on people after i do this is my
last task i think
oh geez uh
what
oh
a lion
perfectly after that
here we go there is sana um
i found this body but i have absolutely
no clues because i was running around a
while here i have a chance i meant no
one i'm i'm on the crewmates side now
i'm not right
i'm not santa i'm not i'm
[Music]
guys
but i think that's something that an
imposter can do like show
that shall we delay that it's big fake
that is like you're part of the crew i
think cronie can vouch for me that i'm
not cess right crony what do you think i
mustn't look at well i i know that
watson and sauna were definitely safe
because the killings took place when
who are considered suspicious to me
would be
they or kiara
why
literally yeah
[Laughter]
then we'll just check um we should end
the game early i'm gonna
is trying to control this whole room
making
me i don't like you no no no watson's
definitely in the plane because i was
with her um
she's a rat i feel like if it wasn't
based
i was cleaning my guts out of the toilet
i couldn't see anything
i thought it was bad
with the gloves
there's not so many people left
you were this close this question
why are you spawning guys
oh hello hello
hi
clumps xd
i feel so creepy when i listen to people
who can't hear me
oh
is
[Music]
what are your plans oh god sneaky rat
oh she can hear but it's very quiet
she whispering
she's whispering so i can't hear her
i can still hear you
even if you talk quietly you cannot
escape
oh
[Music]
i am the perfect ghost it was destined
to be
where is everybody
electrical
let's go
let's see is she doing the mission or
she just lost that's pretty suspicious
whoa
cameras is they really doing tasks
she knows cody's on to her
where'd everyone go
you've got it cronie she's not doing
that cyrus out of the mix it makes
things a lot
uh
hi sheriff maury
it was too creepy
i don't want to be crazy
oh hi i watched your aunt what what
oh that was not that was not a hikori
that was not you just talking to
yourself that was a message to me
[Music]
i watched it all happen we can hear you
now
[Music]
where have you been just now but no just
now oh my gosh
where was i uh yes voter down butter
down
let's make this quick though so that ina
can come back
yeah no no no no no no no no no no no no
what were you doing what was the last
task you did i have a good one
kind of overrated so
i haven't really seen the exact numbers
for the triple i wouldn't be able to it
was emptying
some emptying the trash in main hall
like a diamond
[Music]
i think it's between
storage and like developing room
question question question room well i
know
i had just seen kiara like right next to
me
uh we were together by the doors
i mean i was around
was the one who reported the body too
right
this is my second body i'm recording yes
um
goodbye goodbye
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
it was iris and bay
in the room and it looked like irish
and that's right
is
[Music]
we leave the room right
yeah
bye-bye app you know what that means
hold up how do we leave the room um
um
leave uh exit
goodbye
uh
hello
hello hello
okay good good good good
we are here
in space
out here
oh and there's a new lobby code yeah
there's a code
i'm i'm going in
keep on pressing your senpai huh
why would you put the blame on me
what
i think in the previous round right i
think it's because you're you
are so uh
experienced
say it first
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious
uh
usually i feel like imposters are
usually very quiet like they try not to
talk because they don't wanna unless
they're very experienced in that sense
yeah
yeah yeah
people are usually the ones bust into
the room be like all right so who did it
[Music]
hi hi
everyone's just like uh you
you
you did it
oh i think you know
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um it's probably you callie
it's probably you
oh so it's cali
vodka
big but i'm pretty small right now you
come around corner crow
i do now
okay
no this is a cool kid's corner go away
sorry about the fox by the way yesterday
that's okay i mean apologize for the
fall waiting for oh wait
i saw i saw this
you won't get revenge or anything right
photo synthesis
[Music]
and you know it doesn't matter anymore
right i mean
because you know isn't getting in i'm
going to lobby
[Music]
okay goodbye my friends
alone again
with nothing but
the void
of space
[Music]
oh i think we're going to talk in
discord
this one doesn't work it works for me
mummy got in wait let me try
but we can
we can let ina worry about this
[Music]
can you try making a lobby
oh yeah okay yeah
you might get the same error or dodo the
dough because i got the same error uh
when i tried to creating the lobby
before the stream many times
just try again again again
you get nerfed in this game
the more evil you are
the better connection you have
oh wait my ping is fifth
is nerfing me
in this game
yes
oh hide the screen when typing code
that's right oh yes
looks like where
ina
is there a new club
i'm still
having trouble making the room too so
it's just like
the servers
yeah
maybe maybe we can try i i don't really
think it's closer but let's try maybe an
asian server
we can we can try
do you want to try you know or should
maybe someone else you guys can try
someone else can try making it okay i'll
make one eight in asia everyone change
to asia
okay
code is
oh wait should we not be saying this on
stream i'm not saying it okay the code
is code
code okay
oh d
e and at the end is always an f
okay
did you get in first try
yeah that works
um
if if i end up block screen again just
just go on without me it's like
okay i'm using this card
missing a few
[Music]
cheers
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i forgot how to play the game
i don't know how to do this one
oh i'll do it later this one is very
annoying you have to like boop boop
but i believe this one you tried this
map before i've played it a little bit
last time last time i wasn't able to
unplug the toilet but now the toilets
are clean
um
oh i see this one is clogged
now it's good i believe that you're not
the imposter because you knew what the
task was
uh what task i know what the task is the
library one
wait i don't is it possible to go over
here i don't know oh hi
is it possible to cross this gap
i could just eat
[Music]
the only thing i can say about that is
that i heard kelly's voice close by for
a moment but
that was like i i didn't even see her
close by i only found the body like a a
few moments later wait wait where did
you find the body yeah we're very bottom
right it's uh
the bottom area but i wasn't i wasn't
doing anything i was like looking for a
task to do well why were you not doing
tasks i don't think you're done with
tasks we just got started there's a lot
of tasks i doubt it's a bit okay i don't
know what to do
it's a really big map
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom
left side cali passed by me
that's very funny hahaha it's time to
kill hahaha please
me
4 4 and cali spawn together but kelly
went off pretty
quickly
i was pretty long
i was pretty lost i would not stick
around with anybody around but callie
just went zoom
you just said that you did you weren't
doing any tests now you said you weren't
doing the tasks
oh god i don't want to play the [\h__\h]
game
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab to open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks
[Laughter]
yeah i'm not sure
i'm skipping i'm not voting
really we're skipping okay okay at least
like winner um
did you vote
yeah i voted
i'm not skipped oh you said that
what is this this collaboration again
interesting
that's enough that's enough to throw me
out
really
no
no no no no i think it has to be two
doesn't it
isn't it majority i don't know
for now i'll remember this over here
oh hello everyone hi
okay i'm gonna go wow wow
electrical i'm far from that bring it
prana you stay away
what did i do
um i have to go down
sit down here hello fauna hello hi guys
what is this
i'm crying i can't believe this
i was rejected so quickly but no man
didn't
even do anything
one where where is the where where do we
go i got it don't you worry don't deal
with this side okay thank you thank you
into mother nature
oh you can use this to go on the other
side
oh geez
i'm scared
um
[Music]
don't kill me
don't why are you chasing me
are you chasing me
try me i'm going to press the button you
want him
i don't want to kill you i'm doing tasks
stop chasing me
oh no
we're not making friends this map
hello hello
it's okay if you kill me because it's
revenge
hello hello
oh i have to like clean the whole thing
i see
my only friend in this world right now
is sana
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
[Applause]
the toilet i was on the
i was in the the cockpit
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom
um
we used the toilet
i was not anywhere near that area toilet
i don't think it was me bathroom
i tried i wanted to go into the slide
the toilet but it was locked for me
um because when i found iris's body
right as i hit report the door the
bathroom door closed
i was trying to put the egg on the uh
the frying pan
i was tracking her and she was muttering
for herself
i was talking to my chat i was talking
to my chest you weren't
no i wasn't looking at chat i was just
talking to them so they didn't have to
listen to nothing
are you guys just walking around
completely silent it sounds kind of like
i was trying to talk to you but i was
like no i'm just trying to chat because
i was talking to you was i not
i told you
well i was also in i was in the area
below in the bathroom i was doing the
task where you pick everything up off
the floor and guru i did see me there
but i didn't go up i came from the other
side
someone's in the bathroom
someone's in the middle of the bathroom
i don't know where it was
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom wait
when we spawn back in while i see you
come out no
no we reset ourselves
damn it all right but in the very
beginning i spawned with uh inner and
fawful i can vouch for
i just remembered
yeah just because you spawn with them
you can't vouch for them
i mean i was running around with sana at
one point
lost
okay i don't know for now
okay
if you say so
but are you guys really just not talking
when you're running around
i don't know if i believe them that
they're really just being silent
why are you calling me out
what is this
there's some next level interrogation
tactics
what have i even done
they're gaslighting me maybe me believe
that everyone's been silent this whole
game
dude i'm weird for murdering to myself
i'm not talking to myself am i i'm
talking to two people who are listening
to me right first it was moment who
rejected me and everyone says i'm scary
but i'm just doing my tests
all i can do is my best oh it is
here oh hi
hello oh oh wait oh this is not the
thing hi
um hi how do you
where is it's electric
i'll have to this way
oh i can clean up here
how do i
convince people that i'm
innocent uh i'm innocent
i'm innocent i'm
no one fully here do we do we look at
this
i cannot finish my asking
i thought um sucks
i was uh in the top right area that's
like uh before the wreck
right yeah around the records area
and um when i was about to enter the
rikers area i saw kelly so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her and
next moment she completely disappeared i
went i went into all other like like
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared
man
you can vouch for me i went down to the
bottom and tried to go through the vent
and i couldn't
you tried to go
stop stop stop let me talk let me talk
let me talk let me
let me talk
let me speak let me speak
okay
what i mean is there was a vent down
there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's what i mean
went down to the bottom
right
and we're trying to go right
second time that she says the second
time guys saying this is the second time
out for me she just wants she just wants
me to get thrown out
has a bandana sir i don't know
i don't know
being tested right now
else would you call this [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting kiara
it could be a next level imposter tactic
is true
[Music]
um
wait what if it's
sana and kiara
hypothesis
what if it's oh wait why does oh
actually it's fine just pulling down
sana kiara
i'm scared oh hi i'm just doing today
um
and go to the kitchen with me
after
sure
okay
well we still know i'm innocent now
hello i have been murdered
by emma club
oh by ena can hear you but cali can't
for callie i killed her or she killed me
i mean oh
wait there's a lot of people down there
well i'm gonna finish this task now now
no one can interrupt me well they
probably could
still if they called
me i can't believe it they thought i was
so evil for something or maybe i'm not
evil
i'm not evil i'm just misunderstood
yes
that was
flips
they're fine they're all fine
that's so good it kind of leaves them
are you kidding me
is
this is
beautiful i don't know
it is time for calendar it is time for
the show
what have you guys been doing yeah
right now
is
[Applause]
she's pretty she's committed she's even
saying you will regret this
but at this point everyone has something
about
oh okay i need
i have one more task
one more wire
and then i will be a good ghost maid
ah
cute concept
ghost made ghost maid who cleans your
house when you're gone
can i have one of those
cute
so i need to ask them later because
that's a big game changer
don't kill me don't kill me
i'm trying to find the oh are you doing
this one already right side i'm doing
left side someone goes here left side
right side
i can think of the other side okay
all the way around
it's chaos i can't do it right
now
[Music]
how could you even do
it
yeah i know you can't say anything now
because others are around you but you
know i'm disappointed of you
very disappointed right now
hamster is going hey
okay
um
nothing wrong i have all my tasks done
by the way
[Music]
masterminding this she's going to win
for sure
you're a mastermind inna you hear me
you were betrayed
she got me too she's kind of a genius
oh grab it
oh no
how did you do it
she's about to win
oh hey
hey we're all in the shower it's nice oh
how romantic
this toilet stalled properly that's a
waste of water oh true
what do you have to say about this fauna
um we should hire a new
engineer
actually i'll just i'll just sit here
and let it
let it um
let it water my sprouts
and it's suspicious
oh
kept saying that she was lost and i
thought that it was
suspicious
i mean this is my first time
[Music]
what was the last task that you did the
last one i did was the one where i had a
dress
um
it has been really quiet
[Music]
all right
where is everybody they're already
sabotaging hello
hello hello hello nina is a very good
imposter that's what she is she's a
genius
there's one more person just one more
thing
[Music]
this is your first round
oh be careful babe okay you got it you
got it don't get crazy
right no no we don't go no no no no no
no don't go don't get here
right now
no no no no no no
no
no no
oh
that was not your boy's victory that was
definitely
hello hello
yeah so i have a question so when you're
imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
uh no
you know what but
like if you're doing certain like if
you're acting to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long times they kind of can't stand out
that you're oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh goodbye
oh my gosh i can't believe this
you know was so good
she was so good
i i trusted her
hello
very smooth
smooth entrance okay oh i can't use that
card anymore yeah i can't use that part
anymore
i don't know i don't know this game i
haven't played on this map before
give us a statement of how you were able
to hide your imposter-ness for so long
um
very good i blended in with the crowd
you know even if i could make the kills
i i
waited for my chance i was patient
the performance was so genuine you
actually were jumping on my heart
i asked you not to kill me and you said
okay
that was okay those were my
[Laughter]
[Music]
could you hear me after you killed me
yes i can hear you
was laughing in my ears the whole time
[Music]
i wish i was an imposter for
going to one to the kitchen
hello hi fauna
i'm a little shark who likes british and
green
i can finally clean in peace
maybe also that was cool there's a
shower just saying hi
okay we're the crewmates
that was so fast
hello can i have the floor please she
was walking out explain yourself
electrical
after excuse me taking off kiara's head
excuse me
i have i have the megaphone i have the
megaphone yes self report cause you
panicked uh excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
question okay i saw i was with kiara and
i saw
i go left and then i saw guru was also
in the room that kiara went
that was quick
but i don't know that doesn't mean it
wasn't inna
i watched it
for me
she was right behind
no you was right behind me you were by
yourself in electrical because i was
humming no no no no no
i was humming the berries in cream tune
and i was like i know where i live i
didn't hear that
that's where you killed me last time so
that's haha sugar girl sure
did i stop by the washroom i spawned and
i spawned in the place with the folder
on the table and i went right down to
electrical i don't remember how what
happened never stopped by the
[Laughter]
she wasn't in the washroom hmm she
wasn't in the washroom
we just spawned in i don't know i'm
pretty
i'm pretty convinced can i can i have
the room to stink because you didn't
shower
basically can i can i have a moment
please please
flopped her story she's gone from meek
and shy to very suddenly very demanding
of the room's
attention do i don't know
obviously
on youtube
i have nothing to say about it
should i not have voted i mean i did see
her
walk in
uh oh i probably shouldn't have spawned
here why are there so many
of these wow
um
it's so quiet
what
huh
four
wait do i have to do them in order
what
five how many
seven
i can't do this two
which one was three
three
uh
no seven
four
five
um
six
seven we did it
now we're gaming
this
this one
yes good okay
um
[Music]
it's so quiet
where is everybody
wait i should go this way
oh
hi mommy
being
weird
oh hi sana watch out mum is down there
did you see that hear her keyboard
it sounded like she was scrambling
she tricked me
oh yeah yeah hi try
trash okay there it is hold on i just
gotta shake it there we go
guys i'm doing the laundry
okay
she's
very
oh my gosh it's a dead end
why are you
she's like a silent killer right now
ah i knew it i knew it i knew it
i wanted to go back
[Applause]
i knew she was i should have
i gave her a pass because she's moving
but i should have just like ran to the
button that was
her keyboard movements were those of a
killer
i really nobody's on the right side yes
yes
yes yes
[Music]
that is
over here and then iris walked right
past my dead body you're so cut
on the right side and it said it was
okay and enough was also there so i went
back to the left side to do it but
[Music]
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know you
go for that kill you know yeah
okay i have a question
okay how is it okay that enables watch
of you for protection but it's not okay
if i do that i don't know
when on the very first round when i
reported when i reported ina absolutely
flipped her story and went from the
super meek i don't know where i'm going
to suddenly
super loud and embarrassed i don't know
as if she's trying to exactly
tell her a story
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other thing
she went to go do a task and she ignored
me and i yeah and i want to talk just
now
i did two imposters
did you notice how i was the only one
who voted for
this
did you notice that we were the only
ones who voted for girl and now we're
both dead and i kept having that
because you were being left alone with
ina and i don't know i haven't heard of
anyone
and i wanted somebody oh wait did you
not vote my wife
never mind never mind it was like i was
still getting wait you were dead that's
right you were dead you couldn't vote
i'm sorry
get them
infiltrated
here i'm i'm gonna go there
unbelievable
unbelievable what do you say i thought
about that what's unbelievable
but wait she didn't get kicked out yet
right she was she injected who grew up i
was too upset to see she wasn't she
didn't get rejected she wasn't
asked test
tusks
showered together we showered together
right oh yeah that's true
you will never know that you walked
right past my body
okay
turned into a wholesome interaction
oh
just doing my tasks just doing my task i
know no one's ever gonna move me out
ah
let me get these cuts
if only if only i had lived because she
was she was walking so weird and she
wasn't saying anything i think she tried
to kill me the first time but she missed
i should have ran to the button and and
reported her but how could i it's a
mummy
how could i
uh oh
perfect perfect
she called me evil
she she the first game she said stay
away from me
how
i am crying
i'm crying and shaking right now
but hey
i finished my tasks
actually
i've been needing to go
to the idol meeting
the other one is happening you know this
is kind of an idol meeting but
i i've been saying
i'm gonna go i'm gonna sneak out really
close i'll be back
for a moment
i cannot find the report
i just want to say something i just
graduated
you know going strong again
i think i saw her right before
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
i'm pretty sure she's in the clear too
we saw each other and didn't kill each
other so
that was okay as well
so girl you really could have killed me
okay
[Music]
but i mean i've ran into so many people
i have too many chances
your name no it's not let me answer the
question thank you the microphone is in
my hand uh because at the very beginning
of the match i was singing the berries
and cream song and i went into
electrical and right down here ina
beheaded that person
the story's changed get out okay
nice job detective you can't read your
own handwriting it didn't change
[Music]
i don't know i still
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
um so
[Music]
oh
is
you didn't accuse her of killing you
just said she was more suspicious
but now i actually heard
my mind cutting out
yes it is
[Applause]
all right all right where is everybody
i don't think it's
because
uh
if she was guilty she would not be
she would not sound so salty
excellent
where'd she go
no i'm gonna stick around too long just
in case
okay
iris
here we go
are you not yes i knew it oh my god
[Music]
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only ina came out
and then cronie came in and i said hi
cronie and then nina came in and i said
oh crony i'm gonna go see that body that
ena just left in there and lo and behold
there was the body of islands
holy [\h__\h]
i feel bad i mean i never i never voted
against you but i'm sorry i doubted you
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around i think that was good
i haven't killed anybody
no one suspects you man
well it is true that bae did notice that
she wasn't talking
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
did she get you too i know
run crowley run she's
giggling to herself she's giggling to
herself yeah
[Music]
mom
bobby
kitchen what do you
say to someone to make them feel guilty
for killing you
oh you're alone now i'm gonna
you're gonna have to
[Music]
we still won very nice
very nice
oh man yes
for gigi
i'm not very good at this game
[Music]
is
so it would have been difficult to find
out its moment unless we would have done
all the tasks so good job one good way
is just keep quiet
and positive
suffer moving with good adele because
no matter what
loving girls
i
[Music]
oh
um was like so strong against
the very first round i was like that's
kind of successful
yeah we can't even avina's crew i'm just
like maybe we should just vote
for this
[Music]
does everyone have imposters here dead
uh checked because it didn't yeah the
last round i think it's only yeah we
didn't work
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean i guess i died
too early but it's the same one
we're all right
[Music]
is
i
[Music]
what happened
um
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
i don't want to be killed first
anymore
i want to live
no why is it me
i'm never you
i missed one towel
ah
i never had the imposter in collabs
oh no i wish i was an imposter for a
moment oh definitely not
i'm scared of everyone that's all i have
to say
i thought the report thing flashed for a
second oh geez
all right let's just oh this is a long
one
oh hello
i wouldn't mind pulling like five more
rounds
what am i doing like five more rounds
nine o'clock i did some trash
hello
don't kill me
i'm i've decided that i will live this
this game
ah
[Music]
coney will get that side right
should we go
i just got it okay there we go oh you
just got it good job just got it
um i have one i don't want to go online
on this one
and let me put at the end
if we have three it should be same right
last time
this one
me too
two nine
eight nine one
okay three
i'm good
okay first guy
misha mom
[Music]
over there
i heard shouting
are you good
i'm good i did
are you doing talk i'm doing tasks
did you just do one yes
i'm just doing one now too
oh no
no
i'm a little scared
i don't trust anyone it's been good
doesn't mean that you haven't
i just love hearing snippets of what
people are saying
to their chats
no matter how many times you pull the
trash doesn't it doesn't do anything no
i just didn't but
it was broken no
iris iris iris how could you how could
you
oh
yeah okay i can't crony
this is
as a detective a beacon of the law
[Music]
oh
oh yeah
i don't know
yeah i think i'm going to skip but i'm
about mine
know yeah
i feel like
i could just because i'm not cracking
it might be i can like an egg
my brain was off so i was trying to talk
to the ghost i don't know why
i'm here
i was really cessing right
now imposter
do you think you're sending me otherwise
before i have no idea
i need to pay more attention i'm just
doing tests
i have not been paying attention to the
the case as it were
[Music]
who killed you it's convenient right now
it'll be all right
oh
we were alone and she could have killed
me but she just went off and did her
touch
kindly howdy i went on my way i saw
tiara and we
whatever it was sabotage i forgot what
it was crash course or whatever
i was in records but i didn't see
anything you weren't recording well
you're right council wasn't like this
yeah
i'm sorry
i don't
i don't know if those records it might
have been the room next to it i was
trying to go towards the other side
does it have the
table with the full gun
i'm not so sure
[Music]
know i think i thought it was records it
might not be records if you didn't see
me but i'm pretty i thought it was
records it's like
come on guys
huh i don't even know where the showers
are wait i don't know
that's the second time you haven't heard
a lot from mume or eno yeah
isn't it close oh i was all the way okay
i spawned in kitchen with mummy and then
i went to do my task in the uh the
bottom left thing of course called uh so
our suspects are iris and kiara got it
i don't know usually usually
would be like the duck thing it might be
like the most productive stuff but
gouda can't vote for me right
but i was i mean you didn't kill me
yeah yeah
[Music]
it's really easy to kill people
oh sorry we have 10 seconds
[Music]
i don't know
always giving me a funny vibe either i
made it
loudly in my ear oh man i love you so
much
she kills me
she's gonna kill you
she's gonna kill you she kills me she's
gonna kill you
i will
yeah after i finish my little class here
we go six
three five eight nine
okay
[Music]
uh-oh
did you see anyone full fall
pull in hole um
i have seen a few people
you're waiting here to push the
emergency button just in place
what's going on
i'm gonna give you a protection i will
follow you wherever you can you're
you're done oh no
we're gonna die
oh
i'll do them quickly oh hi
i have two more to go where is she i
have three more uh oh
look how fast i am
you ever see a ghost this fast
i don't think so
this is
did the sucky toilet okay guys bye bye
oh she's mentioning again
i was with ina and iris and kiara and i
left and i saw cali and then now
that will tell you
um
[Music]
somebody came in
yeah definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who
sure if they they both killed them
three times in a row
goodbye meep
emergency meeting
wait i didn't get to finish this task
i gotta do it i want to see the action
but i
i got it i gotta do it
i got it i gotta finish my tasks
one
more wait oh that was it i'm done
good ghost
all right let's see
if we can find anything hurry i'm gonna
get killed she's gonna kill me
oh it's very dangerous run
emergency meeting
you cannot no
she made it
that was pretty funny though got this
thing
oh man what a game
good virus
see you in another life
enjoy the background of space
[Music]
well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
to not kill people that's my job i feel
bad i feel bad yeah
such a good i'll be a good girl the rest
of us
put a leisure on me anytime anytime um
that's the most well random part of the
conversation what how could that be
i'm just
[Music]
i'm not going anywhere i'm not going
anywhere
[Music]
that was fun but oh my god
if only i didn't
[Music]
what are we going to discord are we
going back
oh
[Music]
it kind of gets questionable when you
get it three times people don't even
like trust you off the bats
it keeps giving imposter to like the
same people yeah yeah i was really
surprised that like you would assume
that you would assume that the reaper
would be like the number one killer of
everyone but i'm actually just the task
master like that yeah it's like
i do like the task
when i when i saw you kelly you were so
scared of death
i don't like yeah exactly we'll see
that's the thing is death can't die so
the prospect of death dying becomes a
thing it's quite frightening
i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other points
yeah i was like i was like okay if we
get a double kill like like this is good
but i couldn't say anything so i was
just trailing you around
i didn't know i didn't know if you were
on cooldown or not so
that's why i like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and then i see you went
somewhere else it's like oh no no the
double kill and then i think yeah yeah
all right
you didn't know where i was
right so yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah do you want to talk about it
yeah
coincidence but you know at the same
time like you know the senpai's i i
can't i can't go and kill my steps right
away
i like that i like that way of life good
good one
okay girls i'm gonna go through everyone
from top to bottom again to give a good
bye one by one and maybe tell me your
favorite moment from today or your
favorite kill or whatever so let's start
with amelia watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite moment who has your
favorite kill from today okay thank you
guys for watching and thank you kiara
for uh setting it up again and
organizing everything and my favorite
moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun
i gotta admit
are you gonna kill me she'd be like yeah
you're lucky my cooldown is off and like
run away
[Applause]
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you amelia next up
bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful
um
my favorite moment um wasn't actually in
game um it was when i went to have a
idol meeting and
everything wasn't mayhem just oh i like
it what was going on someone please
explain okay you know when you go to the
bathroom
and then they play the classic and then
your idol meeting yeah
yeah without chaos to manage your chaos
it's chaotic
it's more chaotic when chaos is not
there and that's that's the sad thing
you're gonna have to talk iris very soon
just keep waiting
now let's dial it back just a little bit
give me your goodbyes
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when i was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and i saw sana come up
behind me and i was like holy [\h__\h] this
is where i die
i hey callie and she just walked away
and she's like no i have to do my task
here and i was like okay so we just
switched spaces and we like watched out
for each other it was kind of cool the
bonding moment i was like
oh really
i thought that was so cute santa being
santa all day today
[Laughter]
i'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
yeah
it was really fun
thank you next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work
and i really appreciate it
uh my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
yeah i don't know i i think i prefer
natural indian posture
[Laughter]
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
i'm fine i'm fine i was saying i was
talking to my chat though about like how
i don't usually i don't have
conversations i don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not it's kind of like it feels
very draining uh mentally i guess
i don't like yelling at my friends
i don't know it's just a game i'm not
talking at all i had a lot of fun uh my
favorite moments were
uh and i'm asking clippers please uh the
various perfectly cut screams with the
proximity chat cali specifically the one
that one round where everybody was
terrified of me and every time somebody
would walk by me it would just be blood
curdling screams
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
uh compilation of some sort if there are
enough
[Music]
yeah thank you so much for organizing
this wonderful collab camera i love
among us to bits me too i'm so glad i
was able to do this and i i i would go
for among us like off stream anytime if
we had enough people oh yeah i like it
yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how cali you know when she
found fona's body was like it was me
boys
[Applause]
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words
yeah that was my personal favorite
genuine enthusiasm though
yeah
all the time
when you're uh
when you're imposter though because i
was playing safe i was like okay if i
get all the aggros and maybe the other
imposter can go on a killing spree oh
yeah
when i was in position i was like oh you
know probably i'm probably going to have
to be aggressive
i was trying to clear my name and that
was how i got out trying too hard to
clear my name
because i was yelling in her ear the
whole time
yeah
[Laughter]
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you no no no thank you so much for
arranging this
that's fine
once again
the freebie
thank you so much to kiara uh for
arranging this i really love this game
and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever
the the proximity chat exploded whenever
a meeting happened
and
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so
thank you for that
i want to have fun thank you cronie
next time
hello
thank you kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that
i'm blushing thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned and i said wouldn't it be
something if you're the imposter three
times in a row
yeah that really would be she just
walked away
[Laughter]
i was like floating i was like yeah it
would be really funny wouldn't it
be absolutely drenched in sweat
you know has so much blood on her hands
today
yeah i don't know i think it's killed on
many in the last two games um
well then
you know your goodbye and your your
favorite moments who who was your
favorite kill maybe
oh
best putting a knife for their stomach
well um
it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
the
uh crony in the it was in the first game
or something where she was like please
don't kill me i was like okay
you could have just said sure but oh
you like to get more
would be very scary and intimidating
though
every time when i was sussing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
i was so scared of you yelling at me but
i'm sorry it's you huh
no it's you know you reverse
okay santa give us your your goodbye and
your favorite moment please okay thank
you very much for organizing the collab
cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while
[Music]
pretty much every time i heard cali
scream but now
yes
spending time with all of you guys
i wish i could hug you i want to give
you a big huge
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because i believe everything you guys
say
i don't know
the video
it's so innocent
all right well um uh for me my favorite
moments when i had so many but i guess
the one that uh stayed in my head now is
um i think it was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was assessing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really mad and then
ahmed was like well i'm going to follow
you to see if you're really innocent and
i was like chilling with inna as ghosts
and we were just like
that accruing
just standing there together as ghosts
and then ahmed and guna ran into the
room having a huge fight like disgusting
a kindergarten fight on her head
[Laughter]
oh man but yeah um it was it was a i'm
really glad this all worked out fine in
the end uh you know i had some troubles
in the beginning but i'm so relieved
yeah i'm i'm sorry about the joke no
don't be sorry
yeah yeah yeah it worked out for sure as
the organizer i'm just happiest that
everyone had fun and and no hold on
scuff was that present today
thank you for participating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes i agree with that
yeah it was a blast i'll kill you we
could do this some time again in the
future yeah yeah
hell yeah i want you to know everybody
yeah
christmas among us
yeah i'm sure there's other games too we
can try to find yeah
one more thing i kind of want to do is
like because i organized the ian id
mario kart tournament now that we are 11
years we could do a full en my
tournament as well yeah
11 people like not 12 by 11. is it just
one of the one of the people are going
to be bought is that what it is yeah one
of them probably a bot i think or you
can just leave that one out i mean we
can just do it
you don't have to
join as
well it is uh past five a.m for me so i
hope we can and
we'll get our next one yeah
do you have an announcement
oh sorry an announcement or
oh do you want to announce something oh
yeah yeah yeah
um i have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
huh
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down walking down
your calendars boys girls and friends
[Music]
i'm just really saying it's genuinely
gonna be amazing yeah amazing amazing
this was amazing too
yeah this is so much fun this looks
great
no no no we're not only myths
three
two
one
[Music]
you