[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
assistant
foreign
[Music]
thank you
Christmas
[Music]
ah
chicken again
[Music]
today also I am in 3D and once again in
a different yokata it's a cute by the
way
foreign
[Music]
I have the the hand thingy on but
um
it's kind of really laggy today
like it moves like this oh my God I
don't know the other day it was not so
laggy I think it has to do with how
uh suffering the phone isn't currently
like it's so hot I'm touching it right
now
do you see it where is my hand phone do
you know well it even says that uh
currently it's like high
high load of stress
um
hello
so um Freddy today yeah yeah just you
know
um sometimes sometimes I can show my
hands but they are lagging
[Music]
um
uh also
I chose
I didn't know it's called Ragtime I uh I
was looking for a certain genre of music
that I heard the other day and I was
like um
so now I know it's called ragtime
it's kind of it's not Jazz it's Jazz but
it's it's Jazzy but it's not Jazz right
it's like yes salute somebody said also
Saloon music I agree swingy swingy
swingy
wait
[Laughter]
um
there it is
I found like two that maybe could work
as looping music most of them were not
loopable also I made some snacks like
snack uh cherry tomatoes and salami
sticks but uh in the loading screen I
ate like half of the tomatoes already
um
so I can get through this you know
because I only had breakfast
[Music]
you already also I have um
watermelon in the fridge
[Music]
salt or Peppa no not on tomatoes but
um
I do like to put salt on cucumber slices
that's so yummy um
right I thought so I thought Ragtime
might be fun kind of music to listen to
when I read super chats I had a feeling
[Music]
wait let me fix my I'm kind of like
tilted let me fix this
Bella I'm sitting by the way
I don't know why the sitting pose is
made so that the hands are just floating
I don't know maybe it's because some
girls have like bigger skirts and they
want to make sure that the hands don't
go inside so so you just make it so that
it awkwardly floats on top okay
okay does this look okay now wait I'm
Too Tall now maybe
and too big Maybe
[Music]
how is my it's hard to tell
me my my chat is broken again what do I
do YouTubers work recently it's just you
know because Susan but Susan was not
here with us anymore so who do I blame
[Music]
I just snack until you guys are back
but at least it's not just me
[Music]
um
this is so fitting for a really long
Super Chat reading
you guys saw the clip the other day
a clip of me where they used bgm with
rectum hi
um
and I was like oh I need to find out
what this is called I have to ask kfp
because they know everything
[Music]
um
you can see me eating putting the Tomato
in my mouth
[Music]
hmm
the other one is this
[Music]
it starts
quiet
yeah YouTube chat dying so much
is this right time to
it was titled as Ragtime but Ragtime for
cats
foreign
this one's better
oh
oh there's a bubble machine
yeah this this is ragtime too I think
[Music]
I think
I think so many but a lot of them were
not looping
um
probably because I didn't type in them
oh banjo piano and banjo ragtime
oh you guys can't hear that well thank
God because it would have probably
broken your ears
Google Chrome
wow there we go
[Music]
is Banjo allowed to be in Ragtime
is this really ragtime
[Music]
and what about what about this one this
one looks like it Loops because you can
see visually like
the music Visions thingies so I can
guess
that's not
that's not chaos
let me type in
okay there's like
barely any loopable ones oh what about
this one it was short though
[Music]
clapping
it doesn't quite look like it I'm more
like dancing with my hands but I'm
clapping
[Music]
oh wow
is this really Ragtime I'm starting to
doubt I don't know anymore what Ragtime
is at this point
Too Short though
oh
this is long and loopable I like it it
sounds good let me get let me get that
one
Dixieland what's Dixieland is that also
a genre
oh my God now now with the hand tracking
what if you see every time I touch my
nose because of cat hairs and and you
think it's you know something
something that's not
yeah yeah
yeah
my head tracking in 3D is like so toned
down like damn my mouth tracking too
to use my Freddy so much on stream like
this home pretty
because I don't I feel like I move way
less it's like so stiff
right how's the track and forget about
better because of blend shapes
blend chips
and did you see I'm in she got
um blend shapes
she used one of her wishes to improve
her 3D
face tracking but I'm just sitting here
thinking shouldn't this be like
company-wide you know like we got life
to the improvements so shouldn't we also
get 3D improvements but apparently it's
a lot of work
[Music]
to create 51 blend shapes for every
person because you have to apparently
over work the whole model
I mean not really but you can't just
copy paste it apparently
and yeah so now there's like suicide
Senpai has it and Ahmed has it
and I think Cali is getting it
but using a 1 million wish for that I
just
nah but it's not like seriously Senpai
used 1 million which as far as I know
she she got it like in combination with
her concert
no
Maria I feel so stiff you know I think
it would be nicer if we can just even
get this I think I've mentioned this
before either get it as like a half
million like 500k reward that you can
wish for no it's smaller
smaller Rewards
or
no
oh oh my God see my life today has um
eyebrow tracking
but my Freddy has no eyebrow tracking
like okay even my life the team has not
not good eyebrow tracking but they're at
least not set in stone these ones are
and uh I saw Ahmed with her new stuff
her eyebrows move and it oh
it's just so much more expressive and so
much better
um
no I'm not coming up on a milestone
because I don't get anything for 1.5
even though it's taking me years I don't
get anything for 1.5
but I'm gonna ask
[Music]
I'm gonna ask I'm gonna I feel like I
wanna I'm thinking of making a petition
[Music]
ask every en member to sign it
and request consideration because
compared to Corona times generally
growth in whole life is not as big as
two years ago so maybe it could be
considered to add 500k
rewards smaller ones such as
3D face tracking Improvement
I'm gonna try
you know like
maybe that has more of an impact oh my
God I'm down to two cherry tomatoes and
here goes one more oh
I have to wash it now okay well then let
me eat the other one I picked it up
though and I'll wash it later
but I guess that's my lunch I was gonna
eat it throughout the stream but I
couldn't stop myself
mm-hmm
[Music]
salami sticks
yeah I have to wash off the cat hair
no there was no meow
okay
um
everybody
[Music]
I should
um
where is it
here yes
[Music]
this I want on screen
maybe here
and then I want this time because we
have so many super chats I'm gonna use
hololizer again
to show it on screen
while reading it but let me just uh
clear all
Taps and stones
[Music]
what's up
I should have wished for more wishes
yeah yeah the the genie in the bottle
logic yeah I wish
imagine trying that I don't think anyone
would take me seriously
Chihuahua what do you want for your one
million was
um more wishes please
nobody's gonna take me seriously
are you talking about be serious
Chihuahua
you're serious with us now please
okay where do we even start guys where
do we even start with super chats
somebody for sure
made an effort
to look for you
Zelda part eight okay
you know when I put up the this waiting
room while I was in Japan for the
concert I was gonna put up a
um
pinned comments saying I am not going to
be reading these super chats in the
Super Chat reading stream or whatever I
was gonna put that up and then I was
thinking Hmm
hmm I'll be fine
I
I'll be fine
so I didn't but now in hindsight I
regretty spaghetti I wish I did
so you guys say eight but did I read
them or did I read
um did I read part eight or did I stop
at right before party
[Music]
I should have I should have
that pinned comment up but now in
hindsight like afterwards I don't want
to do that you know I don't want to be
like I'm not reading these ones by the
way
I stopped before it really
Mamma Mia
bum
okay
let me just do some things
[Music]
I'm gonna clean up my
what do you call it cat bookmarks in
case I accidentally flashed them again
because there's so many things I don't
use there
and you might be like
[Music]
God I can't believe she had
n't there's so many like half of this
stuff I don't use it
what is all this
put them in a folder
you could have fold but then
can have folders
wait
Google why are you not here
email
or shh okay I don't know I don't know
what these things are what are these
bangs what is that what is that
what else could I bookmark that I
actually use
colonizer
[Music]
laughs
okay
[Music]
apparently
we don't even use those Excel sheets
anymore by the way because people
probably are like whatever what are
those exo sheets why does she have I
actually have two game safe list extra
sheets
oh I don't even know
I don't even know but uh we don't we
don't use that anymore really I'm
partially Maybe
yeah okay
[Music]
now let me
um Studio mode
[Music]
and then we'll have a
ction
[Music]
thank God for Studio mode
window title must match alrighty
okay
foreign
[Music]
here we have it
she can feed oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
is it I know I know anyone I know that
one is it the horror one
or what if it's the horror one then I am
I'm gonna play that for
Halloween
isn't this another episode no it's not
the paper okay wait let me change
[Music]
okay
ah let's go starting to win I thought
it's just a Super Chat reading stream I
don't need a starting tweet it's not so
important and people who want to be here
they they will find their way ah
um
I don't have to read them I choose to
read them
um
aeon master and Rosa
weird weird part in the salami
okay guys okay guys we're gonna read
all of the super chats
after 5 45
you have to get up in 5.5 hours or no
oh no
good night
yes
um
let me drink some
drink wow you're gonna see me opening
the bottle
[Music]
hand tracking very scuffed today but the
other day at the collab it was pretty
good
um
[Music]
got him
got him got him
aren't they over a thousand yeah
believe believe in me
um
all right okay okay
47 alteration blank
Blanca let's go language
he who eats faces
[Music]
wait should I write down which ones
these are uh
should should I need a thumbnail too
don't die
this one
hi okay perfect salad
perfect setup
And So It Begins okay
I'm gonna be speeding through those
y'all
Productions
[Music]
um
I think I read that yeah
oh yeah very emotional indeed
[Music]
oh wow deep [\h__\h] evidence
oh
I am planning it thank you human
extension Checker 47 alteration Astro
tadpole donations
[Music]
thank you
it's about spare spear spare spear
hi Ultima Duncan black Richard
thanks for the pinky because I just
noticed that I'm finally Phoenix
I'm proud of being one I'm happy to be
part of your community and I'm happy to
have been here this long keep up the
hard work and I'll continue to support
my favorite verb Viva lucky wow yeah
yeah thank you oh can I make a heart no
not really
like this
no trying to do Korean Arts
no
that's not what it looks like
I tried
anyway thank you for the pinky yay
congratulations on being a beautiful
Phoenix
hybrid don't forget that
placement thank you I pray
[Music]
I prayed that life decisions rise of
reduction spanking him finished
[Music]
next
the Diablo one
GG easy
we are still laughing but we will lose
our smile soon enough
[Music]
so I switch
wait
a switch
this is it oh my God
let's make it smaller
okay here we go
home money I need to
[Music]
yeah I also didn't think I was that far
behind what the hell
Japan you know that I did I did I did
Twitter spaces but I didn't
you know I did one stream and then the
waiting room there was no time to read
and then I came back and it was my
birthday it was just too much going on
you know
[Music]
come on
and I want to see Kiana who is bad at
games in real time but unfortunately I
have to go to work tomorrow oh when I
wake up in the morning I'll see a
collection of funny that KIA all right
um
[Music]
no no I didn't die single time I think
I think yeah it was easy
sorry about that if you want to sing
Kiowa die a lot Maybe
what games did I play recently where I
would die a lot I mean Minecraft even
Minecraft I don't die much in Zelda died
sometimes
but if you go a little bit back I guess
guess
I died a lot in pineapple and pizza
and
Hotline Miami yeah yeah I was just gonna
say Hotline Miami
but I I was I don't know it wasn't like
oh I die and I'm like frustrated and sad
about it no no
it was my pleasure I had a great time
every time yeah met Ryan oh that's right
I was dying and I was frustrated about
it yeah
that is another story
[Music]
thank you for the pinky calling 4K oh
yeah
hey I suggested the hashtag and they
were like oh that's cute yeah let's go
with it
they liked it
so we used it
Patsy Duncan
little piece of [\h__\h] thank you thank you
Marcus Menace says
[Music]
thanks for the painting A wise man once
said may just killed in five seconds
dies in Two
eh and I think that applies to Sorcerers
who is the wise man
they just kill him five seconds dies
into
oh cause you die before you kill I think
that applies wait who said that good
then you have 4K party to cover you and
even if you die you'll arise fast like
like a phoenix you are burn them all
with streaming Sparks Look Away Jenkins
oh oh you're making it up and you're
just adding that
[Music]
no one said that
wise man
yeah I mean I don't know I I I don't
think the majors even gets to kill
normally
I mean if we go by that logic that may
just may just die so fast yeah I agree
with that but I mean in other games
but like that and and from my
experiences they didn't even get to kill
[Music]
because they need better healers healers
need to up their game
shitty Healers
we came faster and more more
[Music]
and the tank yeah why why the tank no
keep the aggro yeah maybe the tank doing
something wrong yeah you blame the Mage
for pulling the aggro well that means
you just not strong enough to keep the
aggro well
[Music]
don't blame DPS all the time you know
touch my what
can I touch my elbow using my elbow
well I mean but you know
do like a heart you know so everything's
really inaccurate right now my fingers
are touching so I don't think we can
even do this you know but wait here my
hands it doesn't track elbows you know
it just attracts the hands no I can't I
probably can't and Bones you can ask me
doing to do that when I am wearing my
full body pretty suits
or whatever
or mokopi or whatever maybe it works
with one copy I know exactly what you're
trying to do with that I know exactly
but I'm just saying like it even if I
were able to touch him
then he wouldn't show
right now
I mean no my iron post totally I can't
no no they're totally they totally can't
touch there's definitely something in
the way
I also cannot see my feet at any time
even even when I sit
and have my feet to the side
[Music]
I cannot even see my feet when somebody
takes a picture of them and shows them
to me directly into my face
because my brain cancels out my feet
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I told you to catch the stream on your
birthday
got it
juicy salami
[Music]
to say
Havana
right
that's how Super Tires look no on
YouTube it looks different but I'm using
whole Eliza because it's easier it's
like a fan made website that picks up
super chats it's just easier to see you
know it's sorted by stream and
everything
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
[Music]
IO Castle
depends on the time of day
where was I
[Music]
I hear
I am a team
dancing soon
oh
Nintendo Direct was so good okay iron
reduction
no no
no muffin hate thanks for the pinky
very exciting thank you I'm I am I'm am
greatly looking forward to ff16 please
pass the whole time I have my window
open I'm smelling fish sticks the whole
time from outside
someone's making fish sticks yummy these
past collapse have been fun by the way
one of the GBA Fire Emblem games is
getting put on the switch virtual
console this week oh if you need
something to play on your trip and
connect them nah I already had uh
cane
[Music]
it's so hot
let me turn on the fan
[Music]
[\h__\h] hot so hot I went swimming
oh so refreshing
um
I'm going swimming a lot and honestly
I'm even noticing little Improvement in
my
um like endurance in the pool
how much I can swim
I mean I always I go like one forward
one backward and then I wait
so I don't over exert myself with my
breathing
and then I go on one more lane and then
I wait for one or two minutes and then I
go another Lane and I wait
you know for a while I continue that
yeah I am trying to improve my my back
problems and at the same
from this shitty [\h__\h] sucky summer
[Music]
oh yeah it definitely cools me down
God because like it's a [\h__\h] Heat
Wave right now
I'm freaking again
foreign
I
honestly have to start
with little low level weights
but one what happens if I'm like
too strong for that and then I upgrade
and then I'm just trying for that too
and then I upgrade again like what
happens to all the smaller weights
what are you doing those
[Music]
hmm
Shalom hmm
get rid of them upgrade them at the
blacksmith I wish that could work
but honestly it's not like I'm aiming to
be able to lift like 20 kilogram or
whatever
so I might not even upgrade more I feel
like I'm fine
just being able to comfortably him
endlessly lift the two kilogram per arm
I think that's already link all I need
and want
[Music]
maybe maximum four maximum four I don't
need more than that I'm not trying to be
buff I'm just trying to be able to carry
my groceries or or just function like a
normal human being
[Music]
and I mean also it's more about my
shoulders anyway
[Music]
eat chickens you think chickens is
something I can do already
[Music]
oh
wait you know what
how early
in case there are you buy Super chats
I know earlier where where am I anyway
maybe around here
yay thank you for letting me know about
the fire blender but yeah I don't I
don't think I'm gonna be playing that
uh anytime soon
[Music]
he is Han Solo his hands so low he's Han
Solo his hand so low so low
[Music]
Han Solo I'm so low his hands Solo solo
thank you for them remember message
[Music]
16 is a free demo saves carry over to
the main game oh I didn't have time for
it anyway
um
in Diablo 4 in killshad go to a dog use
the hello emote and you can pet the dog
oh really
just useless facts may be helpful I love
working for you and kfb hey
ah
good employee thank you so much thank
you
wait I'll be going straight to the
actual game I don't need the demo
um
dog petting tips that is very insightful
yes I might use that if you guys remind
me
I might have to be reminded yeah
thank you I love it that you're here
hello how you doing
boom
[Music]
you know which wolf I was trying to do
I have mokopi here now by the way I need
to at some point figure out how to use
it but I
honestly the rest of this month
is just me running around
between countries
busy as [\h__\h] also
[Music]
um
yeah never mind don't want don't worry
don't worry middle finger I can try but
the other day when I tried that I felt
like it was like censoring my middle
finger and yeah and changing it to this
one
but I'm like
come on
it doesn't it's like it has a sensor in
it so that
I don't ruin my reputation or something
ah it was there for a second
[Music]
I think there's an autocorrect you know
Auto finger correct
ah
say Subaru but if you raise your foot I
can't that's that's I don't know you
mean wait which one my ring finger yeah
I thought so too that maybe then no if I
raise my ring finger it raises my my
little finger
and also I can't raise that one so
properly anyway
small finger
a ring finger
um
middle finger
[Music]
um
this one and this one it's it's just
scuffed but it's cute sometimes
haha
thumbs up good job good job
oh wow wow
[Music]
good
blank wait Taco Tech
[Music]
blank face with a pink sticker let's go
Dominic okay thank you thank you wait
who are you happy birthday
yourself
or
don't know
[Music]
I'm just shortening words
oh happy belated birthday
soon
uh
it's like mixed in
oh and now uh
[Music]
doesn't scroll down anymore so
I will show
these all it should be fine thank you
for providing us with the Union room
what is a great space for meeting the
Timken leaders and discussing workplace
improvements
[Music]
I don't remember providing such a thing
no I don't remember that
no
[Music]
hello
no no
that that's not I don't think that
exists yeah sounds fishy
smells fishy about this fishy as those
fish sticks outside smell
no no no
no I think you you made the mistake I
think that you are it stands for usual
room you simple mistake to make a lot of
people make those mistakes sometimes
don't worry about it
thanks for the pinky
beautiful
thank you just like you almost almost as
beautiful as you beautiful chicken thank
you
[\h__\h] we did
soon
[Music]
in the end I mean I think it all went
well
um I'm not sure if everybody like
followed my instructions but it doesn't
matter because people were having fun
and just you know did whatever they
thought it was fitting and in the end I
think it was fine at least you guys know
now what ketchup is
even if there was maybe a lot of ketchup
at times where there shouldn't have been
ketchup but I mean you do you if you
want to do catch on and go on and catch
up but don't forget the mayonnaise
[Music]
don't forget the mayonnaise
oh yeah if you guys have any questions
in terms of pen lights and things to do
what's okay to do what's that okay to do
and and how to do anything at all just
ask jinlo like he knows his [\h__\h]
he knows the
OTA industry in and out
like his back pocket
um
[Music]
hydration proof life on camera
don't shove pen lights down to anyone's
throat yeah
yeah
reasonable reasonable thought
oh yeah he's easy to spot too yeah
the one who stands out the most you know
in terms of like
um
Vibes yeah
okay these are done
[Music]
what's next Minecraft is next
chato
foreign
[Music]
remember one year let's go thank you
one year
this Fountain was so cute
isn't it so cute
teeth are so detailed
[Music]
if you look closely
you don't know about it
oh I asked by the way I asked Kaila
if she wants to hang a bit during my
next Minecraft stream she said yeah what
do we want what do you want to do
so I think Kyla might be around
[Music]
I was thinking of yeah I gotta I gotta
finish my stupid Tunnel right
[Music]
um
uh and then
yeah I I when I finish it I mean she
could help me finish it or afterwards I
wanna maybe find
the other things
that are
new with this update
like
camel camel
I don't care about armored trims to be
honest
[Music]
camel
there's camels right
I want to find Campbell
[Music]
soon and again dungeon face with a pinky
keep on like adorable ocean why are you
so cute
[Music]
um
I'm gonna eat this tomato now
because I there's no hair on it it's
clean
yeah yeah yeah yeah don't worry so much
[Music]
no because
it was still a little bit wet so with
the wetness I could wipe off anything of
the Tomato because it has a really
smooth surface and you know and then I
saw it there wasn't anything on it okay
this was it was only on the ground for
three seconds yeah
[Music]
don't be so dramatic
you're so dramatic
anyway
what's gotten into you huh to write that
right in the beginning what happened
is it the thumbnail being so cute
understandable
Garden Park why are you in the chat you
should be sleeping
[Music]
excited for GTA 4 let's go it's been a
while did I play GTA 5 last year because
it feels like it's a million years ago
one GTA game per year keeps the doctor
away
last summer oh
yeah that's fun looking forward to it I
mean people told me that you know the
more that the the lower I go in terms of
like release order
the more janky controls and everything
will be
[Music]
so that's gonna be interesting since I'm
only used to GTA 5. but GTA 4 you know
it's still one of the better ones I only
heard that some car the car controls
are not so good
we'll see we'll see
[Music]
I guess we'll have to walk more or like
I guess in GTA 5 I never made use of you
know the teleporting stuff
does GTA 4 have it then we can most of
the time try to just use that
yeah Taxi
[Music]
we'll use that more often then
um if it's really that annoying
[Music]
thank you
come outside let's go
I saw some tweets from you coming up in
my Twitter timeline I'm glad you enjoyed
it so much
good for you
okay
thanks for
a freaking rainbow
Mamma Mia Mamma Mia it's beautiful thank
you you gave us a ton of Tweets in the
last 24 hours did I
I counted around 30 tweets including
replies I was looking in the Carefree
handbook and you fried the quota under
acceptable social operations
for giving us too much extra hour time
Naveed is also correct I did the
calculations and your kidneys levels
have also busted upon the cuteness ratio
exciting productive employees
[Music]
[Applause]
that calculation is usually flat and a
little fruity and yours what
is ah wait because craps are usually
flat
but you are still entitled to a big
super Chad also the sweet gaining extra
language ability towards overseas
Simpkins
[Music]
section of the handbook gives you an
orange support keep fighting on that top
Korean you got this oh yeah it's rough I
was gonna do a Korean study stream like
tomorrow
but then I thought well
I should just take another day off and
then just study privately
sorry guys if you wanted to see it but
I think I'll do a couple more
um Korean study streams after my
actual lessons are done
so when I have no teacher anymore just
to keep you know the info in my brain
and maybe learn a little bit more
but just to keep it in there hmm
so you guys will have to deal with that
for the sake of me remembering Korean
Korean movie went along
[Music]
um
I don't think that will help me much at
this level but I did notice that you
know I can already understand
uh a lot of single words
uh
when I watch like Korean stuff
um
on YouTube
[Music]
pretty noise
and finally the lead
ER aggressive stretching after getting
noodle arms claws has many layers but I
can give you a yellow Super Chat for
that
something wrong with that I have a
feeling it doesn't actually exist
just saying we appreciate your hard work
for us boss I hope the shoulders feel
better thank you my shoulders never feel
better
but
thank you for the funny super chatos
I I I I am
a little bit confused but you used my
favorite words and therefore got my
attention
[Music]
thank you so much
uh-huh
[Music]
foreign
we gotta be careful here
Pandora
[Music]
heck yeah I'm so happy your stream
helped me past time as I just had oral
surgery oh no can you say hi and wish me
fast recovery thanks for all you do well
I hope by now you already recovered
are you
are you here
it's been quite a while so maybe even
now you are recovered but get well soon
if you're still in pain I hope you're
doing okay
I wish you the best thank you for the
recipe chat here
[Music]
and
I'm being very careful here
jenma told me
[Music]
this is okay
and open the mic Direction every time I
go to Japan for Hanami I see hot and
cute chicks around chocolate now I see
one too who is going to be around
true true she's the cutest I have seen
so far
hmm
nice
puns hot chicks
I wanna see chickens under Sakura trees
how aesthetic
but you do actually go to Japan for
hanamido
gosh no voice I saw it like once or
twice
purposefully
and then I was like yeah nice
but I feel like I need like a group
or friends to go and enjoy it properly
because I don't know so far
just didn't I feel like you know I
didn't I didn't get the most out of it
[Music]
well Sakura season already over for this
year anyway
[Music]
Japan around Sacramento season next year
um
[Music]
foreign
let's go how dare you play the game you
want and not like we want to well
Minecraft
and
I know I know it's uh sarcastic but yeah
thank you next tune
[Music]
but I shouldn't really be supporting it
so you know Vijay the Moomin silly Mr JC
thank you soon
granulas from got subsidian
really what
huh
oh really
[Music]
I don't know that's not really funny
I'm trying to
um
[Music]
I'm so sorry I tried to entertain you
isn't that joke or be entertained
foreign
[Music]
the moment she heard about me buying new
PC parts she asked me can I get you old
ones
oh how the turbo stain
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
you know when I start saying these
things wrong I purposefully sometimes I
just don't stop myself because I know
this like Midway fruit and oh I'm saying
something wrong but I'm just like
letting it go to see what happens to see
how it ends up it's
just yo something funny will come out of
it surely
maybe this time I should have stopped
myself
[Music]
I just wanted to say where I'm going you
know and this time I I went I went
overseas
that's like Michael Scott's really
is that
I am I am the best MIP speaker of Ian
what wait wait wait I forgot baited
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay the heat is going things to me oh
he's just selling things to me
all right
the best move speakers
[Music]
oh my God
oh God
funny frog I ate a funny frog
[Music]
put it that way purposefully after after
I said it I'm like there's no way I just
read that wrong it must have been how
you wrote it but I checked and no I I
what I don't know
no
okay calm down mm-hmm
cat hair and Danny with the funny
I'm Danny with the funny
fredpanda James Jackson Andrew swollen
dance
ah
can't scroll again but I think I think
the rest of the comments are looking
okay
so I'm showing them
um
[Music]
I need to bring her but you know
recently I mean it's fine we have found
a rhythm she wakes me up at sometime
between eight and nine am
I wake up I give her food quickly half
asleep then I go to idle meeting really
quick because usually usually
like when I sleep I wake up around the
end anyway a million times because my
back hurts from knitting needing to go
let something go and honestly I just
take this opportunity for that and then
you know I would have woken up later on
anyway so whatever you know what a deal
yeah what a deal
you guys not get like
really strong back pain
[Music]
from I don't know over the night from
having to go
no
I mean I just always have back pain but
I I noticed that once I go and I go back
to bed
then it's better
weird
but not from big small just small
yeah my my kidney is my bladder I don't
know or something I don't give the back
pain I think I think it's lower back
anyway
[Music]
I'll never asked a doctor about it do
you wrong to your stomach
uh I I sleep in every position both
sides on my back and on my
tummy both
how scrunched is your bladder pushed
against your spine yeah
[Music]
yeah good question I think um generally
there's a lot of things wrong with my
body but last time I got like an x-ray
you know
and when I was at the warfro orphro guy
I know they don't seem to be very
interested in me
I think once like I was told
my spine is not I think my spine is not
good I mean there's a lot of people who
don't have a completely straight back
but that was long long time ago many
years ago
and then
you know when I started more and more
going to the doctor to check out what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with me uh like last
year and last last year
[Music]
um you know I always complained about
like shoulder back neck pain everything
and then they sent me to get an x-ray
right but they only had me get an x-ray
for a close-up part of my
upper spine that where it's around
um
the neck I think
they didn't look at the whole picture
and that's always the thing where I was
like well
you're not gonna find much are you I
don't know couldn't it be elsewhere you
know the issue
[Music]
yeah I always wanted to do like more
like an MRI and all that but the doctor
is not like you know
thinking it's necessary so they're not
sending me there and and I feel like you
know doctors don't like it when you like
can can I do this and this and this
because I think I have this and this and
this
um
like usually it's like you gotta you
gotta
rely on the doctor to make the decisions
where to send you no no
I haven't really bothered to
um
go back on a doctor trip for a while
because it's just too frustrating to me
I wasted so much time last year on that
and came out with nothing
and yeah just wasted so much time and I
just felt so stupid and and and uh
now I'm just focusing more on doing it
myself
which in the end I think I'll probably
come out with a better result no because
I'm just now trying to strengthen my
back
[Music]
and hoping that that will finally help
strengthening my shoulders and back and
going to massage all the time
to get a little bit of relief Pain
release
um
[Music]
more back muscles helps the back a lot
yeah people keep on saying that so I'm
trying my best to keep up with
that now that's why I bought the
the weights and why I bought the the
flexible thingy and that's why I keep on
going swimming also
foreign
I wish the doctors could have helped me
more but you know
we're just gonna get super buff up there
and then
hopefully we'll have no more issues I'll
have no more issues or at least it will
be a little bit better yeah
I mean in the end you know
it's basically like I'm doing physical
therapy on myself but
on my own so it's not as I'm more
lenient about it than if I would go
there in person and have someone
instruct me but it's okay it's okay at
least I'm doing something hmm
and I noticed I can swim more I I have
yet to notice any Improvement on my back
pain but I can at least swim more
so there's something improving right for
now
um
we'll we'll I'll get there I'll get
there
surely someday
foreign
[Music]
until finally found the issue years
later I recommend you keep trying before
it gets worse
we'll see how far we get with
exercising on my own yeah
oh
mixture of standing sitting while
working although even bought a neck pill
that helps prevent me from shrimping
wait while sleeping or like while
working
yo I really wonder what like
because I have I got chronic um back
pain right at this point back shoulder
neck everything because it's been going
on for
I don't know 15 years
uh so I wonder if I I'm already like I
have like permanent damage somewhere
that cannot really be undone
no I'm not even counting fibromyalgia
that's in my mind that's separate
I have separate issues
[Music]
what kind of bed did you sleep in
hey
[Music]
hotels too so you know you'd think I've
tried many different beds
and I it's always the same I I always
have the same pain
so I'm not sure if we can really blame
my my bed but currently
especially in recent days I
have
uh like I wake up so often with like my
neck feeling like I slept really badly
sleep on the Big Orange bean bag I was
the bean bag on my balcony and then when
when this movie starts meowing at me
going on a balcony and sleeping out
there
[Music]
big enough and then I would definitely
not hear her
because I can really not hear her when
I'm outside
[Music]
I don't know recently
I didn't change my pillow really but I
just feel like I'm always sleeping wrong
the past couple of days that my neck
keeps on
[\h__\h] itself over
[Music]
there it's okay though as I said going
back on the topic I I I've I've I've
come to the acceptance stage right now
this is how it is I have not even yet uh
turned on the the cat food dispenser
thingy because I didn't have time to
figure out how to set it up
um but for now it's okay
she wakes me up at eight
I do that you know I give her the food
reluctantly we're not even reluctantly
at this point I I accepted it I do it
then I go to idle meeting and I go back
to sleep
and usually that's it now now she like
last night
she actually did not wake me up again
after that sometimes she does but last
night she didn't
um
and she she was just happily sleeping
with me on my bed afterwards
just like chunky wonky
yeah she trained me I also started
giving her like you know I always give
her half a package in the morning and
then the next half on the next morning
but now I started just giving her the
second half in the night before we go to
sleep
hoping that she'll take more time that
she won't be so hungry again anytime
soon but it doesn't really
help because I noticed
I give her that we go to sleep four
hours later she wakes me up for
breakfast
[Music]
which is I think just because it's
bright outside so she her brain thinks
oh it's breakfast time
no matter when she ate before
Bieber
she's one hungry for baby yeah and
stoppable food machine it's okay
honestly at this point it's okay and the
the new headphones I'm
I I I you know I could use them but then
I feel kind of bad if I'm really
ignoring her I would feel kind of bad
but the headphones are just nice to have
I'm glad I have the headphones now this
is a tangent yeah I need to I need to
talk about it
I got really cool headphones I tested
them I haven't been using them on my PC
yet though but damn those are that's
like next level noise canceling and
people pointed it out in replies on my
tweets
on my tweet and I agree that this will
be very very nice to have in my next
plane ride
but honestly if website with some
um Airlines
uh I've experienced some of them give
you
um noise canceling headphones for
listening to whatever you're playing on
the screen
more and more airlines are
offering that even already in economy
slash premium economy
they're not as good as my new ones
obviously but they do a decent amount of
noise canceling
[Music]
the problem is the other day when I had
that
my whole like audio system in my seat
was apparently kind of broken because it
had this
never-ending teeny tools
[Applause]
faint
sound in there
so it was kind of uncomfortable to
listen to
yeah and then the next time I flew oh my
God it's saying critical now my phone
says it's in a critical state
but yeah next time it didn't have that
so I I think it's it wasn't the
headphones because I asked them to
change them
and I got different ones and it was
still the same thing so it was like the
seats the connection or whatever but
then on the next slide it was uh
gone because I had a different seat so
it was that seat
but whatever what does that mean I don't
know on our app we have um
I don't know it says
there's like different states like
right now it's red and critical
depending on how much
um I have to say how much pressure it
puts on on the system
it's just really really yeah it's
overheating for sure
it's doing okay I've never had to say
critical before though
critical critical critical hit very good
critical damage very welcome
the phone is dramatic yeah
how many tabs no tabs
[Music]
what my hand is not there
what
yeah we'll see what happens
yeah
oh but I got a new one I got a new one
[Music]
I really like the old one but the
support for the old one is not there not
gonna be there anymore so we got a new
one and
um
the problem is that
the old one I've had since my debut
and Grandma
janma back then
she gifted me
and a fan made
design
iPhone cover
and I've been using it since
and it doesn't fit on this phone this
new phone
so now I just have this empty shell
of the cover lying around I don't want
to throw it away but it also doesn't fit
on the new one
[Music]
I'm so sad I don't wanna I don't wanna
throw it away Jen ma the new phone model
I don't know what's this I don't know
what this one is I don't know I don't
know anything about iPhones
is listening
[Music]
foreign
I could probably find out for you too
janma after the stream I think I have
I think I have the box someone maybe
probably on the box maybe maybe
and last time you know last time at the
debut time you know they let me choose
the color of the phone too and I got
orange because they had really nice
colors and they had orange like what the
[\h__\h] normally
orange is a choice
but they had orange back then and this
time there was no choice I mean it's
nice too it's just white you know at
least it's not like black you know I
like I like uh when when why did I even
get my headphones in Black I was gonna
order them in white but now they're
black I don't know what what made me do
that decision but you know
colored phones are so rare right
the orange was so pretty it wasn't like
a bright ass in your face orange it was
more like a
a little bit toned down blood orange
kind of Orange
was a smooth nice gravy orange actually
it was this no wait a second it was the
same orange as my hair
I'm pretty sure it was the same orange
as my hair
it was beautiful
yeah
well now I'm now I just have a white
phone
which is pretty too but I you know I
didn't get a choice
um
yeah
I will miss my my debut phone
[Music]
it doesn't matter it does make a
difference
it's just because of the iPhone case I
think
[Music]
the cool thing is iPhones they have so
many cases that you can buy right
like I was always as a as a Android User
I was always thinking like damn why are
all the cute cases all for iPhones what
the [\h__\h]
hmm
you didn't see it and you were
emotionally attached
wow it's our connection
yeah they got so much stuff but I don't
even I normally I don't even need that
because it's not like I take my iPhone
outside and use it outside
needed at home
but still that that one takanasi kiwawa
case
was special to me
[Music]
I I apologize
I couldn't stop myself
any longer
where was I
[Music]
don't know
scariest outfit I read I read those yeah
yeah geek production
[Music]
worst things
um before by accident I heard chunkers
once by accident not me directly but
indirectly
once and I felt like
so bad about it
I feel like
That Could Have Ended really badly
if I didn't
dissolve the situation really quickly
yeah I I I can't even say what it was
because I feel so bad about it
um
you know I heard chunky wonky pretty bad
but she forgave me immediately I mean
she doesn't even blame me I think she's
just really scared of the thing that
caused it I noticed every time when
when I interact with that thing
I didn't step on her no no
um
you kick your cat so accidentally so
often he walks behind you
uh no not the vacuum you think I almost
vacuumed my cat no no the moment I
turned on the vacuum cleaner she runs
away in the most hidden spots you could
possibly think of in my apartment
and it's gone until 10 minutes after I
turn the vacuum cleaner off
to make sure it's really safe
I fall apart and lay on the ground with
her
[Music]
yeah they all
in front of you don't think Kitty
cartoons but that's not brilliant
okay I will confess to what happens now
what happened now
you know I have a bed
[Music]
I have a bed of storage
and it's like really heavy
and I am I opened it up to get something
out and she got curious
I didn't notice that she was there but
she was like about to hop in I think
yeah
God oh God
you wanna remember
[Music]
her so bad because I can't even for me
like it would hurt me so badly
[Music]
um
and then you know I closed it and she
screams and I'm like
[\h__\h] for like it was like I think for
two seconds because I didn't realize
what the [\h__\h] was going on and then I
opened it back up and she like Swoosh
ran away
but
yeah I think you know I think that it
was really dangerous because I think
where she got stuck it wasn't on her
tail or so
it was on her I think it was on her neck
I think
like I'm like what the [\h__\h] it could
have killed her probably
right that's why I was so shocked about
it and ever since then I look around me
a million times when I open up the bed
and I look around me a million times
when I close it again
and I'm like so careful like opening and
closing it so slowly each time
um
I'm extra extra extra extra careful
yeah they scoot through like you know
she was like sniffing she was looking
what's inside she wanted to jump in
maybe but now like I think she's legit
traumatized because she does never
attempt that anymore the moment I open
the bed she runs away
which is probably better that way anyway
but she's scared
um I feel so bad you know yeah I'm so
glad she she was fine enough I was
surprised she was fine after honestly
like yeah
it must have been so
so painful
she's more cautious I'm more cautious
but I still feel so bad about it
yeah she must have been terrified and in
pain and my baby I gave her of course a
licky licky snack and many pet pets and
I said sorry a million times
[Music]
yeah
sorry chunky one can
that's the biggest accident I ever had
with her and with smoking you know that
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's that's not even my fault but
yeah it's a balcony sorry a little [\h__\h]
I I I I I can't with her
[Music]
the reason I'm I do not consider living
on anything but the ground floor ever
again
or maybe second floor kitty kitty okay
it's a little [\h__\h] man
[Music]
this movie The Opener of entrance doors
and the jumper of balconies
yeah she is a goblin a gremlin
hardcore popcorn so dangerous dangerous
though
ma'am
my brother's cat fell from the first
story window was okay thankfully your
favorite story should normally still
always be fine but even even then
accidents can happen and go badly you
know people say oh they will always land
on their feet but it doesn't always go
that way
if they slip in a weird way they can
still have an accident and then yeah I
know I know of cats personally who fell
from the balcony balcony that wasn't
even that high and they died
pretty fast
so generally
always be careful when it comes to
balconies and cats
I just thought that you know because
I've I've been raising or keeping them
um for a long time now and all in
different apartments and all that and
they never had issues with balconies
like at rmt's place
they never like looked interested in
jumping up there and jumping somewhere
yeah
but
now now
more and more every day she's more of a
little [\h__\h]
she lives on the edge yeah the edge of
the balcony
fence
[Music]
ah
it's adrenaline junkie yeah rebellious
things
movie please give me a break
anyway let's finish this
thank you soon
[Music]
thank you for the pinky yesterday was my
third
in kfb I love it thanks for everything
you do I'm so happy to be a Cafe pizza
so glad you're still here you know
you know it's hard these days
um
because there's like barely any exposure
like outside of the whole life bubble
that we have now
so there's not many new people joining
you know and and it's giving me many
many fonts of like how what do I do how
do I
um grow
you can't grow but then I'm happy that
at least the people who are here are
staying for me
so thank you so much for staying
all of you
thank you thank you unless you're gonna
collab with one piece
[Music]
yeah Callie's been getting a lot of good
deals and that's really great for her
I'm happy for her
but unless you are I guess with a label
yeah we don't get much like things that
could reach people outside of the bubble
it's really hard
it's really difficult
the bubble is so hard to break out of
your vision
KFC collab
as if as if they would collapse with me
with me
[Music]
and in some way
I'm kind of like
picking a fight with them
since my debut
because I created camping
[Music]
when will this backfire on me
I don't know
I don't know I don't know but
yeah
I feel like you know I'm like uh flesh
flesh tubers and flesh twitchers and all
that uh could be like a reasonable
way of breaking out of the bubble but
yeah
yeah maybe I should do some collapse of
flash tubers
I wonder who would be open to it
remember
like for example
like this famous chess
uh streamer lady was her coach yourself
like stuff like that I mean just playing
chess together
[Music]
I know some of you guys are like no
please no but you know I have to think
about my growth my Channel's growth you
know no I'm not gonna Club Don't Dance
[Music]
no no no no I have I have um
no one in particular in mind but I have
at least like
um
how should I say it
like I I won't just collab with anyone
just for
the sake of views you know
Cheers Cheers would just be so cool
though yeah I really want tearzoo to
make um make a mythical Beings video
and then get me as the expert
maxfort oh Max watch is so funny
collab with Never Summer but she's not a
flash tuber
[Music]
but yeah more stuff like that would be
cool but
it's just hard to find the right people
that
could work well
I
yeah I would always think
very very much about my decisions don't
worry
huh
but let's buy an ad for the Super Bowl
IRL Idols Japanese idols
I mean if it's supposed to bring me
exposure
then we're talking quite big Idols in
life like damn
see I would love
I wanna I wanna collab with new jeans
and twice and so on but as if as if
as if I I would be good enough for them
um
collab dance yeah yeah yeah that would
be cool because like I saw um a niji
Sanji uh YouTuber do something with a
Japanese idol group where she was like
dancing in the middle of them
uh something like that would be so cool
right oh I saw the other day like on
YouTube I mean
[Music]
more shorts or dance covers well well
without the access to actual Goods um
motion capturing
rough oh yeah
um
I can't next Japan trip no I was told no
for no time for recording you know what
I wanted to record for the second MB
they'll try and they'll try again next
time to find time for me
but see see if I can't even if I can't
even do that like there is no chance
that I can just record random Tick Tock
and YouTube short dances
you know
you know just for making some couple of
short videos you know
there's no way but
I am trying to get an accents suit
like uh called Miko and Kana
have
which is I think like 20K
but at least it's cheaper than Amish
setup I think
and then I would at least um you know I
don't need to get a whole room you know
for accent suit you can just wear it
wherever
um
yeah I don't need a whole room for it
and I think it's easier to set up than
making my own mocap Studio like Ahmed
because for that I feel like I need so
much more knowledge technical skill and
all that
20K is not working uh well at least I
can write it off
um
and then I don't always have to fly over
to places to get motion capture done
I don't know at the end I could still
probably sell it when I don't need it
anymore
[Music]
I'm trying to tell myself that it makes
sense I'm trying
once I have it I can make so many
YouTube shorts and so many tick tocks if
I wanted to
yeah I don't know I can write it off yes
but I don't know how much
[Music]
you're right off of that
but yeah
yeah in the end when I don't need it
anymore I guess I could sell it to
another YouTuber or so like okay I'll
definitely get rid of it I'll be able to
get rid of it someday if I don't need it
anymore I think
shouldn't be impossible
does that come with tech support oh I
think generally like these kind of like
motion capture Services they are very
very very helpful
if you need technical support and all
that they're always there like to help
you
especially at that price range
donate to a museum
um
yeah
that's my current thought you know
getting accents
I'm not 100 sure yet but I I sent an
inquiry you know
because you can't even you can't even go
to their website and go look for the
suit and then put it in your cart and
order it no there's not even a price
there's not even like price tags you
have to inquire you tell them oh I need
it for this and this and then they they
tell you what is good for you what
what's good for you and how much it
costs
[Music]
it's like that
that houses and stuff
yo I'm not even I won't even consider uh
buying your property if you don't put a
price tag on it I mean of course I guess
I can't afford it I guess it means I
can't afford it if you don't put a price
tag on it generally that's the rule
right it's okay don't put the price tag
on it I can't afford but who who knows
who knows
you may have lost a potential customer
even for people who are really [\h__\h]
rich
I think even they would prefer to like
look through
properties with price tags then
bothering to waste their time to write
to untagged
properties and be like hey how much is
this
that's so annoying like that
get lazy or easier over the years and
have less and less of an attention span
you know
I don't think Young rich people
young rich people will give you the time
of the day to ask you for your price tag
um
they'll probably before they do that
they'll buy a property that they found
on tick tock
they don't have attention span I also
don't have attention span
uh they raise the price if they think
you can afford it those little shits see
I'm not gonna those little shits don't
deserve my money
if you're about to scam the [\h__\h] out of
me
no
[\h__\h] them even more reason for me to not
uh
inquire the price but do you think
accents will do that to me I don't think
so I don't think accents is
is like you know
that I don't think that's what why
they're doing it I don't think they make
up their prices as they go I think they
have some fixed prices I just don't
understand why they put them on the
website
I think they just like when I first know
why you need it because they can't
produce a million of them
maybe their order to Maine made to order
I mean
they don't produce endlessly so first
they want to know what you need it for
and if it's actually for you and then
and then they give you a quote and then
if you say okay I will buy that then
they order
the product to be created maybe
um
I can imagine that that's maybe why they
do it like that
okay measurements I think it depends
because there's
several
like one I think the most uh high-end
expensive one is like a full body suit
but then they have others where it's
just straps it's not even a suit it's
straps and it's still looking so good
um
I really wonder
because I'm comparing it like in theory
it's just
a much improved version of what we
already have for home pretty which is a
suit I will not mention the name of
because I was told I shouldn't
but
um you know how Ahmed the studio AME has
it works with cameras right so it knows
where you are and for example when you
jump and when you walk around it will
always know where you are and and it
will look much better and then you know
my home 3D where you couldn't really see
when I'm jumping my arms are barely my
my legs are barely lifting and when I'm
walking around the room you don't see it
I'm always at the same spot right
so yeah that suit is
like fun and all but still at the very
very low quality
side in terms of motion capture
because it works on on Wi-Fi and it
works on just you know guessing Where
You Are
and an accents is like
20 times the cost I think
and it still works without the cameras
but I mean I I just the reason why I
want to get it is because I keep on
looking at what Canada does
like you know
the stuff he does with it
[Music]
is legit to me that's legit
if I can use that then damn
I'm I think I would be pretty satisfied
I mean he said it's not always perfect
but
[Music]
that's I think worth it
um
yeah
it's it's definitely much more solid
yeah then my my other home pretty things
Fillion as as far as I know that's some
VR and I cannot dance in me I've I've
tried a little bit it's too exhausting
that's not something I would like to use
for making mvs and all that
like walking around and all that in VR
looks good but
um dancing gets iffy and just really
exhausting and blah blah blah I
don't don't worry about it I will first
ask for you know more details and I'll
consider it and then I'll decide if I
want the accents
no
I also asked amen she agreed with me
that maybe
that would be better for me
that might be the smartest choice for me
the most suitable
you're like five minutes behind on my or
ten minutes behind on my stream
I'm an endorsement good start right I
think so too no I I think I I can make
good use of it
I do think the 20K price tag is
[Music]
kind of crazy yeah but I don't know I
don't know that's also just roughly you
know depending on the product it might
be more it might be less a little bit
I'm not sure
I'm not 100 set on it
track no no no no no no no no no no up
to check is not too expensive
yes it is
yes it is and I don't have the knowledge
and the skill and all that for that if I
want an optic track setup
optitrack is the cameras guys there's
other cameras too
up to check is like as far as I know of
the track is you can totally make some
good quality stuff but
there's better camera resin objectrack
but off the track if there's one camera
may be affordable but you need more than
one camera for good setup
hmm
you need like I don't know one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve uh fourteen fourteen
maybe like I don't know 20.
. you could do less you could do less
but it will be worse quality
and and then I need a whole room I need
to rent maybe outside somewhere an
office or something that's more cost as
well
and I have
watching Ahmed do her things I have
zero confidence
that I alone in Europe would be able to
set that up
and even if it's once set up I see I'm
in still like doing a lot of technical
fixing and this and that after setting
it up a year after setting it up she
still
encounters you know problems and all
that that she is able to fix but I don't
think I would be able to handle that
you know
I I saw her work with this stuff
many times and I would be crying and
frustrated and I would give up
immediately
[Music]
um
yeah and then as I said it will end up
being more expensive than if I buy an
accent so I think it's more reasonable
for me to get an accent you know
I think
we are tangenting too much
accents eggs exactly
how many armor plane rides make the
price of the suit worth it
uh well Manny but it's not only playing
red it's also hotel cost
and it's also uh paying Ahmed a little
bit
it's not just a plane ride
and this way I just have more you know
freedom I can just do it where apple and
I want at home
at any time I don't have to make time to
fly over to America or Japan
in my comfortable space at home
off collabs in exchange ah you'll still
get them don't worry
you know
Mamma Mia my DMs
[Music]
okay we should read super chance can you
guys you guys told me I was in my Super
Chat Zone and you guys pulled me out of
it
foreign
[Music]
but also before that I was tangenting so
okay
us
Minecraft super chats finish on
okay the next one is from the unarchived
karaoke stream
and that one has
quite a lot of super chats compared to
the other ones so it might take a bit
longer
[Music]
foreign
I wanted to check something oh my God
[Music]
let me go on my Twitter
because my but my this
language is English
change I need to see if this is really
what the way I I was told it is
I would change my language of Twitter to
Japanese
already derailed
okay I changed my language to Japanese
now I find
find my
sweet please tell me it's
fake
you know when I tweeted about my thighs
and then I replied to myself with horny
banking all of you I've been notified
that from a Japanese point of view the
Japanese translation
automatic translation from Twitter is
really bad
no
[Music]
oh my God
you're kidding me
laughs
[Music]
it says
which means with with everybody
in that context means
sexual
and the last word is
s-e-x
yeah
Twitter it makes no sense I didn't know
where did you get that from
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
how does it translate to German I wonder
wait a second wait a second is is it
just a Japanese translation let me see
I want to say it with my own eyes
things
um
[Music]
Deutsche
no way
what does it say
[Music]
s
it's
[Music]
it's just as bad if not even worse
any language if you translate this to
any language besides English it will
[\h__\h] it up
holy [\h__\h] Spanish very bad yeah I can do
it
oh my God
you know there's so many Japanese Pros
who probably used to translate function
together a rough idea of what I'm
tweeting about it
foreign
if you know any other AD language in
English please go ahead and change your
Twitter language for a moment and test
it out so you can understand the nuance
of how bad it actually is
holy [\h__\h]
why like I get the horny being turned
into edgy
as itchy can mean something like that
but is the bonking
is blocking another word for
the deed
never heard that before
[Music]
oh dear
Empress Lang is British slang
oh [\h__\h] hell mate I was on your side
you came
I supported your English a lot you know
and then you do this to me
[Music]
English language
what I mean with bunk is but
I can't the one
we have an emote for it exactly that so
this
this yeah
oh yum
[Music]
a
exactly
[Music]
Mamma Mia
I
am shocked
give me a break Twitter
it's all elon's fault
okay
wait which three minutes
wait
oh man
foreign
this one
magical Ben
how could Twitter turn an innocent post
about oily sweaty thighs into something
loose
come on play me it's a common issue with
especially ladies who in someone wear
dresses and shorts and all that like
super short shorts yeah where your
thighs are exposed very common I don't
even know why Cali reacted to me like
that on Twitter today
as if if as you can't tell me Kelly that
you have never faced this issue before
yeah we talked about it too
[Music]
um
I don't know what's going on anymore
[Music]
foreign
underground trains as far as I've seen
also the buses too they all have a
fabric
on top
so automatically
I don't start sweating so much on my
thighs it's really just when it's like
on a plastic seat or something like that
hmm
[Music]
yeah plastic seats
suckers thank you for the pinky could
you thank Sarah Gutenberg for the
general Channel update also thanks to
you for the bless
oh you got the Among Us keychain too
nice so that one's cute
yeah thank you for the support I will
let Sarah know yeah I'll tell her I
think she she already saw all the all
the feedback from you guys
tap the Phoenix Tony and thank you oh
holy bird Travelers tell stories of
beautiful trees bearing pink flowers
that miraculous is sprouted from nothing
The Villages convinced that this is yet
another of your Divine works
love you
I love you I'm Jeffy
Jeffy
I love you
happy
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you for
the past 2.9 years
why didn't you wait for three years
a fun and Adventure dance you're always
a grand old time to see you have fun
singing can you guys read this one even
oh there you go
singing and delicious cooking Buck lead
a buckled buckled
down and don't kfb please continue
taking care of me first super to your
boss thank you thank you that's a weird
timing to send the Super Chat 2.9 years
but thank you for the support I
appreciate it yay
your first one
I'll continue doing my best to be
entertaining to you
um please stay forever
and ever
black donation pulls up by Facebook
you're amazing too for uh promoting
blood donation
[Music]
spending time thanks for the pinky
here's some blood thank you no no
no no
I'm alive still breathing
stop behind
me and you just survive
thank you
[Music]
okay
thanks for sharing the clothes but hell
yeah oh man you're did you hear yet that
it actually worked out
did you hear you must have been over the
moon when you heard that we actually got
people to go donating blood
with that speech videos
thank you
why does she not want to
apps
why the 24 sheesh damn wow
you're making up for one-fourth of the
world's plasma donations probably
frame Circle Junction extra line action
penalty contains of thinking I haven't
been able to support you as much as I
would like lately but life has been
hectic thankfully I started a new career
and I wanted to spread some of my
newfound happiness oh thank you okay
before live and I'll be cheering for
your continued success thank you you've
been busy but you still try to stay hell
say Hello thank you so much for that are
you here today probably not but I hope
you're doing well
I hope your new job is treating you well
and I hope you have fun there
it's fulfilling to you I wish you all
the bestest
say hello again okay
sir 956
um
[Music]
can't forget this is for the ticket for
okay hey hey
you are lacking critical information
it was free of charge but
I'll take it as a tip
um
thank you so much
[Music]
nice
noise
[Music]
thank you
I can't believe this is my mark on kfp
well
missing in Han Solo was that originally
like your idea you know because I I know
I got it like the the info from someone
and I don't remember anymore was it you
oh my God
well thank you thank you for the
marvelous
information
I am treasuring it deeply
insulin angle dancing
[Music]
ready for the pinky give me lots of
comfy songs in the sky okay well my face
hurts from smiling it's been hard to let
go and have fun lately so thank you bye
what's going on do you need a hug come
here
come here chicken come here come here
come come
you got a kiss instead
come on come here come here come here
come here come here
foreign
big
slam dunk that chicken can I dribble the
chicken
no the the it's too laggy it doesn't see
all the intricate motions of basketball
or Wawa
[Music]
and now I can't dribble Ira no I can't
whenever we played basketball and uh
Sports Club
[Music]
I can make it bounce off the floor at
once
and maybe twice but I'm moving very
slowly while doing it
okay okay okay stop
I need something else now that was fun
but not for a eight hour superchat
reading stream
hello
um
I don't know
what's elevator music in Japanese
let's just look for jazz
Maybe
I mean
not what I was thinking of was great too
hey hey
wow I like it though
it's not bad
[Music]
romantic jazz piano it says
old jazz
[Music]
this good stuff Mommy
remind me
this makes me want to kiss all my
chickens
wrong one
which one is it
uh one one nine this one
oh yeah
[Music]
is it too loud
no more Ragtime for now for
you like my big dentist thank you
I'm always in the mood for something
else
it's very
very much variety it's fine
you can smoke coffee aroma
maybe five
ten percent lower okay
there you go
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
foreign
20 20 feet
[Music]
it's not big enough
for most people but you can't
ask a shower Tower
[Music]
Robin
videos
[Music]
screaming around
come on
okay
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
just now hope you enjoyed it thank you
TV table training
[Music]
even thanks mate loving this cut out
okay great set list Your Divine
Exquisite voice makes my heart go Doki
Doki thank you so much
I'm glad you enjoyed it I put
um personally for me I put a lot of
thought into the set list as I always do
but I had a lot of time a lot of fun
this time so
yeah I'm glad you had fun too thank you
for being there thank you for always
being there you're the best
[Music]
wow
thank you thanks everybody
foreign
[Music]
donation from
Scandinavian lands beautiful beautiful
thank you black virgin action
I am the storm that is
approaching something like that
I love this so much your singing is the
best on archived kiaoka is the best you
seriously are the absolute best
you said best three times my German
teacher would have really really really
not been happy with that
word repetition
thank you so much done for the sweet
words
I'm sending Korean Hearts to you even
wait can I maybe fake it till I make it
no
[Music]
maybe the angle with the angle it's
about the angle
[Music]
right
there you go
they're not hello my hand is down
see now we have Korean hot
yay cute
[Music]
the best of the bestest of the best is
the best best for [\h__\h] you thank you
very sweet words as always thank you
soon
Justin Curry Dunkin also I would like to
say
I did not only sing Avril Lavigne in the
karaoke with
the only thing good I remembered was
Avril Lavigne but I sang maybe one Avril
Lavigne song
the rest was like Paramore and I think
we broke on my tune and I sang this and
that and this and that
I sang Evanescence yeah I told you
already
yeah it might it must have made a big
impact because I remember when I sang uh
Everly and Paramore she was like very
happy she had this smile on her face
which told me she was very very
entertained by it
[Music]
and Justin Curry dancing thank you
yes yes the same songs yeah
Sims introduced me to a bunch of really
good songs
Unity Champion for the pinky you sing in
flames it's just so good you sing it
really well it fits the theme right and
it's such a dramatic and Kino song
Perfection I love your kind of August
thank you oh
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
it's nice to have songs where I can just
let it out all out
all out it's fun thank you so much for
the kind words
I am what I torture Duncan
for the pinky your karaoke streams are
rare but I always have the most fun uh
over any other hello ma'am karaoke don't
tell them though thank you I will not
tell them they will never know
don't worry
for listening in we'll do one again
sometime hopefully I want to try with
mokopi and Yukata
um
would be nice
[Music]
I was touching my lips not my nose I'm
ripping off skin
[Music]
very very dry lips right now
oh
I should eat I should eat um watermelon
from my fridge how many it's been oh
look it's only been two hours 40 minutes
wow
I feel like it's been longer than that
because I'm just chilling
okay when we reach three hours I go to
fridge and I take watermelon and I cut
watermelon
hmm
and then I eat watermelon
today I wanted to eat a watermelon a
watermelon watermelon
so I went to the supermarket and bought
a watermelon
watermelon
then I brought the water watermelon
watermelon home
and then I cut the wall of melon into
slices
watermelon
and then I ate the watermelon
[Music]
come on
stalling Wawa as always
[Music]
Sheldon thank you for the pinky love to
hear a song for the Veronica's let's go
yeah The Veronicas
um
they're so great together
[Music]
some sunshine to my day
what do you mean you also bring sunshine
to my day by putting a cat in your in
your profile picture so cute
it's been nothing but rain for the last
few days in Finland oh
that's right and this karaoke is exactly
what I needed right now amazing setlist
yet again your voice has unique charm
that brings out the best inbox like
these love you well what about now how's
the weather in Finland these days
because like
it's so [\h__\h] hot here but I guess it
what's like the hottest it gets in
Finland
summer
I think
you guys have summer but it's like not
that hot right oh
20 degrees and sunny not bad now wow
nice today was 21. wait you're also from
we have two finlanders
hey we have more than two
fat a lot of people are giving their
opinions are you all from Finland
are you all from Finland huh what's
going on
why do I have so many
eh
what
why are YouTubers more popular in
Finland than they are in like
Austria
[Music]
hey that's so interesting wait
finlandish kfp everybody else shut up
only Finland just can't beat raise your
hands quickly in the chat everybody else
thank you
[Music]
shh
one two
three four
[Music]
five nah you're not finished
I don't feel any
okay but there's at least three or four
thin lenders which I think is a good
quota I feel this
I thought you guys wouldn't know this
but Finland sounds cute
and sounds cute
yeah
all right Americans raise your hand
appear so so excited to raise your hand
to it
[Music]
is a
h
stop yawning Wawa
[Music]
thank you
thank you for the red super Chan
Mr big thank you
wow name Buddies
[Music]
pinky thank you for this wonderful piano
okay thank you
I'm glad you liked it please come again
and L cos or A1
nothing's owl alcohol is also thank you
for the pinky amazing singing you did
great thank you for listening
[Music]
I am happy you enjoyed it I did my best
while also having lots of fun
I'm glad you enjoyed it and you praising
me means a lot to me thank you
thank you
yay millennials
Jim Tracy thank you for the pinky thanks
for the Fantastic yellow okay Kiana the
setlist was awesome and you totally
rocked all the songs
thank you I'm gonna do another one soon
then thank you thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you you're the
best
thank you soon for your sweetness
there's a bell dance
[Music]
foreign
next is
um
wait there's one super chat from The
Windy song from thank you
and next is the lapu-lasu oh my God
we're close to the concert superjets
um
[Music]
honestly being able to make a thumbnail
like this
thanks to MMD
being released is so helpful for stuff
like this
yeah thanks for helping me out Jackie
thank you
cute
my eye
[Music]
is
from that time
[Music]
honestly I guess we can cut them here
do you guys want to see the numbers
[Music]
because it takes up so much space
you know no need for numbers okay
good
[Music]
good good good
I might actually maybe can I
oh
[Music]
here's the eye cause ah you could see it
a little bit hmm
camera yeah it's critical still it's
been in critical condition for a while
and I can okay okay okay
some reason these ones are not loading
in
[Music]
Jacob please
what's AIM race thank you for the
rainbow
foreign
from my heart really
I'll always be wanting you only you I'm
never gonna run away from kfp anymore
[Music]
typing
hello
[Music]
driving
sometimes I go out for driving
okay
yeah yeah this means sometimes
this means sometimes
[Music]
so some like some single words I
actually know the meaning of
nice nice nice
okay happy birthday ahead of time
because I'm busy saying birthday to you
so I can't watch your birthday stream
sorry but I really hope you enjoy
special day thank you so much you can
watch the archive I hope you watch the
archive okay
please
please watch the archive
[Music]
saying
uh
[Music]
what's the sale form of pomnida post
Jose oh
[Music]
really it's potato
say oh
[Music]
potato no
yeah it's called casual form is fun
[Music]
and then suddenly suddenly the Korean
Bros
and Young
and didn't realize you guys were here
what are you doing it's hiding in the
dark
[Music]
laughs
I want to go to Korea I don't know when
I should go to Korea in in Autumn Fall
or winter
[Music]
did I tell you guys my best friend she
wants to go to Japan again for the first
time in some years
and she said she wants to combine it
with a Korea trip
I said all right I'm in just tell me
when you're going and I'll I'll be
joining you on those trips
hmm
yeah but I think she wants to go like
uh December January around that time and
that's when you know
I'm probably gonna be busy in Japan so
hmm difficult
[Music]
it may have other plans during that time
but I mean maybe if she goes to Japan
during that time for real I could at
least see her in Japan probably
[Music]
she won't be going alone anyway because
she will be with
boy food endo
[Music]
um
you also told us something about a
wedding invitation oh yeah
[Music]
cause
um
I'm going to Japan
again
I think October
did I tell you guys
to record for something
[Music]
Chihuahua
pocket could have turned it down and
just not go but no
[Music]
oh my God
it does overlap with the wedding I think
I can make it
ah
I can't go to my nostalgic Friend's
Wedding
oh my god let's [\h__\h] go yay yay
so lucky holy [\h__\h] lucky that that lines
up
um
nice
let me tell her
[Music]
yeah nice she was still waiting on my
yes or no
why are people hide because I realized
that I can go to my old old nostalgic
Friend's Wedding
in Japan
um
yeah I should catch the flowers
because I'll be in Japan anyway for
another reason
I wasn't sure if I wanted to fly over
just for the wedding
um but if it's already like overlapping
with something else and this product it
was perfect
[Music]
who will be my plus one I wonder if I
can bring someone and who would I bring
I don't know I think I'll just go alone
I'm fine or am I might might be kind of
awkward depends on maybe who else she
invites maybe she invites someone else I
know but
um
bring Gemma maybe I will
[Music]
hmm I'll think about it
um
It's gotta be someone who will be in
Japan I guess
[Music]
anyway anyway
thank you so much what's AIM
um
[Music]
I hope you'll be back again don't forget
about me okay
thank you
thank you soon first birthday
[Music]
oh let's go get my girls okay okay
read them off stream okay I'll read them
now but I won't wear them a lot foreign
[Music]
I feel bad for Emily too you know in
that moment
no no they're not no
no I think she's always there
[Music]
it's like yeah yeah it's like my
mommy yeah yeah
[Music]
wow wow let him cook
no no
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
but yeah I guess yeah yeah it's
interesting to seeing like actors that
you just like recently discovered from
big movies where they're adult and then
find them later on in like older movies
and you're like
wait that's oh I've had that with
some actors before and it was
fascinating
well no the other way around actually
like I've been watching Seinfeld
and then later on I watch movies or
seriouses again where
the the dude
um not Seinfeld but the other one
he shows up again older in other shows
oh yeah Dwight Dwight yeah I've when I
saw him so much younger and Charmed oh
my God
no not new man
yeah
still did a lot of acting afterwards
is his name Jason Alexander is that him
[Music]
foreign
Costanza
ah I see I see
that's the guy
yeah
[Music]
yeah oh my God that's exactly it I did
see him and Malcolm in the Middle I
think yeah and I was like whoa
damn
hmm
yes the chest guy
yeah that's right
yeah
[Music]
that's it
ah thank you Doug oh my God Mama Mia
thank you so much
[Music]
I'm glad you're still enjoying Gilmore
Girls I thought oh my hand what are you
doing hand hello
chill
ah
[Music]
me I'm not doing it anything
my arm is cursed are you calm now okay
thank you thank you I'm looking forward
to more info about what you thought
about Gilmore Girls
looking forward to it Crews thank you
[\h__\h] hey hey
stop
stop where I have to turn it off
property what's going on with all these
crazy super chats what the [\h__\h]
Wawa we need to squawk since when did
you get fake earphones
[Music]
yourself Amazon is your belt buckle
actually from a Walmart bargain bag
did your outfit come from Ross what's
happening yellow I know you don't really
care about it but come on no I don't
I I take it back I just said that for
entertainment purpose I I do not really
want to support that theory
I just want to say something funny and
you know
that came out
is that true
it's it's an alternative Theory
no they're not glued on with hot glue
[Music]
that well on skin guys
okay so take it back let's take it back
it's not canon okay
[Music]
at some point you'll end up admitting
your sword really isn't popsicle and
you're not actually a real Phoenix
where's the pride the favorite passion
you're an Incredible Edible
Phoenix
you can do anything you don't need to
hide your true mythical mind you could
take bits of love from Final Fantasy the
Phoenix revives others based off of the
quality of the yeah I did
talking about that you could have
someone to wake up after being KO to
going and bringing your soul back from
the afterlife if you wanted to I just
don't
honestly give out Phoenix feathers I
can't you obviously say only
all I'm saying is you have options you
don't have to make weird excuses about
what you can or can't do unless you
meant you didn't want to revive couple
if it's a panic to issue then I do have
another feather brand idea for you maybe
you could get the detective of myth in
the gardening of civilization to help
you find the truth of your abilities
solidify your lower stream
no if anything I solidify Laura on my
own I don't need anybody's help
I'm trying to put my hand somewhere so
it doesn't do the funny thing
food for fun and I'll leave at that good
luck glad I could put that off my Crest
anywho I'm excited ecstatic extremely
hyped for the consonant to sing on stage
oh yeah you were there I'll be in the
armor section so I'll wave a yellow pen
light for you yeah only but only for
that one time right otherwise you always
wave Orange right
right
just because you were in that section
didn't mean that you had to wave yellow
all the time
okay okay okay
thank you thank you for uh all the super
chats but don't marry me so let's just
you know please please understand it was
just a moment of trying to be funny on
stream
[Music]
[Applause]
want that to be Canon anyway
[Music]
um
please understand
[Music]
my my feathers are real just look at I
mean
here it's perfect because we're in
Freddy right now
[Music]
oh God
do you see any
[Music]
hot glue no it's coming from the back of
my ears perfectly fine all is good
ah can you see it
oh
[Music]
other side here there you go
yeah
that's how it is
[Music]
oh my God
there's no cool monks usual room
everybody gets free years of usual room
who everybody who is
spreading false rumors
so think twice about it
[Music]
I have to be strict now because you guys
are being little shits not complying
with my lore
[Music]
stop who
no I said everybody who is spreading
false rumors
right now about my feathers
is going to the usual room for three
years
that's one that's two that's free
[Music]
um one two three
thank you peace
[Music]
you get a kiss though for that
I swear to God my hand
let's restart that
I was going to change color maybe maybe
[Music]
still doing that
stop
yeah yeah
[Music]
Lance the Gallade 1500 thank you soon
thank you
it was so much fun yeah
yo
[Music]
it was so fun that stream
excuse me
stop it
stop it okay stop it
[Music]
it's loving me help
well help me other hand help me
[Music]
my head hurts now
it's time for uh watermelon
I'm gonna go again
[Music]
I'm gonna go get watermelon really
quickly and I have to cut it but I will
be taking much time
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
can you guys help me real quick
I need to come up with
[Music]
the end of my song
eh
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy so refreshing
that's what I need
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so to see and seedless
[Music]
um
how can something healthy be just so
tasty I don't know
oh don't give a freak if I swallow some
seedlings oh my God
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and no and no seeds
and no seeds yeah don't give a freak if
I swallow some seedlings no wait that's
kind of repetitive in terms of words
ah and seedless that's what I said
cut my
melon into pieces this is my refreshment
so juicy and seedless don't give a freak
if I swallow some seedlings
oh
don't give a [\h__\h] if my head's got all
sticky
that works too
um
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and see let's don't
give a [\h__\h] if my hands get a little
sticky that's a bit hard to say actually
they're not related to saplings
no no
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment
uh so juicy and seedless
how can something healthy beer so tasty
that's I still get back to that one
hmm
let me try
um
[Music]
I have
yeah super tricks are not going so bad
you're joking about it but they're not
going so bad
thank you
why are we juicy
um
my mother into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and seedless
um
it should rhyme with less I guess
ah maybe guess
um uh so juicy and seedless
no maybe not guess
ah sweetness
[Music]
so juicy and seedless
watermelons
got all the sweetness that's fun
that's fun
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and seedless
watermelon Scott all the sweetness
something like that
overwhelming moves witness oh
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and see less
overwhelming me with so much sweetness I
added some words to that that wasn't
enough
thank you
hmm
good job
thanks that goes on my album hmm
so much for seedless why
100 original song
I cooked that all up on my own 100
hmm
okay somebody complained about me
singing it now in one go okay here we go
cut my melon into pieces this is my
refreshment so juicy and see less
overwhelming me with so much sweetness
chip
there you go
rock and roll baby
hey hey hey
ah
um
this is my plastic fork
I'm eating it with a real Fork though
[Music]
cut my melon into pieces
slices are
okay too
[Music]
as long as you don't cut it up
and just
cut it open in the middle and then just
like face palm The Watermelon Man
um
don't eat it like that
please do us all a favor I have
toothpicks toothpicks work too yeah yeah
there's actually people who would eat
watermelons like that though
so sad
oh
face melon
[Music]
I only like the wide parts of
foreign
[Music]
second of all you're not supposed to eat
that really I mean
kotako
[Music]
yeah wild steak
what a wild take chunky punch
my God
you crazy Mad Lab
what do you say to your defense nothing
wow what
you're going to melon jail
[Music]
um
actually this watermelon tastes kind of
weird
[Music]
probably not the freshest anymore
not all of it though some parts of it
taste okay huh
I'm out in jail
[Music]
there will be a certain melon man
guarding the melon jail
um
[Music]
okay okay
super chato timer
uh
[Music]
this one
uh
this is not a stream
the stream TM
[Music]
this was a waiting room and then I
streamed a little bit because I was
stressed out and pressured because there
were too many people in the chat
at the like random ending time that I
chose for the waiting room
[Music]
so I was like ah
Shannon what can I do
I guess I'll stream for two minutes
people will find that funny too
[Laughter]
it's like um
it's like that's nothing that's still a
day off
worth it worth it
alrighty
[Music]
there is some stupid ads on my go away
gone
[Music]
here we go again
stream two minutes per day for a week of
the video yeah yeah yeah can do
technically no problem with that
thank you
thank you soon thank you yay okay
thank you for the pinky glad you're
having a good day even though you're
busy and happy to hear your voice by the
way I'm looking forward to the concert
but I love being clocked fourth in
Austria for two weeks starting tomorrow
for work so I might not be able to watch
it live
hope you had a good time when two weeks
you might
actually still be there yeah I thought
so
oh
[Music]
I'm happy for you ludoka
but damn you're still there are you
doing some sightseeing too are you
looking around
[Music]
you gotta look around I don't think I've
ever been to clagan food but I think
it's very pretty there
[Music]
did you go to Instagram we don't want to
know just working oh come on there must
be some time to take a look around the
city
[Music]
no
sounds like a location
actually yes
[Music]
gonna walk around the next two days okay
perfect yeah you should you totally
should
[Music]
but I'm glad you're still in here yeah
wait wait wait wait wait if you got time
to watch My Stream then you got time to
walk around the city
but also
prioritize watching me though
generally
do it Patsy duncast
[Music]
read my next Super chats Upstream oh
okay okay I have more people
wait I want to read it though
ah wait but we don't have that
okay I guess you're making a joke about
for DW but the debutante thing I think
that's an American thing we don't have
that here
[Music]
that was so cute
it was a puff what
no no not at all what the [\h__\h] no
[Music]
oh wait you can't ah you don't even you
didn't even see I was looking at this
one
um
[Music]
oh yeah I remember yeah
The Burrito Boy what
interesting oh Tristan
[Music]
oh
yeah I
felt so bad though I felt so bad was
sent him off because like yeah he was
kind of a douche but then his dad
sending him off to military school
because of that it's just sad
like he was sad too I felt for him
don't you have feelings Doug
[Music]
um
I didn't catch that
[Music]
um
you're getting you're getting to the end
of second season closer and closer
every episode's so exciting every
episode there's so much stuff going on
and you just you get so emotionally
invested into the killer Girls
characters
it's great
so good
what guys what what you don't understand
you wouldn't understand
you wouldn't get it you don't get it
foreign
[Music]
a friend loved GG long time ago well
maybe maybe you should also love Gigi
[Music]
it's so cute
foreign
[Music]
attendance traveled from England to L.A
for this event and I don't know you'll
clearly kick us away as always the stage
is yours what
[Music]
here right now too
I mean in the chat not in L.A
damn first of all I'm glad you got a
ticket I'm glad you were able to go
there and see it in person
it's a very special like experience I
think
your soft water in Japan and then in L.A
damn you mean for four Fest first
damn he got lost in L.A
oh it's water don't go
it's water don't go
huh
go ahead turn hands don't go there don't
go
I'm looking for you
not here today I see
attendance check you have failed it
but you were there at the concert that
is giving you a couple of days off I
guess
from kfp work I guess
I can tolerate it maybe
[Music]
yeah Patsy has been everywhere too Patsy
has been to docomi in Germany for all
from Australia though think about it
damn
in Germany
four fests in Japan
and uh la
man
we should do you a favor and do
something in Australia
but
well there was some panels right from
members in an Australian convention but
I was not part of it was I was I I don't
think I was
I need to do something in Australia I
guess
after all it's my second home isn't it
some way special connection
[Music]
I have smash
what a name who even thought of that
smash con like normally you know Anime
conventions they'll be named like
Kawaii con and uh sakurakon and
um Japan con or a Japan Expo or anime
convention something something
or
um
Desu corn or yeah
sugoi Khan
MomoCon um
[Music]
oh it stands for that okay
okay I guess uh-huh
[Music]
don't you suck on me
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
God
[Laughter]
the Raptor screens don't call me
after
oh man
[Music]
potato
um English I I just overused it I guess
in the collab
[Music]
see my English is only getting worse
because I am around the myth members
that is the only explanation
[Music]
where was I oh yeah that could thank you
for so many
questions you were super chatting all
the time throughout the concert huh or
for out
was that during was that during mice ah
no that's the MC that's my song
oh so at least the beginning
and then here
too thank you thank you
are Extinction space
thank you for
free pinky oh my god boss I finally saw
your concert it's my first time watching
a live concert I almost cried really
because I tried to bike concert tickets
and they won't let me pay for the
tickets I'm trying to buy I try to
repurchase tickets eh then they tell me
to come back in 15 minutes and try again
you mean online like for getting the
real life tickets
ah then I finally got the tickets okay
good the second question I don't know
where I know okay it was about online
where to find the live broadcast of your
concert then I finally found then I
click in first thing I saw is ID fire
truck how much I've missed oh
ID
that is why you guys when it comes to
these concerts you are supposed to buy
the tickets not last minute buy it a
couple days before
and then
yeah get familiar with the website
put the code in
or I don't know if it works with quotes
for you guys but yeah
and then you know recognize where it is
and then you
'll stream
they knew what they were doing when they
said good I was up next after the free
part yo I was thinking
um because like uh I feel like
uh
[Music]
I know certain
times Ian members were already in free
Parts like for example I think in The
Deco Nina concert
right
and yeah just generally I'm I think next
time there's a concert like this where
it's not already set in stone who's
performing when I wanna ask if they can
put me in the free section for once
would be nice to be there for once
one time please maybe maybe fifth Fest
[Music]
yeah Buddha and Bae were free and Decor
hmm
yeah and then babe was free again in the
Yen concert right
[Music]
I want to be visible to everybody too
one time
[Music]
for what I mean by free
because on YouTube there's always like
with our concerts it's usually a free
section where they stream the concert
for the first whatever 15 20 30 minutes
and then they cut it off and then you
have to watch the rest of the concert
but actually paying for it um
[Music]
so if I ever got the chance I want to
ask
Ellie oh my God I want to ask if I can
be put into the free section please
[Music]
so what do we learn from this situation
that next time you should
um
that do it on one day before whatever do
it a couple days before okay
thank you though for watching I hope you
uh caught up on the archive at that
point by now and watched the rest of it
they at least see you somewhere with me
and I end up explaining them to you oh
hey to them
to you I mean the other way around right
thank you
thank you thank you free the Wawa yes
eish
I feel like we used this hashtag before
almost
when I was in YouTube jail
[Music]
um
thank you as well this was great I love
the spice thank you Sparks were flying
let's go wow
honoredom burns down kitchen thank you
thank you for the recipe
your dancing was amazing again awesome
job out there not only singing and
dancing but also I'm seeing thank you
yeah it was it was quite an experience
[Music]
um
uh I wanna I wanna do it again
and then improve until then
yeah
oops
thank you for enjoying it and supporting
thank you thanks for the pinky
absolutely amazing concert
congratulations to everyone involved
fantastic performance gather you owned
all the MCU spots and it was so cool to
see you perform Sparks the idle Powers
Unleashed again thank you
I am very confused why was I in the
middle
I don't know why I was always in the
and also I'm seeing the most
but it made me think afterwards
maybe maybe Ian management is starting
to see me
kind of similar like in a similar
position to fubuki senpai
and honestly that would be an honor to
me and I would be very happy to take
such a position
in Ian you know somebody who's like
um
you know always always ready to emcee
something
[Music]
who maybe isn't like an official leader
or whatever but takes that position a
lot of the time
[Music]
someone to
rely on someone stable to rely on for
management and other members and for the
audience that's how I see fubuki senpai
so
if I can somehow become that I I I would
be honored
[Music]
I wonder if that's how they see me maybe
if you could compare
that
a little bit
um
she's definitely an anchor I see that
like every time I've I've experienced it
in person several times now having her
be the emcee of something where I was
involved in and she's just so reliable
and that's how I want to be too I guess
now
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah
thanks for the pinky pinky congrats to
Halloween
thank you it was very fun I wish I had
to take it on to watch it live though I
live close to you the theater just an
hour away what and also stream Sparks
that's so good I miss your streams and
might miss when you read this
wait so you live close you didn't watch
it live what did you watch it online
but then afterwards what
oh no wait ah with life I guess you mean
in person you wanted to see it in person
but you did watch it live when it aired
uh online that's probably what you mean
um damn living so close and still
missing out must be regretty spaghetti
but I'm sure there will be other times
yeah la seems to be popular choice for
doing things
um
although I don't I don't know you know
who knows maybe next time it's uh
on the East Coast that would be nice too
[Music]
do anything about it but it's not my
decision
[Music]
yeah New York would be cool
New York would be really nice and you
could try to time if they really want to
time it was some kind of convention they
could time it with the that big New York
convention
right
[Music]
well I've been having this big lack of
oxygen this whole time what the hell
yeah anime NYC
foreign
[Music]
as you sparked on the stage all the
girls did their best as well thank you
so much yeah it was a blast and
um
my my favorite was my favorite
experience was dancing together with the
myth girls
our song yeah
um I think everybody was very very
anxious about it but I think it made a
wonderful memory for us and then I think
I saw some feedback saying seeing uh
this song performed live
what did they say
oh no gave it like this theatrical cool
dramatic Vibe I don't know what exactly
they said but yeah
for non-fiction yeah
gives it another whole different vibe
um
I wonder if you guys could see my
totally 100 synchronized steps together
with Eno
that I was already so proud of at the
time of the Freddy debut together
[Music]
this time if you were at the venue you
could look wherever you want
yeah
so you could focus on on me
and then you probably saw how
synchronized we were
yeah no maybe not if you were watching
the online version
my dad's solo also got lost somewhere in
the void
it's okay it wasn't quite a solo
anywhere I don't know why Cali called it
that everybody's dancing at that time
I'm just dancing in the middle facing
frontal while everybody else is dancing
on the sides facing diagonally and I'm
like uh
kind of dancing a little bit more than
the others because I
I just
kind of I poof
for the others and then they danced you
know I activate them kind of
but more than that dance break I wish
the dance break would have been longer
and more even more dancing because I I
don't know
it was not enough for me so remember for
those parts where I was singing solo
the dance teacher choreographer she
wasn't really making much intricate
movements for us at all those solo parts
so I I thought I want to add some more
to that so maybe you guys got a good
look at that this time
[Music]
at my solo parts
movement
[Music]
absolutely amazing job from you on all
the girls the two hours went by in no
time because of all the fun I loved
seeing you light up the stage it was two
hours to him it was indeed no time it
was price again and I hope someday
somehow I'll be able to watch your
perform in person
I hope so too I hope for you that you
can watch something like this in person
someday it's a lot of fun
water you are here
wasn't I looking for you a moment ago
[Music]
it was that you are
you were out shopping in that moment
you lost Cigna oh no
well now you're back you're as beautiful
as the day I lost you
[Music]
yeah it was beautiful
yeah I know
pain stopping on you
[Music]
and dancing thank you for the rest of
the chat doll love wow I was turning to
ashes by your performance but you're not
oh
wait that shouldn't happen yet I don't
know I don't know Wayne what stage are
you in
or it shouldn't happen again I don't
know be careful be careful don't get too
close to the Phoenix when she's dancing
caution caution
um thank you
for the recipe dad Sparks was such a
great choice I hope I can be there and
[\h__\h] for you in person thank you I think
so too I think Sparks was a great choice
because you guys know it so well and
even though I generally think do you is
better I just prefer do you
um it's my favorite child
but
I think Sparks you know is just like
has a very very special place in our
hearts and
yeah I feel like Sparks is known by a
lot of Holo fans even if they're not
specifically kfp
um
right
so I I wanted to give it some time to
shine
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah they were much louder at the
actual venue than you could hear it in
the Stream
hmm
[Music]
and I'm so glad people screamed Kiana
at the everybody's gonna know your name
part twice
[Music]
even though I didn't really
um I don't know I feel like every time I
sang Sparks in karaoke I just like did
that hoping you guys would do it but I
didn't directly ask you guys to
[Music]
but you guys
just do it
because it fits to the lyrics noise
brainwashing worked hell yeah
you did it in the movie theater two
nights movie theater huh
yeah how many people ended up coming to
that one
how many
[Music]
because I only I was told what
70 people
can't believe you got so many people
together
in Germany
in one specific City
I could have gotten 140 or what went
wrong
crazy
damn
[Music]
yeah yeah I mean yeah they go to docomo
too but so I think it's like quite
impressive to get so many people to
watch something at 4 00 am in Germany
uh like YouTuber thing
[Music]
because like even even when there are
some European fans I feel like they're
all very scattered all over Europe
um
I feel like it's not too diff not too
easy to get them all together like you
know
you know for something like this
but fun I hope you guys can do that
again
and
me and Denman were talking about like
the possibility of maybe one day it
would be cool to have like official
um like feelings
foreign
like some concerts do that right
like honestly cannot promise anything we
just thought it would be nice so
who knows
it wasn't a questionnaire that I sent
out eh
if you guys want that or what
they asked about it and the people yeah
what was the question if you guys would
like to see to to have that or what
oh
[Music]
yeah let's do it that would be so cool
watching in person with more people so
much more hype
are the types of venues that would you
would attend
interesting hmm
brain cell rental
[Music]
says Wawa as someone who was in the room
room that's a big room you call that
room spice was definitely the highlight
of the night yeah the energy of the
entire venue screaming don't stop don't
die this is going your own way in unison
was unmatched I'm glad I got to be part
of it thank you like I I was I was
expecting I was hoping for
Sparks to do well because I
as I said I I know that even non-kfp are
quite aware of the song and it's English
and it has like parts that you know all
those like shouting after me parts that
are easy to remember that just stay in
your brain and this time they also put
the lyrics on the screen partially
so it was easy to pick up um
I think it was a great choice English
song not a really new song new songs are
hype too but then you know you can't
make you can't be sure that the audience
is gonna know how to Vibe along so
spikes was a very safe choice huh
yeah yeah nice thank you
also foreign
Sparks was definitely the highlight of
the whole concert no words can't even
express how proud I am to be a fan you
truly are amazing
I can you read that there yet you're the
absolute best ever thank you
[Music]
my highlights were others but thank you
I'm glad you think so
and are you appreciated I'm glad you
enjoyed it
Alec thank you for the pinky
I just got home from the concert and OMG
you were so amazing it was my first time
at a live and I got to meet some kind
some some kind and amazing caffeine
numbers oh that's nice
then when you did Sparks I couldn't stop
smiling plus them so you probably owned
the concert stop thank you
thank you
Sparks was one of the top elements thank
you
yeah the setlist was really good
spot was my favorite thank you
ah I'm glad you could interact with
other fans too and like that's really
like one great part about
being able to attend
a real life concert yeah
hope you got to connect and interact a
lot
after all it was called Hollow in Yen
connect
[Music]
laughs
title drop credits roll the credits
the credits
and General around thanks for two
pinkies Los Angeles is called the city
of angles
and thanks to you girls they were right
oh yeah you're the center of the pond is
very an uncertain world and this thought
a Priceless gift of happiness and
everyone you touch I'm so proud of you
Kiana for everything before meeting you
I didn't smile much and you changed
and before tonight I had never shed
tears of joy before but you finally got
me I sat outside afterward and saw no
changing my life people are lucky
oh
[Music]
that's so emotional wow
oh man
thank you that is a wholesome right wow
thank you so much
um
wow
I'm happy I have this effect on you yeah
good stuff good stuff unknown thanks for
the thinking more Super Chat because
you're too awesome I will never stop
supporting him I also you love camera
forever and ever and ever and ever until
the end of the new universe and even
after that too thank you I know um
thanks for the red super chat that was
an amazing performance
this was the first time I ever went to a
concert in person and it was a great
time I had never used a pen light before
oh so it was fun to try and learn from
watching everyone else yeah you just
have to blend in a little bit it just
just act
what the other people do
it was also a bit tiring but well worth
it yeah you gotta let it all out even
when it's a little bit exhausting it's
over after like one or two hours anyway
so you know
just enjoy it as much as you can
go go go go
[Music]
yeah
just do it do it in a way that you won't
have regrets my shoulders were so sore
hey that's a good thing it was basically
a workout
[Music]
adrenaline it doesn't feel tired yeah
that's that's I mean I think normally
also how I feel at concerts
I feel tired until afterwards unless the
concert goes on for hours and hours and
hours and hours six hours seven eight
ah you got to use uos during Sprites did
you did you crack them yourself
they're fun to crack
oh yes we have done just do it here
[Music]
oh I can imagine you would crash the
bride especially because it was 4 am for
you
quick yes I did no it's so satisfying
didn't they say not to bring those
[Music]
it's an
it's Ultra orange unless it's a
oh
oh oh ultimate
[Music]
oh
ultimate oh sticks
ultimate ocean sticks
yes different that's a different thing
also honestly I didn't really like
stand out to me negatively so I don't
think it really
like destroyed anyone's view or so
right
it was like
problem
[Music]
yeah I want my small number and
it just all Blends into an orange sea
of oranges
orange juice
yum yum yum thank you ever I hope you
can experience this stuff again
yeah one time you can't go back anymore
you want another one and another one
right
and it's only gonna get better you know
always improvements
after every concert I would say
[Music]
GD thanks for the rest of the chat
comment on the successful concert all I
can say now is I'm so proud of you Kiana
and being a kfp you and the girls have
waited long for this and blew me away
hopefully in the future I can cheer you
in person
honestly we waited long I guess but also
at the same time like it's still kind of
crazy to me that we got to do our own
concert
yeah definitely not something I would
have expected in the beginning and even
after the first or second year
still
I don't know
[Music]
it's definitely an amazing memory that I
will cherish and be proud of you know
crazy crazy
[Music]
I'm happy to be part of it it's just wow
sometimes I think about really rarely I
have this realization
that
I am
part of this amazing cool legendary
thing even if it cooled down
a lot now that Corona is over and the
hype is like not so much there anymore
but
I'm part of holom
[Music]
it's so crazy
I'm so
[Music]
glad so appreciative that I made it into
the first gen
[Music]
imagine
I get into a question
maybe I would have made it into second
gen or whatever
but
that would have been great too
but being the first thing of something
so big
That's History yeah
[Music]
we will we will always
be in a special position I think yeah
pioneer
we got so many things
into I don't know
into rolling So Many Stones started
rolling
in German we say that actually I don't
know if you say it in English
[Music]
um
yeah wait he made so many stones
roll
throughout the
English speaking of YouTuber or
International YouTuber Community I think
like I don't think anyone can deny that
you know now now there's like so many
English speaking
Corpus smaller ones
and I mean also non non-corpoles just
Indians
I don't think anyone can deny that you
know a lot of this is due to the success
of myth and what happened through the
success of myth
because before that yeah there may have
been already a couple of
English-speaking YouTubers but it wasn't
this big yet I feel like
um being recreated a big stage
and
put eyeballs on this and showed that
there is a demand for it
and that there's a there's possibilities
and and
[Music]
I forget the world
potential
yeah like a door opener yeah yeah
we kicked off the beat of a boom in the
west I would agree with that
and you know thinking of that and
thinking of
how I am part of the super special
generation with so many special gen
mates accompanying me
[Music]
I I I'm just wow wow
that's amazing I'm I'm honored and this
is so surreal like I can totally see
myself
um as as a viewer
in a different timeline and somebody
else is like in my body
and I'm just a viewer I'm just a fan and
I'm like yeah that's cool
yeah
I feel like I could have done something
like this too
could have been someone else you know
and but it's me and wow that's
[Music]
I will never be
not grateful
for the opportunity that
I have been given
in whole life even if not everything is
100 perfect and ideal
um but
the positives outweigh the negatives
always and and I'm just I I have this
Legacy and I don't want to make it go to
waste
[Music]
I have this chance
that I want to make the most of
um
yeah
[Music]
you're not losing me now I'm here I'm
making a speech but doesn't mean I'm
leaving
foreign
[Music]
wouldn't be the same without you
yeah I mean definitely would be
different I I think like even without me
it would have still been successful for
sure
and that's exactly why I am
so glad that it was not someone else it
was me
it's not
not
something I take for granted that's for
sure my time in Hollow I do not take it
for granted
foreign
[Music]
yeah it's a good timeline
I'm
[Music]
man hmm
my whole life it always felt like the
wrong timeline until I joined Holo
[Music]
damn
foreign
[Music]
yeah we should put that on a t-shirt or
this is a quote write it down
[Music]
so philosophical
yeah don't get emotional at the gym the
other dudes will be like ah
why is that dude crying now
not masculine again
you can cry it's okay maybe go to the
bathroom
[Music]
no it's okay Apple I will Whiplash you
now anyway because I'm going back to the
superchatos
oh yeah just say it's what yeah
yeah act like it's sweat like you're
constantly wiping something off your
face anyway
[Music]
it's just sweat
sweat
bruh
just sweaty yeah it's from my forehead
it's just running down
[Music]
oh Jim bro surprisingly cool I was just
joking I can imagine yeah
sweet I I like the idea of someone
coming up to cruise and be like are you
are you okay bro
and then you tell them about this
chicken lady who is actually a phoenix
who is just so great
and maybe you should become a YouTuber
fan too and then they jump into the
rabbit hole
and yeah then you can always watch my
streams together at the gym running on
the treadmill
that would be so sweet Captain FPS games
why if it's optimized to 30 why don't I
cap it at 30 then
okay welcome to 60.
[Music]
you love rowing while listening to me I
should be rowing too man I have a rowing
machine and I don't use it because I
don't know if it's actually working
hmm
[Music]
do people actually ask you because I I
wonder if you even want my streams and
some people maybe peek over to your
stuff and they're like oh
dudes into anime huh
[Music]
and if you're always there
then the other people who are always
there
[Music]
they're they're maybe they maybe feel
like they can ask you something about it
oh another gym dude
scary looking people at the gym tend to
be passionate about exercise and get
excited to help people sweet
[Music]
I watch you in a treadmill at the gym
too really cute
cute thank you guys for always making
time for me
even for stupid Super Chat ratings
guys do I have the day off tomorrow I
don't know
[Music]
if I have me oh I have meeting go
tomorrow
[Music]
my
um I I recently just very recently
started uh
talking to a financial advisor as I
maybe told you
because I wanted some help with some
things
and
as most importantly to me but probably
not important to the financial advisor
is the acquiring of a property
um
but yeah I think for the sake of
bringing bringing it up to a bank I have
to get so many documents together but I
have to get so many documents from my
tax lady too and then the thing is I
don't have everything so up to date with
my tax money because like she didn't
always put so much pressure on me but
recently she also has been putting
pressure on me like ah you need to do
this and this and this and that please
update and I'm like okay
but it's so much
and and and and by far I don't actually
I don't have I don't have everything
that I should upload but I need
okay
adulting yeah I'm thinking I I need an
assistant
would be nicer to have an assistant but
um
I don't wanna
I want to do things that I can do myself
on my own as much as I can it took me so
long to overcome my pride I guess and
get help from a financial advisor
[Music]
I
end yeah
[Music]
yeah so
I I did my best to prepare everything
for tomorrow I don't think everything is
finished prepared
um
he wanted me to make a couple of
um bank accounts
to put my savings on separate them
that was kind of an annoying process
and because in Austria
there's this thing called handy
signature
[Music]
where somewhere you have to register
to be able to sign things digitally
ah
but you can't just do it like
immediately if you say I want that now
you can't do it immediately and use it
immediately no it has to be like
authorizing whatever and it's kind of
annoying um
and if you don't have that then for
example if people send you contracts or
whatever to sign as a PDF
but if you do have you can put that
signature on there but if you don't have
it then I tried sometimes it works but
often it doesn't die sometimes I try to
just sign it with my tablet
yeah with the pen on my tablet I just
sign it and I send it back but sometimes
it comes back and they're like sorry we
don't accept this either the you know
authorized
handy signature or you print it out you
sign it with your own hands and you send
it via post office to us
[Music]
um
put me signing it with my hand it will
look exactly the same as if I signed it
on my tablet
so stupid
so that's annoying I had to do that with
like two of them and then went to the
post office and
sent it off
today before the Stream
[Music]
say it
yeah whatever so annoying
[Music]
how far I think I'm going I'll
definitely finish these ones
[Music]
it's not like you know this
I feel like it's been long four and a
half hours is not nothing but it's just
kind of boring to keep on reading super
jets
but you know
read things the whole time you know you
know you get it right
yeah
it gets a little bit repetitive too
after a while with especially when it's
like celebratory
situations like this
yeah everybody's so swinged you know and
I want to take it all in
but when I read hundreds of them
after another it's a little bit yeah
[Music]
no please
oh
no I'm not bored with you guys
some of you guys personally
99.99 discount
okay where are we
[Music]
I did read this thank you Ethel huh
did I read this one
I think so yeah yeah thank you
Ultima okay thank you for two pinkies
reporting to from again I just want to
congratulate and thank you for this
wonderful concert Sparks was an
excellent song choice and you were
killing it out there and the takamori MC
was so good hey nothing better than the
and then an excited and Super Wawa doing
the wave
[Music]
people also do the wave
important question
of course you did let's go
[Music]
wow
it's too difficult so scuffed man anyway
uh it was so nice seeing all of you get
a tuning together
you guys are amazing love okay if you
love Kiana yeah kfb is the best thank
you I'm glad you could enjoy it that way
in the middle of the night but it was
worth it
[Music]
next time maybe
at the actual venue if you want let's
give it a go
um
[Music]
and looking for the toppings with the
pinky you've gone and done it you made
me touch grass
laughs were had spaghetti spilled in
I want to hear about that episode thanks
for making me leave my comfort zone I
let it all out at the concert the energy
is contagious I could share forever
Sparks turned the venue into a
full-blown party winning the doctor did
somebody meet looking for the top
and was introduced
by him saying hello I am you did
God damn it
where are the pictures
where are the pictures for my docs
folder huh
yeah yeah you can't enjoy this knowledge
on your own
pixel it didn't happen yeah
you could tell by the British accent
what
[Music]
British
it's not British
you thinking of pudding or so
[Music]
you must have been thinking about
someone else
anyway I'm glad you graduate good for
you thank you for the support
Super Snake Mario Facebook Binky the
concert was so good everyone did great
before the start I had a feeling you
would bust that Sparks and I was like
Hey the performance was amazing streams
marks anyways I just wanted to say how
much you made me and all of kfb proud I
love you thank you
I'm glad I could make you proud yeah and
you had some kind of connection with me
we were in sync it seems if you were
able to guess
that I'm going to sing Sparks
um we're connected
it's because you watch me so often
thank you
never stop Don't Stop Don't Stop keep
watching the Wawa
hmm
I spoiled the durian
uh did I
hmm
I mean
[Music]
did I
I hinted
yeah but even even if I said something
like that that could have that I don't I
don't think now that's just naturally
why well naturally quoting her songs
when she's talking
um
that's how I see it yeah
that that was definitely unintentional
yeah
my subconscious Maybe
[Music]
Maybe
and back to you thank you thank you
cute it's a dunk
amazing performance Dental Sparks was
burned me down you did so well with
girls and MC job the ending talk I cried
a bit just a bit really yes mission
accomplished
thank you
me too I'm glad you got to watch it
thank you very much for the support
here comes the kiss
[Music]
it's okay to cry Fafa
I was hoping for you know the end to
make people cry maybe a little bit
but it was probably more Awkward than um
emotional
thank you for two pinkies Kiana cheering
for you live in the crowd for Sparks is
a memory I'll never forget it was so
damn hype I didn't even cry until I left
with any what
meeting and hanging out with so many kfp
and other Holo fans was amazing too I
even met yako oh these experiences are
what I think it really means to connect
the world I was nervous at first but I'm
so glad I came but I'd never have done
this if it weren't for you Kiana thank
you and happy birthday why were you
nervous
why why are you nervous about meeting
other kfp
or what
just about the concert in general
nothing to be nervous about
just enjoy the moment just let it happen
[Music]
it's about about meeting the people
um
but I'm sure in hindsight you really
enjoyed it right yeah I'm saying you did
so when your brain tells you ah yeah I'm
so nervous about something most of the
time after it's over it'll be worth it
and you will have had a great time so
remember that for the future
[Music]
it's good for you
thank you
Slavic fellow also with two pinkies it
was incredible Sparks at the stage in
all ends on fire everyone was stamping
tearing and
ringing
yeah Kiana is in control I wish I was
there to cheer and then chant kfp give
me kfp together with others ah hello Ian
together with the guests showed their
power during this concert and I believe
so did the fans I hope that cover will
expand further into the list maybe even
pay Europe a visit I know that I'll do
my best not to miss the next concert
well I mean you know
we can eat relatively easily do like
convention appearances but
a full-on concert in Europe when we
don't even ship to Europe
I I wish I could give you hope but I
don't see hope
at the moment
[Music]
yeah
uh
yeah but I definitely want to do more
con appearance appearances I think we
can uh maybe have some hopes for the UK
yeah
[Music]
yeah UK would be nice
now please go and request me in UK fans
or anyone who is willing to go to UK for
a convention
please oh see this would also be cool if
I do get myself the accent suit then I
can do pretty good quality
um concerts for
for conventions
hmm
and Freddie I mean
while dancing
which
adds so much more to the value of me
performing there so wow
[Music]
more Pizzazz that's how your ride
possess
anyway thank you Slavic wow
and then we have a triple run from
travel G damn oh my god
oh boy hey
was that concert great or what did you
go undercover again trilogy
you want the girls with beautiful
shining on stage like the stars you are
knocking everyone's socks off with those
incredible performances
is that a yes
still no fire effect but you never need
them as you start your own fire suspects
hell yeah
non-fiction among other songs got my eye
to Spring a little league really
really it didn't stop when I watched The
Vault after two and just thinking about
the concert gets me a bit emotional
[Music]
I Wanna Give hug
Bravo wow on the mythical performances
thank you it was so much fun
I can't wait to see what you girls will
do next perhaps for the next Ian concert
we'll have a whole new gen to join in on
the fun maybe and maybe I'll join in on
the community meetups and talk to people
well next time and jokes aside I hope
you finally rested well for a job well
done and have had a Happy First Birthday
[Music]
you already knew at that point well I
mean that was July 4th
[Music]
and birthday was July 6th
so honestly realistically
I don't think anyone anyone could expect
me to finish all these super chats in
between the concert and my birthday
right
you try to find them but you couldn't
well if only you had access to my docs
folder huh
[Music]
AKA I'll keep on saying this but or like
you guys joke about it but I don't
actively use my docs folder anymore
it's all in my brain saved
in my brain
[Music]
mm-hmm
photographic memory well not quite but
I must do more meet and greets
[Music]
oh I think my PC parts arrived at least
most of them
to remember
why are you guys so hyped about it
yeah we ain't got a first put it
together
I'm thinking I mean even though I I
won't even get to use it properly right
away
I'm thinking maybe
um before maybe on Friday Saturday or so
we can put it together
no 40 80.
I have a 4080 now
yeah
sometime before the steam sale ends
you can find finals you'll be if you say
eh which one better phone on I heard
fauna getting or got a new pc
[Music]
a 49ers you got herself a 49er
the waste
fona for Real come on
hmm
[Music]
I see how it is I see how it is
she probably just didn't know what to
get so she just got the the supposedly
best
wait
best thing best thing yeah
uh-huh
PC for I believe
that who the hell needs a 490 it's so
Overkill
um she's just trying to flex
or she just didn't want to think much
about it
[Music]
nah good for her I guess
good for her
cope cop
no
I could have gotten the 490 but I didn't
want it
because it's stupid
it's stupid
[Music]
no it needs too much
electricity and it's too big and
bulky not worth the money
economically smart decisions
thank you
when my nergo
economically smart decisions here in
this brain yes
think of the environment for Anna
[Music]
yeah if you break throw it out the
window
[Music]
yeah have fun with that sauna of a room
uh-huh
well maybe huh Maybe
she's like thinking over all these Falls
and fences and corners
she's just creating a sauna because of
the fauna sauna with Sana
[Music]
oh I am
yeah I know the real reason
behind it it's so cryptical
and it's so unclear on first thought but
only a big brain like mine
link mine could solve this mystery
eh
father actually said she wants to give
the 40 90 to utensil
and now she just wants to get rid of it
already is that what's going on
you see
see
[Music]
Honestly though when did she say that
what what why
is she unhappy with it serves her right
I don't understand
I don't get it
she's doing a charity what what to me
why to me I I I I don't I don't I'm sure
there's
people who have shittier PCS than me and
Ian why why am I being the charity case
[Music]
did I get one guide why why would
somebody
yeah I'm his laptop man I'm his laptop
needs to be replaced
[Music]
oh because she's getting a 50 90 now huh
you wouldn't be able to run it with your
browser button
4080 already I would if I would have
gotten the 40 90 I would have gotten a
new power supply too because I'm already
getting a new power supply for my 4080.
that's not the problem I just refuse to
get the 4090 because I don't need it
[Music]
thank you
oh yeah I mean
I was like you know
um what's a good price for 490 only
because you know I I did my research and
then you I mean I did my research by
making you guys do the research and then
you guys said not worth it
and then I let my friends do some
research too and they also said not
worth it so
[Music]
like
smart smart life decisions you know
no I'm not blaming you I'm just saying
we did research together and came to the
conclusion we don't need a 40 90. yeah
anyway
[Music]
people understand right that I I don't
really care
much about or at all what a graphic card
fauna has I'm just making jokes okay
no nobody actually
will
think that I don't know I'm angry or
something please please
like I saw
a while ago I think I saw a clip where
no I don't even know what the context
was anymore but then in the comments
there were like some really butt hurt
people from other fan bases completely
aren't misunderstand
[Music]
it almost feels purposefully dull
I don't know uh people try to
purposefully want to misunderstand
sometimes
no no they want yeah they want to
misunderstand
[Music]
try like I laugh when I
one of these rants like I laugh in
between a lot how can you
[Music]
obviously a bit now my forehead hurts oh
my God
[Music]
I'm slapping myself with the
with this like
it's not a mouse pad it's like a
keyboard pad
[Music]
okay where was I uh
thank you soon next time
you talk to some kfb okay they wanna get
to know you too
I'm sure you'll get along
cute owl in between Simpkins
wow
they won't notice don't worry they will
think you're one of them if that's what
you're worried about
[Music]
I wish to talk to the funny owl right
man you're gonna be a legend people are
gonna celebrate you I believe when you
say oh yeah by the way I'm on privacy
you're gonna be like oh that's right
that dress so nice to have some chill
let's [\h__\h] go yeah you know give me a
pun please
[Music]
oh hey
do the thing Trevor please
can you do one for me please
[Music]
no pressure though
wow
I'll see
okay okay okay okay
no pressure
but yes pressure
report from one of many dopamine groups
we successfully recorded about 60 new
camp
is no you're working at the fries what
what do I mean new ones
people who just grab them and ask them
if they want to watch a concert and
this time and then they got into it what
were they already into whole life
[Music]
oh a lot of people visited the booth
nice yeah you guys had a booth again
van boof
nice good job we had blast with some 17
year old
yes
wait this is the joke right where oh
yeah yeah this is the joke where I was
like
70 chickens or 17 year olds
[Music]
you're one of the 60 oh my God Hello
Ghost got Dynamics but it will come and
helps if you're coming
what damn
Dominic bringing me in more viewers than
some of the collabs that I've done
foreign
maybe maybe I should just rely on
Dominic
[Music]
you guys should just personally drag
people into the rabbit hole for me
do it do it if Dominic can do it y'all
can do it
um
[Music]
that's amazing wow
wow thank you so much
[Music]
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it thank you
for setting that up that is just amazing
I'm glad you guys had a place to watch
it together instead of like having to be
quiet in an Airbnb or a hotel room
so good for you guys let's go
thank you
soon Evans L one two three four oranges
[Music]
16 18 and
20 40 60
80. it's at least a pinky
you almost can't have had too many
positive Super Chips after this point I
had this one so let me break here if
he's Gus saying read in your head skip
if you're too tired no no no I'll re I
can I could really like him let's read
it together
no I want to read this out loud because
it's funny I definitely didn't yell out
your name when you pooped on stage as
first MC for Ian concert history
your performance didn't make me sing
along at max volume like a madman my dog
wasn't jump scared as I definitely
didn't change
he even wrote it like perfectly
two Sparks and a hundred percently
didn't cry learning hearing the crowd
sing along at max volume like a madman
wait what wait ah
[Music]
got lost
because you kind of
doubled something hey what
and I have didn't cry hearing the crowd
sing along with kp's Aussie Kiana
because I got flashbacks of the
entire journey to this point also
definitely didn't tweet out yeah guys
keep being amazing work you're someone
who earned the title OC I know how I act
as a joke but for real people I love you
and support I know I know
um
it's always very entertaining thank you
this is the first time you were honest
to me though wow I will I will frame
this I will print it out and frame it
the first time you were actually honest
to me
to meet directly on purpose even
[Music]
wow that is true love
I'll put it on my on my background My
Stream background even how about that
proof forever
yeah
how devilish
Dominique soon you're really expensive
the pinky incredible performance you
really brought that stage to life and
got the crowd screaming I was just
mesmerized but you can see it there you
were truly meant for the stranger I want
I'm so happy and proud to see my Oshie
be the brightest Idol she can be
thank you I really I really [\h__\h] love
being on stage you know
[Music]
whole life being
kind of focused on these activities
as a side thing
honestly this is so perfect this job is
so perfect for me you know
I can do all these things that I'm into
in one job
I mean
I would love to have done a 3D birthday
concert but besides that you know it's
giving me many opportunities that I I
really appreciate yeah
and hope there will be more because I I
want to do more performances and I
I want to up my game again
[Music]
oh I hope I can
I also want to make more music videos
let's go let's waste some money let's go
thank you mix thank you Mr statue
space wonderful thank you one two three
four time thank you oh
[Music]
no
you'll be back you're down
okay you're always welcome
don't worry about it taking some time
off is fine if you feel like that's what
you need
but I'm always happy to see you again
there's a fifth one I see it
[Music]
conjure was amazing I cheered for you
and the girls from home thank you
thank you I'm glad you got to watch it
yeah and I'm glad you feel comfortable
again to show up
especially at a special memorable time
like this
thank you so much can we take a break
normally no
but if you have to you have to then
that's okay
as long as you come back please
[Music]
yeah
packaging space wonderful welcome back
coming to work okay
thank you for the pinky wow today was my
day off so I watched VOD three times
girl song dancing Harmony passion wait
we watch The Vault three times you mean
you watched
the concert Vlog three times
everything was so nice
[Music]
you watched that isn't this still in the
same day
you watch the three times
damn damn
I guess yeah you gotta look at
everything you know
the first time you maybe not catch
everything
interesting hmm at least two times it's
reasonable yeah yeah
I'm gonna re-watch it tonight for real
oh have fun
have fun
Turn It Up loud
yes yes
I like wanted five times because I
absolutely loved the concept because I
wanted to get my money's worth
very reasonable
thank you wow I'm glad you didn't get
sick of it after the third time or so
um
re-watch great idea oh you guys should
get together on Discord or so
thank you so much
[Music]
I'm glad you got a day off on the actual
important day
thanks for the pinky Sparks isn't enough
to describe that stage when it was yours
that was Blazing Inferno wow
cause blazing
infernals
Don't Stop Don't Stop
difficult I think we'll stay with Sparks
but yeah the crowd could not have been
more hype through that performance
I'm so happy for you and so proud of
that crowd as uncoordinated as they are
worse sometimes
that's okay it will get better surely I
mean you know this whole like the the
Way You Are
[Music]
suppose to vibe to these kind of
concerts it's it's like a whole you know
Japanese culture thing and
it can't be expected for you know na
fans to automatically just
you know I don't know where get it right
away and that's okay it doesn't have to
be the same
Vibe anyway
[Music]
but I personally just always really
enjoyed
vibing to concerts like that when I went
to Idol concerts so but I think you can
like add your uh American or wherever
you're from spin to it
um
you're used to standing honestly even
when to all the idle concerts that I
went to
even when they're seats
we always stand except maybe for MCs
yeah except for MCs when there's seats
usually we would only sit during MCs
and I think I saw during the concert
sometimes I saw people partially
sitting like maybe there would be some
people standing and then next to them
they would be around and there would be
people sitting and all that
so personally I mean this is just a
matter of I guess also
us how much we are able to Hype you guys
up so personally for the future I would
hope that we would be able to make you
guys feel like you want to stand
throughout the whole concert you didn't
want to block yeah that's the problem
when like people behind you are sitting
then you feel kind of bad about standing
up right even if you want to stand up
so everybody should stand up yo
now that's that's difficult
[Music]
well that's okay I mean you're watching
it at a different venue I think that is
totally fine you can do whatever the
hell you guys want over there
you know setting up should be mandatory
yeah I don't know like in in Japanese
concerts it's just kind of like normal
unless like normally from what I've seen
is like on on the balcony seats for
example people tend to sit more because
they're so far away anyway
but if you are in the like non-balchany
in the main middle whatever seats
I I I I I wouldn't even want to sit down
I want to get the most out of it I wanna
I wanna stand up and jump and dance
so yeah I don't know I think
I'll just uh I I think personally like I
tried everything I could to Hype up
everybody but and maybe it's just like a
matter of
culture and and all that
[Music]
um
but I
I want us
to generally be able to motivate the
audience more
to stand and cheer and clap and whatever
make things more hype hype even if we
have to like you know say it out loud I
think that's totally fine to be like
everything
during a song or whatever you know
or everybody stand up let me see your
hands you know stuff like that it's
totally fine right
well I did the hi hi doing Sparks again
yeah
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah
yes hopefully
and I think automatically
there is like a big difference like when
you sit through a whole concert versus
when you stand for a whole concert
your brain will tell you you had more
fun when you stood
[Music]
you get what I mean
when you're just sitting I think your
brain automatically tells you that was
kind of boring
[Music]
so you should like
be open to letting yourself enjoy it I
think kfb learned many lessons from me
already for this topic so I think you
guys probably stood a lot of the time
[Music]
for the ones who were at the venue
but of course I totally understand it if
like people around you are sitting
that's like rough to stand up to laughs
hey
[Music]
thank you for chatting and super reading
no problem Oh have fun at the gym
I was at the balcony no standing that's
all right as I said I think the balcony
is like more
you know it's more normal to
sit
[Music]
and somebody told jinlo to you know to
sit down
[Music]
and
I'm kind of
insulted
you cannot tell someone who travels far
to so passionately enjoy a concert
sit down
everybody paid good money
[Music]
yeah stand up
you looked at the guy funny okay good
I hope jinlo didn't feel like kind of
bummed by that
like ruining the mood kind of like I
don't want to know to feel like that
[Music]
you were standing near that area too
well what was going on in that area
The Clash of of
people who are like
oh and the people are just like chilling
or what
[Music]
yeah I don't know I mean
you could say it's like you know like a
personality difference too but I I
remember when I was at hello project
concerts like sometimes next to me there
would be like
like older guys in suits
really quietly observing the concert
like on my right side there would be
that type of person but they would still
be standing you know
standing and just looking nothing not
moving their body just looking just
observing taking it all in and then on
my left side there would be someone
dancing really hype copying every
choreography of the girl's songs on
stage that was more like you know doing
what the person left to me was doing but
so I think like even if you're more the
type of person who wants to like quietly
chilly enjoy the concert you can be like
the guy on my right side
and I mean the imaginary right now it's
very imaginary
imagining people
people and stand up and just look at it
quietly you know
you don't have to scream you don't have
to cheer you know but let's all decide
to stay let's sit down during the season
let's stand up during the the actual
concert fight
that would be my personal ideal I have
literal front roses I'm going to be
sitting down I get tired selling every
even five minutes okay
okay it's like health-wise not possible
okay
and yeah I guess yeah yeah I don't know
I don't know I personally would stand
[Music]
I would stand
especially if I'm on first row holy [\h__\h]
I think we've held project concerts I
think one time
I made it into second row or first row
on the very very very very side but the
closest I got was probably second world
third row
whoa that felt so crazy to be so close
um I was so hyped the closer I am to the
stage the more hype I am
what
yeah
yeah especially with all that money
spent for such a ticket
[Music]
if you do sit you shouldn't complain
about the people standing in front rows
you because I mean that's just how it is
at concerts and people will be standing
because they're enjoying it right
oh [\h__\h] I dropped my Paddy thing
[Music]
the left side of the front was really
hyping and constant oh that was like a
what visible difference
I went to a concert where general
admission was standing only but front
row so that you can jump around like
crazy yeah yeah yeah that's also
type of
why
pad thing
[Music]
where is my hand there
your fault your fault
uh yeah thank you Merry Christmas
Kevin
[Music]
oh my God thank you for the red super
chateau
great performance thank you you are the
glue that brings everything together and
glue
also when is
Kiana birthday sake just go to Burger
King and get the Oreo shake
um
[Music]
oh man
I've had it I like it the order I'm
saying is good right
yum yum yum yum yum
we have especially at Cafe we have
history with the Oreo shake remember was
it last year or last last year I don't
even know it feels so long ago
when I Euro beaded to Burger King
the order of shape but wait did I get an
oral shake and something to eat or just
the Oreo shake please tell me I got
something to eat too
[Music]
I miss I miss the crispy chicken I want
to I got just a shake oh my God what is
wrong with me
yeah
[Music]
I mean if I didn't get proper food then
it was probably because I felt like I
couldn't properly eat while streaming
ah and some fries okay fries are easy to
eat easy to consume yeah
ideally I would have liked to got to
have gotten a crispy chicken
what about the Oreo McFlurry yeah
probably fine but my favorite is the
Burger King one
is the Jack in the Box Oreo shake the
same
what Jack in the Box this American
Burger can have it
[Music]
I think American Burger King has the
same Shake yeah
pretty sure
starting in the excuse me
well excuse me where's this not a cat
it's like
it's about the birthday shake
foreign
[Music]
I like being glue
you know you know how I'm bringing
everything together as glue not because
I'm gluing things together but because
you know the en members they're so
curious
about the the
glue they want to sniff it so they're
all close by
just to sniff the glue we're not glued
together it's just
everybody is craving to sniff the glue
yeah Ian is just a bunch of glue
sniffers
[Music]
what what am I what a you going on about
oh no glue
what
what where am I going
I can't even make jokes anymore
Pinky
[Music]
that wasn't funny of course it was funny
what the [\h__\h]
huh
I mean it wasn't funny
you guys are not funny
[Music]
green bug in the house why
has window open and it's bright inside
but dark outside
[Music]
flew away it was on my microphone and I
noticed it I was gonna grab it but it
flew away
oh
small small Titan house
[Music]
small small cattle house
Benny small small tattoo house
[Music]
fine fine
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
why why you keep on this so mean
you guys don't like my mom but not
really because my mom doesn't tell me to
read super chats but you guys are like
my mom
[Music]
hmm
I just want to say that I'm also proud
of you and your fellow whole life Idols
you've all come such a long way since
the beginning and grow too much please
take care of yourself
thank you I think this is the first time
superchat from you I think
thank you for your support doctor soon
unfortunately thank you
but mom wait what day is it tomorrow
Wednesday right
things were pinky Studio rock paper Chad
the en concert was wonderful when
everyone started singing the first notes
of SSS I burst out crying what a
wonderful pre-birthday gift for you
for me
I I guess so
I'm so so happy for my OC thank you for
keeping my darkness at Bay I wish you
many many more happiness
I am happy as you all see to bring you
light and guidance
now please follow
this chicken to bring you to the usual
right no sorry wrong so this is just
routine I felt
I felt something routiness in me
everything's good you didn't do anything
wrong you can stay out of the usual room
thank you
[Music]
I'm glad you liked it so much
I'm glad you were emotionally touched
because Every Time We Touch I get this
feeling and Every Time We Touch I swear
I could fly
let me hear my heartbeat something like
that I won't make it last need I need
you by my side so please thank you
[Music]
sweet titty
I I just came up with that for you
that's not the lyrics what do you mean I
just came up with that the lyrics of
what eh that came straight from my heart
[Music]
that could is sending
Sparks feedback
let's start a fight day
thank you oh I thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you wow
oh thank you oh thank you wow
thank you
ah thank you
so sweet and we have another pinky Byron
okay I'm still not sure and you still
are now I haven't been anywhere else yet
because I'm only working in clarkford
and the weather is gloomy oh did you
bring some
sunflower thing me
to make sunny food
when it's gloomy you have to eat
sundelions yes
maybe go looking on the sky islands
for some sundelions
[Music]
sorry I still have tltk in my brain
that's what the chasm that super Chasm
is all about too
if you didn't understand by now
bam
tear them
do you guys have Lookout Towers in
Austria I mean I'm sure we have some
kind of towers that you can
boost yourself out of and then fly
around
[Music]
Chasm one
one of my best friend doesn't want thank
you
cotk isn't real what the [\h__\h] do you
mean of course it's real I played it
and
now I'm almost done with these super
Jazz thank you and oh wait I'm not done
with this one
the food is so good the people are so
nice the city is so cool holy moly thank
you
[Music]
wait can you like remind me because like
you would donate in Korean one but your
name is kind of Polish to me
where do you normally reside in again
you told me before but I forgot those
pagato
[Music]
thank you
hey Super Dad is brought to you by North
VPN
[Music]
oh yeah tell me your Social Security
number two one with my hands I'm just
playing with the keyboard pad
is is you gone by now
[Music]
are you gone you know more here
when did you go ah I guess I got a good
personally to clotting food
and ask you in person
having fun in classroom now it's too
late to have fun in clangford it's 20
minutes after 10 pm
you're supposed to be at home watching
my stream
[Music]
God damn it maybe maybe
I will get my answer later
to tell me later on
[Music]
no don't go don't go to Ian's book
anything but in Splunk
foreign
[Music]
how about that
thanks to you and the rest of Halloween
for that where you don't see it for that
great concert
and I told you to get outside
you prefer Alex book yeah yeah yeah yeah
you guys are fun wait you didn't laugh
about my joke I will not laugh about
your joke
it wasn't funny stupid joke
Taco deck says
um for that great content you're all
great but I only have one Aussie
I'm looking forward to your album whole
of Summer and whatever that was at the
end of the concert January summer horror
I'm here for it and for Kiana
to me it just looked like
whole life
oh there's a green bug
whole life with Diablo for
um collaboration
doesn't that give me you guys Diablo
vibes
but I know it's not I know what it is
we all know what it is and
maybe maybe we find out it's so point
[Music]
I mean yeah you don't know
who don't know I'm saying we know
you don't know
oh
[Music]
wow yeah Diablo let's go
a whole life characters implemented in
Diablo lore
sick
it's a big deal
anyway
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
you can look into the future
oh my God
how did you know
Causeway
you go away bugs I should close the
window
because we talked about
[Music]
one thing Wawa in the free section and
then you guys said free the Wawa or free
Wawa or whatever
oh
he knows
well no thank you for the pinky you punk
it's on my screen I was slapping it with
my baguette shaped keyboard pen
I think it's dead
did you hear the bunkbunk
[Music]
I am so mentally
done
[Music]
can you notice
come on it's only the ones that you can
see now
uh finally back home I want to say
watching you perform
life was an amazing experience you want
the rest of the girls did great I really
loved how you did Sparks and non-fiction
[Music]
thank you
the static camera was perfect to see the
dancing
is that the camera
[Music]
oh yeah
I guess oh yeah right that's the good
thing right Mundo you weren't there in
person that's um
you mean what do you mean camera it
wasn't camera it was us
being there like real people
[Music]
if anyone was always pointed at the
towns no audience
eh what
Oh you mean ah because there were like
screens on the side too oh
is that were they showing different
footage
on the side screens
oh
yeah I guess I mean if you're in the
crowd you don't need
shots of the crowd although I mean
sometimes it could be a little bit fun
to see it sometimes
um only sometimes
makes you more aware of how hyped your
surrounding is
yeah I mean yeah that makes a lot of
sense because like for the people who
are a little bit further at the back you
know who want to see it a bit closer
ah
yeah
anyway and thank you moon dog thank you
so glad you could go and see it Jacob 47
out thank you for the pinky 10 of the
10th stream oh it wasn't a stream I said
it in the title this is not a stream
it's not a stream
but thank you
my Christmas is
June thank you and Evans
[Music]
Mamma Mia how much progress did I make
the thing is I I scheduled Minecraft
early so that we can read super chats
after Minecraft too
um
thirty percent
halfway I prefer that statement
but I doubt
it
[Music]
40. okay okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
it's not even half
40 is okay 40 is okay
wait
let me do let me do one more let me do
the last Zelda stream how about that
and maybe the second to last I don't
know
[Music]
the topics will be different
um
[Music]
we're reading this first
oh Mama Mia it starts off with a [\h__\h]
rainbow
foreign
[Music]
that's a really goober thing to say wow
always act like you don't like me so
much but you're not doing like a whole
Sunday thing like a fake it's another
thing like Evans Ellis doing but you're
like doing a real to another thing
[Music]
um
well an actual tsundere
and then if you want to become more tuna
then you should learn from one one of
now I just don't like you and
my streams that like middle of the night
for you Australian time if you if you
don't like me it makes no sense man no
sense you love me just say you love me I
know you do you have to be loving me
why why are you so nice to TOA but so
shitty to me how can I be more like
oh
[Music]
he was prepared to go to um
wow wow wow it's not like I care anyway
[Music]
it's not like I care
but if you didn't like me you also
wouldn't send me pink Super Chat would
you
so I I know you like me
foreign
[Music]
there you go
I've literally told us Empire right now
[Music]
it could be mistaken for her don't you
think wow now you like me
unbelievable freaking standards
enough
huh what what what you mean I can't
change in front of you guys did you well
did you see anything huh
do you see anything you shouldn't be
seeing you know
no so it's different it's different you
treat this different
[Music]
queen Queen
Wilder thank you for the rainbow
I'm a bit late but I wanted to offer
okay what was that birthday song okay
can someone please stop this music I
cannot hear any music anymore I need
silence
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday
happy birthday to you oh wait
okay okay okay you are my intento
I hacking love you
you are the coolest and also the heart
is full happy birth to you have verb in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
to happy birth to you
is awesome
and such a cutie
she is my OC
glory to kfv happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday King wow wow happy
birthday to you
that's so green thank you
actually that's so cute it's really kind
of cute
um
pretty cute and you did that let's I
don't know somehow pretty Charming not
gonna lie
um
where are my hands there
anyway I had to spend I had to spend you
had to about 280 hours beating totk and
getting every Shrine bubble Frog Light
rude and various other stuff before
watching you play but I finally caught
up and I'm excited
what about the clocks
wait you get you make an effort to get
all these things but did you leave out
the kodaks oh man those poor corn dogs
once again happy birthday and sorry it's
late but you are amazing and good luck
fighting the light wasn't glue it wasn't
so bad
it really wasn't so bad
yes the server line little image you
used for the family is a civilizer yeah
I know I know
I know because I looked for images I
looked for pngs and there wasn't
anything from tltk anything useful
I would have had to link uh
cut out some screenshots
too much work but I found a PNG from
Lionel from breath of the wild so I just
used that
really
yeah what do you mean it's not about
them what
um but yeah I think you know
you didn't really
care much right
okay we have to oh
why you guys
why are you so obsessed with that
thumbnail
I don't
[Music]
um
I don't know if I can provide you with
that
I may have gotten rid of it already
[Music]
I can give you the face only without the
tongue and without the blush
[Music]
um
I think
yeah I've got rid of it already
yeah and I overwrote the PSD
um
and hello
yeah
can I remake it from scratch for you
you do it you don't do it
maybe I'll perhaps recreate for my
Minecraft thumbnail you little [\h__\h]
just to make you happy
yeah I'll think about it I'm getting
hungry I wanna I wanna
um
I'm too nice to you guys at this point
yeah anyway it's okay I I thought
I felt like somebody would notice I was
hoping nobody put would point it out but
okay thank you Queen Wilder thank you
I'm impressed you spent 280 hours damn
but you know I if I would have had more
time
then I would have probably streamed it
for that long too yeah
I understand the ball thank you green
welder
[Music]
um
I don't know what's going on with my
hands anymore
um
thank you wow for Pinky too
I'd like to include your voice in the
World of Warcraft the World of Warships
add on to countdown possible okay I
guess it's World of Warcraft right
can you count down five four three two
one in English and Germany oh perfect I
already don't have background music on
right now
five
free
two
one
fence fear
dry
ice
wow
what else do you need
[Music]
um
Get Wrecked
hey Jenkins
I need healing more healing heal faster
um
or a tank your aggro is on me what the
[\h__\h]
um I know I don't remember what's what's
what's what happens in World of Warcraft
in terms of gameplay
um
[Music]
more dots more dots more dots more dots
use your skill
yo I need a rest please fast hello
get out of the fire you fool
and uh
what do you what do you and what the
[\h__\h] what do you call like the really
good items like relics or whatever I
don't know legendaries whatever
legendaries
epic epic
yo that epic armor that's for me don't
vote on that or else I'm gonna kick you
out of the guild
hands off my loot
need need
loot Goblin who are you calling a loot
Goblin
I'll [\h__\h] PVP your ass
um
oh ah
I feel like
back in the day when YouTube and
everything was still new one of the
videos type of videos that I would watch
a lot on YouTube I think was um
like
it's really simple if you think about it
but voice chat recordings
uh when people were playing games
usually
and it was just a black video just with
like subtitles like all over the screen
subtitling what they were saying yeah
just TeamSpeak and usually it was
TeamSpeak back then
hmm
yeah and I just loved the fights they
got into and then the rage and
everything and the pranks
I feel like there were some like during
World of rock Grove too
simpler times yeah
we didn't use Ventrilo over here we were
all like in teamspeaking I think in the
German speaking
um
gaming
world
I think ventrilia wasn't the thing here
not not very big at least it was
TeamSpeak and Skype
and before that I guess like MSN
and I see q and all that
um
do you speak better than Discord no well
there's no friends and all that yeah
Discord is like more than just calls but
there were some things that I really
liked about TeamSpeak yeah
um
[Music]
I'm making you feel like a boomer don't
worry I'm making myself feel like a
boomer too
I should put on bgm because kind of
awkward otherwise
[Music]
um
yeah the flag I mentioned that before I
think
[Music]
okay a baby soon
for the pinky a year ago on your
birthday I drew a cat Kiana for you that
was the first time I drew and there was
another girl that saw my drawing a year
later she became my girlfriend
huh
they're both girls
thanks attention for giving us a chance
your best boss oh my God
let's go
oh my God
congratulations that is really cute
um
congratulations
I'm happy for you for finding love girls
girls girls they like girls girls girls
I hope you will stay together forever
and watch Wawa together
Fred pen Duncan mod arcade Duncan
looking for the top tank
oh thank you um
foreign
[Music]
Kevin C on last Wednesday
maybe I heard that before
ketchup as a medicine what was it
supposed to do I wonder
didn't somebody say a Korean bro to wake
him up after 5 hours 50 minutes were
literally almost there
hi how did I just remember
it was 5 hours 15 minutes right
for me it's five hours 48 right now of
stream time
[Music]
like
I don't see him in the chat
is he still sleeping it's gonna
oversleep
or he's already on his way
foreign
[Music]
I tried but and I can't I can't imagine
him just relying on me so he probably
got his own alarm happening in a few
minutes anyway
[Music]
um
this one confuses me because they sent
another Snapchat later on I'm not sure
if you are staying true to your name
[Music]
um
here's some MV money let's go let's go
thank you
I will use it wisely oh probably not so
wisely probably shouldn't be creating
two expensive envies at all that's not
very wise but we're gonna do it anyway
thank you for the support spanking Heim
I will use it unwisely yeah
it twice in our books yeah yeah we
should just not think too much about it
just don't overthink it
um
yeah we have to splurge sometimes
somewhere hmm
thank you soon
and you guys I told you to stop and you
still didn't
uh-huh
thank you Islamic fellow wow
Pinky and be fun let's go all of you
thank you
thank you so much
what makes you happy and that matters
more yeah
yeah I think so
the outcome will make me happy I hope
but you guys have to promise me to to
get it to not only one million but two
million or 3 million views
and that as early as possible
[Music]
there's like reasons but yeah
or actually no it doesn't matter so much
about the YouTube
um
videos but
[Music]
at stream on Spotify
Etc as much as you can early on
that would help me in the first first
important couple of months
I would appreciate that
um
Spotify or any other I don't know place
where it's uploaded or yeah
[Music]
not that music brings in much money at
all but we can at least try
[Music]
I will be buying copies and streaming it
yes please
buy copies
please Doom
um jerk thank you thank you
thank you soon
yes yes yes yes yes we are working on
one song right now and then when that is
done we'll work on the other one
thank you I don't know
PG w155
I've been working as curly fry
straightener here yeah
uh for almost three years I'm happy to
support you and be fun with my friend
money I read this on stream I can't
believe you're curly fries right now
that's one of the funniest job titles
I've seen at kfp
thank you
find some time to sell one of my legs
for the MBR
I I doubt that one chicken leg goes for
the value of one red Super Chat
it'll have to be at least two chicken
legs
[Music]
at least two
foreign
it's okay you don't need them you can
learn to fly instead
with your wings
[Music]
yeah royalties are really low with music
you still got our wings yes you got any
ways let's go
hey
I would pay more for your guys's Wings
than for your legs though
I I would not eat chicken legs
but I mean I mean the actual leg part
you know what I mean the the I'm
imagining
the part with no meat on you know what I
mean she can feed I guess rather than
legs
but okay if we're talking about buy meat
oh yeah oh yeah
yum yum
[Music]
crunchy now thank you no not for me you
guys can have it I don't want it but you
guys should be happy that I don't take
your feet
yeah it's okay you're welcome I I just
want don't want you guys to feel
pressured into
buying merchandise every freaking month
Snack Attack
where was I going
thank you though Mary peppers
is this how you use this thing no really
smart I was going to buy I guess I'll
set one of these for once
I was trying to help you guys man
ah thank you very very general feel
chewing
Dragon Days also been evil pinkies and
I'm not okay that's not what I said take
that money and go to an ear cleaner
thank you very much
music thank you for the pinky oh my God
you are
once again using the money I give you
[Music]
smart life decisions am I right
um
[Music]
yeah because Carlos I was made something
for me recently
that was amazing you will see the
results
in a little bit
[Music]
looking forward to
make you guys
hear it
[Music]
so talented
it's so good to have talented people in
the community because otherwise I would
be like oh who to ask for this very
specific thing that I need
um I needed something very specific and
uh Harless was like the perfect guy for
it like
huh
perfect
you will see
you will understand
eventually
[Music]
funds for a cute Firebird heart utensil
oh
[Music]
there it is there it is that's the
magical angle
there it is
thank you
epic what the [\h__\h]
what do you mean thanks division trial
I'm doing my best
I'm doing my best okay
[Music]
spanking him thank you for the pinky
here's another one for the pile thank
you it's getting pretty big
but I am about to
slide down the pile
and end it punch up into the random chat
more MB money boss thank you thank you
it will be all invested trust me
definitely will be
okay okay
thank you foreign
can I get an Italian hoagie on a toaster
is that what they have there
is it good what's an Italian hoagie hoji
what is that
I haven't heard of that before I think
sausage
is so good really
what am I really your favorite
convenient damn
it's almost as if it's
Destiny isn't it
big sandwich a sub sandwich oh
[Music]
well if I ever get to Wawa that's what I
will order then
um
so much Daisy
[Music]
sandwich
um
wait Daisy it was a rainbow
wait that's the wrong one on my bed but
maybe if we should consider selling
Huggies anyway just saying this one's
for the Envy I guess blank
I will have to
have to sit before deciding if it can go
on the menu but yeah
I won't take you to considerations
thank you for your feedback at kfp we
value our workers feedback
totally
thank you so much for the beautiful
rainbow Daisy
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
I feel like I haven't heard from you in
a while it's nice to see you
nice to see you
blue cat thank you for reading for Chad
Tangers first and me is coming I must
have support I love you always give kfp
so much love and joy I can't wait for
the album and splash party oh yeah I'm
so excited for that too oh my God
wow
so high for that partially because I'm
honored to be in the theme song and now
you guys know I'm not only with horotori
but I'm also with us again as you may
have seen on on Twitter yeah they felt
like revealing it
the other units that are not on the
website I don't understand why someone
somewhere on the website and somewhere I
don't understand like how why
where is the difference but yeah
maybe maybe because it's not a real unit
and all the units that were on the
website are official units I guess
because it was umisi like every all the
units that are like actively releasing
music I guess
[Music]
um
probably that's the difference yeah and
I love everybody's reaction was like it
was second still alive like the Japanese
people's reactions were like
still operating what
I totally saw that coming
yeah usaken but I actually I suggested
that
oh yeah they did Homo X for a unit too
that's it I don't know I don't know what
the logic is but yeah I suggested that
we maybe do a collab with us again
before the concert so that it would make
more sense but I thought I could create
kind of a timeline you know uh naturally
but I was thinking that people wouldn't
know that usagan would be performing and
thus
you know it would make more sense but
now people know so it will feel kind of
staged if we do the collab
that wasn't according to keikaku but we
should still do it yeah
I said it doesn't even have to be
Minecraft but uh yeah I suggested to
everybody almost like in order to make
it a bit more natural maybe we should do
a collab together before the concert and
they were like yeah okay interesting
pickle
hmm
[Music]
there's still enough time so I feel like
we can get it going
[Music]
to
um
don't let your dreams be dreams back off
thank you blue cats
[Music]
and thank you from auntie thank you for
the pink super sticker this is the one
that confused me first I thought you
know
hmm
thank you though we're talking soon
blood donation poster boys
oh thank you for the membership gift
thank you
wow so many 20.
oh my God
thank you
[Music]
no I don't think so side by side maybe
you know I see you dancing thank you so
much yeah I was excited about that thank
you
sweaty fat guy donkey
but okay thank you
[Music]
thank you everybody
oh man okay now we must have gotten to
50 come on
uh I'll turn off super chats for the
next stream don't worry for Minecraft
I'll turn it off fasten It Off
Tuesday 41 that must have been more than
one percent
[Music]
no I dropped them
um the cap of my drink
[Music]
for sure
I'm dropping lots of things yeah
okay guys I'm kind of tired
so
ah six hours
[Music]
what's on my schedule for tomorrow my
personal schedule
[Music]
okay just that okay so I can prepare a
bit more if I need to
um
[Music]
okay I can
rest a little bit tomorrow maybe
um I need to record one thing
my one thing I this is when I record
and then one more thing what was that
thing that management things me about
what was it
what is this
oh my God I got I think I got an
excitement thing oh
oh cool cute
there was this what's this
this is it huh is it is this a no that's
not it
ah
[Music]
I spoke to you for a second
ah
okay guys I'm going into I can't share
it's internal
I'm going to go now I'm going to eat the
rest of my lemon pasture and then I'm
gonna
maybe sleep soon after
and I just want to say thank you guys
even though I know it's I it's like it's
difficult I I was reading super chats
for a long time is tiring but that
doesn't mean that I don't appreciate it
just so you know
thank you so much always
[Music]
for being so generous if only my hands
would show
right now
there you go thank you ah
hello
I thank you thank you so much thank you
everybody
yeah
for the support and throughout my
birthday and the concert and my Japan
trip for being a patient now
um
coming weeks you know they you guys have
to be a bit more patient again I think
especially during my London trip because
I'm not gonna stream during my London
trip although that one is really short
but you know
[Music]
and my upcoming Japan trip I think that
nowhere to is my thing is gonna work out
this time
seems like we have a date
and I'm gonna try to even though it's a
really short trip
I'm gonna try to uh
maybe organize a little off collab Maybe
another one
yeah well one of those days I'll be busy
recording and another one of those days
I'll be busy
celebrating
a special day to myself
and yeah so I I apologize if the coming
weeks until the end of July won't be as
busy as I'd like them to be for you guys
on your side they're very busy for me
I would like to swim more
um you know
properly the thing is this trip is only
happening because something couldn't be
squeezed and then the last trip
and you know I
I would have 100 prefer to just do it
all in one trip and not go back and
forth you know
but I kind of have two so
yeah
please excuse me it's it's honestly
really stressful for me to to spend like
you know
12.
15 hours actually like in actual
traveling in transit where I can't do
things it's probably more like 16 hours
if you
uh consider everything from home to
airport
um
and then from airport to airport and
from airport to the accommodation
it's like a lot of time being taken away
from me and it's uncomfortable it's
stressful for my body it makes my body
in be in a lot more pain
extra amount of pain
so it's it's not something I really want
to do you know but I'm gonna
do it so
yeah
um
but then I think August will be a bit
better
I want to go on one small trip in August
with someone special as I told you maybe
it will happen in August
maybe nothing is set in stone yet but
yeah
and then I expected to be gone in
September
you know for anniversary but that's not
happening eBay so don't worry I think
right now it's looking like I have no
plans in September
um
[Music]
so yeah September will be
much time for you and me
and in October I'll be in Japan
for you know some things again but no
probably also not more than maximum
1.5 weeks
[Music]
two at most but yeah
1.5
yeah but even during that time I plan on
streaming
um
it's just so you know that
I will be streaming but I'll be a bit
more you know busy so it'll be shorter
streams and so on you know
yeah it's a busy summer
[Music]
in Japan just have been my favorite
content but of course take care of
yourself honestly I I think it helps me
um bring you guys fresh tangents and all
that
fun stories and it also helps me Bond a
lot I didn't want to take a full week of
vacation this summer yeah I mean I think
maybe that will be the the trip with a
certain person
maybe that
what was I saying though yeah new new
tangents new memories and
it it all these trips like especially
like February January
like and also the America trip
to AME
[Music]
they helped me Bond a lot with the
members behind the scenes
I found it so much
with
especially in the first half of the year
you know I was already close with Cali I
was already close to Ina
um and I feel like I also kind of bonded
a lot with Amma last year around my
birthday recordings
um
but yeah I think I
I
[Music]
wouldn't have it any other way because
the bonds that I have created I really
cherish them I
[Music]
I feel like within myth I feel much more
comfortable now than I felt in my first
year
hmm
I think in my first year uh I felt
uh quiet lonely a lot of the time and
I don't know
that's so good yeah
but now finally with more and more
meetings you know
more and more opportunities to bond and
make memories
it's bedtime I just
be happy to have my gym mates
[Music]
just kind of wish it would have happened
sooner
this kind of like opening
you know
we've been asked if it happened soon
but it takes time when yeah you you
never meet and I know I think the first
year was also filled with stress and
many stress for me like a lot of
thoughts negative thoughts in my head
that there wasn't much space to
carelessly
Bond I guess
and I'm so tired I don't know where I'm
going with my
words
[Music]
ramble ramble ramble ramble ramble
ramble Rambo
[Music]
I started working all online never
meeting my colleagues in person change
for the better when we could work in
person became closer yeah
news
Hungary
Hungary thank you for inventing goulash
I am hungry
I will go now
time
[Music]
okay guys and in German we say I'll feed
us in
unfortunately nice city chatting
[Music]
and
take care
of yourself
yeah and in German we say I'll be
dancing
I was waiting for the hands they are
still so laggy but I am waving I am
waving
[Music]
bye bye bye bye
I am not moving my fingers at all
[Music]
just trying to do coupons but okay bye
bye
[Music]
not my Ninja Turtles
hungry
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
we're High
so talk with this so talkative
thank you thank you