stuffing your face as usual i gotta have
a good meal
here are a few of you fat cats you are
so big and fat why are you so fat i eat
genma it's what i do it's time to kick
him off the table
don't do it kiarfield that's all says
you're going into orbit you stupid ame
feel blunt
i'm a cat who loves to snooze kiara
field you lazy cat i hate alarm clocks
i'm hungry and i want some lasaga
you're eating us out of house and home
he armfield enough with a chit chat
let's get some crap going
where are the free cheese pizzas
i ate those food where are the taco
shells
i ate those food where did all the
hamburger help helper girl
[Music]
you're such a bad kitty that's it i've
had it with you that does it i'm done
that's the last stroke here i'm filling
[Music]
you