[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
hello
ah kitty king
[Music]
um
I am wearing my dirty gloves where
there's there's glue on them oh
oh oh oh oh oh
no you almost had a camera
you almost had it glue and colors I
couldn't find any other ones
it's not sticky it's like
um it's dried out
I really don't like wearing gloves
though because they make my fingers look
weird shaped like this
ah come on whatever
ah yum yum you don't I peeled it off of
this one
that I'm putting on right now
I woke up my camera too late too because
my camera isn't really charged but it's
uh doing its best so let's let's hope
for the best
camera gambate worst case I'll put on
the webcam or so but I don't know uh I
want to say something I don't know if
you guys even already saw it um
uh
wait
[Music]
um
yeah
ah
um
so uh four minutes ago on Twitter some
graduation was announced
um
I just for a hollow live English stars
for a magni and Vesper I just want to
say don't ask me anything about it
because I wasn't told any reasons and as
you know I don't really
have any connection with yeah see you
guys didn't even see it yet
um I don't really have any or I didn't
really until now anyway either
uh have any connection oh my God you
guys are so shocked
Twitter it's on Twitter check out the
whole of English Twitter
um I didn't have any connection
with them either so I if you want to
talk about it then uh yeah this is not
the place I mean you probably know that
but
uh yeah
uh
yeah
yeah I'm I I never talked to them so I
really don't know what's going on
um but
um yeah it's really unfortunate
especially for
Papa
that's that's really the most
um
sad thing ever because
yeah
but nothing I can do nothing I can say I
don't know any reasons I really don't I
I really don't
I can only guess
um
so yeah that's
that's it unfortunately
um I might make a pinned comment
um because of people may be coming in
I do not know any
reasons whatsoever about the graduations
please
don't ask me
I don't even know what to say man like
uh
uh yeah uh
I really don't know what to say
a bummer I guess yeah
no it's like so sad because that's half
a generation gone
like I didn't have anything to do with
them but then still uh I feel bad for
the the generation for tempus like
losing a whole half a generation
um
that's I wish them all the best
going forward because that's so
unfortunate really
but yeah I really can't say or do
anything so uh
I'll just I'll just pin that I guess I
don't know what to say
here there you go
yeah yeah yeah
coronian Callie collabed with them a few
times
so
that's
maybe pretty uh upsetting for them I
don't know
so about the kitchen fire hey wait wait
wait wait wait wait let me put on some
bgm first
um
yeah please please refer oh God uh
uh I think
uh
no well
yeah no I don't don't ask me anything
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah fine let me find
some study video I'm so sorry I
overslept oh my God I heard I heard the
alarm
[Music]
um I Heard the alarm and then I was like
uh yeah yeah I'm awake I'm just gonna
close my eyes for like two or three
minutes and then I'll get up and
normally that works
for sure I don't know I heard it I heard
it ah
I overslept today because
I
closed my eyes after
my alarm
uh
yes
fake regrets okay
um look
[Applause]
it's my toes left oh
wow not quite console lamp but
[Music]
bye
okay
it's very cute uh so what I want to do
today is revise
all my I want to revise all my study
material from my private Korean lessons
that lasted or half a year or a bit
longer maybe or I don't know half a year
I think
I am forgetting everything
[Music]
help
s Google
I love this lamp so much the funny thing
is it has the same color as my actual
toaster and my I have like you know
those retro things the toaster and the
uh the Water cooker and uh my juicer
that I don't use and a couple of others
yeah
oh
and so this is like not even sorted
um not even properly I tried to roughly
sort it like in the first couple of my
lessons
um
I uh just like kept these papers that my
teacher brought me like somewhere and
only like three months in or so I
finally bought this cute binder that I
decorated with stickers and then I put
them just all in there but
um it's not 100 accurate
[Music]
shake it let's find them just um this is
fine this is fine
um
uh yeah so there's like there was a
workbook and a
um not workbook the workbook is like for
home homework stuff and the other one
was like for mainly uh teaching that
yeah the textbook I guess
um and this is all mixed in here with my
teacher copied for me
uh and I don't know I think I think
we'll go through it there's also some
pages that I don't
don't uh didn't do yet some pages
when you need help from Korean just say
tall
[Music]
Tom
let me see
[Music]
help aid assistant support Tom I will
say it all the time though
please help me
um I don't even know where to start like
Ugh
I don't even know like I don't even I
don't even I don't even I don't even
know like what is this
or we can try to read this
can you guys see it let's zoom in and
let them in here oh
[Music]
whoa
I got time I'll just you know the thing
is I have to look away from the camera
and from my camera and from the
microphone when I'm like doing something
here but I'll try to read through the
read through the camera for OBS here uh
yeah uh baby is sleeping yes
uh wait a bit more I'm blind
okay uh
uh
students Korean
[Music]
are there other students studying Korean
question mark
yes yes
I am the student
no no no no no no no no no no no no
um
same sentence
that's so shaky man something is so
shaky
uh
yokoga yoga sometimes they bring up
these like really Japanese names yokoga
and
cute cute
ah
a
does Yoko like kimchi
yokoga kimchi
kimchi
see I actually I do understand this
but if you randomly ask me during my
streams to make a sentence like this I
don't think I will be able to do it
[Music]
I don't know I just want to refresh my
memory
I wanna what is this
what is this
what is this what is it what's the
what's the thing I need to do
[Music]
check
uh what
ah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] uh who
[Music]
I remember hearing some of these words I
don't remember
[Music]
I think this is too stressful
there's not enough battery
ah
let me try to set up the webcam
[Music]
where is this cable going
but I can't position the camera as nice
I think
oh
[Music]
in in Korean when you heard the windows
knowing
[Music]
Korean
um
[Music]
keep volleyball
now where do I put the the
my actual camera tripod though I don't
think it can mount this webcam
[Music]
um
let's
[Music]
um
what if I mounted on myself
nah uh
maybe I
[Music]
um
this is not gonna look so nice though
oh
[Music]
well I don't know how much I can capture
like this
what was it jump jump jump jump jump
jump
come on
uh
[Music]
that we don't know what that was
uh
wait uh okay
um
[Music]
this is way too close we'll have to look
at everything very very closely
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
Maybe
[Music]
big camera no maybe good cat good camera
couldn't
no Chic good camera she is going to wake
up later
let's use shitty webcam now I was just
gonna Translate
oh oh
[Music]
yes wow
ah
it's from crafting okay it's glue glue
are they laughing at the translation of
shitty
what did it like in context accurate I
wonder
okay okay
step aside Chicago
uh what does it say here
I never know what they want from me in
the in these prompts
um
[Music]
I'll say yo what
what does what does it's a listening
exercise is it
but I just listen to myself and repeat
to myself
and we try to remember these words okay
please help me because I I know uh check
is book right check check his book
[Music]
checkbook
yes okay
um
I I forgot I heard it before I forgot
all the basic words
how do I say I forgot
[Music]
all those words okay okay
oh okay I also forgot
[Music]
[\h__\h] um
called
um
[Music]
suck
suck I don't I don't remember souk Suk
[Music]
inside
a plant yeah that's probably it that's
probably it and this one that looks like
a person do you see it it's um you say
it as what and it's um
cloves I think because there's otgadi
oh no it's not double s it's uh One S
here this one but this is a cloves yeah
I remember this one there's
OT and then there's and then there's
ojang
I think
the clothes Clothing
Closet the closet Maybe
uh or or it was something else but yeah
yeah closet let's go
this one this one is
I didn't learn this word I think
suit
[Music]
laughs
uh
[Music]
Tom Tom
pot oh no teacher teacher did not
teach me that one
uh I want to do something here
[Music]
okay
but how do I go lower can I go lower
[Music]
oh oh wow
okay
wow good job camera for a webcam this is
not bad
wait so it was pot
good good good
uh
yeah flour
yeah yeah I know I know yeah no God God
not good uh flower yeah yeah yeah I know
I remember yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
because it didn't it doesn't sound as
as much of a soft word as flower or in
German blue got is just actually got in
German means uh uh God
remember
[Music]
it
what is it from the verb
what
is this
it's just a verb is it or what
[Music]
leave
huh that verb stem right yeah it's just
it's whatever okay
uh
up and yup yup yup is next to we had
this in the Stream before an app I think
was maybe up to it was up in front yes
until he is behind and we uh
we uh we we wins uh over or on top other
is below
yeah yeah yeah okay okay
what is what's up what's up
I don't know sup
shovel
they did not teach me no no no no no no
and pop pop
I heard pup before I think isn't it rice
rice rice rice rice rice rice rice rice
rice rice rice rice rice rice rice yeah
yeah for the comments show them
all right okay okay okay okay
I pass
oh God there's so many words I I don't
want to see them anymore let's go
somewhere else
good try
try
what else do we have oh what is this
this is probably listening exercise
maybe what about
[Music]
I'm so scared what is this can I do any
of this
can I do this
huh
is this can I do this without a CD
what does it say
I think it's again listen listen
I oh listen there's two
wait what is this
[Music]
oh it's probably all listen okay
okay not good
[Music]
what's this ah this is uh
words
this is uh don't don't look at my
handwriting it's not pretty what is it
this is the best thing
oh this looks like something we could
maybe do but then I have to write
something
[Music]
wait I can zoom out again maybe
let's zoom out
a little bit
whoa oh it's capturing my
my Razer USB light thingy
okay that's a bit better now you can see
what I'm looking at I can't turn these
pages
with my gloves
oh more listening I'm just
ah weekdays
whoa words check song
[Music]
greetings
very basic
[Music]
what is this
let's do reading exercise reading and
understanding exercise okay
because I look I'm still very slow at
reading
[Music]
everything is falling apart just like my
life no
[Music]
oh okay
Zoom enhance
and hands okay
and
[Music]
um
I like how the greeting is always with a
question mark in Korean uh hello
uh me uh
[\h__\h]
young is his name
his name is
[Music]
what was Ono again nada
where are you from I think she's asking
he's asking where are you from where are
you from right or is it
is he asking that
is it correct yes
because Saddam means person
is person so I would say ostoria Salaam
I am Austrian uh
is Japan Japan Yoko
um
[Music]
are you a student
uh
me too
[Music]
I remember the word for me too
and
[Music]
um
what this word is so difficult but I
think he's an office worker yeah yeah
yeah
okay good good breathing good
understanding wow wow wow wow
oh this is like about
um nationalities and getting to know
each other
oh numbers add numbers oh no
[Music]
no not the numbers
not the numbers
[Music]
there you go oh let's do one more good
good I want to read and and understand
these words because this is uh this is
probably something with what do you work
soon
Jacob is work
um
so we'll probably ask what are you doing
for your job
[Music]
foreign
his name is Tian her name is Natasha
hello
[Music]
are you from the Philippines
um
no I'm not a Philippine person
Phillip Phillip Phillip phillippian
philippinian Philip what Philip Philip
what what was the what's the English
word for it
Filipino Filipino oh yeah okay
Philippines
okay uh
what
happened
[Music]
what do you do
I'm a student
um
oh
MILF uh
I remember this word I remember this
word I remember she's a MILF
um
[Music]
nice to meet you I guess
me too I hear that foreign
mm-hmm
how do you say move in Korean uh
[Music]
yes yes yes
good this is good
[Music]
let's see and I want more reading
or something like that
[Music]
and this is we kind of did this stuff on
on stream
let's skip let's skip forward oh no what
are these words just practice
okay this is okay we'll do this
we have to
but I can't get that I can't get that
low
oh
take phone
[Music]
at least there's pictures next to it
this is good yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh
oh it's packed again but here it's like
a house
so I guess it's like we're outside of
the house
[Music]
outside
huh
I guess maybe yeah it's uh not not only
book but maybe also like note notebooks
and
the verb for listening
[Music]
oh let's try to conjugate conjugate this
word shall we
help me help me though
is that right
um yeah
what's uh how do I say like
hey yo
Hey yo uh how do I say two two two two
two two
how do I say the the yo form to Royal I
see this is what's so difficult they
turn this uh into an L even though here
it's a t yeah this is why I can't think
of it
[Music]
what's up
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
I'm left-handed by the way
ah
I move over here oh okay
okay well we had this before you see it
looks like a person but it consists of
this
and then the uh or and then this is the
tea kind of It's actually an S but when
it's apacheam when it's at the end of
one of these signs then it you can't say
s unless it connects with something that
makes it into an S but if it's just this
if it ends like this then it's uh it's a
pet team that turns into tea many things
in Korean turned into tea uh at the end
if you have them at the end you know
what I mean
[Music]
by the way
mm-hmm
and not
not see this is also the case this is
actually some not a tea but here it's a
tea
not not not not not
not
[Music]
these
not
ah right oh oh oh
um
[Music]
okay this is is this noon not is noon
yeah I learned this in like the whole
time thingy
um
this is God
[Music]
Valor
okay
good good
why is he is
finishing ah big okay stop it's finished
it means finishing because uh we can say
soup
ending the lesson or story mode
I think yeah
[Music]
good yeah good good it's a verb stem
actually
okay not ending now
[Music]
um
there's a horse
is it horse
a small horse
yes okay wow how come I thought of that
I'm a genius
[Music]
um
I don't even know what this person is
doing here
mom mom
um
what is this person really
I don't know body
body
okay
um
thank God you can't see the order so
well because my order is probably wrong
[Music]
and the pop is the rice
see that don't look
I say as long as it looks like something
in the end who cares
in front in front in front right
okay and then
[Music]
is it ball
is calling the ball
foreign
[Music]
okay
now let's see what else we can find that
we can do
ah broom when we're way past it see I
have actually
so much uh
you can't even tell how much this is
[Music]
it's like I actually can't put any more
pages into this binder because it's full
oh
which is exactly the reason why I'm not
taking Korean lessons anymore because
it's bold no
[Music]
um
good reason right
[Music]
words words words let's remember these
words
[Music]
teared up ask an answer yes
hey y'all
head up hey yo and
um
[Music]
read book it that is reading with those
little little signs can we zoom in can
we get a doom yes wow
class start and good NADA is
the the class
teach
[Music]
storytalking tangenting AKA you don't
even see this anymore it's like down
here
is meet friend yeah yeah I remember
these words yeah yeah yeah I remember
I remember
[Music]
I did not forget this one actually oh
I'm reading exercise
yes I think this is about what are you
up to recently because I like this
phrase
um
is your life
in general
and yeah so we'll be hearing that mm-hmm
let's breathe
let's study
okay
uh Michael she his name is Michael uh
[Music]
yes uh
oh no it's right
how do you say this out loud
[Music]
foreign
so how is your life in Korea recently
Korea life how's it going
uh
[Music]
it's fun tell me
that say me this is the word stem for
fun something enjoyable
and
your your job
that was these days uh
um
what are you doing what is recently what
doing mm-hmm
and hunger colors
I am studying a Korean
[Music]
there then
so he's saying oh is the studying funds
studying Korean is fun it's like yeah
it's fun but it's all but
it's a little bit and I say no it's much
difficult yeah
yay I understand and I was able to read
I think my Korean is perfect
understanding and reading but this is
like
you know what what many people say when
they learn a language they they can
understand they can read but themselves
making a a sentence out of nowhere that
is difficult
[Music]
yeah okay
okay good
[Music]
um
ah conversation
oh this one is about
weekdays
oh okay okay okay okay I read this one
before actually let's let's see if I can
read it and understand it again and
eat it's it's a Japanese name
oh foreign
test Korean exam
when
is your Korean test Ichiro he doesn't
need oh yeah but no no he needs Korean
test yes me too this is my test
was it uh
numbers
I think it was it sounds was it
must have been
ah [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h]
I forgot this
is
[Music]
chip
ship right okay okay
okay but it's not ship world it's she
what
she won
she she won
wait yeah okay and
um
[Music]
wait
is this also El Isam
ill
[Music]
right okay
okay uh
[Music]
ship she was she won
ships
you gotta remember your test exam date
so it's the 13th of October
um
what day of the week
is what day of the week in Nika
and while you're in
evening Monday
[Music]
yeah
it was uh what what you is
[Music]
something like that yeah okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
um
culture right yeah like because it
sounds like it's similar to Japanese
Bunco
doesn't it sound similar to you
culture
[Music]
um
uh when is the culture class on which
day
yeah thank you for making it easy Asian
languages and
Shippy ship e wall and
uh
chill chill chill
[Music]
ship in one
okay okay
so when is your culture Class A on 7th
November this
[Music]
where to
come where are you going uh
[Music]
he's going to
which is also a place I went to a Todo
I don't think I learned past tense
already
I think maybe at the very end but
[Music]
um
oh
yeah I think we were about to learn this
in our last lesson or we were learning
it in our last lesson
I went
foreign
two different past tenses Maybe
both are fine right okay
yay
o I went to
me too
nice
[Music]
ah
let's skip what is this
[Music]
it's all work done
thankfully it didn't have to do
apparently until now
um
oh
[Music]
okay so we're looking for the right
answer or question the answer is from
one to two o'clock
so
um
[Music]
foreign
to wear
uh
um
okay I think that's asking where are we
eating lunch but so I've done this is
this one oh God I have to write it uh
[Music]
wow
I wrote something wrong
sometimes I forget something
eat this night so nice Okay next
[Music]
um
next okay uh
my
catchy and
what
I remember Tony here last year or no
this year no wait that's Maybe not maybe
not
[Music]
um
at night time
[Music]
evening
Kyle
he's going to the church
that so it's a school to school right
it's cool it's cool
[Music]
so late
eh
he's going to school at 7 pm
oh my God
well I guess that would be this but the
real question is Michael C why are you
going to uh school's so late I guess
night school
[Music]
I would say number two
yeah maybe you notice we're now and
asking questions with the yo form
because at this part of the book I am
I'm supposed to use the you form not so
polite anymore but still kind of polite
but the cool thing about the yo form is
that you can ask questions and answer
with the same like form basically Kyle
for question and Kyle for answer
um which is pretty easy in theory I
guess because in the other forms you
know there's like you say Nida to answer
any well you know I'm not gonna say it
on its own because people gonna clip it
and
yeah
you know what I mean you know what I
mean
okay let's read this uh wait
time
what
[Music]
is this
means
[Music]
wait
what do you mean my son
[Music]
oh
ah all right question and I thought it
was
[Music]
a similar word
um
[Music]
ah can I ask a question probably
um
forgot meaning of town but I learned it
uh
haki okay yeah
our town is next
and happy
next semester oh
ah and so I know that's the lesson okay
uh
the answer would be
palom next time
ship
you you
it is
[Music]
okay
she's excited
starting
next in next month
on the 16th day okay
uh so he was asking
um
he's asking this is asking what day of
the week and this is asking
yeah it's this one I don't even have to
read the whole thing on this
[Music]
back
hey Castle
let's go I can speak Korean and let's go
wow wow wow
let me find something new to look at
foreign
[Music]
my teacher
um actually made me
do this
uh here there's like a
[Music]
H you can't see it but below it tells
you to
write down what he does all day and she
made me write down what I do all day
[Music]
it's like at 6 00 a.m I wake up
and so on and I do this and that and
then
[Music]
laughs
what could we do what could we do
[Music]
what are these
come back home what were you saying this
to I am home
I go is words for and so I can say
this Huggle and this Huggle and this
Huggle and you Huggle or go out and wow
but and why you have to think about what
you're saying how come you can just use
for everything that's why hago is the
superior word
a new balance study in Balance time to
study with everything else
I don't know either it was so difficult
when I was having like weekly Korean
lessons it was so difficult to uh like
you know balance it I always was doing
homework last minute
[Music]
before my teacher came
and always regretted it very very much
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what
we can win again let's read wrestling
let's let's read
it
it'll go through sale
am I did I just say please read this
did I say correctly
is
singer improved as much make some
Shadows here
it's very very very big Improvement at
least compared to last year when I was
trying to study alone but nothing really
was happening at all so I definitely
have um a rough understanding of of the
basic of this language
okay
um
[Music]
Michelle she her name is Michelle this
person's name is Michelle uh
[Laughter]
sorry cracks me up every time uh uh
[Music]
that's her name she
she's asking this room
um
uh is it is it her room uh
is this room's room
um
Japanese name
it's the room of
um
so cool
[Music]
the
um laundry
[Music]
detection like very similar to Japanese
word again
Underground
it's ill I think
[Music]
underground first floor is
um
yes yes
[Music]
it's
next to mejam which was I think a little
store or
yeah yeah a little store
so underground there's the mid jump and
then there's the laundry the cetaxil
shill is a general ending for any room
something something chill something
something
um yeah yeah yeah
it sounds like qk so it is break room
where is the break room
uh second floor
on the second floor and
foreign
okay
cool stuff
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
reading exercise but this one is about
all directions giving someone directions
am I doing well I think so yeah
[Music]
um
I love I I have to learn reading so that
I can read faster faster faster I want
to be able to read it
you know
Korean reading I still need my brain to
go on on full
Full attack
um
but kiwawa's low
very slow
okay let's do this
thing
chill
yeah
this is like
sorry for bothering you ah sorry
I didn't
I just prefer forgive me for bothering
you e uh cool
Queen
[Music]
nearby right
it sounds like which is neighborhood in
Japanese
interesting
I wonder if they're also related
those words
foreign
[Music]
which I think was
um
I don't know
bookstore ah who the hell needs that I'm
not going to the bookstore
so Nika is there a bookstore nearby they
uh tea
tea ha
yolk so this is subway station
close by to the subway station kunjo
means um
close by
all right
[Music]
Yogi Yogi
is so
uh there here here here
[Music]
so it's like two there it makes it into
to DARE how do you go there
straight forward
go go straight forward
cool could you go next
[Music]
I was right I think and
jock winter was left orange talk is
right yeah
[Music]
um
Pharmacy was it
[Music]
good
um
bad
but but
um
is right across like
here's something and then there's
something yes ah um
[Music]
okay so yeah you get the gist
I think that means does it take no is it
close I think it means is it close
yeah yeah yeah
makes sense in the context too is it
close by and then
yes it's close
very much
thank you so much okay thank you thank
you I I understand it's coming back to
me guys
[Music]
It's All Coming Back to Me
memories
[Music]
this is the counting Counting various
objects which wow surprise Korean also
gives you different words for counting
different things just like in Japanese
what the [\h__\h]
why would you do that
why let's not look at the time I do not
like look to look at the time
[Music]
oh words
many words let's try to remember these
words because they're already written
here obviously but I want to remember
them anyway
um
I wonder if my real camera could be
revived again
[Music]
I can't move anything right now
okay okay here we have wake up
can't wake up Wake Me Up Inside
[Music]
for uh saying I wake up in the actual
normal form
Royal
[Music]
okay
and Facebook
[Music]
so I said something weird
wash my face breakfast making
means morning
[Music]
and you can basically put shiksa after
morning or lunch or evening the words
for it and then you have breakfast lunch
and uh at noon yeah everything morning
noon evening and put chiksa there and
then you create the word you know for
that time of the day
foreign
[Music]
this is such a
familiar word because preparing in
Korean Jung pihada in Japanese it's
jumbi jumby
um
thank you thank you thank you
thank you to the Chinese language for
creating the base for everything
[Music]
um
today I didn't eat breakfast because I
woke up too late and I'm gonna eat
breakfast after this
[Music]
is that correct to just put Anne in
front of it it's okay right I know
there's other ways to
um say you didn't do something but my
teacher first taught me to just put on
in front of it so we'll add more oil I
didn't eat breakfast I didn't
[Music]
want breakfast
then we have oh here it is uh
[Music]
uh
I don't have to say uh so I can just say
I'm eating the morning
um
is going to work hey yo you know Hada is
like doing something and a lot of words
are just something something Hada
something something had a so
that one is easy to remember yeah
yes yes yes
[Music]
my favorite words are the ones that have
Hada at the end because I I can easily
create the past tense or whatever or the
the the
do it tense
because that one's the easiest to
remember it's always the same
yeah
let's go to school
toy
[Music]
this one I always have problems reading
this you probably can't even see it
have a meeting and call Peter and
[Music]
now you can't see now
I'm sorry yeah
[Music]
it doesn't sound like though
um
that's also undong is also a word that
sounds like the one in Japanese so I
will also remember this one because undo
in Japanese means workout and un dong in
Korean means uh workout
yeah there's a couple more but you can
see them so let's ignore them actually I
want to test the the camera again can I
try
the other camera
they move it around
let's see
ah wait I have to
[Music]
I have to
do it
[Music]
look at that okay ah it's not
deactivated you lied to me
[Music]
okay one second
what did you guys say what was it
[Music]
some something
was that it I just dropped some printer
ink
[Music]
which is a scam I watched a video about
printer ink scam they opened up they
opened up one of those printer inks for
your Canon printers and they measured
how much is actually inside and there's
like nothing inside like I'm not even
kidding there's literally nothing you
can't even see any liquid it's just like
a little sponge that soaked up a tiny
amount of ink I guess but even when they
uh like try to squeeze it nothing comes
out you saw it too it's unbelievable
[Music]
unbelievable
scam
cam how dare they
hey were you charging camera I hope you
were charging because I had you
connected
how's the battery life doing oh 14
that's better than zero percent before
we couldn't handle 14 for a little bit
especially if we're charging while doing
it
let's go
good camera is coming back
this camera is making a comeback
right here right now
just watch and see
no I am charging it yeah yeah but last
time it was it died anyway because it
was
very very very low
ah okay I didn't wait it didn't
[Music]
wait I probably have to reopen that
window
[Music]
ah there it is
huh
oh wait I have to maybe redo it
she screaming stand by residence
[Music]
what did I what am I doing differently
why is it on standby
[Music]
um
I'm so hungry
[Music]
um
yeah my OBS is like having some trouble
finding
uh
camera I guess
[Music]
let me redo it
okay cats
oh no 13 percent
[Music]
activate
Okay
I attached it again
[Music]
oh I'm so hungry
pop pop
it's not working why
it has to work it makes no sense but
it's not it's like stuck on even though
I switched the camera it's stuck on the
webcam that is like Frozen
um
can I like refresh it
I wonder if I can
restart
yes
[Music]
I'm doing something wrong I guess
oh me on it maybe I should have kept the
webcam man let me I think if I restart
OBS I think I think it should be safe uh
if I'm not coming back then that means
it wasn't safe
we'll see I guess
to reopen it
will it will I come back I think I I
think I think I've done this before I'm
pretty sure I came back after reopening
obs
okay
[Music]
don't panic
oh my God I was literally talking about
restarting obvious and the moment I'm
gone you guys even even though you
should be understanding uh I understand
the Korean people may be panicking
because maybe they didn't understand
what I was doing but you guys you're
like
what happened she's
dead panic
um
actually I really don't want to study
anymore one and a half hours is my
maximum
I guess uh but no okay we have gone
through
so do you realize how much does this
this is crazy like I I got so many
so many of pages
so we were like I the camera is working
again it's not as pretty positioned as
it was before but
it's working
you can see my my super cute toe slime
again oh [\h__\h] I'm so hungry oh
yeah you know what what if we don't
study anymore but we test some Korean
snacks that my teacher gave me at the
very end oh my
[Music]
God
all right baby
I have some food
yo yo
it's clearly Destiny
I studied plenty I studied plenty okay
we have we have this
cute it's what does it say see this is
also studying mile
wasn't that the word for horse
[Music]
huh
ah
Mochi soft cow my long is soft
um
and then I have
Concho
chocolate biscuits mm-hmm
and then
dream cake
premium pie with cream filling Moon
's monsoon
yeah that's it uh wow this one's really
a big package like see how much space it
takes up compared to the other ones
this is really big
okay let's try
the big cakes Honestly though like these
kind of snacks
if they're similar to Japanese ones I
probably don't like them so much it is
expensive really
it might be melted though I don't know
it might be melted because it was not in
the fridge and it's been very very hot
so it's a package like this
premium dessert cake
premium
oh like generally these these snacks
where there's like cake biscuits or
something in there but they don't they
you know it's like made so that it's
good forever
they just I just don't really like those
tastes that much uh usually when it's
from
pan and so on I don't know how to
explain it but it just sounds often
tastes very
much like Factory
probably just because I'm not used to it
because
similar ones in Austria I'm fine with
eating them
yeah
[Music]
but I think they're also a little bit
artificial but still they taste more
natural to me okay here is this
whoa look at the camera
and y'all it's zooming and focusing so
nicely I'm so happy oh my God this is
making me very happy it's so satisfying
oh
okay here I go breakfast time
I feel like I've
eaten a snack like this before
um
[Music]
it's pretty decent yum
it's very soft
is it really a premium I mean
I mean I guess yeah it moves fine
not bad not bad not bad there's um
some kind of cream in the middle
um
[Music]
yeah I could I could eat it
when I'm in an emergency like this
[Music]
um
yeah I think if you grow up with this
flavor you will like it very much it's
not bad it's not bad it's not bad
I should be like oh my God
oh good but I'm a very honest person
um
[Music]
I'm trying to finish it at least
um
yeah
it really reminds me of something I ate
before in a snack Box review probably
at least there's food yeah
[Music]
I was very hungry
this is saving my life
[Music]
um
soil
it's good right
right right right
[Music]
we're studying Korean snacks don't
forget about the last word we're
studying Korean
did I say is bad actually
soil
ow
okay
I ate it
nice nice nice nice
these are like little cookies and this
is like something chewy maybe so let's
try this one first
because I already have chocolate flavor
in my mouth now
these are by the way
um Korean snacks that you can buy in
Austria because
I see the Austrian Austrian German
[Music]
translation in the back
so I feel like with snacks that they
sell
in Asian stores here that are important
they're often I mean they have some
popular ones yeah but I also think that
often they sell things that it's really
hard to find in the actual country like
Korea
and I wonder why where did you get these
from
[Music]
all right now we open
it's little cookies in there this feels
like such a children's snack
oh oh it's got a cute shape
a cute
see
[Music]
and
there's some something some drawing on
it but I can't really recognize what it
is
I guess these are the drawings that I'm
supposed to be seeing
hey
[Music]
uh I don't know
okay
that's um it's really tiny I could eat
the whole thing but I'll only eat half
so I can show you what it looks like
inside uh
um eat only half
because it falls apart
um see ah
yeah it's just like a little cookie with
some chocolate inside yeah you know
um
Korean people
uh
e
cookie oh
was it was this an actual sentence that
I just made
I'm asking if Korean people like this
snack
[Music]
yes there there
um
[Music]
I I I don't dislike it but it's
[Laughter]
yeah yeah it's okay
okay
[Music]
we're doing Snappers I miss snack Box
review it it's been a long time
[Applause]
open
up okay there was some something I had
to break
oh
different faces
[Music]
look at this
cute oh God look at this high quality
I'm I'm
sorry I'm getting very excited over the
quality of the camera
turning me on
so this is supposed to be strawberry
milk flavor
I think this is gonna be good
[Music]
um
I am opening
[Music]
oh
it's it looks like
oh this this is actually gonna be hard
to see from the camera I think come back
there
you can do it
[Music]
all right
can you do this too
because on this
it's too bright
it's actually pink not white but it
looks uh like it I wanted to show you
that it has um
basically
what's it called when you when you when
your skin gets crinkly
okay here we go
oh
[Music]
um
the flavor is kind of weird
I don't know
[Music]
it's not like I want to spit it out it's
not bad
[Music]
I sound like a car now
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] any of these that much
um
[Music]
if I have to rank these snacks
actually I think they're all on the same
level
[Laughter]
I
in Japan and Korea I don't like the
snacks I like the food in the restaurant
[Music]
um I think
yes snacks
[Music]
you know what I mean
yes I remember the word for restaurant
let's go yeah that's why I I never
really buy snacks in Japan either in the
convenience stores I only I mean like my
snacks that are like fresh like for
example
from
I don't know anything out of the fresh
Corner that was freshly made you know
but these like pre-packaged things uh
from the factory somehow I don't like
those so much mostly
um yeah yeah yeah yeah chips chips are
chips potato chips are still pretty good
no matter where you go I would say they
just have interesting flavors but yeah
um
I let's let me let me say this clearly
so nobody gets sad I prefer food freshly
made in a restaurant
[Laughter]
is a h no it is
[Music]
um
food
I like Korean food
that is freshly
more
[Music]
um
yeah okay understand
but you know what what Japan and Korea
is definitely doing really good is
Packaging
it looks so nice and cute this one looks
cute this one looks beautiful
this one is cute really cute and I want
to buy it just because it looks cute
yeah
10 out of 10 packaging food 5 out of 10.
six Maybe
[Music]
say something in Korean please
um
[Music]
what what what what what what
um
[Music]
for me
I understand
[Music]
oh
my god
um
[Music]
Channel
[Applause]
some
some some sometimes go
is
I guess
[Music]
I I try to read chat message oh
umida no anio
foreign
[Music]
Korea person
Maybe
in the future no
[Music]
I have so much respect for you thank you
I'm glad that I
I'm I'm so sad this all this all these
uh not not the snacks I'm talking about
what's below it's still somewhat in my
brain
somewhere in there thank God
uh I should make use of my Duolingo
premium subscription
and actually use it to keep this
knowledge in my brain
oh
Kiara
um
me
[Music]
or see me
I was reading comment
ah I studied hard
can you say mustard in Korean what
mustard
killed it
your diet
why
[Music]
um
anio
and kill you
[Music]
I am going to have a members only stream
uh later today that I have to set up and
so if you're interested it's actually in
three hours
[Music]
um
in three hours I have another stream
uh
[Music]
okay
I think it's a free or maybe in four I'm
not sure what I scheduled it at I think
it's in three hours
[Music]
so yup
and Tiana
did I say that correctly come to my
stream
is so
[Music]
oh
is to you have to go but oseio is you
have to come
on sale
[Music]
come
okay
[Music]
but now you get out but then you come
again later
okay or or
[Music]
you going to sleep
foreign
[Music]
not sleeping no no
and until
[Music]
you don't go to sleep good
it was nice talking to Korean Bros again
for the first time in a while sorry I
overslept but at least I feel very very
um not tired
very awake
yeah
Korean Bros
[Music]
wow
okay
um
you
good job good job my brain big
oh my Council on the message wrong you
liked it thank you more drawing
um maybe
okay I
go
oh my God
I go
[Music]
I eat more
and in Korean we say oh
and in English we say goodbye and in
German we say okay
see you again ah
or Apollo
20 minutes
I
think okay
okay
[Music]
and I put a child
bye bye don't forget me
[Music]
okay see you later in my member stream
bye bye
bye bye bye bye
and you
Young
right
[Music]
Korean lesson is over
hey
let's do it again maybe even
one time per month once per month Maybe
mmm
once per month
[Music]
oh
hello
yeah okay
okay oh my God my Korean I am making
sentences left and right let's go
nice
[Music]
what's the month on stream and ideally
more often privately
okay
I'm so proud of myself I'm so proud of
myself
[Music]
great memory retention let's go hello I
am Babu Babu I can make sentences now
because I am
[Music]
um
five years old now when the when do kids
start making sentences
that's how old I am
in Korean
[Music]
at one all three yeah more like free
right like proper sentences
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I am three years old in Korea only
give me milk oh no I didn't say that
today I I needed to let that out
[Music]
okay enough enough
enough
[Music]
your separation excite I'm back in a few
hours okay
hey we've been in this ending screen for
like eight minutes
yeah
maybe
um
foreign
[Music]
Channel
exists