[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
thank you ah
[Music]
I need a clock
all right
I'm doing fine I'm doing fine
just wonderful
[Music]
okay is this clock no
thank you
[Music]
what's up
what's up what's up
[Laughter]
wait you're not drunk I'm not I'm just
so tired
um I also have a cup of coffee and I'm
just really hyped what is it I need to
duck down into the hot glue in hot air
balloon for a second
tomato
okay
hello unhinged hours
unhinged hours with bait we got nine
minutes
hello
[Laughter]
do you like my hot air balloon I thought
it was fitting because you know it's a
countdown to my birthday
nine minutes and end stream no no no no
no so what we're gonna do is we're gonna
stream until it's also my birthday well
it's never gonna be my birthday this
year but until it hits midnight in in
Japan as well so we're streaming for
another two hours
[Music]
welcome
we're straight for 366 days
no
no no no
foreign
67 yeah 367 because technically today is
still the 27th correct you are correct
also
if you guys didn't know there's no bgm
oh my God the bgm wasn't playing oh
goodness you've been hearing absolutely
oh my God I could hear the BVM
oh my goodness I'm so sorry it's been
playing in my ears this whole time
that's why I was like I was I was
grooving but I was grooving to know bgm
oh goodness
how embarrassing
scuffed hours with bae you know what it
is it's just this is
I've always seen other JP uh senpas and
I've also seen some ID girls do like a
Birthday Countdown
um I don't think I did one last year
because I was like well I don't really
have a birthday I did like the
pre-birthday zatsu uh but I thought you
know because I don't have a zatsu plan
to oh sorry a Tatsu Mighty pet plan
tomorrow
um might as well do one today you know
the bgm's in my head I mean come on it's
such a fun PGM
didn't you kind of countdown did I I
forgot
[Music]
do you even have anything planned
tomorrow
what if I said no
what'd you guys do hmm what would you
guys do if I said no to the girls no
you're doing a tootsu oh okay
um just a little heads up um counselors
won't be calling in today
um I wanted counselors to call in
um tomorrow so the only toxic that's
happening that is happening tomorrow is
countries because you know I want my I
want my Council my Council roommates to
call in on my actual birthday
um so today is everyone else can you
explain what a tootsie is pretty much
when
um um people call you
so I've opened the invitation
um I invited everyone on the Ian and ID
side with a really casual message and I
was like yo if you're free and you're
alive feel free to call in
you know if you check the stream and
there's no one calling you want to call
and say hi
to the JP side I literally normally for
that uh I keep saying normally for
tootsus I send a message to people like
last year I sent everyone like an
invitation to join the tops matches
this time I didn't I didn't I didn't
invite anyone
[Music]
um so if anyone sees Twitter if any any
JP Senpai so happens to watch this and
then and they decide to call in great
but you know I have no expectations if
there's no thoughts about you we'll just
talk for two hours it's fine
foreign
that's the thing I didn't want to
prepare a totsimati this year because I
remember last year satsumachi cost me so
much stress
um so
[Music]
this is somewhat a sad birthday don't
worry the real birthday is tomorrow
you have strawberry milk ready I'm
drinking coffee first I
um in like the at the one hour and a one
and a half hour mark I'm gonna pull out
the strawberry milk
oh but also this is a chance
um to talk to you guys because
I mean technically I did stream today
but
um should we talk about that
the next topic of conversation will be
today's stream for the next four minutes
[Music]
how dare you
can we even call that a stream
[Music]
I can't believe you did that well come I
didn't lie to you guys the stream
literally said I'm unboxing the eye
tracker opening the goddamn eye dresser
that's all it said
you can't look at me in the eyeballs
come on look at me in the eyeballs you
can't look at me and tell me that you
didn't get exactly what you told what
you were told that you were getting
[Music]
tell me
receive
satisfactory
entertainment because you were warned
you were given the heads up via the
stream title okay
I don't want to hear anybody shouting
refund
it was literally six minutes unboxing
the rest was allergies
it's been a while since I last dropped
the pink for you happy early birthday
I know I'm a little bit behind on super
chats I will catch up to them after I
revive uh in March thank you so much
because I'm pretty sure I'm gonna have
to I won't be able to read super chats
tomorrow either
um if I get any
me
the refund has expired I'm sorry
[Music]
Bae tell us why did you make us wait one
whole year for something that took you
five minutes and you clearly could have
done it a long time ago
nine
why
question is why not
come on why not
[Music]
like
the thing is it's like the easier a task
is the more difficult it is to
get yourself to do it
think about procrastination
procrastination happens
most often
[Music]
when things are easy
one minute
one minute one minute I should make the
clock
whoa put it right here
perfect
[Music]
what a stream I'm a professional
streamer
29 28 27 26 25 24 23 22 21 20 19. why is
my voice So Soft
ah oh that's better
is that better I feel that's better okay
10.
Evan
seven four three two one
okay
it's not my birthday
[Music]
thank you thank you very much
we have one year until my birthday
Ricky thank you so much
thank you thank you guys so much yes
thank you so much for the pink silver
Bumble thank you
oh
oh my God wait no stop it stop it no
actually don't send supers this dream
um actually you don't need to send soup
with any stream but I'm just saying if
this is truly unhinged times with me
um please save up I have a lot of things
planned for you guys okay please don't
it's all good it's okay my chat
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay we're good
I don't know what happened for a second
I was like bro what just happened okay
we're back we're back we're back
are we now back
[Music]
am I getting denied my birthday
foreign
[Music]
oh no
um
[Music]
bum
bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
laughs
[Music]
oh we're back
oh look at my back
[Music]
are we good okay we're back
sweet
[Music]
wait oh my goodness I was gonna wait a
little bit until I opened the Tatsu but
someone is already very eager
so I'm gonna call them okay
okay this
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey hey
[Music]
hello hi are you okay
are you okay
I've been waiting there since you opened
your stream oh
I'm gonna start for another like 30
minutes bro oh
I didn't realize that was the time oh
I'm sorry
wait hold the tiny said wait where was
it
oh
well better early than never you know
that's what they're saying right
so true hello
I thought I thought you were gonna open
it right away oh no
it's okay it's okay it's okay should I
come back should I come back like what
what like 20 23 minutes
okay
I gotta go take my bath my my little
cute voice in my bathtub was telling me
my bathroom is ready so okay go take a
bath and come back
but but but
you don't call me in your bag
no
I'm not enjoy my bad
so so um happy not birthday oh okay
there's a there's a
98.736 of me falling asleep right after
my bath so I thought oh okay
um in that case before you go can you
sing happy birthday for me please
um
[Music]
I don't know
it's not really your birthday is it
no but yeah I mean I mean come on I mean
I mean the fact that I don't have a
birthday means that come on you got to
take pity on me please sing me a
birthday song
ah for free
um yeah
[Music]
about that
I mean usually I do charge for Happy
Birthday songs okay but I don't have
seen um it is it's it's a small price of
549.99 but what a deal no I know I know
but I guess you have like a you know you
have like a discounted version of the
song I don't really have a discount I
mean all right all right I'll give you
I'll give you uh what's it what do they
call it the um the the
what they call it a sneak peek you know
when they when they can play the game
just a little bit demo version demo
version can you give me a demo version
of Happy Birthday all right
um
there we go
oh my God
that's that's a double version wait
what are you called that was not it that
was the third version Oh no huh
you're gonna add the audio stock life
well thank you very much thank you thank
you you're kidding happy birthday
[Music]
satisfied with that
happy
Court sir yeah
lighter
antenna
[Music]
hung up on me
uh
well in that case yay it's my birthday I
love how YouTube cut off the it hit 12.
happy birthday but love you love it
thank you uh
[Music]
okay I guess I might as well just open
um
calls now I was gonna start in a little
bit because I wanted to talk to you guys
a little bit about what happened today
and the reason why I'm a little bit
unhinged the reason is I'm not
can you believe it I'm not drunk I
haven't had a sip of alcohol because I
am
looking for tomorrow I'm going
I'm so sorry
um
[Music]
um nice I've been preparing for tomorrow
is that literally I was like babe you
cannot have any drinks whatsoever
um but then I also had a recording today
so after the 10 minute stream I had to
go record something
um and then now I'm here and now I'm a
little bit tired I got home a little
while ago
um yay
I'm drunk of being tired
okay so I'm gonna make a little tweet
as well
um just a retweet thing put this open if
anyone wants to join
[Music]
that's on that
that's not can I see this
Pokemon too
begins now
all right now I have I was profusely
apologizing because there actually was
someone who messaged me and was like can
I be first I want to be the first to
call you and I was like yeah sure it at
the 30 mark
let's begin too loud I'm sorry we're
bringing down a bit
[Music]
and then we got the inner Ambush but
are you ready
I'll call them
[Laughter]
hi do you need a picture do you need a
picture for me I have picture oh good
okay here's the answer
happy birthday how much time do I have
again
um as your heart desires ma'am OMG okay
okay
and then she was freaking out
you're fine nothing happened you're okay
you're doing so great oh thank you thank
you very much thank you very much how
are you are you excited foreign
[Laughter]
one of the reasons why I set up this
totally was also just to distract myself
from tomorrow because I'm just so
stressed
um
so yeah oh wait yeah you should
introduce yourself I forgot to ask Anna
to introduce
yourself
please introduce yourself hello I am
mirrors celery
do you really
pie
you're the one who called me celery all
the time this is celery
oh thank you it is very celery
it's okay I have I have been thoroughly
enjoying you using the color filters
is like my streaming Sensei I'm a
professional streamer yes everybody we
know this fact but
is my Sensei I'll find things like six
months later and I've been like
can I talk about
that because your reaction was so cute
it was so funny I was like when I first
when I first showed they how to use the
the color filters for stream she her
face her mouth was so wide open she
stared at me she was like oh my
God for 10 minutes straight and I was
just testing it up for 10 minutes she
was like no
[Music]
these days really is a surpasses the
surpasses what one can dream of my
goodness it was that's too much for your
your 12 year old brain I get it
it's okay it really is too much anyway
no no she's Too Young Too Young she's
too young to worry somehow I'm a Zuma
but has like the I have the
characteristics of a boomer of like how
they figure out everything like
way after the hypers died it's okay
you're so busy
it's good
it's good it's good it's it's great now
I okay so I have something like very
very scuffed I didn't actually get to
finish this on time so I am very upset
what I don't know if you can play
anything
like
um
I have been working with an arranger on
something it is very scuffed right now I
still need to record my piano and
arrange it wait a minute
pump your face
oh
[Music]
did you make it just come up I have been
working with someone to make a jazz
instrumental for play dice I have not
finished it because I was also really
busy but I it was as soon as I finished
it you'll have rights to like stream it
or use it in streams or whatever and I
will send it over to you as soon as I
can
I promise I will finish it through why
are you so cool oh my God
last night let's go
girls
no nailed me I have no idea how she did
it insane
[Laughter]
her vocals have improved so much like in
the time I know her you guys don't even
know I am so proud of you all the time
that'll make me cry the night has only
begun come on
first I was so nervous so I was like
please I just needed to be over
but before you go can you sing me a
birthday song please
oh my god of course um
oh God do I do it do I do a meme version
or singing actually okay
happy birthday to you
you live in a zoo
[Laughter]
you look like a rat and you smell like
one too
[Music]
now are you one are you two are you
three are you four are you five are you
six are you wait do you even age from
this
um I think I'm 12 and technically twelve
twelve thousand three quarters this year
okay okay okay are you tough are you
seven and a half are you done
congratulations on turning it 12 and
three quarters I carry you
[Laughter]
thank you I love you
[Music]
bye-bye
that was mealwi
umely is one of my closest friends
um
yeah
and I suddenly have a feeling of
punching something
but that's so sweet
she did Jazzy
[Music]
it's so beautiful I'm so happy Mary
thank you I love you
[Music]
I love you thank you very much
I will be happy if you touching me by
the way
thank you thank you so much for coming
my goodness
well that was me only oh I should put up
the sign there we go
feel free to call in friends stand by
Paul hey
that made my day
oh was that even proper English
feel free to call in friends that is
proper English what are you talking
about
[Music]
oh
hello hello hi
hey happy birthday thank you oh almost
not really I have a year left
oh what I have a year left till my
birthday
huh
it's a leap year remember next year
yeah
okay well happy birthday next I'll come
back again
how are you
I love you oh I'm pretty good uh I don't
know my toe kind of aches for some
reason with toe aches is everything okay
I was just dancing maybe I stepped on it
weird dancing I want to see on my dance
maybe soon I'm Gonna See You Dance
there's not much to see don't worry
don't worry no what do you mean I feel
like you you have really good like body
wig almost like a belly dance if that
makes sense like I feel like you're
gonna feel really good full body wiggle
Oh you mean body wave
yeah yeah yeah I was like belly wiggle
[Music]
like a belly dance
yo yeah were you like move your tummy
all like
[Music]
try again right now I can't do it
it looks really cool if you haven't seen
it before it's it can be pretty
impressive oh buddy roll yeah I can do
buddy roll yes
well yeah I miss you too I miss you each
other yeah I hope so
[Music]
I hope you're still enjoying Japan
though
yeah
[Music]
did I need to eat anything special for
your countdown
um I have coffee I have strawberry milk
and I have a plate of water
[Music]
yeah it's it was very humid today it was
disgusting and human
it was so nice
[Music]
I didn't wear a jacket I just wore like
a long sleeve and oh it's nice oh sorry
to rub it anyway oh
if I did want to say it but I think
you're really hard working and I think
it's really like I don't know if you're
crazy how social you are and how much
work you do and streaming recording
dancing learning studying like you're
like a superhero
[Music]
I'm happy I got to know you
you I would love to you so much
oh thank you so much oh you're doing
great thank you thank you so much thank
you so much I feel like you're gonna do
even more amazing things
sit downhill from here no no no you're
on the incline
I mean look at this set have you ever
seen such a beautiful birthday
color coordination
is the only thing that has color
coordination
birthday song for me I want a birthday
song for you I was just gonna ask you
for that
please take it away ma'am
I'm gonna do a dubstep version dubstep
happy birthday
that's it
yes
that was wonderful
ah thank you thank you so much
thank you that was the best
oh thank you good luck today thank you
thank you for calling in yeah
okay
[Music]
yo that's some those are some fire Beats
well 30 minutes has passed already what
are you in a Flash
imagine if that was the end and just no
one else called after that
yeah bye
[Music]
anyway I was gonna explain the premise
of this Tatsu which is I'm making
everyone who costing me a birthday song
because I feel like that's funny
um and also I don't think I've ever
heard anyone sing me a birthday song
before
um because I don't think anyone sung me
a birthday song last year except for
myself did I sing myself a birthday song
last year
[Music]
oh apart from Nico Senpai sent me a
birthday song
[Music]
oh
fine gluten all right Chad I want you
I want you to sing me a birthday song
right now
[Music]
come on you can do it come on
I'm waiting I'll even turn the music
come on uh-huh
Never Gonna Give You
uh-huh I can hear it oh
do you hear in the distance I can hear
in the distance
no
oh
hello
ah oh hello hello hi
hi
can you hear me
is your voice okay are you are you sure
um I think I'm okay just don't tell
Grandma
everybody
hi so you we're wrong you're wrong I'm
wrong because I did sing you happy
birthday last year you did you don't
remember I don't remember anything from
us I'm surprised this entire year of
memory I'm so sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
if I hear it again it will jog my memory
you know just you're really gonna ask
the sick Chihuahua to sing a birthday
song to you maybe just say it can you oh
I've never had the birthday song said to
me I'll remember this forever
can you say the birthday song to me
happy birthday to you
Jam in your shoe
happy birthday in your pants
happy birthday to you
wait I do remember no well I mean last
time I sent it to you it was German
different yeah you sent it to me in
German can you also sing it to me in
Korean
maybe
an original original version I remember
I remember oh my God I really did drug
my memory
wow wow wow wow it's not your birthday
though this is kind of like a scam
totsumachi yeah that's the point
[Music]
yes by the way oh
so are you did you like Fire Emblem
yeah
oh no oh no no uh yeah I did except I'm
not very good at it
where is stream number two Bae it's
coming really it's coming are you
scamming us again
it's coming soon I was just a little bit
busy because we are planning on
continuing it
um it depends how poorly I want to do at
least one more and it depends how poorly
it goes if I take like another two hours
to to defeat an enemy then I might have
to I mean but if that's not so unnormal
like even I who nowadays I'm a pro and I
am
um curling my hair around my finger
but for me like they're supposed to take
that long the fights are supposed to
take really long oh even when you're
good at it oh
because you have to think out every
freaking move to like make everything
ideal oh like especially if you play in
the hard mode or so then you want every
move to be perfect because they do a lot
of damage in hard mode oh
um you just don't want to get hit
ideally at all oh my I'm guessing you
play easy mode but yes I mean the
easiest the most baby of baby moons and
I still found that really difficult
um I also I had a I was like working in
your Fire Emblem streams and you started
doing things and I was like what is this
you were attributing skills or you would
something was happening and I was like I
don't know what is that I don't know
what is this what is this magic there's
many things to do but
um
you'll get it I mean what you played
five hours last time how far did you get
I don't remember
um I think you'll get into the groove
because this is my second Fire Emblem
game but the last one you know that I
played was the one that previously
released and that was my first final
game ever and I was really bad at it in
the first one two three streams so it's
normal it's okay but then once you get
the gist of it it's fun and it's chill
because it it like unlike a an actual
like action game or whatever you have
time to think about your moves and and
that's cool because you don't get
stressed out about it oh well yeah
people are saying I'm around chapter
four chapter five
oh I didn't get that far what the heck
isn't too bad at all and it's your
mommy's game so yeah a lot of sports
yeah
well it looks like I'm playing more fire
well I was gonna play more Fire Emblem
when I come back in March anyway so oh
yeah March March March oh yeah I'm
taking a like a couple days off after
tomorrow because
Oh I thought you meant coming back to
Japan in March
I wish man I wish
I wish can I ask you another thing yes
what was your because you stayed in
Japan for so long what was your favorite
memory favorite memory
what was your favorite adventure during
your time here in Japan
that's a really cool question
um
[Music]
I think folk doing a funk I'm doing it
though I don't know I have a lot of
weird memories I think the day all the
memories spending time with you guys was
really fun
actually that night that we all went out
was was kind of was was a highlight I
remember
one yeah where afterwards you uh went to
the arcades and stuff yeah yeah yeah but
but I remember dinner as well that was
really fun
yeah but to know so many people
yellow team outing yeah one yeah and
also like having an opportunity to meet
so many people at once yeah
um oh but didn't you go to excuse me
with Iris oh I did that's not that why
is that not the first thing coming up in
your mind huh Ashley what's your name is
the very the first thing that came into
my mind was me breaking a table but
how
what can I say I'm just buff red I'm
just so buff I'm so swole no that's
that's not true that's not true
I don't believe that no
you didn't look very buff to me
[Laughter]
maybe it's the spikes in your what don't
you have like the one you have on your
collar don't you have this so I'm like
no I guess you don't have it on your
arms right no no no
that would have been a good excuse yeah
I guess not I have no idea how I broke
that table I just I just looked back and
there was a hole is it out of plastic or
what no it was wood
wood I guess it's like a really real
soft really thin yeah and there's
certain types of wood that just break
really easily yeah maybe then actually
you did them a favor because then
they're gonna buy a proper table
yeah that's such a shitty table because
obviously at the shitty table
on the contrary it is now just I've
heightened I've added value to the table
so now chocolate can't get rid of it
because people everyone who goes over to
like
um who does like cooking clubs would be
like where's the table
become a piece of whole life history you
know I I wonder what she will do with it
I wonder
did she say I have no clue
[Music]
yeah guys but
so you can't say you're not saying that
your favorite memory was you're outing
with beirus I'm shocked
[Music]
yeah well oh one more thing what are you
doing tomorrow can I get a spoiler like
a little hint what's going on tomorrow
this is my special thing
small thing small small spoiler small
small teaser oh I can type it to you oh
well all these things I've been asking
I've kind of mostly been asking for the
sake of your um audience though
so there's
tomorrow I'm doing something I'm showing
ah yeah I understand yeah
I think I heard about you preparing
yeah I hope they enjoy it oh
I think they will two more bro tomorrow
yeah I'm not gonna spoil this one sorry
guys I tried to give you spoilers
try you try
is someone calling you like on the side
no no okay so when are you going to
Korea
don't know I want to go this year though
you have nothing planned no I don't not
uh not a career at least
um we should like
um like maybe like overlap because I
want to go to Korea again this year yeah
yeah oh I'm down I'm down I'm down old
school okay wait have you been before
I've never been before
holy macaroni yeah I've never gone to
Korea before I know absolutely shameful
I should be you know I should be cast
out on the streets I cannot believe this
I know what's so cool like last time
when I went for the first time
um I went to like a amusement park
that's indoors a lot lot of world I
think oh a lot of work oh
perfect because you
know where the weather is bad or when
it's cold outside or so you can still go
and there's like so many attractions and
there's roller courses and stuff too so
on this ice skating and all kinds of
cool stuff oh yeah I won't go worth it
I'll go yeah a big recommendation if you
ever end up going okay I'm going I'll go
now I'll go that's probably people
waiting no
wait
[Laughter]
okay there's no set time anyway if I if
if this happens I just go over it
doesn't matter oh good we're looking
forward to your inevitable birthday
merch too oh yeah get hived I don't know
unless you don't get it because it's not
a favorite birthday you know I just you
know this is yeah just nothing's
happening tomorrow I don't have anything
prepared literally nothing tomorrow is
just nothing but how how many years
apart are leap years for four years
so last year was also a scam yeah last
year was also scam
God
how did we hire a scammer
that kind of I don't know feeling for
chaos rant I think it's kind of thing I
like being scammed by you
all right then I'll leave you to it
thank you bye
[Music]
cute
so cute
thank you anyway
ah I feel like a storm has passed
I should
[Music]
all right I should have just waited in
here for a bit okay I'm gonna wait in
here for a bit if anyone joins
you know what it is I'm gonna Circle
through different surface
and just join random VCS until someone
says hi
that's what I'm gonna do
[Music]
Lola that's kind of sad hey
I'm a rat you know I'm a Nut what was it
is that the right I'm a hermit no that's
not the right word
I move around
[Music]
never let them know your next move
exactly
a nomad is that it
any money
[Music]
so much fun so many friends I honestly
I was thinking what to do if no one
calls I mean I we could have just done
like a two and a half hour like I'd say
that would have been completely fine but
it's a bit sad isn't it
any friends watching feel free to call
in hi Mata
uh
you're really planning for no one to
call I mean you never know you know
[Music]
why didn't you randomly call JP members
like she said in
should
[Music]
hold on
I'm gonna call Sister see if she picks
up I also need to figure out my sound
settings hold on
[Music]
wait we have another guest hold on let
me figure out get
watching hold on I need to figure out my
sound settings real quick give me like
two minutes
[Music]
what
I think I needed to restart I go XLR app
something is
oh my God
oh
my God
[Music]
okay how about we do that okay
scared me so bad
you guys hear that okay
[Music]
can you guys hear the music
okay
you guys can hear music right okay okay
I don't know I think my technically I
think I do need to restart my PC but you
know it'll just be what it is that's
fine
[Music]
I mean
all right we have guests and then I have
to guess I want to try
yes waiting for the guest
who is guest
[Music]
let's see if this works
my service works
[Music]
hello
really soft oh my outfit was wrong there
we go
please speak
hello
sorry
[Music]
I was fixing my sound settings evidently
the one fixed anyway hello please
introduce yourself
greetings it is
the coolest and the cutest exercise
happy birthday
I am hello greetings hello hello
why did you laugh in the middle of
introduction bruh when they left a
minute because I'm pretty funny dude I
mean I guess laugh at yourself haha yeah
yeah
[Laughter]
happy birthday
special day dude
um yeah I mean not yet right yeah not
yet but my freaking time sounds like
I'll be the death of me I swear to God
what is it is it really early for you
oh yeah it's like uh
uh 8 A.M ish almost 9 A.M is I'm so
sorry thank you so much for calling me
it's so good so good so I'm so sorry big
sorry it's so good I'm happy to be here
I'm happy to be here it's it's your
birthday we have to celebrate you you
know it's not really my birthday
I mean it's it's it's a special day
regardless oh thank you thank you very
much of course of course yeah
um this is our first
are you nervous is it hot
the nerves kicking you no not really
because I don't have that set by energy
no because you actually didn't really
supportive and super sweet like I
remember you wish me luck in my debuts
I'm on my original song so you're very
approachable
[Music]
I don't know if that's a good thing or a
bed anyway
you do exceed Senpai energy I feel
respect for you like I would take a
bullet for you
oh but yeah like if someone were to
shoot you I'll like I'll like take the
bullet for you because I respect you
that much
uh since debut pretty much how how are
you doing is dreaming good are you alive
it's been fun yeah yeah it's been fun
I've been having lots of fun it's it's
like honestly a bit of a new
new aspect of life for me because I like
like you know like you know I'm mostly
used to doing like musical content
creation so the whole like shift thing
here store editing an audience and
everything has been very very new and
very nerve-wracking but I'm a fresh I am
for sure alive which is good and I'm
having a great time
it's good very good very good to hear
yes yes yes very good early days hasn't
gone anything yet we're not insane yet
yeah exactly
well I'm making everyone who calls in do
this but can you please sing a happy
birthday song for me please
set a birthday song a birthday song
Birthday song
a birthday song I mean I I guess it's
some brand if I sing you happy birthday
in Spanish right oh that's right
you need to speak Spanish Mike I do my
level of Spanish is
wait
wait hold on uh
you okay
how do you say hello
do you did you forgot to say hello in
Spanish
it's on
[Music]
foreign
okay cut me a break I
I tie it
it's okay this guy's been working too
hard
you're learning English Okay cut me a
break too late so I'm fine I'm already
heading there I'm already heading I want
to be a hard-working a hard-working uh
burp too hard working bird well please
sing me um happy birthday in Spanish
I've never heard the birthday song in
Spanish actually it's not that they're
pronounces the words I changed so I
guess um
um
well now I'm nervous
didn't put in the spot um there's two
songs but I guess I like uh feliz
cumpleanos
[Music]
wait wait is the police the same as the
police and Feliz Navidad yeah it's happy
is happy yeah like what does Navidad
mean
Christmas
[Laughter]
[Music]
so it's like the chance it's a happy
Christmas oh
yeah it's like like you know like when
you say happy birthday feliz cumpleanos
you also say Feliz Navidad which is I
mean not happy Christmas but Merry
Christmas
[Music]
I'm not okay anyway thank you so much
thank you for the education
um
well 8 A.M I could never yeah it is a
bit early but I did it I did it
thank you so much I really appreciate it
you just made something
you made noises that I couldn't work out
did you say something
I do it for you
thank you
thank you thank you of course of course
happy birthday happy birthday thank you
very much yeah okay
get back to sleep now ready
[Music]
Feliz Navidad translates to happy
Christmas
why was I never told this anyway that
was hakka from
um
[Music]
very kind very talented
um
probably oh
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah he thinks heavy metal doesn't he
oh yes imagine not know her not knowing
how to say hello in Spanish
shut up
[Music]
in that case I cannot call I feel bad
ah
[Music]
she just finished streaming
wait really
she's with Shira okay okay I'm gonna
message her I'm gonna message her see
I'll message her first
I wanna
[Music]
come on
oh I should leave this PC should I sit
in the other VC
I'm moving
[Music]
moment to all different VCS
I remember seeing calling you yes
that was a very that was also another
thing that I remember distinctly from my
Japan trip
the sudden the very sudden call and I
look at my phone and he said what
dun dun dun
[Music]
hi Callie
boy
are you still playing
stream wait what are you still playing
the game bad game one the game that you
were playing game
game game game yes
[Music]
oh you finished
one join the party things have been
happening
many things have been happening
[Music]
oh yeah I finished game you finished
game I sure did Big oat suit how was
game
ah scary at first but actually it's
super fun I I actually wanted to stream
it really bad today so I finished it oh
congratulations you're playing on the
dead dead space dead streams that dead
yeah dead dead
game yeah game a finished game today
finished game today I'm so proud of you
[Music]
I was curious about the game
uh you know in my opinion I feel like
it's not a horror horror game I feel
like it's more of like a thriller game
but knowing you I think between like you
both you and kiwawa are like really like
easy to scare I feel with these kinds of
things oh
so I just I don't know if you would
enjoy it but you should try it anyway
you're kind of on a roll I feel like you
can play anything
[Music]
okay here's the thing I feel like the
only reason why I was more attracted to
it is because you can shoot back right
uh yeah yeah exactly
uh so uh so Outlast is not your kind of
game I see yeah
yeah that was a
I still have it in my game Library I'm
still trying to convince myself one day
that like to get like absolutely
hammered drunk and try and play out loud
I wonder if that would make it better or
worse would that make it better I don't
know I mean it would be entertaining
both ways but it's just a matter of
would you be more scared if you were
drinking and playing it or would you be
would you be like Brave
that's the thing see normally when I'm
when I'm drunk I get really giggly so
maybe it will counteract the fear and
I'll just stop laughing
I don't know I see I see that's true I
don't know well have you ever played a
horror game with a friend I feel like
you and Iris have at some point yeah
well I've played with yes
um I think we played the observation
game and then I've played is
I still get scared but it's just the
only difference when playing with
someone else is there's someone laughing
in the background oh yeah that's true
that's a really good point we can't give
you any courage huh yeah and also many
with fauna because we did the month of
October horror thing
oh yeah
I'm surprised you guys didn't play dead
space together you can play Dead Space 3
together but it might be a regional
issue thing
that would be funny maybe I'll get you
to play dead space with me because we're
kind of in the same region oh maybe I
was planning on playing a soon anyway
because it looked I it looked pretty fun
when I was working in Iris to stream
when she played it right so here's an
idea how about I finish because I
finished one and now I'm gonna play two
how about you play those two and then we
meet up together in three and we can
play that together
how about that sounds good
if you can do it I'm holding a handout
to you okay challenge
I'll meet you at three dear sister
sounds good sounds good you'll be fine
it'll be an experience
well now hold on they could just about
prove you guys wrong who knows who knows
well we'll say dog space Dead Space 2 is
apparently scarier I see well yeah I
think that's the one I remember scarring
me in my childhood so that's gonna be
interesting oh goodness all right well
I'll see how I go with one and then I'll
see how you go with two and if you get
scheduling too I don't think we're ever
gonna play through
definitely definitely play the Remake
it's super good oh okay I really
recommend it okay wait is that number
one all right yeah it's a remake of the
first one it just came out this year
2023 so yes yes yes yes oh okay so
that's the one that I saw Irish play
okay I will start with that yeah okay
you should all right well you take care
of yourself have a happy birthday before
you go yeah birthday song
sure
here we go
it's Bay's birthday yeah break it down
now yeah
Bay's birthday yeah yeah all right hey
Bae you're my favorite Mouse everybody
knows Bae is gonna rock the house she's
been streaming hardcore and she can't be
stopped hurry up Bae come on and make
that bass drop do your sick hip-hop
moves like you do we know the bay is
always gonna come through whether it is
a game or variety stream Bae is gonna
make everybody's dreams come true we
love Bae she's so cool
in fact she dropped out of school
because she's so awesome she couldn't be
beat but anybody else on the street
that's right Bae say Bae happy happy
happy birthday
again that was brilliant
I don't know what the [\h__\h] that was I
tried to think of like the easiest words
to end each sentence
that's how you do baby freestyle
yeah thank you so much guys you got a
kick out of it I'm gonna go do some
acapella streaming with my little
members you have you have a fantastic
day thank you thank you so much
you're welcome thank you happy baby
bye
[Music]
okay I would like to make something very
clear I did not drop out of school
the reason I laughed so hard was because
yes I'm I'm done with school
um oh is that the first time I'm saying
on screen I finished I finished school
guys
[Music]
yeah I didn't drop out but it just made
me laugh because the timing of like you
won't see many um studying streams
anymore and if people start thinking
that I dropped out of school bruh
oh
yeah that's just casual it's all right
[Music]
is that what the good news was yeah it
was
yeah
I finished Elementary School
anyway
[Music]
uh your feisty
no
I know okay see you
oh this is
um it's kind of my birthday
kind of
kind of fantastic yeah
foreign
[Music]
how old are you 12.
Journey
oh
hmm
[Music]
leap year
baby
[Music]
please one more please
okay yeah
[Laughter]
foreign
sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
hey hey
um
ah
[Laughter]
iversity
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh it's gonna
come here yes Japanese yes
[Music]
foreign
you know
um
hi
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday dear
you
happy birthday
to you
thank you
[Applause]
bye bye bye bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I can now die happy sorry guys you won't
see me at tomorrow's stream I'm just I'm
just dead
thank you thank you oh we've got people
waiting I'm so sorry
hello
getting this picture that was amazing I
love how this is a happy birthday you
man I did not think I could get a
birthday song from
Champagne very good
perfecting good
amazing
next color
have
[Applause]
my ears
oh she's here okay Google sorry
I think you blew out my ears
are you okay it's my phone it's mouthful
I had the volume turned up to Max after
success
I'm sorry about that I'm sorry
that also I was watching the stream oh
good all good okay we're good we're good
we're good
all right
happy birthday
already have these but I these are like
handmade from me I do enjoy am I getting
some
fun
I'm getting them buns
oh
my God I feel like they would hold on I
feel like they would
I'm gonna go into my hot air balloon and
change for a second hold on
oh I feel like
they are gonna fit perfectly
hold on
everybody hold on
oh that's not it
is
oh they're huge
to fit your huge heart that is
my thumbs oh
my goodness broke my hair oh my goodness
what's it behind my ears
oh do you put it behind oh okay because
this is the situation I have at the
moment
why do they cook it
well my child is beautiful thank you
stunning
why do they kind of fit goodness
[Laughter]
[Music]
now you look like me child
she got them big buns hun
looking gorgeous thank you very much
thank you thank you thank you I love
them thank you
yeah yeah yeah I can't get anything
physical this year no I'm sorry stop it
stop it no need you are the best gift
that I can ask for
[Music]
thank you I'm I'm blessed
[Laughter]
pointy finger right pointy finger left
quite tipping
man I actually use that a lot
right do you use that quite a lot for
some reason oh goodness anyway
um anyways how how's your day so far
that's good I don't remember the past
how long we've been streaming hour also
it's been very unhinged hours all right
it's only been an hour
it's very unhappy very unhinged but you
know it's been fun you just remember
oh yeah YouTube crashed like right after
you hit midnight in Australia
the entire platform just crashed and I
was like what what a great birthday gift
it was great and then yeah it did crash
for quite a lot yeah
um and then now we're here hello some
friends cool it's great very fun
yeah well since it's your birthday do
you have like any birthday wishes or
anything birthday wishes
I want
to sleep
I really want to sleep
you know the biggest motivator for me
for the past week has been March 1st
looking out I'm just looking forward to
passing out for an entire day
literally ah right after you're not
first
for two years
actually yeah it's still not my birthday
I'll get one eventually even
eventually I'll get there one day
oh dear
one year to go
I love how people have like you know oh
my God countdown to birthday I literally
I've been having a countdown for the
past two years
honestly
I think she's three years to celebrate
your birthday it really is
that's great I'm sorry that's sad
it's all right that's just me that just
means like on February 29th next year
it's gonna be my day I don't care
says
my day only yeah what's
yeah let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
imagine the countdown after next year
because after it will be four years
until I have another one
once you do get it you have to win for
another four years it's all right good
things come to those who wait oh
goodness
oh child so somebody else will give you
birthday gifts um
thank you okay yeah so you can enjoy
yourself okay
I will thank you so much I'm having so
much fun
I love you I'm having so much fun
But be sure to take it easy okay I will
in March yeah yeah
for sure after tomorrow I will for five
days
for five days
yeah I just need a little I just need a
little recharge a little hibernation and
that's it
yeah Casino birthdays last for like the
whole month yeah exactly
wait but visit camp
I try not to think about it too hard
because if I do then that one single
brain cell that has been working over
time like just forever is just send help
[Laughter]
s they have I hope you have a great rest
of your day night week
the year
the best uh take care okay thank you oh
before you go can I get a happy birthday
song
me yes you
oh okay
anything for you to help me I hope
you're ready I'm ready
happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you
bye bye love you bye
what was
wait what was that awesome
[Music]
something exploding what the heck oh
goodness okay this person's been waiting
for a little bit I'm gonna call them
immediately what was that
a little bit crazy
thank you ollie
[Music]
no snacks oh snacks what's next
you have five seconds to pick up
five four three
[Music]
wait
okay
hold on hold on hold on
she is currently streaming at the moment
[Music]
I'm gonna go poke her real quick
hello you're here I was gonna go to you
I just opened just oh wait
no it's fine it's fine hello oh wait I
wasn't sure whether that was you or
because I just opened your stream and
that was you talking oh my God okay
okay oh happy birthday
well thank you well no I know that your
birthday is actually
29th right yeah
yeah and then why are you celebrating it
in 28.
um because why not first of March
February
but over 20 counts after 28 right
it's a different month
[Music]
every four years exactly every four
years
foreign
no it's actually nice right it makes you
like
keep being young all the time because
you just celebrate your birthday like in
every four years ah yeah it makes me
appreciate you know yeah it makes me
appreciate my youth yes
no it doesn't hurt just you know every
single every single year up until now
it's just no no Twitter balloons no I
just every year it's just balloonless it
doesn't hurt it doesn't hurt the soul
but you know yeah
so that's the reason why you're forever
12.
what happened
wait if she is 12 then
you should be 48.
what
yeah because you're still reading it
every four years right
oh
no
no oh and no
no no
[Music]
no no no no
I'm 12 billion years old okay 12 billion
so you are 48 billion sure I'm 48.
technically I'm 48 billion years old but
actually I'm 12 billion years old
hmm fine
it's so so how is it how is it you're
it's unknown it's still condone right
sorry what
what I'm done but stream stream calm
down right okay sit down yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm so sorry my brain has not been
working I I couldn't understand what you
were saying
yes I'm still doing the countdown stream
I'm a cat I'm gonna count until
uh it is midnight in Japan South Korea
so we still got a little bit left to go
okay sure sure yes yes yes yes you know
but maybe it's the 48 I mean the 12
billion years of age catching up to me
you know my back hurts my brain's not
working my ears are failing me you know
it all comes with age
it's okay I mean
yeah like I mean I'm still young and I
already like you know facing that kind
of issues too so it's fine it's still
young
I don't know how young is Young
how young
are you like you know a middle aged you
know technically but then they try to
delude themselves that they're young or
you actually young how old are you no
I'm actually Young no it's a secret by
the way but yeah
I mean
even if I old even if I'm old you know
like
you're still older than me right because
you're like 48 billion yeah
yeah see yeah but I'm also with God so
no
no if if Kyla is Boomer then
what about you yeah I'm just dead
I'm dead by that standard I am deceased
this engine okay ancient
yeah I'll take that I'm a fossil bro
boss I'm a fossil
where are you screaming yeah I'm
streaming you know like this is a really
good game you know what gaming you're
the you're the symbol of chaos right you
need you really need to play this game
like for real for real I recommend you
to play this game
okay
uh good job the the title of the game is
good job good job yeah they need to try
it right yeah yeah yeah yeah for sure
yes for real for real like for real for
real for real yeah for real this game is
amazing
like for real for real for real for real
yeah oh total chaos all right I will try
it when I yeah when I come out of my
hibernation but yeah sure yeah you
better check it yeah
it's not that long too it's not that
long like you can finish it like uh in
less than 10 hours like yeah do like
separate I don't like how the way you
say less than 10 hours saying that
that's something easy all right it's not
easy I didn't say that it was easy I say
that it's not that long oh okay
all right because normally you don't
really say less than 10 hours it's an
easy game to fit you know that doesn't
no no no I I think they're really going
the same sentence together usually but
no I did this in three parts too this is
like my last part this is my third one
oh my goodness yeah yeah
well check it out thank you so much for
the recommendation
so what's your plan today tonight today
I don't know right now I might get a
refill
I'm just gonna sit here and receive
anyone else calls in that's pretty much
okay
okay enjoy your day thank you so much
can I get a birthday song
foreign
how to sing a happy birthday by the way
happy
wait wait
um
wait uh
happy birthday wait wait
um Let me let me let me call my little
sister first okay let me let me
let me call my little sister first okay
she will help me to do that okay hold on
okay I thought she was about to pull in
on me okay
wait wait wait uh
okay
the anticipation
hello
oh hello
can you hear me oh you're cutting out a
little bit
my my voice caught up yeah your voice is
cutting up why does her why does this
voice make me turn into baby bay
um
he's getting cut off by the by the
filter
I don't have the filter in the Discord
it's already not noise suppression oh
there we go okay you didn't cut off that
time you're doing good okay
let me let me sing the song for you yes
please
yay happy birthday
happy birthday
oh what is your name
my name is
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
enjoy your birthday thank you
you are cute too because you want to
hear my friends
I'll be friends yes
okay hold on let me call my sister back
okay okay thank you
why
hello hi why does that voice bring up
what oh my God okay what just happened I
don't know
I think I think you just made a male
friend I guess yeah and your birthday on
my birthday amazing
amazing amazing anyway I'll let you get
back to streaming thank you so much okay
sure thank you so much
bye
[Music]
I'm very concerned on the
impact
that
high-pitched voices seem to have on me
why does that bring out my own
high-pitched voice I don't know it's
very strange anyway oh we got another
guess wow look at The Cools just rolling
in I don't have any memory of what
is happening
[Music]
okay
guess
let's call them let's call them let's
call them
[Music]
hello hello
no
[Music]
what are you talking about what do we
talk about collabing that's crazy
wow wow that seems to have quite clearly
what I don't remember this conversation
yeah me neither
la la la
hey
[Music]
oh
oh my God oh my God wait I wanted to ask
you about oh my God what's it called
again the the the one drink that you
drank with with aichan and Olga Senpai
what was that again
hahaha
where is this
yeah how was that
bruh you have no idea you need are you
good with better things no no no it
can't be that bad yeah it was it was it
was it is the worst thing I have ever
consumed in my entire life you have no
clue literally
just terrible actually you need to try
it you need to try it yeah
um I want to try legit
literally please it can't be that bad
it's so bad literally there were things
floating in it
um the thing the one that Olga stand by
a boy no the seeds it was literally the
ingredient said
bitter melon 100
yeah there was nothing else in it there
was no anything to like dilute it it was
just a hundred percent crushed bit of
melon literally so when you flip the
bottle over literally you can see all
the Little Fibers and the seeds just
floating like the pulp of the bitter
melon just floating inside of the liquid
and I'm like
wait oh my god did she drink like a full
glasses I took a sip oh
oh you know the serving size the serving
size is 30 milliliters by the way
just as is if you want to dilute it then
you add like water to it but serving
size is 30 milliliters but nothing bad
have but enough of that I nearly puked
I I nearly puked that's what happened
[Music]
oh well it can be that bad oh my God
famous last words
I mean if you're not good with bitter
then it might not be a thing I feel like
someone like maybe Kylie would probably
enjoy it but I don't know I I it's it's
bad it's really bad
well we will see
well I want to be there when you try it
I want to meet you one day yeah let's go
yeah let's go I feel like I should take
a trip to Indonesia
yes totally I feel like there's
something in me that's just bad you
should do it I don't know yeah do you
have like any place that you would like
to visit
no I've never been to Indonesia before
so I don't know bay worldwide yeah maybe
2023 is the year of just travel
who knows it's not that far either so
yeah it's not only that far yeah maybe I
can just isn't like I'll see in
Indonesia Neighbors
like legit neighbors were like each
other yeah
let's do like a hop skip jump we can
disappear for two days go to Indonesia
come back no one would ever know
exactly that's the plan oh my gosh oh
let's go all right well let's go hmm all
right well I'll let you know
well that's
one of 2023. Let's Go All right you did
nice shut up I can't geography was not
my strong suit
all right
amazing yeah but we should definitely
meet up for having me of course before
you know if you visit yes can I get a
birthday song
oh Birthday song even even though it's
not your birthday yes precisely because
it's not nice what is the purpose of
singing birthday songs that's the
purpose it's not your birthday that's
the purpose of not having a purpose the
fact that it's not my birthday but
singing a birthday song is perfect that
is the purpose
okay maybe maybe how a chaos thinks is
not really something I can understand
oh my God
oh God okay
all right let me let me turn off my
voice changer
so now if my voice changer oh oh
goodness okay okay okay okay okay
are you
happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
was that your real voice
dude you should let that out more often
that was beautiful
when I was just talking to myself
[Music]
thank you
they've been talking about for two hours
now sorry I'm trying to send a message
to someone to tell them I'm trying to
it's like a back backhanded way of like
saying please join this totsu because
why not but I'm trying to say in a very
backhanded way of like he didn't need to
come to my totes or anything
um
I'm making this a lot more difficult I
could just ask them if they wanted to
join
why am I why am I just making things
harder for me for myself all right
[Music]
yes okay next
would you have someone else
hello hello hello
oh
try not looking quite good
just invite them fine
hello
[Music]
hello hello
you just wake up hello
no I'm eating ice cream eating ice cream
what flavor
Fruit Loops
you have Fruit Loops ice cream
[Music]
yeah fruitless ice cream
you won I won
[Music]
air wait ah
um
yeah
it's it's a bit melting so it's kind of
liquid now so this is
there you go wow thank you
[Music]
oh that looks so cool foreign
Happy Birthday Countdown okay
thank you Matt thank you
thank you for coming when is your
birthday next year
[\h__\h]
all right foreign
child
[Music]
let me let me Google
ma'am would you like to explain how you
got out of prison
oh my mom
get me out your mother bailed you out
yeah yeah
Mommy Chihuahua when she come here in
Indonesia
goodness gotta have a word
with with Madame kiwawa my mom also
haven't worked with you you gotta be
prepared
oh this is she's a phoenix she's
Immortal I'm a God I'm immortal
but
but she has fire you don't
that's a good point ah
man I feel like why am I reverting back
to my my role as an officer and I'm just
getting I'm just getting corned help
this child
she's got a point she's making a good
point all right
all right nice
how have you been are you you're doing
good I'm good how about you I'm good too
nice nice nice nice
I have a birthday present but since your
birthday is
[Music]
next year hmm
I think I'm saving for next year
all right I look forward to your
birthday gift next to thank you thank
you by the way
next year yeah you can give it to me
next year
Oreo okay what's your favorite cheese my
favorite cheese Mozzarella
mozzarella mozzarella
how about your favorite food cheese
cheese
nice what's your favorite food
I like
like I love
[Music]
um
sorry I have I I have a proof oh are you
okay take care of yourself I thought you
started crying because you were just so
overwhelmed by your favorite food no no
no no no no no no no no I like
what's that
wow you haven't tried it my mom have
taste it you need to taste it too
chillar is uh is made of tapioca dough
oh and then just add some chili powder
and many many MSD you know MSG I love
image oh that looks good good
yeah
yes MSG best white powder
yeah yeah yeah
um
so it does look good oh
oh I want to try it
it's spicy can you handle spiciness yep
I love spicy
but you know Indonesian spiciness is
different from yours I I've heard I've
heard how is it compared to like Korean
food I'm pretty good with Korean spice I
wonder how bad Indonesian spices
foreign
[Music]
it's uh yeah it's it's spicy enough
spicy enough
Pork yeah yeah
huh well
even if I die I do want to try it it
looks really good
sure
what is that yeah what is death no one
no nobody cares yeah thank you for you
for coming
can I get a can I get a a birthday song
from you perhaps
what the heck
how many birthday songs did you get
um currently I'm on
uh one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten ten
sing for me
I need to make the the lyrics quickly
you make the lyrics
I mean it's a song We Need lyrics oh
child you can just sing the normal
birthday song
like happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you yeah
um oh they're not good enough
[Music]
to worry oh
it's it's it's not like I make a new
song only for you or what it's just
nice I don't like I just don't like
common things it's just
overrated Happy Birthday song it's
overrated
[Music]
well how much time do you need ma'am
five minutes please five minutes okay
okay
start from now okay she got five minutes
on the clock everybody oh my goodness is
it already it's 48 already
five minutes what can
five minutes let's see if I can make a
birthday song in five minutes
happy birthday to you
[Music]
I want some stew wait that's not how
what rhymes with you
boot
two happy birthday to you
it's my birthday too
let's go get some Shabu Shabu
and then I'll give you a
chip
you sound like a kindergarten babe shut
up
[Music]
um
genius
yo I'm still rhyming
what about you
[Music]
no freestyle rap career I'm sorry
um
[Music]
Pikachu
this is the power of the Mind behind
play dice leave me alone
[Music]
it's cooking
three more minutes
Toby you have three more minutes left oh
the two minutes what time do we start 48
okay we got two minutes we got two
minutes Miss
[Music]
have you ever tried making your own
version of birthday songs I just did
should we continue do we need the
strawberry milk I'm gonna get the
strawberry milk
um after we hit midnight in Japan
in Korea
where's the lamb sauce oh my God I was
watching Izakaya
um I watched it twice in the last 24
hours
it's just been playing in the background
as I've been working
[Music]
it's such a good show
the animation anime
anime
the anime yeah they have all like the
food like glistened and then when they
drink The Toria is number their eyes go
like all wide and they're like
good
look and then it goes
[Music]
yes ma'am you have 30 seconds
what
you have 30 seconds ma'am
I'm sure it sounds fine you're a genius
Kobo
[Music]
four three two one I think
no
can I get my song ma'am
[Music]
no
ma'am
it's
[Music]
oh
it's
it's bad
I hear a guitar it's really good
foreign
[Music]
Okay so
wait so so you have a sharp
teeth uh-huh
you like mozzarella cheese uh-huh
and then
your name is Hawk was Bales uh-huh
it's your birthday but not really it's
your birthday countdown uh-huh
um
I call you rat uh-huh
okay
so
wait I'm shy
[Music]
you're doing great
it's it's bad it's bad it's not a fun
song oh it's like can I get a normal
Birthday song it's okay I just want to
hear your voice
normal Birthday song
it's so hard to make something in rhyme
with your yeah
yeah that's this yeah I'm one of a kind
you know it's very hard I understand
[Music]
cause you're right
let's eat some more
[Music]
I love your smile with those cute sharp
teeth
welcome
have a wonderful day
our one and
only day
where's it where's it that was beautiful
thank you so much
yeah all right thank you did you say it
did you say you you said you because
it's
good it was good did you hear your voice
ma'am it healed oh my my tiredness gone
you know my my depression anxiety gone
stress gone I'm Healed madam
[Music]
day thanks
thank you so much thank you so much
you're a genius
[Music]
do you get the message of this song
again you really you really like me
because you're right because I'm I'm
right
and Brad I'm right
you're red and red
the color red oh
oh red I'm red yes yes yes I'm rad and
I'm red and I'm red and I'm red yeah
you're how what the hell what's the
difference
rat no I'm I'm red I'm rat and I'm Brad
yeah the animal rat and the color rat
he's just the same rat rat read
Road Rhoden I'm the same
I don't care
okay well thank you so much for coming I
just realized the time anyway thank you
thank you
more with me yes I will I will
thank you okay bye bye
I just noticed the time she's so cute
[Music]
oh
thank you she's so cute
she's so cute
[Music]
I'm losing my mind
answering something wait
[Music]
30 seconds
okay okay I'm gonna take the first sip
when it hits midnight 20 seconds okay
we got the milk
three two one
it's still not my birthday
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh thank you
[Music]
thank you
thank you so much the Buns
what I can't read
[Music]
foreign
it's still not my birthday it's very
strange
um I don't feel that like oh my God it's
my birthday because it's not my birthday
okay we have some people waiting oh my
goodness I did not expect this turnout
but amazing
um
Pokemon
[Music]
at this rate we're going for another two
hours we really are
it do be like that
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
America
[Laughter]
Union
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah this one's his name
[Music]
is
coming
tonight
you are perfect ready
[Music]
pokemon.com
is it
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
battle
s
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
perfect already
yes yes
ma'am yes
yes ma'am
hi
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
but
[Laughter]
[Applause]
happy birthday
[Music]
turn into a monk
amazing
ah my goodness let me take another sip
of strawberry milk
remember how I said I was gonna stop
at at midnight
yeah
looks like I'm I'm just I'm just
I'm
we ain't stopping you know we still have
how long do we have we have 12 hours
until the actual stream don't worry
about it
fine
I'm
talking about it
don't worry about it
[Music]
ah
man I'm having so much fun talking to
everyone
I don't know if you can tell
do you like compare this to my last hot
soup can you tell like I feel like I've
become a little bit closer to everyone
can you tell
there's a lot more banter
ah I remember last year was always uh
you know I was
being as polite as I possibly could and
I was asking them questions and now I'm
just so unhinged
speaking of um unhinged
um
thank you
did you pop over the week zero yet no I
told you I'm not having alcohol tonight
I'm being a good girl
I'm not having alcohol tonight
[Music]
you've grown a lot and it's still not
your birthday I know right can you
imagine
what would happen when it is my birthday
just become a completely different
person from the amount of growth
wouldn't you say
so many friends
all right I'm gonna try cool
oh
[Music]
she turns into an ornery song
by my next birthday
go through an ultimate puberty like
what is it growth spurt that's what it
is
no need for alcohol just jet lag so true
truth how many birthday songs have we
collected tonight one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve
[Music]
don't pretend don't forget chat song
that is true 13. chat song
thank you very much
and I got a chip
from the energy from Cobble
what
what a blessed birthday and it's not
even my birthday
[Music]
crazy
12 songs
the scam is running smoothly it doobie
maybe I'm trying someone else
actually no we're gonna wait should we
wait
[Music]
and he needs this they're just away from
their seat
hold on we can just talk until
they're ready
oh try should I call someone else ah
UA
yeah buddy
[Music]
still not real birthday
to you
happy birthday to me
happy birthday dear
you and me happy birthday
[Laughter]
yay yeah yeah true my I I'm truly
birthday it's your birthday
thank you
happy birthday to you each other thank
you
yeah I'm gonna go out
always
yeah
Cheers Cheers Cheers
please no more please
really no more
yeah I'm preparing for you next time you
came to Japan no
no no no
no no no no no my goodness okay okay
now go I know
it's very bitter and some some YouTuber
or Entertainer and drink it as the
punishment
Bieber have you ever heard
so yeah we must try it next time we will
come to Japan actually I I I've tried it
actually did you like it
um it's it's really Nick and Nick with
um
[Laughter]
no I will save you don't worry
we drink it for me
no no no no no
no no I I
tried traders in Japanese yeah Japanese
punishment as an Entertainer yeah
you were great live streamer as always
so yeah you must try it yeah you think
she's using the content cards on me oh
my God
yeah
oh my God
[Laughter]
I'm curious looking very uncertain
my goodness
great great women us gaining many
various experiences in Japan
foreign
[Music]
myself
you said you were getting ready right
yes
[Music]
perfect already
so
endure anything right true
foreign
[Music]
okay
I will prepare Samsung for you
anyway happy birthday happy birthday oh
thank you thank you thank you
Happy Birthday to us
[Applause]
too
[Music]
okay her English gets better wow
so much
um
[Music]
hello
thank you
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
Nick
I
[Music]
[Laughter]
bastard.com
[Music]
hahaha
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
a bit more
okay
[Music]
Baba
today
[Music]
somebody else
oh yes hi hi hi yeah
more
[Music]
haha
[Laughter]
that's good
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
happy
birthday
[Laughter]
happy birthday to you yay
getting robbed
I'm getting robbed of my birthday
actually robbed
foreign
[Music]
today tomorrow and today tomorrow
today
tomorrow
[Music]
later
that's true later I have it later that's
what it is I have it later
[Applause]
I think this may be the last one I'm
looking at the time it's getting a
little bit late I still got
[Music]
I got a message from someone
else I may have misread the message
[Music]
foreign hello
no
no no
I'll just show you the I'll read the
message now I got a message from
somebody I know
um
ever
yeah bye bye bye
hold on
[Music]
technical difficulties
huh
[Music]
whoa
I just put the Buns behind my head oh
they look so good
okay
[Music]
I'm gonna show you guys what I got from
a zoo body senpai
sounds good
[Music]
you guys ready you guys aren't ready
your message
my best voice
[Music]
um
myself
[Music]
you need to work on that
yeah bye huh
[Music]
it feels perfect apologize
so happy
the badge is gonna get confiscated back
you don't know that
Town Mountain
for what it's worth I'm gonna put
um
shoot this picture
but right here
[Music]
thank you
um I might wait for a little bit though
someone else who asked um if I was still
open to the topic was still open but
they might have gone that's okay we'll
wait for you a little bit if not then
I'll just end stream because I really
need to go to sleep I need a way oh I
need to set up tomorrow's stream let's
do that now
yo setting up stream while streaming oh
you know
[Music]
let's set up stream while streaming
and that's all schedule stream Disney
this isn't it
[Music]
dream section now this is called
efficiency you know and then after you
guys finish watching this you can just
wait over on the other one amazing now
bye that's not what I wanted to do
still not baby day
um
what should we name the stream title
guys
should we name it Tech technically a
birthday stream
[Music]
the greatest scam of your life
scam day
no I don't want that attached to my name
excuse me
um
[Music]
not good babe
oh my god
[Music]
um
birthday stream not clickbait
[\h__\h]
I love it birthday stream not clickbait
amazing
[Music]
birthday stream for real for real
and then in the description we can write
maybe one day
and we'll get
I will celebrate
my actual birthday oh wait no
367 days left
till my birthday
[Music]
put an eye-catching thumbnail oh don't
even worry about it
I've got the best thumbnail
the best thumbnail
best thumbnail
it's actually a beautiful thumbnail you
guys know you should go you guys should
know me by now and my thumbnails
beautiful absolutely beautiful
[Music]
don't include anything else I don't
think so
um
thumbnail is
[Music]
oh beautiful
okay
looking good
[Music]
okay we're lagging a little bit but
that's okay okay today at two no 12 p.m
jst which is 2 p.m okay
double everything correct hashtag still
no baby day birthday stream for real for
real not clickbait
um
367 days left till my birthday tea heat
some nail changed perfect
amazing
[Music]
this sounds very optimized for YouTube
big bro
[Music]
biggest bruh
it is
[Music]
live streaming isn't available right now
I don't want a live stream I just want
to set up the Stream
[Music]
no I don't want to go live
what
[Music]
Okay Google Google never mind
okay we good I think we could be good I
think we're good okay
[Music]
don't go in life that'd be nuts
it's not 300 and
oh is it 300 how many days is it
[Music]
wait is it still the wrong thumb it
should be the right thumbnail though
what
height
360. that's the right thumbnail for me
[Music]
beautiful thumbnail thank you
maybe you need to refresh
um let me just change
the maths real quick
yeah so
um
Lisa did my thumbnail again this year
they're so talented
they're so talented and then the logo is
done by Spirit snare
366 days there we go
[Music]
Fitness is a base special
get excited I hope you guys enjoy it I
don't know I'm kind of nervous oh well
wait so what are you gonna do you're
gonna have to wait and see
he's gonna wait and see
[Music]
yeah all right I think I might end zatsu
here because I think
the other
person might have gone it's okay
but we had a great turnout today we had
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen fifth well Fourteen and a half
including sugar
14 calls 14 birthday songs 15 plus chat
oh amazing this has been a great stream
everybody thank you guys so much now get
the sleepy I will go to sleep now I
promise
thank you so much
thank you thank you
[Music]
I had a great time I had a great what I
had a great time spending time with what
I had a great night spending time wait I
had a great time
spending all what
I had a great
it was great spending time with you
it was great spending time with you guys
I'll see you guys in a couple hours
well in 11 hours or so
um for the actual birthday stream so
[Music]
hey I'll see you guys later okay bye
I forgot to say annyeong
[Music]
thank you