so
my
hello pam please how are we doing today
it is celebration
[Music]
thank you guys so much for 3k
subscribers why is my chat shrink again
it's fine earlier give me a sec i can
fix that easily so it's
it's nice shape there we go now you look
better chat needs to look good for the
celebration
it's not fair if you guys are tiny
anyway i need to know if you're here or
not but first i gotta go up for a sec i
gotta go up for a sec
i gotta go up for a sec i saw there were
some super chats early
so thank you kite and joey pampley
yeah yeah yeah i finally get all the
apples i guess i guess you're not gonna
give them away anymore
i guess it's fine to share as long as
you also give me apples it's fine
it's fine it's fine i'm going to be
generous because
it's the 3k celebration so i can be
generous
that's a lot of apples too i appreciate
the apples
i got here and alex thank you as well i
may not be able to watch the stream
but i can at least since that is fine
vod is also acceptable and i appreciate
the synth of course
appreciate i appreciate it well i just
saw another one come in
where'd it go from stacy thank you cece
hi pam i love you congrats on 3k thank
you stacey
i love you too anyone who gives me money
i love them
that's just how a ceo operates i guess
it's fine i also love you guys that
can't symptom
i saw it in the chat before it showed up
for some reason it was slow
emily thank you so much for the super
chat
whoa congrats let's celebrate yeah yeah
yeah i'm gonna do my best to celebrate
i don't know why they're showing up so
late on my stream i apologize
i'll probably read them before they show
up for some reason
emily should show up soon if it doesn't
i gotta
i gotta have an issue with this program
that's making everything not work
but that's not showing up where is it
please show please show
you know it's not working and that's
making me really sad
but i appreciate that oh there it is
there it is
it's just for you emily it's just for
you
whoa and go rider as well thank you
congrats on 3k boss thank you
we're never going to get past the intro
are we what i was trying to say
oh my god oh my god oh my god
akka super already what the
oh it means a lot to me though if you
think the stream is worth that much
especially when you have the option to
watch for free wow wow wow wow thank you
to the best ceo here's some funds for
more knives and apples thank you
the it's gonna be a little delayed
showing up but i promise you'll get a
really nice sound
i went all out for the aka super sound
and goal rider yourself show up too oh
and the bad gamer whoa
whoa hey go blast congrats for the 3k
sub unlocking super chat membership
thank you
i got some updates on membership to
share in a bit and there's one yeah yeah
that's just for you just for you
[Laughter]
i got some nice lovely sounds i don't
know why the alerts are so late
but my time oh my god i paused my timer
i paused
[Music]
all right timer's going it's just
inactive for some reason for a minute
but it's working
i don't know why it froze oh and y'all
car thank you thank you congrats on 3k
thank you
thank you i wanted to congratulate you
but i guess i'm now here
to be fair is pretty great honestly it's
pretty great
i was trying to think what noises would
make it make it nice for you guys
i thought that one was pretty fun
[Laughter]
but i had to make it for akka soup
special
special but all of them are very special
and what i was trying to say if you
can't sniff it's okay it's okay
it's not gonna be all end-all honestly
it means just as much to me
if you're here watching the stream at
all i'm participating in chat
or if you like the video or if you share
the video like
you have no idea that means about that
so much as well
like superman super chats are wonderful
i appreciate i very much appreciate
very very much appreciate but but but if
you can't i also i also appreciate you
i also appreciate you i know that not
everyone can and i don't want everyone
to feel obligated if they literally
can't
so i still i still really really
appreciate all the support i wouldn't
have gotten to 3k without every single
one of you okay
okay so every single one of you is
appreciated
[Laughter]
i said don't worry every single one is
appreciated so please don't feel guilty
or apologize if you can't
whoa and archer emilia oh the first
magenta supply you get you get a really
nice
a really nice sound too it's an original
it's an original song cover
that i wrote yesterday
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you emily for
the raid
[Music]
you like my new original i worked really
hard on it
yeah i appreciate you emily and all of
you
and what i was trying to say though oh i
already did say it about if you can't
super chat it's fine
it's fine yeah there's so many comments
okay for those of you who are here on
time
you are promoted to
early access pamphlet so you get all the
information
on everything a little bit early a
little bit early
which is pretty great and ah
thank you so much to 79 for this up i
meant to turn sub notifications off but
you know what it's fine
it's fine i think it's better more
celebration oh hearty wow
wow wow thank you thanks for all the
extra work this morning boss you're
welcome thanks for um putting up with my
tech difficulty screaming time
[Laughter]
you guys don't even know oh my jesus you
have no idea what tech difficulties i
dealt with oh my
[Music]
the worst ones ever and fog crush thank
you thank you because i needed to hear
it again the curse is too strong you're
welcome
i'm glad you enjoyed the course of the
pam caillou
if it might die though if i get if i get
copyright claimed on it it's gonna die
[Laughter]
maybe i sound so much like caillou
i'm sorry the notifications are popping
up so late it's something i'm gonna have
to try to figure out for later yeah
but at least for now you get to see them
at least for now you get to see them at
all
and um what i was gonna say is that
those of you who are here
join me in oh there we go oh you get a
better one
[Music]
i hope it was worth that for you
[Laughter]
that one caused me physical pain to
record this it better have been worth it
for you
kaiba needs a party hat
you're not wrong you're not wrong give
me one sec
give me one sec give me one sec
let me see if i can find him a party hat
for at least one of them i don't have
time to put it on all of them
i think one of them does
uh this works it says it's from fallout
does kylo want a fallout part i think he
does
i think whoa whoa whoa two more while i
go out of the window hold on
hold on three more oh my god
from caleb's prime tension so you ready
for the last episode of shadowhouse
no i'm terrified i do
actually i'm gonna spoil something i
have i have
something
something related to shadow's house
that'll be coming out at some point
you can look forward to that i love the
show so much that i wanted to make
something dedicated to it
and that wrath thank you congratulations
boss keep up the good work have a couple
apples on me
you know what don't mind if i do give me
a second
oh i need some anyway
and now you're dragging the leaf we get
how this works
thank congratulations and melodic
congrats on 3k pen please proud to be
here day one yes
yes congrats to you guys as well because
the community has grown so much
and i appreciate it so much like that's
what makes streaming so fun you know all
the community
so thank you guys as well hey one second
oh no
no no no i don't know my soundproofing
fell in the head again but this time i
reached it
uh uh it's fine
[Music]
okay okay i got kaiba
his party hat i got his party hat give
me one sec i'm gonna put it on then i'm
gonna move on a bit
[Music]
party hat where are you where are you at
party hat
party hat oh there we go
i put it on the one that you can see it
the most
and there we go is that better
i think it's okay
congrats you deserve it boss if you
reach 30k thank you that'd be wild
that'll be really funny someday
someday someday someday
anyway if you're demoted today
you get to be like a celebration cracker
like the ones that you explode
because i want to celebrate and it's
going to take some sacrifice
so you're going to be an exploding party
cracker
but not to be confused with explode in
my mouth
that is still banned in this workplace
and if you put it on your resume i'm not
hiring you i'm not hiring you
just you get to explode in general
okay okay i'm gonna have a few sips of
tea and then we're gonna move on to the
agenda for today
god i still can't believe we got so many
supers in like the first 20 minutes
i haven't had time to do anything yet 89
viewers what the
whoa thanks to all 89 of you that's
really high
i'm like startled
okay okay
in case you haven't noticed before i go
on to the agenda
the timer over here is for the
announcement relating to free shipping
and some
other secret announcements that's all
gonna be when the timer hits zero
other than that for now the agenda for
today
i'm gonna talk a bit about membership
perks and then some karaoke
shipping announcement and surprise we
might get back to karaoke if you don't
finish it
oh hey inward mouse games for the 666
cursed
super nice i dropped 666 to resurrect
ubu pam
keep at it boss oh flying bonnie for a
full second
only for a few seconds there will be
asmr
later though actually but it's gonna be
some kind of cursed asmr
so i hope i hope you like cursed
[Laughter]
okay and then
yeah that's right after the announcement
actually depending if we go back to
karaoke for a bit it's going to depend
um then we're going to play some slither
io maybe you guys can join my game and
find me maybe not i don't know but we're
going to play some slytherio for a
little bit
joey thank you again for the two dollars
i appreciate the other apple oh my god
and five dollars
joey you don't intend oh my god are you
just testing the sounds
you are literally testing the sounds i
appreciate
thank you and thank you and thank you
and thank you i think that's the right
number
be prepared for lots of sounds from joey
these sounds are all for you they're all
for you
it's a joey celebration it's a joey
celebration
i actually put all the fan art i could
find so far
at the end of the stream and for a
slideshow so you'll get to see lots and
lots and lots of art
he also drew the naruto headband that
gave me the power
to beat ninja gaiden bosses
and knocks aren't thank you thank you 3k
congrats by the way i love how fast you
talk thank you
it's it's i had it i had
a small enough amount that i'm not super
drunk today
but i had some caffeine before stream
because i'm really tired from
tech difficulties i figured cathy
it's caffeine would make this more
interesting so
i had lots
anyway i'm going to wait for all the
sounds to go
no actually i can move on a bit i
thought i was moving on to a slide where
i'd have to like
there you go you got ooh pam again
invert mouse
you can thank joey for that
[Laughter]
caffeine is king dial yeah but it makes
me drunk so it's kind of not king for me
or does that make you like extra king i
don't know i'm
[Music]
oh yeah there we go i promised i'd let
you have all the sounds
anyway moving on a bit to the member
perks you may have noticed it's actually
not
letting you join membership right now
type noise um youtube decided to crap on
me so we got to give them a good
bunk they decided to put the membership
tiers back in review so um
we don't have membership yet
but i'm going to talk about the perks
that come with it because i want you to
still know what you're getting into once
it opens
because the minute it's open it's going
to be alive
so we got some neat stuff
for the first year it's going to be 6.99
us
and for that's going to be pam employee
you get loyalty badges which are these
play asia coins in three colors
and after a certain amount of time you
get my bow my cute ball
because my bow is adorable and everyone
wants my bow
youtube kunwai i know i know
and you get some cute pam emojis which i
was hoping you guys could use today but
i guess not
next time next time next time next time
we'll start off with those four but we
might get more later
there's gonna be members only streams um
they're gonna be
probably more oriented to like playing
games with members
or maybe some miitopia and members can
put their means in the game or something
like that
it'll be kind of like funny silly things
i think that'll be more
member interactive but don't worry
there'll still be three streams a week
that are normal you won't really be
missing out too much if you can't but
there will be super bonus ones for if
you can
and discord ranks and access so you'll
get
specific um roles in discord so you can
have
members only access to content and stuff
maybe some early previews when we're
recording something
maybe maybe some sneak previews
maybe i can put up a preview of the
shadows house thing soon
and um for that as well i often play
games
well not often but lately it's been kind
of often games
off stream like um if i'm doing a collab
of practice
like i might have um playing among us
with people on discord to practice
before i collab
so i'll probably put the lobby code out
to members first if it's not full i'll
put it in the other one as well of
course
but if it's going to be full i'm going
to give members priority i think for
some of the off-stream stuff
but that isn't to say i won't ever do
some that'll be in the main discord i'll
probably do that as well
especially because i want to test among
us 15 person lobby at some point
and i'd rather make that open to
everyone because that's a lot of people
and um pamphlet e plus that one's going
to be us999 a month
but that's going to come with pam packs
and what that is it's a mix of like
visual and audio files
um so it's gonna be like wallpaper
probably related to a recent song cover
it's going to have
voice lines so i'll be making like maybe
three to five type lines
each time and they'll be really related
maybe not related but
they'll be kind of like unique stuff
that you can only get from the pam pack
and sometimes it might include an
acapella version of the song
too as well as an instrumental if it's
an original or maybe a high quality
version if it's a cover
so you don't have to rip it off youtube
and that'll be pretty cool and i'm
really excited about the packs we
actually got one done
already so hold on i'm gonna mute my
music for one sec
okay okay so for this month
we're going to be having do you
recognize this
we've got a remix a piano remix
of virtual pleasure and this is a little
sneak preview of the instrumental
and i'm going to be singing with it as
well of course so there's going to be a
piano cover i'm actually going to
premiere that one on youtube
probably tomorrow and that's going to be
pretty exciting i think and
in addition to that to match the theme
there's gonna be some wallpapers
i don't know i can't remember if this
one exactly is included or not
it's gonna be some it's gonna have the
instrumental version of this song for
sure yes
it will have the instrumental of this
the virtual pleasure piano
you can thank noblewall if he's here for
it he worked
so damn hard making this piano version
like you have no idea
he even panned the piano notes to
different ears
he worked so damn hard so damn hard
give a shout out please to nobuo he
worked he deserves it after doing so
much work preparing for this holy
so please yeah nova was a genius yes he
deserves a lot of credit right now
and in addition to the instrumental and
music stuff
this is a preview of the voice files and
stuff that come with the first
provided the first pack so you'll get
like
um ringtone cuts that are actually the
right files you'd need for apple and
stuff too
and get virtual pleasure and you'll get
the virtual wizard piano
acapella of the original virtual
pleasure and if you know all the panning
and stuff going on in that song
you'll understand how how neat that
actually is it sounds so cool acapella
and you'll get some member lines as well
including workout alarm
a work alarm and a dramatic reading a
virtual pleasure
that one's a show stopper
it'll be a good time
so anyway i apologize that you can't
join right now
but you will be able to join you will be
able to join but you're gonna have to
connect your discord to your youtube
in order to access yeah and the
membership should be live in about 12
hours or so
but as soon as it's available you can
join i don't feel the need to wait for a
stream you can if you want because i
have some notifications
but you don't have to you don't have to
okay so
i'm gonna be doing a bit of the karaoke
now
and i'm gonna just switch over we'll see
how many songs i get in before
before announcement
definitely sold me on the first month at
least nice i hope that you'll enjoy the
pack
and actually the first month i can't
guarantee i can't 100
guarantee but there may end up being a
bonus pack depending if we get it done
in time for the first month so it might
end up being two
because you remember that song cover
with crowd participation
it's in the works and i'm hoping and
hoping fingers crossed
it'll come out soon fingers crossed
it'll come out soon
i cannot guarantee in case something
goes wrong but fingers crossed
definitely this month or next though but
hopefully
very very soon and i still have that
shadows house thing
that probably won't have a pack involved
but the shadows house thing
i do plan to release the full thing
public for that
it'll kind of be like a free example of
what you can expect from pax
you know what it i'm gonna spoil it
you know the ending from shadow's house
nine-nine
i did a cover of nine-nine that's what i
did um when i said i was late
almost late for my last among us collab
because i am
like i what's the word
i i like last minute like yolo recorded
a song cover it was 99 from shadow's
house
so i'll be releasing that and i'm gonna
put the acapella version for free on
youtube
because i want to use it as an example
of what you can expect
also i just really enjoyed it and i want
everyone to hear
it okay
okay can any can chat explain
what the membership is about it's
basically a monthly subscription to the
channel where you get bonus stuff
like you can still watch it if you're
not a member but
you get bonus stuff if you remember it's
kind of like a weird it's like twitch
subscriptions yeah it's like a way to
support your favorite streamers and
stuff like that
much excited for that cover yeah yeah
yeah i figured after you mentioned
shadow's house i was like oh boy do i
got a prize for you
okay i'm switching the karaoke room one
second
okay okay okay i need to get a bite of
apple
and then we'll jump into it i don't know
how many songs we're gonna get through
today but we're gonna do some at least
give me one time
i need some good apple for that quote
okay okay so the first song that i want
to sing i actually don't have the
instrumental
because i was too shy to ask for it
so i'm just gonna sing tv size acapella
give me a sec okay
so what i really wanted to do for this
karaoke
is do like a shout out i want to sing
songs as a shout out
for my senpai for my youtuber senpai
so what i wanted to start with was a
song by the youtuber who kind of
introduced me to youtubers
i know i mentioned made mint and mori
and ollie really inspired me to like
do v tubing but the person i found out
about me tubing from was actually phoebe
town tv
like phoebe i collab with her during the
among us collab i was i was like
freaked out fangirl mode when she's like
yeah i'll join the cloud
because i followed her before i even
knew what youtubers were for her music
yeah
and i was really stoked so i want to
sing a tiny bit
of her original song whimsyland but i
want to sing the english version
it wasn't mint mint was the one that
inspired me to do v tubing i watched her
um
ace attorney streams and i was like i
want to do this this makes me so happy
but i only found out about youtubers
because of phoebe
but mint was definitely the biggest
inspiration for becoming one myself i
think
but yeah i'm going to sing a bit of it
only a little bit because
it is a harder song i want to sing the
full one someday just not not today
i don't have the instrumental either i
was too shy to ask her for it
okay i don't have the lyrics for the
japanese one so i'm gonna do the english
one
hold on why is that so low and there we
go
i'm gonna turn off the sounds for my
super chats for now
so if you want to get a sound i would
send something later
if you don't care you can go for it i'll
check in between every song but
i don't want them interrupting so anyway
i think my timer paused again no it
didn't pause it's just if i don't have a
certain thing up
it doesn't move okay
i'm gonna sing part of whimsyland but
it's gonna be the english one
okay okay
[Applause]
okay everyone wake up my little
bumblebees
melody is in blue
listen to the two
i see that life rushing swirling through
the
air come along for the ride
spread your wings and don't be good
i'm waiting right around the bend
here in
[Music]
may all of your glories disappear
one two three with nights
[Music]
oh my god i forget again holy god this
is embarrassing i'm sorry
[Music]
make the world a new work of art
nature's one big collide is called
connecting life to
life overflowing with hope and with
strength
here in our worms
and that's all we're doing to that
because it's acapella so it's a little
awkward
but i really recommend looking up
phoebe's channel
because you want to hear her sing it
it's really really cute
her her songs are really great she's
released two eps
highly highly highly recommend yeah
[Music]
my timer paused again give me a sec
there we go now it's back
okay okay secondly i'm gonna sing
something just in case you don't have
time to get back to karaoke
i'm gonna do this earlier
[Music]
it's not one ring angel despite what you
might think
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
i'm going to jump into a singing and i
guess it is
it's also a youtuber original but this
is the only one
and that's not a shout out can you give
us a link for the channel yes actually
yes
yes give me one second i'm gonna do that
she mostly streams on twitch but you can
find it and her music's on youtube so
i'll send to youtube
um
oh no oh no i did something that
up chat give me a second
[Music]
okay let's try this again uh stream okay
hold on hold on
oh no it's not gonna come back
okay i gotta get something real quick i
can't see chat at all on my end
i just accidentally killed it trying to
send a link i can get it back though but
it's not going to be as pretty
i have to get the pop-out chat
but i'm going to give you guys the link
because i want you to hear phoebe's
music
there you go they go they go it's a good
opportunity to get my pop-up chat so
it's mine
gave me an excuse to go on the link for
a minute there we go
okay okay so the second one i want to
sing is
a youtuber song as well but it's the
only one
that is not a shout out to a senpai any
guesses
any guesses it's gonna be
and maybe my own i haven't actually sang
it properly since debut
i sang the goofy version
now i'm gonna sing it for real
[Music]
i'm hoping that the timing will be okay
i had some issues with the audio
so let me know if the timing is totally
off i manually set
every single song's red horn
but i have a bad feeling but it won't in
the end so just let me know if i need to
fix it and i'll try to get it for the
other songs
[Music]
and get my lyrics in case i mess it up
from stage
[Music]
is
virtual pleasure i need your direction
two dimensions
[Music]
virtual pleasure i'm living in a dream
my hands up on your
[Music]
i can't believe
but nothing matters except
[Music]
i promise you i'm here to stay
i need your direction to dimension
[Music]
my hands up on your
can we make this
[Music]
i thought that membership was a really
good time to bring this one back because
it's been
it's been quite a while hasn't it
wow there were a lot of tears during
this one thank you thank you i
appreciate all the dynamite
for those of you who are new here
because wow wow there's a big number of
people
um my life oh hiccup my light stick
is dynamite
[Laughter]
i thought it would be more exciting that
way you know you know
i just thought dynamite would be really
fun
four months give or take nah nah nah you
have a goofy version in the middle
join me in the ether come and take a
breather
i feel like that was worth it that that
one
was excellent that one was excellent
if it's different without the goofy
voice i know
i know it's kind of sad the goofy one is
just
it's just god tears it's just god's here
[Music]
oh perfect you gave party explosions
please because you're late so your
demotion is you get to be a party
explosion thingy
so one of those is you blowing up to
sacrifice and make a nice explosion
of celebratory things pikachu
[Music]
there you versus okay we got 17 minutes
i want to do a few more songs and then
we're probably gonna
move on temporarily and then come back
because i'll sing more
okay the next song is actually um
it's not from a youtuber but it is from
a virtual idol group a few of these
songs are
i actually knew about this group for a
very long time they're very underrated
they're very very underrated they need a
lot more views
are any of you guys familiar with abyss
idols
it's a small indie group that makes
online original songs i'm gonna be
singing their first original song which
is rainy season
um i'm gonna have to
get up a youtube video to see the lyrics
i might watch them honestly
because the thing that i i thought i
wrote down the lyrics i did not
i did not so
ah i'm gonna have to watch them in a
video
while i sing and the timing might be off
uh it's gonna be beautiful
it's gonna be beautiful anyway there's
nothing called rainy season let's see
i'm gonna add that in the description
real quick
[Music]
and it's a really upbeat exciting song
so i thought it would be good to start
near the beginning
it might be a little scuffed but i'm
gonna do my best just let me get
just let me get up a part in the song
that i need
i hope desktop audio wasn't just on okay
cool that would have been really loud
for you guys
give me a sec
okay okay that should be wait no i'll
give you a second
okay okay okay okay i'm gonna mute that
so i can listen to my own version it
should work um
yeah here's my audio
catchy barfing did you eat garbage
don't eat garbage during my celebration
okay okay here's let me try to get some
here
[Music]
oh my god i didn't first play i can't
see the lyrics
[Music]
i need to sing it properly i need to
hear
i need to know where i am in the song
okay
[Music]
okay this should be a little better this
should be a little better
i know i'm a fan of the music already
this is my jam it's so good the guitar
is fired
absolute fire this song only has like 5k
views it makes me depressed it needs a
lot more
okay here we go
this time i should have the lyrics
[Music]
okay
the name is rainy season let's see
[Music]
oh
i'll wait a minute
[Music]
okay
me
[Music]
what is normal people music anyway i
don't know
[Music]
i don't remember this part
[Applause]
[Music]
you guys better thank noble for that
piano version also i'm going to drop the
link to this if you want to see the
original music video
oh it has like 7k views now it still
deserves more
give me a sec i'm going to have a piece
of apple and then sing one more before
we get ready for the announcement
i want to do a harder song early
and then we'll get back to some others
the next one's one of my favorite
youtuber original songs i cried like a
baby when i heard it
i'm not always the best at singing it
but i really really really wanted to
sing it
whether i'm good or not it means a lot
to me
okay let me just check it looks like i
missed a super i missed the super
yeah yeah from sck
here's for giving me something new to
listen to you guys thank you thank you i
hope you enjoy the new song to listen to
i i really hope you guys support abyss
idols because i love them
they actually made a newer song and it's
about gambling
but i really wanted to sing rainy
seasons it's a debut song
but they made a song about gambling and
it's really fun i highly recommend
listening to their song about gambling
it's called tap tap tap
anyway what i want oh thank you thank
you amanda central for the sub thank you
thank you thank you
what i'm gonna say next it's a song
from hollow live indonesia
i wonder if that gave any guesses
i cried like a baby when i heard the
song it's so beautiful
but i i haven't actually tried singing
the whole song out loud before um
i think parts of it we'll try i want to
say muna's song
um for noble mvp thank you
i will forward that to the blue somehow
i might forward it
mentally because i kind of want it but
in spirit it goes to no below
i will make sure to hire him to make
lots of new lovely things with it
yeah yeah so it'll go back to him in
that way
anyway i'm gonna attempt to sing luna's
song
attempt but it's a very beautiful song
so i'm gonna do my best and then we'll
chill until the announcement time
i'm very both excited and nervous for
this one
i found an instrumental cover all the
credits are going to go in the
description later so if there's a song
you want to listen to
it'll be in the description later don't
worry okay here we go
[Music]
oh
so
[Music]
but
yet
[Music]
foreign
oh my god
[Music]
a
my head
[Music]
oh
m
[Music]
me
this cover's still beautiful for the
instrumental
yeah muna's song makes me just cry so
much
i hope you guys enjoyed it it's a really
really really beautiful song you should
listen to muna's version
it'll be in my description later so you
can find it
it's really really beautiful yeah yeah
yeah yeah
um yeah the comment
yeah norwegian dragon ball is right
gospels plus caffeine 1.2 times lyric
reading speed
i keep getting messed up because my
brain's reading the lyrics faster than
the song
it's also hard to follow anyway we have
53 seconds till the announcement so
we're just going to chill here for a bit
i'm gonna grab an apple with my 45
seconds
i always enjoy your singing thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
anyway we're going to talk about the
free shipping and stuff in like a few
seconds 26 seconds
so basically just as soon as i finish my
[Music]
apple
oh hey going to run gaming thank you
thank you thank you i love play asia
much love from australia
much love from pamela oh my god there
goes my alarm screaming in my head okay
we're gonna talk about the free shipping
event
okay so for starters
the free shipping event is going to be
part of the summer sale there's no
minimum order required
the only thing is it has to be able to
ship air mail it has to be able to ship
oh i gotta get the sounds back for that
it's gotta be able to ship air mail so
it can't be like over two kilograms or a
certain
certain bigness what's the word a
certain like
largeness i don't know
it's like anyway it's gonna be free
shipping for all of july
all of july all of july
yeah you can thank me baby
it's i was hoping it'd be out a few days
ago but like when i told you guys i
would get it to happen
but i had to put it through bureaucracy
and it took
a few days it took a few days
because everyone was really slow
yeah i can't order too thick can't order
too thick
it's gonna be all of july though yeah
baby and it's gonna be
um airmail only as i said so like two
kilos and what is that
for pounds um
i don't know i kind of want to know that
too so let me check
so like 4.4 pounds ish
4.4 pounds issue can i buy a box of pam
stickers oh boy oh baby
oh baby i got some updates for you stay
tuned and find out
because this isn't my only announcement
this isn't my only announcement
we're gonna browse on the website in a
little bit and show you guys
i said two weeks no i didn't i said all
july it's all july
it started you can't i'm i didn't lie
i didn't lie it's all july but it's july
hong kong time
so if you're going to make an order at
11 58 p.m pacific
like you're late you don't get it if i
taught you anything it should be don't
be late
don't be late you can use it for
pre-orders too it doesn't have to shift
during the period you just have to order
during the period
i know i'm going to use it for
hashikhime
give me that switch physical bl give it
to me
so yeah yeah yeah yeah this announcement
isn't even my final form
i got some other news for you i got some
other news for you
and about that we're gonna go on the
website can i buy the kazoo probably
i think it's the right size basically it
just has to fit in an air mail box so i
think so
i think you can buy the kazoo anyway
i'm gonna talk a bit more about that
shortly
i'm just trying to get my chat back up
so i don't miss anything okay okay
okay okay i'm gonna go through the
website and show some examples of things
that can ship airmail
in a bit but for now i want to show off
other announcements
okay here we go announcement number one
i mean i'm i'm just watching some anime
don't ask me i don't care i don't care
i'm just watching some anime
i'm just listening to some music i don't
care either just let me jam
i'm do some karaoke with myself
i'm too busy deciding what game to play
next stream
and i'm too busy playing a game by
myself
i'm too busy reading fan fiction
[Music]
i just wanna chill with my plushies
i don't care
i care cause everyone's gonna give me
money
yeah yeah yeah i'll tell you more about
these oh yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay so we got some new merch you asked
can you buy a box of stickers the answer
is yes
but they're new stickers they're new
stickers
[Music]
and yes as james said they also work
well as
is it a full set yes oh it's only a full
set let me tell you more after get a
bite of apple
these stickers are not gotcha these you
can buy separately
are you before me oh wow wow thank you
follow crush i like the pan stickers a
lot but you're doing them on knives
makes me nervous
what you don't appreciate my artistry
you don't appreciate my artistry
anyway i'm going to talk about my new
merch
and so we got a box of stickers
it comes with all of them these are not
gotcha stickers
if you buy it you get every single one
of them
there's eight and there's eight
do they come with knives they don't come
with the knives
unfortunately i wanted that but
apparently that was illegal
so they don't come with the knives but
you'll get a set of all eight of these
and in case you haven't noticed in the
video
they shiny
so if you like sparkles you get shine
and they come in this cute little box
it's a really really small little box
so you can basically tack it on to any
order and it won't affect your shipping
cost
at all they're very very very
lightweight
and they're really small too so you can
slip them in like any package size
really as long as the package is bigger
than this but i can't imagine any
packages being smaller than
because all the stickers are piled on
top of each other right
and they come in this cute box let's see
you can open up the box and get this
cute cute cute design
and of course it's drawn by 3pm draw
like usual and yeah
that's gonna be an exciting announcement
so for those of you who've been upset
that you didn't get the gotcha and
you're like
i want to get all the pam stickers well
here's a new set and you can buy the
full set
a full set and it comes with a cute box
now the packaging is really really nice
okay okay but that announcement
that announcement
is still not my final form
i also have some more merch
so in case you have a bunch of switch
games and you want to bring them
a lot of places but like it's kind of
hard because the case is really big
and you're thinking man i just wish i
had a smaller case
you can buy a mini pam case
it's a keychain size yeah but it holds a
switch game
and it has me on it and
the front of it where you see the player
logo
is see-through so like if you put your
games in it you can actually tell what
game is in it ccc
you can see the game
they are super super cute they are very
cute
so these are also available ayah
i love small things and i love switch
games
so these make me really excited that
these exist
i love them a lot
so yeah that's that's my merch
announcements for today
what do you guys think of my new merch
so
far
[Music]
okay okay
i said so far for a reason
because there's actually one more
surprise
in case you want a 3d pam
to infiltrate your home i got you
i'm sad that my model isn't letting me
smile properly ah
give me one sec we're gonna talk about
the last one in a second
in just a second i'm gonna like reset my
face
reset my face because i can't smile and
it's rather upsetting
give me a sec
i'm gonna be bloody for a sec
i needed to switch to a different face
for a second
[Music]
ah i still can't smile today that's no
fun
that's okay we're gonna get the little
smiles today usually i have this big
dopey grin on my face
but it's not working that's okay
you get you can hear the smile in my
voice you can hear
the smile in my voice a one-on-one pan
figure
well do i have a word for you remember
my dream of having a pam statue
in the office it came true there's a
life-sized pam statue in the office
it's kind of a 2d statue though
it's it's a life-sized 2d statue
it's a life-sized 2d statue
i'll take what i can get for now
it's great
so now i can assert my dominance when
anyone comes into work
it's lovely it's lovely
and now that that's out of the way i
actually do have more merch
in case the 2d stickers aren't quite
good enough for you
you may notice that one of these things
is unlike the others
which one okay okay children okay class
which one do you think it is which one
is unlike the others one of these has
something
very different about it
class does anyone know the answer class
does anyone know which one is different
ah joshua i got it first we got some
papercraft pams
one on the bottom oh you're right
the one on the bottom
has no snow shorts just like a white
t-shirt you're right that one's
different oh my god
anyway this is gonna be another thing
that you can buy it's paper craft pam
it'll i'll ship to you in my 3d form oh
yeah baby look at that
look at that
it's it i a box has become me i have
infested the box and
become i have become paper craft pam
this one's great yeah look i'm pretty
chill
i i swear i won't create an army i swear
i'm not shipping these to you so i can
have an army of physical forms to
infiltrate i
swear
and yeah just so you can get a full view
oh got me spinning in circle
ah fly me to the moon and let me stay
among the stars i just got the words
wrong that's why
michael jack five thank you thank you i
believe in pam's supremacy
what a coincidence me too
thanks real kid for the sub yeah yeah
yeah
it's a lambo oh yeah but you get that
money
it is kind of labo pam isn't it
i've also this yeah you can have me on
the couch watching my stream with you
they're in every corner of the office
and seem to be every corner of your
house
ah i fit in a mug i found a nice size i
fit in a mug
and you can reenact hot tub stream in
real life
but i kind of recommend that you don't
put actual water especially not hot
water
or coffee in the mug because um
it might melt it and i i don't really
want to melt so
i would prefer it if you don't do that
and you can also if you feel like having
something extra cursed
you can also put nendo limbs on me
instead
it's extra cursed that way it's just
extra curse that way
it's friend of mine pam's plan for
global domination invading homes little
by little
nah nah nah
nah what are you talking about now
or if you're feeling like even more
cursed oh wait no
that's another image for this one you
don't have to buy just one either
you can make a whole army of me you can
make
a whole army of me yeah yeah
yeah we need a pam we can color you can
color this one if you want you can
scribble on my face
that's why you can buy more than one so
you can scribble
on the other ones
and just in case that's not cursed
enough for you
you can also put it together wrong
massage roll thank you for the super i
know this is just so you can more easily
sink the knives into us when we watch
the sensitivity training video no
no no it's actually kind of hard to
shove knives through boxes
it's kind of difficult for me of course
anyway anyway anyway i want to go
and look these up a little bit on the
website show you how to find them and
stuff yeah
yeah yeah yeah give me a second
[Music]
oh the banner's up now too cool cool
cool okay one second
okay okay we're gonna go on the website
and show it off a bit
so as you can see with the new banner
this is for the free shipping event
and you can click here you can click
here to find all the panel march
you can also search your blocky pam
here you got the mall i got the mini
case a few new photos of it
yeah see it opens up so you can put
stuff in it
before i look at the others i need a bit
more apple my throat's drying up to hell
and back
and of course because it ships by air
mail
you can also get the patent merch with
free shipping
but honestly it's probably more worth it
if you're gonna add other stuff with it
the mini case is 8.99 the sticker pack
is 6.99 and these are all u.s of course
see and get all the cute little images
in my sticker pack
and here's what all the stickers look
like but like digital form
okay funny story i actually have
headphones that look exactly like this
my physical form uses them a lot
so that one's there and you got the
paper pair
oh yeah yeah look at how cute it is
as they infiltrate your homes
and of course just for me
of course i didn't even notice that come
in
thank you again for the super congrats
on reaching 3k he's to greater success
and i hope that you'll go further
even further beyond 5k very least thank
you
thank you maybe someday we'll reach 5k
we're growing we've been growing really
fast since we reached 3k
so it might not even be that far off to
be real
okay i'm gonna oh why did i just click
anyway
there's a video on the website in case
you don't know how to put it together
we're gonna watch it right now i'm gonna
turn it down because i have my own music
playing anyway just in case
you need some help putting it together
there's this video so first you gotta
like
actually open the package and stuff
because if you don't open the package
you can't really put it together that's
fun how it works
and then once you get it it comes in
these little flat pieces
you gotta open them up yeah it's a
tutorial
it's the tutorial arc and gotta pop it
out
you're gonna pop me out
[Music]
why am i getting ads on a pam stream
it's ads for pam merch
it's joint you can click it and buy it
it's helpful
although i guess you're already on the
page and if you find it on youtube
anyway yay yeah you open it up
and you gotta pop out the other one it's
really good if you like
fold all the sections in advance i
actually kind of had trouble making it
[Laughter]
because i really really suck at putting
stuff together
but the tutorial makes it a lot easier
so be sure if you buy it
to check out the tutorial don't be a
dumbass like me
yeah and there's a lot of little tabby
tabby tabbies
you want to fold every single little
tabby tabby tabby tap tabby
because if you fold all the tabbies it's
a lot easier
to put it together
and then you just pop the tabs in the
hole
you just put them in the hole you have
to make sure it's the right hole
if it's not the right hole you get
dumped remember
that's what we said last stream and not
lasting the last ninja gaiden stream
but it's still relevant you gotta
remember
and then there's the head there's a head
there's a head my head is done
i don't have hair yet so i'm like half
caillou but
i got i got part of it i got part of it
my little
especially my little aha gal but um i
think i meant a whole game
don't fold the ones at the top of the
neck yeah yeah yeah
i'm gonna pop out my body if you don't
pop out my body you've only got a floaty
head
you've only got a floaty head and a
floaty head is cool
depending if that's what you want i mean
the one that i made i kind of popped the
head off and sat it on something because
i thought it was funny so
yeah and then you just have to fold the
parts of my body too
because if you don't then the same thing
it's just gonna fall apart
my body is sexy look at it that nice
square body
[Music]
i would tap that nice square body
oh yeah everyone thinks hourglass is the
perfect shape but really it's paper
shaped
nice and square nice and square
i guess it's more like a triangle square
i forget what that shape is called
trapezoid maybe
yeah you gotta fold that body with care
don't make me punch you
thanks jordinger's meowth put this up
i'll say your username is beautiful
dancing pam is just cheering and
cheering for this
oh yeah my hair takes up a lot of space
on the sheet so be really careful with
it
you gotta be really careful with it
my hair is nice and curvy though it's
nice and luscious
and so the hair looks kind of strange on
its own but if you bend it a little bit
it gives it that nice wavy texture like
i actually have
yeah yeah trapezium maybe
and then you just pop that in as well it
looks kind of strange from behind but i
mean ideally you're not looking at me
from behind anyway because you want to
see my lovely face right
that's the most important part i need to
pop my head on my body
because if you don't it's kind of
awkward
my head alone is nice but my body alone
is kind of depressing
[Music]
i'm almost done almost done you just
gotta pop out my limbs
i'm gonna pop out my limbs you could put
the legs in the arm slots and the arms
in the leg slot if you really want to
but i don't recommend it looks kind of
stupid
i may or may not know because i tried oh
my god i killed the video
what did i do i gotta go back to showing
how to put my arms and legs on there you
just stick them in
and then you put the head on and then if
you want to you put my cool sunglasses
because my sunglasses make me the badass
ceo that you all know and love
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i'm sexy am i not that's one sexy
papercraft
that is one sexy papercraft
i love it i love it okay okay okay
and i want to show a few things that you
can buy with air mail
because it's a size like it's
kind of weird you don't really think
some of the stuff that can fit in there
mail you would never guess
we're gonna oh oh oh you know the new
fatal frame
if you want the new fatal frame game
well guess what you can get it and it'll
ship airmail so you can get fatal frame
with free shipment
whoa i want to get fatal frame
cute girls and spooky ghost best game
best game it's not out yet but i know
it's going to be best game
i want it i want it so bad
can also get the doki doki literature
club limited edition physical version
i think i think i think that one's not
too big
you know if you put it in your cart and
it says if you can get
um you'll know if you get it and it says
you can ship airmail
if it doesn't say airmail that might be
a problem
ninja gaiden if you don't have it yet
you can get ninja gaiden
i don't think you can get a switch
that's too heavy and probably too big
but yeah you can get amiibos you can get
amiibos amiibos work with the free
shipping
so you can get you can get cloud amiibo
you can get the cloud amiibo
i think the cloud amiibo is pretty sexy
so you can get that if you want
what else do we got oh digital oh man
guys i have a secret to tell you about
the digital purchases
so the digital purchases are eligible
for free shipping
did you know the digital the digital
gift cards
always have not only free shipping
but instant shipping
i know it's amazing instant global
shipping holy
we're just not good it's like instant
shipping to your email inbox like
wow wow wow wow wow
and yeah approach pro secret tip from
james
you can split big orders into smaller
ones to get free shipping if it's too
big
if it's too much weight you can just
order multiple things
yeah um video games yeah yeah of course
if they're the right size if it'll fit
in an air mill boxing yeah yeah yeah
can confirm the digital purchase
instantaneous thank you fog crush
anyway toys of course some toys can fit
as well
um i'm not entirely sure if this one
might be too heavy or not but i just
want to show off that we have it
we have this super cute pickled
pre-order like holy
holy look at this like damn damn
even comes the gun i think i love this
so much
it makes me very happy i gotta double
check on the size if it's eligible or
not but like it's really really cute
a 3ds it'll depend on the weight of the
package for 3ds
i think it would be okay but i'm not 100
on that
but just in case pecora isn't eligible
for free shipping i do believe nandroids
are
oh you've got aqua so you can pre-order
the aqua in android
it was free shipping and yes it's cute
and she's so cute oh my god i changed my
expression and it like kills everything
look at her blushy blushy because yeah
you get the aquaman though at least
i think pakoda but i'm not sure it
really depends on the way
anyways go back to toys oh no actually i
want to show one more
jungkook
and so we actually have a line too um
the um pop-up parade figures
usually they're small enough to fit in
our mailbox and they're like
really really good quality but they're
really cheap like
37.99 for this like holy
this is a whole wife and this is a whole
wife
and i'm pretty sure this would be the
right size for airmail like holy
look at this pre-order
and holy holy
it's like my favorite thing we have on
the website right now
i just i love it so much holy
holy look at that jingle jingle is
my wife she's like my ultimate wife
i know she's ultimate model but she's
like ultimate life
yeah pop-up parade stuff is legit
some plushies if they're small enough
are also fine i'm not 100 sure about
this one but
the kezu the kezu
if it's small enough you can get it with
the free shipping you can get the
kazoo
i also just i saw this on twitter
earlier and i need it
i need it it's godzilla hamtaro
it's godzilla hamtaro and i think it's a
very small plushie so i think you can
get the godzilla
i'm taro i am in love with the godzilla
hamtaro
miu is that's fair miyu is better than
junko mew is like
100 top tier there's also pie mom
you're against an impact there's also
movies
so if you want to buy the croods wow
you can you can or fate heaven's
fate say knights have heaven's feel you
can buy that and it should fit
naruto live action gonna get him taro
godzilla i'm pretty sure
i'm pretty sure because it said it was
like 10 centimeters or something right
that should fit
that should fit oh yeah yeah yeah
and music music most soundtracks on like
cd
they're gonna fit like oh what what
i didn't know that the ost was coming
soon
well if you're obsessed with this fine
man like i am and you want to listen to
music from moriarty
i guess you can pre-order that of course
like other top tier music mirror
replicants i don't think i don't know
about this one because it's vinyl
but we do have the near replicant we got
some k-pop as well
if k-pops your jam and get some k-pop
with free shipping
that's always good dragalia lost song
collection
if you wanna it's like better than that
if you wanna listen to the music from
the game that caitlyn voiced in
you can get this regalia lost song
collection and get more ecd
it's still in stock if you haven't
bought it you can get more ecd with free
shipping
and hollow live second fest be on the
stage that should get free shipping
or blue bloom as well
a lot of bts but i mean there's other
kpop as well i believe
like if bts ain't your gem you can get
naked korean man whatever this is i
don't know but it says naked
that's for you dj's out there there's
lots of stuff
lots of stuff black pink lots of stuff
and books um it's gonna depend on the
book i believe because some books can be
quite big or quite heavy
but there are some books you can look at
as well including some yeah by magazines
and stuff
if that's your jam for magazines so i
think it's gonna depend a lot of them
are probably too big but
it's probably worth checking it's worth
adding to your cart and finding out man
it's worth adding to your cart and
finding out there's also always kind of
the weird that you can get as well
there's an 18 plus section that i can't
show on stream so don't worry you digent
there's a whole section for you
there's also like um clearance stuff
oh wow a lot of it's showing us sold out
but there's lots of cool stuff lots and
lots of cool stuff
what's alvarez i'm curious
oh my god full-length mirror versus cat
cats is this you you can buy this weird
figure a full-length mirror versus
cats that's pretty great
i could go for a 64 gigabyte video
memory stick let's see if i got them
i think so
i don't think we have them actually i
could be worth checking though maybe i
typed it wrong or something
anyway that's that's my info
about the free shipping sale
the info about the free shipping sale
i hope you guys are excited to order
some
and add some pam merch to it
my march came out just in time just in
time
for you to add my stuff to all your
orders and help with my world domination
plans
yeah i'm gonna go back to some karaoke
and go back to some karaoke
because i got oh my god why is it still
there
we're not singing this again as much as
i love it
i got other stuff to sing
okay okay okay okay one second
i'm just making sure i didn't know okay
okay
so the next song we're gonna say oh the
bad gamer thank you thank you
well that's the chat for the night
thanks and congrats oh yeah
please get that money hope to see more
amazing streams just like always thank
you
no worries if you have to go it's all
good
yeah melodo crystal h and panty party
are still evasion available
i'm playing asia exclusive you can order
those with free shipping
i mean you could sing that again nah you
gotta do that another day
i got some other songs lined up that i
want to get to before we play games and
asmr and stuff
so next the next song
i'm gonna grab a piece of apple and swap
my teas in the meantime
i wonder if any of you can guess it's
not an original song but it is a parody
so i thought it was close enough any
popular youtuber parodies that you can
think from me shouting out of senpai
it's a pretty easy one i think some of
you can guess it
give me a second
we actually do we still have the 64
gigabyte memory card for vita
i don't know why it didn't show up for
me but it's there you just gotta look
harder than i did
it's a parody by a youtuber it's parody
by a youtuber
um
i'm getting up the lyrics
multiple of you guys guessed it right it
is say
i know i sang it before but i'm missing
again
i can't not give nanners a shout out
okay
here we go
i try to keep it wholesome
[Music]
is
i never said
[Music]
oh
please trust in my confession i swear
[Music]
dirty words
no need
[Music]
is
so
[Music]
you guys believe me why i'm saying so
you guys believe me right i'll say so
i'm saying that i'm gonna say so right
i'm very sensitive i forgot to add it to
this
instrumental goes on forever i think i
up
[Music]
that was shout out to nanners because i
had to
you can't just not give nanners a shout
out if you're a youtuber
i feel like she really was one of the
people other than coco she's probably
one of the most influential people in
getting detours in the west
probably for individuals in the west i
would argue until she joined me so to be
jojo
niana's probably the biggest one
did you put the mic in the chicken coop
are you insulting my singing
are you insulting my singing don't make
me go yandere don't make me go younger
i will i will get my knife don't insult
me
anyway anyway i got a few more songs
that i want to get through
i'm just making sure i didn't miss any
supers because i had to mute it
i didn't we're good we're good we're
good okay
oh i didn't mute it i'm gonna grab that
now because that would that would shock
me to death
if it goes on pills i don't know if any
of you guys are gonna know this but it's
another
song i wanted to personally promote so
the link will be in the description
later i think that's easier than
something in chat
are you guys familiar with moon jelly
i've collabed with moon jelly twice now
um no no no i've collabed with moon
jelly three times moon jelly was in
my among us collab as well as the gardek
phone and the among us club with the
gardek phone crew
um moon jelly is actually a music
producer as well yeah
and her stuff is incredible her stuff is
beautiful
i wanted to sing jelly's original song
one day
because when i first heard it it made me
cry like a baby
it's really beautiful and i asked her
like can i put it up please gonna please
and she let me sing it she even let me
sing a version
that has her harmonies in it so you'll
get to hear
kind of do it it's me singing with moon
jelly's harmonies
i hope i don't up her song because
it's really beautiful
but you should absolutely absolutely
listen to
her song after um give me just like one
second just like one one one
one one one one one one sec one one
a quick message i gotta shoot a quick
[Music]
message
okay okay okay now i gotta get the
lyrics up and then i'm good
okay i'm gonna try to see moon jelly sun
it's really beautiful
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
the
i hope one day
i won't have to pretend
my suffering will end
i hope one day
i'll find the one to give me
the reason to love again
why am i why am i
[Music]
always
to hold my hand
[Music]
oh
i didn't remember
[Music]
that oh here when i open my eyes
i wonder if this
one is the stormy seas will still
i know one day
i finally will hear you
i know one
[Music]
is
is it really
[Music]
is
stand where i am
by your side
[Music]
sun
i hope you guys liked one day by moon
jelly i was really really really happy
that i got permission to sing it because
honestly she did such a wonderful job
it's just
it's such a beautiful song and it's so
underrated
and guys just like abyss idols it it has
like
5 000 views let's get this to way way
way more
i'll put a link in chat quickly but
there will also be a link in the
description later
please support moon jali
she's going to be debuting soon as well
i believe yeah yeah yeah
that'll give her tons and tons and tons
of support tons and tons
and tons and tons and tons and tons and
tons one second in a second
bit of delay just delay there was
terrible delay earlier i spent
so much time fixing it i don't think i
can get it any better
one second one second i'm gonna take a
minute to try to fix this
hmm i gotta fix this if i can but i
don't know if i can
give me a minute give me a minute i'm
gonna try adjusting because you see the
next
few songs coming up on two of them are
very fast
very very fast so i want to fix this if
i can
i have a question for you guys um is the
voice a little early or is the voice a
little late
is the voice earlier late
because it's not i've heard that they're
off but i spent an
hour syncing them up but i guess it's
off again
i gotta try to fix it real briefly but i
don't know which direction to go
because i can't hear it so give me some
[Music]
is it is on time
okay music slightly early
i didn't notice any
i'll adjust it very very slightly very
very
slightly then give me a second
i just brought the voice forwards of it
i'm not gonna it's not gonna sync so
nice with the visuals i'm afraid but
i think it's more important to get the
timing for the audio for the next few
songs
okay okay so for the next song
voice early or instrumental late oh it's
the other way around
[Music]
i'm so confused now i'm getting the
opposite i'm getting
me oh music really okay okay music
really but i had someone else tell me
the music's late oh my god i'm confused
at least i'd say so
uh slower ballads are okay
um i think we're gonna have to just go
with it then
i'll have to try to fix it better for
next time maybe we'll do some of these
songs again yeah
cause i'm a little bit confused i'm
getting conflicting advice here
give me a sec give me a sec for the next
song
i need to transform i need to transform
a little bit
give me give me a minute
i'm so excited for this next one noble
hates the song he hates it
it's from another virtual idol booth so
not v tubers
but a virtual idol okay
it's a virtual idol i don't want to
spend too much time fixing it if i'm
just gonna it up worse so
we're just gonna go with it and it might
be totally off but that's fine
okay i'll spend more time next time i i
did get it
exactly on sync in my tests this time
but good goddamn
okay
trust me when i say this is not what
you're gonna expect at all
like holy so it's a virtual idol
group right
but it's also it's awesome
i'm laughing so hard just thinking about
this it's also
give me a second give me a second
it's gonna play the instrumental a bit
this is gonna spoil it but
okay my png is not working so we're
gonna have a static image we're gonna
have a static image
my png has been acting up today i can't
get it to work for the life of me like
goddammit
that's okay that's okay it's gonna be a
static image
ah and so you see
you see the next song
is from a boy band and i did not
want to sing it as i am i wanted to also
join the boy band
i wanted to also join the boy band so
here we go baby
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's hot man's time hot man hours over
here
my voice is really high but i'm going as
low as i can
it's about the best i can do
[Laughter]
i'm going to sing and greedy by care
brush a part of interlunium
i was gonna save this song for you by
song only karaoke
has the entire song is just innuendo and
in your face innuendo
i reached out to interlunium and i was
like hey can i sing this and then like
oh i'm okay
so i got permission to use it i'm so i'm
so happy
i'm so happy
so we're gonna sing it i gotta adjust
the song a few times though because i
have to use desktop audio for this one
for some reason the instrumental isn't
working in my program just let me check
that two things are set up and then i'll
get it going
give me a second
i think that should be good
okay okay okay okay okay the song is
gonna be very cursed coming from me
i don't care
okay give me a second
the timing might be absolutely
for this one
but we're gonna go with it oh and these
are my boy band
these are the other members of
interlunium i replaced one of them
okay here we go give me a second this is
gonna be the curse i never practiced
this one on purpose because this is
gonna be scuffed as hell and that's how
i want it
give me a second
[Applause]
when i see you i'm smitten don't need no
permission to pay you a visit on the
dance floor
i got tunnel vision i'm digging the
rhythm
i want more you're one in a million baby
i can feel it this kind of tension's an
act of war
but i'm not into loose and it's you that
i'm choosing someone that i just can't
ignore as
tempting as pandora
[Music]
don't be frightened by me take my hand
follow my lead feel that fire burning
inside you quell the flames or let the
heat guide you
your eyes gazing at me this surge of
electricity
swelling like a wave of temptation
drowning you
an endless sensation worry worry not
cause i'm with you
it's a world you're not used to but
[Music]
baby know that it's fine to be pretty
all of a sudden i'm the only one that
you're in love with we just begun but i
already got you feeling something
there's no running from it might as well
just submit to the music for the night
until the sun is coming
up now everybody wanna dance holding on
to you not letting go like it's my last
chance
you should know i think i'm bout to
catch a romance even if it's only for
the moment like icarus i'm falling
and now you've got me crawling forward
tonight yeah
yeah i for tonight yeah yeah
if
[Music]
don't turn your back on me take my hand
follow my ring sparks are flickering and
resounding can you
feel the storm that's surrounding us now
a breathing instant
vapor beating onto your skin boiling
blood it's rolling and steaming leaves
you scarlet
[Music]
had the forbidden food inside a rivery
baby no
baby when you're with me it's all right
to be greedy
to be
greeted baby when you're with me
it's all right to be greeting
[Music]
don't stop looking at me take my hand
and follow my lead
soaking through to your very being loves
the light that can be deceiving still
it's gonna erupt float's so hoarse i'm
bout to blow up
i feel my currents coursing within you
ended with
shock the dance we do worry worry not
cause i'm with you
it's a world we're not used to but i'm
down to continue
we can make something brand new hurry
hurry let it control you
now we've had the forbidden food inside
our paradise very new that it's fine to
be pretty
[Music]
know that it's fine to be greeting
yay you can't see me but i'm cheering
real hard right now
because i really wanted to sing this one
but i wasn't sure if i could pull it off
i'm a little i'm i'm a little more on
the waifu side
but sometimes sometimes even the best
wife who just wants
he wants to turn to be the best husbando
yeah
and yeah yeah yeah now his boy band pam
i hope you liked my mail form
i drew it myself
i got a little too excited and i got
carried away
i got really carried away it's fine
and it's totally fine it's totally fine
i just
i got carried away i'm gonna have to use
it again sometime because that was
that took so long and so long
i probably lost a lot of viewers i think
i probably scared some people away
but you know sometimes it's worth it to
just
be your own boy band if you can't
have a personal husband or harm you just
make your own
you just be your own husband though it's
fine
i forgot to add it to the list though
again
it's it's it's great it's the easiest
solution just be your own husbando
thank you fun crush for the super what
are these feelings coming over me
that is love for your new husband
i hope i hope i left everyone with some
very confused feelings
[Laughter]
okay okay
okay does mail camera pants go oh i have
to put it back so you can see
i need to confirm that i do not wear
pants because pants are unacceptable
um give me a sec i gotta erase myself so
you can see my mail form again
um no no
i have shorts i just hid my legs because
i didn't color them properly and the
color is bleeding and you weren't
supposed to see that
but no no pants only shorts only short
turns
i am the best husband i am the best
husband
i played enough with tommy games that i
know what makes a good husband
so i'm confident that i can be a good
husband
okay we got two songs left and they're
one of them is one that i really like
it's a youtuber song that has a very
anime feel that i really enjoy
and i think some of you can probably
guess it just based on that actually
i gotta get the words up give me a sec
goddamn i need a bathroom break but i
want to finish the last two songs first
mm-hmm
trying to get the lyrics okay
okay okay so the next song is by
piana and it was her first original song
i really enjoyed it i heard this one
before my debut and i got really excited
to debut because of it
i'm gonna sing but the instrument is a
piano arrangement and i'm gonna put a
link to the cover in the description
later because it's really really nice no
thank god there was no delay for the
husbando song
the hezbando song was perfect
it's the power of husbands it's the
power
of husbands okay we're going to think
[Music]
tell
fighting to the dark
song needs angry eyebrows because that's
the power of determination
[Music]
no
don't break
[Music]
foreign
i've been trying to find my destiny
but i keep
[Music]
could you tell me please
me
[Music]
i promise i will find you
i super appreciate that none of you
pointed out
my voice crack i was like glancing a
chat with oh they're all gonna
laugh at me
i guess the rest of the song was
mesmerizing enough that you didn't care
i like that song that's really nice i
heard this piano cover and i was like
damn
the only thing that can make kinotory
better is this beautiful piano cover
because i i just wanted to use this one
and i got permission from the person who
made it so i was like yeah
yeah yeah yeah anyway we got one more
and just one more karaoke song you can't
have
you can't sing a chiata song without
singing a song by someone else on the
right
i think some of you might figure out
what the next one is based on that
just give me one second oh my god i
think i left the desktop audio onto my
shoe
i hope you can still hear my voice loud
enough
anyway i need to sing a song by kiana's
other half now
my kiana's other half and angry angry
eyebrows stay on because it's more fun
oh yeah yeah yeah any guesses that i'm
going to sing from kiara's other half
i think it's pretty obvious so i'm just
going to put it there
does this make you a kfp employee no i'm
a kfp
sponsor i'm a kfp sponsor
i invest in kfp i'm too busy being a ceo
anyway we're gonna for the last song i'm
gonna sing
maury's debut song again because maury's
debut song
was like mint made me consider wanting
to be a youtuber
mint made me thinking wow this would be
really fun but mori's song is what like
finalize the deal
i heard maury's debut song they're like
that's cool i want to do this too
mate made mince was the one who gave me
the idea though
so if it wasn't for her i don't think i
would have even considered but maurice
debut song i was just like that is
unique that is fun
that really solidified the deal for me i
really look up to how mori's content is
still unique
so i want to sing i want to sing this i
hope one day future youtubers will be
like the song is called
virtual pleasure so there's one point oh
that'll be really sweet
no one has to though but if they want to
i mean like get the instrumental because
i want to put up a karaoke version
eventually
so maybe someday anyway i really gotta
have a bathroom work but i want to sing
this last song first so we're just gonna
we're just gonna go and find a weird
song is pretty fast i think we can do it
and then take a bathroom break
like i said don't pee muscles oh yeah
yeah yeah
here we go i don't remember how the
intro goes in which i
live again would be cool but there's no
instrumental like i need one where she
released the instrumental yeah
what i wanted to sing was off with their
heads i'll put their heads is my
favorite maury songs thing i love to
sing off with their heads
but i don't have an instrumental so it's
not happening right now maybe someday
anyway we're gonna just go
[Music]
on
human erasure can't stop the pace sir
make sure we're standing off my running
slate first jealous haters out there
high fives
no one's gonna fly this i believe
you kid is all hell in a little sense
but if these are i'll tell you they're
show dollars and cents you may not exist
between us like
along the lines so you reap what you
say so you gotta know ain't it
so could you let go of your soul for me
not ever much do me a favor
murder is
[Music]
eye opening taking words again
right off the cuff and script my own
thing where's
the clear set of those ask me can i take
a first class must have
a blast humans come at me actually
whatever that means guess whatever that
means come a little closer
then laugh at me if you take my advice
you'd be killed by what you know no
but inside i'm kind of nervous and i
don't know what the word is for the
other side of the gap say
so setting out do what i'm supposed to
do i'll get close to you don't mind die
just like if it's all right you
can i end your life
[Music]
human
me and mori are good friends because me
and my knife skills i bring her lots of
clients
i bring her lots of souls because i end
people
someday someday pam and mori collab
someday in the 100 year future
anyway i like i like seriously got to go
to the bathroom
i wasn't kidding so i'm going to put my
my one of my loading screens on briefly
while i go to the bathroom
or i'm going to pee myself and then
we're going to come back for some asmr
it's going to take me a minute to set up
so i'm going to grab my other mic
but i'll be back in the team i'll be
back in a few if anyone comes and asks
what's going on
please let them know in chat that i'll
be back very briefly okay okay
so
wow i still have that up
guys i made a mistake
i made a mistake
on the way back from the bathroom i
picked up
my apple to have a bite in my apple
and i dropped it
i dropped it on the floor
i don't have any more apple
so that means extra mouth noises for the
asmr
i hate mouth noises i don't know
if you guys like them or hate them but i
hate them
i'm just checking if i missed any supers
the whoop ham is not back this is normal
pack just
normal pam just quiet it's normal pam
but quiet
it's gonna be cursed asmr though because
i hate asmr
so i'm going to do asmr it's going to be
cursed only
is this an archive stream this this is
an archive stream
masano thank you for the super those are
lots of tears
i'm sorry cats cats thank you for the
super as well cats
if you see any cats you know what to do
if i see any cats sneak into the
warehouse
i'll tell them that you love them a lot
i'll tell them you love them a lot i'm
gonna have my alert noises off for the
asmr
because it's real quiet the volume
does that is the volume too loud or not
loud enough
i switched mics it's kind of hard to
tell
it's supposed to be kind of quiet i
cranked i'll crank it up
temporarily
give me a second
i cranked it up uncomfortably is that
better i cranked it up uncomfortably
i can't get up more
and then i'm gonna fix it because my
ears are bleeding
is that better i turned the music way
down so it's there but not
interfering anyway
if i have to read asmr and i
hate it um
i decided the most cursed thing i could
read
is uh fan fiction
that's really really popular a number of
years ago
it's um i got a green blanket just for
this video i got a green blanket just
for this video
can any of you guess what it might be oh
my god my blanket has a hole in it
oh my god my blanket
anyway um we can't have apple by asmr
because i dropped my apple on
the floor and i don't have an apple
anymore
and i'm really bitter about it so we got
to go the rest of the stream with no
apple
we'll see how long i can last without
anyway i want to cry a little bit
because i want my apple back
anyway i gotta get it up but um
give me like one sec give me like one
sec
okay i hate asmr so if we're
doing asmr
we're gonna read the check is love shark
is life
but only chapter one that's the full
story and
everything else doesn't actually matter
so we're gonna read it but we're gonna
read it exactly as
is exactly as is i'm gonna give the link
in case you want to read along
just in case you want to read along
i had to go away from the mic because
that was a loud laugh
okay here we go shrek walk into room at
no no i'm gonna wait
i'm gonna give it a bit longer because
where there's a delay i gotta make sure
you guys can click the link if you want
although i guess i guess it's fine
you'll have the link if you need it
okay i'm gonna get started okay shrek
walk into
room at night donkey there
hello no no hello
say donkey seductively
hi say shrek with a small smile
you were such a negoti boy
says donkey what the
are you doing you
ripley shrek
[Music]
find himself aroused by the moystertius
man in his room
okay say shrek oh wow warning this is
slightly 18 plus if you're not
forgot to live a warning but now i did
so if you're still watching it's your
fault not mine
okay don't get penetrate shekel full
force
beauty the say shrek in between
screams
yellow shrek at the wondrous donkey
clock
naked men lay on tick out
doing the frick frack diddly duck paddy
quarterback crackerjack bio feedback
back track thumbtack sidetrack tick tock
murderously
shrek feel his anus expand
with all the force low
donkey that was nice then
fiona walked in she screamed and yelled
at shrek what is
doing then she slip on sunglasses
well i ain't dealing w this
say fiona tipping her fedora
i've just been friend zoned
say fiona what
shrek adam donkey
god bye come licker say fiona
as she block out of the door shrek
and darkly look at each other
with lust in their sparkling eyes
let's freakol farak
and we sell they frictical fracked all
night long
like this if you cree ever team
that's what you get
i hope you enjoyed the asmr segment
i gave you everything you wanted
[Laughter]
i had to give back somehow because like
because like you guys all like the asmr
but i hate it
and the stream is to celebrate you guys
not me
so i had to did i miss any supers during
that i gotta check
i wasn't looking
okay i didn't if i did it would have
been your fault i don't think you want
your name on the stream during that
segment
okay that's that's gotta die now
no more asmr back to the loading screen
i die thank you forever me too my sanity
die
my pride is die my brain is die
[Laughter]
does the membership included weekly
remember only ace of mine no
no
maybe in the voice in the pan pack
someday there might be a short asmr
though i don't know
i mean the virtual pleasure acapella
sounds pretty asmr if i'm gonna be real
okay um i wanna
go back to normal and play some slither
i think we're probably gonna play for
like 20 to 30 minutes or so
but i gotta switch microphones again
because this one only works if i'm
really close to it and i like to
have my microphone really really far
away so it doesn't interfere with
tracking
so i'm gonna i'm gonna be right back
if someone writes fan fiction maybe so i
i
do want to do a spooky pam fiction
reading stream
and my discord a bunch of pam employees
wrote some very slick
horror based creepypasta type stuff i
think it would be fun
i think if an asmr boyle told me game i
mean
i would play an otome game in asmr voice
if it was the only way you guys let me
play it
i gotta spread the word with all my
games
you read all the protagonist lines and
narration asmr
maybe other members only experiment to
see how it goes
uh anyway i'm gonna switch microphones
because i wanna barf
i hate air support and knife can feel
how dry my mouth is with no apple so i
bet it sounds nasty
i have switched back give me a second
so
okay i had to change the volume on the
microphone back before i made your ears
bleed
okay now we're gonna play a bit of
slither i
have this thing already up let's give me
that
and you know she's excited for the
catboy game yeah i thought my pam please
were joking when they said there
was gonna be a male nickel platter but
apparently not
we're gonna play the cat boy game i
promised you guys many months ago when
it comes out and play the catboy game
and you think i'm gonna back out no i'm
playing the cat boy game
okay i'm just double checking hoping i
didn't miss anything in there okay
we're good we're good okay i'm gonna
play a bit of slither and i'm gonna turn
my alerts back on now
it's in this noise version let's go
you can try to find me in the game if
you want audio is low
hmm
i shouldn't be low
is that better i cranked it up a little
bit more
a little bit more i don't want to overdo
it
because it's been peeking a lot lately
and that's been making me really mad
is it okay now audio good audio good
i'll wait a second before i start
because it's going to be harder to edit
it while i'm in the game yeah
audio okay audio okay
just before i get into slither i want to
make sure
make sure no one's else is saying it's
low is it okay then
or do you mean the audio for the stream
in general is low because it is quite
low
it is quite low i'm you're good okay
okay okay we're gonna play i'm gonna be
obama
no you know
boss you can try to find me
no i feel like that's too too general
as you guys might want to try to find me
in the game somehow so
i don't think it's very nice if i use
boss because that's something a lot of
people might use
i'm bad at this game so
my goal is going to be
destroy one big snake
or worm or whatever i don't think i'm
gonna get
really far in the game i'm not gonna win
or anything but i want to destroy one
big snake
wreak havoc on someone
i'll ruin someone's day
okay here we go
[Music]
pam have you seen the end of mega lobox
season two not yet not yet i'm still
watching it i'm really behind on that
show to be honest
no spoilers please i'm really loving
season two
okay oh yeah oh my god my music's not
looping
i'm gonna i'm gonna just fix my music
sorry that was worth it i need my music
there we go now i got some looping music
now i got some looping music okay
i'm so bad at this
i just wanna ah get out of this area
when i'm very small and i can't play
tricks on anyone yet i like to get
off to the side oh boy oh boy
i have a lot of trouble controlling this
game too ah
i couldn't go and eat that but i feel
like everyone's trying to eat that
uh yummy yummy yummy
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy i gotta
destroy someone once i get big enough
oh yeah hello little baby i will spare
you you are little baby
i will spare the little baby
i spared a little baby
you it's okay
i want to change my skin after this i'm
boring
i gotta be more interesting yummy
yummy yummy
you guys are really quiet are you trying
to join the game
crazy
ah yeah it's not a big one like i wanted
but i'll take what i can get
no you don't no you don't
oh yeah trying to find me good luck
it really sucks that my map shows where
i am on the screen because you guys are
gonna come destroy me aren't you
if i know one thing about my employees
is that they like to destroy me so
you guys don't play very friendly
sometimes probably i'm not doing too too
bad but i'm going to die very soon i bet
that's fine
i took out a little guy this is round
one
i just gotta take out a little guy yeah
if i suddenly get surrounded i know you
made it in
holy holy that's a scary snake
i actually took out one that size when i
was practicing earlier
i saw his head and i just went for it
and i dove in front of his head and i
killed the heck out of it
oh my god i thought i killed it for a
second i was so proud
but i didn't it's fine i'm a little sad
i'm a little sad
i'm a little sad i wanted to wreck that
red guy that'd have been hilarious
[Music]
this isn't too too bad for my first run
is it the actual first one doesn't count
because i was actually just
experimenting and had to fix my music
oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah oh my god the baby's gonna kill
me isn't it
oh yummy yummy
i got greedy
that tends to be how i die in games okay
five seventy seven
five seventy seven let's see if i can
beat that today
i was doing okay i expected to do a lot
worse
that wasn't too bad though was it
i'm a bit of an aggressive player oh i
wait i didn't change my skin let's just
give some free food i want to change my
skin
all right okay here we go
the rainbow's kind of cool
oh i like the starry one kind of but
on fire change to play asia colors ooh
yeah that's a good idea
oh my god he's so happy that's so cute
and really terrifying
i like this one that's the one i killed
earlier
there's a big gigantic one like huge and
it was this kind and i just
killed it
and i laughed so hard
i'm trying to see if i can find
something play asia themed
if not i'll go with this one that blue
is also fitting right
black's clothes
let's see if i missed anything that's
blue and white oh there we go there we
go we can just lay
this one i'm gonna blaze this one
here we go
time to die this game is so scary
i hate the big ones that are predators
and just go after all the small ones
like you
go after the other big fellas go after
people your own size
don't ruin the fun of someone who just
started
i think 500 on my first try was good i
can settle even if i don't get better
than that today i think that's pretty
good
of course it's not leaderboard quality
but it's pretty good for me
you guys have seen my game skills also
while trying to read chat like goddamn
you guys have no idea how hard that is
it's good though it's good
i like interacting with chat it's just
hard
are you for me thank you tgn
super chat to replace the fallen apple
thank you i'll use it to buy another
apple
ashley i should probably start funding
my whale for ash fund as well
i need swimsuit ash also there's
swimsuit hilda and marianne as a duo set
my ship sent me ah oh crap i dropped my
wallet oh no
i got this money that you just gave me
do you need to borrow it if you dropped
your wallet do you need to borrow it so
you can send it back to me and sim
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
i spent way too much today at playasia
well i hope the free shipping helped
i forgot to show hashime buy hashihime
buy hashikim i'll show it after this
round it's eligible for free shipping
and i want people to buy it so that they
make more
and show it off after this round that
was my plan
but i forgot and i'm so mad at myself
bossy be played ai sonia files no i
haven't i own a physical copy i just
haven't gotten to it yet
but i know i'm going to really like it
[Music]
man i'm just leaving a baby hiding from
all the snakes
that's the secret you just hide in and
you do great
if they can't find you they can't eat
you
ah i was gonna try to him over but
i screwed up
okay i'm going to show hashikime real
quick i know that most of you don't even
want this but buy it anyway
so they're making a physical release of
a bl visual novel
but apparently even if you don't like bl
it's like a top tier story
and the art is just beautiful like the
art style is so unique
the art is so unique like look at the
colors
apparently the whole game just feels
like a trip to like there's whole
psychedelic scenes and stuff and i'm
just like whoa
i want this so bad i screamed when i
found out that we were selling
um get it i'm gonna get a copy it looks
really really cool
unless this weird frog what time
period
i'm not gonna say in case i got it wrong
but taisho taisho
taisho came to tokyo with the site set
on getting accepted to the imperial
university
however he doesn't pass the entrance
exam he's so undisciplined and wrapped
up in endless fantasies that he's kicked
out of his boarding house after only two
years
through a stroke of luck tama mori
begins to live and work
at umebachijo
a used bookstore there he enjoys
wheeling away his time as a student
preparing for entrance exams so taking
advantage of friends who are also
from his hometown but one right after
the other mysterious deaths
fought befall those friends and
realizing he's been repeating the same
raimi three days over and over again tom
amody finds himself racing throughout
jinbocho to scoop them in this pop
occult mystery that surrounds the death
of his friends
what is real and what is a hallucination
these scenes are the hallucinations
i'm so excited to play this like goddamn
will you play on stream
i want to i really want to
it depends how many of you would run
away and never look at me again if i
play this on stream but oh
god damn i want to it's beautiful
at least the first part of it at least
the first part of it so that i can like
yeah murder mystery bl it is a murder
mystery bl
honestly this is gonna be contrary to
what you guys might think but honestly
i'm kind of more excited about the
murder mystery than i am about the bl
because murder mystery is like my love
but i'm excited
about both
it just looks so good it looks so good
i'm getting physical for sure
[Music]
okay i want i'm glad at least one of you
want it
same i'm glad two of you want it
it's the type of game i feel like my pam
plays might not enjoy but i'm very happy
to know otherwise
maybe i can play it on stream then
i definitely want to i definitely want
to
sounds like a good murder mystery right
i know i'm playing some more i love how
one of the
leaderboard people is milf master
loser
oh yeah
[Music]
i want to sell lots and lots of copies
so that more of
physical copies of games like that get
me i watch and play along nice
nice that makes me happy it makes me
happy
i really want to play some automate
games eventually too i'm playing through
pio fiore right now and i'm absolutely
loving it like god damn it's incredible
maybe i'll do like
a short stream of it one time testing
the waters member only or something to
see if people like it
like a half an hour i don't know weekly
member stream where i just read otome
games
storytell story time style to see what
people think
if there's a love story and it's good i
couldn't care less it's bldl or straight
same
same i just like good love stories i
don't give a care good characters i ship
everything anyway
just give me a good story and i'm sold
but i'm excited that it is a bl physical
game just because we don't oh
we don't really get those like ah yeah
yeah
yeah baby take that little snake
but i feel like the story looks so good
in that game that like even if you're
not into bl it looks like a game you
might actually enjoy if you like murder
mysteries
like from what i've heard the story
alone is worth playing for
and i think there's like an 18 plus
version and an and um
you can turn it off if you're not into
the 18 plus stuff but you still want to
play it
so it kind of has a way to play it for
everyone
i don't know which switch has though it
might only be 18 plus i don't know
aye aye had to stop playing pio fiore
temporarily though because um
ah my mouse froze oh but i killed it's
fine
it's fine um i had to stop playing
temporarily because it got really
gruesome at one part like someone shoved
a knife under someone's fingernails and
twisted it
and as much oh is that duck this is the
dock i wonder if that's stuck
they abandoned me so i don't think it's
stuck it's um
it's um yeah i i i like horror
but i i draw a line at fingernails i had
a little trouble with the karachi
because of that too
i think your nails are kind of yucky
and that's my husband too he's torturing
someone and i was like uh
i started playing again just a little
more slowly
i only play it like half an hour a week
or so because i'm also playing famicom
detective club in like a billion other
games
so sometimes i don't always play it very
fast i mean you're nice just be all and
i loved it yeah yeah yeah
that was so good yuri on ice was so well
done that like
it doesn't matter if you're into bl or
not it's just a good story ah
your little my mouse
froze and i ran into it you little
2015.
we got almost double last time i got
killed by a
baby i got healed by a baby what the
yeah that scene higurashi messed me up a
little bit
i was like look
all i'm gonna say is i'd rather re-watch
i would rather
re-watch the fingernail scene and then
re-watch the intestines scene
in the new one the intestine scene was
too much for pam
too much for pam because what i really
like about higurashi
is um what i really enjoy from higurashi
is the psychological horror
and i felt the new season for a couple
episodes just got too gratuitous with
the
gore it was like it was so much gore i
didn't enjoy it anymore
it came around a bit near the end but
there was a part in the middle that was
just like
ew i'm not getting scared i'm just
disgusted
i want to be scared not disgusted
okay let's try again
maybe we can do another stream later
where we play more slither i don't know
i thought it'd be a fun game to chill a
little bit today i don't think i've seen
any of you guys in it though i don't
think you guys are able to find it it
just kind of sucks
that's okay another time maybe we can
figure it out
oh huckle okay okay i played hakuoki i
really like saito he's my favorite
i thought that my favorite was going to
be kazama because his voice is really
hot
he still has my favorite voice but saito
won my heart for sure what i like to do
when i play otome games is actually make
the decisions i would make if it was
really me
and then see who i end up with because
i'm like oh that would be my real
husband in this universe
instead of being someone who plays every
root i like to play them once and make a
decision as if it was me
but of course i'll go back to it and
play again if i get a dead end or
something and i die
because that's not a ending oh
i can't get it i can't get it oh my god
oh my god
just let me i want the glowy
i knew where do i clock in you just type
in chat
you're good that is clocked in i yeah
i didn't get involved i didn't get them
you can only join when we know your
personal ip oh sorry
you can try to find it you might end up
in the same server
you might not you can try
you can i know you can wow what the
that's the biggest one i've ever seen in
my life
almost said that's what she said that i
managed to resist
that's what you get
i know you can get a list of these
surfers though and you can try to join
that way
you can get a list of the servers online
and hop between them and try to find it
oh yeah yeah give me the glowy give me
the
give me the glowy
um if your face runs into someone else's
body
you die so basically if i get someone to
shove their face in my butt
then i live and they die
[Music]
um
i almost got him he's too good
it's too good
ah purple glowy i like the really glowy
glowys i like the really glowing colors
we're good we're good
yeah if you're gonna play in otome you
might as well get a husband otherwise
what are you even doing
someone should make an otome game and
put hus pando in it
so i can date myself
i didn't say my goal was to kill a big
one
ah
i didn't do it but
um
oh yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
and that was close
this game is very chill until it's not
i never played the girl dating games
though still atomi um those are usually
called these jojo games but some autumn
may have
um options where you could date the men
or women characters usually indie games
like western indie
otome games i find are better for that
but um
yeah i killed i killed iq
iq but there's also a number of japanese
ones
like my favorite ones that i make you
grim you can date rapunzel
but she's just a wee but that doesn't
want to leave her tower because it has
snacks and video games
she's pretty good i think there's
another one that you can date another
princess i can't remember which one it
is though
nah miss don't you dare
uh uh yeah i'm doing okay
i'm doing okay i've only played katawa
shojo i haven't played that one but i've
heard it's amazing
i kind of actually meant to a long time
ago i just didn't get around to it
don't you dare
yeah yummy yeah
i'll kill you i'll kill you don't you
dare
piggy
i almost got killed by a pig
yeah that's what i've heard about katawa
shoujo it's like really really good
inclusion ah
i love some socially like good games i
don't know the word for what i wanted
but i know what i wanted to say
do allusion soft games count as romance
games well it depends on the game and
how you play it
yummy yummy yummy
yummy yummy yummy i think it's gonna be
my strongest fun
i just killed a baby pam why are
you so ruthless and heartless
because i am
i eat baby snakes for breakfast
oh yeah
i'm doing pretty good i think i'm on the
edge of the map though i don't want to
go any further
snick
oh yeah anyone heard of dream daddy oh
i've heard of dream daddy
i haven't played it though somehow
i know most of my friends have played
dream daddy
i feel like that could have oh man i
should have streamed what the i
should have streamed dream daddy on
father's day
oh my god i'm stupid what a prime
opportunity missed
what a prime opportunity missed damn it
there's always next year i suppose
ah
i wanna kill the pink one
a lot of other people it looks like are
trying to kill the pink one too
oh no you don't oh no you don't
oh no you don't what the okay
oh yes you do i can't get i can't get
that way around it that's okay
yum yum yum yum i think the pink one
died it wasn't me though so that's kind
of tragic
oh the kfc dating game is good i did
play that one
i kind of want to stream it on like
christmas eve or something while eating
a bucket at chicken
it would be nice if i could stream that
one as a collab get some people to voice
it for me or
enough for with me get someone to do
each character i kind of want dibs on
colonel sanders
oh
oh rainbow giants
yummy
[Music]
oh man bernie sanders is in this game
you guys think it's the real one
it's so laggy i know the leg is making
it really hard for me honestly i want to
cry
it's not too too bad for me but it's
enough that it's like really upsetting
me
like every once in a while it just
glitches a few frames ahead and it's
enough to really mess me up
yay
i hit the back button i hit the back
button i hit the back button
i was so big
there's a shortcut on my mouse and i hit
it by accident
excuse me while i internally scream
no pain pain pomo pain camel
rally was over 1600 nice
let me try one more time that was gonna
be the last one but um
yeah i'm not letting it end like that so
i'm gonna have one more good round if i
have
a bunch of shitty rounds i'll keep going
but i have one more good one
yeah that was definitely a bad end
god something so aggressive you're
one-eyed freak
no no that's what you get for trying to
kill me
that's what you get i
eyeball man oh my god it's lagging so
bad right now
holy that was terrifying ah
see that round sucked we're doing it
again
have a drink first
i want at least one more round with over
500 yeah
and it's really hard to play this game
with the mouse
when my mouse space is only six by six
inches
[Music]
don't kill me i'm just babble i'm just
bamboo
i'm just babble
i'm just battle
what the usually the edges of the
map are very very
relaxed this is a very hostile
environment
okay
okay okay ah
that's what you get yum yum
oh yummy
yummy yummy
oh this a fire emblem is a good one
especially three houses i bought three
houses just to date the characters i'm
not even ashamed
to say it i ended up coming to enjoy the
gameplay but i think
everyone knows the real reason i bought
it was the date ash
ah oh my god
messiah at least one of you got in
you're not allowed to kill me i'm out of
here i'm out of here this is my last run
don't make me shrink don't kill me it's
my last run man
i run away from you i run away from you
yummy
now i know how kiara felt when her fans
sanana murdered her
yeah oh my god this guy's huge
i kind of want to find the head just
follow in its wake
no one wants to be near its tail i'll
steal all its poop
[Music]
i guess missandro's gonna steal his poop
then fine i'll go steal someone else's
poop
yummy yummy ah
ah yeah
yummy yummy i sure do love eating
because i'm a little wormy worm snake
sparkly too
oh yeah oh red one
oh man i got into the aggressive corner
i got into the aggressive corner
oh get out of there that's a scary place
that's a scary place
i was kind of mad that anna wasn't
marriageable in three houses if i'm
gonna be real
anna's pretty great
she likes money i think we could get
along pretty well
oh yeah this is a scary area
oh wow
[Music]
smooth criminal i feel like there's a
chance that could be one of you guys
actually
a sanro looking a little small there
buddy
looking a little small there buddy i
killed a big one i killed a big one i
did it my one stream goal
i did it i did it
oh yeah yeah oh yeah
oh yeah yeah this is gonna be the last
one so i'm doing decent again
whenever i die it's over
but if you guys are enjoying slither
maybe we can play sluther again during
some number streams
ah but i killed one big
that was my goal i killed one big
i don't have to kill one of the biggest
ones but that's okay
yummy yummy yummy i never played three
houses
highly recommend i actually didn't
intend on playing it if i'm gonna be
real
um someone bought a copy and i asked if
i could watch them play it so i could
make fun of the game and oops it became
one of my favorite games
i ended up not making fun of it
i ended up wanting it a lot and then it
took over my life
i got like 200 hours in that thing uh
so hard to control because sometimes i'm
moving a direction but it's like
it doesn't move in time it's a little
bit slow just a few frames
but enough frames that it makes it
really awful
i guess there's about like basically
yummy it's i think that's why it's such
a frustrating game
the lag is real oh yummy
ah oh james i found you
there's no way you'd hurt me right i can
fire you you know
[Music]
i can't really compare three houses to
awakening i literally only played three
houses because the characters were hot i
didn't play together
i might have to look into them though
because chrome is also pretty hot
i almost bought the chrome amiibo just
because it was hot
oh yeah
i'm eating so much poop
come as a himba yeah that's why he's
perfect
that's why he's perfect
if you disagree that promise krom is
perfect you're fired
oh yeah
yeah i think we're doing pretty okay
this time i'm satisfied if i die
whenever
i'd rather not obviously but i can
accept
that i've made it this far and perhaps
i'm not meant to make it any further i
can accept
i can accept that it's my it's just my
time
when it happens
[Music]
i want to kill but i want to kill not
aggressive snakes
yummy
and that was a possibly deadly snack
i'll see if i can get this guy
oh he's dead
okay that was a little scary for a while
there
it's just a little scary for a while
come on come on baby
you can do it you can do a pam oh no you
can't do it oh god it's trapping you get
out of there pam get out of there
i backspaced
oh my god i can't accept the backspace
is the last one so we're going again
we're going again
i know i was about to die anyway but i
didn't even get my number
so hold on hold on
i'm gonna run into one for a sec my
wrist is really sore i'm gonna get my
brace on
i don't wanna hurt myself just let me
run into you there
oh my god oh my crap on my desk
i feel like i'd have an easier time if i
use my braces
i'm hoping my brace will also prevent me
from clicking that one
because my finger is starting to twitch
and it's hitting buttons when i don't
want it to
i'm hoping with the brace the nerves
won't be so like
messed up i don't know i find sometimes
if my fingers start getting all twitchy
the brace helps
okay let's see let's see
this will be the last one for real
as long as it's over 500
oh wow whoa the leg there was real bad
yummy yummy
oh gummy oh yeah
get that good energy and get that good
energy
you're no longer baboo you're no longer
baboon oh yes iron blue warriors is
pretty dope i like that one
that was another fire emblem game i play
i didn't play very much of it though i'm
gonna admit
but i enjoyed what i did play
i want them to make an update with three
houses characters and warriors
i could try using keyboard but i feel
like i might have an even harder time if
i use keyboard
oh jesus
he can't count me if i'm near his butt
you can't go backwards
yummy yummy yummy yeah
yummy i'm not going back for that it's
too risky
oh god that one's so scary i think that
blue one's trying to wrap around the
whole map
i'm missonro no this is my last round do
you really want to kill me
already in my last round i don't think
so buddy
i don't think so buddy i'm out of here
i'm out of here
[Music]
oh god oh god oh god i think i got
caught in a trap oh god oh god oh god
oh god oh god i didn't
it wasn't over 500 so i get to keep
going
kill this on real time
no you don't you
ah now i'm just really terrible so
are you again because that one's just
really bad
yummy
[Music]
uh
oh my god that one's so scary
yum yum yum yum
that was close ah
how did i survive that lag man
yummy ah
oh that was terrible
yummy oh no we're not even gonna try
yummy
yummy oh
ah this is going to go around his own
body i can't get him
i think i'm more risk to myself if i try
to catch him
he's smart once you're big enough to
wrap around yourself it's really hard
for people to kill you it's kind of
cheap
[Music]
scary green boy that one's shrek the
snake
i got dumped by donkey so he's really
sad and he's doing uh
um i'm eating everyone in his path
revenge rampage
yummy oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
i killed a big boy i killed a big boy
can i kill a second big boy nah
can i kill this one oh god no i can't
this is really scary i'm not gonna
try that
yeah the brace is really helping me not
have my finger over
or twitching on the button so if i die
this time it'll be a death not a
backspace i'm pretty confident
[Music]
oh
don't you dare don't you dare
oh yeah yeah i'm nice and long now
[Music]
oh yeah
i'm getting decent this time
i haven't seen any snakes in a while
though oh there's some snakes
part of me was like am i alone in this
game
that would have been weird
hey bubbles i used to be bubbles like
you
one day you'll grow to be nice and long
like me
i probably should try to encircle more
snakes huh
oh yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy and no
one's here to try to steal it from me
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
can i kill this guy now he's gonna go
over his own body okay
i wondered oh
oh no he's too long
too intimidating this american's really
[Music]
long
it kind of is like snake game on phones
you see used to but i think you can
probably still get i can't even get this
one on foams probably
oh yeah this is a pretty solid blaster
and i'm content with this
i'm just going to follow this red trail
yummy yummy
yummy
where am i i'm somewhere on the
map what is that
i thought this was melodic and i was
like oh you got in too
i was gonna kill you congrats it's over
3k thank you
thank you
[Music]
another tokyo mirage sessions can the
new tokyo mirage sessions have the three
houses characters but like
future that would be incredible
hilda's got to be an idol of course
mercedes i feel like would be one of
those like psychics
ash would just be a good boy maybe he'd
work at a pet store
selling supplies for cute pups
i'm doing okay i will kill you no you
won't
what a name yeah i've heard the gameplay
in tokyo mirage sessions is really good
i've never actually played it but i've
watched someone play quite a bit of it
i still find it weird oh i got
killed by aqua
i was 1497.
that's not so bad that's not so bad
i think that's pretty good that's gonna
be it though
that's a pretty solid number it's it's
hard to get very far in this game while
looking at chat and everything so i'll
take what i can get
i want it over 500 this is over 500
this is acceptable
okay that's it
we're gonna sit here for a little bit
but that's it
why say music so quiet
let's crank it up i hope
you guys enjoyed the membership
celebration even though on youtube
up the membership
so they're not here yet don't worry they
will be
they should be here in like less than 12
hours i think at this point
so don't worry you'll be able to join
membership soon if that's what you're
interested in
and if you missed what the perks were
don't worry you can go watch the vod
near the beginning i explained what the
perks are
there's some cool stuff including pan
packs which has voice files and
wallpapers and stuff
i think it's gonna be great yeah yeah i
only encountered boss once and
accidentally crashed into her that's
what you get
that's what you get for questioning me
too many times
i hope you guys enjoyed the super chat
celebration mostly because membership
didn't quite happen did it
we got to do some good karaoke
do some cool merch announcements yeah
play on march if you weren't here
there's stickers a mini case and paper
pans and they're all really really great
so you want to check them out on the
website you can just search ibakipam on
playasia.com and you'll find the merch
it's exciting i claimed victory over
bosswood victory i didn't see it if i
didn't oh yeah it's not real you get
that much oh yeah thank you y'all tired
thanks for the stream boss you're
welcome
thanks for the super yeah yeah baby
okay so we got um
we got that golden um i forget what i
say
and we got yeah the merch the merch i'm
a free shipping event so you can get my
merch with free shipping
and buy some games with it and stuff
boss i can't wait for you to release the
royalty-free version of yeah
yeah i'm gonna put a preview on twitter
of the virtual pleasure piano
sometime tomorrow and it actually has a
nobuo face reveal
and so if you're curious nobuo face
reveal is gonna be on twitter tomorrow
it's gonna be a royalty free version but
the full version will be on youtube
tomorrow evening at my normal stream
time 8 p.m est yeah
on the schedule but i'm gonna schedule
it shortly after this actually
and um in the pan pack you'll get the
acapella of the original virtual
pleasure and you get the instrumental of
the piano one
if you sign up for the employee plus
tier
but in the meantime i'm gonna go
in a minute um yeah saturday
saturday's stream we're going to be
doing pam news so i'm going to be
talking about just like some recent news
and highlights and stuff
and yeah that's going to be interesting
i think show off some stuff
it's going to be interesting and then
on later on on saturday a couple hours
later i'm gonna be doing a members only
stream
so even if you couldn't join today if
you want to join in on the members only
stream
and play some games with me i haven't
decided yet we'll probably use the
number discord to decide on a game
i'm kind of leaning towards maybe gardic
phone or something though
just something kind of like that's
accessible to a lot of people
um yeah yeah yeah so we'll figure that
out later
and it's probably going to be i don't
know we'll figure that out
that'll be a good day i think the two
streams on saturday
for now though i'm gonna peace out i'm
just checking one thing before i
go before i go
go okay yeah i think i'm good
i think i'm good i'm gonna peace out now
because i'm tired
after all that i'm a little bit tired
but yeah yeah yeah
thank you guys so much for showing up to
the celebration
and for the supers and remember don't
feel bad if you can't super
because you can always you can always
join the discord oh my god my eyebrows
you can always join the discord there's
a link in the description actually you
know what
i have the pop-up chat so i can i can
trigger some buttons um
if you're not in the discord it's a play
asia discord but there's a pan chat
section
where you can talk and we always talk
about stuff there
and you can also follow me on twitter to
get nobuo's face review
and yeah yeah yeah if you like or share
the video too
um like the stream or any of my other
stuff it's also really really helpful
it's like liking and share subscribe if
you haven't already
honestly that's like also very very nice
and it helps a lot i really
appreciate it but for now i'm gonna
peace out
so i have a very long ending section for
today's stream
because i wanted to highlight a bunch
a butt load of the fan art so far
so i actually have to cycle through a
few slideshows it was too many to go in
one
ah i'm ready thank you
oh yeah thank you john john duck for
sharing the free shipping as well so
people can get more info on that
i'm going to go though the chat's still
going to save but it's not going to show
up in the stream and neither will the
alerts
but um i'm going to put the ending
screen on now so you can see all the fan
art so far
as a celebration yeah yeah let's go
[Music]
do
i put the wrong slideshow and it had
some weird in there
let me and let me just let me just i
just switch that give me he's like
[Music]
do
to
[Music]
now
do
[Music]
now
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you