[Music]
[Music] I'm
Iris. Thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you.
[Music] There's
a bit of lag.  Yes, I had a very
touching experience with my brother, so it
's a secret that happened today. I
don't want to die, but I'll
continue.
[Music]
Hello everyone, good evening. I
'm Kihara Takanashi from Hololive English.
[Music] I
have experience with this game.  However, I
'm nervous because it has never been imported during the distribution, so please
help me out.This
game has a bit of a map and it
can't be helped in a game with lamps, so I
think it will definitely happen.It
has to be included.  Are you
talking even though your voice doesn't come in?
[Music]
While I'm making this, everyone please introduce yourself
Paradise
[Music]
I'll do my best
[Laughter]
[Music]
What are you doing today?
Thank you very much for your kindness.
[Music] As
someone who has played in Japan, I hope that I can
ask everyone about things they don't understand
[  [Music]
Thank you in advance. Thank you in advance.
I'm
Hololab Awakening back button today. It looks like I'll be able to
talk a lot with everyone, so I
'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
[Music] I'm from
Gamers Shirakami. Today is
Eh, this Armon training camp.  I'm definitely going to go crew bait
with that Hakos cheese on my head.Thank
you very much.Thank
you very much.  I'm
really excited, but
please do your best. I'll try my best to use both English and Japanese.
By the way, I can't speak English.
Thank you very much. My
face is liver liver
face. Fifth Stars Yukihara Rummy Hey
[Music]
Just saying yes.  There may
be some trouble, but please stay warm until now.
Thank you very much for
your continued support. Big trouble tends to occur, so I
feel like I should do the weather in the cat's room once.
So let's do it at high speed.  So, if
I call you, please say yes.
Yes, those who couldn't hear you, please say you didn't hear me. Yes,
yes. When you get closer, the voice gets louder, and when you move away, it gets smaller.
Right.
[Music] My
name is Top Shaxx.
But, I'm Comet Hoshimatsu.
Thank you very much.
[Applause] Can you hear me? Yes
, yes, yes. Yes, I
'm the white team. Yes, I can hear you.
Yes, it's Paradise.
[Music] I
can hear you, yes.
[Applause] I
can hear you. Can you hear me?
[Laughter]
[Music]
There's a bit of a lag, so please wait a moment.
Aoi
[Music] Lee, I can
hear you.
Can you hear me?
[Music]
Just like before, it
only sounds very tinny. But, I'm asking you to continue as normal.
Maybe it would be better if we talked over Discord instead of normal.  That's what I was thinking.
Well then,
please. Now, I think it's ok to mute Iris
[Music]
first.
So let's move on. Okay, let's go like that.
Let's go ahead.  [
Music]
[Music]
Senpai
Oh,
I've never done it either. That's
right.
[Music]
Wait a minute.
[Music] Do you want to
continue? Okay, then here.  OK, do you want to
continue?
Yes, Is this a meeting?
Yes, I saw Ramy Ramy's dead body, and the
senior Elite Meco-senpai was
really jumping into the lunch box.
[Applause] It
was love
[Music] [
Laughter]
Huh?
[  [Music] I
can't help but feel like I saw that person for a moment, but I
wonder who that person I was walking with earlier was. Was it Aki-senpai? Was it Fubuki-senpai from Axis? I think it was somewhere around there, but she wasn't there with me.  I was the only one who saw the
corpse. I didn't see anything. I was so
moved by being able to talk that I didn't look at anything.
[Laughs] I
guess I was nervous. Let's do it.
[Laughs] It's a
test play.
[Music]
Mito-senpai, my junior over there is lying.
Are you really saying that?
[Laughs] He
only tells the truth, right? There's nothing he can
say back. I'm
sorry.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Who are your friends?
[Music] I
won't kill you.  Please,
please don't kill me
[Music]
Definitely,
that cheese, that cheese. Well, my new
member Bales-chan
wants to eat it, but
wait, it's dark.
[Music] I
can't hear you, I can't
hear
you
.  [Music] It's a
voice next to me. I
can hear it. I
wonder if it's a voice. Hello, hello.
In front of the door, Paradise is standing in front of me and
telling everyone to follow me, so everyone is following me.
What the heck is going on around the entrance to the office?
It's the admin or something near the entrance to the
Green House.  I was
doing the entrance task for Paradise, and there was a
power outage, so I went to fix my retirement, and when I
went to check on it, it was dead. Is this
Aiai Balbaru
Button? It's
Barebare Button.
[Laughs]
Even before that.  That's it.
I couldn't hear Corone-senpai's voice anymore.
Hmm, where was I? I was in my management office.
Oh no, seriously, seriously, right before that,
Suisei-senpai and Corone-senpai were also there. So,
I was there in the office.
I could already see that Swiss-senpai had gone, so I
went to the control room. I thought that the lights would be turned on anyway,
but there
was also a possibility that it was a selfie. You
know, I can hear that voice this time. I'm going to kill that one, right?
Korone.
Corona-senpai couldn't hear Corona-senpai's next line when he was talking about that. He
killed her from below, right? So, it's
strange that Tsui-chan said that line when Sui-chan and I were out of power.  I
was with you. I was with Sui-chan. That's why I was there. There
was a power outage. Oh no. Because I was inside.
If you came later, I'd understand, but you came first, so it's
probably not true, but look.  I haven't seen it, but I
haven't seen it either, but I wonder if
Sui-chan will say the line when it comes to which one of them is.
[Music]
That's right. I want you to listen to me. I
want you to listen to me.  But you
know, there's something I want you to hear
from me.I've been hearing the voice of the ghost of Miko Senpai for a long time now.I'm so
worried that I
can't talk anymore.
[Music] I
want to do something with my brother.
[Music] It's okay to
do it twice, once, twice, and then
switch to the normal mode, so it's ok
because the big brother will come back in the middle.
[Music] I'm
sorry I can see it, but it's a little bit
in the picture.  It's okay, I'm fine.
No one's going to come in like that
.
[Music] It's like we're
all here. Let's
find out.
[Laughter]
[Music]
What should I do? Air syrup, no, that's
not true [Music]  [
Music] Something
like that
[Music]
Please
Thank you, thank you, OkOk
[Music] I think something
like 60 is fine.The
default one is the first OKOK.I
might be able to do it here or there.I'm
used to it.  Let's do
it. Name of the country. Yeah, it's North America, but I want to get it in. [Laughter] I've got this one in. [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music] Stop it, stop it so I can eat you.
Stop it, stop it, stop it [
laughter] It's
going to turn into a childbirth lunch box
[music]
Or maybe
Paradise was
there too
[music]
[laughing]
[music] I
'm in the Communications room
[music]
[laughing] Right
now, I'm
going to do that task at Electrical.  Then I met Daffodil-senpai, who was the
type of person who felt like standing there all alone,
and we talked for a bit and then left again.That's when I
found Electrical.Actually,
I
went counterclockwise from the cafeteria to Electrical,
but in the meantime...  I
didn't see anyone.
Everyone was on the right.
So
when I went to Electrical, as Tiara said earlier, I
think it was because Tiara came in.
From the cafeteria, I went to the administration first, and
from the administration, I went to the electrical.  I
see.
But that's it, right? From the cafeteria, the
admin must have gone down and met someone from Electrical.
Because we
went to Adbin.
What's the timing?
[Music]
[  [Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Well, it's like Electrica and it's fine. I was
screaming at my place too. No
one said anything. Yes, I
found Noel.  In terms of timing, there
is a possibility that Mr. Button pressed the button to erase the sketch, which
is not correct, but now the
electric was dead.
Yeah, that's right, that's right.
So in terms of timing, the timing when he found it
and the timing when he pressed it
was that.  But that's what
happened just now.
[Music]
On the
contrary, on the contrary, no one has done it yet.
Schiffer Noel-senpai, I
think me and Fubu-chan stopped it. Yeah, I stopped it, I stopped it.
On the other hand, there are
people who haven't stopped the oxygen.  No one,
when I tried to go across from Lamy, it was over.
Yeah, it ended right in front of me,
so what are you doing? I made you do it. So I really had the same timing, so
now... [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] I
went to the shield room, but
there were two events going on, so I
thought this was definitely going to happen, so
while I was heading from the shield room to the storage room.  That board, and
if that's the case, I'll be standing between the storage rooms, right
in front of the communications bean.There's no
storage space.I'm
Japanese.DiscussionThe
last time I met with my senior was in the shield room, in the front and in the
back.  The one that
Fubuki-senpai put in the wrong lunch box once.
Do you know? It's over there. I wonder if it's
Senpai.
[Music]
What's going on?
Hey,
Button-senpai [
Applause] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Laughs]
No, no, no. I was
running and asking if anyone was there, and the
first thing that
came to me was Iris, so I killed her.
[Laughs] I
should have done that. [
Music]
[Music]  ]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Hello Akorone-senpai,
can I shake your hand? No, no, you
can believe in me. It's
far away.
Hello Christmas tree Sears.
[Music]
[Music  ]
What is that Christmas day? This
is a Christmas tree. I
saw the body.
Yuki and Senpai and I
went into Denki Rare and there were both bodies.
[Music]
I was the last one to be Elite Mikoto.  I saw it on the set of ``Yeah,
Electrical.'' Well, there
was another Runramy here.
[Music] I
think another person came in after that.
Wait, Discord now.  I think Miko-senpai
was translating that deep voice in English with the Japanese army for that older brother,
but after this, she said, ``I want to
do something with a demon,'' and then I want to do something real in English.  I
wonder if it's a dub kill of Iris and Paradise, but when I find it, the only people I
find are me, Paradise, and
Tiara.  Kira was there like a tiara,
and I saw three people, and there were two.
[Music]
[Laughter] I'm
going with just one vote, right?
My
Spoo
[Music]  ]
[Laughs]
So many things are being exposed, no, no, it's so cute, so, so, so, so, such a
reversal, a
lie, so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so soSo soSo soSo soSo soconstandingvinsssssssstanding" I saw that things
just.
Sui-chan was lying on the side of the road.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] Do you
have an explanation?
Just say it back to me.
Even if you were to say it back to me, I
guess you were just trying to get to the first birth room.
[Laughter]
In the oxygen robe.  He was about to go. He
came from the oxygen room.
No, he didn't come. He didn't come. He
didn't come.
But the
archive is the proof.
[Laughs]
Yeah, I don't know now, but
...
[Music]
This is still that.
Bad timing.
[Laughter]
-
[Music] I
can't hear you, Kanami-chan's heavenly voice. I
can hear voices at different volumes right now.
Who is the other impostor who is living at different volumes now?  I
think there were probably a lot of two-person actions, like
double kills,
etc. In that sense, I think Ramy-chan is a little
suspicious to me...
[Music]
Could you please change it up a bit
?
[Music]
[  [Applause]
[Music] This
is Iris.
Can you hear me?
[Music]
[Laughter] That's
so much fun.
[Music]
[Laughter]
OK.
[Laughter]  ]
[Music]
Everyone has finally
broken. It
's a virus. It's a virus. It
's the same map. [Music] It's like a vtuber. It
's true
.
[Music] -
Please
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
By the way, I'll try it again.
I'd say it's a poster, but it's a little boring.
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] I
saw them doing something in the boiler room near the water
[Music]
I  When I hit the boiler,
Fubuki-senpai came from above.The
security staff
told me that I had killed him.
[Music]
At first, I was alone with Senpai.
So, this one, I thought that if that happened to Senpai, he would die,
but he wasn't killed, so I have
a little faith in him.
[Music] I
don't know, but I guess I can
see. When I
looked at that, two people were dead, and I
said if I didn't let it go, I might wear a double coat.
When I went to the management room, Tsui-chan was there.
There was someone there.
[Music]
[Music] I
saw it. I
saw it. I saw it.
Ah, OK.
YES
OhYeah OHame.
Oh, OK. Senpai. Let's do it.
Water-senpai.
Joint.
[Music]
[Music] Hey,
uh, where's the dungeon?  I found it,
but
Olly-chan
was dead in the weapon room right after exiting the boiler room, or right after exiting on the right side, but
Fubuki-senpai and Alice-chan, who are very suspicious of the captain,
try a little practice
and the first thing that happens is the
moon.  There was some repair work to be done
that month, so I went to the electrical room electrical for repairs, and
Fubuki-senpai and Iris-chan were there, but
Iris-chan was there too, and there were a lot of other people there,
too, and there was a
blank space above Boilash.  There was some
work to be done there, so I went there and
then Fubuki-senpai and Iris-chan
came. I thought they were there, but they
were out at Boilush, so they
weren't there.  That's why I was working alone,
and those two people
probably did it after they had done it, and then they came back up after they had already done it, and they were
different, right?So, if they
passed each other and looked at each other, it would
probably be the leader.I couldn't kill them.  I
guess that's because that time was a cool-down period, and I think it's like you're not there anymore, right? No,
you were working on your tasks in the boiler room, and then they sent you that fire
from above together.  When I came with my brothers, I was
just heading in the direction of Uemoto.
Yeah, that's why it's strange to testify to that. Eh,
who's there?
Noel
isn't in there. I
went on the left side and saw her boobs.
[Music]
Oh, hello.
[Music] I
think so, but if you're feeling a little scared, I
think you can just wait and see what happens, Iris-chan. I'm sure there's a cat watching somewhere, surrounded by a fence.
[Music]
I still have one emergency left, so
yeah.  Well, you can
put it in and
make it sound, but if you
do that and it causes a power outage, I
think a roller would be fine, but I also
think it's fine
[Music],
but I
don't think it's fine either.  I guess I'll put it in there. Let's go on an
adventure.
Okay.
[Music] It's supposed to end. You're supposed to end it. That's it. [Applause.] I'm sorry. [Music] I
thought you were gone somewhere. I
lost sight of you.
[Laughter]
[Music]
This is it.  What's going on with the kill cooldown?
27.5 Yes, but is this enough?
Yeah, let's do that. It's
okay.
[Music]
Start
[Music] Hey, there are
three
[Music] There are
three,
Mr. Teacher.  I saw
[Music] I
saw you there with Senpai, and
I was the one scanning it, right?
Below that scan, there's a little map.
Map, um, it
was Porus, um,
D Kanchami.  I went into the nation room, and
when I was going out, I saw them go out together.
Where was the body? Well, it was mainly in the women's room. So, Olly
thought, ``Oh, I'll find you, and I'll do it,'' so
maybe Olly pressed the report himself.
No, umm, it
was delicious to recommend twice as much.
[Music]
[Music] I don't think
this is
anything special.
[Laughs]
There's time to vote, so do you want to decide? I'm
not a suspicious person, but the next one is
Imposter.  Well,
this year, I was with Chiara-chan.
Yeah, right now, those two
have been together for quite some time, so it
's probably safe for both of them.
[Music]
I guess I'll go with Fubuki-senpai.
Follow someone
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes,
Paradise-kun
Where, where, where,
where, where, appeal
OK, Aki-senpai, ah, nice
pen cue
Drop tails are often on the side,
right? Mr. Left and Right Mr. Yes, I
went to the left.  Well,
as I was walking towards the right side like this, I saw
Chiara-chan at the bottom, vibrating, and I
saw Lamy-chan and Button-chan running on the left side, so I think these two are probably different.
Um,
[Applause] They
ran.  I did
n't know where anything was, so I
ran around all over the place.
[Music] It
ran towards the bottom,
and there I was, Chiara's
dead body.  It
wasn't there yet when I was feeling all excited.  When we
met and held hands together, I
thought it was teamwork TT, but then he
got killed.
[Music] We
also
overlapped, so I couldn't go anymore.
Button-senpai is already that
impostor.  It's happened so many times,
but if I become Impossa next time, I'll kill myself.
[Laughs]
In the end,
I'll be Impossa again. I do
n't want to do it
today either, but I don't want to do it again today.
Ok
[Music]
Impossa.  I want to see it.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [
Music] [Applause]
[Music]
Noel-senpai, me, Rami-chan, and Comet-senpai
Of all the people I'm with, Noel
is dead, which means that for me, the only ones I'm going with are Rami-chan or
Comet-senpai.By the way, that's
right, but
Noel and I split up soon.Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
wait, this is a bit...  Wait,
uhm,
that's what they did for security purposes, and
privately, I thought the same thing, this button.By
the way, Ravi did
n't remember it, so yeah, there's no way he didn't remember it.
There was a lot of
people there, so I remember there was that other person,
but
yeah, no, no, no, this one is a bit strange,
no, no, I
think this is a button
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] I
want to hear it, Nami-chan, tell me.  But, you know, they
were there, right? There was
Sui-chan,
Shishiron,
Ramy, and what's more, Noel-san Parker.
[Music]
Father Anne outside
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
Karaoke,
then. Karaoke,
yeah,
it's a tour.
[Music]
[Music] I
guess I should ask you where you are first. I'll tell you where you are. Hmm.
I was in the room next to that. That's
right. The
others are in Akiro.  There's something spinning around,
and there's something to turn, boillash. I
saw Kana Aki-senpai, and I'm breathing, right? Yeah, I'm in the
oxygen room. The vacant
senior is the government. It
hurts, because we were together for a while. Eh,
where is the location?
Right in front of the middle door of the Upper Pon room.  So,
the door was closed, and I think they probably turned off the lights and
let everyone go upstairs.I
guess that's what happened.Where was the
body?
I think it was someone who had been near the weapon room before the lights went out.
[Music]
I was alone with my senior. We were
in the math room. The
amount of oxygen was right in the oxygen room. Yes, it was in the oxygen room.
Yes, I guess it was in the electrical room. So
who was near the body?  Who and who,
Chiara, uh, who was so far away?
uh, when did he die
? I
wonder if that person with a face that doesn't look like a photo is what he was. I was watching him.  I didn't see it. I
think he probably left it
as is. Yes, that's why I was chasing him,
or was it someone I happened to meet?
I was on the left with Konone-senpai, and I
left it in the electrical room.
[Music]
Safety, safety, oh, it's difficult. What should I do? I
might not understand, but this is a problem.
I think you'll show up every now and then.
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey, this.
This is what I should have
done. What did I do? What did I
do? No, I can't do
this anymore.
[Laughter]
Is this a confession? [
Laughter]
[Music]  I
made it look like Lamy. I think someone else is the culprit.
[Laughs]
That's right, big brother, it's suspicious, suspicious, suspicious.
This is definitely the culprit. It
was a little suspicious,
but
I also think that Ori will be next.  At the beginning of the turn, he
was laughing so hard that I thought it was suspicious.
Really?
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music] [Music] [
Laughter] [Laughter
]
[Music]
Karaoke Sisters Probably
Charm Best
[Music]
Who was the last person to see it? I saw it there.
But my brother wasn't there with me at that time,
but I
feel like we saw it together
[Music]
Laboratory  It's on the side. He's there. He
was doing it. He was playing that guy on the edge. He was
doing it. Yes, yes, he came out. Who was his 5-minute senior? He was in there
with the descendant.
He was in there, but he was
red.  There's a girl who looks like Noto has a medical checkup,
but I
remember getting tired of it, but
Sui-chan, on the other hand, why is there an emergency meeting now?I'm
sure Fubu-chan was probably with me right now,
right?  There was something called Vital over there, and I
saw someone die recently, so
if I remember correctly, Miko, Senpai, and Olly
went into the women's room together and said that,
and even after they left.  I'm
pretty sure it wasn't Tiara and someone else who went in as a group.
No, it wasn't someone, it was Achilles. It
wasn't someone who was a senior. It
was a woman. There was only one person who went in.  But
before that, I saw Lamy-chan in the laboratory,
rubbing Tiara-chan, and I think I
might see Button-chan around the corner as well.The
two of us said that we were going in together, and that's
when Olly and Miko-senpai happened to be.
[Music]
Where were you in the future
? Why don't you go to the storage room and
see what's going on in Tom's office?
[Music]
Please,
[Music] I
remember you.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
not the leader, I'm not the leader. It was really dark and I couldn't
see. I
really
wanted to find it. Where did I find it? I
know, I know, I know. Normally, the
leader was on top of the electric. Eh,
Mizusui-senpai.
From the laboratory.
Yeah, that
electrical room. That's dark.  So I
went there to fix it, and Sui
-chan told me that I knew the truth, but when I
tried to leave, I was
behind Sui-chan.If that's the case, I'll
definitely get suspicious because there's a dead body there.Is it
Sui-chan?  I
think it was Noyle-senpai's name,
but the moment I saw it, there was a sudden flop,
and he was about to fall, so I
think he really died.Well,
given the situation, I fixed it and the screen flopped.  Well,
when that happened, Noel was nearby,
and when he went out, he saw a dead body.
Noel went to the security side, so
I went from Electrical
to the right side, and at that time, he flopped and
fell down.  It's not
impossible that someone else could have killed him and made a U-turn the moment Noil came in. I
think that's the case. It would be
a bit strange if Noil was actually the security guard at the moment he collapsed.
[Music]
[Laughter]
If you talk a lot, it might be a bit like that
[Music]
Please stay behind Sui-chan
I haveNowyoubling
Fightisto
Oh
your my bends
Fighting Sundays
please
Donki-senpai
can't
[Music]
Where was Vital's
eye discovered?  I think I saw it before.
Vitals is the part on this map that looks
like an electrocardiogram.
[Music]
Well, I'm sorry about that, but I
can go get some ramen.
Right Kou-senpai What
was it that just climbed up to the top of the bottom left? What kind of passage did it use to come out of the top right? There's something
strange about it.
Okay, everyone, let's talk about Miho-chan.
Time.  Please, I
was watching the cat for a long time, right? So
who was the last one to go there? Yes,
at the beginning, I was
doing tasks in the room where I was with Miko-chan and Lamy-chan, and then there
was a power outage in the electrical system.  When I woke up, I
thought I should go that way, and I
found it near the area where it came out from the electric, but I
couldn't find Minnie for some reason, and the
last thing I did
was, yeah, but, but, that's
about 5, 8 seconds.  Since we only ran together, I
honestly
don't think I can make that judgmental judgment now.
[Music]
Maybe it would be faster to find the reason for Fubu-chan's death. That's how I
thought she might have moved by venting.  But, I do
n't know when
Corone died, but what do you mean when he said he saw it?
Well, it was officially confirmed, but when I
looked at it on the camera in the security room, it was visible,
even in terms of time.  If there's no more left, so there
's only one person left. I'm sorry.
[Laughs] It's
okay. I'm not doing it, so I
don't think
so. Mondo, Niko-senpai,
Okinawa,
a chance. It's not Cascus.
Communication
[Music]
Who's going to finish with just one more?
[Music] I
want someone to come with me. Well then, comet, I guess I'll go
with Senpai. I'll say something just in case,
but I'm alone with Corona-senpai right now. I
'll say it.  I'm just saying, yes, I
saw it, yes I
did it, so I guess this is why we're all
together. Well then, I'm the one who follows someone.
Recommendation: There
's one thing about my seniors.
Each task is
my fault, so it would
be a
waste if that happened.  So, I'd like to talk to
you about that. Everyone, I saw you go into the reception room, and it was directed by a female. [Music] There's something about this senior that I think is a little suspicious. We've been
searching for the camera room for quite some time now.  I was running towards it,
but
even though I hadn't finished the task yet, Crouse-senpai
went to the task stand with me for a really long time,
so I
guess I have something to do.  It
wouldn't be too hard to be alone,
so I thought I'd go with you.Yeah,
when I looked around for a while, there were about 5 people in the electrical room,
so when I thought about it, I thought there was only one person left,
so I looked in front of the vital signs and saw
Fuu-chan.  I saw a woman acting like this because she was dead,
so I think Coroney killed Wanchan.
[Laughs]
[Music]
OkOkOkOkOk
Where is this senior sesh saxophone? Hmm, what
happened? Yes, I
thought he wasn't dead.  I
wonder if everyone is doing well.Someone is here.I'm going to follow you.I
feel like I can talk about the task.I feel like I can talk about the task.Okay,
me too.Okay,
then, please give me your best regards, Corona-senpai.Yes, okay.
[Music]Hmm, I
honestly don't know.  But it's
difficult, that's
true, that's right, that's
right, there's definitely one person left.
Yeah, then
skip. Okay, then I'm more than happy to follow you. That tic, Senpai, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes.
I
was concentrating so someone must have gone to the other side.
After that, I suddenly looked behind me and
Kirara-chan
was dead. This was
Open Rose-senpai.
[Music] On
the right. It didn't
stop, so it was me and Swiss-senpai on the right.  It's
not here because I went there.I
remember the grandma who was always using her hands, and her hands
were big, so
even though I could see her shaking her head, I was Corona FC2. My
senior is still on the left.There's
no possibility of Aki-senpai like me.
There's no middle ground, but the
leader
kept using his hands and
went to the left side first.
[Music]
Hmm,
before I reported it myself, there was definitely no point.
Let's cut off the paradise that is attached to the left side.
However,
when the two of us went to the left side, various children
were chatting, but
everyone
went to the right side and Paradise-san
[Music]
[Applause]
It's because Koruru-senpai
didn't do that task.  You said it was suspicious, right?
Mine was
trying really hard.
[Music]
Let's stop. You must feel sorry for the
other person. Be kind to him. Be
kind to him. There's no chance.
From now on, he'll be more kind to you. [
Music]  ]
So, this is how today will end.
Well, we had a few troubles, but it
was really good.
[Music]
[Music] This is the
first time even the cat has had to do things around the house.  That's why I would like to hear your impressions.This is my
first time doing this big collaboration with my JP seniors.I was
really nervous and I couldn't lie, but I was
devastated inside, but no, it
was a lot of fun.  Well, I don't know, there was that
ID and en, that
Ollie, and
Chiara Chiara-senpai, but
everyone was good at Japanese, so I don't think anyone would say they're better than someone who
doesn't speak Japanese anymore.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you. You know, I didn't become a crewmate this time either,
so I
hope you'll call me again next time.
[Music]
New features too.  It
was so much fun, so fresh, and so
refreshing.Amogas was introduced a few months ago, and I
think everyone got really hooked on it and played it over and over again, but I thought they were getting a little tired of it,
but this time I used this feature.  It
was really refreshing, so I
want to do it again.
[Music]
I want to get really good at it too. I
want to do it again.
Aki-chan, that
scene at the beginning where I was so lively was after I died, and I
talked to Lamy-chan about what color her liver's face was.  Look,
even though I wasn't able to witness the scene, the incident already
happened in the conference room, so
nexttime I'd
like to be there like that, so I'd
like to do it again.
[Music]
Here we go.  I'm
shy,
but I feel like I was able to talk properly today. I
want to praise myself. Please play again.
[Music] I'm
sorry, Leader, but I'm in a bit of a
hurry. Is it alright?
Yes, everything was really fun.
Thank you.  Thank you
[Music]
Bye bye. I'll be participating in the research. [Music] I'm very happy to have you. It's
okay if someone asks me.
So
everyone had a lot of fun, so I'd like to do it again.
Thank you very much
[Music]
Well, we met up and helped each other out, so now when
everyone
smiles at me, it's
this one.It's
cute.Yes, it was
already fun.I want to do it again.Also,
manga is a little bit like
that.There are ways to say things like this, but
even if I say to my senior, it's personal.
[Laughs]
Please let me talk to you again.Thank you very much.The
good thing
was that I started working with Airi last year.We were
able to make a poster together, and we got a double kill.Thank
you very much.Let's
play together again.  Thank
you, thank you
[Music]
Now that we have shown a great bond,
Ramy is able to communicate with Sui-chan
at all, so I
thought to myself, ``I really don't want to hold you back next time'',
so it was a beautiful and brilliant double kill.  I
want to decide, so let's dig deeper. I'd be
happy if you could call me that. It was interesting, it
was a lot of fun.
[Music] I
let you get rid of all those people for a bit, but it's the
number one thing you can watch as much as you want. Even though I
can't speak English and I'm a little bad at it.
Thank you very much for playing with us. It
was a lot of fun. Let's play together again.
[Music]
Thank you everyone for coming out tonight.
Bye bye
[Music]