[Music]
oh
k k
boo wait I'm too
small you want to see my costume
bigger k
boo boo I'm so scared already no no no
just kidding uh wait my face is stuck in
being
sad from this game well yeah what it's
scary I'm sure it's scary it's supposed
to be scary I
think yay hello everybody I'm going to
put you um I don't know here for
now it it is it is time for me to play
this game it is destined to
be ever since this came out out I don't
think it was ready last year's
Halloween um and I thought when it came
out like okay I I I know I know I have
to play this but I will wait for
Halloween whichever Halloween it is I
just pray you can survive this thank you
I'm scared for me you seem scared for me
too yeah I saw coron sire playing it I
know mumay played it m can we appreciate
my costume I love how the little BBS on
top also have a costume they're like
part of the ghost attire and then a
little little not Z zombie zombie zombie
chicken has a little little basket to
get candy cute and my Kito c one is the
angel on my shoulder one is the the
devil on my
shoulder cute made by
blue oh of course thank you
blue blue is the best you forgot I was
bad with horror how could you forget
that the reason I never play horror
games is cuz I I I I I I'm scared I'm I
I mean you know people kfp likes to say
that I did quite well with previous um
explorations of horror games like uh
Outlast wasn't too bad eventually at
some point
but I don't want to purposefully put
myself for the
suffering when I
know I don't it doesn't spark joy in me
you know why would I do that Mory
assistant Mory assistant I was pretty
like scared of what could be but I guess
that wasn't too bad
either like actually
overestimated how scary it could
be um but
yeah nice choice yeah oh oh my God we're
already uh ever since the preat started
going crazy with the Polaroid it seems
thank you guys I was thinking this will
be my costume for the Polaroid I don't
know if I can let's let's see how long
like this takes this game um I saw m
played it for like two and a half hours
or so
maybe um but I was
thinking maybe if we still you know if
if it doesn't go too long I can sign
them today if it does go too long I can
maybe sign half today half
tomorrow
um I I made it cheaper for you guys cuz
I felt bad that you know I didn't want
to like Rob you
guys make you guys like yeah suffer from
Hunger
starvation um but that uh probably
results in me getting even more Polaroid
orders well well well I just want to
show you an example for the people who
don't know what's up but also for people
who watch the VA um so I started doing
like Polaroids
recently
um it's like an incentive for everybody
to to make it more special for everybody
who um wants to donate uh pinkies or
Reds last time we did it for Reds today
there's a discount for pinkies um
basically H what we're doing here's the
menu oh oh big yeah I saved it so big uh
menu number
[Music]
one butam menu number two so we have
wait let's start from the left side we
have a speeda we have a Dracula we have
a witch we have a a toilet paper
fan uh we have
a
zombie I made these orders by the way I
said which costumes I want uh we have a
ghost man ghost chicken so cute man and
we have the pumpkin chicken we have a
clown scary clown we have a skeleton or
dead be chicken could be both a cat
chicken which was um Duma just drew it
after I said oh I want a cat chicken um
as a present but I thought oh actually
that could be a Halloween costume too so
I put it there and then to fill out the
you know the row cuz I didn't want it to
end
there I thought oh wellow I I have some
others that from before look a little
bit like they could be costumes so I put
put those in there too uh these are
again made by Duma and now we have
special frames too I only thought we
were going to get one but we got three
I'm not going to make you guys choose
them though because that's going to be
uh too annoying to switch out every time
I think
um but if we get rid of this now let me
just show you what it would look like
roughly for example if we take Spider
Chicken oh it's so big
[Music]
like this okay I'm too low but you know
like kind of
like yeah yeah and I prepared some pgs
from me and then I would sign it on top
so last time it looked uh like
this cute and some people even printed
it out which is so so so
genius so that's how it's going to be
we're going to do that at the end of the
stream for now we're going to be uh
playing chicken feet and also I'm sorry
I didn't put out the schedule yet I was
waiting I got confirmation that I can
announce on my schedule already one of
them I guess we'll just be doing that uh
now because I can't wait any longer what
is this my teabag kind of broke a little
bit oh
no oh oh well um yeah I was waiting
until the last moment so I'll make the
schedule after the
stream another thing to do another thing
to do too you I'll surprise you with
what it is
um after the stream all right
[Music]
um such a I'm so Happy Family Feud went
so well too oh my God what a day what a
day what a day I wonder how big I should
be I want to show my costume but I have
to I can't be too big so like this
maybe
[Music]
so many laughes yeah it was it was great
right it went so well it went so well
I'm so happy everybody seemed to like it
I saw no complaints Road Islands I'm so
sorry the thing is I I I I I I I think I
like I'm very aware that road island
with OA is ridiculous and of course it's
Road I've heard it before I've seen it
before but but I it was like 6:00 a.m.
for me okay my brain was like on on 4
hours of sleep which is nothing for me
maybe 3 hours I don't even know and and
and I wasn't functioning okay like so I
just write what I hear automatically my
brain just like
autocorrects to r o a
d but I think it it added to the comedy
so
yeah oh we just saw clips of it nice
nice Rhode Island yeah it's it's no but
for Ark Knights I thought that I
genuinely thought during playing Ark
Knights that Rhode Island was
fictional I I did not
connect Rhode
Island yeah I always thought it was
fictional the crony saying Las Vegas is
just as bad
yeah
e Robo eh what do I sound like a robot
well why what I shouldn't be sounding
like a robot do I still sound like a
just one second okay yeah I thought it
was fictional what the
[Laughter]
hell L said Europe was a country so
don't even listen to what gura
says okay guys I guess I can't put it
off any longer longer I hope this is
okay to play with
keyboard is there any settings I should
change oh yeah we're on full screen
today I didn't care to change it oh WD
look with the mouse run uh right or left
shift okay Crouch c l Okay jump yeah
that's pretty everything's pretty
intuitive shift for one C isn't that
like the same as
Minecraft I think so that there's an
inventory there's an inventory
tab okay thank you for hosting easy I
was looking forward for to this for a
while while
while good said she wants me to get us
Wheel of Fortune too but Wheel of
Fortune wouldn't really be a big collab
it seems she said it's like three
players or so maybe that's like a
smaller one we'll see we'll see I'll see
what I can
do
chicken
feet has
begun di Dylan Dylan bid
presents
yeah oh dear the music tell me this is
comedic uh horror please tell me it's
it's comedic horror I won't be scared
right damn I should have gotten out my
my
my pulse it's my pleasure to welcome you
to the most sophisticated beautiful and
intricate science facilities in the
entire world I'll be your guide today
you can call me Sergeant Corey I can't
actually tell you what my real name is
for confidential reasons but I always
thought Cory was a nice name
Cory anyway we've got a lot of work to
do I'm sure you've already been informed
uh a giant chicken oh oh yeah lots of
death oh M yeah it's a it's a pretty bad
problem a but I have faith in us we're
going to make a great team ah did
Anthony go your location wild again so
I'll always know where you are I'm here
to
help okay now enjoy the glamour while
you still
can you'll be heading deep into this
facility and I promise you is the best
that it'll look goober research goober
go
this I feel like Cory was not my
friend yeah
Anthony one of the Anthony's oh
beautiful
art crap all right our first destination
is actually below us so uh find a way to
get there I maybe through a vent no good
luck I want to look at the beautiful art
here wow so
good a what do you see in this abstract
art I see like something like a spider
or
something this is too bright to look at
guys I don't want to I hate Halloween I
don't want to be for to play stupid horn
games Anthony just come back come
on please
is ah [\h__\h] scary already
man
[\h__\h] it'll be fine it's comedic horror
probably it won't be so scary just have
to not take it seriously gasoline or
what
w w nice oh this one's nice to they're
all nice oh
vent he said something about
venting I don't want to
that's one vent oh there's a knife
there's a
knife right that's a knife no a pile Dr
is that is that what you call a pile
driver I don't even know that just came
to my mind right now but uh what do you
call
this in
Engish a screwdriver what's a pile
driver what's the
difference wait so now I have inventory
use a vent ah with this maybe I can open
a vent okay so I had to get it oh why is
it so dark
it's a wrestling
move that's a wrestling move
okay I don't want to
[Music]
play when during Halloween streamers are
always expected to play games like these
oh now it's gone I can't use it anymore
okay no I don't want to I don't want to
I don't want
to no no hey I just want to tell you you
got to be very careful here you really
shouldn't underestimate this thing if
you do see the chicken just run try to
hide somewhere where he can't reach you
uhhuh and how do I win this
game how do I win it like what's the
goal what's the end goal capturing it
but I'm running from
it
[\h__\h] it says chicken it can't be that
scary that's true I should just give it
a hug then we'll be good right
ah why am I so scared oh my God it's
been such a long time since I played a
horror game nothing is
happen you see back up if it's really
bad I'm going to get niso so yeah ah
it's so dark it's so dark man I made tea
by the way so that maybe it calms me
down and also that it calms my voice
when I scream too much cuz girl boys
we're going to be
screaming I
don't can't I can't what is I don't I
don't it's too dark like why I hate the
darkness okay okay okay no I don't
[Laughter]
want I'm just in a weird mood I think
I'm in a weird mood
am I do I have to fall down cuz that
seems like the end of the
vent why is it open
anyway
[\h__\h] it's not it can't be like right
away there right
like welcome to go la shut up
steam
isn't this where I started [\h__\h] the
music scared
me should I try opening this
door it's
[Music]
close
did you did you see that was a shadow
but there's literally nowhere where I
could go that door was close there was
something and there was
something there was something
[Music]
there [\h__\h] I hate
games see
it's
there it's like moving it its neck in a
chicken
way but it's
like maybe I should walk quiet like
Crouch like
[Music]
this it's probably just like chilling
there oh
God okay it's a it's it's around the
corner it hasn't sensed me yet like
where would I even
go hey was the door really
closed I feel like I need a key for the
door
[\h__\h] that's you in the corner that's me
and the spotlight scaring my attention
why would you do
that
okay okay to together have to advance
but like chicken is there maybe we can
talk about
it is this a revenge for
old you saw it be very
careful make sure you don't let it catch
you
obviously obiously shut the [\h__\h] up you
bastard a um listen I know this might
seem annoying but there are three levers
down here that you'll need to pull uhhuh
they'll open the door that's going to
let you
proceed now I understand how redundant
that may seem but it's all in the name
of security oh oh I can understand that
good luck I'll talk to you soon be
careful down there if I stay alive yeah
free levels to unlock the exit door uh
is it that is that it is that like older
is
it I was saying um maybe this is the
revenge for all the months I put them
into the usual
room okay so I know that the chicken oh
will be walking the
corridors how how how is this not the
exit is it just a
picture might just be a
picture there's a vent
there any any item that glows up I could
go through here to hide it's a stupid
ass
picture
okay okay wow very pixelly my nose is um
is itchy where is this chicken where are
you you wouldn't want to hurt or scare
your tantel right there's a
lever there's a
lever
I wonder if footsteps like if it's good
to generally
Crouch if you can hear the footsteps
from uh far away or
so this this could be a good place to
like hide from it too maybe I wonder is
that
glass I'm safe here
right hi
Anthony oh you're so beautiful you're so
pretty you're so chunky oh I'm going to
give you nice chicken feed if you just
stop haunting
me byebye cute butt really cute butt I
admire your butt I wish I had such a
nice butt Twerk it For Me Anthony come
on okay all right it's really slow I
guess it can get really
fast
potentially there's another event but
like this
one's shut
up I
just I just
felt I just felt some sweat dripping
down my
um
skin I need a shower have
this I don't want
to where already why it that's the sound
of it coming closer right okay
[\h__\h]
ah okay okay I don't I I can't be this
slow I won't be able to advance
much
I think I heard the human or whatever
that is talk and that freaked me out cuz
he sounded freaked
out
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] why did I go over here this
seems to be like it's fa place to walk
around it's still
there coming
back oh
no can
chickens see all
colors I don't remember why did he come
back he smells fear
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] you tell me no
idea oh man he smells me he smells my
sweat yeah the salty
sweat oh God but isn't he going
to
[Music]
I
was Dam that chicken is
fast it's so
fast why is so fast oh my God wait my
teeth oh my my throat is going to hurt
so
much m
at least this tea is
amazing
chicken you had time to run well I was
running
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] so wait there was a lever here
should I still no no I'll go other ways
for now it's good that I'm aware of
lever oh here's another lever
okay that
was I think I just saw it in the corner
of my eye oh what is
this what is this we just moved
Sebastian into the Red Cell while work
continues
downstairs I know he isn't really a
human but the things they do to him
they're horrible oh that's the dude it's
like growing up in prison but worse he's
got no friends no
freedoms the the dud I honestly don't
know why Eric is doing all of this to
him Eric at least he has an education
but even then I think it's just for the
sake of testing they're testing so what
if he's genetically modified a human in
there human is a human
right wait so Sebastian is the dude in
in the in that one red
cell thing not really a cell
but okay is this lore
important
mutant Sebastian the chicken no no his
name is Anthony I'm pretty
sure so on which side is the chicken
now [\h__\h] I'm not good at this although I
should be good at sneaking NY NY NY NY
NY NY NY sneaking there's a door m
oh [\h__\h]
oh
oh I heard footsteps and the buck buck
buck it's it's close it's so
close
[\h__\h] where is
it maybe it doesn't seem to go over over
here so for
now we we walk around
[Music]
this he's there how small is this
place does he does does is
does the computer like like follow where
I go like does the chicken automatically
go where I am or oh God I'm sorry I'm so
I'm so scared let's go this way
maybe there there's more than one
no no there can't
be oh oh
oh I found found a
[Music]
key okay okay okay okay oh oh is this
where I was is this where I was trying
to get through where he caught me hello
ooh
[Music]
feet run run run run run run run run run
run run run run run
run okay okay okay second lever second
lever I did it okay okay now I just need
to find the third lever which is maybe
behind like one of the like a door don't
remember which one was the one that
needed the key maybe the key is for all
the doors
[Music]
M okay I wonder if that's really
actually it but that would be too short
maybe there's
like a catch should I go all right I
can't I can't cuz it's closed I would
need maybe another
screwdriver so can
I [\h__\h] I'm going to fail like it's going
to fight me
again
y
[Music]
y okay okay okay okay okay it actually
lost me before I even went through the
hole okay okay okay okay okay okay I
made it I made it I made it this is not
the end yet okay [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] my
heart
ah ah Mama
mia
fu I'm going to get a heart
attack I don't know if it's safe to
go oh
yum
yum I don't hear any
sound oh no I hear
them a
man that was
faint okay it's coming this way so let's
let's wait for
it maybe and then walk behind it
hopefully it doesn't suddenly turn
around right that would be
terrible
oh okay it seems to have quite the vi
the wide uh what's it called
fov field of view
it was just chilling there I I didn't
think it would see
me okay
okayy that's that's exactly the great
thing for when my stream starts you know
it you know it chicken so proud of you
for
remembering our
greetings
okay too early I have to give it more
times he's so fast he's my biggest
fan yeah
[\h__\h] can't do
this oh
man
a [\h__\h] my pinky also hurts from
Crouching go away go away
Anthony it's not it's not it wasn't me I
didn't put you in the usual
room it wasn't me
[Music]
no he doesn't understand proper
etiquette for fan
meetups yeah oh oh he does come back
okay I think this is our chance we have
to take it like he'll be walking around
here
forever oh should I go
now but he goes does he go like like
this have to follow him
then oh
God he going to show up behind me any
second [\h__\h]
okay pause pause in here pause pause
[Music]
pause okay okay okay wait where are we
where are we where is the
door where is the door that I need to
open
so maybe maybe that way I think that way
but I don't
[Music]
know but
wait
[\h__\h] is he coming from this way yeah I
think so yeah
okay
[Music]
than v wait this is the one I
the door the door the door the door the
door the door door door the door door
the door the door the door the door pull
free levels to unlock the exit door what
is the the key the key okay the key
might be for this
door oh [\h__\h] he seems so close they just
they they won't let go of this
door but he never actually walks like
right
here just have to check if it's
safe he didn't see me though he didn't
see me but okay that's that's where it
connects okay that's
where the red and the blue rooms are
okay ah but he does he does walk over I
remember him like going there but then
going back right I don't
know maybe I can go
now oh what the
[\h__\h] okay uh there's a leather there
must be a catch what's the catch what's
the
catch
hey
mommy KY you must have seen
me go
away go away I'll never come out
otherwise okay so what exit the area
which area
like can I actually find the exit door
like where is it what is that by the way
I have to push
that it's so green like glowy green how
the [\h__\h] am I supposed to go he's stuck
here is he
not no this this green L
okay I see
[Music]
maybe
there where would I where would I
go where would I
go okay I have to go that
way where did he come from
anyway
now I'm in the usual room
man what if I fail now do I start from
the
beginning maybe you can reason with the
Nugget I I don't I think this is one of
my underdeveloped chickens who just
don't understand what I
say should have taught them all equally
my
language
hi hi such a pretty bird such a cutie
bird you're so
pretty
oh maybe maybe maybe we can be
friends
overdevelop okay okay we'll give it a
bit more
time and then we
go
okay oh there's something
there oh it's where it came
[Music]
from
no no
[Music]
no
no no w w wow do I start from the
beginning oh I start from here what
before I pulled the lever no it's after
oh thank God there's
checkpoints oh thank
God I will need a fro
candy I will need a fro candy haven't
had froat candies in a while but today
is the day today is the day for Ro
candies let's
[Music]
go don't choke on it trick or treat
yeah not the candy that kids would be
happy about I
think okay I
think you need to bait them at right
hole and then you run from left
Hole uh
you don't mean here right you
mean that other hole where I where the
message was maybe I could I could
probably bait him from there too
actually but I don't know where I'm even
going to
go could work here but it's such a small
space and he's fast wait I I cannot hear
him
now
okay why is it
closed no way that was that was that was
open
before no or is this a new is this a new
area no but I came through here I
[Music]
swear oh okay let me
check we just moved Sebastian into the
Red Cell while work continues hi
Sebastian I know he isn't really a human
but the things they do to him they're
horrible let's go here again okay okay
we're moving we're moving I just need to
find where to go next cuz I have no
idea is this open now it is
open wait I'm not going to be chased
both by this crazy Sebastian human
and a chicken
right hi Sebastian uh no
Anthony I will check out the Reda I
think it's telling me to go
there it's just a human just just a just
a human just a weird
human what could possibly happen this is
Jurassic
Park true oh oh he's he's escaped he's
escaped um I thought I was only going to
be chased by a chicken
today we didn't this was not this was
not in a contract this was not one we
talked
about that's not cool that's not [\h__\h]
cool or did the chicken open it and eat
him
and I'm
next I surely got
him this is why you don't leave chickens
in the usual room for too long I'm late
cuz you forgot daylight saving a I put
correctly on my on my schedule though oh
wait there's no
schedule there is no schedule no
schedule for today yet oh
hi can you tell me the direction or do
you have Direction issues just like me
okay I understand but what happened to
the guy who was in here huh you want to
tell me about
that
[\h__\h] Chicken brain can't remember what
it did 5 seconds ago so no idea it
seems do we want to know that's froggy
wa in a costume no froggy Wawa would be
tiny
okay you can go away
now you can go away
now walk away SC scoot scooty
poop that way is a wasn't that a dead
end for
you no wait the door there's an open
door for him now there is
there but isn't that to the right [\h__\h]
I'm I'm I'm such a chicken I'm such a
chicken okay it was it was good that I
didn't go I I
think maybe or was it maybe I should
have
gone maybe I should have
gone in that
moment that was my chance but he's going
there again but for how
long if he goes around the corner I can
go otherwise he'll see me pretty
[Music]
sure
[\h__\h] I'm not here what do you mean you
me go go go go no see he sees everything
my
God this
chicken it's so
stressful so
stressful my tummy
H my tummy h
wen't oh my tummy
horn
okay okay I can do
this I can
do he's
close he'll always be close I
[Music]
guess isn't Nisa also pretty bad with
horror
games okay he'll he'll come here here
and then he'll make He he'll do his turn
and then I'll
go right you're coming right yeah
okay no she love yeah right right she's
been yeah playing them regularly never
mind never
mind I
mean doesn't necessarily mean that she
doesn't get scared
but hey that's not that's not what we
talked about hey you're supposed to go
there and around the corner
a thank you for the all the pinkies
guys
[\h__\h] no no no no no no no no you can't
see me I'm not
there what
what what
a
bug get
[Music]
out there was like for a moment there
was this battle music
again but it didn't look like it was
hunting
me ah it was clipping
through
okay oh
[\h__\h] uh
is it going to go to the to the
left please tell
me come on
Anthony it's time to lay an egg or hatch
one
please [\h__\h] it doesn't go anymore there
[\h__\h] I have
to have to risk it for the
biscuit
I have no
[Music]
choice he didn't even notice me that
fast I think
but oh it was good then I
went what
maybe was there some no but the vent is
closed over
there
right
fck a damn it damn it damn it damn it
Dam
itam
I should have brought like some some
some uh some chicken feed to scatter it
around and like just lure him
away why am I so unprepared why did I go
into this so I'm
prepared why are there no tools for me
to make use
of
you
uh no the screwdrive I have no items
right now when you use them once they're
like used
forever
risky risky risky risky risky
breakdown Fe night stream fever night
okay where am I wait where is this I I
got to go that way probably cuz I I
don't really remember going there
much okay
ah this is maybe a good place to bait
him if I see him over here I could bait
him here and then I run that way unless
it's like all
connected or I can like literally I have
I guess I got to go out a little
bit what it's terrifying what if I don't
make it walk
walk
I don't even know what there is on that
side Master Baer takasi Kiana
returns it's it I think the game knows
what I'm trying to do when I'm in this
vent it just it just won't appear
anywhere and then I I'll get surprised
guys at some point oh oh it's there is
it
there hi wrong side you should go that
[Music]
way so where does that
go hi
hi hi baby
hi hi there's a there's a
there's all of kfb waiting for you
they'll be nice they'll welcome you back
you just you just got to stop bullying
me I'm sure they'll understand we we'll
all welcome you back and you can work
like you you used to before back in the
day we're not going to throw you in the
fryer don't worry I know you're scared
of the
[Music]
fryer I I I know I said that because
there's so much meat on you that's the
only place where you'll ever end up at I
know I said that but but I I I I it's
okay I can sacrifice 10 normal siiz
chickens and leave you
alive
oh but only if you leave me alive
I completed level
one no
no okay I did it I did it I did level
one let's
go all right you made it I only stop
we're getting closer that part just keep
going there's
more the
Cooper is that another one wait where
where did that person ever end up at
like we never saw him I guess he really
was that implied that he was
eaten there's two buttons that we can
push maybe one and this level is hard oh
[\h__\h] maybe one
we we will start at but the other one
will be the exit
again oh so far visually it's quite
pleasing
elevator wait before I press that let me
oh there's another thing to
close oh ah lore
message this is Mrs Lawrence Sebastian's
new teacher Lawrence of the lore I am
here with a progress report he's coming
along very nicely he's improving in
practically Every Way Reading Writing
and speaking okay the guy I do have one
concern he seems to have scars on his
body I don't mention this in an
accusatory way what happens when I'm not
here isn't any of my business could it
be from the chicken I just thought I
would bring it up in case they were self
inflicted I'll be back next
week okay so the test
subject was he kept in
here
momentarily
well a nice time for a nice little story
isn't
it is this going to bring me down yeah
all right guys if this is so much more
difficult I don't know if I can get
through this but we're going to try oh
that's a little bit
dark I don't like Darkness but I'm going
to go to the light
ah okay that was not the size of a
chicken that was more like a
person please no jump scare please no
jump
scare oh he went that
way oh [\h__\h] that's
scary
[Music]
man okay it's a barn no no no no no no
no no
no no no no
no no where is the chicken or is it not
about chickens
anymore
[Music]
what I'm going to
go I'm going to go
now
maybe it doesn't even look like there's
good places to hide from a chicken no
like Vents and stuff I guess this could
be this could work
cuz I can't go through such a small
space or here
too but okay there's
like not it's it's just a a place to go
through quickly but no yeah no this this
this could be a safe room we have to
remember this
[Music]
one still no
sight according to my map the exit to
this area is locked and it can't be open
from your current location uhhuh looks
like you'll need to get up there where
that blue light is MHM there should be
an elevator system that can help
you yeah yeah that's
fine before I do
that it's not about a chicken anymore I
see the person I see
him he's just like chicken stilling
there I see his
head can we stop cuz it's not about the
chicken
[Music]
anymore
okay
um are you freaking kidding
me he's going to probably stop start
walking once I press this button
oh what was this one okay okay I thought
maybe could be for both but it was for
this
one
really so much for the jumping
feature maybe a little bit of a a run
but what does that do for me if I go
there just an
escape
M yeah okay yeah but okay maybe this is
just another place to
escape so there's nothing to do up
here is there no buttons to push okay
okay
okay is he still there
yeah yeah he's so
tall he's so
tall okay he he doesn't seem interested
yet in me that's okay oh I could Escape
here no not really oh I would have to go
through
here okay okay okay this is this is more
Escape
options you didn't see anything are you
blind
you will die in this
environment as long as he's not haunting
me we want to look
around check our
options okay another escape room
basically
cool it's weird to have an underground
Barn that that is weird is that a
[Music]
thing that's the second door
yeah and there's a button up there where
I'd have to go hey he's still there oh
oh oh
oh he ducked he ducked maybe he's on the
Move now
M
okay we're playing hide and
seek hey [\h__\h] why can we go back to the
chicken that was kind of
funny CH return off the chicken
please
um
no no no no no no no
no
please please please please I don't want
to go
there oh he's certainly there I'm sure
he's
there
man guys can you play this game for me
and and I I'll just act as if I'm
playing it like Sniper Wolf
please
please please I can't do this I'm not
made for games like
these not I'm not I can't I I would like
to be no actually I don't I don't know I
don't need this I need I don't need this
in my life you
know or is he gone like completely did
he go somewhere else maybe he's in
there okay okay
okay is this button for the elevator in
the
front
Okay Okay secure this area n n it
probably is for the front yeah so I have
to like run really fast and that's
probably when he'll show up the moment I
press the purple button maybe maybe
maybe
maybe [\h__\h] my tummy hurts today
wait could it be no my tummy already
hurt a little bit before the stream
actually [\h__\h] it really
[Music]
hurts my tea is
cold can can I can I can I go for a
moment um I'll I'll be back I'll be back
I'll be back back I want to maybe see if
I can do something about my tummy
horn
um okay I'll be right back sure I'll
will come back I'm not I'm not escaping
from this game I I'll be back oh yeah
there's no Escape
anyway please wait for me and give me
mental support you're tmy H too she
never returned no I I will
return I promise pinky promise okay BRB
hopefully um let's leave a
note to
[Music]
scared
no uh okay I found a chunky
wonky and she was cute and she was
waiting for me in the
bathroom she cute she fluffy she
[Music]
chunky okay there's nothing to be scared
about there's nothing to be scared about
it's just a game it's just a game it's
just a game it's just a game it's just a
game it's just a game it's just a
game I know what's going to happen the
moment I push this
button it's going to come for
me
find a pipe and use it to fix the oh
check out this here I'm happy I'm
actually kind of
happy okay I'm happy oh wait you I'm too
big I'm too big wait but I'm kind of
happy I the chicken started
walking a it's not about the human
mainly okay the human is probably just
going to show up at each level like kind
of teasing and then at the end maybe
maybe there's some kind of reveal with
it but I'll be continue to be chased by
the chicken
okay okay yeah I'm happy about
that I'm happy mly
happy
mly mly mildly relief what did it say
find a pipe and use it to fix
the elevator system okay a pipe ah this
part a pipe oh fre oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
woo okay all right yeah definitely more
difficult to hide from the chicken
here
um the rooms are very
big and you know chicken can see very
far pipes I haven't seen any I wonder if
they
only if they only show up
after you push that
[Music]
button have you tried being friend
shaped I wish I could be as friend
shaped as this chicken hi by the way how
come you don't see me here that's like
no logic there but
okay it's going through the side path
not for the
middle I guess okay once I get like uh
once I get the part then the elevator
will work then I'll go up there push the
button and then that's that's probably
opening the exit door
again so that's when I'll have to run to
the exit
again what I don't I don't even see
you
n wow did you guys see
him
how how else am I going to
do
[Music]
this
ow at least he's like pretty far so the
distance if you know where to
go it's manageable okay go don't go so
crazy with your bug bug okay chill oh
he's excited he's so excited he's been
waiting to play with a friend for a
while got to Rush maybe try to run you
mean around him
maybe thank you thank you
guys seems like maybe wait is he still
there no okay not visible to me
now oh big doggy doggy can you see me in
the
dark oh there's something
there okay okay is he walking around
there oh I see his big butt his big
fluffy butt he's checking out the room
oh go go go go go
[Music]
yeah close door ah yeah the the right
was that the button the the door opening
closing button is that what that
was
[Music]
H oh it's so
hot why is it so
hot
okay this
difficult M finished this game
right oh oh he went pretty far there
okay
okay he's going to get me he's going to
get me he's going to get
me
I I wasn't sure to
go okay I I outran him still that's
impressive okay like okay I think I'm
like a little bit calmer generally
because of me uh being very aware of the
situation
now that's good that's
good
well what
why I'm not here there's nothing here
that was the other test subject
okay I I think wait I think I'm also a
test subject they put me in here just
like the other
dude I'm also just being used
abused as a test subject but why me I'm
the tental I'm the
CEO I shouldn't be needing to do
this oh there there he is fluffy butt Mr
Fluffy butt oh coming around
again next alien isolation oh hell
no
[\h__\h] the jump scare slowly will turn
into annoyance okay rabid than
being actually terrifying
okay such a pretty chicken so many
people could be fed with by
you and yet you refuse to do something
good for
[Music]
Humanity I'm done being nice to you and
inviting you back to
kfp your lost cause Anthony a lost cause
yeah
I'm not proud of
[Music]
you okay
byebye I'm I've Got The High Ground now
sucker it took me like a moment to like
press the button cuz I I wanted to be
sure I'm like actually pressing the
right thing I wanted to be
calm okay well what now we need to find
the pipe it's surely not in this big
room is
it
okay another little escape
room we can see what he's doing from
here it's over ant
chicken thank you thank you for
applauding
me where you going to go what's she
going to do huh she going to outrun
you I'm just going to outrun
you yeah yeah you impressed with my
skills now aren't you e you got no
chance you don't mess with the master of
kfp I can't do anything about this huh
can't even see me cuz you're too
stupid can't put plus one and plus one
what what one plus one together stupid
chicken stupid
stupid stupid stupid all you can do is
BU and K
Kitty doesn't even know how to say a
in
Weak
weak I don't see any pipes what about
here oh that looks like a pipe to
[Applause]
me okay I'm I'm more confident
now
oh he this it's programmed to like
always be near to me man
[Music]
man okay okay quickly back to a secure
place is it there now or
there I got the pipes I got them got to
get back to the big
Hall
I think it's there oh yeah oh should I
run a little
bit
no
okay I heard it like
trampling it came running at me me
aggressively I I okay I think like here
even if you stand like this it won't
like react right so I thought here over
the fence it would be okay but no it
doesn't really count as a safe zone so
it will react to you I think that's how
it's
programmed okay
okay leave our alone yeah I'm going to
send my Army of chickens against
you no no no oh bad chicken
no the music the music
man oh I'm going so far let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's
go okay okay okay now I I'm actually
doing a Bad Thing by giving it time to
come over to my area again I guess but
it's okay that's
okay
oh
oh that's what I bought that's what I
bought okay
okay so that's going to be the challenge
is it going to be camping
there
ah
ah going to go back right to the
to no there's moments where it's like
here okay well maybe we have to like
running run in a circle or
so that's good it's good I have
everything under control I'm I'm
mentally stable
now the Juke use the power of the Juke
what's a what's that juke
box is juke like baiting
him that's a strat what running in a
circle well chickens can run in a circle
quite well too I think Juke means
dodging okay well i' i' i' I've taught
i' I've shown myself before that I could
outrun
him and there are checkpoints and I
think they're quite nice to
me what should I before I pushed a
button bait
him and then what when I'm
running past here I quickly press the
button and continue
running you know what I
mean like maybe bait him from
like closer to the exit from the left
make him like on the left side make him
see me make him run to here the left
side I run past this barrier then I push
this button and then I go that way you
know what I
mean one Circle basically but but start
baiting him before I push the button but
then uh well me pushing the button will
take a moment
though I gotta make sure to
have a good amount of distance between
us I wonder if I like die once where do
I
restart like which situ which which
position
okay where is he
now
uhhuh uhuh if I
can
[Music]
I did it I did it but it was too
close I stood on it and all I can do in
that moment is
waitu camping outside I guess
[Music]
oh oh where where where where was that
n how where was
he maybe push first e uh so maybe there
is time calculated for me to push it and
then bait
him who knows how long it actually
takes yeah
maybe we test that
out timing okay okay okay
okay what point should I bait
him 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 I can't see it going
up from here eight oh I no I kind of see
it ah okay I'll count it again I want to
know I want to know the time maybe that
was 10 seconds it could have been 10 SEC
[Music]
[Applause]
or great counting I know I was
like were like 8 seconds cuz I counted
kind of
fast where is it doco
do chicken
doo
oh
there so maybe okay I'll just try it
[\h__\h] it I'm not
scared you can see
me
okay okay that's the way to
go it lost track of
Me no
no
ouch my throat it lost track of me and
that was perfect I didn't oh it was the
perfect
timing but ah
alas it was too stupid to jump over was
I not supposed to jump do I just like
walk over I don't
know was difficult to I have to crouch
jump Crouch or just walk
Crouch you timed
it damn you're so you're so
involved or are you the chicken and
that's why you're timing it so that you
can be faster next
time was that the reason you timed
it okay Crouch walk all right damn that
could have been so good and that was
kind of almost first
try wait so I got him from I got him to
see
me from the left
or yeah he saw me from the left right
like
here witness me notice me be conscious
about me
hi oh
maybe okay it's because see it didn't
lose track of me so then it's actually
too much
time I clicked it I'm pretty sure I
clicked it
[Music]
properly
h a button first oh yeah right the
button
first so what did I do I pressed the
button and then I went to the
left
like when I see him that he's on the
side I press the button and then I go
there and then I make him run
around a [\h__\h] now I'm too scared oh he's
on the right side
okay okay press and then bait
okay I can do this I can do this I
pretty much did it all
already I'm literally the chicken in the
cpop right now I'm in the CP who's in
the coop now that's what you guys are
saying
probably um press and then bait
right
hi okay run run run run run run run run
here he forgot me he forgot me Chicken
brain
bra okay
W oh chck brain working to my advantage
let's
go okay so behind here is the button
this is the
button this door is closed now right
it's not going to like open up
Suddenly it's going to open afterwards
maybe oh checkpoint I see the
saving
back [\h__\h] my
Thro ah it's not so smooth my transition
from running to crouching is not smooth
enough
man okay
did you hear that
laugh okay oh my
good oh that was the completion Oh I
thought I have to press something there
and then like you know oh okay
okay
oh oh you aren't who I thought you were
oh but that doesn't mean you're
different what exactly are your
intentions M are you talking to me you L
are you looking for a way
out he can talk are you here to hurt me
oh I I was going to offer you another
job you wouldn't want to hurt me no
right no I I I swear that was just a
joke a joke to my chickens I want you to
stay away yeah and I really don't think
you understand what's going on here
maybe you should become a beber break
free and Escape you have a great voice
none of you humans were strong enough to
stop
me others weren't so lucky they weren't
strong
enough wait one second I want to make it
Lou no I can't now and I killed everyone
you did I got my way good good job I
guess and I won't stop at you okay
but for now I'll give you a chance oh
just open that door and I'll give you
your freedom that doesn't look like now
promise me that you'll leave yeah got
that I will [\h__\h] come
back it's not a real door it's not a
real it's not a real okay okay okay
okay hey what are you doing don't kill
yourself yet I mean uh
wait wait a minute how how did you get
here I don't know from where you were it
should be impossible
to this is really strange you shouldn't
be down
here we can work with this just hang
tight oh wa is this still and if you
find any sort of tape recorder please do
not play it there's a lot of
confidential information down here you
tell me that now I already found two
wait now are those two voices the
same this this was the the the
introductionary
person oh [\h__\h] do doesn't look like
something you would use to kill a
chicken or is or is this what you use
that's terrifying no I don't think
that's what you
use
[\h__\h] is this level free this the final
level is are for
levels that took me a moment cuz I was
looking somewhere else looks like a
[\h__\h]
robot do you see it you see it
right if we shall the chicken this maybe
he'll think it's one of his
friends hey go away you'll go away when
I get closer
right yeah
okay maybe he's a friend maybe I don't
have to be scared maybe maybe this is
the the one guy who's been like
surviving here forever he's been trying
to make himself Stronger by like putting
some weird robot armor on himself to
strengthen himself so that he'll be
Invincible from the chicken and
eventually maybe be able be able to
escape or or even kill the
chicken maybe or maybe not oh dear that
is
poultry or is it no
wait uh this is poultry but this uh
maybe a a different
animal all right let's
listen this is Eric's audio Journal day
561 today marks the 20th anniversary of
Sebastian's birth the product of project
rebirth the world's first genetically
modified
human it can read right and even speak
it's
incredible the Pinnacle of our
discoveries we still haven't revealed it
to the public we have to wait the more
tests we can do the better chances we we
have of improving it we just need more
testing but it isn't perfect it it isn't
and we will reattempt project rebirth
within the next 5 years what does that
mean I don't care what the executives
say I don't care what the doctors say I
don't care what the mother says we will
get this
right
uh the the mothers the mother
did he say mothers or
mother does he have a
mommy
so Sebastian has been uh made to be
a a very special
human oh I saw shadow that must have
been him
again okay okay close door maybe for
later
button oh okay okay two buttons no
person and a hammer that I can't take
okay ah tomato tomato potato
potato oh oh connected again
oh okay okay okay it's fine that's fine
it's fine what kind of place is this
what we're dealing oh is this a dead end
the other side should I go there no
that's an elevator again is it oh yeah
oh oh I understand ah blue uh purple
button run around go
elevator wait sorry I was too stupid can
we do it
again can I reset
[\h__\h] well that's not much
time is this something going to be
chasing
me when I do
this okay go go go go go go go go
go okay y I'm here nothing chased me
maybe it was just
practice just a little bit of practice
I'm in the vent
again oh
oh
okay
interesting
small
corridors oh
jumping oh
hello
hi you don't look normal to me man he's
talking too do you see his mouth
move am I going to be tasted by you now
or the chicken
again I wouldn't mind if it was the
chicken
honestly I feel like I can still make
friends with him he he wanted to let me
escape after
all
freaky he's a he's a robot now was he
ever a
human maybe this is just for me to walk
by and WI and like just uh I don't mean
to scare you you and I we are not
different oh yeah my name is sebas yeah
that's what they've always called me
okay friend you I've been following you
know I've been
listening I know that you don't work
here no not really you are oblivious to
what's really going
on I've heard your radio that voice
uh-huh he hurt you I know him he hurt
you right he's not who you think he is
maybe it's the chicken his name is Eric
Eric yeah he created this place he's the
one that has caused us this pain this is
Revenge on humanity is evil yeah I know
this he is a monster I did think you
weren't evil he wants to cause more
pain yeah you seem like you and
I we can stop him
otherwise there gun he is going to kill
us why is there a gun both of us why is
there a gun why is there gun is using
you and he'll kill you you're a loose
end you've seen too much and the
chicken he wants the chicken that's why
he sent you right the poor the chicken's
name is Cooper I doubt he told you that
Cooper oh no it's Anthony when Cooper
broke out he saved me Cooper now Eric
wants to capture him again Cooper saved
you or Eric saved you he wants to cause
more
pain I've got a plan I'll save us okay
you just need to lure him down here just
follow his instructions I'll save you
lure Eric or the chicken sorry I didn't
understand can you I lure whatever I
find I
guess uh he's got a gun
though hopefully it
doesn't accidentally shoot
me maybe he should have given me the gun
he should have given me the gun and I
just shoot the the chicken or or
Eric okay so I figured it out yeah this
place has gas pipes running behind the
walls oh if we pump sleeping gas into
the pipes we can put the chicken to
sleep without damaging it too me too
though and of course you would also fall
asleep but i' just wake you up plain and
simple yeah at this point do that seems
to be our only option mhm so you'll need
to let the gas into the pipes first then
you'll need to release the gas simple
enough if this is the last time we speak
before I wake you up of course then I'll
I'll just say it's been a
pleasure oh carpets probably made by a
carpenter find a way to let the sleeping
guys into the
pipes okay
easy
easy easy but wait we're baiting him
though so is that really my
goal are you behind this
door why is there carpets
here
oh gas
release why would I do
this and how much time do I have then
huh
what ah wait I open the door and then I
release the gas or I release the gas and
then I open m
[Music]
m h bad
ending okay let's see what happens how
fast the chicken is going to come out if
it's there at
all that wait wa my keys
broke how did how did I still how did I
still there oh there isn't gas in the
PIP set okay oh
don't you broke broke at the glass
[Music]
please
oh
okay
um so it would be going in circles
now
what
well I'm not sure where exactly it is
now
[\h__\h]
oh
right come
on anony it will be a a painless death I
think rather painless more painless than
the other deaths people were planning
for
you okay you'll just fall asleep
yeah where's your carpet this more
comfortable for your beautiful chicken
feet only the best for
you
okay
okay okay oh SM
chicken smer smaller chicken
why small small
chicken where can I hide
here SM chicken you guys are not safe
yet he probably going to eat
you
a I have to save them they're normal hi
babies big Che oh maybe they are the
babies shei can definitely be can of
ballistic who's even feeding you there's
actual chicken feed on the ground I
think a little bit here
maybe are they also going to be
big I don't think so that doesn't seem
like
realistic I feel like this one chicken
would just lay huge
[Laughter]
eggs anyway n
what the [\h__\h] was that ding-ding
sound
hav't oh wow this is
grotesque uh why did we fall
down maybe this is where I turn on the
gas maybe I actually found the right
path oh dear okay not this is
a a place to
escape ah
H the rest of the cow oh you think that
is like the the other part of that thing
we saw before oh nice nice glitch or no
we're just out are we
no
ooh
okay what are you going to do there it's
a dead end
right do I run
[Music]
now
seems like I am inside and
outside I shall follow I
[Music]
guess is there something here to pick up
oh oh go back and oh that was the
sleeping
gas okay so all the to do is go back and
release it but we don't really want to
do
that but for now we'll follow the
objective why is there so much like bgm
stuff going on it's confusing me giving
me all kinds of
Vibes is it
safe it's too safe it's too
safe
it's too safe a this is where I fell
down oh I came from there I
[Music]
wonder yeah I think
so the
climax ah is this is this is is this oh
that's already the room I
think and the door just wasn't open
before ding ding ding again who's making
a ding
sound like a
bicycle
Bell okay time to
go well if this is really that
room oh I have to jump over that because
I see it now there's a rope down
there uh okay so
I'll I'll jump over it then it won't
make the
dingding
um yep okay nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice I'm a pro now I'm a
proo I've got so
far I've graduated from scared
chicken let's
go quickly jumped over and then ran to
the safe Zone
yeah ah those are the little chickens
right I didn't even see them when I ran
past
them
hi they still seem to be the same
size okay where so I went that way last
time right and I went for the I went for
the vent and it fell down but um I need
to go this way this is where I came
from need to go back there but I don't
know where to the big chicken is right
now there's me over there hi
P
cute jber what's the G oh oh
what what who was it
[Music]
chasing or is that just oh is that just
a thing it does now like randomly
running
around H he's chasing his
dreams this is randomly running around
man it's excited or already knows
something is about to go
down
well chicken do chickens have doomies
too like
cats
dogos oh hi
oh oh w w
oh oh ding ding oh I didn't even do the
ding-ding
a uh where was it where was it oh
[\h__\h] here
here uh per Eric's instructions we must
execute the 43 newly delivered pigs he
says they aren't pure enough or
something they aren't pure enough order
more order more he's also requesting
that we produce more rat embryos of uh
type 16 bre also just a reminder to
perform the usual nightly cleaning
routine you forgot last time clean the
bloody Machinery sweep the floors and uh
dust off the PES and deposit them in the
bag the PES oh and uh that's a Bastian
kid he's not affected by the sleeping
gas he's noted
by find something stronger something
stronger he's not wait one last thing he
knows that those pigs we need to
reorder Eric says he wants exactly 98
pigs exactly 98 okay what does that
matter not 100
98 got that why do it will be terminated
if the count is off by one shut up now
Eric words not mine wait so that wasn't
Eric uh but Eric knows that the sleeping
gas doesn't work on the
chicken I
suppose so if I turn it on with this
knowledge I now know it will only kill
me why does it know that I'm
here I should still be hidden one
[Music]
two come down come down go somewh
somewhere else
no oh do I like get it to go over here
if I do
that 100 with me then why does why does
it need to be that though why does it
need to be
100 oh he meant it works ah it works on
ah it's doesn't work on Sebastian sorry
I'm confusing Sebastian thinking it's
the chicken
sometimes oh okay oh that's good
then that it doesn't work on Sebastian
oh so where is this room again I
can't was this
way yeah yeah
yeah
okay I'm in the room room
but I don't want to be affected by the
gas right but like can I go anywhere
where there is no
gas it was going to go for here probably
and here and
here let's press it let's try
it yes yes thank you thank you compl
level three you have no idea how much
this means for yeah I'm going to die but
maybe he's going to um save me the the
the the guy the
Sebastian maybe he going to save
me wow that wasn't too bad
yay chicken is asleep I'm asleep I would
thank you oh uh I can hear him I never
actually learned your
name not that I needed to or even wanted
to you did well as an intern and I'm
sorry I had to end this way your
sacrifices in the name of science
what
Eric how how did you it's over
Eric it's over it's gone down please
it's going to save me
don't please oh
yeah two shots one for the chicken one
for
Eric you me we never worthy of
forgiveness me no him right I'm worthy
of forgiveness
for you yeah I'm so
sorry this world didn't deserve
you and you
deserved so much am I going to die
[Music]
anyway did he kill himself
actually or did he kill me
why am I alive
you're
safe hi I killed Eric nice he's gone
good job he can't hurt us
anymore Cooper's also gone okay good job
it's better this way he was filled with
too much pain and anger he was never
going to return to normal mhm he
deserves peace why you're so nice she I
told you for the first time ever I am
free oh dear you and I we share
something
special we are
human I don't know about you I don't
know about
[Music]
you I am
human
um
I uh
uhoh
uhoh I am human
uhoh uhoh just shoot me just shoot me
oh okay h
I did it I I did it I completed chicken
feed y I'm so proud of myself oh that
was so painful in the
beginning add it to the list add it to
the list add it to the list of games I
didn't
miss oh my God Sebastian was
Dylan best
oh the the
human
oh that was I I did have a feeling that
that was that was going to be like you
know that that he was going to be nice
actually I didn't immediately understand
that Eric was going to be the evil one
but
yeah oh my God thank you for playing no
thank you for
for letting me have this experience that
was actually um raising my
confidence I I'm I'm proud of myself for
actually finishing
this cuz first level I was so terrified
second I was gaining confidence third
was
easy I'm so proud of you thank
you
K I did it for you I did it for you
we're never going to see such a big ass
chicken ever again I'm I'm not going to
let them do this to you anymore I'm not
going to let them turn you into a
monster anymore I'm going to protect you
I promise I'm sorry for selling you to
that company I he today ster a big
amount of money and I really needed it
cuz I needed to pay my taxes I'm so
sorry I I won't do it again I really
forgive me you know I love you right
right I love you I just wanted I I
thought he would be the doing well over
[Music]
there I'm sorry it was only one I was
only one
I I won't do it again I just wanted the
best for
you I just wanted you to grow big and
strong but it seems like it was a
mistake you should stay small and
chunky
yeah okay you forgive me yeah
oh thank
[Music]
you you're cute the way you are you
don't need to grow big and
strong you're
fine just like
[Music]
that oh
man I was intense though W horror games
are intense and
tiring
sheesh DLC [\h__\h] no why is there a
DLC I don't have it is it free I don't
want it I'm
done DLC doesn't
count how long is
it it's
free I saw something on the home
screen no no I don't need that in my
life I I don't need
it
uh no no it's done it's done the game is
done mhm it's very short no I'm I'm I
I'm mentally I have closed this chapter
less than 30 minutes of game
plan M Hony
really 20 minutes well but people also
said this game was going to be 1 hour
and I still took 2
hours [\h__\h]
hell is this a
prequel and game finisher not DLC
finisher
grateful yeah yeah I am I can't
R uh find a find a
way okay
uh
uh everybody
hey don't close no way
man well what this is when he just grew
big and and then everybody's was like
[\h__\h] I'm out of here or
what no way man [\h__\h]
you
exit
oh wait are these is this the same
layout
okay okay okay but this doesn't this
room is like dead end the chicken won't
get in there what was that for ah one
one green light
okay got to find more of
those is there one in
here
see
[Music]
one a the music holy
[\h__\h] just going to keep on
running is this the room where I already
was
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah oh oh that's interesting that's
interesting
looking oh
blue it's hard to see [\h__\h] oh
God huh oh oh oh
[\h__\h]
okay
okay so no need to go to to the blue
part anymore right but where's the last
one I have a hard
time
understanding where is
what it what like
n you can't have seen me like I was on
the other side maybe ah maybe cuz I
wasn't like crouching inside like again
only this counts
[Music]
maybe no it's not going to take more
than 20 minutes no no
no maybe it wants me to be fast in this
one all right what's here
before I've been here
before let's go that left
way don't know when though is there
really nothing
here I music so loud chill a little
bit where is music I can't see music
music is it too loud
[Music]
guys
wait that's pretty loud holy [\h__\h] that's
loud on OBS okay little
bit okay just just went
by oh hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi
hi and
goodbye where is the next
one there's two lights now where have I
not
gone oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] is this this is a room I haven't
seen ah there it is there it is there it
[Music]
is okay I he's going to wait there for a
while huh he knows that's my last
lever
H okay you can go thank you and then I
have to find my way back to
the the actual exit door my my feeling
of uh direction is
really wrecked right
now oh oh it's right there yo is that
it is there another level it's too
simple it's too
[Music]
easy oh the music is calming
down honor of Cooper
burn the evidence burn the evidence All
Pro of
rebirth it's too late to
think we've lost our Second Chances
we've got work to
do they want to prove they want to
delete all the
evidence but it seems like they didn't I
found a bunch of
it
oh it's a hole I have to fall down here
oh no it's bloody bloody
helmet okay now I feel like I'm going
down a a water slide in the park go go
go go go
go I'm safe I'm safe thank you for your
Relentless dedication to science uh-huh
science do for science facility is
currently under lockdown employees are
expected to shelter in place all exits
are locked until further
notice please contact facility
authorities for more information I did
it an error has been detected in the
elevator system contacting support teams
no take action as soon as
possible
a wo wo w w w w w w wo what if I jump
can I jump does that
help am I
dead just Out Of
Reach maybe you'll do
it no maybe another
day what did
no complete level one of chicken feed
breakout how many are
there
oh I asked you a
question 10 Dr
brand another
ghost please just leave me alone
I'm
scared I'm safe in here I'm
safe are you
though are you
really evolve
[\h__\h] Val sponsor me please find a Val
and use it to unlock the the
exit about to hear there's a
button what it do oh I closed it closed
the
door
man
mankind
oh sponsor me please B I need a b right
now I need a bve
urgently where's the chicken where's the
[Music]
Val where am I oh is is here
again oh man man what is this hiding
place
okay no chicken yet probably only
chicken when I get Val or something like
that can you leave the lights on
permanently
please let's hear
it this is Dan brand of sector 6 I'm
hurt and bleeding bad stomach wound I
got attacked after getting separated
from John and
Charlie and now I'm
here and it's it's not looking good the
radio's dead and I'm getting lightheaded
me
too Sophia H if you're somehow listening
to this
I just
please know that I love you I'm Ki I
know things could have been
better I just wish I'd realized it
sooner once this is all over we'll see
each other again we'll run far from this
place and we'll be
free both of
us under the
stars I
promise man I'm going to find her I just
wish I had another chance I'm going to
relay your message don't
worry key is it on you
no wait
so there's just the door and
that's oh seems like I have activated
the
chicken
wonderful damn is it because I found the
[Music]
person I'd like to find the Val maybe
now some doors are open again I don't
know oh
man okay this
uh damn
it damn it where could it
[Music]
be I activate all the chickens they
just they just are gra gravitated
towards me is that how you say it oh
there it
is I wasn't sure if the the the shadow
was
like
okay go away go away go away is that the
door that's closed now huh can I open
it
sh is this
open
no
okay
uh
guys still ordering the Polaroids huh
don't know if I can finish that today
[Music]
then that's
close I prefer the like fast running
sections I mean maybe I could run fast
here too but doesn't give off the same
Vibe you know like the emergency
Vibe 200 over 200 how much did I have
last
time M
Mia [\h__\h] it go
here okay no chicken
inside yeah yeah I know I died thank you
it's pretty
obvious like
80 last time I had like 80 for
real that is uh
yaai hey what would you guys think if I
signed them off stream or do you want to
see
it cuz that's going to take a
while
H please do it off screen you can do it
off screen I would prefer off screen you
would prefer
it no problem either way I like to see
but you would need to do a special
stream of it stream because it's
cuter I don't mind either way whatever
works for
you
H yeah the thing is the we week is
pretty busy and actually you know when I
was talking about the
schedule uh you know how you you guys
were like oh don't play FF take the day
off take the day off and so I tried to
but then I was notified of another like
Minecraft related
stream that I should probably be at so I
might not be there like for the whole
thing but I figured I should be there at
least I will not be
scared what is this [\h__\h] I don't have
the valve y I don't know where it
is
I don't know where to hide here either
or can it even go
through yeah yeah no there's like two um
there's one that's mainly practice and
then there's one that's that's practice
and like they call it zenya side it's
like a the night the evening before
celebration or something like
that b is probably behind the door that
needs a key a key now I need a key too
but no this looks like it opens with a
Val anyway okay yeah I can't go through
here
okay oh I haven't seen
[Music]
anything and I mean it's it's it's
voluntary but I'm also the like
appointed leader of my group in English
leader kind
of so I feel like I also should be there
for sake of like translating for other
members who want to be there um and yeah
it's fine it's probably not going to be
too
long where is it the
chicken yeah so no break day but there
are like days where the streams are
really
short so it I'll be fine I'll I'll be
fine I'll be
fine I could also still say okay no
member stream this week to make it a
little bit easier on my schedule we can
decide that the like cuz the member
stream currently that I want to do cuz
I'm currently in case you don't know I'm
doing member stream weekly at the
[Music]
moment can't I can't find it I
can't
that's here again does he have it doing
M streams Weekly right now and
um uh the one for this week it would be
at Sun On Sunday I think so we can just
go through the week and see if like at
the end of the week I I have like the
energy and stuff for it but no matter
what I think it'll be a watch along this
time cuz we have been doing other stuff
anyway recently
watch along should be chill
so we'll find a way to make it all work
out yeah where the [\h__\h] is this
n I'm not even really scared anymore so
I just I'm just frustrated I can't find
it where is the
thing what are you watching I don't know
we could continue things we started
watch watching
before there's nothing
here
either Home
Improvement are you fine with bit
perfect
too oh people actually say that's what B
too
oh Violet ever got a movie
H I think I'll just watch that on my
own did I not watch it
yet Val
do was I using a Vive or valve I always
like don't
remember I'm I I know I'm using the one
that the other girls are not using
that's the only thing I remember the one
that's supposedly less
good oh I'm using the Vive oh man yeah
yeah I am yeah see even more reason for
valve to sponsor me I would like a valve
cuz like the hand trackers are better
cuz for Vive you have to hold it uh and
you can't get like finger tracking you
have to control it yourself with
buttons and the other girls were always
able to just like I don't know there's
like a ring around your hand or
something and so it tracks your finger
movements somewhat a little bit it's
pretty pretty nice I wish I had
that huh
what [\h__\h] hell I can't find
it
[\h__\h] is this key in the
valve is it in the dark wouldn't it
still like have to glow up maybe it's
like maybe the thing is like I can only
see it
when the
light is red that's not often so I have
to pay
attention
H it's not
here Val index headset is better quality
but only one finger tracking you can get
the controls separately well but you
know I honestly I don't I don't care
anymore about investing in my VR setup I
think because I am investing
$30,000 plus into my home fore
set up
so okay let's go
here eh 13 what did I say
13 not
13 still
enough
maybe the the key is hidden in the feety
fluffy butt of the
chicken yeah but that's the that's the
like the
first um the one time payment but then
there will be like some monthly payments
and whatever month I want to use it I
have to pay for the um like software
it's a subscription if you want to like
stream it stream with it you need that
so blah
blah I don't
know I can't see
anything n
this
up its
butt unity's business
model
yeah yeah
so not cool oh what about this button by
the way about
oh oh a this is just another opening for
that
room my pinky
[Music]
hurts
ah I found
it wa which room is this is this one I
just
opened K
get n in Minecraft when I crouch too
much my pinky will also start
hurting by the way the games the games
that sign up up for I'm still not sure
what they assigned me for I signed up
for like three games and you get signed
up for two I'm like I could do this and
this and
this I
wonder do you guys know yet what kind of
games there are cuz I think people can
already stream their practices so you
may have seen them
already are they all new games yeah
pretty much pretty much yeah there's
some surprising
ones there's no bread eating
[Music]
context okay the key we go to
the the room where the dead dud this or
what where is that room
again this is the valve
room
so not here huh
okay where was it
again there was a jumping to eat
the oh maybe there is I don't remember
that you have the valve no I have the
key oh it's just part of the obstacle
race you open the stream to a jump scare
oh you missed all the biggest scares
though cuz I'm not scared anymore I mean
I I I can't help but scream when it's
chasing me a little
bit but I'm not really that terrified
anymore thank God it's just it's just
like with um
Outlast quite quite scared um
initially I then you just get used to
it yeah I got some great scares out of
me are you happy I don't [\h__\h]
remember where I got to go
though y y y y y y y y y y y y
y this is it this is it yeah you always
this is the this is the key literally or
not literally you got to have the thing
that you're scared of Chase you and then
just naturally you will run towards the
the place where you actually got to go
nice I got
it
woohoo get to the valve trackers
now I have to remember where that ah I
know it's through the the room through
the the opening that's like like a slit
yeah the
narrow the narrow
opening was there a way to get there
from the right
side maybe
not
smart am smart so smart it hurt my brain
H oh I could go from
here but it's hard to see chicken is
[Music]
there there was but you closed it oh
when I open the other door oh
okay
oh I hear
chicken chicken from left side oh yes oh
yes chicken come to the other side yeah
go go you can do it you're a big chicken
who's a big
chicken now is an insult of
course
[Music]
um was that what was that what was that
I made it I made
it That Shook Me To The Core that
opening wasn't how I remembered it that
was weird [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm
weak level two complete I guess it also
has three
levels
interesting [\h__\h] my arm my
arm my arm hurts from the
shock uh Panic Strat just run at least
now when I run
I'm I'm quite confident with it I hate
it when I don't see where I'm
going dead
end and this way
oh [\h__\h] my arm also my Thum it hurts so
bad when I woke up the night before my
uh I put a lot of like um healing cream
wound cream
B on it and then I put the Band-Aid on
top and I slept with that and when I
woke up it hurt so
bad and I noticed I
noticed when I took off the
bandage that's a small one
no when I took it off I think like a
little bit of like some liquid is like
coming out of it just a tiny amount is
that bad or
good the [\h__\h] was that chicken
though is this where I came from
no or is
it is this where I came from and then I
this door was open so now the chicken
opened it up or
something
yeah maybe I infected it [\h__\h] hell
you guys and you guys are like oh you
sharp knives is better you won't get
hurt and now I cut myself with a sharp
knife and I even get an infected great
but now it's feeling better now I think
is it no well it still kind hurts to the
touch I've had this like for a week now
and it's a tiny cut it's infu a tiny
cut it's not a blister no oh oh he's
gone of course yeah I'm not spooked by
that that's for beginners that's spook
Halloween for
beginners yeah [\h__\h]
you God damn
it
God the the the light is like even worse
now I've lost
interest I've lost
interest just let me
throw your patience wa probably the last
level
probably it's dark for so long
wait can I still go this
way would I not want to do that makes no
sense probably just go this
way you fell asleep during this stream
how can you fall asleep during this
stream
no I wasn't even trying to run
[Music]
I don't want to my screams are healing
banshe she
screams
chicken oh
oh 1 2
three I don't believe
it what's
the 1 2 three one 2
three 1 2
3 can it be so simple I'm going one two
one 2 three that's the real code it's
not one 2 3 it's 1 2 one two
3 is that like an actual like proper
order what happens when I do this ah
okay depending on which one I have
pushed it probably opens certain
doors go
away go
away
go
yeah that's
right [\h__\h] it's so
dark it's so
[Music]
dark ah Trigg
me
oh I don't like
it
oh this is the door that
opened bunk
bends nothing else though did I let
somebody Escape no there's no one in
here right yeah let's
listen this is Ken from sector 1 I
should have left when I had the chance
this place isn't right it distorts
reality I mean Sebastian was born a
completely healthy human boy But as time
went on he became sick unhuman
monstrous and Cooper yeah Cooper was
born a completely normal chicken oh
really but he grew grew like a weed
sheesh within a couple weeks he was
doubled the size of the others yeah and
now this happens and I think I saw who
did it it was an older woman she broke
through the security and unlocked the
cage old woman she looked Vaguely
Familiar couldn't have been a former
worker though I'm I'm a young woman she
released Cooper she yelled something
yeah I was trying to rescue him
understand all of it but I'm almost
certain she said Sebastian
name I don't know I was trying to that
doesn't matter now fix the situation I'm
getting out of here so should you he's
calling me
old okay but then one of
these ah number one has a a
screwdriver number two doesn't seem to
have
anything okay we got to go back to that
[Music]
room uh I think I came from here
[\h__\h] I hate this I hate
this ah yeah okay good number one should
have just gone with number one
huh but no I want to be
special what something I felt like
something pushed me to the
side h
what do I do with
this maybe in the second room maybe
there's something I could open with that
no
no what are the other rooms for then
just to trigger me to confuse
[Music]
me a gate of the
light not here
right I saw a vent next to the switch
room next to that
room
[Music]
oh that came out of
nowhere
h i just appeared out of nowhere it was
so quiet I was like this is suspicious
anyway do I have it I don't have
it ah no way we start from here
ah this one
mhm oh my
god oh okay now hold on then I know
where I
am
okay number
one room one may no no I I saw the vent
yeah yeah I saw it just now I perceived
it didn't I come from
here
optic illusion or
what wait wait I'm
confused imagine a change when get a
game open no but I came from there like
then would would it have already been
different
it did the tape say it changes reality
nah no
way it's
real it's real maybe now it's not door
one
anymore
ah what if it's not door one
[Music]
what if it's it's probably not door one
let's go with door
three
ah resetting me to the
beginning but then changing the reality
that I know
maybe I can maybe what if I let myself
get caught a few times until I return to
the reality that I
know big
brain just cycle through all the
options okay um but like what the
hell this is the
vent
I have to go this way there's not even
any other option now oh
[\h__\h] oh that's
something what is this room the
beginning
no my f my my
[Music]
finger
do you think it
change do you think it changes again
maybe no not my fump my fump is okay my
my pinky is not
okay maybe it's set up so you can only
move forward in the same clock Direction
why would I do that get that check the
week is a long
time should I turn on the hand Cam and
show you
I currently have a Band-Aid on again I
basically like sometime I put it on
sometime I don't cuz like I notice when
I don't it's just like I I I slept one
whole night without it but it didn't
heal much at all like not at all and I
noticed like when I do things during the
day
that like the way I I I use my Thum it
like I feel like the the
opening when the wound is like on the
side a little bit like open
still I
can
uh
like like I feel like I just kept keep
on touching it and like it's it's
sensitive it hurts and then it opens up
again like it's constantly open
though yeah I do change it like pretty
much every every day sometimes even
twice a day the
Band-Aids stop touching it I need my fum
it's literally like I need it every day
it's on my
mouse let me go and
see
no I didn't disinfect it but I washed it
with water sometimes a little bit of
soap
maybe didn't try to like touch it too
much though I I didn't want to irritate
it I'm trying to not irritate
it all right we run oh oh think get it
right no don't tell me it's still one no
it's number
two it's number
two ah
mag I'm going one two one two three so
so so sweet when you go and kiss me I'm
taking aect
picture you stuck to me like a
there it is
hi
I will not let you do this for much
longer
oh it went around the corner there's a
you can walk around the
corner y y y y y y y y y y y y y y y
uh [\h__\h] I'm here again where is
[Music]
the I don't care I don't care there
there there no [\h__\h] it that's
not there there
there okay okay okay uh so number two
okay but now I went
through didn't I come from that side
again
it does change it does
change
Chang maybe the wall is only on one side
but now I am on that side again where
the wall was
but maybe after walking through it
once it's just fine now who
knows okay went that
way big fluffy shadow
butd
no go back
now
[Music]
away depends on where the chicken passes
for
maybe went left
again again don't have much more
patience you might want to like move on
now if you want more screen time on W
more
Channel don't
stupidly drag it
out
he came
[Music]
back can't push this button
anymore C works too actually maybe I'll
go with
C let try
see but then shift running is also still
there with with my with my small smaller
finger where is the chicken now huh
where did it go I didn't pay attention
probably that way again to trigger
me why is it why is it shifting oh wait
you can do
that
oh
[Applause]
you can
slide it scared
me it scared
[Music]
me the
magic at the end of the
DLC took me long enough wait so what now
the vent the vent [\h__\h] if I get caught
again I might not have the patience to
do it
again the
vent wa so where would it be I go that
way or that way left or right
guys
right it's currently too F again have
you guys noticed he's waiting for me to
come out he's going to where whatever
Direction I go he will be behind me
basically or right in front of
me was he in front of me last time and I
turn around or [\h__\h]
hell yeah is running the only
option
[\h__\h] but it was like immediately so
close to me last
time how do you do
this it's just waiting for me it's just
going to warp Wherever I
Go
get to the buttons first but it's still
going to be it's like I think I went
that way and then it showed up
here but now I know now I know how to
slide oh
[\h__\h] commit commit commit no okay [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] where
where wait I know that was the best but
like how why do I have
time okay n hold
off don't so wait I I saw
it wait Did I was it behind me in front
of me I'm
confused think it was
behind no it was the same situation but
this time I I I ran away
faster m was behind me
right oh this time it's not quiet he's
he's there I already triggered him he do
be walking around probably a little bit
oh oh yeah that's good that's good
that's better than not sensing him at
all there he
is I think I prefer that was this way
really the shter way
though
my fingers are
not capable of this
anymore sh my
finger it's not smooth anymore where is
it
where's it coming
from
y y'all
attention all employees of goober
Laboratories my friends it's time to
give up yeah we had a good run I'm fine
but not all good things are meant to
last thank you thank you for your
Relentless dedication to sence this is
like um thank you and good night what
was that
game it reminds me of a lot of these
funny games of
narrators portal yeah science Aperture
[Music]
Science when is the chicken going to
come HH when is it going to Shook Me
[Music]
h
oh that um brick walled exit will open
up when I push this
probably that's the last thing I might
have to do maybe and then some Parkour
here should we
practice and exit wait okay but where is
it going to come from the chicken just
doesn't seem like there's much room to
play like it's not going to pass through
here is
it I I push and then I
run and then it shows up maybe I don't
know where but how is
that well no matter what no matter what
checkpoint is
basically here
so let's test it out let's get my my
stamina
back
wait
[Music]
oh
wee touch down
okay I could go for here to ah maybe I
have to do that I maybe I have to use
all the possible shortcuts probably
probably okay wait wait wait wait
wait we we we start and imagine imagine
practice run push H [\h__\h]
wrong St false
start
push that way I saved the
most steps that I possibly
could okay okay see I I fought
everything through question is only
where's the chicken coming
from
h
what if it's not a chicken this
time okay I can do
it parkour
parkour oh a [\h__\h] I see ah it's not even
about a chicken it's really just about
uh being the most efficient in time I I
I I had a problem there that's
[Laughter]
okay that's that's a lot of speed though
sit how far away can I push
it oh from
[Music]
here
okay too
far
uh here over here here may
here
ah it's when the it's when it gets big
okay that's when it works H okay so here
okay gosh
it yeah yeah I crouch too early and then
I get slow too
slow
that's
fine what is this last section not even
being chased it's just about most
efficiently getting through this
parkour
okay
here
[\h__\h]
knock
H what I can't get much faster than
this d That's slide a few
times
okay that was pretty
smooth oh that was
faster that was kind of slower again
[Music]
H right let's start from the
[Laughter]
corner got to try
again okay
okay
I feel like an like an athlete right
now [\h__\h] I'm not even going to try
it tick tock ticktock ticktock it's
already closed
Dam okay
okay three two
one
ah ah
ah
push and push
ah push no too early [\h__\h] what is this
part of the game what is this
push
okay okay okay okay
okay [\h__\h] n that's not it that's not it
that's not
it did M do this too did M do all of
this
game I
wonder at least not scary yeah right now
I appreciate that I
guess guess she didn't do the DLC
okay you little
[\h__\h] no no no that's not
it false
start why am I stuck here so
stupid
h no who that's a [\h__\h] Millie second
there
what it's like a you should have put
this in the beginning of the game is
like a parkour training or like slide
training and all that dad cuz like I
didn't even know about sliding until
very
recently is that blood on the
floor is
it can't see
[\h__\h] yeah
yeah yeah not a big
deal not
surprising what was this
part nothing
just a bit of tomato juice speaking of
tomato juice going to make
boness boness I think after this I
bought some
ingredients oh [\h__\h] hell
man oh yeah okay I see I
understand
oh yeah okay that's why they did
[Laughter]
that what are you trying to
say
I do I do be getting a second chance
though okay I just need to turn around
[Music]
faster going take
me I got stuck on the wall or
something yeah shut up shut up shut
up uh I have to it seems like I have to
minmax this
too think I should turn to the left but
I want to turn to the right I just like
it
more it's more
intuitive
[Music]
okay wait I was I was sliding there a
little bit at the end uh cuz I thought
maybe maybe maybe they want me to slide
like why else would they teach me
uh I died wait it's different
now
what why is the sentence different
different uh but seems like I may have
had to jump or should I slide there at
the I slide I slid too early I guess
maybe I have to slide at the end of that
bridge cuz why else would they teach
[Music]
me slide
jump how do you slide
jump you can't you can't do that I
I that's not really a thing I think
maybe the slide comes after I run jump I
guess what is this
Apex yeah this is run I guess okay huh
why did you teach me to
slide
and
go run run run run run run run run run
run run run run run run run run run run
run run run run run run
run what did I learn the sliding
for
oh well you have The High Ground you
deserve this wait what what are you
going to do with that but maybe you
do you made it further than of your
colleagues so I congratulate
you that doesn't mean you
won not
yet you're free to go wa wait Chien
walking
backwards myit that's funny I don't
think a chicken would naturally walk
backwards do they do that that's so
funny to
me
just like a car
[Music]
she on why am I turning around so
slowly I'm
shaking are you regretful scientist yeah
you asked me that before regretful of
the experiments yeah yes I am regretful
of my Escape KP already forgot forgave
me something else
entirely do you wish you could go back
make different decisions yeah that's
what retrospective is
about all you humans are the same it's
too late for that
now however you've been given a
gift you are the only
Survivor the only one with a second
chance never forget
that you and I we something special we
do kfp we do we are alive we are and
many are
not
yeah I I if they're nice if they were
good
chickens I might revive
them well that's pretty hey I
exited
oh really happy
ending more or less really suddenly
chicken shoots me from behind or
something like
that
huh
huh okay I double completed this
game hope you're happy
now that was more than 20 minutes
though we did it I did it I freaking did
it yeah
yeah chicken
[Music]
defeated defeated that chicken Fe
defeated I was
exhaused thank you for playing thank you
for making a
game see if I would have played it
earlier then I probably would have not
played at DLC ever cuz it wouldn't be
out yet and then I wouldn't play it just
for the DLC again so it's good that I
waited for today thanks for the
membership
download so oh the dude I don't want to
see this anymore I want to get out of
here skidadle I don't want to see
anything scary anymore until tomorrow
when I play Fatal Frame what do you
think is scarier Fatal Frame or
this
genuinely want to know Fatal Frame
easily no no
no
no no
no has cute girls at least
yeah it's way scarier Oh Oh that's oh
too bad I'm I'm kind of like weirdly
feeling like um like I'm getting a cold
or like my tummy h i I think I have a
tummy flu oh too bad I might be too sick
[Music]
tomorrow
H oh man okay let me check something um
just I'm I want to make sure it's
happening right it's happening right
what Fatal Frame Fatal
Frame po
Rosses
uh
well be
fine it says waiting for reply I I
entered it like a week
ago let me ask
jenar
JMA my Fatal Frame request say still
waiting
[Music]
a week
ago I got to play it tomorrow but last
time we had something like this you know
when I was like uh I don't know if it's
going to be okay no wait I don't know if
even told you about it but for Age of
Vampires and Final Fantasy last
week um like two days before or so it
also looked like nobody even touched it
yet and then it was fine then it was
fine
anyway I did tell
you it might be fine it might just
always be like a last minute
approval H we'll see I I'll go on um
I'll continue to
plan uh towards it um so okay you know
what are we goingon to what are we what
we are going to do
if I understand
correctly last time I did the polar
WS
uh I got like 80 80 or 90 right and it
was like it took a while
um
right now how many did you say I have
accumulated let's see
Hyer
230 yeah so um holy
[\h__\h] I thought it would be less cuz you
already got polar wordss recently guys
but these are special I guess damn 2
there's 232 pinkies and nine Reds even
though it's you could have gotten it
with a
pinky
um you crazy crazy crazy
people
crazy people it was too good of a
deal I might have
contributed so you know what we're going
to do I will sort it I will read all the
super chats now that are not
pinkies
uh there's not
many um and I will read them out loud so
it's like a normal super chat reading
and then the pinkies and the Reds also
later on I uh throughout the week I will
write the Polaroids and I will upload
them on the community board cuz there's
230 how long did it take me last time 2
hours through S
80 uh yeah but don't worry they'll turn
out
great you still need clarification for a
name number as I was in few yeah if
there's no like please sign it with this
name then I'll just sign it with your
actual name and uh
yeah it be fine holy [\h__\h]
man yeah this way I think I'll I'll be
like at least somewhat fast if I do it
off stream cuz I don't tangent
and yeah I
can I can set it up uh smoother
maybe eh no I mean your your
username anyway that was like uh part
one of my Halloween streams tomorrow is
part two uh and then that's it um it's
too much for
my small
smaller soft Phoenix Soul uh that's
enough horror for the whole
year but I'm proud of myself I'm quite
proud of myself feel like I I made great
progress so I went through the whole
thing even D you'll see my throat hurts
a little a little
bit so another reason to not do it
now but yeah horor cro met proud of you
too thank you enough horror for eternity
well at least for for one
year but tomorrow with Dana actually
we're playing Fatal Frame which in case
you don't know if you're like a little
bit newer me and Lena were trying to get
this going last year and I did an oopsy
and applied too late uh to per
marinos um but yeah we were going to do
it last year and I even have the
thumbnail still somewhere ah there it is
I don't even I don't even have to make
the
thumbnail it's already
done the hecking per marinos
[Applause]
pretty I need to figure figure out who
did the fan art cuz I don't remember
anymore it's too long made this one year
ago that's such a cool fan art
right a collab one year in the making
yeah it's tomorrow at uh I I was you
know cuz it's with Raina um it's earlier
in the day for you guys because you know
she's in the time zone over there so I
thought um we'll do it like Japanese
prime
time
yeah so
uh let me turn on the bgm it's not going
to be long I guess
but yeah one more thing I have to do
after the stream is make the schedule so
I make the schedule then I'll cook and
did I have something else to do I could
sign some Polaroids already damn now I
have to I have to sign
D I didn't think I'd have to sign so
many
[\h__\h] cuz like I also have you know the
the actual merchandise um The
Anniversary merchandise polar rewards
too but it's okay I'm making progress
with those too and and and I still have
a lot of time for those but why am I
giving myself so much extra
work but I you know I want to give you
guys something special too and and yeah
so I think everyone's a
while I want to do this for you there
might be something else happening
tomorrow that you guys might want to see
but I'm not
[Music]
sure um we'll
see we'll
see is there is it is
there
tomorrow
no no maybe not tomorrow oh but did you
see Hat's coming
back do you
see
[Applause]
finally I hope she's back like for real
for
real
finally it's going to be I think the the
the mood and the atmosphere is going to
be brighter with her back
everybody's going to be
[Music]
happy
yay I I dm'd her when I heard that she's
coming back I DM her like I'm so happy
oh my God I we were waiting welcome
back I'm sure she's getting bombarded
right now but she even
replied oh let's go here
just for a moment
oh oh it's capturing my I think it's
capturing my uh my Photoshop
oopsie thank God that was the thing I
had open in Photoshop and not something
else
yay Halloween them room
yay
o is there some RPG game jrpg game that
you guys are looking forward to right
now that's coming soon
anyone
uhhuh
uh-huh
[Music]
uhhuh uh-huh
aha
[Music]
mm
uhuh
well uhhuh uhhuh uh-uh
uh-huh
uhhuh uhhuh
uhhuh oh
[Music]
interesting 4 while I stay away not
scared anymore I've been through the
trials of
Hell aka the usual
room oh no not
more h no I'm not hinting
H just trying to see what you guys are
like paying attention to in general in
terms of
games just a personal
interest let me explain it to Japanese
Bros too if there are any
here
so I'm just going to read the the
smaller ones and I I will read the red
ones too just because they they I think
no I guess what did I did I give them
kisses I didn't even give them kisses
anymore I guess I don't have to read
them really I'll I'll I'll look through
them quickly on
stream let's see
uh unknown dangun just to see if there's
anything I like I should be
answering in case they ask a question
they would like to be answered I some
magic d space wonderful
D thank
you spicy
chicken thank you Bo
73 D Dusty
D see St stuff like this I wouldn't want
to miss happy belated birthday Dusty it
was this
month can't I can't miss another year
without celebrating it with my cute
kamhi yeah let's
go happy late birthday thank you for
telling me I don't know what exactly it
was hopefully it's not on Halloween
isn't on
Halloween
although like it could be good to have
your birthday on Halloween because you
can like there's always parties going on
you can just you don't even have to plan
your own party you just go to someone
else's
party Halloween party and who doesn't
like to have a dress up birthday
party that's awesome it was the 12 okay
then then that won't work
out
well done happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your pants too happy birthday to you
Dusty time to dust yourself off get that
dust off of
you a new year a new you right or or the
same you same you is fine too
but don't let don't let the dust get to
you
haty you'll be Dusty again you're just
Dusty in general makes me think of the
dust bunnies from Sims those are really
cute man are you a Dust
Bunny
cue a kiss a birthday kiss
link d delsa d King DOA Chief D doomsday
Dan great night
Rex Mr
[Music]
Big
Rene thank
you oh you liked my end of the world
voice B thank
you there's another pretty nice one
upcoming I'm not sure when they're
releasing it but maybe sooner rather
than
later H and the next one is kind of
special for a
reason but yeah if you got to listen to
that you
forgot I get all the voice thank you
yeah end of the world was pretty
cool
abson you finally got a job offer for
the place you wanted to work at I don't
want to thank you wait you're not even
going for Polaroid
Epsilon Epsilon or did you send a
separate pinky or something like that
that are you here absolon just making
sure for when I sign these
things now's your chance if you want
to give me a
note otherwise I'll choose one for you
and I just sign it for you whether you
want it or not you got the voice bag and
you forgot to listen to it
Nan how can
you yeah it's an easy way to to support
us
H well doesn't seem like he's here H
maybe maybe he sent a separate message
not sure but I might just give you a
random
one then you can also write me a Twitter
message if you hear this uh in the VA
and it's not too
late my voice is ASMR level in there
what what
what
[Music]
oh well for now you get a kiss and I'm
glad you found a job that you actually
like from now on it will go hopefully
only up up up
up I'm glad that you you know persevered
through the harder times good job good
job for holding
out Spectre F Baron sky
so that's all the non
pinkies so I will go
now and I will um make the schedule
immediately I'm so sorry it's so late
but it's going to it's going to look
nice cuz there's going to be a stream
every day
woohoo
y I had fun today even though that was
terrifying and exhausting I feel better
now though
[Music]
hope you enjoyed watching me for once
with very extreme
emotions doesn't happen often you got
some good screams some good
noises freaked out
wahwah don't do members this week and
even if I don't that's still not a day
off but there would be a really short
stream only on the day we'll see I'll
put it on the schedule for now and then
as I said if I feel not up to it at the
end of the week then we can still cancel
[Music]
it it be fine I mean there's some stuff
that I still have to I still have so
much to plan off stream for the 3D
birthday uh delayed birthday
live um there's like there's so much
behind the scenes
like and I also have to learn the dances
still and um now I also have to figure
out what to do with the MV
like I don't know it's
like the
suit it's a little bit of an annoying
[Music]
situation with the suit at the moment I
don't know if they're going to send it
out anytime
soon
um so I'm thinking now I'm
thinking I really want wanted to be Frey
and I want it to be within
November but it might just have to take
longer which is bad it's bad for a
reason I don't really want it to be
after November cuz then it just makes no
sense it doesn't fulfill its
purpose but I might have to
yeah and I don't want to like change the
plan now
because
no I kind of committed to it and it
already has a
coral and I have an idea for it
now um December is your birthday life
yeah if it really doesn't work out if
they really don't send the suit now in
time then maybe I'll release it around
the birthday
life but it won't fulfill its purpose
that pisses me
off oh
well oh
well want it be too close to your vision
release no I don't even know like when
that's no no I don't even know when that
would come out when I would put it
out
maybe I'll do it a little bit earlier
then like a week or so before the
birthday life I don't
know well there's many things to figure
out many things to take care
of
but oh it will be all fine it will be
all figured out it'll be all good in the
[Music]
end
okay so I hope everybody is fine if I
sign these things uh off
stream complaints please send them
to the usual room please deliver your
complaints to the usual room in
person put it on the table in the usual
room yes the door will stay open if you
walk in yeah it will not close behind
[Music]
you just put it on the table I will I
will pick it up from
there what did you read Super Chat of
the last two
[Music]
streams did
I oh maybe I didn't the last one
[Music]
stream
Oh you mean Family Feud and Final
Fantasy I completely ignored Family Feud
cuz probably doesn't have
much FF and the
FF okay okay we can do that we can do
that no problem no problem no
[Music]
problem family field has a little bit
little bit okay okay
okay
k no no Final Fantasy yum mon let's read
super chats from Final
Fantasy yesterday that was yesterday it
already feels like two days ago cuz I've
been I've been I had a long sleep after
Family Feud relatively
long something between a nap and a full
[Music]
sleep 12 hours left for Final Fantasy
more or less
[Music]
oh probably kind of two
streams interesting you checked other
streams I
[Music]
see you want to play it
yourself that's okay that's fine I
understand
[Music]
well two should be fine two streams
should be
fine okay jaob 47 D ah oh ah did you oh
you got it back y let's
go
nice now you have like two
accounts that have like the wait your
other account what badge does that one
have but damn you have so much to flex
thank you for being so patient you could
have told me earlier next time tell me
earlier I'll try to do something about
it I'm glad it's resolved now
though double badge damn he must be a
genius nice happy ending space
[Music]
waterful d s Don no thank you for the
red chat so I will have my
three-year-old emblem always happy to
see you on the streams thank you
sunm yeah once you have it you can Flex
it everywhere show it on off like you
just don't care or like you do care cuz
you got to be proud of that thank you
for all the support for such a long
[Music]
time
than did I read right dou
[Music]
stain you an egg
potato egg potato two of the best foods
in life
combined okay that's already it
apparently
next is family
field people are like oh thank you so
much for organizing but honestly this
one wasn't a big
deal I just all I had to do is uh
write at
everyone I wanted to play family field
who wants to play with me at this time
and
date and I chose like I chose a date
before I had all the participants so I
was basically trying to get a decent
time for Na and non na like uh
Asia I I thought well I'm the only one
it had a page
too okay chill
chill so I know it ended up not being so
good for EST but it was fine for PSD
unlik uh whatever there is in the middle
CS it f
right
shitty for me but you know I was happy
to sacrifice it to make it possible for
others I know in the
end making doing a using a time slot
where
uh Asia and na
was you know accessible wasn't even
necessary cuz nobody from that side of
the globe ended up participating but I
was just thinking just in case and then
it was already set in stone so oh no
no okay so what I miss something what do
you mean that a second page why is it so
[Music]
short what what do you mean stream
before ah or you mean um wait what do
you
mean which one do you
mean
[Music]
for for the Final Fantasy
one oh it does have two pages
[Music]
why normally it it's not that okay
pyke I a be and space
waterfall that's
weird that's so weird
H the pole
okay Jim Tracy take 47 uh not out oh my
God wait I have to get that out of my
brain now I want to I want to add it to
your
name when I read your
name now it doesn't need it anymore
Jacob 47 that's it than sh that's all we
need it's all we
need
wow it feels
wrong we faction D for one 2 3 four five
eight eight yellow super chats thank you
that's like a pinky at least thank you
so
much saying hello to all the
participants very very welcoming and
kind of you
sasuga as to be
expected unknown thanks for the pinky
love for
love
Unown Grumble demon dog D soon obuse D
Alvaro d v faction D TD D Jackson be
thank you for the pinky I always admire
your ability to bring people together
SAS collab Queen thank you yeah I was
surprised first I was a little bit
worried that maybe I wouldn't get so
many
interested participants but oh actually
filled up quite quickly
M was kind of a like uh she was like I'm
not sure if I can participate can I
maybe say like last minutes and I'm like
yeah sure hell yeah so I was happy the
day before she told me sorry can I still
participate I'm like [\h__\h] yeah cuz this
way thanks to her
participating um I could be the host
otherwise I maybe would have
participated as a member to make an even
team but I didn't really want to do that
anyway I felt like more like
hosting he m m without M I feel like it
would have gone down differently
huh yeah she's very uh very passionate
about
it
so it was a pleasure to have
her
yeah one hell of an addition so true so
true
she was the
key was great having her it was great
having all these girls they're all so
cute they were all great participants
great
contestants this was you know I was I
was um hoping to organize like something
big for you know Halloween I know it's
not a Halloween is
game but I didn't feel like forcing
myself to do something necessarily that
has to be horror for everybody I just
wanted to do a family
field when I saw that there's no no no
like really big Halloween collapse going
on for Ian this year I thought hm what
could I do oh yeah I got terms for
family feeld recently let's do Family
Feud then I was going to do it anyway
eventually
yeah so I hope I could make the H life
English fan
Community happy with this and and uh
Enlighten their Halloween experience
with it even though it's not spooky at
all that was the goal basically I think
accomplished it a so thank you Jackson
Cory man D Jackson FB D V fashion d
oh yeah before before the
stream we were um in the in the voice
chat um we were
beautifully
majestically in like a chore kind chore
core what do you call it people who sing
in the
[Music]
church course
chore no chore is a chore like a house
chore choir
choir like a choir we were singing um I
brought it up kind of the uh both the
American and the Canadian Anem and I I
let them hear my my my Canadian Anem
first
and then I witnessed the real one and
then we also sang the um they sang
mostly I just mostly listened the
American anant too was beautiful
especially in Nissa and then I was
saying like I wish
maybe I I really I think she has
potential for it she's the voice for it
to Sing the anthem at like a a like a
sports a real sports event in America
[Music]
somewhere I want her voice to vibrate
through a sports
Stadium I want her to be like
oh can you say with her kind of choir
like voice
Qui you know what I
mean cuz she can do it w for your Orion
visa for Super Bowl oh wow going big
yeah the theatrical voice yeah yeah
yeah so I just wonder like in Japan
whole life has already been through Yago
uh kind of at like sports events right
like uh yakyu um what's in English again
yaku
baseball I wonder if some place in the
America would do it with NOA I want I
want it to happen I want it to happen M
I want her to sing the national
anthem maybe there's a team of some
sport that's like really into anime
stuff maybe there's a whole life fan in
one big sports team or not doesn't even
have to be big one sports team and and
then they wish they watch this or they
watch whole life in general and then
they say hey that's a good idea WWA I
will check with my team and see what we
can
do and and then they get they reset to
sing for their opening whatever I don't
know how it really works
but there was an MLB player that
listened to a whole member's face hey yo
hey
yo
[Music]
MLB well I put this brain warm into
nissa's uh head head I wonder if she'll
if she's taking it seriously at all I
think she should like I think she should
uh have it as a goal in her
head and then aim for
that would be
funny we
F recycled from the USA game show oh
okay okay okay the questions we recycle
from USA game show show SS on the
Ubisoft store Page I
[Music]
guess
room
a
[Music]
forong Jacob 47 D te
Tracy H
atie random collusion D for the rest of
chat yay family we are
family I got all my sisters to
me We Are
Family yeah thank you indeed family big
[Music]
family
and
[Music]
family thank you GD thank you for the
red chat thank you for this incredible
collab two of my OES together fire
doggles oh you you got some new OES
besides
me I don't know about that I'm not the
only one
anymore I'm not your only one
anymore you have to split your focus
[Music]
now
GD thought I was the only
one g d d you are now g
d
sorry so you went from one to three cuz
they're
two
so that's all that's definitely a d
d it's fine I hope I'm I hope I'll be
your number one
[Music]
still ah hi Aura happy
Halloween thank you you my come okay I
hope that doesn't
change throwing the old away cuz it's
boring going with the
new thank
[Music]
you is that why you added the ERM was
that stand for is that for letting fuu
know
something do be
new the ERM what is
that
what is the
ear K bubble an abbreviation yeah of
what
e ever
remaining
mother ever
[Music]
remaining ah Elite
rafian
Milkman employee records
manager did you get a job at foka or is
it your job
here I didn't I I didn't know you were
employee records
manager yo okay okay I am
relieved relieved y
I
see I see yeah I couldn't be mad at you
you you you've been always so
loyal to
me thank
you for the
pinky ah you keep track of the employe
numbers okay that that's the record then
okay makes sense really fun collab T
don't worry about Rhode Island since it
wasn't on the board and the next state
they were going to choose was also wrong
yeah so the result would have been the
same I guess yeah also party dress call
us matching the first
[Music]
teams
what you mean my my party dress
color-wise was on the red side so it
matched the the non blue team is that
what you're
[Music]
saying Road Island compensates for crony
going for Las Vegas yeah I I do think in
the end like even when we wrote it
correctly it was still not there on the
board
so it's
fine I did I did I did help too here and
there a little
bit I feel like I I wanted to hear Amma
a bit more
[Music]
though Amma
was I don't know I should have given her
more time to speak I don't know I to
hear am
more maybe that's just just the teammate
inside of me but
um yeah I guess she's just a little bit
quiet cuz there's so much going
on she did help me a lot though because
uh when I was like preparing for the
stream the thing happened again with
like when I would share screen share uh
the game to the people in Discord um it
was like doing the robotic not really
robotic but like the laggy sound thing
again and I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I can't
have this happen now there's so many
people waiting for the stream to start
and like expecting a good stream I can't
have this audio problem again and in
that moment I was only with narissa but
then Amy came in and I was like
am good morning am I might need your
help and
uh a yeah yeah first we were thinking
maybe trying like OBS ninja it's another
tool that we used sometimes before but
not really so familiar with it um but H
then she had the idea of like instead of
capturing
either OBS or the game capture
directly uh instead of that turning on
the virtual camera in
OBS and then in Discord instead of
screen share it would be like turning on
a webcam because OBS turns into a webcam
when you turn on the virtual
camera and that actually
worked the problem was only that through
this uh I couldn't quickly easily maybe
there was a way to do it but in this
situation I couldn't uh share the sound
with them but the sound wasn't so
important for the game I would say at
all
really
no it mirrors
[Music]
it really but they were able to read
things though if it was mirrored I don't
think they would have been able to read
it
H seemed fine they didn't say anything
about it being mirrored so I think it
was
fun
no but yeah um sasuga I didn't think of
that I thought it would just be the
same same problem if I did uh like a
webcam you know but it worked Hallelujah
a that relieved me big time and also I
did all the characters I did them
beforehand off stream um I played one
round uh to get some points for items
too and get an understanding if if I can
type quick enough I wanted to practice
typing so I prepared a little
bit and then I wanted to do the
characters so uh that we wouldn't have
to spend too much time on it on stream
or like right before the stream it did
take a little while so it was good that
I did
before and then before the stream I gave
them I showed it to them and I gave them
the option to change like small things
but they were mostly happy with
it so all prepared quite well I would
say
[Music]
yeah secret solo FF
stream H yeah it didn't really crash I
think that one crash was only because I
had it open like through the night and
then the switch was like
on it was not like completely off I
guess it was just like standby or
whatever I don't
know so it was just open for too long
more or less and it was open in the
background it wasn't like open
open but it didn't like that yeah that's
okay that's
understandable it
happens it added charm yeah it had good
timing okay so uh where was I a
yeah
mdp thanks for the red super chat
amazing collab ladies thank you all so
much for playing yeah I thanked them uh
afterwards too many times we talked a
little bit everybody actually I was
surprised surpris everybody stayed after
the stream was
over they stayed for a while and we
chitch a little
bit no until I said oh so I'm I I got to
go I'm sleepy and I need breakfast and
[\h__\h] and then they
[Music]
skedaddled yeah oh they all stay yeah
even the
introverts I was like what's going on
it's so late for for them yeah even
crony who was falling
asleep
yeah they all
stayed n so that felt pretty that made
me quite happy that they didn't
immediately say like okay bye I'm out of
here
[Music]
bye made me feel like oh
family
[Music]
I was moved
emotionally thank you
[Music]
C Cruise D the bump D Sky d zly d Mar
PPP D FAA d sword Works d py d and space
waterful
d I like this music it's so
cute
um that's supposedly
it I think I'm caught up now tell me if
I'm
[Music]
wrong tell me if I'm
wrong okay what do you mean I missed
part four
I don't think I did like it's even like
the link for Super Chat is like it looks
like I pressed it
before they that do these super chats
sound familiar to
me they sound familiar to
[Music]
me
oh I right
[Music]
so they all sound familiar to I read
these
yeah I did I
[Music]
did okay okay I don't know if you heard
Yin Jong I don't know if you heard but I
will be signing them off stream okay and
then it might take a few days but I will
upload them in the community board on
YouTube in a giga
file folder maybe I'll even do it in
like um like part one part two part
three after I get a few done like 50 or
so
okay you got chat
folder take your time thank you thank
you you're going to be cute and this
time I'm going to vary the poses a
little bit but I will be doing it with
this outfit with my
[Music]
costume I took a few I took a few
screenshots
actually where do I have
[Music]
them
here so for example there
me
[Music]
um
ghost
couple a ghost
[Music]
couple like
these
and
crafting this but I think white back or
should I do a dark background I find a
nicer background cuz last time I also
had like some kind of pattern in the
background I
think but do you see how cute this would
be actually all the ones who chose the
ghost one would be matching with
me
isn't that
amazing oh my room would be nice
yeah you can sign over both white and
black for
Signature I I'll I'll figure it out I'll
figure it out that's why I picked it hm
Miss opportunity yeah everybody who
didn't know what my costume was going to
be maybe missed out but there's so many
cute ones this one's so cute
the ghost one so
[Music]
cute yeah okay the chance is uh going to
be gone now in in uh now cuz I'm going
to leave now and I'm going to go cook
and first I make a
schedule I have to get up early tomorrow
too actually y y I have something what
do I have
something okay so in ger we have it in
guys thank you for
today you happy
[Music]
Halloween tomor 11
p.m. stream with way Fatal
Frame what console was it
again did I even buy it last
year
I don't have it on
steam pc switch
steam oh
both
[Music]
H
switch all right bye-bye guys good
[Music]
night I have an
idea
[Music]
oh
oo
Boo
Boo Boo
woo
[Music]
wooooo
Boo Boo Boo
boo
[Music]
Bo
[\h__\h]
[Music]
double has the bgm always been
double it's weird what did I do what did
I
do ah by
[Music]
bye Ena Ena
streaming is the ENA
[Music]
streaming what she doing
like oh like
[Music]
this
you heard
[Music]
that chicken
braid say hello to her