[Music]
do
mm-hmm
[Music]
do
go
[Music]
to i forgot to uh turn on my mic on
myself
you can do it again you can do it again
i'll say it again
hey
[Music]
oh my god
football when i
said cooper 12 times you did not show up
in my stream
i showed up a few hours later
yeah that's too much
okay everybody uh welcome to our first
collaboration actually the first uh
non id
senpai that cover is collaborating
and and we're gonna play portal 2 for up
to
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah i
played for the one and portal two
last week and the week before uh
kubo has not really played this game so
and i will we we will have to help her
and teach her yes please probably
getting me money yes
we will help you don't worry
i will i will carry you
[Music]
and hopefully afterwards you you will
love me so much that you will not ask
anyone else to be your mommy ever again
select your favorite animal i i already
love you no matter what mommy
[Music]
hello
i like to hear that
maybe
maybe it's just because you're excited
but my chat says that you're peaking
again please usually really
my voice is speaking mommy
i'm sorry no no no problem
she's just excited she's so energetic
you know you got that this is like with
ollie you know they just peek you have
to
deal with it
guys it's so perfect because she's the
blue little one and i'm the orange big
one
it's so perfect oh my god
yeah really we really complete each
other yeah yeah
but we didn't really start uh yet uh so
we're starting completely from the
beginning guys uh
let's see uh it will probably be two
streams because i don't think we can do
it in one stream but yeah let's do our
best cover yeah yeah i'll do my best
please and the first mission is to
choose your favorite animal i think your
favorite animal is
[Music]
what what do i care about
these things i want to choose my
favorite animal there was a chicken
there
eh i don't even know what these mean i
think this one is sink i don't know in
english
what are these which one is a good one
chad
do you know these
i don't know
maybe
i am or see you because it's like see
you
i don't know
what are those a-u-a-u means gold
apparently a-g is silver
ah
[Music]
what are the other ones i see cu is
copper oh
so these are like metals i guess
yeah okay i'll go oh hg is mercury cd is
cadmium
see
yeah that's the only one i knew
okay let's go
gold uh use your pink tool oh
owl
really okay what's your problem gladys
deserve your partner's interest observe
it gladys is a weird lady
yes you indicate to your opponent
i hope you don't change your mommy
because glad it has kind of mommy
tendencies
yeah the lady who's talking to us she's
like a mommy no no no you're better than
this mommy oh boy
yeah but what did she say
remember to say i was listening to
[Music]
uh
i think we have to
somehow figure out the uh
the game by helping each other uh even
though we're on different sides but
you sure ah i gotta use the ping oh okay
oh
oh i made a portal you made a portal can
i make the portal 2
yeah with f like point at something and
then press f
ah
but how many i can only make two ah
there we go okay oh huh
so uh i think we can both make how many
portals one two
ah we can make two portals
both of us
so uh
you press the f in one spot and then you
yeah
wow i'm a
hacker device shut up gladys
i was explaining it to her wow she's
such a
already triggering me but okay we have
the gun now
oh yeah yeah we have the gun
now we can do it with left click
okay ah left click and right click oh
okay so we do can we we we are able to
make two portals
you can make a dark blue and a light
yeah that can make a red and a yellow
cool
next area
there's other oh yeah you press the
button oh yeah yeah we have to do
teamwork teamwork yeah family
how are you gonna tell us how heavy uh
cover is
yeah
no variances come on nice
don't tell them my weight okay okay nice
it's open
right
you can make another one
i made a portal on top of your portal
locations to your partner oh we can use
pink
oh
yeah yeah ping ping i don't know
a portal over
there um
there's a glass
separated
yeah there's
the glass
it's already oh wait i make it for you
wow this guy is nice
moment that would be too early no no no
we have to think harder kobold let's see
how smart you are today i hope you're
smart
i hope you okay your iq
i don't know maybe it's below 100.
yeah um
my mine is 180. mm-hmm 1800
oh there we go okay so put the cube on
this thing yeah yeah yeah yeah
easy
peasy yeah don't fall into the oh wait
there's no water on your side but that
water don't don't fall into it okay
i see your water there okay yeah
can you push that button
with
um you know those barriers if you put
the cube through it it won't uh
it will disappear but what do you want
from me oh wait i'll give the cube to
you for now ah
maybe maybe
nice catchment oh yeah yeah yeah exactly
okay wow
what
okay
nice nice
nice we have to think with portals yes
yes yes
think
wait
oh there's water
and some uh portal surface
i think i know
okay yeah someone has to push that
button
i think i know oh and then i didn't see
that one boom wow oh
for me thank you
yeah yeah yeah that's for you yeah oh
okay i'll post a button
[Music]
oh my god
nice well i think we did pretty well so
far i gotta go into the orange one i
think are you going to the blue one yay
what okay oh yeah oh oh techno music
again technology
[Music]
you don't play a robot you play a
human
yeah you should play the game kobo you
need to play if you if you're done with
this one you need to play portal one and
portal two okay richmond center here
center it's very funny but why don't we
all just agree to call it
all cooperative testing courses begin at
the central hub
from here transport you to the new
testing course i don't really listening
to gladys actually
yeah don't worry i'll listen to her you
don't have to listen thank you mommy
oh oh they're counting our steps oh
oh
wow okay so there's two buttons over
there oh
i'm going
you can use this new portal i think we
can stand on both of them maybe what if
that's necessary
oh
oh where are we going
roller coaster
wow
so cool wow
okay what is this is
this doesn't look so uh clean anymore
yeah no quarters selected extra courses
take place after the main courses okay
um
art therapy
we're doing art therapy art therapy
that sounds good
sounds interesting please proceed to
this uh disassembly chambers
that sounds like they're taking us apart
kobo
okay what if i stand in the blue one
does that work
oh no no no
okay it doesn't work okay okay that's
fine i like my color i like orange
yeah that's later that's the dlc what
what what why why how did we get to the
dlc huh
this is super hard stuff what chad says
that we went into a dlc uh post game
that's really hard wait how do i go back
oh no
100 000 years since i last thanked you
for testing
remember those humans you found because
they're all fine in fact we solved
science
[Music]
what it's an exploration of how we're
all devices go back to the hub
can you press escape
so we got
[Music]
why did others know my fault the game
led me to to go here
automatically
what
that's confusing maybe one day we can do
the difficult dlc but i think right now
yeah now we're not big brain enough
so we're not supposed to press those
buttons can we just go in here
oh
oh if we stand on those buttons we can
open up this door
okay
tim building now we're supposed to go
here
okay
kobo what's your favorite kind of game
um like the genre
[Music]
moba and fps i guess
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
and from one i know you don't really
like fps game right
yeah that's true
i think you gotta go with there yeah
oh
hold for partner view oh that's so cool
i can see what you're doing if i press
tab
oh if you press can you make a portal
uh
[Music]
i think i understand maybe um can you
can you stand on my button for a moment
okay oh wait i need to open up
ah i come back
can you come back here ah okay
and then
stand on the button
yeah
um
i think i i need to wait open open up
again
can you go here maybe there's some clue
here huh
no no no not too you're
to your right
hello oh no hello
hi
oh i came for the other side even though
the door was closed i'm thinking maybe
what does this do
i just feel that door just open the door
go from my portal maybe okay
and and then go for the door
[Music]
but come back here come back to the
original and make the other second blue
portal no i think you don't just go to
your portal
oh yeah that's true i can go here too um
[Music]
like albert einstein
so far so good somewhere so good yeah
one of you
if you uh like moba and fps so much how
did how long have you been playing games
or are you just like new to games
i mean i play
you know
humans i have my pc since last december
you know i just so i
i started to play pc games
like since january
i've had my pc since i was like nine or
something
you have to go back i think and press
that one button oh yeah yeah i didn't
see the button and before that you have
no computer
science collaboration points what
you had no computer before that
yeah
wait
oh wait oh
open up again please okay i i have an
idea uh
wait wait wait uh where was it
orientation
wait i'm confused i lost my orientation
can you open up again okay
okay uh in the back i made a wait wait
open up one more time okay
oh wait is that gonna work
ah yes ah yes it is okay go for my
yellow portal okay
hi guys
[Music]
wow
oh my god
nice
yeah
easy hey you played games in the
internet cafe before nah
no because just says you played games in
the internet cafe no internet cafe is so
far away from my home
oh you guys are lying then how did you
get that info huh
[Laughter]
okay the buttons will activate something
that's like time limited
and what is it oh oh oh there's another
button there's some signs yeah
there's another that one does that one
okay x and
dots i suppose there's probably
something up there
that one is
that one uh-huh ah
yeah
and the moon okay so
so i i think um
when i press this
jump on this yeah
you see you see up there there's like a
loading
loading sign and they should
yeah something should ah we have to
maybe activate all of them at the same
time yeah yeah and then something will
drop from from above and then we can put
it into this hole
okay okay yeah let's go two what yeah
cool
nice and nice
[Music]
i have the ball it looks like you kobo
thank you i think it's just like
yeah you're really friendly thank you
totally a compliment um
easy
easy we're speeding for the game but but
cool but this will probably get much
more difficult
is your is your mom not gonna be sad if
you call someone else mommy
no your real mom
she's fine
she's watching us right now
[Laughter]
yeah sorry um
i'm her new mom now
i mean she's waving at you right now
ah
i can't use my hands but i'm waving back
totally
oh wait
wait wait no i can wave like this maybe
am i waving
not your you're not
how does this work
i don't know
oh well
hello mommy hello my name
wait is my mom is laughing
hello
yeah
and robot okay so
that's what oh that was already genius
kovalev yeah
[Music]
cool i am
very very glad this is going good so far
oh
i was worried that because you didn't
play the game that maybe we would have
some problems
[Music]
i hate them i hate them what
what what's so cute
always shoot me
it can shoot
yeah not for that wall but once you're
like
yeah
oh yeah
so we have to eliminate them basically
you can pick them up if you press e like
when you're right in front of them
but oh what is that oh
cute uh
but let's see yeah we first have to
oh okay okay
how to
how to shoot them with this laser
i think
um
wait can we have another cube
[Music]
that was actually uh cobu's fault but
it's okay it's my phone
you were on the button and then uh you
left and i was standing on it so it
closed and it crashed me but it's okay
it feels nice sometimes feels like a
massage
[Laughter]
oh
yeah
sorry about it
okay okay wait i i will figure this out
this this this is my um
ah
oh you pray oh yeah yeah yeah it gives
us
we can i thought we can
we can only have one
unfortunately we can only have one but
um how did you
okay how about you oh we can do it all
right we can do it through
i took the weight cover oh yeah go in
through here
no
oh yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait can we
oh we'll do it through here yeah yeah
yeah
um
almost almost we have to change the
angle a little bit
there you go
now
kobo you have to i think you have to
make a portal oh yeah and one at the top
yes
wow
i just got this part
still in the way
should i just
run there and throw them over
um
we still need to get rid of them
otherwise if we walk over there we have
to we're gonna get killed by them
well we can try to kill them with the
laser maybe but i mean what's the what's
the point of this button
that's a good question
okay okay
[Music]
yeah you saying what's the point of the
button uh was important because
otherwise i wouldn't have thought of
that
damn
nice
[Music]
asking the right questions
thank you gladys thank you thank you
[Music]
yeah we did it kind of uh the other way
around normally you kill the robots
first and then you figure out the rest
ah
yeah normally i don't know what you
think you are doing
we can download this importance
yeah that's good i want to do that
[Music]
do you know her
thing it's like she likes to do uh rock
paper scissors and it's called tsunamaki
junking you know it i don't know about
it
it's like she sings
usually she always loses
yeah
i don't really get much but okay that's
okay
no problem yeah don't worry about it
so
what if we stand both of them
uh-huh
this looks complicated oh no
oh no what is this all
something like a cube will come out of
here me no no we came out of here never
mind
but
that cube that reflection cube that's
over there we want to bring it here to
the laser yeah so first of all
stand
stand where where
i
wait
okay
[Music]
and now
is it okay to go here
oh yeah yeah yeah
oh
should i make just in case a portal here
i'll make one there
okay don't crush me global no no no i
wanna
okay okay okay
yeah yeah
no i'm scared what no no it's okay i
mean i think you just yeah yeah stand
there stand there
and boom oh help it nice
okay now back
maybe you're just okay
[Music]
i can use my portal and but now i need
to go back up
oh
wait wait wait wait no no you cannot go
back you need to
wait can i shoot portal there no
[Music]
well i can't really go up there but i
made a a yellow one over there so i'm
sorry i have to go back again yeah yeah
yeah yeah
i get it i get it
i'll go through
oh yeah thank you
there we go
nice and nice
genius
i suppose we probably need one here
but where does it go where do we want it
to go
um uh here
we go
wow nice big gray mommy phoenix
you just
don't listen to gladys don't listen to
her
yeah i'm just listening to you
that's good that's good
mama
emma i'm
never had a daughter before
competition no you have fun
blue would be winning
shut up gladys
i'm winning
what happened she standed for the word
competition blue is what no it's not a
competition okay it's not a competition
yeah it's teamwork oh not a competition
uh however
we need
um the laser to go to three different
places
also what is this
no it's the same cube it's respawn again
oh
oh yeah oh
okay in case we lose the first one
that's how we get a new one but
maybe we start by activating this
one what the heck what is this oh my oh
no don't get crushed global
and nana i'm gonna be fine
i'm here oh wait on this flag okay now i
make the middle platform move but i
think you have to jump over the laser
uh oh no where's let go
[Music]
it was very dramatic it was very very
good
[Music]
what's this again i think okay okay okay
okay no no
oh
sorry about that yeah
[Music]
okay
we need a portal on that side
yeah
and another one
i think you have to go back and i have
to go
uh
ah can you make one where the yellow one
was
here here
yeah yeah ah the other color yeah
and then i will i think i'm able to go
there alone okay
you make the the dark blue on on that uh
exit
ah
[Music]
yeah you're right okay
oh
okay
so
[Music]
with a goal of not failing horribly
i don't know when you're trying to say
gladys but i think we're succeeding
immensely eat that gladys
yeah take that lettuce yeah
you know gladys is uh she really likes
to test people it's like her favorite
thing to do so we're actually just doing
her a big favor she's playing with us
hmm
this next test is
we have to think outside the box cobalt
outside the box okay
not portal
it's so dark
huh
outside the box oh there's something
there down there
ah
let's go
yeah
oh
insert disk
i don't think we can do that can we
insert this
i think it's just
the video that i always placed
it's and
[Music]
same time probably
uh okay countdown
calm down what is that i don't
understand that countdown let's just say
it in discord uh
one two
three
oh
hold the f but
what wait i'm sorry my my mom
yeah yeah okay hello mommy
mommy yeah
never mind
[Music]
okay
i'm faster
i'm sorry
three two one go oh
oh okay do i have to go for this here
again nice and nice and nice
it's like a frisbee it's so big
oh spidey
movie
you managed to complete this braiding
let's
oh i almost forgot when you go outside
the testing courses the only way i can
retrieve you is to violently disassemble
you
then carefully reassemble you
lock up
wow okay
she disassembled us we explode what the
heck
we did everything correctly
this is so mean
very violently why are we back here
stop it
so funny
there must be something wrong with the
reassembly machine we did it correctly
see what happens
[Music]
that's that's not very nice but okay
oh we need to go to the second door
second door
yeah over there uh
yeah
huh
okay oh
mass and velocity
we will learn some things about mass and
velocity
which don't worry i don't really know
what that means either you're not alone
oh momentum oh
okay
uh cobalt you do you know the word
momentum
this course i forgot anything about
physics to do that
i will teach you if you look at this
picture followed by me raising them for
another ten minutes you see that one
right yeah um let's see you fall humans
shut up goddess
i'm teaching my child something
let's say you fall out of that portal
as a pup
and then you you you fall into that
portal down here
um
that is called
momentum and the higher you fall
the more
um like like okay wait no let's say you
fall out of here and you fall into this
one yeah let's say if it was a big fall
then once you go through this portal
again yeah uh you will fall like this
way
very very far away so that's called
momentum okay perfect explanation
[Music]
oh if you didn't understand it but i see
i see okay okay i think let's check it
out
here we already have an example but oh
cobo can you go down first
not into the portal yeah can you make um
a blue portal where my yellow one
is uh a dark blue portal
there where i can't read yeah over there
okay and now i show you momentum
momentum
learn
[Music]
get up to the top okay here go for my
yellow one ah
i am carrying my child and now you fall
and do the same thing fall for the
yellow ones i'll just fall momentum
wow
wow so cool
damn
[Music]
but it will get more complicated okay
like this is probably also oh no
uh-huh i see something here that's where
we have to
fall through maybe
oh dear
aha
i'll go there too okay okay
so i think first of all
can you make um
a blue one here
blue
here and then one like somewhere uh high
ah this one this one this one okay okay
yeah i think
let's see
nice
nice i pressed the button i don't know
what happened
what happens um
what happens nothing happened wait wait
um
[Music]
okay you have to get to
this one
yeah yeah i know this
i can help you maybe ah
yeah you make the dark blue one here
yeah and then the light blue one here oh
yeah yeah okay
it's the sea
[Music]
nice
robots are superior
[Music]
yeah um since you
don't really
you didn't really play games until
recently you didn't have a pc until
recently and uh i don't think you have
much
experience streaming as far as i know
but then how did you
all the ways humans can die how did you
like find out about the whole life
audition testing well
basically
my friend just sent me
like ah
yo kaboo
uh whole life is opening audition you
should try
so i'm just
just genius friend yeah
i'm just a good friend trying my luck
yeah
oh so they they had a good idea that you
would probably fit into whole life well
hmm
what is this i don't know what is it
mess
wait
um
yeah
i don't prefer that again
i know
[Music]
i hope you don't throw up
yeah
wait okay no wait do that go go there
again
okay
you just keep on falling
uh yeah yeah keep on falling uh uh okay
um
[Music]
i trust you mommy
um it's the right idea i just need to
get rid of these things happy
i come back
okay
[Music]
that was that was fun
yeah how was that on purpose okay cobalt
eat so sorry how do i get to your side
what does your button do
um
and what does this little button do
oh it does the same thing oh okay oh
they just want me oh
oh it's my turn
it's my turn to
boom boom
thank you
oh god i'm scared don't forget
[\h__\h] me
i know work no
i think you have to uh get rid of the
upper one
first
okay i'll go
wait oh
oh
[Music]
a trash fall
yeah you have to trust the other person
and just let yourself go oh i trust i i
thought you were trying you said trash
stressful okay
trustful
the best way to build confidence is to
first recognize your institution
room three out of eight by the way ah
eight from a massive philosophy okay
okay
one second we don't have the time
[Music]
it's a com compliment
yeah oh we have the same thing again
and i think we want to fall
oh dear
oh
what is this
ah it's getting very complicated
uh
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay i'm gonna throw you again okay okay
okay i like to be trolled
eat me girls invite okay i'll try
yeah you press the button i make the
floor you run back baby
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh but wait don't don't don't don't
carry it through there because the ball
will disappear
uh
i think
[Music]
can i can i throw this thing
okay wait where does it go again ah i
think up up here oh my god mommy kiara i
can go up here
what
i mean yeah yeah you can but with the
ball you can't go there because the ball
will be wrong
here
okay
[Music]
appreciate the desire to stop and smell
the test
open that other sentence
nice and nice and nice nice nice
my daughter is so cute
what's your favorite food
favorite food huh
i like japanese food and korean food
for example
ramen
you were the only subjects to pass
there's a korean right i never had that
before oh it's it's really good yeah you
should
uh try it you already know
is it spicy
yeah
there's spicy one and there's like the
uh normal one
also everybody in the chat says silor
silor chilo
is uh like indonesian street food
actually yeah it's a good snack
yeah it's a small i want to look for
that
yeah yeah
oh what is it made out of it it's
basically just a flower
[Music]
and and egg
well that seems like something i could
eat
uh-huh
and yeah
[Music]
uh-huh you will fall upwards and there
will be a button and i want you to push
it okay
where were the buttons
maybe first time you just take a look no
pressure no no no no no
i'm looking at your cam right now so
where's the button it's up there it's up
there
so you will fall from here
okay let's try it that's right okay
i'll do the other one okay okay
it's okay oh yeah
are you falling
yeah
[Music]
we'll try it a few times
is
[Music]
after i push the button here you should
drop the part over here oh
make the other one right
[Music]
good job
i'm so proud of you oh sorry you can't
bring your ball with you
i'll buy you a new one when we get home
really
yeah a new box
okay
a new one
so proud of my daughter i thought this
would be a disaster but so far it's
doing really well
i'm happy to be useful
okay
oh
i'm becoming gladys i'm just testing you
kobo i'll [\h__\h] out
we always go first okay so that mommy
doesn't break her precious bones in her
body yeah
[Music]
uh you have to go back first we have to
time this um
when you jump through
say go
uh when i jump okay
wow
[Music]
all right now i jump okay
wow
[Music]
i think we need to uh
maybe
make a portal
while you're falling
wait you would fall yeah but um
no no no i think we we need to uh just
just redo
we do it but um
no okay okay oh oh
oh
oh okay but uh
can you actually make your own your own
portals here okay i'll put them yeah
yeah and because if i walk through here
my portals will disappear now i make one
here and and where
oh
here i see it okay
oh my god
the other side
i'm hurting yourself
i don't know self-destructing okay
but how do i get to you
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
again
um
i think if you walk
through there
your portal will
disappear
um
[Music]
think
mummy brain hurts
very hurt maybe think it hurts maybe i
can do this i don't know
ah can i
no cause yours disappears the moment you
walk through but
about two
[Music]
do it again because i messed up yeah
oh okay no problem
it's okay we learned oh maybe i should
have done something here first uh okay i
make the same portal up here okay and
you make yours over there okay
and then you fall through
okay and then you're on the other side
again
then
i know how to go to your side too but
oh there
ah
okay
uh can you make a dark blue where you
made it before
here
no uh here
i think
i
think or maybe that's right
or maybe no no no no actually
i know uh i don't know yeah i'll leave
it like that
okay
oh wait oh that doesn't work uh
oh hello
um
uh
is there something here on this wall
yeah yeah no no that means
there's like a
what is that
it's like i don't know this target sign
yeah
[Music]
um i can't i don't know
uh can you
mommy
told me
thank you chad
thank you nice one thank you chad yeah
thank you
all right where are we going this time
we're speed running oh oh oh okay i
think first step you go through my
portal over there okay
and then you will be catapulted over to
that button
[Music]
oh this is someone's fun with two people
oh
okay but i can't do that and i don't
know now i gotta put myself to that side
uh-huh
yeah
[Music]
now i'm here ah
oh wait it closed again i'm sorry but i
think ah damn it ah
there's like two
two platforms where i can make a portal
one is angled one is straight
and
i think
if i know
um
[Music]
okay
but that can't be me can it be me
i'll i'll go
wait how did i get there before i'll go
here again
and then
and then wait this door
closes when you get off of the button
right yeah
okay
um
uh go to the catapult
to
take that cue first
yeah and i think you have to fall uh
and then you know pick it up like when
you push the buttons in the different
room
maybe
[Music]
sorry sorry i think i think i know okay
um
can you make
a boom
a blue one
here
wait
okay
i don't know that no they won't that
won't work
yeah i'm probably overthinking it's
probably easy wait we have catapults
right
yeah oh yeah okay ah where's the cotton
uh a blue one here okay
and then a blue one where the catapult
is um
wait i'm try i try
okay but why don't
why am i here then why am i up here
okay
i got the ah you have the cube so you
can put the cube where the button is i
think it doesn't go through but wait uh
okay okay i need to oh i get it i get it
okay okay
yes
i await
yeah but i don't think you can put it
through the barrier i think it will
disappear
oh
my god
yeah
yeah it disappears
but they drop it to the floor now oh
yeah but
can i can i throw it up again
throw it up there
i wonder
if i uh
to hold it to pick it up jump
right it's almost there
jump
nice
yeah nice
now please push the button so i i'm not
stuck anymore yeah
thank you
i'm
free yeah
okay we have that open all the time now
but
i think like
how how how how how can i
[Music]
we have to fall through this one to get
over to that side but we need a lot of
momentum
um
ah
but this this barrier kills my portals
the bear kills the portal
[Music]
i want to
get the momentum to fall
out with the port with the little
catapult
is there any other
think
so now we both have one of those moments
i'll test some things
sometimes you have to
test things with your hands
yeah of course that's not enough i knew
that
um
[Music]
maybe and i do
no i'm not sure
oh but i'll try
[Music]
let's try to go there can you
can you
you look at it maybe
i'm thinking shooting a portal while i'm
falling somewhere
when i go
oh
what what what what what i don't know
uh i'm overthinking okay
[Music]
is actually backstabbing me but i don't
understand what they're talking
um oh your chat is backstabbing you yeah
i mean they're telling
they're they're telling them
different things actually but they tell
me how but i don't use i i
don't really understand them
ah
i wanna go there
oh backseat i'm in back seat sorry
oh
yeah yeah you made a portal but i can't
go for your portal
i want to
i want the portal
i want to go
what the [\h__\h]
oh no no that's not really what i want
to say
does it get rid of the barrier if i get
rid of the cube yeah yeah no no no no no
no mommy mommy
i get it i get it okay now
now now it's my time to carry you
this time
okay
so now
you need to
um
make a portal in your catapult and go
here and i make a portal here and here
and then you boom you you go to my pearl
and boom
yeah
i went to yours okay yeah i even needed
something like that noise
[Music]
wow i'm so smart
and now you can come down here
yeah
that's what you look like right now
together
isn't it nice when you when you solve a
puzzle and you feel so smart yeah yeah
yeah i feel so smart now if you want
more of that you should play portal 1
and portal 2.
okay
you should play it solo on your on your
stream
i'm sure your audience will love it
[Music]
okay
i already see something so there's a
catapult here
i'm guessing
it will shoot me into that and then
maybe i want to go out of here let me
test uh-huh
wow oh [\h__\h]
i'm somewhere
and i might be uh stuck
but no okay i'm just investigating
uh okay i'm here
hi hi what does that do oh it opens the
door okay
so
where are we
where did i come from up from here oh
there yeah
it wasn't nice and temp nice reflexes
yeah yeah
oh i must have almost gotten it
so wait i fell through
i went through at the catapult to here
and
while i was falling i guess i made
another one
no i already made before that i made
another one here and i went to i went
over this i think
over that barrier the glass
and then
i made another portal there
uh i have to think with four portals i
think cobble needs to make some portals
yeah on the other side maybe uh-huh i
know but um
maybe
ah
i see okay okay you you have a blue one
there and uh you make uh the other blue
one here i think
yeah i think i think so
now let me come to your side
you're right
then i will reach the place where i can
push the button
[Music]
okay oh [\h__\h] i'm coming
yay
[Music]
yes
oh
[Music]
we switch it around you do the portals
where i did the portals okay i do the
portals where you did the portals
okay
first you have to go to the
uh to the catapult first
okay
and then you make one where the
the sign is
yeah
and and another one another one uh no
the dark blue one needs to go kind of
next to the
uh uh it should be like somewhere there
yeah yeah exactly okay okay i got it
okay okay we're ready
oh no
oh
did you don't miss the portal
yeah
it's not on plane
um
yeah the dark blue yeah exactly and
[Music]
don't fall into the water cool boy it
will kill you okay
oh oh oh
and one over there
dark blue i wanna go in here
oh [\h__\h]
oh you're going over there oh i feel
like it works differently okay
we need a what else is there
there's another
nothing here another there's another
catapult another one to go back i think
uh here
yeah
[Music]
ah
come back cube
um oh it doesn't range
yeah oh i think when okay
um
the following thing is gonna happen kobo
you're gonna oh [\h__\h] oh well maybe i
will do it yeah maybe i will do it um
because i i understand it i think uh
[Music]
when i fall
through
um well when i'm on my way to
this yellow border yeah yeah you push
the button because i have to catch the
cube
i get it okay
um
oh
[Music]
okay we'll figure it out we'll just go
for an endless loop
where do i stop where do i stop um
[Music]
it feels like we're in the surface okay
you're coming here
but i find something
consequence of death
this is love yeah it's not science
beautiful yeah chad what do you think
are we going to are we going too fast or
is this
are we going at a good pacing i think
we're so smart that we're speeding
running the game
yes
we're gonna make a new record that's
gonna be in the guinness
world book of records no guinness book
perfectly average that sounds um nice
and also not so nice thank you
okay
oh
i think
we will have to push those buttons
at the same time by falling
out of there but
oh [\h__\h] oh my god what what
okay
you make the same portals that i did but
you know the dark blue one here
yeah oh
wow
did i use this one okay go
let's go
oh the praise it feels good what do we
have we have a laser
what is this laser
oh
[Music]
because of the cube
i think i activated that with the cube
because if i get rid of it
oh no it just always does that okay
mommy
there's something here here and here
okay
yeah yeah yeah
um
i want to place the cube the other way
around uh and then make it go through up
we're flying to the cube
okay we'll place it uh this way
oh [\h__\h] come on
i thought we can we can we can go
[Music]
um this is kind of lower than i thought
it would be
i want it to be higher so i can send it
through
but can we like lower or raise this
platform oh yeah you're right um
and then the laser maybe we'll go
through here and we can send it to go
through here
and then it will activate this one
it will probably
uh raise or lower if we push this button
so we have to go through this
catapult
[Music]
with the catapult we can go through
that
uh
back to the portal
and then
we want to go
i don't know where
maybe
[Music]
what is on the other side i wonder not
can we walk on can we walk here no
okay
can
[Applause]
we there's a catapult here oh i just i
just see the camera
okay
i see what you mean now you probably
wanted to go for the size
yeah okay
i'm here this is the first room okay
um
[Music]
oh
i don't understand oh
[Music]
i understand nothing but i kind of
understand the thing but
but even if we go for the catapult where
do we go from there
over over
the for those uh crushy thingies
naruho don't yes we have the spirit
believe kobo
i know where we're going with that
ah this
it should not it won't erase it will be
like tilted and then shoot
maybe like that i don't know
ah
i think
oh
ah
what if i go for oh that doesn't work
what if i go over here that doesn't work
i thought that was portal surface
ah
yeah no never mind i was wrong i had i
thought i had an idea but i didn't
oh i think
what it gets so close if only there was
like a platform right there
are you going
don't help me i don't i want
i want to figure this out
i'm scared of getting crap crashed oh i
might have to hold it
[Music]
we'll go for the portal
okay we don't have much time though
let's see okay
okay okay okay what is happening oh
this is the platform
okay wait what what what do we
i think i need to
stand here
okay
how high does it go
ah
does it raise you so you can yeah yeah
yeah yeah
and you fall out of here make a make a
blue one here
and a blue one there okay
okay yeah yeah okay i get it maybe
okay
oh i do something else i do this and i
do
that okay
uh
i wait for the
the crusher
pressure okay
ready
[Music]
i i didn't reach the catapult
um but you think you can if you try
again
yeah maybe yeah yeah yeah i can i can't
[Music]
okay you do that part i guess you have
to put a portal here
and a portal there
where
uh
here and there okay
and i will do the thing that you were
doing if i remember oh yeah yeah okay
okay let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
oh no
you make it
i made it come over here
oh i'm ready let's run online
wow
would that be funny and that would be
funny
that would be something gladys would
like to do damn so smart mommy phoenix
what did that do and then opens
[Music]
you make a portal make portal here
and there's no no nothing for portals
here uh
um we have to beam fast
or
what
um
go here and then it opens and then
something
[Music]
something with the ah
wait kobo i'm gonna you wait in front of
the door you wait in front of the door i
wait in front of the door
we will throw not our bodies we will
throw the cube instead and we wait in
front of the door yeah
i think
is that possible
i don't know yeah i think so we can
throw the cube and um
but
i i will
make a portal here and here so i can
quickly move from
okay but i think that's enough time
ah
um
[Music]
[Applause]
is impressed by our genius brains yeah
mommy didn't expect his brain
coco you have been
you
wait let me listen to her first
this is just a thought experiment
just to see how much time you'll waste
thinking about these worthless documents
i have the correct time zero seconds
okay glad this choice you're sure
you're such a tunisian okay
i wanted to ask you while we're looking
at this uh-huh
um
you've been
in her life
for one month now yeah
have you gotten used to it
um
[Music]
i guess
maybe
maybe yeah
yeah i mean there's still some some
some things that you think are difficult
uh
not really
huh yeah everything could you if you
have some questions you can ask your
senpai
yeah
yeah yeah i always ask
uh
from ollie senpai
oh you can ask yeah i gotta send bye too
i mean i wanted to i i want to chat
other senpai from other friends but
yes you're shy
i mean besides that i'm shy
moment
what what
what what what what
oh what what did i do i pushed the
button but what how what did i do oh
yeah
what does that do a cube cube
first cube up
and down down
ah it changes that direction
ah i i think i know yeah
[Music]
you jumped a little bit later than me
yeah okay
like two two or three seconds maybe
okay okay
yeah
uh no
good
oh wait maybe
huh
yeah you jumped when i push the button
maybe that's the right time okay okay it
goes up
and stop
maybe that was too early
uh let's go
oh yeah okay a bit later
okay okay i see i see i see it more
later
mama maybe
three seconds after i touch the back
okay okay
and
one
[Music]
i want to push the button
okay
yeah yeah
and let's do it the other way i'll i'll
go for this one
and i'm like
oh yeah it doesn't matter well down here
it doesn't matter
okay okay
okay i'll wait for you
okay i'll jump
push
one
two
three i'll go
uh no
okay
that was already falling down again when
i was uh
on top of it so i couldn't reach i saw
you
so
oh
i will be
uh i need to jump a bit earlier maybe
yeah
okay okay i'll kill ya
easy peasy lemon squeezy koopa challenge
okay one two three wee hmm
[Music]
okay
and now we have the reflection oh yeah
oh i have to hold it again
what's happening
what happened wait
what does that do
um
ah
it turns red what's happening
how does that help us
so that you can fall for the fan now
or we need to go there
yeah because we can draw a portal here
here
[Music]
oh
um there's
uh i can draw portal here so how can you
go through the for the barrier oh yeah
[Music]
here
uh-huh
but there's a portal deleting barrier in
between
okay i'll try to go here what do we have
here
um
is that that um shutdown thingy
uh
um is that is that uh
something where a laser has to go
through can you can you can you uh can
you shoot the laser like here
through the window oh
oh
i can't go very high
okay here here uh uh here maybe
yeah i could wait i have an idea maybe i
can send it through here
and then
oh there's yeah yeah there's a yeah yeah
nice
okay i'm not quite sure oh
um i need to protect myself where am i
sending it
out
oh
smarter than when i played this alone
does this help you is it too high it's
too high it's so high uh
go down a bit well i can't i can't angle
it lower but can you move the portal a
little bit there might oh no you can't
it's
alright
then i guess i could wait uh
just drop it
it's not low enough
nope
no okay okay no problem no problem no
problem no problem
what about now
ah it's not coming through no way
um
we had it
huh
we had it just for a second correctly i
didn't shut down
oh
nice okay everything's perfect i think i
have to come to your side now yeah yeah
yeah yeah you should come come on
oh my god that i really need we're not
gonna buy i can fly with you
[Music]
wow
are you
are you sporty football do you work out
nah
i mean you sleep and
okay because when i saw those stairs i
felt like oh in real life if i have to
walk up those stairs i immediately get
breathing problems
wow that's never too strong
[Music]
watching with mommy
why are you always kill us like that but
that means we have like the second
chapter done how many of these are there
we did two of them
how many other six or something you are
doing
okay we have two out of five or six so
let's do one more today okay so uh this
uh this three third level gonna be our
last around
what huh
[Music]
how many level again
um chad says five and one uh dlc and we
have two now so if we do one more then
we have three out of six
so half
which is perfect because then we can do
the other half next time okay i see that
so this is our last level
for today yeah but it will be it will be
pretty pretty long anyway yeah for today
for today okay okay okay
we're going to get up there you need to
go here
[Music]
yeah and i saw our
uh our short video from him or her
that we okay oh you'll just fall through
my portals
that's all right yeah oh yeah the the
the horse riding yeah yeah yeah the
horse riding
that's very cute
yeah yeah
um
i don't know if i can
if it's like smart to really buy you of
course but
if we ever if we ever meet uh then i can
i can book us a session to ride a horse
at a beast okay
yeah let's go ride it together i miss it
too i went uh horse riding when i was a
child
for like one week but never again
it was only one time
so i want to go to i want to ride a
horse as well oh by the way
see this is a bridge
that we can send through the portals
just like the laser see
yeah damn
i see it okay
you can walk through the portal and walk
for the bridge
can you say damn again
damn
no the the way you said it before so
quiet
damn cute
cute cute cobble
damn i think we need to
send it through
these ones
okay wait uh uh
let's uh stand should we really do this
together huh i'm i'm kind of worried um
oh
that was close
can you do the dark blue oh no no we're
too low
oh
and we did it together oh yeah
now we don't think with bridges we have
to no we don't think of portals we think
bridges that's what i wanted to say
okay
we have a one here
where do we want it
and when do we want it
now aha there's a catapult catapult
wasn't that hurt
i have an idea
oh you have to make the portal cover
you have to make one up here
okay
and then don't uh later
when i am like up here
you make one down here i say okay
it's gone but not yet not now okay yeah
okay and now
[Music]
oh
i need a ball
where is that ball oh
you're gonna get a headache if you do
that
i suppose has something would do to do
with that i want um
[Music]
where is the ball is there a butterfly
oh there's a button
over there
[Music]
can you make
can you make a portal here mommy ah
yeah yeah i have an idea
i think one needs to be here
yeah and the other one needs to be here
yeah
[Music]
okay we got the ball
wow
this is so much fun
yeah okay
now you have to help me to go
up again
um
wait
i uh
it will kill my ball
um
it will take away my oh wait what if i
let's leave the ball first
oh no yeah i know
[Laughter]
okay we gotta press that button again
i just wanted to put it on the floor so
we can test it out without the ball so
we need some more bridges um
we need a bridge that will stop me from
going
up there or stop the ball from going up
there yeah yeah exactly
just like that
ah and then
nah yeah no let's test it so for example
let's say i'm holding the ball
i jump up here in the bunk ah and then i
need
oh thank you but i was gonna pick up the
ball okay okay okay
okay oh you're gonna after i bunked uh
the first bridge you're gonna make a
lower one yeah yeah yeah uh-huh i'll try
okay
come on
it actually works
[Music]
so fast quick reflexes yeah thank you
you
rode a horse before road ridden
when was the last time
uh it's
um
um i think long time ago
yeah i think it's like maybe like
10 years
six years ago
oh so long time ago yeah but you really
like horses huh i like horses yes we can
make a portal over there uh-huh oh
you make one
um and then a a dark blue one
wait uh
i think we will fall uh if we do this
now
can you go back a little bit
yeah yeah um now
make a blue one where exactly where my
red one is
oh
my no not quite i oh that was a thinking
mistake i think i think i'll
come here
maybe uh-huh come here
and uh-huh
like this
maybe
[Music]
yeah genius we just needed the first
bridge to see the the wall where we can
make the portal yeah oh no ah
mama
yeah i have to make that one we go back
again
and now
[Music]
and then i think we have to do that
again
[Music]
up there up there
oh
okay we're setting there
a blue one here and there's no one there
oh yeah no need to go back okay
oh wait it's higher
i'm a bit taller than you
even if you fit i will not pitch
is that it is that it easy peasy glasses
you need to make these tests a bit more
difficult
[Music]
sorry i actually had something in my
throat because when i was outside today
um you know sometimes when you when you
uh swallow
your own spit and then it goes into the
air breathing tube and then you go like
[Laughter]
you you die because of your own spit do
you know what i mean
i basically i couldn't breathe
and now for the whole day i i have uh
something in my throat now
we tried oh no you just sit there
is it hard does it hurt that is inside
no it just feels like i need to cough
the whole time
yeah
[Music]
repeat after me repeat after yellow okay
are you laughing at me um
okay one
two
one
your failure brings back such
no glad
[Music]
i don't think i even want kobo to say
like who cares about
[\h__\h]
um
wait my i think my
i want to turn on my echo but my glowing
solar is not working
[Music]
moment
okay then i i will do it without my echo
okay can you do a three two one go
okay uh
three
two
one
okay it's time for me to die
stay alive okay i need you i need you we
need to uh finish this of course yeah
yeah
okay
yeah indeed very much
what are we doing here oh there's a
bridge there and a button oh yeah
um
okay
uh
okay i think we can fall down on the br
oh i can't bridge
wait i can't oh
can you can you jump
dangerous
okay let me let me push that button and
let me see what happens
you can go through my portal the one
that i made over there somewhere and
then you can attach the ball
and it should be
here
yeah hello
you're poorly stared
how did i get here oh
no
okay okay try to
uh
yes
okay now you want to push the button i
can push the button
and better it you're a good catcher
i had it but it fell down anyway
okay okay one more time
nice and nice to get
you i gotta be careful but kobo where do
i bring the ball
um
let me let me let me uh
let me
check the ball let me protect the ball
and you make a portal uh to bridge
us okay yeah yeah yeah
here
and oh yeah that was it oh yeah and oh
boy
you're nice and nicer we're done yeah
i'm not sure which one is your face
[Music]
we already have the portals we just have
to push the button again and and grab
the ball you want to grab it yeah i want
i want to try it you can do it
yeah it's safe now
maybe
you're the smartest member in whole life
indonesia
i hope so
who do you think is the smartest member
in whole life indonesia
[Music]
don't say anything wrong otherwise your
senpai will kill you
i don't know maybe it's all the same
part because she
she
math yeah yeah
i hate math
yeah can you make a portal
can you make a portal here
oh yeah yeah and
and maybe here
one more to the right i think
uh to the right
up but uh angled straight
and go straight
yeah it has to be more straight so it
stops yeah exactly does that work so
okay
i see now i'm here
but what for
i wanted to go here but ah
oh can you make uh the dark blue up here
yes
smart cool
i see
wow
i uh
you know you say ollie knows mathematics
but you know how to program a website i
think that's really cool
nah i mean it's it's not really a big
deal it's just
it's not really advanced though
no i think it's a big deal
you're sure okay i think i need to uh
somehow
make one
so so that i can
stop it stop you oh [\h__\h] i uh um
okay can you make your blue one the way
you made it before yeah oh yeah
you're right okay
[Music]
wait if you had uh if you didn't get a
pc until very recently yeah how
when did you learn coding before that ah
i have laptop i use laptop usually but
it's like how long have you been
studying the coding excellent work
for
for for the website i think i
i just want to learn about
it like
around how long a year maybe
a year
can you learn it that fast
i don't think it's fast though i'm i
mean there's still so much i need to
learn about the language i use
i guess so
but
when i saw your your debut stream i was
like so excited because you know there's
there's hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds of youtubers
so it's noble that some things are like
some people do the same things but you
did something that i've never seen
before you know
i've never seen someone do
a like a website for their debut stream
that was so interesting and i really
liked it it was very original
from my point of view i don't know how
to code websites so that's amazing but
probably maybe from someone who knows a
bit more coding maybe it's kind of basic
i don't know but but for me it looked
really cool and it was something really
original and that was really nice to see
someone try something new for once thank
you
[Music]
we need to praise each other there is a
japanese saying um
uh to describe yourself uh you can say
uh
no
this you can say if you praise me
[Music]
mommy big movie mommy yeah
she uh she lives by that model she has a
song in the original song it's called ho
menobi and it's about
praising someone and then
getting better by being praised so she's
all about that it's a really cute song
you should listen to it i have a listen
to noel senpai song
okay
okay she's really sweet oh so battle it
i think
you have to make this portal
after
i
jump up like when i'm up here you make a
portal down here you know what i mean to
stop me maybe maybe we can try and uh
yeah after um
up there ah
oh yeah first of all
it kind of has to disappear completely
oh there we go no okay
yeah okay and then so far so good what
number
um
was that even a good idea yes yes yes
how do i bring
why do i bring kobold up here
uh by
um
maybe you can get rid of your portal by
sending it here
okay and then
i
ah then i get rid of your portal
[Music]
i can make my own portal right oh yeah
hello
we need one up here
the bridge i think
where oh
it would be the dark blue can you make
dark blue up there oh yeah oh you're
right oh
damn
oh yeah we just looked her away yeah
yeah i forgot
thank you for the cats
[Music]
it looks like the same room uh
another one
or we can can we [\h__\h] ah another one can
you make a blue one
um like here
and then another blue one down here
i don't never mind it was all good
no
[Music]
i'll drop my dark blue portal
okay
yes yes yes and boom yes
yes yes yes yes yes here oh where are we
now uh-huh
and now
i make portal here oh yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
and now
and now and now what is this where are
we
and exit is up here
oh
oh no
oh no i lost the portal oh no oh no
not bad
[Music]
it's okay but okay so how never mind
never mind
[Music]
so
can you make a blue one here
ah okay
and then we go back
we go back to me
oh my god the other blue one here oh
oh smart really tennis mommy quinoa
wait i'm not finished i know
[Music]
here and then go back go back
um there's a this is funny i like i like
this puzzle there it's not too big brain
it's easy for two small brains like
us hello hello no no we went back sorry
i've had an optical illusion moment
this one
ah
[Music]
copper makeup blue no wait no that that
one is not the right one we can draw a
portal here and decide
oh in this
yeah
maybe it
can be useful
i don't know
[Music]
and we're going down is that where we
came from
because the the arrow says go down and
there is a portal platform here
ah
do you remember going here kobul
i cause i think i've never been happier
yet yeah yeah i think
i think so
should we
i'm scared to make a portal there
i don't want to mess it up momenta oh my
god
oh okay momentum i want you to can't
wait to pour it over there
yeah a light blue one yeah a light blue
okay okay okay
we need to go
just get rid of them
[Music]
get rid of the portal and we put it
together maybe yeah yeah yeah
let's go i mean let's go can we
go
mommy mommy
oh no
[Music]
failing gives me no new day i know where
it
is
you you start from the beginning again
okay it's okay i i'm gonna die too
don't die no maybe it's helpful if
you're already i see you hello
i see you
oh no because i just
uh hello because i just um
um
maybe
maybe don't worry i'll figure something
out um can i draw portal there
wow
[Music]
i'm already here wait oh oh
oh
okay
wait did you actually make it up there
to the top yeah
yeah yeah
oh
was i just too fat to go through
nah i don't think we can we in the
portal fit
uh two of us
yeah
um so
i wait here okay i will drop the portal
are you ready oh yeah okay okay i'm
ready
okay
um
this reminds me of that meme
[Music]
where the parent uh lets the child like
tosses the child and lets them fly can
you guys remake that meme with me and
kimbo i'm the parent
i don't know the mean dolphin
you will find out
[Music]
it's my intention
kind of different from the other ones
i like this one
[Music]
can you say it again
um
[Music]
we have
something interesting here once again oh
yeah here maybe oh where did you go
you're still there okay 105
fall through my portal oh whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa
whoa
uh-huh
hello i have the bridge i have the power
of the bridge where do we want the
bridge wait i'm trying to go here
yeah
maybe
what are you doing oh
can i make a bridge for you as you know
there's nothing to
[Music]
okay we'll figure it out
i can go there
[Music]
is there when you jump up there did you
see something where you could build a
bridge in theory wait after something i
forgot what i saw
okay
you
[Music]
or i could i guess you fly too damn it
uh but uh
i make the flying oh damn it we have to
get the portal yeah we okay we made the
bridge
yeah
i'll get the portal again
[Applause]
i know i know
[Music]
here
wait i can't
never mind
yeah yeah i think i understand what
you're doing i wanted to try something
simple similar i think
no no no no no no no no
one when you see
[Music]
oh
yeah
i think
i think we can't do it at the same time
hmm
and we have to order a little bit of
wrong probably oh there you go you're up
there now okay okay i know let's go you
can jump you can jump okay you can jump
you can jump you can down you can do
okay
yeah yeah the order was just needed just
a little bit of adjustment and now
can we make one here
no uh your light blue one goes
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're right
okay
[Music]
can we make that jump okay one two three
huh
[Music]
do everything together
um
all right all right we're gonna make
this
this looks difficult but together we are
a big brain i believe
first of all
see what's here
wow
that hurts
uh
there's another platform here oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
oh
okay oh
you're making some bridges
i want to
fall through there
or can i make this bridge go here ah
i am i can but i don't think
i think you're supposed to fly further
not walk through the bridge
yeah
do you have an idea
i have no id
yeah it's okay we just walked in here we
can take some time
think slowly now we'll be slowly
we had something similar before
i'ma try something
oh
trying always
is good
i see
when you're up there
maybe you have to help the one who's
flying or so i don't know
well of course there needs to be a
portal here what if um
huh
i don't know
go here again
[Music]
we
have
had a feeling that maybe we understood
something but
we're getting closer so when i fly in
there you probably
make
a portal
but do we need the bridge i don't think
we need the bridge but you can only make
it
no no
get rid of the blue one
make it somewhere else
yeah
and
now the other the light blue one too
the light the light blue one
[Music]
yeah uh uh
not uh both of them
both of them but i'll fall
nah i won i
won't fall
where okay uh and then cause i don't
think i want the bridge instead
you
uh need to uh when i fly up there you
put like for example the light blue
portal
on the platform
[Music]
like where
here danielle
[Music]
uh but no that doesn't make sense either
because i can't directly fly can can you
go up
here
yeah i tried but uh the wall
you know it will stop me here
and go higher
but ah
[Music]
oh
mean high hmm
okay that's for later
[Music]
wow
no
that's not it
thinking noises activate
yeah i'm everything probably thinking
too complicated
[Music]
but
if i go here
it will just get rid of my portal
ah what
i don't
no i don't know i don't know i don't
know um
light blue portal
somewhere
chat maybe do we need that help
short time please
we we we solved so much on our own maybe
one time we can
we can get chat help
backstabbing time what do you mean
backstory time
you mean backseat time yeah backseat i'm
sorry
i was i was trying to stay back sitting
but i say
influence
i'm sorry
yeah i know this is this is gonna be a
jump um
this is gonna be a jump and that one is
going to be a jump but we also have
bridges so what do we do with those
bridges how do those help us use portals
to go around the field
mommy
oh
you know momentum uh-huh we're gonna use
this momentum
so you go there here
use the catapult
and momentum here
here like so young you're flying to here
yeah that's what i want to do ah
and this is what you're gonna do oh
but i can't make
a portal there okay maybe i because
maybe i can go there
i i go there to make a portal
wait wait wait wait
wait yeah can you make one there and and
on that side and i just make a button
how do i fly through here ah
why
can you oh do you have to do it while
i'm falling like let's say
no no
no no no that doesn't
what
[Music]
are you going coupon you want to make
one here
[Music]
go go go
come come to the beach
okay
hi and come here and
come here
and you make the portal you make the
portal
yeah cause then i don't go through the
barrier
yeah
and then blue
oh
damn oh god
did you get that from the chat or did
you know yourself i know it's myself
awesome
i'm sorry
yeah he's okay
[Music]
now
i make one here
and
ah
i want to put it where the catapult is
to cut off
we had we probably just have to do the
same thing again
like put a bridge here
um
[Music]
so that i would go down
yeah yeah
something like that but i think with
your i need your like i can't do both so
one person has to make the bridges and
and come up here
can you yeah come come up here to me
here okay
ah a balloon
um
and then here
right here
here
okay yeah
and then
i can go back down to the catapult thank
you
thank you
now we need a little bit lower
[Music]
i see it i see
uh okay okay uh
here yes
yes yes yes
will i be able to use the right color
yes okay
[Music]
i think you can use the oh no no i
cannot
but i can make the bridges for you from
up here i think i see everything oh up
there yeah
like the bridges i just tried to not
fall down
or we did it in the wrong order
um
did we
but i can make i can do the same thing
uh probably
you will go
do what i did and i do what you did
okay
go to the
catapult i make one portal here and one
portal here
and so now the bridges are mine okay
and uh
you make those yeah
fall through the first one
yeah uh go through the first catapult
yeah now you're there and then can you
go on
where are you running below me
are you able to go on on the bridge that
i made
the first one
here
yeah and then go here yeah okay stop
stop stop stop
and now we bring you
here i mean i'm i'm it's okay no wait no
wait okay okay
huh
wait
ah the catapult the catapult
you have to make a portal
uh one at the catapult and one like
down down there you know
okay uh-huh
uh and oh yeah now we bring you back to
the catapult you go back again oh wait
wait wait um
now
yeah and this way we're both
understanding this riddle
because we both do the same thing no but
yeah now you jump in here
yeah should be fine jump and then you
may make it here
oh yeah yeah yeah
okay
yeah yeah that's that's what i did
before
okay okay okay and now uh
whoo
make the portal all the time
um
okay one color
and then come down here on the bridge
[Music]
it should be dark blue yeah
[Applause]
oh it's okay
but it's really hard indeed
that would be like yeah i think we could
have finished it earlier if you were to
jump first i don't know the chat was
saying that you should have jumped first
but this way we both understood both of
our parts we switched rows yeah yeah are
how are we
are we done with that or do we have one
more
this is a bridge building exercise i
know we have humans ah a few more two
more
mostly because you can build bridges out
of tears
oh
those stupid words are there again okay
um first of all koko can you make one
here
okay
and then one here
because now with my fridge we are
protected from the carrots oh my god
okay
wow
hello
they still can shoot me
bruh
[Music]
yeah we'll
find a way
i don't know how you died there um okay
i think just wait for the timing okay
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
um i think you gave them too much time
to shoot you
okay
drop your portal again so the yeah the
orange one
ah we need
i i
need another wall i think i need one
more
can you make a one here
[Music]
and boom yeah nice
and mommy
yeah
very genius
escape escape [\h__\h] nice mission yeah
i must look down because i was looking
at the chat there's a bridge okay
sorry
oh okay
oh you can make the blue one again
okay
we need one to block them
[Music]
there is more bridges up here
maybe
[Music]
no no don't deploy turret no no
uh
can you come back here
and drink where
uh actually maybe i oh we don't need
ah we don't need mine anymore do we
so
i put
okay but uh
no
i wanted how do we walk over there
though
[Music]
yeah
someone has to push the button combo
apple's for you mommy
okay i'll i'll i'll get rid of it yeah
yeah let's go let's go
really yeah
uh first i'll go here okay eh now
you might die mommy mommy mommy
come on
hallelujah
[Music]
it's easier than the previous one
no we're just getting smarter kobo we're
learning now we're learning we're
learning to think with portals yeah yeah
we're getting generouser
[Music]
yeah yeah i think now is uh
what that smell is seven yeah we're so
close
[Music]
what
look away look away
go somewhere else stop
stop starting
we need to pick brain time okay what do
we i want to see
okay
we can feel the wall if you make one
here or here somewhere here
maybe yeah maybe you won't see us oh
you're right
yeah go close to the wall okay
and
oh i make one here
and that way we can go up here but then
it will see me
yeah it's okay it's okay uh go up there
and then
[Music]
mommy
mommy i made these tests any easier
they wouldn't
yeah that's true gladys it's okay it's
it's challenging i like it
yeah we need the protection
again it's about timing okay i'm running
here and
ah we can maybe just
okay let's go let's go go now
wait okay where where uh oh okay
just
[Music]
mommy just go up here i'll protect you
i'll be reassembling
yeah come ahead and burn
yeah yeah just just go out there again
i don't i don't i'm not sure if i
understand yeah no no just just go let's
go let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
once we're up there can you change the
the yeah yeah this is what i'm gonna do
okay
nice
okay okay okay okay now yeah we can
make one here
and one here
oh my god
what happened did you
did you push over the turret
oh no it was even one of us huh where
are you
oh you're still there ah
i thought i thought you're you're the
one who died
oh it's a little nice
[Music]
nice guy mommy is a phoenix yeah yeah
you're immortal
nice yes yes
okay
don't get caught and
we will
figure this out
uh is there a bridge no
i think it needs to be higher yeah
on their height like here
but let's steal
let's
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i'm becoming reckless it's okay uh
ah i can make one too maybe no
maybe no i can't um
can you can you push them with the wall
try making one here
i guess not
yeah
it's just inside of them
okay
i feel
like
uh-uh is there there's more in the back
oh no
but they looked the other way
[Music]
what even happens if we push that
button
think think
think we need think to walk think
think
ah
i wonder if you can
send it to somewhere where we can like
um
splice the bridge
i love the bridges but i don't see
anything because there's i can't make a
portal there yeah
i think so
uh
thinking
let me get that i want to try
um
what is this
[Music]
we're just putting
i'm just putting the portal wherever and
hoping that it will work but
[Music]
what if i put it here oh
no that's for later i suppose because we
have to catch the cube or the
uh
circle later a circle
bubble ball
ceiling there's nothing on the ceiling
can can we just
push that button fastly
well we can try we can try ah
which one do you want to be protected
from
oh the other one didn't even see you
that quickly you pushed it what happened
i
don't know
push it again maybe it was the cube
maybe you dropped the cube
it opened up ah
oh i can hide here i can crouch by
crouching
oh no
that thing opened up over there can you
make a portal there
here or
here
oh yeah i can
so
ah walk through it
will you be able to push over the turret
from there where does it bring you wait
i'll test that
don't leave me alone
it's better than you dying
wait we both died okay yeah
because you die your portal also died
uh i wanna stay like through that portal
and see what i can see when i say okay
okay
[Music]
oh okay they can't hit me
oh if you jump down there can you reach
the button maybe can you make a
portal there again up here
here i'm right behind you
yeah
stay small
one over here one over here don't get
killed yeah
run
okay okay
one two three
oh
[Music]
okay what button is this uh and it it uh
oh it dropped oh my god many bombs
cubes okay and i
think i know what to do with that
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait wait uh uh stay
there yeah
there we go ma drop the uh drop the
balls again uh-huh
oh
higher maybe
one more
oh i see
oh
i was thinking to stop them so that you
can pick up yeah yeah i picked up you
did i pick up one but how do we get you
back here
should i pick the cube
too
i mean we can still get it later i
suppose but i don't even know where we
need to bring it i'm kind of still stuck
to ah we just want to kill those turrets
first otherwise we can't do anything
yeah but how um
can we
drop it on them or throw it at them
when this one goes
ah
yeah
i mean i i don't mean to do that but i
don't know it can be like that
i want to get the second one
[Music]
so that's the
so that's the flash
okay
can we do it again over there
push button again please okay i push the
button
[Music]
oh i'm so sorry i am so sorry i didn't
want to do that
how do i get to your side
um maybe it was a great job come come
here come here to my portal
to my portal uh okay i'm sorry can you
do it again yeah i'm just trying
something your portal okay and now we
don't have to
but it disappears ah
when it closes
[Music]
on top yeah yeah yeah okay okay easy
peasy mommy
[Music]
maybe it works with this one oh oh oh
i'm sorry oh yeah
oh my god oh my god okay
right
oh okay
okay
nice nice nice nice
these tests
[Music]
thank you gladys congratulations thank
you for completing the broken oh yeah
yeah complete easy broken easy test
oh are they broken they seemed fine
gladys
don't put yourself down like that gladys
yeah if you play the game um solo one
day you will
understand
the
that voice that keeps on talking to us
much better
[Music]
yeah outside there's a lot of banter and
the human she's a very interesting
character
okay
by accident
[Music]
for safety oh why do they want us to put
the cd back in again and then we're done
so
cd
yes
okay okay i'll come to you just a little
more
oh
what
you know that that city in bahasa is
actually a fantasy
[Music]
yes
okay that's interesting do i have to go
through this hole wait you can't wait
no i can't
okay
ah
we have to bring this ball
i i think i know if we have to stop the
flow of the laser
by putting a ball in between
oh yeah you're right then maybe the door
will open
but the question is uh
if the portal is ah do you see anywhere
to make a portal oh yeah okay
i'm done i made the portal
yo smart but i need another ball okay
okay
okay we need another bottle and put it
uh here again
where the ladies are in
yes guys guys what is this or flying
online
oh
all right still the bridge maybe oh yeah
bridge
oh
so
oh it goes ah okay we'll catch it here
[Applause]
you can't catch it from there okay okay
i can i can make portal from here
oh
but
it won't fly through there i think
there's another one here
another wall
oh yeah oh
hmm
i see you see
make one here and one here
uh
okay yes
oh where'd you go i think you're well
you would be able to catch it there
maybe
see when it comes out of the block
[Music]
wait
where is it
how it looks
it's too far okay okay
maybe i can stop
it
once it's uh there's just one one more
thing
maybe
you're right okay that that's more
simple
you think we can do this at the same
time again okay uh oopsie
count down three two
one go go
yeah nicer
oh wait there's a little bit more
a little bit more
bridge wow thank you for telling me that
it's the birthday i see that
[Music]
what do we have here yeah exit is over
there there's another one
right here
ah
oh
what if you walk through there
for the yellow one
hmm
i can't well i can go over there too
even without the bridge right yeah
all right um where do we need the bridge
or oh maybe
[Music]
i guess momentum
maybe
yeah we need to like fly fly from here
yeah
go there
wait where was the first one that you
pointed at the first one
like from here and we
yeah but where do we start uh maybe
ah hello
okay i see where we're starting that's
what the bridge is for
okay kobul
i think you need to come up here i'm
here
um can you make a blue portal on on the
two maybe
on the two uh
uh
i think no one one here one here and one
down here
ah
yeah
okay and uh
oh yeah and then i guess i can get rid
of the
we'll have to test it out
ah
oh you can fall down anyway okay
oh it just brings you there okay
how about how about
uh
i stop you somehow
you stop me
i will stop you not stab you stop ah
hmm
perhaps
make up make the bridge uh
sorry can we go back once
okay
but then what ah
we need the bridge first here though for
the momentum
what the [\h__\h] making like what happens
if i do this
oh no that's not it i want to stay there
i know i know you dropped once once you
are up here
once you are up here you drop your
portal here so the bridge will stop you
you know
okay
yeah okay
i believe i can fly
i believe i can
touch the sky
oh sure
not don't maybe
i'll just make a portal somewhere while
i'm flying
i'll jump after you jump
okay you just make the portal and the
one there
right
okay okay
uh
it's too
not enough
me i was not gonna oh
no no no
i
couldn't huh
we'll figure it out it's not like what i
expected but oh wait i think maybe
maybe i know
maybe i know maybe
you know there's two platforms oops [\h__\h]
that's the wrong one oh yeah backpack
there's two platforms right
two um like here uh number one and
number two
one is for you one is for me
one if we jump at the same time meet in
the middle and stop each other
that's crazy but
oh my god so
[Music]
uh you yeah you wait there
cause
when i make
uh uh i'll make a port yours is fine
yours is fine you'll just fall into your
blue one and and you get out of the
light blue one
i will
have to be faster than that are you
ready uh
wait um
you're ready just believe in me trust
fault trustful successful okay mommy
okay fall into your hole and everything
will be good okay at the same time at
the same time
stand right in front of it then stand
right at the top of it okay because the
the bridge will disappear okay three
two
one
i love you mom mommy phoenix down
[Music]
i like that there was nothing else that
we could use to stop us so we just used
our own body yeah
[Music]
and we'll be reassembled gently anyway
yes 41. 5 33 41 18.
5 33 41 18.
yeah that was a cool ending
very cool
did you like the game yeah yeah yeah
it's very fun
it's a bit long
i never expected you to make it
maybe i think it has a very big
satisfactory
satisfaction
satisfying effect
if you play it alone i think it will be
a bit more frustrating
and but i i still want you to play it
um
one day when you're done i i definitely
gonna play this too
to uh you know practice my small brain
yeah yeah
yeah it does make you feel smarter after
you finish the game then you're like oh
wow i did all of that i figured that out
dude
and if you need help you'll always have
to chat they love back seating or back
stabbing they love both of that
so you can always get help from them but
don't play it alone before finishing the
co-op with me now because we started
this we have to finish it yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah promise
maybe we can continue either next week
or the week after that we will have to
see how
our scheduling works but let's do it
soon because otherwise we will forget
how to think of portals
[Music]
i'm crying
everything happened
the moment she came into the voice chat
channel she was peeking and screaming
oh my gosh
i was very excited
i'm sorry for my work in english
no it's fine we completely uh
communicated fine i think completely
perfectly fine everything was fine i
understood you mm-hmm
and as you know oh
as you know my english is
not the best ever because my first
language is german did you know
me
sometimes you make up mistakes like that
i make some mistakes like that too
sometimes
okay what is that again dance down
when i read super chats i always say the
name and then i say thank you so i say
the gamer creed
and so on and i say
today for playing with me
[Music]
[Laughter]
have you ever been to europe before my
what
have you ever been to europe before rap
europe your rub
rub
what can you spell it are you b
right
e u r o p e the continent europe
europe
yes
how do you say that in indonesian
uh europe
oh
continent
right where have you have you been
before to eropa
yeah i haven't been
outside my country
at all never at all i even have
riding you have a passport plan just
once in my life
oh but within your country inside your
country yeah it's inside my country
it would would your mom allow you to
visit mommy kiwawa would your mom say
yes
or does does your mommy not let you go
alone
can you come to me i want to i want to
come to you i mean
yeah yeah my mom should approve
really
yeah take good care of you
yeah i
permission that she have to say yes so
it's okay
you have to travel around the world you
have to see everything yeah i want you
have to go to see all the horses all
along the horses yeah yeah
yeah yeah absolutely one day
one day because i i want to meet kobo
one day it doesn't have to be in my
country we can also i can fly to uh your
country i can fly to indiana
i can go i wanted to um i went to i
wanted to go to uh
bali
i haven't been to bali though i want to
try to go to valley you haven't been to
valley either let's go let's go
i think that's a good idea
ah yeah yeah yeah oh my god i'm so
excited
when you're like
embarrassed or excited you
act uh very strangely but um
sorry yeah
yeah yeah let out that yelling
aggressively very good let it out let it
all out very good
you need to let those emotions go
otherwise they will be inside of your
body and you will explode someday
kfb what do i do she's so cute can i
adopt her i want to adopt her how do i
adopt her
i want hair
i will i will let you go now but we will
see each other again to play more
portals too okay promise brahman thank
you
[Music]
thank you everybody for watching us uh
club's channel is in my oh
[Music]
yo
who's channel is in my description she's
a new member joined one month ago so if
you um if you didn't subscribe yet you
should subscribe to her channel okay
okay yeah yeah yeah and subscribe to
mommy chiara
too look at my viewers this is a good
mommy pinx yes oh thank you thank you
can you um help me say my ending
greeting in german do you also have an
ending greeting
my my my opening is also my ending
oh okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
like my ending is and in germany we say
alf pinatin so there is a german part
again i say goodbye in german
oh yeah what is that
i won i wanted to try
yes it's alf
auf
wiedersehen
auf wiedersehen
and in german we say and we say together
auf wiedersehen okay wait wait wait wait
i still uh just just
sing
yeah you just say auf wiedersehen
au vida sin like that okay
well yeah exactly okay and in german we
say
in
[Music]
yeah more portals yeah
okay okay i'll go to my ending screen
now okay you can also say your ending
ending greeting if you want okay
at your service now
thank you for watching
[Music]
okay i changed my screen
so
[Music]
you