[Music]
so
ticky
oh you can't you can't you're welcome to
use kkk the key
oh good morning
the kick is uh the german way of uh
of a rooster
uh saying what's it in a cockadill dude
what is it in english oh wait i'm immune
but i'm is muted for real like is that
not
the meme but um is actually muted in my
stream
all right one second let me let me i
mean you guys should be watching both
perspectives
anyway so that's that but let me let me
try to
uh wait um
i miss mew that oh no
no real i think no wait can you talk
again yeah no you yeah i think it
actually
is true but you can never trust them
ever since that one incident
wait oh yeah let me um
where would uh oh dammit why why why why
why let me do uh let me do
can you can you talk now okay now never
now i have never game audio nor almost
so that's not it how about this one
can you talk again ah oh there we go
there we go ammo is not muted anymore
now you gotta i mean i hope that
everyone is watching both perspectives
but just in case someone missed it you
got to give them another kick
[Music]
wait they see that my last bomb exploded
my testing bomb exploded
we tested the game once and um
uh on on amis side it did not explode
but on my side the one that i did was
where she was uh
telling me the stuff it exploded bye
don't worry we're gonna we're gonna be
fine
right i'm a professional
uh we're gonna switch turns in who is
gonna be reading
and who's gonna be defusing
and other members usually play this game
like with uh language barriers so i
thought we both speak
perfect english i mean sometimes i don't
but
close enough um but i thought we could
like create a little bit of a language
barrier ourselves
by me sometimes sometimes we could do a
turn where i speak japanese only
and then we could do a turn where ami
speaks
spanish only it's gonna be terrible
i understand zero spanish
and we could also do a turn where i
speak german
we could try that'd be interesting well
i mean it's not gonna go anywhere i
think the biggest chances we have is
when i speak
uh when i speak japanese i think you
might be able to understand a little bit
yeah but when you speak spanish i will
use my google translator on my phone
and quickly look up the words that
you're saying if i can even figure out
what you're saying
okay so yeah but i think that we can get
started with we can get started with
english
yeah yeah that's a good way to start all
right
yes are you are you ready should we
who who who should defuse the bomb first
i think because yours exploded maybe you
could try going again
okay okay okay we'll do um
and once again everyone make sure i
think both me and ahmed have
the links in the description i also have
a ammo's point of view pinned in my
comments
so you guys better watch both because
ame has the manual now and
uh when we switch turns and i have the
manual and she has the bomb
okie dokie
okay uh
why is the room so dark okay okay
bump and let's start with the
with the weird buttons with the weird uh
thingies
okay uh we have a c
with a dot in the middle uh okay
then we have a trident good as trident
trident okay and then we have a p uh
but like horizontally flipped
he horizontally flipped yeah
and a three a three the number three
will that turns into a snake
and has a v at the top of it
wait a sec a horizontally flipped p
yeah yeah yeah yeah that was the third
one that one oh okay
you sure it's not verdi wait
uh oh is it is that is that not the same
then a free that turns into a snack with
a v at the top got it
we got it okay first first it's the
trident
yeah okay and next it's the c with the
dot
okay and then the p u
and then the three again yeah we're
starting to have a really easy bumps i
hope we get some more difficult ones
later
oh but i have a i have a lot of wires
now on it
one two three four five six wires
um three of them are black two
are yellow and one is red
ah
cut the fourth wire look over your watch
and now we got the button it's a red
button that says
press okay hold on
and the button is ah
it's weird cause i don't know
there's so much text to read hold on
are there any batteries on the bomb um
what does the battery look like oh yeah
yeah how many batteries are in the bum
hmm i guess two or like i mean
two pack package packages there's like
one with two small ones and one with one
big one
okay uh
is is there a lit indicator with the
label
frk
[Music]
there's a there's a label that says trn
trn ah
there's a serial number if you need it
uh okay well the only thing i said i see
that has
wait wait i guess i think i see it has
more than two batteries you just
press and immediately release the button
but okay
do you want to try it i mean we have we
have one strike okay yeah okay
didn't work okay okay
uh it's the red button it says press
and it has three batteries pretty much
yeah
and trn is that one for three letter
code and then
serial code we have to
also there is an hdmi cable slot
[Laughter]
okay okay okay hold on i'll try again
oh it's not in the above i see
okay hold the button down until the
light on the strip comes up
and keep holding it okay yeah okay
uh when any five is in the countdown
timer
you can release okay
[Music]
um
i did not explode i heard that you want
me to explode um
i heard you want me too
all right though um i think next
i will read the manual ah okay
uh i will maybe turn off should i turn
off the game audio
for that what do you guys prefer do you
guys prefer if i don't have the audio
one
it's kind of uh maybe a bit distracting
let me turn it up okay okay
wait oh my god i don't hear her either
what is she streaming do you guys hear
her on her stream
he crashed on my stream oh no
i'm here oh
wait wait a second let me let me get
back and uh
you know you know the thing yes
sorry i don't know what happened my dog
maybe
stepped on the router really that
happens sometimes
oh yeah
okay there we go i fix it
oh you're back okay you disappeared
again and now you're talking to me again
so
no i don't know why it's never happened
to me before which is
hello hello yeah i hear you
you hear me yes okay okay good
i'm back in your room and
there we go okay nice one
almost existence is fading
oh it doesn't happen again well oh are
you trying to defease
uh are you are you backing ah are you
back in your stream
ah yes yeah okay okay all right
okay then you think
are we ready to continue is it okay
yeah probably okey-dokey let me open my
manual
yes okay i'm ready
anytime okay
i'm starting it okie dokie
oh all right move this hold on
all right we have the symbols and
wires should we start with the wires
yeah okay
so the wires there's three white wires
three white wires
is the last one white all of them are
white
all of them are white and then cut the
last one
okay oh no that was wrong
ah cut the second one okay that's
correct
that's kind of like contradicting though
that's contradicting stupid manual
i mean okay okay no
time to get angry
symbols okay we have yeah the fourth
keys and then there's a
three that just goes off into a snake
okay yeah and then there's the c that
goes into the curse of o
uh uh-huh yeah but
where are those together with a second
snake and see
snake and see snake
and see
[Music]
am i blind oh snack and see
snack but they have to be together in
one row
oh wait oh maybe you're thinking of a
different way can you describe the the
one
again the second one uh it's a c
and then it goes into a little loop oh
yeah okay
uh then describe the first one to me
again please
it's like if you start to draw a three
and then your hands start to shake
and then okay i got it i got it okay
okay the next one
it's like a pie symbol but with a little
line through it
i think it's a pi symbol what's the pi
is that oh
wait what does supply symbol look like
um but i guess it's this one from you
said there's a line going through it
yeah yeah that's probably what's the
fourth one
uh it's the x with the i in the middle
okay i think it's this column yeah
okay then you start with the c that
like continues to scribble
and then you go with the x with the i in
the middle
okay then the three where you
couldn't write anymore i got it okay
nice next there's one more thing here
now
um it's new it has it's like a green
grid and it has a one in the center and
then there's four
numbers on the bottom that i can press
so it's like putting in a code it looks
like
there's a number in the middle and then
there's four numbers down below
yeah ah maybe this one
uh what does the first number say one
oh on in the on the screen or in the
buttons and
on the screen yeah it has one yeah okay
like i guess press the button in the
second position
okay it has one green dot now and now
there's a bunch of different numbers and
now the two is on the screen
and we only have a minute left by the
way oh god press the button in the same
position as you press
okay the second one again okay okay
it now has a uh one in the middle again
oh again the second one again the second
one is wrong that one
no what has the one again in the middle
of the screen we have 40 seconds
oh if but which stage are we in now
wait does the first stage okay um press
the button
again in the middle yeah it did again so
now it's a one again
20 seconds which wait is that the second
stage now
yes yeah okay uh and there's a one in
the middle yes uh press the button
labeled four
okay next we don't have time it's four
five seconds and wait now all right
now i realize my mistake oh what does it
say now what does it say now
well i mean this one i at first i had to
figure out what
which one were you talking about because
we didn't do this one before
that's true maybe we should have done it
first nah it's okay no no no no first
time i mean if you defuse if you happen
to be in a situation
of you having to defuse a bomb and you
have never done it before well then what
other choice do you have
there is no practice time it's do or
die didn't
all right um um do you want to try the
same bomb again
like we're probably gonna do it i don't
know up to you if you want to go or we
can try again
okay try again but this time in spanish
okay so i'm i'm telling you or oh i see
i'm describing the bomb to you in
spanish i'm not wait oh
ah yeah yeah okay you just grabbed the
bomb to me in spanish yes
okay let me open on my phone uh
google translator uh from
spanish spanish spanish
spa spanish spanish
spanish time is going
[Music]
uh
um
yeah okay i think i know what you mean
um second button
okay
next
next stop squiggly
your spanish sucks
uh lightning
what squiggly lightning uh
ah and it must be this one so that means
wait and it's not that column
then it must be it must
it must be this one i guess because
there is no waters of that one
but what wait the first one you
described an age okay that's that's
that's the second one that's that's okay
what was the first one you described
bubble blowing oh wait it's here as well
i got it i got it okay
and what's the fourth one
backwards okay i'll get
spanish not as good as i thought
okay then first do the bubble bubble
blower
well let me see wait let me tell you
what a
bubble blower is in spanish do we have
the time for that
then you do the lightning
no eh
what
wait wait wait wait wait wait so the
first one you said was the bubble blower
the second one you said was a squ was a
squiggly
squiggly thunder lightning thingy the no
the
the second one was the h with the
squiggle
um and then the third one i guess was
the thunder the lightning and then
the sea that's backwards
eh
[Music]
um
okay do the bubble blower again
the squiggly thunder again
no okay [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
did it explode no okay
let me rethink every ah
maybe you're talking about
[Music]
i don't see any other thunder i mean
this one is pretty close
okay maybe do a bubble blower first uh
wait what what did this
okay um yeah i need to practice
all right do we wanna or do we wanna do
it the other way around i defuse the
bump
and uh okay i i talked to you
well this one okay let's do first i do
one in english and then i do
one in in in in german or spa
and not spanish uh japanese
all right all right martin i i'll get a
bump
real quick oopsie uh
second bump okay okay
wait so i'm just describing to you in
english uh yeah
let's do one english round again okay
oh yeah you have to turn on the game
sound one second oh [\h__\h]
okay well well
okay we have let's start with um with
the
with the thing with the big number in
the middle and four numbers underneath
oh okay okay okay
the first i see it okay the first big
number the big number is number one
okay press the second position button
okay
next number is number one uh press four
oh okay yep and next number is number
two
uh press the button with the same label
you pressed in stage one
so whatever was in the second position
in this first stage what button was that
oh i don't remember
i didn't know i had to remember ah
maybe i think it was a four
god damn it now let's start over
starting over
now now i have to remember okay i don't
remember okay
okay now it has a stage one uh number
two in the middle
uh press the button in the second
position
okay that was a four okay um uh now
there's a three in the middle uh press
the button in the first position
okay that's for three three four yeah
yeah
now there's a one in the middle press
the button with the same label you
pressed in stage two
[\h__\h] it was scraping it
you said stage two
stage one number two in the middle press
the button in the second position
okay number one um next up is uh
number three the button in the first
position
okay number one okay easy easy easy one
one
number three press the button in the
third position
okay one one three okay one one three
one one three
uh one press the button in the same
position as you pressed in stage one
which position is the second position
and i should have listened to it
[Laughter]
[Music]
i guess we don't we don't need other
languages to
create a language barrier this is
already
difficult huh it did wait what was the
full sentence that
you were going to say uh press the
button in the same position
as you pressed in stage one
but i
okay you want to try again yes i would
like to try again
um okay
i'll do it in japanese though oh okay
you're gonna describe it to me in
japanese
yeah okay let's see
okay japanese round thinking you always
might not be as bad as the spanish round
because i
have some maybe basic knowledge
okay um let's start off with those
numbers again
uh
same numbers as before we were doing
yeah
okay uh press
the button in the second position okay
um
press the button in the same position as
stage one so the second one
okay okay
[Music]
um
okay press the button in the same
position as you press in stage two
so the button in the same position
you're pressing okay
okay okay
this is the last switch
press the button with the same labels
the same number
as the one you pressed in stage three
sun
[Music]
okay
oh okay okay okay okay
smiley
and then let's see okay
and then the three okay and then the
start
okay
[Music]
uh
cut the last wire
that was so easy because japanese uses a
lot of english words so i
i wasn't sure if i should use them but
it definitely makes it a lot easier
[Music]
[Applause]
but like in spanish i guess you don't
have so many
lone english words do you
uh i don't know i mean you definitely
don't say yellow and black
yellow is mario maria
okay i think you should uh defuse a bomb
again
okay uh i guess the next one will be a
bit more difficult so let's start out
with english
okay
i'm ready when you're ready okay i'm
ready i got the bomb
okay detective tell me what's going on
uh okay oh let's do the numbers first
with the number in the middle and
the other numbers underneath okay easy
peasy
all right there's a four on the screen
press the button in the fourth position
okay
one uh press the button labeled fire
and now two press
the button with the same label
that you press in stage one okay
or uh if the display is four press the
button
in the same position as you pressed in
stage two
uh uh
with the same okay i got it okay
press the button with the same label you
pressed in stage
one same label
i gotta start over from the beginning
okay
okay four four uh press the button in
the fourth position
okay
one uh press the button labeled for
press the button with the same label you
pressed in stage one same label
okay
one press the button in the same
position as you pressed in stage
one fourth position
okay what
um press the button with the same label
that you press in stage one
okay i got it all right next wires nicer
wires wires other wires wires wires
warriors oh there we go how many wires
you got
detective five uh five wires okay
um one white two red one black one red
mm-hmm but there's only one
red three red and then that
then last one is oh okay i think nothing
here applies cut the first one
okay now next
uh
yeah i think wait just in case
uh how many batteries are on the bomb
uh one oh one oh uh four
oh there's a label label prn
oh no okay okay by the way okay then uh
press
uh hold the button and then
tell me what what it shows blue and
release the cotton timer when release
the button when it has a four in any
position
okay
[Music]
nice nice nice
okay okay okay maybe i do a bump next
and i do it in german
okay okay do you understand
any german no but i know german is
fairly similar sometimes
yeah english is a germanic language in
some aspects
okay but apple for real i will only use
german words now
you you you may use your phone with
google translate if you want
okay okay oh yes uh
the lesson is my channel it's uh
oh
[Music]
b
[Laughter]
[Music]
like yeah okay red blue black black
yeah yeah yeah okay
[Music]
okay cut the first wire
okay okay
what are the other ones uh vice okay
wait
are there any yellow wires no nine
uh is the last digit of the serial
number on the bomb
an odd number
uh odd number
oh uh is there only one
yellow wire uh
nine kind kind
uh are there any red wires
nine nine okay cut the last wire
[Applause]
okay okay okay uh
is it display the one with the button
nine
oh what is it a radio
nine is it something we haven't done
before
nine
is this a big button
um
smiley smile on x
with e okay okay okay the six
then the bt
and then the wait what was the other one
smiley and x-men
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god it's supposed to get harder as
you go [\h__\h] the next one
oh my god
i mean we did it did work well but it
would have had to be an easier
easier bump yeah yeah we would have gone
if it was the easier one
yeah oh my god good job though good job
detective
thank you i'm gonna try spanish again if
we're gonna play another one
yeah you should you should try spanish
again i'll describe
the thing no you describe the bomb and
i'll try to help you defuse in spanish
oh okay okay
but the the difficult one again
uh yeah we have no choice i mean i could
so i'll have to use some english that'll
be fine okay okay
i mean what choices have you used from
what i heard before
all right let's go starting oh i speak
english you speak spanish
oh wait let me open my google translate
okay
uh okay
okay uh so uh let's start with the one
with the four buttons i have two of
those by the way
okay um the first one
is like a like a man with a shield
holding a shield but the man has three
legs
this okay yeah okay okay
okay and then we have a c with a dot in
the middle but the c
is turned around like it looks to the
other side
uh-huh
and then we have oh that has uh like uh
you said it's a bubble blower okay okay
and we have uh the
it's just it's just uh it's just a
little scribble
it it's like a curve and then a zig zag
and a curve
okay okay okay bubble
okay
ah
[Music]
okay next doll again and the four
buttons
and one of them is a black p turns to
the other side
peep and then one
is a is a small b with a t in it
okay then we have a trident and a smiley
face
okay
okay this is a good way for you to
practice some spanish
[Music]
okay wires wires let's do some wires we
have
one two three four five wires two of
them are
white two are black
and the last one is red
uh two white two black uh one the last
one is red
okay
first
[Music]
are
we should do a turn where i speak
japanese and you speak spanish
okay okay work okay uh another wire one
uh one two three four wires one blue
one no uh white one black one one red
the last one is red
everyone in the chat is laughing in
space
um blue white uh black red in that order
okay uh one minute left we have two
buttons
one button i mean one two two big
one button is blue and it says press in
the middle
uh
[Music]
thank god
10 seconds
[Laughter]
we were so close
i want to do it again you speak spanish
again let's do it again
we will get there but that was kind of
an easy uh bomb
i would say because the the wires and
the buttons are somewhat easy okay we
again okay okay we have again uh two
uh two of the four buttons let's start
with one of those
uh the symbols okay and one of them
is uh the japanese katakana for
key pretty much but turn around okay
okay oh you know what i'm talking about
then we have uh an e like a round e
to the other side with two dots on top
okay and then we have um
an n but looking to the other side i
guess it could also be an
h with if you have fantasy oh and on top
of it it has like a little something
okay okay okay and then uh the last one
i don't know how to explain it's like um
it could look like the the the
silhouette of
of a head of a person
[Music]
one more time please
okay
no one more one more okay
see a copyright
okay then squiggle that's like c
uh or c or o c o squiggle
ah writing and then we have boobs
oh
[Music]
it's like a it's like [\h__\h]
it's um what is this what is this
it's the
the small letter y but upside down
yes okay
okay
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h] we don't have much time okay
let's do the wires fast let's do the
four
wire four wires one is blue two are red
and the last one
is uh white
[Music]
uh blue blue red red white
in that order
and we have one two three four six wires
and in this following order blue
red yellow white
black red so there's two red ones and
everything else is only once
blue red yellow white black red
okay big buttons big buttons one minute
left
okay uh one button is red and has press
in the middle
ah
okay yes
press okay until i see a line
okay okay
so
yellow button says press in the middle
uh should i press it and wait for it
[Music]
see okay uh white white white blanca
we're getting real good at this
okay let me let's do one more and i read
the manual for you do you have any
specific
language wishes um
or
[Music]
okay let me turn off my bgm
okay okay
and uh okay
okay start okay
okay first there's a
big yellow button it says hold
um
yes
there
[Music]
okay next uh another yellow button
[Applause]
and then an x with an i in the middle
hi hi and then uh six
hi hi hi hi hello smiley face okay
and look okay
[Music]
oh okay there's
uh two wire modules and another symbol
should we do symbol again
a lightning bolt hi hi
hi and then a backwards c with the dot
in the middle hi
hi hi hi single kitty and then the
bubble blower
hi hi hi hi and then the upside down y
with
okay
[Music]
a
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
first one has one two three four five
six wires
okay there's two yellow two red two
black
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah one minute and 19 seconds left are
[Music]
i think our most success successful runs
were
when i was talking japanese and when you
sometimes when you were talking actually
no i think when you were talking spanish
i [\h__\h] up the most time right we had
one good spanish
one i think yeah maybe but even in
english we had some problems
and someone in my chat says i'm a two
kia free does it mean uh
uh i'm exploded two times i exploded
three times or we won two times
i think you won three times what does
okay so team effort anyways yeah yeah
nobody won
we we survived
nice and that's fun actually like
creating our own language barrier thing
yeah thankfully um you speak uh
absolutely wonderful spanish
can you can you teach me like a tiny
little bit of spanish
ah okay what do you what should what
phrase
[Music]
maybe um
oh i got one
[Music]
are you wishing them a good night yeah i
said no i'm gonna say good night
[Music]
[Laughter]
yay thank you
for collabing with me today thank you it
was really fun thank you cara for
inviting me also for making a thumbnail
for me because i
i didn't you're welcome i had fun making
the thumbnail
i like um these like partner style
families actually
before the stream where we're talking a
little bit about everyone's like whole
life english
thumbnail creation styles right yeah
you can see like how everybody makes
their own style yeah
kelly and ina kiara we all have our own
style yeah gura has like always like a
big face of hers
and and and
amma keeps it simple kind of
simple a lot of fan art too
and uh
kelly uses like always the same fonts
like um and
she has a very specific style and she
puts like a lot of like words too
on hers but oh yeah nice she always has
like a like a little small
japanese text on it too like or roughly
explaining what they're doing in
japanese as well you know
yeah like you have used a lot of
colorful fonts like you use this like
purple blue
font yeah yeah yeah yeah i tried to um
make the font stand out a lot yeah
here's like a glow thing yeah and you
know uses like
sometimes sometimes she keeps it very
simple and has like some weird gorilla
art
yeah enos passion is graphic design
it's a good thumbnail yet i love it
i love it oh well let's let's continue
doing our best with the thumbnails
oh thank you for collabing today i hope
we can do another one soon actually we
should do a full member collab
sometime soon again we didn't do one in
january oh wow that's crazy yeah this
has been a while
yeah since christmas right yeah that's
true
all righty uh in german we say
alfredo's in thank you everyone yeah
you just you can you can take over all
of my greetings you can say kikiriki and
i say i don't mind some content
bye bye that was fun come on thank you
for watching bye
[Music]
you