do
jeez hello oh my gosh
horrifying
[Music]
hello i think we're going to use in-game
audio but for now i feel like yeah
just for the intro yeah
good and you're muted on discord by the
way
don't know if you're talking to your
viewers but i can't hear you could i
want to hear your voice
goodbye
[Music]
i had everything muted [\h__\h]
yeah we are not afraid of no ghosts we
are not afraid
okay we play if we played a little bit
of this game and i got so scared i
almost cried
so and you only got scared because it
got dark
because i was alone if one of you was
with me in the dark it would have been
funny but it was just me by myself and
it was very frightening
yours
[Laughter]
is mine like dropping mine my game my pc
does not like this game
all of a sudden whoa no
whoa red frame drop whoa
oh yeah oh this is just the internet
possibly uh no it's whenever i whenever
i'm in the game
it's just yeah uh
let me let me i'm gonna adjust some
settings real quick okay i'm gonna leave
the lava here and come back okay
okay no problem by the way guys i bought
a lighter
and i bought some salt because there was
none
so i didn't salt yep i did i did
salt i bought salt yes sauce cooking
what's the salt do uh i don't know maybe
you can use it in exorcisms
i'll bring up their mom and i'll buy a
thermometer
how are you guys moving around i'm stuck
uh at the st at the screen
or is that is that good uh that's kiara
huh how how did you break free from
justin oh ah do we not have a tripod is
that why the camera thing didn't work
probably i mean i just i tried to sit
down the camera but you can uh you can
pass it on to the floor or something um
the the camera in the truck never showed
any
anything besides outside uh
did was the green light on when the
camera did you see
cali just turned the green light on uh
yes i turned it on
there we go i'm gonna buy a tripod
because i have exactly 25 dollars
perfect oh perfect okay that should work
really well then
oh wait no i need to be level two and
i'm probably level one
yes we're eleven level one ghosty
hunters
after this one we'll be level two i
think oh yeah
cannot go shopping hold on i'm joining
back
and i'm coming back hey daddy
let's see if this helps yeah
also uh chad says that the salt can be
used to track the ghost via uv
oh so if they step on it and then they
like leave a trip
yeah or something like that i don't know
we'll figure it out see i see a seat
wow oh we're so cool this is like
this is like a an anime or like tv show
or something we're like cool
ghost hunters and this is our home cool
subjective
no oh my god
very scared possibly yes
okay uh uh by the way we're gonna we're
gonna use the proximity chat right
yeah we're gonna use english so we're
gonna mute us on discord once we're in
the game
okay i'm ready
okay i'm ready we gotta
select wait should i turn should i turn
around
on or off what does that do i don't
understand why my game is
all of a sudden now like
maybe it has to do with the fact you're
also streaming
well why this game what yeah
strange oh well if your
ah maybe that's what it is maybe ah
yeah yeah it drops performance when it
doesn't consistently hit 60 frames
so yeah maybe oh my now everything is
going wrong oh i love this game oh my
god
that's cool we got time we got time no
problem i'm just going to sip some music
i got five dollars in the stream take
your time take your time duda
oh this is bad what happened
did it get worse everything everything
is going
very wrong all of a sudden oh no what do
you mean
welcome to hollow en
this is always gonna be let's go i'm
gonna restart my game
i apologize if you wanna play around
without me please
please go ahead we can wait it's cool
wait who's this no problem what are you
doing i want to try and learn about some
of these ghosties
huh
[Laughter]
are you good man how are you good are
you uh
are you are you oh no
um wait what you're like
ah my game turned into like a strip
a strip on the screen what happened oh
okay oh my god
i think girl is the next
ghost this is not going to plan this was
working fine about 10 seconds 10 minutes
ago
i think the ghost got to you your pc
no not the oh it's okay not everything's
going to be perfect i mean look at look
at the character models and how they
might it's a good game i'm not
[\h__\h] on the game it's just have you
guys tried running dance for you okay
thank you crap for you callie let me
dance with you callie
thank you is this you you trying to
tango in here
[Music]
get a room yeah love birds i don't know
about sexy but i mean
there's a dancer
[Music]
just watch from here
shut up chad what's what's with your
hands though
what about my hands i have hands your
hands very weird
i don't see my hair when you're like
that you look like you're gonna do the
naruto run
you're gonna like you're doing it
wait does it did anybody else like tweak
their settings at all or is this working
fine
on everybody else's i didn't change it i
tweaked it a little bit but i don't know
if it
did anything uh
okay how are you doing yeah this is
weird how do you fold over like
cardboard
okay well i'll try this whenever you
look down with your mouse
you're doing that pose yeah
the only thing is we can't be very fast
oh my god
[Laughter]
very slow naruto
yeah naruto
[Music]
[Laughter]
i hear i hear um i hear the voice of
amelia watson
muted okay listen
and mute let's try this again okay us
messages to help
solve this problem once again it's going
it's going it's going it's gone it's
gone
so bad what what what exactly happens
is it like lagging yeah every time i
every time i tab into the game and i
start moving around
uh i don't rub it just goes
it goes bad um did you restart the game
stupid question
yes i turned it on and off again okay
um all right so how about 60 frames per
second
and one 920 by 1080.
i think that's what it's on yeah maybe
double check
okay yeah are you free to want to play
around without me
i feel so bad like this i don't feel bad
all right you're good um and also make
sure the game and obs are at high
priority
how do you close the door ah okay okay
cali let's play hide and seek all right
sure whatever
um where do you think i am oh wow you
hid pretty quickly because
tony hold on a sec it's fine we've done
this before um
sorry everyone i don't i'm sorry this
time
yeah take your time no worries
you underestimate me i will find you
hang on hang on a sec
all right you hid pretty well i give you
that much um oh
you crashed i wonder uh getting colder
colder
hotter hotter hotter hot hotter
hotter hotter cold cold cold cold
hot hot not me you know are you the dude
you're supposed to find oh wait you're
fit oh my god
amelia is doing technical support right
now in our discord she's not in the club
but she's
in the discord helping lots of technical
stuff
amazing i'm amazed
[Music]
oh kiara there you go where were you you
have to tell me wait this looks better
on my side already wait
i am gallatin
i'm in the closet oh
trapped in the closet i close the door
like that
peekaboo okay i'm coming out of the
closet for you cali
thanks
yeah it's only when i tab into the game
everything all of a sudden just goes
really bad
um is it because uh you were hosting the
game
possibly maybe hmm oh maybe i'm not
hosting
i think i think i'm the host now this is
good
i'm gonna stop right there we all know
what happens
when you try to sing that strong on
youtube uh okay
it seems better because i'm tabbed out
oh my tavern
also it's obvious that's dropping me
into the
red yeah obs is dropping to the rim
um uh you guys play player game
without me if um while i figure this out
if you want
i i i'm not sure if i can do it you have
to go down
you're the most experienced one when it
comes to ghosts
unless it's not that bad should we just
try one like this of them
all right let's try let's just try let's
just try it okay
what was the girls in this chat and he
says kathy
go to hell what
i'm saying select
a house yes
the farmhouse the farmhouse with the
moomoos
oh they're all um are we using in-game
chat or are we using yeah
yes yeah just for now okay
oh
put in the thermometer
okay good not ready
also is everybody that like does
everybody watching know what phasma
phobia is
have they played it before oh yeah good
out please a pro explanation about the
game
uh pretty much er ghostbusters except
it's us
we gotta hunt down the ghosts we gotta
search for clues before the ghost
gets us and kills us in front of our
team
hello it'll be easier to explain as we
go along i think
yeah who is this sir uh-oh okay
in-game voice now okay
[Applause]
how's everything going guerra
you know it's it's it's going it's going
okay okay grab the stuff always
people who are alone okay so we can we
can stick together
no no we gotta we gotta lure it out
first
yeah spread out you gotta spread out you
should be able to use the same thing
anger it and get some paranormal
make sure to refer
[Music]
[Applause]
oh kelly you're only 17.5 degrees
oh you're 15 minutes now okay okay
makes sense that's fahrenheit right no
degrees i'm probably fine i'm death just
don't worry about it
okay everyone ready grab their stuff i
want to go in i got the key
oh yeah actually i got the brand new
someone else grabbed the flashlight
do i have to be the one uh to capture a
photo of the ghost um
[Music]
the camera that i have is that one for
taking videos or for taking photos
the one for taking photos is the one
kelly has the one you have is for videos
like
okay um i have to put it down in the
room where we think
it is okay
use a flashlight you guys all have
flashlights
uh we only have limited amount of
flashlights so the one over there is the
uv
light for seeing fingerprints and stuff
i need since you've brought
that it might be useful yeah kelly
without a flashlight
oh damn she was so scared in the dark
how did you all get lights how did you
have one
hi i'm here too i'm adjusting more
settings yeah okay it's okay it's okay
okay
take your time i'm going in first i'm
not scared
hello lights camera hello
mary davis
[Music]
probably scope out where the
what this hello oh shoes
i'm dropping frames this is her little
cup
oh i see guitar
that's a guitar do we have all the all
this stuff we need
well we don't have as much sticks but we
do have a camera to take a picture of
her if she
does pop up i think
is this a life switch
so we gotta find like closets to hide in
right
oh there's an upstairs
this is a big map
can we turn off this radio wherever it
is
a key turn it off
[Music]
where's the radio
what did you hear that no one saw that
well maybe it might be in the back wait
did anyone check uh
where the breaker is
oh yeah i'll go check out the in-game
audio is
horrible ah such a nice neighborhood
can i walk any faster
now look any faster slower than mr
pierce honestly
uh oh
i guess there's no breaker on here is
there a way to change the map
click uh
ah thank you thank you oh it's in the
basement isn't it
i see my friends
so the breaker is in the basement i
believe
okay her soundtrack is going pretty well
pretty well
not bad girl has been in the dark for
too long it's fine
i don't have a good feeling about the
basement
it's the radio so okay ghost
[Music]
yeah we can go upstairs oh geez
said nobody ever but okay
mary davis give us hey guys
oh there it is
nothing's happening
yeah i don't have a flashlight and it's
already on the shoulder right now i'm
coming down there
oh wait did the light go off uh
oh dear that's okay
should be fine
okay
wow
subs freezing temperatures freezing
temperatures
freezing temps guys nothing written on
the
book yet that radio is really bothering
me
guys we got we got freezing temps in
this on the stairway
that was like minus 10.
no it was like on the stairs i think
yeah yeah
in the stairwell but when i went up a
little more it turned back to normal
i want to go upstairs now harry davis
oh my god wait did you don't you guys
i heard something callie
hello mary davis how are you mary david
yo mary you owe me
okay i'm gonna check for hey uh i'm
upstairs
freezing temperatures in this quality
right here guys freezing temperatures in
this closet
[Music]
i'm gonna turn on the spirit box
mary davis
mary davis can you give us a sign
how do i jump how do i drop an item
again
we might have to go out to check our
sanity we've been in the dark for a
while just thinking okay let's go back
i agree let's go back here no don't stay
there
he's gonna die it's all right it's all
right when they're alone
can you check our sanities when you get
to the truck please
[Applause]
[Music]
um
she might be in one of the rooms in the
hallway
oh that's uh i don't see much on the
camera
can someone reposition the camera
um
how do you rotate the camera yeah i'm
definitely thinking she's in the uh
closet here we're okay we're okay
over
is it upside down it might be upside
down
[Music]
uh rotate camera left mouse and then you
can place it with g
uh roger okay
friends
[Music]
is
is it is it working
all right
[Music]
freezing temperatures you know i'm done
guru i'm downstairs
there are dumpsters don't contact us
you saw ghost serves okay let's check
you only have 35 percent
oh my god the light turned off you okay
the lights turned off
are you okay yeah i'm okay i'm okay
i can't guarantee the ghost drives uh
all day
okay who has the flashlight you need to
go get the breaker
okay let's rule down some right now we
have freezing camps ghost storm
beauty
amusing temps you know is that you next
to me yep that's me
mayor hey um so what's uh what's going
on
uh where is everybody over
uh
over
oh do you see my shoulder light you're
okay let's do a little small discussion
here small discussion
huh
okay
let's narrow down let's narrow down some
candidates first and then we can
uh figure out what to do from there yeah
okay
okay that sounds good
no need to die for uh that yet
but it's fun oh not yet actually yeah
not yet not yet
do we have anything anything besides
freezing temperatures because the ghost
or have some and
some people in the chat said that but i
wouldn't trust it uh that much
i didn't see it myself
i don't think it was there i think they
saw a flashlight
i didn't see any orbs i only saw the
temperatures
um yeah well temperature we can still
rule out some
so um
can be erased
we didn't have emp emf 5 though we only
had emf
2 unless it booked out
so we can rule out a few more too
actually
great yeah using
did we try the spirit box
uh i can try it some more i didn't
really do much with it
it's still i think i still have it i
think
yeah since the the ghost only responds
to when you're alone
we probably have to send one person
there
a volunteer as tribute okay
but you're still only at 24.
22 23. look at all that
okay
and i'll report back as long as i can
before i you know
good luck i'm also gonna go into the
house on the ground
oh yeah if you can get a picture that's
great but
[Music]
she's going in
is that the basement or is it upstairs
oh there has been an increase of active
there's been an increase of activity be
careful
oh oh there's a lot of activity
got it in the closet over
activity is dropping over
you go out your sanities at seventy
percent
sixteen what's that
oh this is the upstairs okay
is it hunting
wait kelly
callie where are you oh my god
kiara answer me please
okay
[Music]
keep searching keep searching the
activity's dropping
girl you might have to get out of
i there that's kiara on coming out of
the house right now
did you see that wait you can take a
picture of kelly's body take a
let's take a picture it was a pool door
oh my god kuda is that four percent
percent sanity
girl maybe i should take the portal
you good i can't see does anybody have a
do you want to give a flashlight no i do
not
do you have a flashlight cara
kiara
like dangerous yeah
well if her body is close we can just
get it
get it and get up oh yeah yeah hi
i just got a picture how do i take a
picture
oh did you get it oh she died on the
stairs oh my god
smile oh that's not your face this is
your face
who's next i didn't get any evidence do
you want the spirit box
somebody else could have the spirit bugs
oh
oh oh yeah
find the closet there's a closet
upstairs upstairs kiara
kiara go upstairs go upstairs
there is a closet to your right
i hear noises
there's a flashlight on the ground oh no
ah
alright uh how good are you guessing uh
guessing on the
answer
huh okay okay let me let me think let me
channel my inner um
detective work
okay
[Music]
okay increase chance attack in the dark
turning lights on will lower chance
attack
okay freezing damps
uh
we'll attack more often than any other
ghost
what do you think it is i'm thinking
right now
um okay
we only have like the only solid
evidence we have is
is the freezing temp what the
possibility of a ghost storm
oh okay do we wanna
huh
i like how we're just chilling next to
uh our friends bodies
it's still warm that's pretty it's like
over here
let's see it's a bit cold you know
freezing temps our bodies still warm to
keep us
toasty for a little longer
uh okay oh if only we had the salt we
could have
probably tried something because rats
have a toxic until
salt um because we don't take a uv
like you think we can maybe we had a uv
light didn't we
in the truck i think we i think we did
i think okay because i'm thinking it's
rather a
wrath or a mirror
oh yeah turning the lights on okay i'm
gonna i'm gonna check
if you have the uv light here
okay girl oh how's your sanity
your son is that 0 girl
i think you should get back in the truck
i'm perfectly safe okay stay here
stay here keep me informed i'm gonna
go check if there's any uh fingerprints
if there isn't a loan yes if there is
any
and i die then you know what to do
i believe in you okay
i'll keep you up okay
okay you guys can see that you're going
for this you're made for this
top detective sorry i if you
plug your ears on it
[Music]
can you search for doors
so far okay
uh also check the camera just in case
you see any ghost storms
i am i am watching the camera i just saw
your feet run by
okay okay yeah i'm upstairs
okay
uh i think i think on the door if you
find the the prince on the door will be
rather easy to see
[Music]
um
yeah yes yes yes i'm still here
okay okay yeah
if i'm dying then i'll scream before i
go so you'll know
that sounds like a very good plan
what's a good song just wait the ghost
can hear us
if we talk too much
[Music]
we can get something
i feel like i hear footsteps i'm scared
can you tell me the other day can you
tell me
um the other characteristics of
other characteristics of a mare
a man
here yes yes the mirror
okay turning on the lights
uh lower the attack chance but it's been
dark in the house for a while
yeah that's what's been thinking
[Music]
okay um i didn't see any fingerprints so
it's a yuri but it can't be
a stronger effect on people's sanity but
my sanity was was pretty much zero and
it went for kiara instead unless
um
yeah let's go for mayor
i think we we left them dead for long
enough
okay okay huh yeah we didn't get to use
the spirit box because i'm a dummy and i
had it
it's okay it's okay maybe i should have
brought it and then use it oh well
okay um
i dropped there do you want to try it or
i think we should at least get another
game in so they can play a little more
okay did you fill in your journal
yes yes yes yes yes okay okay
[Music]
whoa
rip i like how the uh
the not dying oh
welcome back i prepared some jokes for
you
i was a yuri
okay okay chad is actually good at this
game
no no my sanity dropped wow
oh wait maybe it is um
oh someone dropped kiara dropped
did she crash there she go
hello who's left
uh
yeah i tried to leave the the menu
button here you left the room once again
okay okay oh she accidentally left the
group
she'll be back she'll be back she'll be
back oh there he is
huh you're already home i'm back i'm
back
wait is this in the chat because it
doesn't actually know what they're
talking about
it's the sanity um attacking thing like
the whole group or just one person cause
like if it was like an average
between everyone then it started
attacking a lot more after like gurus
dropped
really low right so oh it's the group
it's the whole group okay okay
that makes sense ah
by the way you you got some uh the the
the journal
was in the kitchen so we should have
eventually moved it upstairs
so oh yeah right in there and also we
should have been looking for the ojia
board oh yeah luigi okay
[Music]
next time we move it where it belongs
hey can i buy a flashlight if you have
30 dollars
uh i think i have i think i have 10
bucks and some bus tokens and some
pocket lid so can anyone lend me like
maybe 20 bucks
i mean if someone has extra money then
they can buy more
you don't have to you know i'm five
dollars short i'm sorry
[Music]
don't worry it's fine we're all broke
i'll just wander through the darkness
again that always works
we already have a ghost writing book
right or is that a different thing
we can bring the maximum of two maximum
of two but we already have one
so we can bring then i think i'll buy a
tripod now i keep talking without
pressing the button
same same again i was like okay so we
can bring a maximum of two
and then we already have one so yeah
okay i bought the tripod so we can have
the camera
up higher and see more things now okay
um all right gotta select a job is it my
turn now yeah i think so
okay so which one did we do before just
now
that was like a house yeah that was uh
that was a normal house it wasn't
there's like two farmhouses and then one
normal house
tanglewood street ridgeview roadhouse
and edgefield street house
want to go to texas texas we shouldn't
go
we shouldn't do something too big though
we shouldn't do something too big
because we're never going to
finish it let's go to texas
texas cities is it a house in texas okay
let's see recommended team
size one oh okay that means it's a
smaller amount all three different
single floor house with a basement the
owner called this morning
said it sounds like a dangerous ghost is
haunting the area this one sounds
dangerous so you'll have to be careful
with this one
gather evidence as soon as you can more
info when you arrive
in size small okay
i'm not scared anymore what else do we
have two-story six-bedroom with a
basement
possible ghost sighting this one sounds
dangerous yeah wow you
could've told that one gather evidence
and leave recommended items thermal
and then the one that's in it seems like
around ny
two-story four bedroom with a basement
okay the ghost of ame will keep us safe
okay so i wonder if you guys want to do
the one the one-person one
yeah let's do that let's do that
we're going to test okay okay yeah
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait
yes wait wait wait uh i have to add the
tripod oh yeah oh yes
okay there we go hey
also how do you guys use the items that
you buy
uh you have to add them in the equipment
yeah yeah
okay got it got it okay
the ghost responds to yeehaw well
we better try and find out howdy howdy
folks
howdy ghosty
oh yeah now you're addicted okay good
okay okay okay we're good now
there is no salt though there is no salt
cali
but we might need it we need it
and chicken oh i thought if she dies
emergency rations you got it ready
welcome
howdy
starting the yeah oh prevent the
ghost from hunting with the crucifix
have a member of your team witness a
ghost event
close the area near the ghost using
smudge snakes
oh we're missing someone uh
cali i think oh yeah sorry i was talking
and you guys didn't hear me
um nice okay richard brown only responds
when people are alone come on
you should oh you're behind you can't
come to anger and get some paranormal
activity
refer to your journal does anyone have a
crucifix
no i think that's not even no crucifix
uh oh well i'll get the book
oh did someone take the emf thing with
jake
yeah i have it okay oh okay okay good i
i thought we didn't have it for someone
using
my lighter
razor lightest boys this is a sad song
oh my god look at this little
there is so wait is there a limited
amount of salt or do you have like in
the salt
sorry is there really a way to turn off
push to talk
um i might have to like go into the menu
i don't know maybe yeah
uh yeah forget that maybe next time yeah
um let's see three uses on the salt by
the way guys
oh okay okay okay roger
if you need more i just want you to roll
on some gotcha and you'll have more soul
this is a ghost event i think with
how snow we are doing these things i
think this might be the last game
yeah maybe okay let's let's do our best
to get this one out
our goal is to have everyone alive let's
try
yes let's
go here we go
here we go should i say the iconic line
hold on i'll wait till we get inside of
the house
[Music]
you think that'll summon the ghost hello
let's get some light popping out in here
hold on
i have a lighter from me after side
uh what's the name again oh nice setup
what's the name of that it's richard
brown richard brown richard brown
what are some what's with some richard
nicknames richie
it's a bear richie
oh my god you clipped to the door scared
me
how do you even open the closet door
how do you open the closet door again
um
[Music]
oh wait that's one of the objectives
experience a ghost event or something
like that
i'll check the i'll put the temperatures
okay i don't think he's at the dinner
table i think he's hungry
oh richard brown guys we have some we
have freezing temps
freezing temps oh god
in the kitchen freezing he's definitely
there he flipped the cup
at me freezing temps in the dining room
okay should i use this okay
somewhere lights here maybe i should use
the salt guys is there lights here
richard brown
i'll put some salt in the kitchen huh
that was me by the way that was me that
was me oh i dropped the i
just jumped in there i dropped something
can someone give me some light
light yeah yeah yeah yeah salt is it
working when i try to use it i got it
richard brown
wait did i don't turn this on
oh there you go richard brown
maybe he'll talk to us richard brown are
you here
hold on i have the book i'll put the
book down
i put down the book is this a picture of
you richard brown do you have a monocle
and a mustache
oh my gosh when you have the flashlight
on the face i thought it was the ghost
that was like
ricardo brown
ricardo richard brown how old are you
yourself oh you're a coward
which direction should i put the camera
uh towards the
towards the dining table uh dining table
okay
richard brown
wait this is
domo richard brown
richard turned on the camera i turned on
the camera
okay you guys you guys stay here i'll
i'll check if there's any fingerprints
[Music]
richard brown would you like to be a
guest on the contest
richard brown are you adult
thunder richie brown are you
[Music]
we got a three three on the emf i don't
think he liked it when i asked him if he
showered i don't think he likes to
continue
can you ask him what shampoo he uses
richard brown richard brown richard brad
richard brad richard brown
richard brown is starting to sound like
not a word
maybe we can ask him some questions are
you here
richard brown richard brown
are you richard browning smelly uh
kiera are you alive
okay okay i thought i didn't hear you
for a while i thought you
been died activity from the ghost uh a
little bit
okay yeah he's here he's on this i think
it's it's when the emf
paragraph is saying we should turn off
the lights but i don't know how i feel
about that
yeah i don't know
and this was a it was a three on the emf
maybe we should turn off the left
richard brown you know how to swap
confront
i think is
okay pick up this pencil and write you
coward
hey girl i'm gonna leave you alone
always turn off your lights
kelly yeah i have to wait
okay
he threw something on the floor
richard brown
what's the song for oh never mind i know
what to solve for
richard brown richard richards richard
brown richard brown richard brown
do we have another
i think we really need to be alone
[Music]
wait emf iv
oh it's emf 4.0
wait it's game of five
it's only four one two three four it's
five
that's four
and i'm still not sure because the chat
was like 50 50 on whether or not it was
go starts or if it was
red
richard brown
i can't pick it up
wait who's taking pictures leave someone
in here
richard brown richard brown where are
you
hello here it really doesn't
[Music]
oh fingerprints
back here back here come on come on what
i'm upstairs upstairs come on it's
either a race
or a banshee i don't know if you guys
can see it but
oh how did you see that you smile
ah wait tell me again this is it that
green thing that showed up there
yeah fingerprints i want to take a photo
of it
do you have the camera yeah the camera
uh oh a bit more a bit more
it flew off the table
did anybody get ems five
we only got a four at the highest
fourth the highest richard brown we
haven't had any footsteps
so it's either a banshee or a race
please
tell us are you here
richard brown please write something
richard brown howdy maybe maybe let's
just talk to him and not use his name
maybe he doesn't like it with me okay
please
write something
has anybody heard footsteps
please write a message
well it likes to be it likes us to be
alone right and the the banshee also
likes to be alone okay it stalks people
who are alone where's kiara give us
a sign
give us a sign
yeah it's freezing time i feel like it's
a banshee because the alone part
okay should we test it out yeah probably
give us a sign okay what do you think
it's better
cali or yeah oh dude
chad gets chat made a good point i'm not
talking about it
sign hello richie
give us a sign richard is this the keys
to your automobile
automobile record i have obtained your
keys
richard what are you doing richard miss
brown
please scream
scream
oh that doesn't sound good footsteps
footsteps
[Music]
oh oh lights flashing it's a bang
okay
oh
i saw the ghost on the live camera by
the way it was really pretty
what did it look like
oh it looks like yeah
i think it's a banshee i don't i don't
really know how the other ghosts look
like so
i'm not sure okay let's sing something
like that
the truck told us to get it away from us
using a crucifix right
what that what's that mission come up if
it wasn't
a fan shoot does it come up if it's in
our banshee
here okay
but there was a footstep okay others
would sit
but we didn't get emp 5.
brad
you can't be tracked by footsteps
fingerprints
freezing tabs unless the emf thing is
uh you know bug
um
it has to be abandoned
a porsche little poltergeist
footsteps because i i'm pretty sure
uh i think jesus
okay jeez
check for ghost storm okay
okay i'm calm now i'm calm
what do i even
she's just she's holding the camera
here oh man we can take a selfie
[Music]
jeez
okay let's focus on the game
okay um nice legs
oh guru sanity is always so low there's
no
activity though
oh did they figure it out
do i have to bring back the items you
know
the tripod at least at least my
thermometer uh
i need a thermometer maybe at least my
thermometer please
when i bring the tripod i can't bring
anything else though it was like
i don't know i don't have to
uh oh that says no thermometer
you know um thermometer can also be
uh uh read as salmon
i think it's pretty soon
my thermometer my friends huh really
give me i too witnessed my thermometer
friends
ina died in front of me i washed it
my thermometer
wait wait girls wait wait wait wait
aren't banshees only female and this
name is male
1 ah
don't worry about it is that random does
that matter in the game i thought
banshees were only
irish banshees can be male maybe
like the raw matter
not okay maybe not in this game okay so
wow this would be good for gesture
drawing screen kept this
oh no my items
no wait don't wait please don't leave me
please i'm not in the truck
welcome back i've prepared some jobs for
you
all right what is a wrap
oh
wait there's oh you know the bone is it
called
the bone evidence why am i level one and
you guys are level two
because you you died
uh in the first game so early i guess i
don't know ah
yeah i suppose that makes sense that's
fair ah
oh i have 45 dollars still can't get a
flashlight
money what should i buy it like do i
still have my thermometer maybe smudge
sticks i'll get the smudge sticks
i have 285
[Music]
i want a head mounted camera
that sounds fun all right oh now we have
new vlogs squad what can i play through
our flashlight with this
let's see okay i need a flashlight
uh and a thermometer can someone help me
budget this
look for a small one
ah you don't really need any of it okay
how about tanglewood street house size
thermometers and a small three bedroom
single floor house the basement got an
email from a friend
he says there is definitely some kind of
like we don't know what their mom
head there and gather as much evidence
as you can so a ghost removal team can
finish the job
okay let's go okay
yeah i'm ready spaghetti lighter and not
thermal they're okay lighter
level two i am also ready
spaghetti
okay sorry i was buying my thermometer
i'm ready
uh okay let's go
last game last game wait a minute wait
guys guys guys can we turn off push to
talk
oh oh yeah we have to like leave the
lobby to get to the settings
if i recall we have to leave yeah
forget that forget that next time okie
dokie
okay let's go
fast loading all right boston what do we
got
thank you hey ina yeah
what does this look like on your screen
what does this look like
[Laughter]
you got possessed by someone everyone
to everyone that just goes response to
everyone so
you should be able to use the same to
anger and get some activity make sure to
refer to your journal
all right um a photo of dirty water in a
sink i can take a picture of that that's
insane
um thermometer
i'll be checking the emf
i got the book too and i'll take the um
oh oh what's the mission um
i thought i would have a member witness
a ghost event dirty water
in my future okay after this i have a
lighter for the smudge stick
i just do excellent do you like it would
you like me to give it to whoever has
this much sticks
i know i think anyone else wants money
nothing you i don't know how to use
things i don't know
either but we'll learn i have maybe one
of us
can have the sticks and one of us will
light them i have the lighter so we can
do that then
got it all right sounds good let's move
out ghostbusters move out
i got the keys
hi friends welcome to my crib
welcome back
what was the name again oh good good
question
daddy car oh it's the same house
oh i guess it is i'll see this time
there's no bone what was that bone
before then there was a bone
and the previous house went oh yeah we
could have brought it back give us a
sign
oh
[Music]
i've been wondering something something
something give us a song
oh i can't jump i don't see myself
patricia clark patricia
i'm gonna check the basement
i'm gonna follow you
wings you should clean up your bones oh
take a picture of the bone apparently
guys take a picture of the bone patricia
clark
oh that's right i don't have the camera
no dirty water is this a chicken bone or
is it a
camera i'm useful i'm useful i can do it
all right this looks like the uh where's
the sink
right though right
back leg chicken bone maybe a turkey
oh okay yeah good good
oh light flash flippers
or maybe twitter doesn't show up until
oh
good point girl let's check it out i
picked up the bone
he's got the bone oh
enough there's water in here oh we got
emf4 emf4 in this position
uh yeah um four
uh uh it's gone now it's gone
that was a four yeah only five is the
clue
okay can i put the
it was i was successful
no i saw four lights only
like it's fun now why is it gone
kitchener give us the next amazon
bestseller book right patreon
patricia clark hello patricia
trisha misha clark
where are you patricia clarke
huh
is it my radio i don't know
do you wanna try putting it down you
hear it now
i let some kid yeah i'm gonna leave some
salt something
what is that that's my radio that's my
spirit ah okay
oh oh
what what is that what's that always
there what is that
it's not salt oh it's myself ah okay
okay
i wonder where else i should put it
maybe
i'm gonna bring them i'm gonna be
careful so that
they don't get salted
by the ghosts
[Laughter]
patricia clark can you speak to me
please write something
please write something okay nothing here
[\h__\h] up give us a sign
they say turn off the lights for spare
box response so i'm going to turn off
this light here okay i'll check the
upstairs
oh
speak too much
okay
i think it might be the kitchen
[Music]
where should i put the camera in the
kitchen
girl can turn off the lights here huh
again here is it here
here you can try it like this
hand print hand print yeah fingerprints
fingerprints
fingerprints everybody put fingerprints
in your jar i know
fingerprints
nice nice okay we haven't had any
the lights are dead the lights are good
it said kill in the box it's like two on
the box and therefore okay so
oh
will do you we need to get the
evidence we have oh we have fingerprints
okay true
okay
all right all right
[Music]
okay i'm tucking the uh sanity etc
um there's not much ghost activity
uh our sunny's looking pretty good
oh the breaker is uh
i think it's upstairs or down it's
downstairs downstairs
i think so in the basement it should be
right
like slightly right up the stairs you'll
see it it's pretty small
okay our sunday points are doing okay
kelly's at 84. girls are 74
tiara's at 78. there's not much activity
so i think it's okay for now
no freezing temps
okay down there
please get the box
oh the box is on ems
it's okay i'm still here guys i'm still
here don't worry
i'm alive i'm alive
oh i'm a little too big
[Music]
it went down again oh activity is going
up careful
girl you're alone might be getting ready
to hunt again
i'm in the basement
okay the breaker is right to the left
yeah right there i'm gonna go
i don't think there's a hunt yet so
please
[Applause]
a great job
okay we can see again uh
what else can we try wait can we narrate
down
since we have two evidence right now
fingerprints yes yes we need um
i really want to see if we get dirty
water in the sink
that's pretty rare
um
[Music]
did someone make it ring no it's the uh
there's the phone
good question where is the phone
also it's definitely in the kitchen do
we have to pick the phone
we have to look for the ghost store for
a good evidence
do you have to turn off the light for um
the ghost story patricia clark is this
still patricia clark
patricia clarke where
[Music]
no we did not have freaking temperatures
please write
patricia hello has anybody seen a ghost
orb no no but i repositioned the camera
to the basement so maybe uh where should
we
where should i put the camera definitely
in the
kitchen it didn't see anything when i
pointed it to the kitchen
okay i relit the candles wait did you
set up the camera
yeah i got the camera but in the kitchen
i didn't really see anything oh you just
just leave it there just leave it there
because the
ghost is here definitely in the kitchen
give us that sign do you want to use the
i mean we already have spirit box
evidence so we don't really need it
um unless you wanna can we like rotate
this
uh huh
[Music]
patty give us a sign there you go
yeah pillows patricia uh freezing throw
something
patricia clark i'm gonna go check the
camera for ghost like things okay
okay i'll go stop only in the night
vision okay
uh so we have to turn off the light then
don't we
yeah it only went down to like three
oh
what's happening
huh
[Music]
okay i'm gonna try
wait someone's dead no we still see
their sanity it's okay they're alive
they're alive
oh i see them still bright i think they
turn on the light
wait why'd you move the camera
we have to turn off the light
all right
no i don't see anything
it's in the kitchen it's in the kitchen
i need you to put the camera down in the
kitchen
put the camera down and turn off the
lights
and then turn off the lights please
i uh callie's at 61
girl 52 and kiara ff 49
thank you yeah there was a slight peak
of activity just a moment ago but it's
dying down
may i please ask what you're doing tell
me
it look like you're possessed there for
a second
over
okay there's no activity oh keeps
turning on the light
right what does the ghost look
like look like honestly
there's no activity yet over
these look like burnt potato chips
or fries
small white spots so it's like those you
know like when you take photographs and
you see like small
orbs and you're just like oh this is
cool this sounds like that
very low activity
their sanity is okay i'm the highest
sanity
mm-hmm
is in the garage
[Music]
um
yeah i should
i'm scared
okay
hello
can you hear me
oh there was a second activity
it's hunting
wait colleen callie no
callie
callie's dead
i saw her near the i just saw her go
across the screen and then she was
silent
wait during the hunt does the
walkie-talkie does not work
maybe i couldn't hear you guys or
ah
okay oh there is a radio jam
yeah they said kill
so we need ghost riding to make sure
that's the spirit
what is that noise yeah but it has to be
alone right
if they want to write down something
they gotta be alone
okay um i have the most sanity so maybe
i can go
get the book and put it on the kitchen
table
oh update journal right now
but it's in the it's in the kitchen so
i'm just trying to see if i can move it
to the kitchen
table okay
goodbye thermometer i'll
bring the bring the lighter because it's
cheap
okay okay i'm gonna make my way to the
dining room to see if i can
uh reposition the book to the kitchen
okay do you need help i can help oh do
you actually have a flashlight i could
use
go out good look at the camera
camera oh
camera do you see will you see the body
i see nobody wait what
oh you got that's what you don't see
that what do you mean you don't see that
i don't see anybody what are you kiara
i guess my game is bugging or something
i don't know your 70's at like 30
soon okay anyone can get me a flashlight
into the uh
the kitchen and then i'll stay there
[Music]
it must
be the writing so it can only be the
spirit
okay f hello i forgot your name
ghost that's a good point patricia
patricia
trisha right in the book pictures out
there's no one checking the activity why
are you all here
huh what the what you're supposed to be
checking the activity of the ghost
gummy in the van yeah at least at least
one person in the van
and then you can you can you know
patrice shop trish trisha
oh we can leave and come back if you
want to move
very good camera angle placement i must
say
oh yeah trisha trisha
uv
okay i don't see a flashlight
are the lights off they are
yes they're obvious well maybe not
all right maybe leave the book on the
table for a while
yeah put it down yeah let's try putting
it down
okay somehow
hey patricia you stink
peace shower
patricia clark where are you
pictures of clark wait don't don't sign
don't don't use the flashlight
oh okay all right that's what's he doing
in order for the ghost to use it
patricia clark give us a sign patricia
clark please write in the book
patricia clark hello
patricia clark where are you
patricia clark
already
yes
but then i don't know what happened do
you can you scroll your item and
oh yeah i think i see it in your hand
oh yeah sorry
you know where did you go you know where
did you go oh where did you go
this is hq hq
to go squad
yes i read you over is everybody okay
over
i think the chicken died over
i mean oh no okay uh
she's at the door over
uh i can't i can't seem to open the door
over
there
[Music]
yeah she did i think
no books here books here books here okay
no writing
no writing no writing no writing and no
arms
do we take a 50-50 we can you wonder
oh it seems like wait give me a moment
i think i'm frozen
uh ah uh-oh
no frozen and like uh like my avatar
will you write in this book please it
can't be that hard just pick up the
pencil
slap it around throw it across the room
push me touch me do something come on
huh i'm still around sorry
i'm okay i'm okay
come in hello ina to enact shark in that
shark
okay i'm back i'm back oh hi hi
hi so it killed me where is this ghost
it kills her here
should i bring the thermometer back just
to check where it is
okay i'll bring the thermometer back so
we can double check where it is
[\h__\h] camera and garage
okay apparently the book and uh camera
is in the garage
camera camera is in the kitchen still
you're out your 70s at their 18 19
what's that coming from okay
okay roger that you want me to keep an
eye on the activity
okay we'll do it
no activity so far
oh activity is going up a little bit be
careful
you just walk
huh hi hi hi hi hi my hand this one
huh that was me oh
i was like is that the ghost of kiara
talking to him
[Laughter]
okay no activity so far if they write in
the book will there be a spike in
activity
i i don't know i put i put the i put the
the the book in the laundry room
um yeah let me go turn the lights back
on in the house so that we can use that
everyone just go and go in blind go in
dark or do you want to guess
what do you want to do um
it's rough oh there was some activity
i want to see if she wrote in the book
move the camera
oh okay you wanna go to get because
if it only hunts one person at a time
uh hmm yeah then
one of us can see be
the bait and then come back alive
uh i see i see whoever it gets i will be
the bait yes
no we don't know who it will go for it's
just you know you don't know where it'll
pop up
so whoever oh there's okay
there's a spike maybe the road in the
book
okay we gotta go check the book okay
let's go together
and then if okay if there's a hunt hide
in the closet
save yourself make it out there alive
okay
[Music]
okay godspeed
oh i'll keep the i can't you see that
okay that's big hampering
what where oh i see i see i see it
big oh something beeps what was that i
don't know
sounds like a microwave are your hot
pockets then uh
are you leaving oh i'm just seeing if i
can pick up
here's emf if i have do i have too many
items
they have too many items yeah i can
leave the uh
hold on uh
i have too many items i'm gonna i'm
gonna drop the lighter
okay and pick up the eff
there you go
okay now we're okay
did you hear that beep was that you yeah
i heard it too it was like a microwave
i think it is the mic oh it was the
microwave she's making hot rocket
what flavor though that'd be a pizza oh
pocket emf 3.
write in the book no email five is the
stinky [\h__\h]
where's the book i threw it down
here uh
did she take the balloon
what's this
i swear i threw the book down
aye aye
um the book and the book has glitched
into the wall
oh i don't
the book is gone okay does anybody else
have salt get up i picked it up
okay i picked it up wait girl check the
salt see if they're
um see if the uv picks up anything
right here oh oh it's in the kitchen
is it in the kitchen is in the kitchen
it's like that way here
there's a salt footprint apparently do
you have the uv light girl you can check
over here yup there we go right here
they guide me guide me where are you
right here right here in the in the
laundry room
hi hi can i go into the garage like that
do you see any footprints
no it's a spirit
it's a spirit it's gotta be a spirit
oh you don't oh okay apparently you
don't need a
we don't have who had the camera cali
okay my cha is saying it's
culture guys
but it did step on the salt right so
so the salt it's like it's like a little
when you like sprinkle on the floor
it's like just a pile but with the
spirit walks on it
it leaves like a footprint wait but can
dead people also walk in the salt and
leave a footprint though that's the
question
hey the phone's ringing again that's a
loud spirit though maybe it is a
poltergeist no
okay it keeps making noise it's loud
yeah and it threw a bunch of stuff
didn't it earlier or was that the other
one i forget
i think i think i was that was richard
that was richard okay
um ah
hmm
i'm gonna guess poltergeist
it moves something did you see that did
you see that did you see that
wait what in the camera or it yes
also the book do you like how i placed
the book
where's the book it's right there you
see that white thing
it's right there oh i see i see oh oh
yeah i think it is poultry guys it's
moving a lot of stuff and like the phone
ringing
um yeah well
here goes nothing oh here was nothing
you ready
ready
you're two percent i'm a fifteen percent
it's gotta be poltergeist believe
welcome back there's some jobs ready for
you
hey
[Music]
that's the first thing i got right
i died right at the door though right at
the door i wasn't about to leave i
you can't leave during the house
oh yeah you have to hide
you know what i watched right now that
was cool
i thought it got you and you died you
found it so quickly
no i i just remembered there was it was
an open door but i didn't even close the
door but then
it had its eyes on you again
[Music]
we did it good job everyone
yeah let's all
uh quote-unquote run
yeah it's a narrative walkie walkie walk
okay i think we can uh
all right thank you two hours of ghost
busting is enough right
[Music]
that got pretty watching pretty scary at
times
i'm sleepy reaper yeah that was fun yes
that was fun i keep saying let's see
we should go back to this
[Music]
oh
i expected it to be much much more scary
but the chat says
because we were uneasy it wasn't so
scary i guess yeah that's much scary it
was so scary
[Music]
i mean thousand back but level one
number two
okay it was fun
let's play it again please
[Music]
maximum four players but we want amma to
be in there too how about
i play together with cali right like i
visit her at her house
we play just as one player there's no
other reason i just wanted to so that
amick enjoyed the game there's no other
reason why i would want to do that
yes hallie can be the mouse and you can
be the wizard oh like
yes yeah so we can play this five next
time
let's do it
okay that way that way
me and kelly can mentally support each
other when
when we're like scared in the darkness
yes oh you're gonna see the dark oh
dear yeah
big brain big brain all right
does anybody have any announcements for
the week
yeah my new song is on all streaming
platforms go check out
today and if not it will be it will be
there
it will be there soon for spotify but
itunes and whatever go check it out
please
awesome i'm i'm collabing with
polka senpai this weekend
but that's it that's all i have to say
okay
how about you lina um well i
still have to put up my schedule so uh
yeah i think tomorrow instead of
bitching kitchen we're going to be [\h__\h]
and movers because i recently moved
[Music]
i like that look forward to it everyone
okay
all right everyone thanks for watching
thank you
thank you guys catch up on the flipside
[Music]
bye
you