[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
assistant
thank you
[Music]
foreign
assistant
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
what what was that for us
I had a frogs
[Music]
[Applause]
yes once again wow oh yeah you say wow
we say well can you well try that we're
gonna respond
oh really um okay
I say
yeah yeah
[Music]
wow
stop very coordinating
morning
oh my God it's a beautiful day to play
uh a lot of jackbox games I would say
oh yes yes
Emma it's shaking that are those pen
lights are those orange pen lights on
I'm just hitting my head
it's my image
very close to yourself everybody
may I introduce my my my uh birthday
party participants on my left side is
Anna
[Music]
oh thank you it's almost over
yeah
thank you for coming to my birthday
and then next to phone for confidence we
have
Sony yeah
happy birthday
thank you it's gonna be a great time
you're gonna win
um killer sweep oh
is that the I the idea of playing Jack
books but I'm like really bad at it
because my my English part of my brain
is just not that fast
but it's okay because I have fun is that
like a that's a lot of words to just say
it's okay you have the you have the
birthday buff oh okay I'll try to use it
wait I want to say one thing uh I
already have fun on Max but people are
saying fauna kind of quiet make myself
louder oh how loud do these do too loud
that's never too loud is it better guys
it's better is this louder am I louder I
can raise everybody a little bit more on
desktop audio Yeah
okay perfect okay and then next we have
almost time
[Music]
another blue person
hello I have many blue people two blue
people
the blue is overpowering maybe the blue
will will create a group
secretly and destroy us all
signed up for a group it's more of a
pair
we are the blue walls
no they will take over no
oh no we have no chance against them I
mean what do we do
uh we can bong
the blue Alliance anyway yeah that was
my my path to you to say hello well man
oh uh hello everybody Amelia Watson
problem Englishman number one detective
Wing wow oh wow you did the whole thing
[Music]
happy birthday oh thank you
you're looking very
um
low res today
[Music]
are you okay
I'm sleepy I woke up from a nap but my
pixels will come later naps are the best
thing I wish I could have taken no
they're bad no they're dangerous no good
good naps good dangerous okay and then
we have someone who's still in the state
of a couple months ago
[Music]
the body don't start till I walk in
and let me raise you hello
I mean Dr oopsie I don't know yeah Dr
oopsie Disney World a doctor a doctor
she's smart
yeah doctor of oopsies dangerous
competition
[Music]
um
oh since all of you girls also called
into my call-ins although not all of you
called into the the cooking Collins but
let me just update you the cake was so
mediocre doctor
I posted a photo yeah and I mean it
looks mid but I hope that it at least
would taste decent but it turned out so
mediocre
screaming I mean that's not bad
at school but it was so underwhelming
is that glue
was too hot
put some ice cream on top scoop of ice
cream
vanilla that might be good did you get a
good Instagram picture yeah it's on
Twitter the picture is fine I guess
um
it's boring you know I don't know my
mom's coming over on Sunday and we will
attempt a new tart probably
it was my first Avatar and I think you
know it's very important to
get the dough right I think I got the
dough right I just needed a bit more
time in the oven and also I should have
I should have really used maybe Frozen
butter you know there's many tips and
tricks
[Music]
and the the fruit you know I use that
fruit because I wanted it to be orange
but in hindsight you know canned fruits
that that that took a lot of the flavor
away
carrots
and one something sweet like characters
I don't know apricots
cots are also orange kind of yeah I was
thinking of apricots too but a carrot
cake that's a carrot tart that's a
quiche
what no but what if it wants to be a
tart are you just telling it it can only
be a quiche
[Music]
you want to fight it out huh you want to
fight it out
that torch has a dream
we should find it out in some jack
boxing box box box I lived in some
weights today and I I can easily break
your arms okay
oh damn I can't even reach you so you
can't break it wait no you can't get
stronger I don't want to be the leader
we're tired right now yeah you were tied
your left hand is weaker than my left
hand and my right hand is weaker than
your right hand okay so let me work out
one arm then
I don't believe
you
look like popular
but only half of them
okay I I don't worry I can't I probably
won't gain that much but but baby baby a
good challenge a good way to challenge
you to also you know lift a little bit
oh I gotta lift because yeah
currently just lifting both together
yeah but I'm just lifting two kilograms
of Weights it's just two two kilogram
weights each so telegrams nothing I use
I use like uh what is it like a 500
milliliter water bottle oh
[Music]
I think it's both because if you do 100
reps of like one milligram of something
that's not getting you anywhere
well to it to an end you know it's a lot
yes but oh wow see we're already in the
mood of discussion and fighting so we we
should get into it
we have fired fired up yeah it's a Fight
Club I wanted to play in a trivia Murder
Party first uh so let's see uh I'm so
stupid I'm so bad at this one just yeah
just believe
how do I give you girls none of us won
this one we all do I have to hide oh
[\h__\h]
they don't
I know
okay you guys
stream a mode please wait I need to open
a browser okay uh how what where do you
go um what's it called
TV wow you said that in sync
they should they should clip that and
use that for the cake
so
[Music]
it's green as a professional streamer
does
go into it you can probably join first
yeah yeah okay okay
let me join um
[Music]
[Laughter]
I got the blue one leave the room leave
the room and then come back wait let me
come in I can't it doesn't work
I refreshed I'm just a potato sack
I like that it looks like a pillow yeah
the peanut one one two three four five
we're missing one there we go now oh you
want a different one
I wanted to shower
yeah but it has it has like a monocle so
it fits me better oh
you know take each other's colors for a
little while I'll move something I tried
to leave already
okay
how do we press everybody in
everybody's in I start cause I'm the VIP
ew it looks different
let's go can you guys hear the audio
chat yeah
whoa oh this song hits hard
I like it
yummy yeah as a button we're as cute as
a button
I'm vacuuming on the vacuum are you
being vacuumed
oh no cleaning my worst enemy
tonight
oh that's bad
that sounds interesting you just said
good on stream oh no
yes
and we die if we don't get it right no
audience is here too hello
what's in your mouth let's just get into
the game never mind
do people know this
I don't know
nothing yeah every
Middle School
how's the IQ level in Austria
oh
[Laughter]
yeah
describe
[Laughter]
please oh we have to drink uh poison
like ideally a not poisoned cup yes you
first thank me right now oh so we still
have a chance thank you
only a letter away but oh you're so
different
from so I keep thinking
you don't want to kill the birthday girl
right
I did choose the
okay
I like how nobody picks her clean
[Music]
glasses
[Applause]
what oh my goodness
[Music]
what's the head on the ship
no way
I can still guess even though I'm dead
but I'm not getting anything for it Ryan
and then even if you're dead you can
come back yeah you're smart
well I've never heard of these words
before toilet you've never heard oh I
didn't know
which one sounds like the most out of
you know I thought that was the poop
thing no
that was the captain's headquarters or
something
fingers oh fingers
oh yeah okay yeah yeah oh you know how
that works when you cut off a finger you
cannot like you always like blocked from
giving a specific answer like a or b or
c even though that even if it's the
right one wow these are gonna make a
great necklace necklace
because I still need the middle finger
slide that's just code on it
okay next question good morning Miss
Bliss became what 90s TV show dude I
don't know what
what 90s what what I don't understand
what the sentence means
are we too baby for this
good morning Miss Bliss is the show's
name
I guess they changed names
[Music]
I I didn't even I've never heard of
these shows
oh I couldn't choose that anyway it was
blocked off
you know it's so smart I don't know I've
just been picking like what
here's how this is going on if no one
takes the money
Tony we have to be in this together
um
yes yes
be smart be reasonable is this where
console Falls
yeah you're right
[Music]
okay
but the host sounds like Cali with the
voice changer true yeah like when she
does the the go XLR
um
[Music]
yeah
You Stay classy
courage that one sounds right I'll stop
which one I'll choose
the first one sounds reasonable
You Stay classy San Diego
literally who yeah
wait I'm on fire
let's go
Let's test your memories
[Applause]
oh I'm so bad at these
little orange green blue green orange
blue orange green but it's also
different that's not Orange
you're right
oh yeah simply make sure not a single
person does better than you or you die
it's that simple
this is confusing in like the UI oh wait
oh oh I remembered though I want to redo
it
[Music]
I messed up I messed up oh
that is tricky
it's okay I'll come back please
things
[Music]
is this is it over no oh no
this question is just a quick reminder
that life is futile
hello
it's definitely for
eign
I feel like the first three things I
cannot imagine although I mean it must
have been like a different reason like a
heart attack or something
at all times
oh yeah because maybe it was poisoned or
something or he choked on something you
know yeah someone else to defend
yourself
I'll still punish someone so make sure
someone gets hurt oh oh interesting
what you gonna do what you're gonna do
what's gonna get punished
[Laughter]
take some money
[Music]
um
destroys us all game over we're doing
the final round
because you can still come back to life
though
I'm alive oh nice well at least we made
it to the final round this time oh yeah
it's only me
it's a race
I'm coming for you what
character what what oh you guys don't
know I don't understand it's a single
prompt so far
I have no idea but um
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yogi Bear
I want a European version of Jack bugs
party games with references from Europe
I think like a otaku version oh
go skin on extra answers
[Music]
I'm gonna
I don't know
Harvard I have no idea
easy I don't even know who this is
he's in cars right it can't be cars I
haven't seen the other ones either but I
don't know
I don't remember I don't watch films
y'all
okay okay okay
[Music]
I don't tell me how I don't know these
names this is great I don't know either
straight edge dark and stormy sounds
cool
[Music]
I don't know
fire has clam juice and it doesn't it
like Bloody Mary
surprise
mama mammals what's a Nightcrawler
these real animals
it's a quick question again
the only real one that sounds to me real
is Manatee oh
let's go
that's good that's good the tiebreaker
okay it's so American
um help me
sign his name is
Benjamin Franklin right
this is discrimination Nicholas
the next question
this is very scary
I can see him doing it
I have no idea what
I can see him doing all of them he's got
a lot of tattoos tonight
he probably has a pretty [\h__\h] book
boy if I've ever seen one oh my God I
guess not I guess he's not a funky boy
she is the Funky Boy so he doesn't need
a tattoo a little bit
monkeys there's no kiwawa even though
I'm quite the monkey
the [\h__\h] what was this mean monkeys are
just like I don't like oh no I'm still
I'm stupid I'm stupid
unfortunately I have no idea
oh you move anyway even if you have two
wrong ones
Mortal Kombat Mortal Kombat
so cool
[Laughter]
anybody played Mortal Kombat here yeah
so yeah not really yeah they gotta step
up let's go
oh my Kiara
okay okay okay okay what the
vampire bat sounds so wrong that maybe
it's actually right
is it is a bat a rodent
is it a flying rodent what is a bat is
it it's a bad it's a bird's own thing
not a
possums yeah
oh
so bad for me boys goodbye
what basking shark that sounds right
lemon juice I heard that too whale shark
it's all good don't worry
that all sounds like I thought a
Wheelchairs
and none of them is Gouda
this game
why am I not everybody
is that what they mean I'm guessing
okay
I don't know I I don't know man I don't
I don't know either isn't that like a
what does that mean Goosebumps it's like
a book series
nobody got it I think oh
why did we explode
yeah
dude you are smart enough
sad music
oh rest in peace
I'm like California wow
Arena time
that wasn't the council so we've only
counts as we've you all are still alive
I am not immune to poison I I accept
that allergic to poison well
okay Council sweep
the ride on the back of your Victory
it's okay
even though I didn't ask like a single
Quest I didn't answer a single question
correctly until the like very very end
round there
Cuba thank you
for what for for letting me win over you
oh happy birthday
thank you oh it's not like you're only
doing that for my birthday right because
you also let me win with the doors the
door racing right yeah
thank you ah I'm so honored
okay no need for the credits right nah
should we play a different one right
away
yes okay yeah which one I'll go buy like
the popular choice
which one do we want I know they like
TKO and I know quiplash is like a
classic espionage
[Music]
is this way you guess percentages or
what yeah it's like pulled you can pull
the audience and then you guess like
it'd be like what percent of the
audience knows how to drive a car
about my audience
or our audience
yeah can I can I can we do this one hey
let's go yeah
oh do I have to hide the screen again
probably right yes maybe okay make sure
is this
family friendly in the audience and not
the oh okay
it says audience on
yeah I think that should be good then
okay a lot of room code hiding do you
want that
uh might be a good idea room code hiding
okay where is that in settings
a lot of room call to be
I don't know
I guess you have to like toggle it when
you get to the screen so you can like
hide it and then show it and then hide
it turned on to avoid the most
provocative I guess we should turn on
family friendly filters
okay let's try with that uh
for sure
let's see
[Music]
oh okay
wait how do I turn I hear okay there you
go there's the code girls
[Music]
are you sure
thank you okay I am I'm not a chicken
I'm not a phoenix to all ages
okay is everyone ready
uh I think we are and again
um anymore
[Music]
right
we need all of you to participate okay
let's join us you know you sound a
little too painy there
into it okay computer what do you want
for this wait I have to hear the rules
because I don't know how to play this oh
I want fanny packs is it my turn
I've worn fanny packs I am very
interested in this because I am biased
against fanny packs wait no it is using
the audience okay okay
yes 20 and I think it's more no because
like as a child I think a lot of people
wear fanny packs I feel like I think it
is kind of in again yeah anything ever
have you ever done this uh I say I say
in the past
kind of suck
I agree with that oh my God
you guys were Fanny back I don't
I I think you know it's maybe it's it's
nicer nowadays people like to wear their
fanny packs over their chest right does
that still count as a fanny pack I don't
know yeah
um the 90s were different times oh okay
here's something I started candy
what percentage
oh that twister your electronics they
come with it yes
Electronics does that count or like
bread
sometimes it's bread sometimes yeah yeah
some Electronics I think it's
um
Electronics ties I save them
you cannot even say like anything but
higher oh wait I clicked in the middle
what
um
I thought I was a hoarder but at least I
don't save my friends
my man no shame candy sometimes when I'm
doing stuff in the kitchen and why do
you guys record it is
you never know double points
no Gouda
every day really yeah every day only on
days when I'm feeling extra special oh
okay maybe
not many days
it's our audience here they're just like
us
you don't think they're misrepresent
they would misrepresent it
all right let's go oh yeah
Sims make their beds
[Music]
nice um
oh I'm up next
[Laughter]
what am I guessing
all right don't get this wrong
Adam what does that mean
particularly
well actually I can't explain it
oh yeah explain that's right yeah
if you if you mess with it it explodes
explain it
attention in class right
all of you think it's more
[Applause]
what now because they got Google open
nobody said you could use Google
yeah it says
yeah
you're right but they believe you oh
okay what am I guess
oh yes
I'm in that percentage Count Me In
[Music]
they're cute
all right
wallpaper oh is it a nude woman
no it's mine
they're pants everyone will have like
their anime anime girl wallpapers
let's not count something like okay you
know for example yeah yeah yeah
they're okay so you can't consider
people as pets
oh
my cat says my phone wallpaper I also
have my cats with my phone hey I say hi
people always say I gotta know
thank you
we have to know our audience guys who's
watching yeah but I think there's a lot
of pet owners
as your wallpapers guys call Life
members obviously
yeah I need to do a wallpaper review
themes yeah that's the most overused
freezer expression in the workplace hear
the most
in Japanese
this is mean does this mean what people
say or what they think is overused
what's used the most right first yeah
[Music]
although
let's see or you can use more than one
yeah we have to chose three that's free
okay
I think I chose
[Music]
spamming something that I wouldn't have
thought
let's what everyone picks it's a little
touch base
uh-huh what's what does Circle back mean
let's Circle back on it three four five
seven four yeah
oh
it is what it is
let's go I'm giving up
[Laughter]
there's a similar very much used trails
in Japanese sweep is real sweet yeah
don't go away
it's all about giving up at the
workplace that's how
that's how you feel better
like oh thank God it's Friday
but maybe not anymore
I'm so positive that was very
interesting also crony does ears from
the dog they really look like your hair
thingies oh yeah
oh I don't even know
it was maybe intuition from your side
should we play whiplash
birthday girl where'd you go
this is the one with the the funny
answers right and then two answers
oh this is my comeback game should I
change settings audience play along
um
you have to be funny yeah yeah and I I'm
not funny but you know I'm hungry should
I do audience play along
I don't think so it says their answers
will appear on the screen do they trust
them
uh
wait was there uh
where's the am I blind the the height
code thing I don't think the sun has
height code okay then let me hide the
screen
and we shall applied our game
please let us in this chat no
it
I'm green let's go oh oops I mean got
three eyes yeah I feel like that that's
already in kind of giving her some extra
power
is everybody in yes yes okay press the
button press the button push the button
down
[Music]
all right guys you can join now too
coming
[Music]
here
soda somebody opened in a cold one no
anything for you guys not me definitely
not opening a fresh doctor
anyone I love I love Dr Pepper
I know
and inferior
well okay funny answers how much time 80
Seconds uh
ah
um
what what do you call the person that's
sitting in front of you
not next
cheating no
um
oh uh crop
[Music]
amazing okay I got it
um
oh God what okay I'll just go and name
it
oil time
challenge mode no Hollow live answers
insert yellow wait there's more
questions
I thought there's like two okay
um did you put Yago Watson
you'll see
um
if you can't think of something hurry
and be funny
right now no I can't be funny
[Music]
no
and Van Gogh gave his remaining oh then
listen no okay
oh no the second one sounds like
something else
[Laughter]
well it's like Yago and Van Gogh put
together okay
it wasn't that bad yeah I just liked it
yeah the audience like okay
[Applause]
I think
oh there's one sounds familiar
wait the second one sounds kind of funny
doesn't it sound familiar um
only myth will understand
although I exaggerated it
um
forget me
it's a real story I mean it happens okay
when you eat crabs they're juicy
what what's the first one is that just a
an Emergency quip
sounds like a quick list yeah
maybe
isn't Coldplay the band but it's
actually just one guy
Cuba
thanks Juana I got you
Google come on come on use your brain
juices
Edward Scissorhands would have been a
much different movie if it were called
Edward Edward scissors
Ready Set both
glow stick hands
it's a it's an idol fan you know
what really
[Applause]
let's do elephants
[Laughter]
oh my God
to read out loud
I was laughing too much
who's able to use uh um
jelly more jelly
it's meatloaf with beef jelly no it's
not
definitely not okay
love fauna where did you get the um
do you have a German keyboard on your
phone no you can just hold down the
letter and it'll give you access to all
of the uh
you only got my vote because of the
umlaut you know it spoke to me
okay come on
okay now or never let's use some smart
answers
[Music]
health
oh no
I don't know what that means but let's
go with it
ah
[Music]
okay I don't know if it's funny but
I don't I don't know series mode for a
moment there yeah I had to focus because
this was my last chance to get something
going don't be serious be funny but in
order to be funny you need to be serious
first
yeah
I like Discord so crunchy yeah
sorry maybe that's me my my streams
man go with the blue
I know I don't know man oh
be funny be funny right now right now
very funny
why are printers oh no printers okay
everyone both are your favorites
oh hmm tacos
[Music]
wait today don't just um have a problem
with letting out the ink is it like a a
resource that is very valuable tell us
you know tell us oh I get it oh no I
didn't vote it wasn't even Ina's answer
I think I might have to go but I'll
still be playing in the game because I
need to uh I need to attend the meeting
oh okay okay okay
I'll still be in the game but bye-bye
oh my goodness
I feel like I've seen the first answer
before God damn I miss the feeling
where are the boats damn audience I got
distracted by crony leaving okay
the hardest class you can take at clown
college
okay
oh my goodness
take your pick choose it wisely
please please please
I was thinking hard with that one
yeah
sounds so bad oh wow okay
well yeah many people still go into the
usual room even though I try to make it
very uncomfortable
[Music]
whoever wrote that must know that there
are many kfp watching
[Laughter]
what's up with the usual room you don't
like it anymore
[Music]
now
what should it have been Jeffrey balls
or something what
I see
um
okay look listen listen it's because
Andy dick in German means um you know
fat
so I thought I make a joke
well okay
[Music]
that's the first thing ever happen to
anyone though does anyone do that I mean
but it's like I could never never do it
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
that's the end of round two let's take a
look at the scores
oh mumei wrote To Me
she said she cannot help me cheats
she thinks I'm doing great
no because I told her in the in the chat
in the this in the Discord call I told
her to help me with my answers
[Music]
it was just a suggestion
new cartoon character like a okay just
word in this word clown is a very
popular theme in this round yeah it is
yeah
oh [\h__\h] Brody okay
[Music]
I did the same thing as someone else try
again the same exact thing
I don't know what to write
I don't know I don't know either I had a
feeling that she would write the same
thing
crony would have wrote it oh no oh I
think I got the problem
using all
I have no brain power I was gonna go for
the same for this
okay in round three there were three
medals Gold Silver and brown
truck
oh you have to pick two or three
oh okay
seems so ah silver gold silver okay
clown the boy man sounds like
Cali
[Music]
they're not so convincing
but let's see
who will take the wind
Clowney yeah I was gonna say clown
sounds fun
I want to see Clowney win yeah I think
so too
the gold
sweet
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right that's it time for the see I
could have gotten that because I was
gonna type the same answer wait who's
this
real
[Music]
top dancer
stupid fatness
it's a good answer
oh man
can I ever win
it's so sad I need to win some games
it's hard to learn these TKO the drawing
t-shirt one that one oh maybe I will not
win that ever no because I panic at that
one all the time too
what possibilities do we have maybe one
that we haven't played before is there
such a thing oh
I don't want to look at that that's very
very very
back to back oh
very sad okay we have left over the
T-shirt game and Faking It what's faking
him
everyone knows the question one of your
friends has something to hide find the
faker before it's too late
[Music]
in person
yeah it doesn't have to be in person it
said like raise your hand or something I
don't mess up step it up
I missed that what Seven Up
it's a game that we desk yeah I feel
like people like touched your thumb like
a little too like a little too long did
you ever feel like that
I think for me
just a little too much oh have you guys
ever played like the the what's it like
the mafia game where you have like a
secret handshake and then like everyone
goes around shaking hands in the room
and then like after like after you get
hand shaped by like the mafia or
something you die in like two two more
handshakes and stuff
simulator
[Applause]
Camp games well I'm gonna go with the
T-shirt one then yeah okay
here okay I'm gonna be drawing on my
phone I guess me too oh I guess I can
move on over to my tablet
you're just gonna win again because
you're also you have the best ideas
you do is there is there something oh
yeah there's a bird but ah there's also
a flame flaming looking boy
oh
cute
Victory quote victory quote you got a
victory Club
okay
I'm ready to start all right serious
mode on
it's Corona still participating I don't
think so oh I don't think so
okay oh my goodness my character looks
scary I thought I wasn't like this
welcome
faster just as my father was and his
father before him oh wait that was a
paralegal though
this is not the one where we fight in
the ring is it
no yeah no no the shirts you create draw
and make phrases and then combine them
on t-shirts
makes sense
you're winding path to Victory
style of this one yeah
[Music]
is of no consequence I mean it's of some
consequence but like don't stress out
basically use the suggestion button if
you're out of ideas altogether okay I'm
always stressed out drawing right now
okay let's go
wait we draw a drawing wait what is just
no prompt at all anything
yes yes yes yes yes okay
it's Focus time yay all right
um
I'm gonna draw something that is
irresistible
[Music]
how much time do we have left
I don't know one second 50 seconds 15 10
seconds don't stress me out
multiple I did one hopefully just one
[Music]
wait I just wasted mine myself
[Applause]
okay you wasted yours how can you waste
yours
okay mine's in too
okay
free images Max I only was able to drop
one oh I think we go one by one and then
we write a prompt or something and then
like it goes and then we draw another
one and then like
yeah
for one drawing yeah
time's up show me
show me the suggestion button if you oh
I guess yeah drawing two begin oh I
guess it's drawing two now it's kind of
like garlic phone yeah
oh this is two out of three
um
[Music]
Clueless
me too
[Music]
what's a draw what's a draw
hello Raiders tell me what to draw oh
God
60 one minute left
um
is it cheating to look up our references
ah
no
okay
[Music]
okay I think I got a good idea out of my
own
brain I'm so proud I still have one more
to go
[Music]
30 seconds is fair easy peasy
oh you're not speed running the game I'm
making it very easy though
easy for yourself or is it for us
I don't know
okay don't hold back
oh God
one more one more drawing last one
oh God one more out of my ass I gotta
pull these out of my butt
um
[Music]
when in doubt
draw
cute
person
[Music]
oh sure oh sure so it's Rocky Adam
no that's not what I meant
guys can you spam Pian emotes in the
chat please oh reference
oh thank you oh
I got it naturally right
and now I'm giving it away though don't
you have to guess again which t-shirts I
mean not directly but
it's okay I don't mind you guys knowing
which one I drew
I'm not gonna vote for it
[Applause]
okay
three two one
okay why is almond red pretty good
patient
only I'ma finish no I finished mine wait
what happens I I submitted it
I submit mine I hope it wins you
sometimes it can be delayed last second
I want mine to be submitted
uh write something oh I don't even see
the T-shirt okay
um foreign
number one in
[Music]
um
number number two and
gouda cracking them out wait wait wait
fauna has six wait you have to do more
than three just go as many as you can oh
okay
um
you were inspired
select one of each to create your
T-shirt
oh my God
hey I'm not getting all options though
only four options okay oh wait ah but
different ah whoa that's good
ah nice nice
oh wait you only make one t-shirt though
okay uh you get to make another one in
the next video okay okay it just it's
like juggles all the other oh jumbles
them all up wait Chad is Chad also
looking at t-shirts already or not yet I
think the voting comes for them later
yeah they vote later
chapter two hard shirt oh we're looking
at sharks
or funny
[Music]
please look for me cry
[Laughter]
[Music]
I like that one
[Laughter]
merchandise now yes yes
you have to get it separately from the
birthday merchandise
thanks the crash is slowing in
I can sign it for you guys too if you
want damn
yeah
oh come on
come on there no way that the shirt will
win
what's wrong with him
what happened the left turn has no
chance
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
that's cute
did you draw the one the taco did you
draw it nope that's not me yeah because
I saw a different one it looked more
like you
darn hmm
the taco is winning oh yeah
indirectly indirectly they're
representing you
break wait so did you did you draw an
and add the phrase on it or I just put
it together so I didn't write that and I
didn't draw it oh I stole other people's
words
[Music]
are they just scrapped
that's that's not nice I put so much
work in them there is no eraser no
that's not there's but there's a going
back button
okay there's no good to help me oh
[Music]
oh I have no ideas ah finished
okay okay how much time okay okay okay
uh yeah 40 seconds oh that's long enough
time no I'm feeling I'm feeling pretty
confident about this one
[Music]
I wonder if anyone would actually wear
like the Imaginext
I'm sure they would I really like the
Starbucks one though who drew the
jackbooks shirt
yeah do you think it wasn't
a default one oh no way was it
for real all the shirts at the end I
think there's the winners
um
oh God oh God
did mine go in oh God I did it so last
second again okay okay
you can buy all of them funny stuff
funny stuff well my other problems that
were Maybe funny
um
[Music]
uh
I I I'm being so poetic with these but I
don't know if that's good
oh
I used up all of them last time do they
carry over oh I don't think so but you
can write it same again maybe if they
haven't been used yet remember them oh
God
ah
um
[Music]
all right
keep drawing
cute
[Music]
but I like the drawing but I don't like
the titles
[Laughter]
you gotta make it work okay I made it
work
[Music]
s
okay gone to lit
how cute
is that
um
okay
this is rough because I I drew to
Grimace Shake but I put together the
other shirt what is the Grimace Shake I
keep seeing you it's the daily dose of
suffering purple milkshake vanillas yeah
I wrote the title and I drew the the art
somebody put it together correctly hey
everybody
I wrote that title too
t-shirts
[Music]
oh that would be cute
that should be new
homeless merchandise it was actually a
really good idea
new Challenger
cat t-shirt is everybody okay
one thing we need
I think we need some uh
positivity and happiness in the Stream
yeah we like negative titles you know oh
oh oh oh audience vote I genuinely think
that the the taco face on the purple
shirt is just something we need as
actual merchandise
it's Sasquatch
what is that is that a like a I don't
know Bigfoot with a shark tail I don't
know
sorry
[Music]
or not freeze breakdown
powerful but do I get points for being
the one who made up the title
I didn't know if you do get points if
your thing is used yeah that is only
fair because it's my copyright chapter
five
okay let's get real and only one no more
drawing oh yeah this is the this is the
um Battle Royale of the t-shirts
oh
of the best t-shirts
a good um a good combination though
future Inna merchandise
whoa oh the right one would win oh oh
they're they're pretty tight though oh
wow I mean honestly it's it's it's a
decent I'm actually dizzy from laughing
oh I got the slogan
the tournament oh wait no never mind
I'm sweating profusely
sufficient suffering
everybody
oh oh slogan used some three shirts wow
[Applause]
it's my passion
audia's favorite
yeah yeah that one was like imagine the
smell it was So Fresh So Beautiful
what's that well yeah
oh God
no it's because she submitted so much
you know not many people could use it oh
champion won the tournament nice uh
integral shirt combination in the end
let's go
oh okay that I think we circled back
yeah
a better artist than me
nice so turntables
I'm taking your um like the obligation
to do art streams in us it's my job now
oh thank you for taking my job you can
do instead you can um I don't know what
can you take from me
my oh my
my endless for chat readings
I'm the artist of myth now
or whole talk imagine Inna doing Holo
talk
kind of an interesting idea maybe to
switch like you know the main thing that
somebody does
I know yeah you know switch it up
somebody does whole talk and then
somebody uh does Amazon's new show and
somebody whatever what do we have of
like typical things
[Music]
um
so yeah somebody free other girls take
over chat cast stuff like that whole
Shuffle yeah
fauna's Minecraft I mean everybody kind
of plays Minecraft but yeah maybe
somebody can take over building the the
tree
we would appreciate that wouldn't you
appreciate somebody taking over the
truth my baby oh really
Girls Talk members with chat cast
members
good I can do ASMR oh
oh dear I mean it's not like you haven't
done it before but one second yeah more
more please
Hollow Shuffle you hungry maybe eat one
of the t-shirts
not the stinky Grimace taco
can I just say it um imagine the smell
good is the one that uh explained the
Grimace shake to me while a couple days
ago I had no idea what's going on I'm
curious what is this
character like the Hamburglar but
grimace is
he's shaped like a purple nugget he's
basically you you know could it be
improving my mcnuggies
milkshake if you check McDonald's
Twitter I guess today he said goodbye
though he said I'm out this is yeah what
happened he's done he's done I guess he
had like a week a week of birthday what
like a month
naked
[Music]
you actually drank it
yeah I had it you lived
it tastes like a cereal milk but it's
supposed to be like lavender flavored I
think oh
yeah
yeah a whole bunch of stuff there yeah
I'm
food that's like lavender flavored
before
it it can be okay I think I had like
lavender cake before maybe something
like that that's making me really want
some milkshake from not a milkshake but
like the what's the thing from
McDonald's the shake or the ice cream
yeah
the m m one oh but the Oreo one is where
it's at because
speaking of Oreo can I I wanted to
recommend well because we're speaking of
shakes too
um the Oreo shake from Burger King is
like one of my favorite things to order
ever
it's really good yeah I guess so but
it's not as addictingly sweet when you
do it at home
it's better better yeah are you gonna
make it in an air fryer
no air fried milkshake huh I just
thought you know Emma can make anything
work in an air fryer bless you
thank you
well okay we kind of played every game
except the one that seems to be
unplayable so I'm quite satisfied with
that
[Music]
too bad you don't have a Jack box six
there's like a really fun personality
quiz on that one where oh yeah I like
that one oh wait let me see if I have
Jack boxes do you have
wait what uh I think this is the only
one I own probably
white lip line let me see if I have it
and then we can all play it still so I
have four as well
will it show on the Stream
yeah that's yeah what do you have to
like stream it over Discord would that
be well I could I could enter it on my
browser and then you know yeah
you have six yeah
should we just play that one game I
don't mind doing more and I'm cold I'm
cold Uncle okay let me let me one more
game I'm pretty sure it's it's a really
short one it's that uh it doesn't take
too long personality quiz
[Music]
which one was it
oh it's called Role Models just if
you're on a phone
number for it it doesn't like prompt it
unless you press it so you just don't
press it wait so wait should I capture
the Discord stream you know
um I think you can pop it out and then
capture that only okay
oh my god oh can I see the code just so
I can join just to be sure okay uh
settings
like um
capturing
wait Discord is always you must be the
guinea pigs
wait oh my God there's lots of things
going on in my brain right now um Let Me
Close check was party pack free
I'm yellow wait wait wait I'm I'm I just
gotta wait yellow I got blue
oh my God again you're swapping
oh okay I I'm joining and then
I got red
uh
wait let me try to capture hey
yours looks like mine why'd you copy me
I did it first yeah right is it possible
to go full screen on the popped out
window
um oh yeah wait I got okay
drop it out there's like no full full
screen I think I got it I I think I got
it uh okay wait uh and then does it do
window capture was it just like is it
window capture might have to be window
capture yeah probably let's just close
the rest of this chord or something
just to be sure
oh I got it yeah I I switched to a
different Channel where there's nothing
written
I think I think um okay I think I got it
set up I'm just not showing it yet
because it's still showing the code
oh wait oh okay
don't take a picture
[Music]
okay
you can you can press uh start I guess
it's like something from Naruto
Naruto
what's his face
Naruto Toby yeah totally there it is
Toby Maguire Spider-Man
does this chat hear the game audience
we theorize every friend group has some
version of the smart one the popular one
the troubled loner who I can change
okay okay
where's this you guys we just never
played this before hello test subjects
we are ready maybe once like a really
long time ago great great louder okay
louder
like one of the categories of one of
these so vote for Chronicles okay hey
wait wait what am I voting this for
so I don't know to find these things to
all of us here
uh-huh yeah so if it's something if it's
seasoned yeah you'd be like Moana in
Spring and I think you are in the summer
oh all right tiebreaker let's see I know
I don't know
[Laughter]
okay karaoke song guys there was nothing
shown it's nothing a popular karaoke
song are each of you
you got the names of your fellow Lab
Rats drag each one to the role you think
fits them best that includes yourself
sign next to each role yeah I don't know
these songs either the answer you're 99.
yeah
I Think We're Alone because I sang it
the other day on my stream
oh so you drag okay okay
[Music]
it's kind of funny
who wants to run who feels like they're
Born to Run
I don't know any of these songs I'm just
going based on the the names I'm saying
I was born to run though
yeah there's other uh things we can pick
like categories this is just the first
round I think yeah yeah yeah
wait the way I did it I don't really
like it
oh this the gist of friends is oh yeah
[Music]
let's look at those votes oh let's get
it on but wait
let's hum that song did you vote for
yourself science
I have no idea trust me
thank you it's so smug
well this one is yeah pretty kind of
funny
know yourself or at least
thank you
fits so well it's a Batman Drive
[Laughter]
I couldn't figure out how to undo
something for you after all that data
I put this as just a friend consolation
our house
[Applause]
[Music]
that was so good I used to watch Full
House all the time when I was younger I
did too but the new one did you get the
roll and some science I just like that
song better it's the only song You Know
we'll pick it we'll pick a better topic
on this here's where we landed okay
just a reminder I'll reward you with
pellets when your answer is the group or
when you do the best in a tiebreaker
experiment keep that in mind if you want
to beat your fellow guinea pig
do you win only based on if more like
the most people voted for the same thing
it's not really about winning it's just
about categorizing your friends what do
you guys know the most on here famous
cats famous cats yeah because I know a
lot of famous cats famous cats but it
has cats in it so yeah
[Music]
hey that's interesting [\h__\h] I want to do
both
well we'll hear more about
maintenance
okay okay
[Music]
there's an obvious yeah next to the role
you're most sure about there's an
obvious one there can I see okay
what's Cat in the Hat though
anyone knows
the Hat what doctors
no yeah
is what kind of cat is that an angry cat
I finished I'm not so sure
is uh Dr Seuss the guy the black and
white cat with the really tall red and
white hat striped okay
[Applause]
Green Eggs and Ham am I sending a photo
of Captain what about Cheshire Cat what
color cat was Cheshire Cat
it was like a purple yeah but that
doesn't fit wait oh wait never mind [\h__\h]
I guess but only like judging by color
I love lasagna
oh I am Garfield literally incarnation
of Garfield
uh I hate Mondays too
PR field
[Music]
popular choice
Hello Kitty
oh gonna need more data to settle this
time
I feel like um
we already know we already know
yeah
history uh
we have a really good report card though
yeah that's true what's your best meme
that you came up with that you created
if I told you I'd have to
zip tie you and leave you somewhere oh
[\h__\h] oh no it
is a secret
[Laughter]
too late
I created a lot of stuff too orbius oh
yeah
that's great
wow the floor
it's Cuban time again
2 670 of them get lumped together
oh it continues that's the thing to
break this tie sure I can't what
happened I want to give it to Ina
yes
he gave the creepiest smile and our
first is up to you
well I have more teeth yeah you have
like crazy too if I guess science
pellets to the winner so do your best
believe it man you think I guess like
the Cheshire Cat does have those teeth
yeah
creepy smile yeah a lot of people are
saying Ina too though um
yeah a smile you know yeah
I got the hit
yeah I mean I mean the smile is cute too
but you can you know only judge by the
teeth at that point because they're both
cute so the only thing we can go by is
those shark teeth those are terrifying
things
yeah
but I don't really think gouda is a
Cheshire Cat though no I don't see it
yeah you're done fuzzy I can kind of see
it like a mischievous Forest Gremlin
shut up oh
there she goes there she goes
I love the face you drew down okay
as a Cat in the Hat it's because you can
pull like anything out of his hat and
you have oh that's true
um
you are freaking me out with these
predictions
freaky freaky
I don't know this point system let's see
what this is yeah it doesn't really
matter I don't think based on your rules
your total opposites
there's a clown just a salty oh how do
you entertain the kids give you to write
an answer that fits the trait above your
head decide who did the best
yes
oh
I accidentally entered my answer without
finishing
that's fine
for the first time but accidentally
popped them what what okay like purpose
actually
for the answer I prefer fauna
um oh okay
teach them a lesson those kids
them last one last one what's up
Carnival attractions
oh yeah that sounds kind of fun we can
do that yeah lots of different because I
feel like a lot of the other ones like
game show hosts there would be names
villain's speech sounds interesting too
like it's gonna like work he's a random
movie oh that's true yeah I won't know
anything again
okay this one's probably understandable
how are you oh
okay okay
it's hard
we're Kitty roller coaster we're gonna
do roller coaster it's just a roller
coaster right
but it's rickety rickety what's rickety
it goes
unsafe we're gonna scream
oh it's it's like one it's like the
wooden roller coasters
oh they're wooden roller coaster you
feel like you're gonna die I think so
all right
I just I would like hear Kiara screaming
a lot if she's on there I wouldn't want
it anyway
water-based
I don't know what the duct tape
or something I didn't know that oh yeah
if you're sure about your answer
it means we get more data okay yeah test
me test me
here's what I want you guys to do
what
do we have to dance
[Applause]
[Music]
says without getting dizzy
hey guys
it's fun okay did you spin I spin too I
got up and I took off my headphones yeah
me too
Wendell who did it first
I think Yara did it first
okay it says as long as you can I I I oh
I think I voted backwards it's hard to
tell
oh
[Applause]
I want the merry go round yeah and I
need to I need an easy
um attraction because the Merry-Go-Round
of life
and I'm kind of like a horse
oh
a lot very interesting okay I don't know
why but I voted for that now I like a
mysterious place
because she's so sweet and and her ASMR
is also so sweet
fall in love with her
hey kind of love
that's the lineup
[Music]
on this experiment yeah I didn't know
the 99 more conclusion I mean I think
this is the results
we're not leaving here until we find out
which of you is better at being you oh
what three things are essential to have
a perfect Saturday night okay the answer
on your device okay um
[Music]
what do I need for Saturday night uh
free things uh smoothie chunkers and
yeah a chicken smoothie chocolate and a
chicken a chicken ice cream
oh I have to be spooky
[Music]
type whatever just type what you want a
time yeah
[Music]
cute Saturday night our spooky Saturday
I want a catty Cathy Kitty Cathy
Saturday night
oh
I can pack into their reverse
[Laughter]
[Music]
that speaks to me the most close my eyes
and pig
captured saplings it's cute it's pretty
cute
sounds scary
oh
similar
[Music]
how much time 40 seconds oh God
make a blind pick up line let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
in the chat all of us all of us no
pressure everyone no pressure at all
okay there's the data oh that's vote on
our devices now wait oh my God I'll be
right back make like a fabric softener
what damn they're both good these are
both really good
let's wait it's snuggle of fabric
softener yeah yeah
I don't know original you know like my
mother my mother
it just didn't fit with heartthrobs you
know you're just you're just unhappy dad
your mom likes me so much
spooky hard working Hustler oh oh
hungry snarky quasi romantic okay
not very moody okay
with the most total science pellets is
still met a gamer over here for kids
bedding for points
I literally didn't even know you could
do that
honestly fading
[Laughter]
wait how do you bet your points how you
do that yeah prediction
take this
looks like that was insightful and fun
yeah it was fun I like this one
I learned a lot about myself and about
you people
[Music]
um
we're just people now huh
I see how it is I'm so scared to press
on the screen again there we go okay
here we go it's gone yeah wow
nice titles I guess I gotta change my my
Twitter handle I'm not so spooky yeah
you ended up being spooky at all you
know
maybe it's darker oopsies yeah
that's true it's like how like in like
fan art and stuff everyone always makes
me evil and I'm just like
[Music]
how do you feel about being a villain
um sometimes you gotta have some
villains in the world oh to bring out
the good in the world right exactly
[Music]
um
that's actually so philosophical I know
[Laughter]
well oh my God in one minute it's my
birthday is over which is perfect it's a
perfect time
well then okay that's that's over
um we're done celebrating me but thank
you for celebrating me today thank you
thank you for having me sir thanks for
having me here it's nice to have a
birthday party yeah yeah I wish we could
eat some birthday cake together but you
wouldn't want to eat my birthday cake
anyway trust me
yeah I would eat it it's it's pretty
depressed pretty boring it crossed the
craft was good because it tastes like
Christmas cookies
oh cookies yeah yeah yeah just a plain
really plain ones though
[Music]
thank you guys for watching today
uh yo I don't know what to say uh this
was my birthday yeah birthday merch
above my head but also the link is in
the description there the link in the
comments is a different one that's also
very interesting yeah bye bye bye bye we
have a towel and a beach bag and finally
I love the bag thank you it's very big
very spacious for going to the beach but
also to going to other places but we
also find a combinations finally we have
a chicken merchandise
[Music]
I touched it IRL
um and it's very very soft very squishy
um
I I really I wanted one for a long time
because like so far you know when we had
myth Anniversary merchandise uh that was
also plushies but that was my Kotori
like mascot right the inner designed
before oh that's right I never had my my
dakuma chicken so third finally is it's
you it's literally you guys so please
instead of getting my birthday
merchandise it will arrive in six months
approximately
wow record timing I can't record really
yes that's like the shortest I've heard
yeah never mind I mean that's six months
is usually y'all six okay I mean it
depends some people are like especially
I think I hear a lot of stories from
European fans who experience more delays
than others
[Music]
yeah you'll already have forgotten about
it and then you get it and it's like
Christmas yes
yeah so thank you everybody who already
got it thank you for watching today all
the birthday streams and thank you girls
for joining me and for calling in and
playing yeah
[Music]
I am now free years old and two minutes
that's not something to celebrate
yeah I'm young so young
remember what you say in German
[Music]
I'll probably not be streaming the
following day because my my tax lady is
stressing me out about updating all my
oh YouTube
yeah so I I should probably get into the
problems yeah yeah I guess okay
Spider-Man I'll take care of that before
she leaves me forever
um no not tax evasion no
I would never have to always say that
um I'm too much of a chicken to do a
thing like that
chicken yes I like the story
thanks
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]