[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
candy
I'm so sorry
uh
I'm sorry
uh today when I'm playing Age of Empires
2 I'm sorry we're playing in exactly one
week
at the same time
I was surprised so many of you actually
were looking forward to it me too
actually because I played off stream
today for like two hours and it was
actually enjoying it
so I'm really sorry
very very sorry
yeah
[Music]
the thing is and I need to
um
ask uh very much in advance to play it
but
um you know how we scheduled it like a
week ago originally
and
um on the same day as I was gonna play
it I canceled that one too because I was
lacking sleep and then but on that day
no one said anything to me about you
know perms and so on I thought this I
thought it was fine
that time but I guess no one noticed so
today I've been informed that this one
is not gonna work out today I'm sorry
if I was warned about it last week then
we could have prevented it but nope so
I'm sorry about it
uh yeah some games are a bit more
complicated than others
um we'll have to respect that
um but next week next week for time is
the charm guys
yeah
oh
did you like the tutorial yeah as I said
I had a lot of fun with it
um actually the last mission was really
challenging the one where
um the king arrives and you have to
um destroy the other parties
um the rivals uh Castle
that was actually pretty challenging
William Wallace yeah that one was
challenging like they kept on sending
raids while I was busy still trying to
build uh my Army and then kept on
killing my people and then it took me
quite a while until I finally got to
build my castle and finally Willen
William Wallace
finally arrived but yeah for Scotland
yeah
surprisingly difficult for a tutorial
but the rest was fun
and I already feel like I learned a lot
anyway so we played that again again we
tried to play it again next week
with us next time definitely all good
because now
now now everything will go according to
okay Kaku
yeah
so instead we'll play our beloved cult
game
um yeah which I love very much so we'll
have fun with that will we
I am currently all right well will you
show the screen or what come on
come on you can do it OBS there you go
so proud of you
I just currently am I'm checking out
this place because it's new
I just started talking to this dude
plimbo let's see what he has to say
[Music]
the Bishops are nasty pieces of work but
they're doing good enough job of keeping
the waterways open and trade trade
flowing around here well with you going
around killing them it opens the gates
of all sorts of monsters beasts to start
sinking my shock
Yeehaw scary things baby with gnashing
teeth and all the fairy stinks and the
face that could curl the milk just like
me mother-in-law wow
[Music]
so you best be making this ride each
time a bishop dies a nasty beast called
a witness takes its place a bishop
ah the big boys right
and that's what he's got witness
like it when you're playing my nose folk
will pay a pretty Panic photo I have
witnessed you get me their eyes I buy a
new boat and we'll call it a square all
you need to do is to return to places
you have killed in a bishop defeat the
Ferocious Beast that hasn't moved and
bring me their eyes simple enough
oh I got two
there you go
hard to [\h__\h] wow why
what did I forget to put on my shirt oh
[\h__\h] just kidding
this was on purpose I'm showing you the
badonka dunks
a little bit different from last time
okay
motivating the cult hell yeah
you know what's cool like I attached
that book to my hand and with that hand
post it actually looks like um like kind
of holding it
and it actually works quite well
but damn look at this squishy bang they
say these creatures have seen all there
is to say and stood in silent judgment
for the Millennia just like me
mother-in-law
take days found it on me travels means
not to me but a crown Bearer might have
some use for it
three more to go I have one more
actually
oh he also gives me those things huh
also I'm failing that side quest by the
way that we got last time I'm not
picking up that uh
thing from Dark Woods unfortunately I
opened the game and I completely forgot
about it I should have run straight into
the Dogwood and then I could have maybe
made it in time but now whatever
whatever
you got another eye plain bear was
starting to see your appeal
surely Safety and Security is something
plain bow takes seriously especially in
me line of business but I could never
bow me a head to another so don't think
you'll be able to convert old plain bow
well only two more to go take this has a
token of me thanks
the quest kind of sucks why why
why you think so oh drop an explosive
bomb when you were all cool that's
another one of those cards that let you
make damage while you're rolling not bad
could get that one a question wow that
was a lot of faith
mmm
killing items
oh
[Music]
one of those I kind of want to get
or maybe both hello we have a lot of
money
wait does the bomb also hurt me
could I do friendly fire with that I
wonder
anything else we can do here oh
you can buy a follow-up form here
but no
this is pretty in here but not much to
do okay
okay bye bye I have to do something
about my face
there you go
Phoenix it won't hurt me no Friendly
Fire okay good good
that's the crab on the pier that's a
full room for free oh
what's up
later thank you again for rescuing
musical too in fact he's so grateful
that he wishes to marry you what do you
say
oh he's he's a coupling on uh he's he's
what's the word for couple in English
I've got some tea by the way first time
in a while
matchmaking I guess he's trying to do
some matchmaking
[Music]
I mean
I guess am I currently married to
someone I wanted because the ones I
married they also died and then I think
I revived one or two of them but I think
we're not officially married anymore
so I think yeah why not
[Music]
why not easy Quest I know that uh wow I
know the other ones might get jealous
um
became friends
Destiny well now everybody listen
listen
[Applause]
Oh indeed now let's um do some rituals
first of all I guess we're having a
wedding
wait who again sickle one right we
should go to [\h__\h]
I think I was so cool no
there's a this mic so I guess it's
sickle too
okay okay
wow
[Music]
congratulations wonderful
and then do I have enough to revive
someone
uh
uh no okay the thing is apparently we
need 20
um peeps for the last door so we we want
to work on Reviving as many people as
possible we've been losing more people
than winning some people I feel like
um
my rings to go one in front of us to go
to
everything is being being done properly
oh this is the last one we can do
interesting before the floor and
everything now except that one
glory for toil which will perform my
ritual at your temple which allows your
followers to work for free days and
nights without getting tired oh
perform original at your Campbell
declining a day of rest so your
followers will not gain will not work
that day and gain 80 plus 50 no I think
I'll do this one they're not losing any
faith so
there's nothing bad about this one
right
nothing bad about this one the thing is
like we have so many rituals I don't I
don't even do all of them I don't think
I would use this like what for
I need that to work
[Music]
okay
oh I got an achievement gospel ah
because I got older
possible
options oh my God all rituals full okay
so wait what happens now instead of me
getting those
those Stone thingies
the Commandment stones
when I get an exchange
I wonder
just nothing
is there a reason for me to work on
loyalty now
[Music]
um
nothing okay everybody go to sleep
let's see what's going on here I didn't
really play off screen this time
um
so I don't know what's going on
coldkey
yeah sorry about AOE too I'm really sad
about it too I'm sorry
I wish
I wish I could play it for you guys
today
I'm so sorry
well well well
sometimes these kind of things happen
um
so what am I what am I doing here zero
one just cleaning up here
okay shall we go out for
oh Absolution trade a new day with no
one in prison beautiful
everyone's doing so well
um okay let's start the day by making
some food perhaps
[Music]
yeah
a berry ball I don't know why it's only
one star honestly for me a berry bowl is
10 out of 10.
foreign
I would love to eat variables every
freaking day
I love berries who's that
that reminds me
a show I was watching
um
remember remember
how was it called again
I mean that's I'm not giving you much
info to work with but
the Great ah so good I wonder if there's
like any announcements about a new
season hmm
[Music]
oh let's build a mushroom sculpture
if there's any announcements about the
new season you guys gonna let me know
immediately
I do have one or two people in kfp that
constantly inform me about these things
which I'm I'm very thankful for it's
very useful
um
which one is the mushroom sculpture
ah
that one no
this one ah what am I lacking a few more
golden bars okay oh [\h__\h]
can you clean that up it's your job
you you show series yeah yeah
go
quick somebody do this for me because I
can't do it myself also thanks for the
pinky
oh it's one of those super chats again
tapped out of the game there you go
please do it faster
and besides that oh yeah let's summon
someone
once again oh this person triggered
we like you very much here please
continue supporting also we have an old
dude again
who is this old God God
I wish I could give you like an infinity
necklace or something like that Garfield
oh man I'll have to sacrifice you again
what are we gonna do about that
Garfield
I can't revive anyone either right now I
think still in cooldown and lacking the
bones anyway
okay well we gotta hope he survives
I think we activated something that
makes it really bad if someone dies
um while I'm gone
right
I feel like
Let's Travel some
I don't have enough although we're
almost
this cooldown is almost ready but we
need bones so let's go get some bones I
guess
go get some bones
everybody got food everything's fine I
think wait I could summon another demon
all right let's see I know that means I
have to build like another one you know
what I'll do that
uh
God damn it ah
lacking materials
uh wait maybe now not anymore
oh what does that [\h__\h] no
no it was an accident
wait did I just lose materials because
of that
wait what
is
one can use so easily destroy things
like that a [\h__\h] hell
ah
I wanted to help build it
I canceled it it could have at least
reversed it to the normal State not
completely demolished it
yeah ask for confirmed please please
okay what does that do to my summon
we'll check it out in a second
okay I'm not sure maybe I didn't lose
anything from that
let's finish this
it's my summer yeah my summer cold
outfit
[Laughter]
[Music]
am I in my book always has to be close
by so I can check
so uh
-huh
this seems like
It reversed my summon
seems like I can summon him again though
so we have this one
okay and then the second one
[Music]
lies away and returns of like how often
I wonder
starting next week with a half of a
spirit heart
[Music]
oh
this one is the best in terms of
Health drops
not one of those why not
okay facility let's go
what day I'm in it I didn't count the
days wait it says it on the top all
right day 77
wow we're pretty far
okay I'll make some food and then I'll
go
um oh dear
wait are you gonna clean it up no you're
laughing at the poop
that's no laughing matter
I'll just look
there's a chance that this will cause
illness but oh well
no salmonella and my fish not all
why is no one doing this consecrating
why
all right oh [\h__\h]
okay
I think ready to go
oh oh okay okay here uh nope shut up
record starring followers
uh I guess so
we need new followers anyway right
why not
food please
okay what are you ordering which Burger
do you want that kfb hmm
we have the Yago Burger the Phoenix
Burger
some vegan burger or vegetarian whatever
you want mate
oh
I'm so sorry
you have to live with this name now
that's the only thing I could think of
now
okay then we need to make even more food
but hey we got more pizza people yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay let's do this hi hi so much
freaking food
wait wait okay enjoy everybody
stop starving just eat food
[Music]
I am Divine I know
Exquisite and divine
um
okay can I go now
we have enough beds oh I probably don't
good argument let me check
for oh
yes I do 14 beds 14 people
yeah I do I guess I do
okay I have a feeling Garfield will die
while I'm gone
well what you gonna do wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait sermon first
oh Quest
[Music]
no what the [\h__\h] the second time
someone's dying
like he he wasn't like what 86 or 90 or
so of chances of surviving
how lucky or how unlucky am I
oh God
don't look at him
what do you mean
so sad for cooling I liked you
know
[Music]
that is
so sad
at least when he's already wrapped in oh
God okay I was gonna say at least when
he's already wrapped and um
he's in the toilet paper people won't
throw up anymore right is what I thought
but I guess I'm wrong
hmm
okay
it's night time again [\h__\h]
can I don't come to sleep yet guys I
wanna do a sermon
foreign
[Music]
okay
now let's go fast
and disturb them no I didn't
no they they were on there way too bad
they were not sleeping yet
all right apparently uh we can open the
store
yeah we're ready to go in there
honestly I just want some bones but
yep let's do it
did you take the money out of the type
books no I guess not
foreign
[Music]
getting closer to the end of the game
but probably not finishing it today
[Music]
which is fine
okay nice we start with a sword oh and
yeah right we have the cape that gives
us all four cards
in the beginning okay
they're not so bad
oh the hands of rage on the top right is
a new one that I bought
and hit down to half a house okay
okay interesting cards not so bad
could be worse
no Hammer yeah point of corruption
explosive projectile okay
it's only been a couple days since the
last time I played this
so it shouldn't be too bad to spot your
silk oh yeah right we get more new items
at once again
once again okay
let's try to be fast
oh hello
[Music]
Miranda
hello
[Music]
friends
he lost his freedom
[Music]
would you like to find out
at the office
[Music]
does that mean you're
nah he just brainwashed you you were you
were not against me to begin with I'm
sure of it what does that mean
no
no kill him
died
what the [\h__\h] did I have any choice
that's some very sad
I had no choice
ruthless
at least I mean hippie toes
wasn't didn't mean that much to me I
guess so
there would have been others that maybe
I would have been more sad about oh
spiders oh [\h__\h] okay they move fast
and they get dragged back up okay
I've yet to take damage
is that audio Fine By the way guys
I hope so
oh you're fine okay
yeah
I'm pretty strong today
yo when are they ever attacking how do
they attack us
they're they like don't do [\h__\h]
weak
why are they so weak
I need more bones please up or down
upward down they slam onto the ground oh
say okay now now I got some damage here
oh big boy
[Music]
big boy has a big skeleton
yeah yeah I feel like I just heard of
meow but I think that was my imagination
pick up everything
I go to the right side here so I'm gonna
go back once
thinking that this was maybe the dead
end
oh no this was also not a dead end
what the [\h__\h]
what
ah okay okay now wait if that's all they
can do then they are welcome new new
enemies for me welcome welcome welcome
I'm guessing I'm not supposed to run
into the yellow balls
okay
ah now I realized those hearts that have
been dropping are thanks to my demon
right
nice
wait who do you keep on shooting
there's no enemy here who are you
shooting
you're fighting
the air
ow it's every 10 seconds here nice
okay now I don't have my blue Hearts
anymore
okay
tell guys how has your days been so far
how you doing again
how are you doing guys how are you doing
eating lunch oh
what do you have I ate I ate garlic
baguette for lunch
it's my birthday oh happy birthday nice
recovering from the seafing oh
that's gonna be gone fast I went to
animal
today oh
what did you buy
garlic bread is fire hell yeah
crispy cold
[Music]
okay uh
plucking eyebrows
yeah girl stuff
pluck my eyebrows too
I used to hate doing that because it's
like was so painful and my eyes would
tear up so badly and I would like get
the Shivers from it but then I realized
there's a trick for plucking eyebrows I
mean I love you guys already know this
one but wash your face with warm very
warm water
we'll do it right after the shower or so
and then the the pores will open up
and if that like it will just
easily go out the hair will just
swoosh it won't be very very easy that
way
yeah big life hack oh I'm surprised some
people don't know it okay cool cool
oh oh
this would bring me two followers that
path but
oh no I don't know do I want that I
don't know I don't think so I want to
revive my people because they're already
like if I revive them they're already
already loyal to me although it does
take a lot of Bones
I've been pain plucking my hot hairs for
ages what
you didn't know
you're welcome holy [\h__\h] yeah even like
honestly it even you don't even have to
wash your whole face like it even works
if you just put a little bit of warm
water on your eyebrows wait a few
seconds and that usually does the trick
for me
hmm
hey educational stream that's why I eat
more girl sucks
I mean eyebrow plucking honestly some
some guys do it too so it works for for
everyone
it's our advantage to plucking instead
of Shaving yeah no stubbles stubbles
um and won't grow back as fast as just
by shaving yeah yeah yeah leave it to me
who has killed some of her hair is
forever for eternity to answer your
questions regarding getting rid of hair
I'll just go this way whatever
lingering presence of shamura can be
felt
collected dungeon resources have
at least there's bones here
what the [\h__\h]
I came here to get [\h__\h]
balance that
I need some examples
[Music]
your little [\h__\h] [\h__\h] at least this
place is small
oh thank you for watching my stream
cute sickle
sicko's Rachel Elders okay I thought I
thought someone died thank God no one
died
okay of course I have eyebrows
you're just plucked
every now and then I don't do it that
often though
but like I'm too lazy to do it like
super regularly
don't give a [\h__\h] about my eyebrows
[Music]
I think my
relatively existent fear of spiders is
disappearing thanks to this map because
they make them look so weak
foreign
pluck my eyelashes what the hell
I do that
who does that
it's insanity
I mean when I feel like some something
feels loose
I might just like with my hands
I wouldn't call it plucking but I guess
I would pluck them but like not
not on purpose like with my eyebrows
okay two two curses
um
interesting I think I'll go for this one
okay
I thought I could get that last hit
there but
ow
[Music]
my precious blue heart
you know there's some people on this
Earth who are really lucky to have like
really really really long beautiful
uh eyelashes
mine are just normal
it's one of them did you see her
eyelashes
she got it from Nabi mama
they both have super long eyelashes
oh I tried like um there's there's a
certain type of mascara not all mascaras
do this here's more girl stock but
there's a certain type of mascara that's
um basically
uh adds tiny little hairs to your
eyelashes while also you know painting
them black
um it actually works quite well in
making your eyelashes longer
it doesn't look as clean as it as you
would want it to be
can I tried that one
um when I was young I applied quite
often
um
peach fuzz no but but they are kind of
fuzzy
um yeah yeah and then there's some
then there's like you know obviously
obviously there's like you know
eyelashes that you can stick onto your
lashes but I don't do that like during
like on normal days
only on very very very very
special occasions
I would stick on some eyelashes
but I don't like the feeling
so I don't like wearing eyelashes
um like fake eyelashes too often okay
you guys know that song is from
California and it's about
about eyelashes
about fake eyelashes yeah very cute song
oh
I'm absolutely rocking it today
maybe it was a good choice to play Cult
of the Lamb today oh
I didn't see that one coming
even more
good that I have that explosion attack
it really helps when he spams the small
spinners
okay I'm being a little bit not so
careful oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay
okay
okay okay okay okay there's just too
much going on you know
I might die
what was that saying foreign
I
didn't have that many hearts to begin
with when I went in there
oh yeah
[Music]
welcome
you are one of us now one of us one of
us
oh
uh which one should I choose which one
am I low on
um
I'm not sure
you guys see my materials like somewhere
I don't think so I don't think I can see
it I guess I'll
I'll go
tap
oh thank you
they're all pretty balanced I wish they
would give me bones
give me bones
thank you for listening to my wishes
okay
returning to come let's see
um how they're doing
[Music]
95 bones even though they took a lot of
items
before the bus but still that's a lot of
Bones we can revive someone
or send someone or even both Maybe
that's a lot of
stuff quick
slow
I'll be fast
now we should sacrifice Garfield
and oh there's there's two old people
now huh
indoctrinate him first wait what was
that what does that mean again
foreign
animated version coming soon
have you guys noticed both Buddha and
Kelly started doing members only
wallpapers too I feel like I started a
trend like they saw that I was doing
that
and we're like hmm we should do it too
Wawa
hahaha
okay
sending unfortunately guys
wait what did you mean by indoctrinating
friendly lady yeah
oh oh
yeah
mine oh thank you for memberships
[Music]
Ah that's what you mean
Garfield I'll see you again sometime
just um wait a little bit I'll be quick
man
[Music]
uh at least the faith is going up
um
and we could also sacrifice someone
how
I still don't quite understand the
difference this is besides this one
giving me loyalty and this one giving me
Faith
I mean this one also gives me Faith I
guess this one just doesn't give me
loyalty
should I do this one too I have so many
bones now I can revive someone too
because I have one more oldie
yeah
who's the old one
it does has taken you finally
all right
wait that's my it's not why do the
people that I marry always have to die
so soon
and go crazy yeah
was a short marriage maybe it was all
according to make
me I saw it coming it was like a little
bit short wedding so why not
okay
[Music]
um
we could even continue but you know
providing someone
but the faith will go down a bit
but while we're at it why not right
oh
this is
I see so you stay married even when
they're dead but you know no one can be
jealous if you know the other people
married people are dead
[Music]
one two two three two one three three
one three three
seven Patty is on seven
broccoli
oh yeah right because we had once
revived but cruelly but I wanted to
actually revive Brooklyn Junior right
and I was like [\h__\h] when I accidentally
revived for Cooley instead okay
[Music]
this time I'm doing it right
welcome back why does that one lower
Faith because they believe so much in
sacrificing but they should be so
impressed by the fact that I can bring
someone back in the first place
what the [\h__\h] anyway did I do my sermon
already okay why is everybody so
weird
wait let me let me talk to you
what just happened there were like a
million notifications also my face is
really low did they just automatically
oh [\h__\h] thank you let me fix your bed
really quick
or is it your bed
oh he has wait there's two people
sleeping in one there's a bug here
this I think yeah there's broccoli
levels broccoli my husband in one bed
with lapless on top of each other what
the [\h__\h] is
fun
what's that as if I don't seem to see
what's going on here I revive you when
meal you jump into someone else's bed
unbelievable
[Music]
NTR RTA
oh my God
I'm so sad I must divorce you by killing
you again
her scandalous right
so collecting Loyalty Rewards now is
meaningless Ryan
but I still do it
in order to make develop even higher and
it will help because if you level them
up
they are better as a demon at least
that's at least one thing
um okay oh doshio
oh what's your cool dance yeah
yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
okay now you're welcome
I don't think I have a bed for you yet
I'll make one immediately although there
is an empty bed
there is actually one and what do we
call you
we were talking about lashes so let's
call YouTube okay
[Music]
you know you will be a blue
obedient terrified of death okay
I went from Sesame Street is that so
worship
[Music]
again and again and again and again and
again and again and again
more more and more worship
every day
foreign
one thing I did today was watching botan
senpai's new outfit reveal
he went for some kind of casual look but
I really liked it it was cute
very cute
did you watch it
[Music]
got like a twin tail version as well
because it reminds me
um when she has only the oh dear
when she only has the t-shirt on with
the twin Tails reminds me of that one
girl from Idol master
Cinderella girls
where you know that girl's t-shirt says
or something like that
yeah
answer answer
is
[Music]
okay
and love
oh okay ah demon summon
[Music]
triggered of course my to go demon
you work you lose
not in kfb though don't follow that in
kfp
[Music]
there
go with you
so sermon
I have to go to IKEA I'm gonna land oh I
I want to go to IKEA Hotel there's
something I want to get at IKEA
hey we have an old person again
[\h__\h]
but now our cooldowns are half so maybe
we can do one again very soon
[Music]
oh wait a second can I not just do this
one
increase the starting level of weapons
once again
yeah you wanna go buy something and then
I wanna also eat some katula
foreign
so how's that ritual looking
okay that will take a while
[Music]
we could
oh
there we go maybe go brainwashing ritual
why not then I'm a little bit less
stressed out although maybe I should do
that
um after the next trip because the trips
will get longer and longer and I'll be
gone for longer and longer
maybe next time
then maybe something else once we love
for you oh
wait ah I can't do anything besides that
one and that one though
because of bones okay I love this one
[Music]
I haven't done a bonfire Rachel in a
while feels nice
nice that
okay he goes up
wait food before I go
um
Mighty meat Fest
okay
how you like that ah
[Music]
please don't eat that
uh
no no no no is he
no okay no one ate it nice
also do we have enough pants right now
wait how
you have it down to 11 again
is it doesn't that count the ones who
are currently demons
foreign
s because of the the fish and the meat
the meat tangent are you gonna survive
one trip of me going somewhere
please survive
silk cradle
part two oh okay and now again we'll get
a good weapon
oh receive double the health getting
extra hard another hard rolling yes okay
I like the rolling cards
it's another extra attack without doing
anything with effort knocks back and
poisons enemies nice
okay let's do this
let's get bones
I really need bones more bones please
what what
interesting new enemy a caterpillar with
spikes
nice okay I think no damage
I want the actual [\h__\h]
okay no problem
foreign
[Music]
guys I'm still for the anniversary one
year anniversary I'm so like
thinking
what to do for my anniversary I have
like some ideas
but yeah
I'm not sure
I'm breaking breaking my head over that
as you say in German
in German we say
yes two year
two year anniversary
[Music]
um
foreign
Delight oh is it a new a new place we
can visit where all that glimmers is
gold guaranteed meet us this cave opens
seven days
ah perhaps we can get some stuff when we
try gold
I guess
that means the other room might have
been a dead end so let me go back up
foreign
[Music]
all the Japanese girls do 3D concerts
for their anniversaries I want to do it
too
you'll have to take what we get
foreign
I wish I wish guys
I wish
more Freddy kiwawa dancing please
which is also another room here what the
[\h__\h] where should I go first
that books
sake
huh
oh this looks like a no it's also not a
dead end yeah
what
okay we need to eliminate this guy
immediately that that was okay oh
yeah I killed it before it's come back
what
he sends it out and then it comes back
to him so that's her not to roll towards
him because it will bite your ass
I just gotta
go stay away
tangent has reached old age oh no
okay I think the other one was the dead
end after all go back again
once again
oh he's the Healer right I forgot I have
to take care of him
don't
yeah
and we got so many bones again
lovely lovely love them
super nostalgic song for me
kind of a joke song though
you don't want to hear that song oh you
know it
Suga
you can open this one
no no no no no no no no no no no no okay
I need to know the difference between
these again
uh
uh this one is
which one was this again
pretty nice
nah I don't need that many I have enough
a follower
on this one
okay
the one on the left is your gold replace
with food
oh okay
come on we're following your wisdom we
make this offering normal music dancer
it will get no answer
[Music]
Nemesis will be your destiny
foreign
[Applause]
there goes the no damage run
and you get slapped in your face
see my strategy though I run into them
while they're spawning while they're
still all together
to get that
AOE damage
anything else now nothing left to offer
wow boring boring
foreign
[Music]
well I went awaits indoctrination
Now give me that money
oh it's not even that much not nice
nine
super nice
couldn't
okay so I will go
um
actually
I think I'll go for this one I don't
need food hmm
I'll take that
just drops food and not gold wonderful
let's go on a walk everybody
yes
oh he's gonna do it again
go that far huh
no
no no no
it would be an awesome cosplay
a character that you can cosplay
if you're a fan of the game but I mean
it makes more sense to cosplay the land
or so
foreign
enemy
okay we have a free
free pass and I'll go this way first
oh
chop that treat do we really want to I
feel like
that tree it's kind of scary
[Music]
I will be fine right it's just some
extra wood
foreign
we got two of those
[Music]
when I get hit now I have four in total
holy [\h__\h]
out
okay caterpillar spider scorpion we got
all the favorite foods of half jam on
here we should invite her for dinner
come under you
come get your dinner
I mean scorpion though she ate a
scorpion before right I think so holy
[\h__\h] that's like
so badass
it's so scary at the same time
damn girl
she ain't scared of nothing
nothing can stop oh I can't stop it
where am I there we go
nice fast and easy
most powerful Idol
yeah she has withstood many challenges
oh oh are we gonna talk
foreign
[Music]
my followers again
foreign
[Music]
the one that they changed
my God yeah
it doesn't matter I will become God In
The End
ow
If Only They would spawn some far apart
in this big ass room
all right
sacrifices and so many revivals
I'm not scary guys I'm thinking of both
revivals and sacrifices I want you guys
to die and live and die and live forever
cycle the cycle of love
this one
the Phoenix way exactly
and the thing that you guys all wanted
to do wanted to become
more like Chihuahua
foreign
not quite Phoenix but something similar
to that perhaps yes oh
[Music]
what is that
new that's attendant
I didn't even look at the other one [\h__\h]
oh no it's a curse oh I stand I see I
see I see
I liked the previous attack
oh
all right
all right I'll take it
last but not least this room
you know already at the beginning of the
stream today and for some reason
I feel like I have no energy I wonder
why
my head my forehead hurts and my eyes
hurt you
it's weird I just got enough sleep wow
nice attack
I did get a lot of sleep actually this
looked pretty well
set up on Haley I don't think that's the
reason but hmm
I think
kiwama just needs more vitamins Maybe
Maybe
maybe that's why I'm lacking energy
forehead is hydration
how do you know that
it's not really so
and I think hydration and vitamins I
should take
to take vitamins properly
oh the hammer oh hell [\h__\h] no I'm not
taking that no
yes and I'll take this one but I don't
like that projectile oh
I'll switch I'll keep the other thing I
have which is
draw strong wait
wait nine okay now it gets confusing
anyway I'll recycle this one
you Hammer yeah come on
okay I got one really unnecessary hit
there
but okay
oh migraine is this what migraine feels
like
is I'm not feeling that comfortable well
you know the girls got a stream a
streamer's got a stream of YouTubers got
a stream
oh
why why did I do that again
hey
you little sucker you're a little tiny
sucker this this map is not nice
I hate this map already
come here or be shocked by my demon
where did oh that is
oh I could take some pain pills I
usually don't take them I feel like my
painkillers are probably
um last time I checked a lot of my
medicine was
um what's the word
outdated you know what I mean
past its uh due date
expired yeah a lot of limits
painkillers too you guys still take
painkills even though they're expired
would you do that
oh [\h__\h] that is so powerful
this is so powerful
be fine
I know he's okay
foreign
would never take any expired medicine
kills are likely still fine just less
potent
doesn't work as good
I see
I see I see
oh that land
oh
God damn it no not before the boss fine
don't take all my speed
it's behind oh my beautiful hearts
foreign
I wish I had some blue ones sort of the
Dead hearts
LaPlace has reached old age okay
hahaha
I don't have very so much chill chill
thanks for worrying though maybe I will
take a pain color
okay let's see
oh what what
oh God
oh my God oh my God so much poison
that's that's not nice oh there's no
space to be
oh
[Applause]
at least it's dropping high thank you
oh spikes
come here
spinning
[Music]
[Applause]
because I think oh damn he has a lot of
HP huh I was supposed to say because
it's going well it is but also
sheesh
[Applause]
okay okay okay okay
ah
oh God
oh god oh there okay now that is looking
bad oh
[Applause]
my gosh
foreign
[Music]
again I wonder
I hope not
small ones please small ones okay
okay look it doesn't look like he's
gonna spawn again
[Applause]
oh wait never mind it did fun
wait where oh I got a lot of parts back
nice oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
Niche let's have space
final form no thank you actually don't
want it
oh really okay I'll take it
uh how cute look at those those tweezers
he didn't stand a chance they did stand
against they were pretty strong but I'm
just so good at this game thank you
thank you for the rest of the chat
clap clap clap applause applause is
exactly what I deserve
um
back to the Cults we go halfway through
I feel like we're speeding today it's
only been one and a half hours
oh
ah
I think there's a cat hair in my mouth
um
somewhere
now I'm not gonna finish the game
I'm crazy
yeah yeah I don't know I can't get it ah
I guess I'll just have to swallow the
hair
yeah oh my head okay you know what I
might actually really go look for a
painkiller
um
I got the cat here but yeah BRB I'm
gonna look for something because I don't
I don't feel so a lot of headache this
is quite strong
see you in a second or two
sugar might have okay good we eat some
chocolate too
foreign
[Music]
I found
a couple of painkillers that were not
expired yet
nice
nice shot
and I'm gonna take
I'm gonna take the one that's famous for
headaches
aspirin
normally whenever I don't feel well I
just rest but
I want to stream today so we're gonna
do something about it if I am able to
open this [\h__\h] hi chunky wonky
can't open it
let me try with a pen
oh that works Alex
drink lots of water
I don't know
[Music]
why is this [\h__\h] so hard to open
child proof cab yeah this [\h__\h] is weird
what the hell
okay got it
okay
kind of do need to go to an Isle meeting
yeah remember to hide Drake guys yeah
[Music]
oh
no I mean generally my goal for the cult
of the Lamb streams is always to kill
one one boss
and at this pace currently we're going
pretty fast today
I want to jinx it but we're going pretty
fast so I think you know don't have to
cut it short but yeah
yeah uh let me actually cut an idol
meetings
okie dokie guys
and back
back now
we may continue
that's a big bottle I never say so you
know what I will say for once
[Music]
oh divine inspiration unlocked once
again
what do we get this time
um
honey
sorry
hmm
differently than the last okay what do
you mean what's different do you mean do
you mean do you mean my testicles
should I go for
I really don't like the missionaries
even though it says like 86 and stuff so
far my people have almost always died
hmm
bone decorations
look at this one
yeah I don't even have to get the bone
decorations first
what the [\h__\h] are you wearing is this
how you speak to your cult leader excuse
me how [\h__\h] rude
[Music]
foreign
barely lost any faith while I was gone
what's going on with that
Mr ritual
uh no we can't have the cooldown's still
there oh but it should be gone soon
meanwhile we could sacrifice uh revive
someone which will know what to say but
we'll just do a sermon right after
[Music]
okay who do we want back
what do we want back
I didn't I can I can revive tippy toes
yeah the one who
tried to kill me interesting but I don't
think it was really him you know I think
he was manipulated
[Music]
I'll
um who hasn't been revived
at all yet
surprise and remember did I ever revived
her prize
[Music]
tidy for level seven
I revived already several times it's not
fair
gonna
go with
um
[Music]
perfect shot I haven't seen him in a
while
let's let her rest
hundred two years old amazing
okay and then a Snowman
I want to have a sermon everybody
70 70
Bang Bang
[Music]
beautiful okay now we wait for the
for them
uh ritual to be possible again to
sacrifice someone
see what else is going on here
oh [\h__\h] a bed is broken
always go and check your beds there
might be something broken
and then maybe get some food here
[Music]
oh you're right for me now don't they
yeah because they upgraded it
oh God
[Music]
Oh
I thought those
but no that's
that's why you [\h__\h] fool all the time
I thought those ever since they
harvested it goes in there and it
doesn't just automatically go to me
cooking time cooking with you
don't need that
I'll clean it up
their eating sounds are so cute can we
build something what could be a
useful oh
I guess this thing
oh [\h__\h]
oh no no no no
why are you guys not going to sleep
after that sleeping
[Music]
don't be so stupid you too
oh
finally
final needle
okay then we indoctrinate you hey no no
cute name Why Don't We name him guys I
don't know
[Music]
let me name him
head horse
[Music]
let's call him aspirin
ha
[Music]
Brown pink
welcome to the calls
[Music]
my happy little pill
make my headache go away
la la
[Music]
no don't look
um
see life can end so suddenly out of
nowhere you need to appreciate life
make the most out of it
can be over in an instant
oh yeah I still have one here that I
didn't use yet
don't even think about it hey I mean you
come in here you immediately have a
class for me these new recruits have no
work ethic are you talking about
yourself if you ask me they should have
to prove themselves make them work for
the night
uh ah you want the ritual oh yeah oh we
can do that
I was gonna do that anyway I think
apparently according to aspilene you are
a lazy boy
apparently you don't like working but
you're welcome to prove him wrong
day
foreign
and he's easy to level up okay
interesting
ah bold claim for my newest recruit yeah
tangent before you die I will sacrifice
you we don't want this to happen again
I think now should be ready
foreign I know it's so slow
okay
then
let's do this for now
[Music]
no time for sleeping you can sleep when
you dance
yeah that's what I like to see
is it nice to be so productive and
efficient
I already preached it okay now why why
do you guys look sleepy literally told
you guys to not be sleepy how is that
possible
okay I will allow you and only you to
sleep
collect award from aspirin where is he
Mercy
is this how I joined the culture you're
already part of it do you want to double
join the cult
double is always better
interrupted you sorry you you should
thank me for Reviving you though
I want you to
no
help
can you help tense the farm please
okay wonderful I still don't know
where
okay
beautiful
[Music]
why is
Donald Trump trees
why are they all just praying I just
told you to do something
not tasks available what about that farm
it's still there
not the the tree farm
weird okay
[Music]
and pray for me I guess
I want you to I want you to I want you
to pray for me instead of crying for me
booked
the worker might be sleeping oh
perhaps oh spider spider was sleeping in
the tent
okay I'll make a little bit of food and
maybe I'll go already to the next level
[Music]
we have to pay your salary twice I guess
that's
his
don't say how I made you do it
wasn't me no no no
um
maybe what else can we make them work on
I wanted to build the mushroom sculpture
mushroom sculpture ones and decorations
finally we can build it
I'll just
I'll just build it
no please can I place it there
you go
beautiful go go go build up fast do it
fast
we can finally finish that mushroom
Quest
foreign
looks nice
return to social okay let's go but I'm
so scared that
um that one follower will die when I'm
gone
it always happens when you don't want it
to happen
singing
[Music]
it was awesome
how highlighted his voice before I'm so
inconsistent
[Music]
how many
I can give you more
I still cannot wait to see what happens
he's um going a little bit insane
Moore have pledged themselves to you oh
interesting
can I give you more like any time now or
no
I guess no okay now just uh will have
devotion ready for me whenever I come
[Music]
it's not good for him
but okay I'm not his mommy I will let
him do what he thinks is best for him
what he wants to do
okay
um two old people
um
rituals
[Music]
foreign
I can at least do something to be
productive while I'm waiting
for the other ritual to be ready
oh yeah
okay
[Music]
the fishing ritual did you finish the
Midas Quest what was the Midas class
foreign
[\h__\h] we have three old people
oh sacrifice close to me what
new location wow
holy [\h__\h] you guys are loaded with money
I'll come welcome look everyone we have
a visit today
did he melt them with gold
should I've seen that somewhere before I
thinking lord of the earring The Hobbit
in The Hobbit
oh stop laughing now guess may not look
like much but fortune favors the gold I
mean ball
my dear new friend meet us cave there's
a certain class of clientele there's a
golden path
if you can meet those standards welcome
please look around you're my guest here
I will leave you to peruse what
should you have any questions meet us
it's here to help I have questions but
I'm not sure if I'm really allowed to
answer that didn't quite seem like a
genuine offer
um
that enemy bodies explore damage
yourself get plenty of devotion from
your followers for free
Julia Visionary left should always use
we can offer you our devotion for great
friends the price goes up the more you
want it down the longer you live
is how long can you resist
what yeah
nah unnecessary what is in here
oh yes this is where we trust our
precious gold to the gods sometimes and
there were never once they give back
more other times it is lost but it is
not for us me Immortals the question
present company excluded of course but
for the use of such a service the
organization would require us let's call
it a donation
someone of your talents shall we say 10
gold and chocolate bars
wait for what for what what do I get
sacrifice follower
and I get golden exchange are you still
[Music]
I hope a lot
um who seems the closest to death
triggered
I got a costume part
oh yeah they die with their necklaces
it's fun it's fun we have a lot about
those
and when we get I'm sorry don't be
scared what the [\h__\h] no don't be scared
[Music]
that is
very
[Music]
terrifying uh the golden crowd wait now
now wasn't that also a fan Game of
Thrones
oh [\h__\h]
wonderful wonderful yes much better I
have a few more of these if you're
willing to help me grow my collection ah
those things
blah
he has too much gold he kills people of
them
oh yeah crown for the king yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] believable
foreign
[Music]
to Gold that's cool but then please
don't touch people
foreign
[Music]
threw up actually impressive
um
but yeah
[Music]
sand
I have one loyal person yeah yeah so
we're gonna sacrifice that one the
purple one over there
your time has come
you slept with my husband so
justice justice
um
what was this again ah
like the cleansing choir and harvest
motivation okay I'll do this one
what did you miss that when that
happened
foreign
[Music]
space and time with those mystical
mental side mushrooms oh sure sure okay
right after this virtual once this one's
over you guys get the other one
but now it's time for
almost almost
yeah
almost
[Music]
I can get one of those now but I don't
really want them hmm
oh [\h__\h]
Chris is still double damage because I
don't know what I mean at home
okay won't use it but
honestly it's weird that the the basic
one is kind of the best even though it
doesn't do anything
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay damage now increases we're set
swimming wait a second actually
[Music]
dodging
I will go back to this one now because
it spares us a lot of time so we don't
have to go to the turret rooms all the
time
actually it saves us a lot of time
actually decent one but they're all not
really like they don't blow my mind but
did I do the fishing yeah
yes I could go fishing Go Fish
oh [\h__\h] fishing is here
it got hard nerfed recently oh is that
so was it better before
hmm
fishing time guys
I know this is the most exciting content
[Music]
they want the mushrooms you can have
them I don't like them
more exciting than watching paint dry
well yeah at least I agree with that
yours at work it's hard to catch a
stream does
1000 High
say hi more often or else
[Music]
it's nice that you're trying to be here
thank you
day 85 can we finish it before day
hundred hmm
probably not
around around 100 we're probably gonna
be done
by the way tomorrow
uh at night my mom's gonna come over and
sleep over
still in the usual room
and my mom's gonna come over
so tomorrow I'll probably
um no Super Chat reading proudly but I
still stream
and the original time should be fine
no Super Chat reading probably so I'm
gonna try to do that today
and yeah she's gonna sleep over I think
for one night
I haven't seen her in a while and
yeah
I think it's time
so I said mommy you can come by and she
said she's gonna make tonkatsu for me
because I keep on talking about it
wait did someone die of old age did I
just read that correctly
you [\h__\h] could not wait for my ritual
none of you
unbelievable
yeah I don't think she ever tried making
it before but
I will tell her how to make it and she
will make it better than if I would make
it even though I'm the one giving
instructions yeah
foreign
you need a lot of oil so I don't like
um dealing with so much oil
is
[Music]
I hope I still have some tonkatsu sauce
though I'm not sure
I hope
oh wood
oh God
say Nico
psycho
sauce
[Music]
I love everything about
yeah Bulldog sauce
okay I'll go back once and check on the
on the dead people
let me get a devotion clip first
yeah I love
um the Sesame
Sesame Sesame
salad dressing from Japan
I never see it here but in Japan I ate
it all the time it's like such a
Main
and
salad dressing where is the dead person
I see someone dead
[Music]
I thought I saw
I thought I saw it say someone died of
old age
I don't see nobody right
[Music]
okay okay I will do the sacrifice now I
think now should be possible let's see
how many old people currently exist but
Baka I think just while I was gone grew
old but
let's see everybody come in it's time
once again oh
no
okay I didn't die there you go 52 53 oh
[Music]
I feel like LaPlace has been old for a
longer time
I'll get rid of Laplace first
and then we should be able to do the
other sacrifice too very soon
party Kindle
[Music]
and the other one needs a bit more time
okay
[Music]
they're brainwashed I don't even need to
do a sermon no no no not brainwashed
they're um they just don't need to sleep
all right
but it's locked isn't it locked in place
anyway
LaPlace has ascended congratulations
[Music]
this thing I swear to God is broken
no one's sleeping
no one's working
foreign
should I just make a new one right next
to it
perhaps
[Music]
okay I'll make a new one
um
there we go
[Music]
foreign
no problem for me
[Music]
it's time to have a maternalist become
healthy why that's pretty lights in my
Combs no heaven is heaven
don't tell them lies
Heaven is beautiful
[Music]
tonight not bad
hi
hi hi hi
oh
level up
oh congratulations let's now eat the
food stop being so hungry all the time
oh you too
the cold is going so loud
[Music]
wow
wait uh
foreign
notification whenever a certain ritual
that you want to do
is ready
to be performed again that would be nice
the alarm
[Music]
I'm gonna inspire you
for your followers seems so hard it
actually kind of is I thought you know
getting up to 50 60 100 or whatever
would be easy
but no
not at all also that that's fine that
was carrying a freaking what coin and
this one is also carrying some Lumber
strong spider
okay I should maybe go for another trip
[Music]
oh God my eyes are so tired but I think
my headache is gone
I [\h__\h] that one up didn't I
don't know
I think I didn't [\h__\h] it up
surprisingly
but very tired is that a side effect or
am I just always [\h__\h] tired
I know I'm checking it like every
[\h__\h] second but God damn it
should I just send
one of the old ones to be made into gold
again
[Music]
so connected to him anyway he's pretty
new oh I don't have such a important
bond to him
Ma
and I I guess I need the stone
I don't know if it's worth it to make
him gold I
well then we but then we get that piece
of stone you know for completion's sake
I made a good team what
oh [\h__\h] the one that I always was using
I don't need more I why do I only have
one of those why are they so rare
[\h__\h]
ah
wait
let's see
oh wait this is new that's actually not
that hard it's a random enemy and
explodes near them we just need to level
him up
[Music]
man he's gone my favorite one is gone
but this one's not bad this one's also
attacking
Lazy Boy let's see can we Inspire him
where is he
[Music]
is
this boy let me talk to you
[Music]
I can give him a gift too
maybe I can revive me I wonder
hi Chris is a loyalty we'll Live Twice
as long as the usual life expectancy
that's also nice
okay I'm ready one level half
yes yes milk to the baby milk to the
cold baby
where are you going
go work on the farm please
is it possible to have more than one
person working oh I guess not
because the moment I told him to work
there
the other one left
oh
I thought maybe I could have more than
one working there
well that stuff kind of sucks
okay
um
milk for the milk okay so now plus two
that does he do it more often or does he
just do it stronger I wonder
in any case I want you
I want you
I need you
I love you
please help me this time
and then I guess one that gives me
hearts
um
[Music]
free perfect shot
okay perfect shot I want to keep alive
possible
KFC 48
riddles and I will be the akimoto son
the notification I saw wasn't that
someone died but then someone will die
if they don't rest and it was okay
enough food I think now it's fine to go
for me
okay
bye bye
oh he has a pig
you know
if we're really lacking I don't know a
way to set the extra to hammer oh
temperatures 10 chance okay good we're
gonna be on the map okay not so good
fish
projectile okay that's that's there's
two good ones in here okay it's an ax
that's fine and
this explosion okay let's
power
uh it's so slow I hope we get a faster
weapon soon
responsible then she has metal Castle
my best friend she also
um flexed tonkatsu at me the other day
so
what are you looking at hello I'm fine
you Crown bears are all the same nothing
without your drawing followers
like that you stay tuned to who he wants
you'll never live up to him wow what a
hater chill give me a chance
give me a chance and you'll see how
awesome I am
get out of my way I've got knuckle bones
to play in this come on play with me
what a real challenge
gamble addiction continues
since you hated on me I'm gonna destroy
everything you built up here
for the non-believers
I'll leave you one patch of grass good
luck with that
[Music]
okay
unnecessary for okay
yeah
oh yeah
oh Hearts here a heart broom
I will come back if I'm missing some
hearts
doesn't he normally show up before the
enemies spawn
what was that normal
like he shows up he leaves and then the
enemies spawn but this time the enemy
spun first and he interrupted it felt
like he interrupted them or did I just
kill them I don't think so
hmm
have you found it right here
[Music]
beyond our brothers
he says that so often wait wait wait no
wait who is the other one who's the
other one and it didn't tell me his name
as farina's died no
no no
Seiko wanted us
[Music]
he did
that's so mean
we're done no
okay
that's why I need to get as many photos
as you can in this dungeon oh yeah
there's so many sacrifices in this one
okay there's no route where
we can get
um a follower I'll take that one
like emotionally connected with my
followers because it will break my heart
[Music]
oh that was easy
all right come back
anymore now
sad imagine you know you streaming it on
Twitch
when you throw it on the plate the
followers are viewers so but the viewers
can like they won't control the fight
right
but it's kind of sad when one of the
viewers then turns against you
how interesting though
I'd be okay with you killing me to be
honest oh is that romantic
okay I guess we didn't need the heart
room
I'd have to put you down Kiana LOL
excuse me
wait there's no
oh no there is
okay okay I shall go here then
let's get the followers
[Music]
there's a blue Hopper nice
oh what's that that looks new
York is that like a poison scorpion all
right
[Music]
what do you mean Circle one I just
killed Super One
I'm like 100 sure
he's dead
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm confused
on it
come on ah
did I lose a demon
how could I lose a demon
wait but yeah where are they
Oh there's uh they just you know
sometimes go on a trip but where's the
other one
[Music]
disappear normally you they can't kill
my demons
I'm confused
no the shooting one is still there and I
did get a heart here in this half heart
but it should be there maybe it's a
display bug
oh the bomb demon is once per fight
really
but there is he's shooting
he's shooting something
anyway
[Music]
um
I forgot what this means again
I shall go
[Music]
I'll go here
what four round release the cold and
tick 81 coins well I'm so rich that I
actually don't give a [\h__\h] about that
but wait when when will he leave like
immediately it didn't say when
how dare you think you can leave well
that's not an option
ow
L okay nice
I'm not gonna go back for him to stop
him I think or should I
then I have to do all this again you
know
what do you think guys should I go back
and stop him put him in prison
[Applause]
or maybe I have enough time
but this is a big big
um room because we're at like level
three
I should have time you just need to
hurry a little bit okay
okay let me chose one room with hearts
so no enemy there
foreign
oh guys by the way so on on I think was
it Tuesday Monday Tuesday I started and
also finished
watching Wheel of Time
yeah I knew from what you guys said that
it wasn't gonna be that good so like my
expectations weren't so high you know I
see now you see both demons
my expectations weren't too high
I expected some level of
French or
low quality but honestly
it wasn't it wasn't that bad I mean I I
definitely have some criticism for it
not everything's perfect about it [\h__\h]
but I did kind of like it and I'm
looking forward to the next season
they budget the books I made into
something that's not real time
I see well then once again as I said
yesterday in the collab of Amir
when you don't know the books and you
can't be disappointed you have to see it
as like a different product you know a
different thing which might be sad you
know but you get used to it it's always
like that isn't it
isn't it almost always like that
I'll go for this one
the tentacles that much actually
the direction is kind of hard to get
right
going in fresh yeah
and let me see do I remember my thoughts
about it
I don't remember that to tell you
something about the show
two of them man anyway
ah
what did I think of it
um I like the oh I like the the main
um
the main what what were they called I I
said I or something like that
is
[Music]
the blue one that follows or like brings
them to where they have to go
I liked the actress and
um her
her role her personality in general
I said I am
but then big surprise I don't spoiler
but around the end the big surprise with
with the biggest eyes that I am the
leader who oh
hello everyone the story beat up a heart
oh yeah yeah it's you again
Wayward heart return at last crusaded
the hollow of my chest stands for
reunion may I
and what do you mean
a reunion
may you what
may he what
oh he wants
what
one of my hearts
sure no he takes my
weight are you taking also the follower
behind it
[Music]
he gives me like a golden heart what
is
I need to only find it and I will see
her again I have waited here for so long
and all I want is about a moment
together once more
wait what
what
oh at least there's some blue hearts
don't give me that give me that thank
you
something
he took my thing
my heart
okay
oh
really that's nice
lose Red Heart cane disease hearts
[Music]
out let's hurry up
wow
oh they eventually spawned if you don't
kill their egg early enough oh
foreign
protector quite a lot but I genuinely
found the the whole concept like some of
the situations kind of cringe
like the how they interacted like the
other eyes that I how they interacted
with their protectors like when they
kept together and stuff
that was kind of Fringe
and then there was like you know that
one group that had like
what like a
free or foursome
what what
um kind of weird
okay some of that was kind of
and it felt it felt unfitting
um but also
what else
and also I remember about the show
remember [\h__\h]
no
it's fancy seeing you here
[Music]
need to turn instead of two chains
most voracious of appetites curve can
contain
[Music]
most Adventures of ideas cut off and
cauterize before keeping chairs to rot
and spread oh
very Alice what other records was given
how does one kill their food yeah good
question
oh
oh wow really it all you give me is
wisdom
what was that room for
eign
[Applause]
all right
[\h__\h] wrong direction
um
uh oh you know one more thing I found
French about
Joel was uh Now Sports is it a spoiler
alert you know that the dark one it's
not a spoiler alert I don't think it's a
spoiler the dark one is
visually I don't know not so well we're
represented
I feel like the way they chose to
represent him is so boring
just a guy in a suit really
it's like kind of anti-climactic
you asked me
I understand it's so like generic it's
so boring like you could have done so
much like look at it already feels like
they got some inspiration from Lord of
the Rings so if you want to get an
inspiration from Lord of the Rings then
look at their Sauron okay
or whatever look at anything evil and
Lord of the Rings and take inspiration
from that although like besides the dark
one I feel like the rest of like enemy
characters were falling
I think
no
I also liked the twist they had with but
some some people are they look normal
but they're actually like followers of
The Dark One
that was interesting
all if I was subscribed below the Rings
the description of him in the book is a
lot scarier oh
I see it
oh that was cute
I would use it if I didn't want to
recreate my golden path
[Music]
you have no idea what I'm talking about
yo rule one of kfp watch what I'm
watching and keep up
keep up guys
what
oh
kept me waiting there I thought it was
[\h__\h] again
oh aside
no wait that's a curse right oh yeah
it's Chris it's I'm actually I have the
same one right now but this is
one more level higher okay
you know yeah yeah yeah okay I'm
confused sorry brain empty moment
[Music]
extra cologne
also generally I liked the main
characters
I did I did like them although
kind of tacky a little bit the the
relationship that's going on and then
the jealous scene
what can we do
but as I said you know I feel like
I feel like I'm blessed by having so
many of these kind of fantasy shows at
once right now
because that's one of my favorite genres
you know
I'm just hashtag blessed
um
foreign
[Music]
it was attacking yeah
oh but you know what oh oh I really
hated that um
food who was
um
killing or like trying to
eliminate all of the ice today
pink cringe yo like obviously scary as
hell but also cringe as hell and
but I guess
they did a good job and making him
scary and cringy I guess goal
accomplished that must have been their
goal
cringe in what way
I don't know I don't know how to explain
it describe it
oh silk cradle oh stronger than still
huh is that so
and the white cloaks were pretty
terrifying honestly that was good
because like it made me go really
Doki-Doki whenever they would come
across them
and it was very dramatic when when you
know the two
friends were kind of
uh caught in his tent trying to convince
him
and then and then it was it was quite
the cool moment when finally I forgot
his name but you know the one dude
activated his
his
magic or whatever that was uh the wolf
thingy
um
but at the end of the season it feels
like he's gonna turn against them right
I don't know is he is he it wasn't quite
clear
why is it clear I don't know anyway we
have a bus fight now let's go again
[Music]
manageable though
oh or is it
it goes away pretty fast
[Applause]
and he doesn't seem to be calling any
friends
[Applause]
why is he so easy compared to the one we
had before
but the one thing is like when they
don't call their friends that means you
won't get any or like enough for more
for using the process oh
[Applause]
the walk before it was way more
difficult
[Music]
yeah the one before it was way more
difficult what the hell oh
[Music]
beans and beet fruits
it's a new new vegetable
healthy healthy okay we have one more to
go guys
boss fight next
if that guy is gone what's his name
what's his name who was the one who
wanted to leave did he leave
did he steal my money
with my face
wait wait we wanted to do the
brainwashing ceremony anyway
I was gone for too long guys
holy macaroni
[Music]
yeah bye did I fail the quest
let's see
oh
I did
and what's gonna do it now
anyway can we um sacrifice someone let's
see do I have someone old I should
sacrifice the one who wanted to leave
who is he wait what
huh
what where's everybody
you [\h__\h] kidding me
[Music]
yeah we will let them join because I
where is everybody
decorations okay sure I will do it yeah
yeah I'll do anything you guys ask me
for
eign
[Music]
I'm gone for like five five minutes
and for real though like how I couldn't
really happen faster
[Music]
pretty difficult
he did steal my money huh but 81 coins
is not much it's fine
um
[Music]
anything that could help me
higher capacity healing
[Music]
promise motivation
um
not really that sounds that helpful
[Music]
Tuscany not online
oh
[Music]
yeah I guess if anything then like stuff
like this
um
I don't have time for this holy [\h__\h]
my God
did he just sleep why why I didn't get
notifications about that what
I didn't get notified
are you the center went so who's
currently in the center or is no one
descending
they just look angry but are they
don't they have like red eyes when
they're descending
I did oh I was preoccupied I wasn't a
tangent oh damn of course tangent also
left us
uh
Mamma Mia
and we don't have to sacrifice anyone no
one's old either you're not descending
but they look hella mad and that makes
me mad be so mad
wow
I'm I'm like what what
what
oh I don't even need to [\h__\h] make so
much food
barely have [\h__\h]
but we're gonna accept like some
starving people
so you
um
[Music]
he's a 10 because he's not gonna be here
for long probably
temp
welcome Tom
I was never tempt before
what about you guys here being a temp
sucks oh don't wait no no during school
I had to do a temporary thingy but like
oh maybe
like two days or so
I did I did it at my mom's job
at the time that body's oh [\h__\h] okay one
second
um
stressing me out now
[Music]
does anybody know the song
I know I know I know I know I know I
know at least look they're believing
they were
done
you know
you guys don't know
I've been up to me so no
no
song is called the stress from an idol
I'm hella crazy
oh what's the propaganda speakers
finally what a cult really needs
stupid centers all right
um work faster
I'll just put it here
oh my gosh
what is that are they both in range
I could put one
here
[Laughter]
because it makes them work faster so I
guess those are the important spots
pretty much
oh
they also pray faster oh
wait the where I put it now it doesn't
reach it does it
[Music]
I can
it's hard to place it here though I
guess we can place one like
here because the one I placed here
[Music]
it doesn't really cover I'll put one
here
could help a little bit
rest
okay okay
everything's being taken care of again
but like when I leave to go on a crusade
I I almost have to just accept the fact
that something like this is gonna happen
acceptance expected
over the entire ground
oh
[Music]
well they sleep fast if it's over there
sleep faster that's almost like saying
wait faster
is a certain amount of time
or is it I don't know maybe maybe it
does make them sleep first
you have enough to cover the entire
place I guess so
all right give them something to work
it's hard to see now where I put them
I'll just do it roughly
foreign
needs propaganda speakers too
how about this is that good enough
[Music]
it's fine they need fuel
that's fine we need gold bars gold bars
for fuel
it's okay apparently we soon soon we
will get
um
and oh dear
I need more toilets perhaps
soon we will get
apparently money instead of the the
devotion
and I'm building up a toilet
oh come on I'm falling asleep to watch
only me having a propaganda Tower next
to the bed
it's ASMR to fall asleep faster
day 19.
Selena
[Music]
oh wait that was not
I thought it felt another grade there I
guess I didn't okay
wait is there still a dead body around
that they're gonna take care of it I'm
getting confused
[Music]
in any case it probably doesn't hurt to
put another grape oh it's getting more
and more
damn
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
I need you
urgently
um
[Music]
um what are we calling you
um
plans
stay
don't go don't leave me like all the
others
[Music]
please
foreign
[Music]
kind of fuzzy I haven't showered in days
probably
wish
[Music]
Inspire him right away I'm lost right
now now he's washed he looks better now
please stay starving it go go go wait I
make food I make food
no no
no
um what do we make
okay
dinner time
homemade food
I want that
I want
also the propaganda speakers are still
not build what are you guys doing work
faster
[\h__\h]
I also have to build free decorations
okay
okay you know stand
yeah
[Music]
don't you have original voice oh
no no I said we don't need that right so
we went for the other one it wasn't
option though
20 gold boss how long is it gonna work
I know one gold bar okay
class
you're welcome fake Pokemon
go back to sleep no no go back to sleep
and rest for you
okay where are some finished speakers
this one's finished
[Music]
oh so slow
mm-hmm
I wanted to build another toilet as well
are they still mad I don't think so
the Poop House another one
okay good good good good good good
oh next finally if I'll prepare some
more food because they were actually
starving
um around the end so I guess that was
not enough
[Music]
let's see or yeah
we should do the brainwashing ritual now
or like at least before I leave
for the last bus the next bus
because I'll be gone for a while
and also we resurrect someone now
[Music]
it's really necessary that ritual holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
who wants the one who wants the good
Demon was it sicko one
nah
do you guys remember does someone
remember
cutie patooty
or otibitos
triggers
oh so wait it looks like I cannot revive
that one for Real uh
Ellis
stuff
[Music]
it turned into gold So Gone Forever
it was good
[Music]
okay
um
am I I'm not ready yet I think to go
I'll make the decorations because
otherwise I fail another Quest
that's another important thing I guess
don't take up a quest right before you
go on a crusade unless you plan on
finishing it
mm-hmm
what are we gonna build these ones are
pretty
[Music]
with this oh that one's big
I'll put it here there's nothing in this
area
one
[Music]
I like this one so this reminds me of
uh
the the main yes that my first main
Festival
somehow in in Austria I don't know the
style of it it's kind of cute
um
here I love it
[Music]
I mean it doesn't really look like a
maple but still I don't know somehow it
reminds me of it
[Music]
oh
I'll put it here
but they have something nice to look at
and light up while farming
I love it when you talk about your
Homeland Austria
[Music]
ah
normally it doesn't give me much to talk
about
yeah
[Music]
Ulster is quite decent
why are you crying you should work
help help buildings
[Music]
you're not you're not building
there you go there we go
my cute little pinkies
bunk hammer
it's cooled down a bit now yeah the heat
wave is gone thankfully
I was thinking about going to the pool
today but then I know I ran out of time
[Music]
no one's no one's doing this either huh
busy
okay now they're
all running oh except this one
will help you
I don't wanna help you
whatever I'll help you no
no
you got distracted
you can't like stored some money from
you I already paid me today oh sorry
[Music]
you should probably get more people to
be able to sacrifice if you die
what do you mean
more old people no I don't want so many
old people
and he's broke now but he's happy to be
broke
yeah
the sound that comes from the propaganda
speakers is just a really loud
that surprised me man it's just
and lamp one
dress let me inspire you they speak
about the missing by language yeah
used to play this game what the hell
why hasn't she yet
okay collect Rewards
an icon whenever they're in
in the range of a speaker
where where's the one who gave me the
quest
here's the one
oh it's still yeah oh sorry by
interrupting you dear Lord oh my God
Divine Majestic
she already did was she
doesn't see her playing it
but I think she would like it
hope you're doing well today oh I'm
feeling better now yeah my headache is
gone and I don't feel so tired anymore
nice oh I already did what I wanted to
huh
[Music]
something else too
if we can combine the ritual fasting
with the brainwashing then we have to
worry about nothing when we leave
could combine that what do you think
guys
foreign
[Music]
am I ready to go
I have a feeling we might you know
possibly fail
at least once but
um
I make some food
my knee
subscribe
to bed so you don't have to oh
true that okay but if I do it now I'll
disturb them their sleep
there's only one empty bed oh there we
go
now we're ready
will they really not break anymore also
it seems like I don't have enough
materials to do it for all of them
what is it gold bars
I won't break okay good
that does look really nice they look
really pretty
it's like they're glamping
glamorous camping
I wouldn't mind living in one of those
I mean maybe not forever on long term
but
oh someone's sick
[Music]
how did you get sick is it my food I'm
so sorry
I thought my food wasn't that bad
they put too much salt in it oh my God
I'm so embarrassed
[Music]
ah pancake mix
okay let's see by the way maybe one of
the new ones has something nice
uh
oh no
[Music]
no
why is that one so rare but okay we'll
go with Lazy Boy
is and
and one of the heart boys
okay
okay I'm ready and then we do the two
rituals
and
free
fake pumpkin oh plus five
okay
last away returns of highs
please save me
oh I already actually have the level
three demon thingy
I could
summon three of them if I upgrade it
even safer
[Music]
ah but it needs the gold bars
I don't have them
I need more I should make one more of
those tables
because now it seems like I need a lot
of those gold bars
second one
audio is working good
what my stream oh yeah it should be
working
production Plus
I do have a lot of gold nuggets okay
okay
[Music]
there should be nothing to complain
about for these people
all right
okay maybe for the next time we'll have
three demons remind me guys please
remind me thank you
but for now
maybe we can do one more yeah
okay
then
it's ritual time
just for safety we are doing
um this one first because that one makes
the faith go down the other one makes
the face go up
if you're sticking notes write it down
yeah because I already forgot what I
just said
[Music]
and then following that one up
two days
I might even be gone longer than two
days but I'll try to be fast
[Music]
is the fasting also two days
because the thing is even if I leave
food now it will go bad by the time that
they would need food
[Music]
passing is three days okay
well I hope I hope I hope it's enough I
really hope so
I'm gonna go now
I already miss you
I'm here I'm here
let's go
the fourth time we entered this place
all right let's see oh okay
those are decent cards enemies will drop
more for four rolling into damage we're
rolling into an enemy with damage them
overall damage increased enemies have to
transfer effect that one was kind of
unnecessary but okay
[Music]
thank you
no Hammer please
[Music]
last night my luck was so bad off screen
and on screen I kept on getting the
[\h__\h] hammer
not this time
I would I would leave this dungeon
immediately if they gave me that stupid
ass Hammer again
oh wait that's purses I don't like it
that's kind of weak
I missed even
I'm stupid
I'm letting myself get hit
unnecessarily
by the way
um
let's talk a little bit about rings of
power too did you guys watch it
the first two episodes honestly first of
all I have to say thank you for
releasing two episodes at once
that is so kind no no don't have Prime
nope never will yes no no most people
say no are you guys not even planning on
watching it
definitely checked it out we'll watch
after the stream okay
not interested and why because of like
Prejudice or because you don't really
like that kind of genre
foreign
Ty are not interested
ah come on well
um I will tell you what I was when I
what my fonts were though because I
watched the first two episodes
first of all I will say I do like the
actress for Galadriel she's pretty and I
feel like she fits the elf look
clothes
[Music]
are you ready for the point of the
shopping place
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
yeah well okay so
um
let's see I liked the actress for her
and I did think the dwarfs were
quite good too
um so what do they call it the heart
puts which is those are Hobbits right
those are just Hobbits I think
the hard foots I gotta be honest they
didn't give me that typical Hobbit Vibe
at all
if it's like a predecessor of the
hobbits okay but I still feel like they
should
should have like been more Hobbit like I
don't know there was like you know
there's these two young hard hoods
two young ones
um I would say their faces
you know they have a little bit more of
like chubby faces not the most prettiest
faces I feel like that's a bit more in
The Hobbit direction for me puppets are
just you know
they're not supposed to be as pretty or
so and I like a little bit of the
chubbiness on them
um so those two children are fine
especially the the one
um that was like kind of freaking out
about what her friend was doing
that girl
I feel like her face was very
hobbit-like
yeah but the other ones the adult ones
also not only the way they look but also
their behavior was partially
Kamina so Robert line
um
I don't know
oh
wait
else
also like in like the Lord of the Rings
and and
um
[Applause]
The Hobbit I feel like they
their facial features were more like
more elegant and I don't know it kind of
looks more sophisticated I guess
like it's they stood out more and then
it fitted it fits them better
um I think some of them were fine like
the uh
the dude
oh the friend of Galadriel
uh he he had like some facial features
that I thought were quite elfish
elrond yeah elrond elrond was fine the
lateral was fine
and maybe one or two others
yeah but then again I was I was
disappointed by some others but you know
[Music]
I'll go this way
oh
can I cancel it oh
yeah
you guys again
don't go for the beachward scenes oh
sorry sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
I'll leave you alone now don't worry
just taking the food okay
foreign
[Music]
one of my friends yet but maybe that's
yet to come
and also the humans I guess because
it probably felt weird because in The
Lord of the Rings they never really
I mean correct me if I'm wrong but I
don't think I ever really shelled how
the humans live there was just you know
they stumbled into the team but they
never really showed like their villagers
are so right
oh
oh man my memories
okay but
um
I think
it felt kind of unfamiliar to me
um I mean humans are just humans so they
can look whatever the hell they want to
look like I guess
but the main human lady you know that
mother
they're like
she looks this is kind of weird but she
just looks too much like she's from this
age you know what I mean
she looks too modern her face looks too
modern to me and her her eyebrows this
is a a problem I have in general with
like
long on TV shows it's like
um when they when it's like fantasy
shows like that or so or shows where I
would think that the characters would
um judging by their role would never
have time to pick pluck their [\h__\h]
eyebrows but yet they have all that
perfect the perfect most perfect
eyebrows that as a girl you know that
eyebrows normally don't look like this
naturally you know they definitely are
filling them in with makeup and plucking
them like I I don't believe that in the
in the medieval age or whatever that
anybody cared about plucking their
eyebrows and that that was a thing at
all
so I looked at those kind of things
sometimes in TV shows and I'm like
that's not realistic my immersion is
[\h__\h] ruins thank you these people are
not supposed to look this perfect and
Polished you know you know you know
yeah but I mean she was too bad her
looks weren't too bad but I just felt
like it was too perfect
too polished
I'm hard to impress
just take off your [\h__\h] makeup look
more natural
why why you look so perfect if you and
Alex then okay and I feel like the the
Perfection is stick for the perfect
face the Flawless Hair and all that it
comes by Nature I I like that okay
you look like a supermodel by default
and that's okay
wait
foreign
had a little bit of a XPS lag here
[Music]
but I'm judging it from a very neutral
point of view and if anything I'm way
less um critical than all of you guys
are about it to be honest
I'm not judging what you guys think
perhaps I'm judging
my mom however watched it too and they
did not like it
yeah but
um
I really like having like all this
background story took a lot more that's
like a big plus for me there's like this
big galatrail Arc that's going on that I
didn't expect at all
especially in the second episode
um I'm not gonna spoiler but what's
going on there
it's like it shows you a completely
different size of Galadriel
and really makes me see her Human Side
even though she's an elf
well it makes her seem so much more
human you know
Cleaver or this thing I'll take this one
thank you my soul
and Lord she's an Uber powerful
sorceress she doesn't need a sword
but she looks cool in armor and with the
sword and all that
ah you again oh yeah right
feel the heart this time no no don't
even talk to me
give me that give me the blue one
it's boxed in the
fat one
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell
I need the blue one
[Music]
um
oh he doesn't want anything from me
anyway
guys material clothes or her being a
warrior mod see I didn't know that at
all because yeah I'm I'm a bad fan I
didn't read the books
so bad
very bad fan
okay I they owe me a blue heart but
let's see
let's see how they make it up to me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I forgot I had a different
weapon now
[Music]
what else what else what else what else
foreign
[Music]
I'm curious to see more I'm curious to
see where it goes and even if it's not
like perfect
the fact that there's and
any kind of new
um video form of Lord of the Rings
related content
as a as someone who loves the movies
I I just feel grateful for that you know
more or less Rings makes me happy I
always love getting lost no exactly
it's not perfect of course
but it's better than nothing that's
that's my stance on all of these shows
all of them didn't the house of dragons
is probably not as good as Game of
Thrones although I think it's early too
early to judge
um but better than nothing we love time
as well not the best I'm showing that
genre but it's better than nothing
all right
foreign
in certain
ways but I guess when it comes to TV
shows I'm very positive
what line about Morgan what line was
that I don't remember
reminds me
foreign
emotions going on behind the scenes
glad you're so optimistic yeah
this talk killed my heart what
[Music]
what feedback
both
and you know
I I said I'm excited to watch more
relax you little [\h__\h]
stop being so [\h__\h] picky about
everything take what you can get man
you know people like to picky
giant skull wow
my take was balanced too
like I liked some of the
actors
I disliked others like short other
choices it's just
you know like that human ladies certain
actors just don't look like they would
be in that kind of medieval fantastic
World maybe in the modern show but not
on the medieval fantasy world
and
[Music]
I'm not saying this
because of like
you know I said the same thing about
what was his name Damon what's his
what's his real name from House of the
Dragon
Damon
uh what was his real name Matt Smith
yeah I didn't think he he fits in well
either and the girl renera neighbor
he they also
oh don't fit well and and the The King
The King
no not that much he doesn't look like
um like I would imagine a
a Targaryen
um
thank you
hmm
what I'm still watch it and I'll still
enjoy it
just
a general observation
could be better but it's okay the latest
oh
I guess I'll go with the ax yeah
Luna Lovegood's dad oh interesting
I don't have the face of him in my my
face in my in my head right now
Matt
is that isn't he a doctor
King being portrayed that way is on
purpose to set up the power struggle if
we see him as weak it makes it easier
for us to accept him being on the front
I can't see that yeah they definitely
want to give him a weak image
[Music]
yeah it makes sense
oh God
and back there we go I danced it
yeah baby
okay
finally dodged that one correctly oh
God he's gonna do it I end in and out
okay
oh he's gonna do it and in and out
she's learning
I hope he's gonna do it and in and out
and in
yeah no hit no hit let's go
oh I like the sword
I shall go with that even though I just
upgraded my weapon but okay
my phones are getting sick what what how
is the is the fasting over
well then see that
I'll be fast I'm already at the end
oh [\h__\h]
time is running my tangents aren't too
long
okay [\h__\h] all these items
uh
you have a struggle of being an
Entertainer
I'm lagging
[Applause]
Oh I thought I feel like the FBS are
struggling
where are you gonna go oh
okay that was a dead end let's go let's
go let's go
it's okay if there's safety
even if one or two free time I was just
gonna get more
well I missed everyone with that
foreign
[Music]
like barely taking damage yo
I mean I keep on improving in this game
also a lot of people have been telling
me to play more like uh types of games
more games of this time Roblox games
we can look into them after I'm done
with this one maybe that's gonna be one
of my new favorite genres yeah
foreign
[Music]
games like this where the rooms are
assigned randomly
was that the thing
[Music]
yeah okay
if it doesn't have this um
not fully healed if it doesn't have that
element
um that this one has the really
stressful cult
organizing that might even be better
because it's pretty hard maybe they have
other elements that make it like really
difficult all right we'll probably have
to die once and sacrifice someone but
let's do this guys
no time no time had this yeah I know a
lot of people keep on recommending me
that one so I say that as a as an option
let's go
big boss fights
I'm gonna Focus
there's some water
please be decent easy oh what do you
call that bug again
oh thank God we have the rolling dust
damage thingy what the [\h__\h] is that oh
he like spams bombs
okay okay so far
it's easy
wait I already did so much that what's
up
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay
oh
[Music]
oh he got me there
straight out where am I where am I
there's so much action
I don't think I got hit from that one
though I kept on rolling into where he
was gonna jump
oh [\h__\h] now I got it
oh
one heart left
nice
[Music]
oh come on
[Applause]
there's a nice last hit oh
stop
make your dog good thank you for else me
I know I know I look too pretty to be
human but I'm a phoenix that's that's
why
a little silk cradle thanks thanks guys
I actually wow I didn't expect to
go through here without one sacrifice
damn
big answer to my demons as well
now let's see how my cult is doing
[Music]
I brought some
breakfast didn't let anyone die either
whoa lesson three hours yeah last time
last time we were struggling much more
because of my other reasons but
from half an air house which one and I
won't cry it's 12 hours
[Music]
have I not sacrificed more than that
what is he Counting
a lot because
yes
ah ascending
I only do it that those like four times
all right
her [\h__\h] Style
[Music]
hey how's it going guys uh a few sick
people
[Music]
oh my God
so relieved
everything's fine everyone's happy
thank you
how long was I gone though
the rituals are over right
[Music]
the faith is nice because of killing the
big buzz that must have helped so the
original probably ended it went down a
bit but not too much and then it went up
again thanks to the killing the boss
five days oh damn
fit I'm surprised they made it without
the food though
oh
okay that means today's mission is
accomplished actually
wait you go to sleep please
I got everything first try and I didn't
sacrifice anyone's today last time we
sacrificed so many
wouldn't say my gameplay was
particularly bad last time but
apparently this time I was just much
much better
wow
[Music]
I already told you right
on point skill increased yeah the gamer
in me has awakened welcome once more is
there enough gameplay surely surely
surely definitely
because we have to do the the last bus
are you good why are you sleeping on the
floor oh do I did I run out of beds
oh yeah
I have 14 bands and 10 followers
[Music]
right
why are you sleeping here
I'm so tired I need to be sent to bed
because I would I would but yeah
[Music]
aggressive man
you are fake polka okay you shall be
ascendant
so I might just enjoy sleeping on the
ground yeah in a style
all right let's send someone
[Music]
uh exhaustion from
frosting or what
our only old person right now wow
they're going easy on me now
[Music]
you might have to grind since IRC you
need 21 followers okay okay yeah that's
no problem we can even buy followers so
I see no problem of that
show okay last one once a day eat a meal
of anything
to receivable height
okay
yeah
wait so if I don't go in the Crusade for
like three days
I can gather
more like a couple as many as I want of
blue Hearts one per day
or does it cap at one
I wonder
but that sounds actually pretty nice
[Music]
foreign
hahaha
why are you not sleeping Tampa sat there
waiting to go on the mission okay
their chance of dying is very high
though I think because especially since
they're new
I I don't have a good feeling with that
go sleep please
our first pumpkins
they look so good
I'll do my thank you for reminding me
it's even seventh upgrade yeah
[Music]
we need more gold bars damn I'm really
lacking a lot of gold bars
no ones hold it
almost doing it
[Music]
oh wait you know what yeah I will talk
to you uh
we can unlock something what is this
thing again a place for phones oh
do I get more devotion then
[Music]
two followers at once and I don't like
sending them out there but you know what
I'll do this one
can we refine more or how does it work
and requirements for the final boss is
to have 21 followers I currently only
have nine
[Music]
yeah I'll prepare them
I'll prepare them in time
so we want to stand
wait
yeah chances are he's gonna die but I'm
gonna send him for gold coins
good luck
[Music]
okay
where where are you there you are
welcome
foreign
[Music]
well everything's going way too
smooth right now they're so
happy you guys being happy makes me
happy
oh
yummy I like beach roads
[Music]
um
a bit more a couple more bad upgrades
would be nice too but I think they need
also gold
um was there any way of me to earn gold
anyway for me to earn gold
I have replaced replacement
oh which oh the ritual yeah true oh yes
yes yes
um
[Music]
I do still have a bunch of gold coins
but no they're slowly but surely um
running out
sorry brain is has stopped to work
apparently also why did I not move that
like closer
I'll move it after it's done
laughs
I will help
starting to get tired
I'm actually feeling better than at the
beginning of the stream so I'm fine but
yeah since we did the thing that I
wanted to do I will
um
I will oh sorry I will start reading
super chat soon
[Music]
money ritual is so broken yeah right
wait last time it gave me like insane
amounts of money what
[Music]
you mean
I'm so so lonely so lonely
also these fields recently they're
like never filled up enough what the
hell they can't keep up with the amount
of work
okay I'm gonna make some food while
they're sleeping
[Music]
what oh
okay beautiful
okay
oh I'm ready for you guys to wake up
again
um
thank you
nothing to do for me
wake up
okay
I guess I'll do this
oops
good morning 96
welcome good morning sunshine
yeah
what's the quest that you want to give
me oh no
oh no
[Music]
but that would give us a new follower
I guess
was that which one was that
um third one or the second one
I know
least favorite yeah because I also
failed it so many times
[Music]
to give me some money or is the money
ritual
[Music]
s
oh wow how many
points lifestyle was much more
thank you
why
all right I'm a little bit disappointed
guys where's the money
in a while since the last time I did it
you guys should have earned enough to
you know impress me
foreign
don't waste the cool Downs
let's resurrect oh no how about you
what's up frog welcome back
congratulations let's hope you live a
long and healthy life
thanks guys for super jazz
yeah I don't want to look at these
nothing new to me
also here nothing new right oh yeah
oh you guys are so devoted wow
I'm impressed oh thank you
thank you stones are overflowing
I guess I could leave it there for today
oh
[Music]
take my money thank you
how weird oh money gone young how did
that happen
okay now I really need a lot of those
okay I should upgrade those
now but they're in the middle of doing
the thing
let me take
actually really much faster than before
that's good oh this one I also wanted to
upgrade
so let's do that
she got me spending oh spending all your
money on me and spending time with me
[Music]
mommy mommy
like a piece yeah baby
that's the good stuff
great this one and then we can
what did I what was I gonna do
[Music]
it's gonna upgrade something ah
this one ah I'm lacking some materials
God damn it
I can't rest before I upgrade that guys
go back to work
[Music]
it's okay guys thank you thank you
for the support
time
you know ever since I saw an energy
doing
or maybe I shouldn't have wasted it
there huh
ever since I signed into doing like um
Super Chat readings where she writes
down the names of people with her hand
I kind of felt like
I wanted to do something similar not the
same thing but I can't think of
something that's similar
similar and and different
[Music]
if you can think of something guys
you're welcome to
tell me
yeah she was using a translate I saw I
saw she was trying to speak German
or like half a translator speak German
cute
my new lamps would sell for excuse me
it's just writing down some names
I wouldn't suffer from that
Brian's name
that would take
insanely long
I can't do that
um
I don't know I can't find some some
equivalent
ah
Oh
Come more and more and more maybe I
should make one more of those
now
ah wait no before before we build
another one let me upgrade one first
I'm lacking a few more materials
let's see
I'm lacking
one more of those stones okay
draw hearts let me just write the names
in your art app with the heart
yeah because she was writing them on on
a checkie like on a Polaroid
um style kind of picture
and I thought that was really cute
idea because like I know that too from
and I was an idol otaku
foreign
it's very familiar to me you know
but I don't want to do the exact same
thing
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
it's getting crowded in this place now
so um
come on
[Music]
oh now you can make a much bigger cue
nice
but they're not doing it faster right
they're just
you just have a bigger cue and now he
stops
[Music]
I don't know
um
well well I could do this endlessly
um bye you guys some of you guys
sleeping in the back beds when there's
these better ones open and unoccupied
I don't understand you guys
I would upgrade it but then I guess I
would wake you up so
I shall wait
I prefer the the simple lifestyle
reassign yeah whatever too much work
also why weren't they oh I guess that is
probably bugged isn't it
I'll eat it then because the food
it was still there but the hunger is
relatively low I don't know why they
wouldn't eat it
all right my food then
oh wait
let's go
beautiful beautiful beautiful
that one has nothing
there's someone in prison we haven't had
anyone in prison for such a long time yo
vegetable Feast oh with the Beet fruits
nice
okay
what don't mess it up Kiana
rhythm game vibes
everyone's happy
she looks quick
you're welcome where's my thanks
[Music]
bro let me inspire you congratulations
I turned at the right time I heard money
for you
thank you for coming to the stream thank
you soon
welcome but we're like pretty much
ending because like I already did the
boss like I'm so productive and good
today
such a gamer
I mean let me just let me do this now I
can only do one
something in the cube oh oh
I didn't look at that one yet
[Music]
all right
foreign
yes basically they are KP employees
The Entity of them would be kfp I guess
yes yes yes
[Music]
should go work
foreign
[Music]
under control
this is how you lead a cult
it looks easy but it's not that easy you
know
[Music]
okay I think I'm gonna end it here read
superchata hi
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I might be
um I might play a little bit off screen
before the next time
then I I hopefully will not forget about
the side quest and then do um it before
I fail it once again
um
thank you for the screen capture as well
thank you you too you are welcome to
stay though if you want to
sticking around till the end thank you
we can remind you oh yes
but you don't know when I will play it
off screen
when I plan to do that it might be very
spontaneous
also I'm I'm gonna I'm opening a
chocolate bar called ballisto right now
um
one of my favorite ones
[Music]
of course the purple one
what else
okay let's go to my office
oh why am I here
[Music]
yummy
foreign
are so good
yeah
do you hear bgm now
I think you should be hearing it
no
oh
Jen how about
um
oh
wait do you hear it now
um
okay
but let's wait because I can't hear it
oh well
that's fine I'll read super chats in in
silence
relaxing
you know the UK has really good comedy
shows it's really inspiring even besides
the task master I found a show that's
like
um
uh like they there's like uh Comedians
and celebrities
from the UK and then
um they're they have like two teams
and they read out something that could
be either a lie or the truth
and I try to convince the other team
that is the truth
even though it might be alive yeah would
I lie to you yeah yeah yeah
now I'm thinking that could also be like
used as an idea for a stream with the
girls yeah
they have really good shows I like uh
British humor British humor
I'm gonna eat one more chocolate bar
no I've never watched Monty Python
eight out of ten cans what is that what
is that about
facts in the title is very very
interesting
never hear about German humor
um
I don't like German comedians that much
um I used to watch some back in the day
but
no
I'm gonna throw some funny ones but I
also haven't seen any
um
german-speaking Comedians and like over
10 years probably
it's a British comedy quiz show kind of
thing the the cats one eight out of 10
cats that one
foreign
comedy
shows
on comedian steps they had
of the brunette you know jokes play
scheme
hmm
the host does a survey 100 people on an
obscure subject
and then place you to guess
what the server result is
you guys should like remind me of those
climate British comedy shows that you're
mentioning now
in um a Twitter reply afterwards
so I can check them out before I go to
bed
um
mm-hmm
yeah yeah like if I could probably do
that as a stream yeah too because like I
just asked like 100 or like more even
more than 100
um
kfp members or so
or just whole life fans in general
have a Google doc or whatever
or a community poll hmm
thanks to you and Kathy YouTube started
to recommend me toss most of the videos
well you should watch them start from
season one episode one and then work
your way up I'm at uh I think season 11
now
hmm
Whose Line Is It Anyway I don't know
that one
how many episodes per season
remember it's very varies from season to
season but it was I think like
eight to ten or so maybe per season but
they're all relatively long
um
nice bites of Comedy bite-sized by
bite-sized bites of comedying
for when you need a little laugh and
happiness in your life
yeah five for the first few 10 after
that
I love Whose Line Whose Line is great
it's amazing oh wow wow so many Fanboys
and fangirls
of who's lying interesting okay
remind me of that one then please
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait wait my my th OCC sounds the same
as when I say f-u-c-a-c-k
laughs
quickly
I just can't say I teach man
can't say it like you must say it
anyway let's read super chats I think we
have to read uh the OverWatch ones and
the last rest stream ones right so
starting from these ones
[Music]
let's go
okay
let me see what we have
oh wait
wait yeah yeah I just remember it
then let me go with those first never
mind suck me mango
uh which which one is the ah the 10
anime watch along
foreign
I have yet to continue watching them but
I will I will
I will but right now there's so many
shows I watch you know
all those all those fantasy shows
but I will continue watching at least
one or two animes from that
so we can chit chat about them
now I'm scrolling down
I finished call my dad
down you went straight into binge
watching
the plural of anime anime or animes
um I think both kind of work
they both are fine
no I didn't watch my charm collection
either yet you know that's also
something I should should be watching I
bought that whole collection but I would
have to set up my PlayStation in my
bedroom
um to use it as a DVD player
I haven't done that yet
[Music]
glitch
they do have some kind of way of making
things plural
uh
but
[Music]
um
it's not always used I guess
okay I think I found the start
there you go
okay
[Music]
wow I forgot in that kitchen a Pepsi
Duncan okay
happy birthday thanks for the pinky and
yeah it was your birthday on that day
I'm not sure if I saw it in time it
probably you sent it probably in during
the waiting room
but congratulations attention to today's
my birthday but enough about me thanks
for the fun stream uh these last few
weeks fell into the YouTuber Rabbit Hole
since May thanks to you and have no
regrets can't wait to see what you have
in store for us and thanks again my OC
since May
fresh meat freaky fresh small chickling
at this point I suppose
thank you for joining joining us nice to
have new people here too welcome welcome
hope you're having a good time and Happy
Belated Birthday once again
congratulations
hopefully next birthday you will also
spend with us
yeah looking forward to having you here
for a long time thank you for supporting
me
giant firing
the game
oh what would have never thought so
okay
after and that is the reason why I named
my nickname after the anime
[Music]
I'm so happy to see that my oh she
enjoyed watching my favorite anime from
the bottom of my heart thanks I love you
I love you too well you're welcome you
know
um people didn't really recommend Violet
Garden I think while it's ever gone in
when I asked for recommendations but I
you know I had to think of you so I was
like
oh I should I should add that one to the
watch list shouldn't I
I'm sure Violet Apple Garden would be
very very happy about it
you're welcome
and I promise I will continue watching
it
pillbox
[Music]
is a real I saw it in their profile on
Twitter it says they're a big fan of AOE
too and they drew a fan art uh of me
like in the world of AOE too
and I didn't
um play AOE too today once again so I'm
sure like they were like really really
excited for it and I didn't play it so
it felt pretty bad
[Music]
I'm sorry
next week I promise you look so good
um
I was good yeah they already did like
many fan arts of me thank you so much
please continue drawing kiwawa okay
I didn't get it wrong right it was pill
bug I'm pretty sure the game would
create thank you yes
thanks for the pinky glad I couldn't
catch the stream before going to work
haven't watched about half of these
animes and it's the first time I've been
able to catch in a long while thank you
as always hope you're doing well I'm
glad you were able to check it out oh
even before work yeah
forward did you manage to watch all
those animes before work with us
it's quite a long stream actually
thank you very much for participating
I hope you're doing well too please take
care of yourself and thank you for your
support and your love thank you
black virgin nuggets
well I must have sneezed so often in
that Stream So Many sneeze chats
I'm gonna skip them this time Evans
I'm glad to hear that some of you guys
were interested as well and some of the
anime that we watched and also continued
watching them yourself
without me
nice
yeah judging by the super chats you can
count that I sneezed three times
okay
let me put it up here
thanks for giving our suggestions a try
of course
it was a pleasure nice to watch some
anime again like you guys gave me a
reason
and I needed that reason so
cute
scrolling I'm scrolling to the next
Super chat some scrolling I'm scrolling
to the next Super Chat I'm scrolling I'm
scrolling to the next Super chats to
send you my dances hey okay I have
arrived
accordions
I
don't think you were that late though
this seems to be still quite in the
beginning of the stream don't worry
about it
black virgin Danke Schoen
and um
sounds like
hmm I'm getting insulted in English
thank you for the Reds thank you so much
for coming to Seoul popcon even though
it's late I was so happy to meet the
attention in person this is my first
friend super chat with my heart I'll
enjoy today's broadcast
stand for again ah you lose [\h__\h]
why did that become a new chant
not the first time I see people writing
while syls
it's like when people chant ymd ymd
Yamada
why l s y l s
ony down I'm so happy you were able to
go to Seoul popcorn thank you for going
there and seeing me there and supporting
me there asserting dominance as a kfp
member thank you so much it means a lot
to me
um
hopefully you'll continue supporting and
continue watching my streams alright not
only the the clips yeah
Red Hood 777 thank you soon
thank you
thank you I'm Noah thank you for the
rest of the chat I'm very grateful to
kiwama for giving us Unforgettable
memory wait did I
I didn't read this before right yeah
yeah
I didn't I didn't right
I don't think I did did I
yeah I didn't write
I'm getting paranoid
okay good
even though it was a hard time for you
to participate in the second semester of
uni starts in September so it would be
hard for me to see all of your live
streams but I'll try my best and you
have to
you have to watch money
when his dreams please University and
kiwawa must be balanced
[Music]
oh man
it's I guess it is time for people to go
to school again huh
it's not very nice
it's cool bad school
I sometimes try to watch her stream at
Uni but it will be hard
I'm sure it is already hard enough
without watching my streams so yeah I
wish you the best all of you guys who
goes to University
but don't forget about me
okay and here's a case for you to
remember me
[Music]
thank you
and thanks also for coming to popcorn
yay
nice exciting we're excited thank you
for the pinky hello me again
oh German yeah mine to dance tonight
away throw the handy auto collector yeah
yeah I kind of so good
when us Germany being kind newbie said
yeah
thank you soon
you can give up
[Music]
I'm so proud of you what an ultimate
betrayal oh was that uh was that when I
killed by
I wonder
cute
um
I will I I I I didn't want to betray
pick or ask them why
although you know in that situation I
wasn't sure what to do anyway like I
wasn't even sure that what I was trying
to do I was just standing there and I
was like
well might as well kill everyone who
comes across my path
I didn't expect suddenly pickled
assembled to show up but
I
I don't know what my goal was you know I
was standing there and I was like a bit
well I can't set or no what do I do what
do I do
and then new new person shows up and I'm
like
uh no I don't
originally I wanted to like
um go through the door and then sneak in
and all that but the door was closed so
I couldn't and then I was kind of stuck
I was cornered so I just killed whoever
because I thought they would kill me
otherwise
so I just did what
I had to do they probably
may have even left me alone if I
wouldn't have shot them but you know I
was in the middle of a very chaotic War
oh they would have 100 you think so
you think so
have you talked to people since but not
directly no
yeah yeah I saw her reaction she was
very shook
shooked shocked that I was part of this
too
I just want to enjoy some PVP at the end
yeah yeah
at that point everybody was just killing
everybody
personally
well thank you Skye hope you enjoyed it
I think you did you're welcome
[Music]
cycle
foreign
[Music]
like everything was insane
her whole base like everything she had
in the chest and the stuff that we saw
was by finding out everything
um
I don't know yet either how the new
season will go but I'll keep an eye open
it's the server is not open yet I guess
it's gonna open like on the on the 9th
or so I wonder why it takes so long why
why
yeah we only saw the leftovers yeah
yeah I heard she took down because
everybody's helicopter several times
I'm like
what
[Laughter]
that's insane she had like a proper air
defense what on Earth
[Music]
literally a fortress yeah so actually I
was also thinking like oh what should I
do for next season and I was thinking I
kind of want to like build a proper
Fortress like like something that looks
like an actual medieval Fortress you
know what I mean like
like really big walls and inside
actually pretty big
um I want to build it like a fortress or
like a castle or so
like something big and maybe even use a
real Fortress or Castle as an uh
inspiration as like a guide
um something big but then I wonder if
we're actually doing like team stuff if
if I really should be doing if I really
should be putting so much work into my
own building
when probably the last fight if it's
team versus team will happen probably
somewhere on an empty field or or will
happen with some buildings that we built
specifically for that or so
so that's why I'm not sure if I actually
really commit to that maybe just for
flexing
to show
you know to to have like a powerful
image
yeah even maybe if I build something so
amazing
maybe they will want to use it who knows
I don't know
questions questions I'm not sure a lady
must have a castle
yes
this lady must have a castle
oh
I have an idea
I wonder if there's like
if there's plans of like High castle
High castle
but no I'm not like that what am I
thinking of um The Game of Thrones
um
my dear
Natalie Dormer who is the character she
was playing again I forgot but her
family hi Garden High Garden was it was
probably high Garden
foreign
or
although that probably won't work you
would need an island to recreate um
Dragonstone that would be sick though if
I could recruit I mean
look probably if I build it in the water
like um like pecora
but I can't
I can only build like you know those
those paths out of
whatever a wood Stone whatever metal but
not out of actual like soil
so it won't really look like Dragonstone
at all
Marjorie Tyrell yeah like her family's
home
but I wonder if there's like detailed
enough
um shots of that place to recreate it
but I will think a little bit about it
in any case we could even do a real one
that exists in Austria or Germany
hmm
castle in the snow
it's cool too I like snow
um
but I I will want to build it somewhere
close to a convenience store or close to
where the crater Crater where the crate
Loot Crate response
anyway
no no one will rock it my my castle down
no they were respect it
can I really do castles and rust and I I
will be creative I'll give it a try
maybe
any team you want to join
well preferably
you know pickled us team
yeah so to show my worth and my value
and show her
that I am on her side
um
[Music]
okay
that would be nice to make a bird-shaped
castle and have a full auditory group
[Music]
but Louie didn't play Rust at all right
until now and we may never
did Reina did
and what it it could probably just be uh
turducken we did oh
a lot of really she's addicted I must
have missed that
I think she only plays when I don't I
know I'm sleeping
um
that's nice okay
I know to be friends with fake another
enemies exactly
anyway let's continue tangenting too
much man
um
where was I
hear Siri
thanks for the sneeze chats
thank you soon
[Music]
foreign
hmm
nagato
no no no
toys
[Music]
um
neander
Seattle
oh yeah yeah yeah hey I get along well
with clearly so I'm guessing coyote
would join pakura's team if if I could
have were to be the leader of something
that's good
clearly strong clearly strong
did I say Senpai again I don't think I
did did I did I did I
did I
I did good
expressed interest in joining me
commento
and because if she does that then like
that team is too strong who's gonna be
the opposing Force
who you can't have all the strong people
in one team what no no that's so
unbalanced you no
foreign
[Music]
thank you guys thank you
nice nose
thank you wow
damn
thank you wow wow overwhelming
gazuntites
and adding a dog
that you think too much too much save
some for yourself
good job hundred thousand subscribers
and revenge perhaps you were the real
winner honestly
I might have been
I think I got so much out of that
episode
[Music]
and
no no really big like losses like
whenever I died it was not a big issue
not a big deal
ah
but they were so nice like giving me all
those scraps what the hell everybody was
too kind
it's not like I killed people to get
them they just gave them to me
now
much did it foreign
already finished because like
spending so much on gambling and giving
away so much
she must have it finished right
I hope so
not that she wastes so much on
other people
you don't care about tech only again but
well her home looked
pretty good
that is
Advanced as pecanized place but still
close to 10K on gambling you mean in in
the whole season or on one day oh please
don't stay on one day
she could have given all that to me
please don't say it on one day
no way
she no oh
my God
she kept on gambling it how much did she
have in the end
I'm
I mean in the end I guess you probably
just gave everything away because she
didn't need it because she didn't use it
for her texture
oh my God
crazy focuso
eventually it was full of scrap oh my
God
saw her she didn't leave that room at
all
she's so cute
every time she jumped towards the wheel
and she was yelling the numbers holy
[\h__\h] my heart it died from a moment
I did tell her let's call Nabu I did
tell her
oh yeah I was trying to start a
conversation about tunic at some point
but I I didn't know what exactly to talk
about
I mentioned that like the the ending of
the golden path was crazy and I was
going insane because of it
and generally it was a really good game
but besides that even though I loved the
game so much I couldn't think of like
anything to say about it into a fan girl
about weird
hmm
but I'm just happy that someone else
played the game
yeah
I should show her oh I wonder if she saw
the exploits of the certain bosses I
should show her the exploits that I
think she would find them very funny too
foreign
like in general in an open chat and a
few people reacted to it and were like
oh I will keep this one in mind
but they probably forgot about it
already
um the game is
that a big capital I or an l
thank you
X Vision 64. thank you happy belated
birthday
thank you
the stream was a lot of fun to watch
always fun to watch you having fun
looking forward to the rest of the week
too thanks
for the pinky I'm sad about the complete
set of your birthday merch but never got
the email to enter the raffle because
turns out the email server [\h__\h] up and
it got lost ask Jack was too late for me
to enter the raffle for the meaning
great hope in future I get my chance oh
if you're the one whose tweet I saw I
sent
a screenshot of it to my manager and
told them to handle it
and I was told they would uh
contact you
I think it was you unless there was
someone else with the same situation
I didn't didn't like react on Twitter
directly to you but I that was not you
well then uh
[Music]
well then
with someone else and let me do the same
thing for you
[Music]
fixes it I'm the fixer
foreign
[Music]
like just buy a space wonderful kfp I
wonder if they would like find it
uh
we were supposed to get an email for the
entry yeah if you bought the like uh the
right amount
um oh you know what like if there's more
people
um who have the same issue
um please you know what can we have kfp
in their Discord collect all the cases
oh yeah check your junk mail but if it's
really not there then can you guys like
collect it and then send it to me ASAP
so I can ASAP
let um management know so that they
contact you and please include like
maybe a screenshot of the purchase and
your email address or as well that would
be dope
and then I'll take care of it
but you gotta be fast I think
you're welcome I want you guys to get a
chance if you if you uh you know
eligible then you're supposed to get a
chance at it even if you don't make it
into the middle grade you're supposed to
get a fair chance so I I can't just look
at that happening and accept it no
um so be fast yeah because I don't know
when the results are supposed to get
come out so go go go go go go go please
please thank you everybody who has an
issue
go join the kfp Discord if you're not
already in there and then I don't know
do something do your magic and then send
me a list
okay you do the the
bureaucratic is that a word in English
work and I I do the rest
okay
foreign
introductory classes to skills ah that
one I already read that thing
yeah I said I wanted to do some classes
like that sounds like fun Christmas chat
and we'll still be here a lot just might
not be able to stay for the full stream
every day like I used to anymore I
promise I would never ever leave
carefully or forget about you Kiara I
know of course not I'll continue to
support you as much as I can until the
end of time
yeah I'm not worried about you I guess
I believe in you thank you for
everything
[Music]
yeah
okay soon sweet sweet unknown
thank you
the most radiant Phoenix store manager
thank you very much thank you to the
council group and other mythical
appearances I have a free life and have
many friends I will continue to support
you oh thank you
thank you I love your name thank you for
the red super chat that you shouldn't I
appreciate it very much
thanks mate
you should and last but not least
thank you guys
for the rest super chats and now we can
read OverWatch super Jazz let's go
[Music]
you like the Clickety Clacks and they're
nice
yeah let's get it started
in here
you little [\h__\h] and no no no I don't
know what you mean no no no no no no
she learned that from me wonder why is
saying none or how do I say it what is
that
[Music]
what what kind of sound is that supposed
to be when do I do that
[Music]
no no
I just kind of do it sometimes
[Music]
is there a clip of her Nana's
I don't know what you no no those are
pretty cute no no no no no no
Coco talked about Gucci gang what she
must have gotten the same video in her
feet as I did
what I'm talking about Gucci gang
she should cover that song Gucci gang
Gucci gang Gucci gang Gucci gang and
she's probably gonna make it sound so
good especially if she does an acoustic
with a guitar
it's gonna make it sound like like an
like a really emotional song a
meaningful song
like
[Music]
Gucci gang
I like that
how much
[Music]
boys
and question out of curiosity about
YouTubers if you could pick an avatar
that was an anime film that represented
you as a person what would it be
I mean it wasn't anime
I wouldn't
think I would choose
anything
an animal
honestly
I mean I saw some funny ones like for
example
um some some Japanese
uh
um artists and YouTubers I saw they were
using interesting avatars like for
example like a teacup or so
it knows I find interesting but
generally
[Music]
like cats just like a full-on animal as
a YouTuber Avatar
I find
no thank you
yeah like like sense is a teacup yeah
yeah I love that one
I love that one
but not really something I would choose
for myself no
question
and yeah
Brandon Myers
Daniel Valdez Jr
[Music]
oh yeah
thank you
[Music]
um
this was lots of fun by the way if you
go to Highlands you can see videos of
your own Islands from your games oh cool
I wonder if I have any highlights at all
Jim Tracy duncast
that was a great show to watch I hope
you will get to see more of FBS art yeah
well not too frequently but every now
and then it's fine yeah I had fun
it was really bad and it's fun I had fun
thank you for watching and being so
supportive of it
hmm
um
pinky FPS Pro in the making oh thank you
is it
am I really though
hopefully one day I can be helpful in a
team
thank you so much
play Fallout New Vegas Kiana
yo I don't know the differences in all
the fallouts I know there's several ones
I don't know the differences sorry
production
that's the end
that's the end of OverWatch super chats
thank you everybody
[Music]
it has Blackjack oh
oh interesting
very interesting
now we can read the Super Chat spam
today
are you ready for that
foreign
oh the first couple ones from the
wedding room might be about AOE
perhaps maybe
gutter
you Vegas is amazing not sure how good a
stream game it is oh
all fallouts have so much gmca music
yeah I heard that was the problem
um
[Music]
stream that I almost forgot I'll be
sitting on the plane on my way to
Sardinia right when your stream starts
oh
I'm jealous hope you have a lot of fun
build a strong Army and defeat those
enemies love yukimawa thank you very
much
oh I hope you have a lovely holiday
ah
Sardinia let me look that up I've I've
seen it before but
I need to visualize it
Italian island in the Mediterranean Sea
[Music]
oh it looks gorgeous oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] I'm coming to
[Music]
oh is it easy to reach
because I I know just you know when I
was trying to fly to like Greece islands
and I checked out all the flights to fly
to Greece
um like a lot of the nice islands that I
wanted to go to were hard to reach well
yeah
airplane
pretty hard to reach like long layovers
and [\h__\h] for some reason
very easier oh
have a nice
oh
wow
[Music]
I see
no
pinch bars it's been I was just like
[Music]
foreign
laughs
oh oh no
[Music]
I
um I know I know I know
you know you may think okay don't go
vacation because oh you're not gonna
stream and all that but but but once
again it has been proven in August When
I Was Gone on on a vacation I still
streamed more than everybody else in the
whole live English and also I saw my
total numbers
my total numbers in total
and I'm forehead
um everybody else in Hawaiians even
though I take so many vacations
this is not even my full power
this is not even my final form
so yeah
can't complain kfb I think
kind of more
let's take our love thank you
thank you
[Music]
I see how much I will um stream in
September where I'm not I don't
currently have a vacation planned let's
see let's see it's been a while since we
had a month where I didn't travel
let's see
I think I I want to be appreciated for
streaming so much for you guys
but I can stream even more I could I
could
but you know I'm always trying to
balance
um my sanity I'm trying not to go crazy
so even though I could stream more the
question is is it smart to stream
anymore
also not everyone not everyone is really
like
not everyone
how to say processes
and experiences
the act of streaming the same way
you know someone like coyote
can stream millions and millions of
times that would be
impossible for me too I need some
breathing time in between and some just
shutting off my brain time in between
however streaming itself is fun for me
and often a way for me to
also
you know
have fun and get away from things from
real life Escape
but yeah
um
yeah well
you know actually just today I I saw
because it was in my recommended
articles on my phone I saw an uh an
article about Paul Pokey main is that
how you say your name
uh about like streaming less
and it made me think yeah
like streaming
it was also written in an article but
like it's it's a very very very
competitive
um
business like
it's probably even more on Twitch in
terms of how long you're expected to
stream
and yeah to stay relevant and to get
them numbers of viewers and subscribers
or whatever
on the website where there's so many
[\h__\h] streamers
you just have to be always online I
guess
um but it was also crazy to see the
percentage of how many
twitch streamers actually make a living
out of it it was like below 0.0
what
[Laughter]
below 0.0 I'm making a living out of it
that means even there's an insane amount
of streamers on Twitch
or it's just really not
not a good source of income
but I wonder they probably don't count
sponsorships and and merchandise don't
do that I'm not sure if they count that
because from what I know a lot of
tourist streamers make a lot of money
from merchandise too right
they do
they probably don't
I wonder
yeah there's definitely an insane amount
of streamers though it's boom so much
and yeah burnout is easy like
because it does it does like pressure
you mentally so much if you're trying to
make it in that industry
yeah you put a lot of pressure on
yourself
you have to because it's really hard
to be relevant
and make a good amount of money from it
um
so
you know I might be streaming
comparably a lot but
to like the rest of Ian but
I think it's it's good to stream less
like it's it's definitely good for your
mental health and all that and to not be
burnt out
just because someone streams more than
others doesn't mean that they're a
better streamer
that's that's the thing
it's just
different ways of
different ways of doing it and there's
no right way of doing it
as a streamer it doesn't mean that you
have to stream a certain amount of
hours per day to be a good streamer
you know those those standards may have
been set somehow and now the
expectations are so high but in the end
like I get complaints that I stream too
much and people can't keep up I stream
quite a lot less compared to the average
twitch streamer right
how how would you even catch up with a
twitch streamer
how
so I think I if I stream any more than
this and you guys are gonna have
troubles catching up right
you're some of you already have troubles
catching up
if you have a job then you'll definitely
have troubles catching up a job or
school or whatever
I probably shouldn't do much more than
this even if I could I shouldn't
probably
hmm
because not saying you have to watch
everything but a lot of you guys seem to
want to watch everything
maybe that's fomo or too much love for
me
you don't have to watch everything
I don't want to stress you guys out by
streaming too much and then you can't
catch up and then you're like whoa
he was dreaming too much I can't keep up
hmm
I can only keep up because I can watch
you at work yeah hallelujah thank God
for these nice workplaces
which ones that aren't massive ones lose
a lot of Their audience if they take
breaks
I don't think that's only twitch
streamers
I think we're we in whole life just are
kind of Lucky it's not the best example
like even when someone in her life takes
a one month break or so and they come
back
they usually just go back to normal and
have a nice big welcome and go back to
normal
thankfully but I think in general it's
not just twitch it's also YouTube
or wherever not only streaming also if
you just don't upload the video for a
long time then the algorithm [\h__\h]
hates you
yeah that's a YouTube thing too
my Holo is a family yeah yeah yeah
thankfully
I would still be worried about
taking such a long break though
I feel like I'm on a on a constant
hustle and struggle
um
so that's some worries I have to but
I still give myself you know breathing
time to breathe and vacations and time
to recharge and all that
damn attention so much today
oh
yeah I guess on Twitch they they just
drop you much faster that's sad
but I think that's more of a thing with
real face
flesh tubers
I feel like V2 with fans in general once
they have an ushi even on Twitch I feel
like they they stay with them
no
well I don't really know I don't really
know but I assume
foreign
yes now YouTubers fans are more invested
aren't we having a nice talk today
aren't we
oh wonderful how lovely
cup of tea perhaps I do have tea with me
but
cold by now
let me continue reading super Chandos
thank you for two pinkies says aoe2 is a
big part of my flesh only years oh
and this new and exciting Journey for
the ages of Empires is a pheasant
surprise this adventure is why when
trying FPS RTS and even considering
Elder Scrolls game hands me at the edge
of my perch well Elder Scrolls was
always I would say kind of up my alley
oh
that wasn't so far off as a FPS or a
horror game I would say
Dragon Quest Dragon Age may be even Mass
Effect
hopefully but who knows don't live your
love for a lot of drinks and uh uh and
no one drinks a lot of drinks game would
be
apt
appropriate perhaps like Shadow of
Mordor Battle of male or two an owl Can
Dream right I don't know I
I I
feel like I mean I could be wrong tell
me if I'm wrong but I feel like
games from such big
book and movie series
usually are not very good
like you know
they're just good if you're like a big
Fanboy fan girl
then you enjoy it because it's that
universe but
the game itself is
um
mortar is good
uh-huh Shadow of Mordor is pretty great
uh-huh
those particular games are actually
pretty good
[Music]
what kind of game is shadow of motor let
me look it up
oh
optional adventure oh it looks like
Ellen ring
kind of
noise
like Alden ring
is there Golem in the game Circle
except way easier oh no that's so good
thing to know
oh there it used to be online gameplay
functions
does it have good lore
good Lord of the Rings lore
do you play a human looks like a human
to me
that's debatable not really I would say
so hmm
sets before the trilogy
Lord
it's at least interesting
alternate timeline oh
and what publisher is this
Warner Bros
so many publishers
one of those
if we get something
did we ever play something from one of
bros before I forgot our
stands towards one of Bros
I think I asked this before about hell
Harry Potter
happy rather
um
potty rather
you know played Lego Star Wars oh
beg for bless
keeping this in the back of my mind yeah
thank you for
letting me know about this game
yeah
2014 that game has been around for a
while
wow
guitar
[Music]
what better way to spend my birthday
than to kick back relax and watch my
Aussie oh birthday
can't believe it's been another year
already my life's gotten a lot busier
since then but throughout it all I can
always count on you to put a smile on my
face and make my day better love you
lots lots oh and I didn't forget what
you told me last year no donut for me
this time I got myself a cheesecake she
okay you choose cake I wouldn't really
normally choose as a birthday cake
but okay as long as you like it you know
it has to be a cake that you want that
you enjoy
was it good was it a good one
was it tasty
I hope it was yummy
happy happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday
happy birthday to you
a variety pack of cheesecakes nice
catching the most out of it thank you so
much for spending your time with me at
your birthday with me once again
I am honored and I appreciate it
celebrate celebrate
let people love you and hug you
and
yeah have a good one
thanks for being part of kfb once again
and happy birthday
no no energy drink no no
no
um
let's say that Ina falls into a deep
sleep to save her the rest of myth must
bring one of their cats to where Ina is
sleeping
well Kelly doesn't really have a cat
does she
I'm his
Buddies
I can stay with her for a day
oh yeah and I'm in the in the American
lands perhaps okay let's assume she's
she steals that cat
which of your cats can you trust to save
Ina and behave themselves
oof I don't know how my cats would
interact with other cats
um but yeah if anyone then it would be
smoothie
I think smoothie would be friendly this
movie is friendly to anyone
I don't know if she would be friendly to
one of the cats but
it would be her
yeah she's chill she's not scared of
anything like John Grace is still scared
of the vacuum cleaner whilst movie
doesn't give a [\h__\h]
so I have High Hopes in this movie
um
easy and her softness like Silk is gonna
heal inner
surely
[Music]
a virtual makeup dream yeah I don't know
if that would be possible somehow
sounds difficult
you know generally like makeup on anime
characters just looks kind of weird like
putting on like big lipstick it just
doesn't work so well um it works for
some specific art styles but with an art
style like mine
it doesn't quite work
it looks weird most of the time
um
yeah
but in theory I would like the idea if
it would work better on anime faces
and don't even have lips
barely have a nose to highlight and and
put Shadows on
[Music]
no resection
oh no no I know I know a lot of Japanese
members do membership wallpapers for
like ages but
I still think that the other em members
may have seen me post about it and then
we're like oh
could do that too oh that's it thank you
soon
thank you for the red super chat once
again touch is there ever a time when
you don't send a red superjet
is there any ever any other color
possible
maybe your YouTube is bugged maybe the
only possible color it gives you is red
thank you very much
[Music]
very very very generous
his favorite color
understandable it's a nice color
very very
I don't know how to describe it
only in Japanese koi
I think these are some flush chats thank
you guys soon
I can't say this Saturday morning is
gone how I originally thought it would
in a couple ways
what is that scrub thing mean but I am
delighted to experience kind of a lot
differently than last times thank you oh
sorry about the cancellation
Monday
several times thank you thank you soon
15 beat God thank you
oh a rocket launch got delayed and you
were like looking forward to that one oh
I see
it's been scrubbed
interesting choice of words
[Music]
I'm not usually the one who phones that
it's been a nothing approach as a fan of
classic horror action movies I've been
burned too hard by that already with all
the modern reboots oh
let's see oh well you do you I do me
the code thanks for the pinky are you
part Alphas because you sound naturally
perfect nice Victory anyway I'm going to
go back and pour it to the piano Shrine
carry on yes continue praying give me
your devotion more more more
thank you very much
very sweet of you thank you
[\h__\h] 70 thank you soon
oh yep I heard of that one too
if I am looking for another game I'll
consider this roguelikes I will I'm
Tracy dankerson Cruise Duncan
[Music]
even though we aren't a cult question
mark you are doing such a great job as a
cult leader yeah we will follow you
anywhere thank you please follow me
cute little chickens imprinted monkey
cute
a kiss for you
goodnight kiss
thank you so much for the support
oh
I am a chick
that was close
to
foreign
[Music]
and now I have to refresh
that's right that's what I had in my
mind
why does everyone who streams a lot
starts with the letter k
silly true it's just a coincidence
and there's other people who start with
Kate and maybe don't stream that much
and there's other people with other
letters who stream a lot so
ah
um
[Music]
I watch you since your debut I just want
to tell you even you take your time for
a break I will be there every time when
you come back oh
it's very nice to hear thank you
I'm counting on you
Skye thank you for the pinky attention
may I ask for a blessing from you but to
another kfp colleague Nina diesel she's
feeling unwell and is resting right now
but I still want to tell you she loves
you oh no did you get the sea thing
I hope not
please get well soon
I shall bless you shabby Bank
please recover fast
um
my mom recommends chicken soup
uh
I think you know where to get the
chicken from
bed rest
do I have to force you
go go go go
Andrew thanks for the pinky
oh thank you for the Emojis next time
use some words
[Music]
ah
um
dog Hood
thank you for the pinky
my mama's at the end of tails of the
rice bus I can finally go back and watch
it right stream about spoilers ow I'll
be interested to see if you're ceiling
broke at these end game Shion
Revelations Alvin reminds of can you be
so devoted just want to let you know
boss no comment this serious if there's
so much at a rest thanks for working so
hard
thank you that's very sweet
oh I wish I wish I wish they would
release a new tense of game every year
but then the quality would probably be
pretty bad so
we have to give them time
yeah
what there's something I wanted to watch
tonight good I'm so I'm so
on time
something I wanted to watch on midnight
at midnight
Southern shock yeah just remembered I
was gonna forget about it
I said I'm getting done relatively early
today holy [\h__\h] the stream is only five
and a half hours long because that was
just such a good gamer today
this is the thing guys
if you want me to stream longer then you
should not want me to improve at games
because the better I get the less I will
take for games the less time I will take
yeah
we need to find a good balance and maybe
that's what I've been doing all along on
purpose
[\h__\h] gamer but actually I'm just a
really good Entertainer yeah also
because I personally think it's Charming
to see people suck at games for once
yeah then you can also feel better about
yourself because you guys love love
feeling better than me at games right
don't you
he always feel Superior when you watch
me play games
that gives you confidence doesn't it
yeah yeah there's many reasons why I
usually suck at games today I just
couldn't hold back all my power was
revealed my true power
uh
I love seeing you get better
don't think you're bad what
you're good at playing as normal
struggle once in a while playing thank
you
[Music]
doesn't mean you can beat elephant ring
if I wanted to
no that that [\h__\h] is tough get that out
of my face
continue improving makes me happy thank
you no one is good at first
yeah
you're sporadically good at games
you know very entertaining people being
bad is fun as long as they aren't just
stretching on the game yeah yeah
yeah refreshing
and Lang wants you to struggle to
success like
like very rewarding not only as the
player but also as the viewer
hmm
about Mario 64 shut up
there's certain games that no matter how
hard I try I just don't get better at
and then there's other games that even
though they're very difficult I do nail
them often enough
it's interesting it's just you know
strengths and weaknesses to everybody I
guess
oh
surely try another Mario game at some
point oh and and and and
the other Ori game
I did see the other day that uh now I
have perms so
previously for some reason I didn't but
now it seems like I do
so we can play the other horror game
um
but wow that will be another big
struggle
I wonder if it's even more difficult
than the first one
that was why it was really amazing to
watch you play Elder ring because you
perserved and improved also my Dexter is
really bad
I'm watching Buddha being only slightly
better than me at DMC it was cool
uh-huh
over two is easier oh thank God a lot of
you guys seem to have that opinion
oh thank God
um
foreign
don't worry
one is pure escaping
oh
or two is more aggressive or what
um
[Music]
ha
not the cute little monkeys
they have a lot of run sequences yeah
that was so stressful oh God I still
remember that part
and like where the water and the wood is
which pretty much could be any place but
then you know the Big Owl ow was it an
owl yeah
it was like in the background and um I
just I don't know if you guys know what
part I'm thinking of but I died so many
times oh [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
so painful oh my God we certain thoughts
are easier than others but I remember a
certain parts relatively in the
beginning of the Escape
was like especially difficult
ah ah
yeah
but I did get better at it yeah
or he's like Dark Souls yeah like side
scrolling
uh whatever the genre is
Dark Souls
unnecessarily stressful like they were
specifically crafted to make the player
anxious in an otherwise still game
um
oh I know about little witch no better I
had my eyes on that like for years now
I downloaded the demo like what feels
like four years ago three years ago
I know about that game
I'm sure we wouldn't have problems with
perms because there's whole Live members
voicing characters
yeah
anyway uh
c-a-s-d-a-s-d-a-s-f-a-s how do I say
your name
yeah I know I know
because you know you could disconnect
from Russ seconds before anyone asked if
you would want to hang out I know and I
did write to Anya afterwards
I was like Abby I'm so sorry I didn't
know if if you would have asked me
before I logged out I would have joined
you guys
and she answered me and she was like oh
no problem at all don't worry
yeah I offered to play in the next
season together
feel bad about it what the [\h__\h] that's
such a insanely bad timing
oh man
and Bixby thank you soon
yeah I'm sure Emma knows about it Mrs
Duncan Martin ain't dungeon for the
pinky hi ninja I hope you get to play
AOE too eventually you're not sure if
this would work but what about a game
stream similar to the anime watch along
like one hour different games to see if
you like him and want to continue oh
I I don't really like mixing different
games in one stream
uh I'm thinking like of the Vault
viewers and like people who don't know
me but look for specifically certain
look for game Planes of certain games
and then you know I I feel like for
those people it would like scare them
off if it was a stream that has a mix of
stream games
I I just like it to be more organized
and separated like that it feels cleaner
um
if I was like maybe streaming on Twitch
at some point then
I think that's kind of what they do
there so that would be fine but on
YouTube yeah I know Army does it but on
YouTube I mean I just don't really
feel
the idea I also
kind of
like first of all there's certain games
or like
games are like developed Publishers who
don't want their games to be mixed in
one stream and
and even if they would allow it
I I don't know there's some kind of like
I don't know
if there's a weird stance I have that I
don't know how to explain
hmm
editable chapters yeah
too much effort
consider it to the viewer yeah but also
consider to the to the game creators you
know I
this is kind of weird but I know that
for example artists
um
some of them don't like to have
their art
mixed in like the same showcase or like
for example the same tweet
as another artist or the same thumbnail
as another like have two different
artists art displayed in one thumbnail
whatever
um also I noticed about photographers
and so on too because like they don't
want to be compared or whatever or for
whatever reason like they may have some
weird reasons but I want to respect it
and now I wonder if like maybe game
create game Publishers and all that
um they maybe don't like that either
maybe there's some out there that don't
like it whatever I'm probably thinking
too much into it but in general like
that reason and then other reasons make
me not really want to do it I just like
it having I just like having it be more
organized
um yeah I don't know maybe one day I'll
try something like that
I mean in a 12 hour marathon stream
obviously I'm gonna mix games you know
definitely the only real time where I
would do that
try out different games
yeah yeah yeah you know what in the
marathon we're gonna do that anyway
and now I'm thinking more and more maybe
I should do a 12 hour marathon on my
birthday on my anniversary
[Music]
laughs
maybe I should maybe I should maybe I
should you don't have to assert
dominance
as the the long streamer
maybe I will
can it be on a weekend
well my my anniversary is on a Monday I
think but
uh I could do it on Sunday anyway to
like spread it out as well
to
hopefully spread it out like the
anniversary is the solo streams
could do it an hour early it could be a
marathon up to
midnight
where my anniversary would be or like it
could even go past that but that could
be the goal Marathon towards the
anniversary
that would make sense
maybe I will do that I'm kind of in the
mood for a marathon you know
laughs
I'm kind of in the mood
well
oh
[Music]
endure endorscho
thank you
hell yeah
F why would it be the 18 no I mean the
11th yeah because I think my anniversary
is on the 12th
Ian record I don't know
I don't know what it is
we can't break it though
anyway let's finish this [\h__\h]
and one last refresh
ing
commercial
[Music]
oh you know what iron beating would
actually be
good to include
but then I would have to set it up
but I feel like it would be a chill
chill filler
oh well
for the pinky and get reports from the
mind but I'm fine I'm doing my best to
have this money to send to you and keep
supporting you no
and now back to the
homo P.S your model now remembers Mr
Kitty after dark front art
what
was that mean
no no one understands
Google
it's an album
ah it's a song
I don't know what you're trying to tell
me
what are you trying to tell me
I'll come out with you
foreign
you saying I look like that
I don't really agree but okay
let's see
well anyway
ah
I hope work is not too exhausting vital
in any case
take a good break in between okay take
care of yourself
thank you for coming by to support don't
hurt yourself while you're working hmm
thank you thank you
thank you
oh thank you
[Music]
I'm done thank everybody
now I shall go
and you guys take care of the thing okay
with the meet and greet you know
foreign
[Music]
if anyone didn't get an email check your
junk
oh folder
if anyone didn't get it then fast do it
within today like compile something
either if you're not in the Discord then
just send me like some info on Twitter
and I'll try to send it over to the
people in charge okay
let's see check your junk folder your
emails
yeah
okay
unbelievable
I just saw something that I thought was
not funny okay so energy when we say
happy death day not gonna go now have a
nice evening everybody
foreign
fun fun fun fun fun fun with kiwawa
every day
Fun With Flags
thank you guys wanna come up with me
see you guys tomorrow
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]