e
don't
[Music]
keep
around
[Music]
me
come
[Music]
me
you
[Music]
could
I
[Music]
you
told me I'm
[Music]
momy M my m m my m
M I feel so hot let me get ice cubes
[Music]
know
so fire that I burnt
up needed ice cubes
here oh Ice Cube
ASMR K
KY it's kind of
nice wow that sounds like some fancy
instrument isn't that
nice yeah I just
um ch Ed down some soup of some
bread like
yeah literally 5 minutes before the
stream until now
so that's why I feel a bit
[Music]
hot not not soup with
ice no no
[Music]
no I got up a little bit early today and
for that sake I tried to sleep early
last night and it worked but then I was
still so tired so I took a nap a nice
nap after watching a million episodes of
Breaking Bad breaking my
bed breaking my bed while watching
Breaking
bed uh yeah I had a little
meeting early
today good meeting
about my next 3D live that got
delayed but we're like figuring
out I figured out a new theme for a
different
season yeah if you remember it's going
to be in Winter and everything was
Winter themed but now now it's got to be
different
themed yeah I think it will be
nice
anyway m
what what the [\h__\h] C on
them
[Music]
may well well well
well I'm still keeping like all the
songs and all the members pretty much
the same so really just talking about
concept but yeah there's a new DLC for
Age of Empires Chronicles battle for
Greece
o
oh
oh and there's something
called the Doomsday Heist for GTA my my
steam is telling me
stuff is this what is
this an in-game event the [\h__\h] is this
GT H GTA online I see to this day I
haven't played GTA online
bruh can you believe it me the GTA
finisher of all
times mhm
mhm with GTA we went to New York and we
went to LA from one Coast to
another yeah
I do want to play though GTA online ear
when you played H I was listening to
your streams
as oh [\h__\h] oh
no that is a scary thought I shall
consider this for the future when I raid
um people but I felt like I had no
choice I'm sorry I've been
pressured I've been pressured I'm sorry
oh Diablo 4 DLC is on sale right now how
much it was so expensive so sale is Big
Tas the cat on
sale but I have to install it if I were
to buy it now to get the cat now I'd
have to install it then that's going to
take a while
the 25% it was like 60 bucks
right vow what
this okay okay okay okay
Diablo do they say anything here about
the hello not
loading ah 25% off the new expansion
purchase now how long is this is this
going to be I'm going to purchase it
another time
perhaps yeah everybody's talking about
picota getting nominated which is great
but remember the rules guys don't bring
up unrelated topics
uh you deleted all the rules oh well you
should have remembered them by now and
also it should be common courtesy
you say they're not you know the rules
though you know the rules and so do
I had had to force me to Rick Roll you
because you pretend that you don't know
why you
know a commitment to the rules is what
I'm thinking of you wouldn't write this
comment to any other
YouTuber I just wan
to tell you
how you understand I'm no I'm I'm not
like that strict about it
but you
know tell me when I'm nominated you know
but I guess that
means are
out right and WWA is not nominated
that's okay that's chill but are only
I'm curious who else is nominated see
now you're forcing me to talk about
it now I want to talk about it sounds
yeah it's because I'm tabing out and in
and out
[Music]
chill I'm cutting I'm cutting I'm
cutting out
mios
M you're nominated for the most hats on
a single vtuber head
award oh the game awards ah not the V
Awards the game
awards
ah I thought I already saw the
nominations for
that this is
new was your audio being okay
don't be bothered by such
simple my dear chickens life is not
worth it life is not worth
being
all worried about such
frivolous
[Music]
things but that's cool okay that's cool
that's
cool the [\h__\h] game awards
wait [\h__\h] that's cool they're going to
mention her name and during the game is
that the show from the guy the guy the
guy who's always in seeing
it well now you got me [\h__\h]
hooked I don't I don't remember his name
jof
kayy wait let me look up
his oopsie Jo of
Kay oh oh yeah him oh [\h__\h] they're going
to mention p in that show now okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay wait was
there wait for best content
[Music]
creator with four other flash V2 uh
flash
tubers iron Mouse won last year ooh ooh
that's what I was was about to ask like
uh other YouTubers who got nominated in
the game awards before but yeah I think
I remember iron
[Music]
Mouse that's interesting because um Iron
Mouse is like you know English speaking
for most of the time I suppose p is
jeopardy speaking though
so
strong strong
Awards
[Music]
exciting hey but I thought I the game
awards but I thought I already voted for
it no no I didn't I only
nominated some people for YouTube Awards
I think yeah yeah
yeah the thing is for game awards like
95% of the names of
things except no maybe not so much for
the games like 95% of the people they
bring up I don't
know but games okay I would probably
know a few of the games that they bring
up in the nominations but mostly I don't
know what they're talking about about I
think
oh same really look at me I'm so
cool blending in can you guys see my
character is mi2 camouflage can you see
she's in the middle generally the game
is centered on the character so you can
um try to focus on the Middle with your
little lowquality chicken eyes and try
to see she's right right here in the
middle in the very middle of the Open
Your Eyes Open Your Eyes focus focus
focus that's a really good
camouflage what please change the colors
of your outfit K I really cannot see
where your character is follow the dog
just look at the dog same thing
basically
like I'm not white I am eggshell colored
okay if
anything uh yeah I guess we're going to
go straight into it and go to this place
whatever that was today I shall be
immersed hopefully and uh emotional and
empathetic and remember how to ride my
pet
that
nice and there's a cat so I don't need
it I need I don't need the other cat all
is good
do I remember how to play last time it
was really hard for me to
stop wait what was that D it's
gone proceeds to laugh at a widow no no
to today I shall connect
emotionally with in this game
Uber this is
dark who
mysterious oh look at those speed
dos or Bay Monastery this dude is he
following me get away get out of
here sorry was that not epithetic of me
I'm sorry
no I got a little bit confused there she
just wanted to escape but she bks it to
a jar a wooden jar what do you call a
wooden jar t t
t egg sack
e barrel
barrel
barrel but don't you like the descript
wooden jar this place has been taken it
reeks of forbidden
spells please norath how bizarre it is
to hear from you your Charming
Apprentice arrived just this morning
with disturbing news but he made no
mention of you what am I to assume you
did not send him please join us at orb
as soon as you are in
H uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh um I I I feel
very affected by this
notice I'm back home
W
to the path
of wait an empathetic person will
probably not destroy the shelves and the
the books
um but the Hornets yeah get them out of
here oh tiny baby Hornets cute oops
sorry accident wait have we not been
here before did we go back in time again
a little
bit I don't know this looks
familiar but we did spawn with these
camouflage cloves that I set at the end
is anyone here it's very empathetic of
me to ask if anybody's here because we
don't want to hurt anybody
accidentally with our sick moves and our
fire Mur Mur in the
Mur so he was saying
murder lock the
doors what about the
others where are they they sound so
close I need to talk to
them wa wow um well I guess these are
donations to the God here but um I am
just I'm just I'm going to collect them
for now for
safety and then I will deliver them to
the god afterwards if that's
okay is it too quiet by the way I can
turn it up oh another tithe BS sorry I
mistakenly took them because I thought I
was playing Eden Eternal I have many
good good
excuses can you tell oh this is a door a
mechanically sealed
door little Qui audio
[Music]
good muchos SC
money here a little bit
0.5%
louder oh what is money in uh Spanish
tell me ah didn't
chill chill oh my
God oh my God many people is
dead what happened oh Crusader skull I
have to retrieve it place the Crusader
Skool in the pedestal hey yo what up
there okay but let me check out
everything else
though there's so many dead
bodies ooh let the bodies hit the
floor I think I'm thinking of a Jennifer
Lopez
song
yeah very empathetic of me to think of
that song while I'm looking at dead
bodies right
right oh
see he who shall look around
everybody every every Everybody yeah
shall be rewarded for their
patients over there
maybe we should leave them in I don't
know that was kind of
scary okay you can come out cuz I'm I'm
pathetic it sounds like I'm saying I'm
pathetic so excited when I walked into
the sacy that day finally sorry I was
reading enter the and explore for I was
trying to read now I'd give anything to
forget
for okay down to
business oh okay oh oh who are
you I think people told me before I
ended last time that this wasn't even
going to be so
long we'll see it looks pretty big so
far punished for imp prophetic reading
can't believe it
what why did all these doors open
suddenly oh to give me money thank
you appreciate it wait what is this
button on the floor oh no I thought if
you stand on it something
happens mhm
okay other
side how are you guys doing today
h have you done your homework whatever
that
is it's a
Monday yeah Mondays Mondays are not very
nice I know from
School times that I was not looking
forward to Mondays nowadays it doesn't
really matter but you
know talking to my guild about playing
on the new New World of Warcraft classic
servers new wait are they starting from
zero
again that would be cool
honestly classic
classic on the 21st man I'm busy on the
21st
[Music]
no properly classic more than the old
how how is it more classic than the old
servers okay let's go in the
middle what are they not going to add
any expansions they got add uh blood
elves
though that's classic for me
still I think blood elves are excused
that was the you know golden to me it
was the golden
hour
of world of Ro CFT no expansions at all
vanilla I mean okay cool I feel like
that's um a good idea after so many
years ew ew
ew don't play on release day you're
going to have 50 other players killing
all the start area Wes and Boards yeah
but that's fun because that feels like
you're back to Classic times when it was
like actually like the real deal when
people were actually still playing the
game in like in in the beginning areas
isn't that a great feeling to have like
it's alive again you've traveled back in
time how many years 20 years I don't
know 20 20 years maybe too
much after three hours it stops being
fun being fun no no not for
me not for
me although I feel like
for for
streams like streaming mm RPGs makes me
feel pressured like I need to hurry the
[\h__\h]
up so that I'm not losing everybody's
attention but if I played privately I
feel like you know would be so
chill let sa save save her every
moment protect the
AR I didn't even let let him finish a
sentence I'm such a
[\h__\h] your free chat skill is
op I
try it can be op I have my days where I
have nothing to say and then I feel
super nervous when I
stream 20 years old is it really 20
years old they also re-release Warcraft
10 and2 not a huge
re-release no point going to water War
for classic just to grind to Maxum
stream what are you talking about why
what do you mean there's no
point oh because if you mean only if I
wow if I do it on stream then there's no
point
a random scattered prism nice
nice forcing yourself saving
it maybe one
stream but yeah they kind
of planned it on a day where i'm not
available but reconnecting
Hello is my internet okay it says
reconnecting to Diablo 4 my internet has
been a little bit weird today today and
yesterday at
times see it says up here reconnecting
to
Diablo but okay as long as my stream
is
online retail World of Warcraft that's
what you call it the current version
commissioned during the time of troubles
the or archive once served to codify
heresis for the
Inquisition since then the archive has
expanded to the study of all evils
restricted to only the most devout
Scholars of
Zach
you why did you let him in
have a problem with it oh there's a
second part already critics rightly fear
the dangers of our scholarship but
ignorance of evil offers little
protection from it our insights have
proven invaluable to paladins aradim and
Angels alike in the fight against the
darkness was seems you have lost the
fight of Darkness too bad to evening to
evening I shall keep it
safe and
then are you okay are you okay sorry are
you wounded where is the Abbot the Abbot
happy birthday toilla open the door and
the pale devil smil he took the
Forbidden Knowledge sh it's all right
I have a name okay can you walk there is
no way out what knowledge remains must
never leave un to evening I shall keep
it safe and into the night Hereafter
he's a bit insane you must protect the
arive okay you what bro why did he just
suddenly
die he was alive a moment
ago bro
was that really worth it staying here
for just one little chat with
me should have escaped although it
doesn't look like it could
have poor bro I feel for him must suck
to die and not be able to revive like
me yeah did the ghost kill him
ow sorry my my gameplay might still be a
little bit
chaotic I get a little bit more
organized for
sure anroy bolk Bren or whatever his
name was interesting
name did you see my schedule guys guys
tomorrow I'm
playing
uh oh level up I'm playing the game were
you
clean I've never played that game before
actually I still don't own it need to
buy it
still is that on
steam power wash simulator
yeah yeah I've been invited
I I I couldn't believe my eyes when I
got invited to a
collab I was like
what is this
real so even though I don't no like
normally on my own I don't think I would
have ever picked up that
game but for collap sure okay at least
it's not an FPS game or something
but even for that I would probably force
myself maybe maybe maybe depends on who
asks it's mandatory homeowner
training chilling yapping game yeah I
don't think I'll do my own POV because
from what I've seen from this game
like there's not such exciting things
happening in the game that I you need
several povs right
that's what I
thought good job dragons or
[Music]
Hydra oh hey I don't even notice these
guys
spawning went under attack
Jey will be there no matter what thank
you yeah I think shiy might be the only
one streaming it on the
day a point of Yap yeah I will make many
points of Y
hopefully um let's see we have one
available point we could put it into my
Inferno fill it up sure let's do it
let's do
it yeah and then on Wednesday we have
the go collab and then I thought you
know I still kind of want to play Holo
cure before I
leave so I squeezed Holo cure in as
well two streams on that day so even
though I'm taking four days off you're
still getting four streams in that no w
almost no WWA weak
damn damn
kfp getting
spoiled proper days off not days off no
for real I'm I'm not even going to be
home
so I I'll be uploading YouTube shorts
though dance
shorts working on the remaining ones K
and
po yeah and then maybe some extra ones
who knows but for those I don't know
we're going to take our time through the
day I've prepared to accept this burden
of knowledge yes knowledge is really a
burden
sometimes but sometimes it's also a
relief you
know unto evening I shall keep it safe
and into the night herea it seems like
their model unto the evening I keep it
safe what happens in the evening bro you
who would seek to know Darkness kneel
before the light speak the words of the
litany and accept our holy burden
H
okay interesting wa now it wants me to
look at the statues again oh
yeah I already looked at
them okay
oops H the first one I
missed holy
bird you're just saying that because I
pronounced it weirdly huh from morning
my eyes were opened and I saw the coming
Darkness laas is visiting me what I'm
surprised I didn't think she was going
to visit
me
La you're welcome to visit me though
from morning my eyes were opened and I
saw the coming Darkness through the day
I have prepared to accept the burden of
knowledge unto evening I shall keep it
safe and into the night hereafter
oh oh magic words they
worked wow I didn't even have to think
about it it just happened on its
own Abbott's quarters wow
oh okay are we fighting in
here Abbott wake up we need to leave now
no I deserve to burn with the rest of it
where is
Elias gone
he said the ruin of sanctuary was
imminent
and only I could help he going to summon
a lesser evil lesser evil he took all he
needed and
then why do they call it lesser
evil he murdered them lesser than what
oh
sh
oh oh how oh my God what the [\h__\h] idolon
oh it's dark idolon of
orbe idolon make me think of one of my
anime mm RPGs they were called
idolon think that or
Kingdom I need just days
I'm so hardcore fighting while sneezing
man that must suck when you're like I
don't know in [\h__\h] Lord of the Rings
or something in the middle of the
battlefield fighting the Orcs And you
just get a sneeze attack because maybe
you got hay fever or something crazy
like
that man oh I'm I'm inside
no ah yeah
bit yooo
ity phase yeah ity face no not
now I do not possess an itchy phase now
human knowledge shall be shared among
the children of
Lilith and no secret shall be kept from
them and the liars and learned things of
the world liar Liars perish in their
regret oh my God I solved the puzzle he
he's a
liar liar liar pants on
fire it
Liars Idol transits to a phantom of
sorts in Greek oo not
all okay we are we leaving the the
dungeon wait is map not
M how do I open the
map the
tab doesn't work though
[Music]
weird uh wait can I not is this again I
can't leave the freaking dungeon
normally
why there wasn't even a proper reason
last time that
happened all right the emote wheel thank
you how do I open the emote wheel again
uh
oopsie ah did I re rebind
it um there it
[Music]
is I
can't can't open the map normally either
what's going on is it is something
bugging
out I guess I live here
now I could probably Town portal but do
I want
to guess I want
to but what if someone's waiting for me
outside no no the map I didn't change
the
map okay I needed to come here anyway
fine but still
weird l oh you're up
there
Hi
um diot and scholors were murdered by
Elias
Elias what did he take Scrolls from the
fidden archive he has the means to
summon a lesser evil what do they call
it that what is that the name of which
bloody one a weird name where oh we
don't know of course Elias could cover
the STS blood but Alessa could Wipe Out
the continent or Worse come Elias's Pat
demon is inside pray it leads us to him
mhm I'm it still says I'm reconnecting
to Diablo that's so weird let's begin in
there I feel like I'm going to eat some
human heart in there
game of thron's reference by the way it
was protecting that fool
genma oh my God this is Elias's
work but where is he that's crazy the
answer lies in the
stomach what the [\h__\h] e whatever those
beans can we make chil Con car with
those
beans a soft Noble's hand
Elias would have to feed this thing
sound of fancy boots that's someone's
son or daughter we should burn demons
this is
wrong I guess La of isn't much of an
empath either the crest of the ruler the
Royal House of Gan former ruler
obviously that's enough old man the dead
deserve respect the Deads deserve
nothing when the living are in danger oh
[\h__\h] now Goran has a new ruler and we
have Elias to thank for
it the dead may be worthless to you but
that Medallion could bring peace to
those two
morning fine if we are to find Elias
then we must also travel to
gulan meet me there and be swift about
it
Swift okay I'll be Taylor Swift about it
oh and avoid the city Gates too many
cannibals m go to the cliffs we'll find
help
there cannibals at the city Gates I
still can't open the map bro it's it
even says here tab H maybe we need to
restart the game or something or let me
reconnect my keyboard but Escape
works and space works and wsd works
[Music]
oh wait does this have something to do
with it with it having like a
reconnecting issue I can't click on
controls that's certainly
weird
uh is this saving my progress though if
I restart the
game I would hope so
I'll restart the
game
okay
P doesn't sa when offline oh [\h__\h] that's
what I
found no
no
but let's
see if you're offline and D4 you can't
play the game what the
[\h__\h] you know offline you're either
online or it puts you but it was saying
can't connect to the game okay I'm going
in
Surprise uh this is concerning
uh wait how do I open
my wasn't I level 32 no wait no no wait
we're fine
maybe map is opening at least how do I
open my
skill
thing I he five out of five okay that's
to me the sign that it did save okay
okay okay okay okay my eyes can only
watch so
much oxen tribe Forge
Master what do you need are you
the no you're not
need to look at the items that I've
gathered
oh plus seven might be worth
it 22
intelligence oh I should put a slot on
that how
annoying uh what this heart heartless
Antiquity
week there should be a button to like uh
get rid of everything that's weaker than
what I'm
wearing 22 intelligence pain
Loop wantas
um whoa Prodigy soulat
hoop um using a cool down restores 15
Mana sorcerer only this one's
interesting cuz it's orange
too worth good upgrade but it doesn't
have
[Music]
intelligence what do you think
and this might be interesting
and my rings both have Intelligence on
them this effect is pretty nice early on
you can just re an AIC so to
intelligence at oh okay we can try that
The Prodigy aspect wait what is The
Prodigy aspect
what you mean the using a cool down is
that called The Prodigy
aspect let's go to the
occultist no
mean you in here let's try this out we
haven't done it
before uhuh wait wait is that even it uh
imprint aspect craft Salvage enchant I
guess it's
imprinting wait how does this
work what's the Codex of
power do I need another item that has
like Intelligence on it
enchant ah
okay item to replace aex
[Music]
of doesn't matter which one I choose
like could only the first be replaced
with intelligence
or
so get rid of Max
life okay wow
177,000 I
18,000 re the life until see
intelligence oh okay
gotcha
uh it big
ah I can choose from
here it became wor not not really worse
but sorry sorry sorry and then I choose
one and then I do it
again it becomes more
expensive 7%
damage oh I became 50K
No
70k 2 for intelligence POG POG
POG yeah
baby
nice cool you will be back the stars do
not lie I will be back we'll see about
it it might turn out a lie girl
okay okay and I want
[Music]
to
uh first of all I need a slot on this
and this but I guess I can get rid of
this
ring good Salvage good Salvage uh who
does the slots again the jewel person
maybe do you do that no be wary of
Bandits who does that again I thought
the the Bonk Bonk guy did
that you can also upgrade your potions
oh that was a quest
right fight hard ehy I just walked past
him Devil's pay oh this person Jeweler
there we go
[Music]
um add
sockets oh ah is it because it's orange
it needs extra stuff all right I guess
we won't get it cuz or can I make
this A Shard used to improve jewelry
with an item power greater than 350 at
the blacksmith clo Jeweler collected
from salvaging legendary
ooh and Mythic jewelry with an item
power upgrad
the blacksmith
BOS do I have anything in my chest
[Music]
perhaps no these are not
orange I didn't think about that the
Betrayed by orange but maybe it's still
worth even without the for example this
one we could switch this one
out and okay
but I can still add another socer to
this
one
easily okay and then where did I do the
other thing again
um
switch
yeah okay
oh know this doesn't have a place
anymore just put it in
there
okay are you able to improve gems like
if you take free flaw gems you can make
a Flawless gem uh don't ask me such
complicated questions I probably can
uh like here yeah right I don't know I I
oh wait this wasn't here before these
weren't here
before these are new aren't they I feel
like they're
new you have gem dust that you can craft
into
gems uh
wait no got to break down smaller and
then craft bigger
one you can craft higher quality gems
depending on how many gem fragments you
have you can craft higher gems the
higher level you are
mm yeah but are are these these are new
right should I craft these
material cross Diamond fragment cost to
craft
10K only the small ones yeah sure I'll
break
them these are just
fragments in here I have the
intelligence ones uh intellig
topas no I can't make the big nice
topas I can make a chipped
one but that's only plus 10 so that's
not that's not even
better we should craft the higher level
gems
[Music]
upgrade my
weapons with tempering you
mean select a rare legendary item or
recipe okay let's I don't
know for example if I put
my um
uh this in
here I can add utility or defensive but
even if I hover over it it doesn't tell
me anything
so
oh uh
interesting does this give me all of
these free
things but I'm still like switching
armor so often that I'm not sure if it's
even worth
it one of them do I choose or is it
random I'm guessing it's
random lucky H I don't know about
utility maybe
[Music]
defensive random
okay let's we can try this
temper item this will bind into your
account okay but it can't break
right oh wow fancy
oo 4% Dodge chance okay I like Dodge
chance let's try another one
plus 12 maximum life
okay let's try the helmet
too
M it's not that worth it when you what I
thought but oh well
plus 8% total armor
ooh okay that's enough for
now you'll see the amount of tempering
charges on the bottom
right okay oh couldn't you see the
resources it takes because I'm on top of
it let me make myself
smaller maybe a little
bit where are we going now now oh he
wants me to go all the way over here
swiftly he
said we shall make a
way
[Music]
yippee plus eight sounds kind of plus
eight oh I want to fight
them hug hug
hug take down sword hug instead
that one's kind of on fire and still
doing stuff what's going
on fish
folio and a
ring
oo can I flip these bodies
no okay
this way
yeah oh are are are are these the
cannibals bastards
pass what where did he mean there were
cannibals what is he talking about
maybe all of these dudes are cannibals
too iron
wand no prophecy oh
dear skeletons skeletons
cell pick up your skeletons they're
scared oh there's a person there why are
you fighting
this this is so weird I I don't know
like there's people playing but only a
couple and I'm
like like
he is this one of you
guys I don't understand the like how
online Works in this
game it's basically an MMO but not
really like I imagine there's more
people playing but they kind of like
are on different
servers even though you can't choose the
server like automatically it's separated
or
something I don't know yeah in it's
instance that's what I mean
yeah he's running away
you don't need to help me is that an ice
Mage she had like ice attacks so I'm I
suppose she
is but do we have the same like for
example if I open a treasure chest it's
still
hopefully a closed treasure chest for
them right
ice
Mage ooh a
staff plus
six 47
intelligence pretty good but you
know they take away all ability to grief
randos in their modern games
oh another person wow I actually seeing
people out in the
wild
crazy but I guess it would be really
hard to stream snipe if it's instance
have you guys been trying that secretly
and I just haven't seen you guys yet
tell me the truth chicken tell me the
truth are you trying to find me in this
game ah
yeah Shakes
You Shakes You harshly tell me the truth
chicken tell
me what the
[\h__\h] don't lie to me don't lie to
me what is this place I'm getting
distracted
oh I'm so distracted oh
no better go
away by the way I'm in season 3 now I'm
I'm going to try not to talk too much
about it today because I don't want to
spoil people who are in the middle of
watching it but I'm at season 3 now for
Breaking Bad and don't worry I'm still
going to watch arcane
but it's
like you
know I don't know I can't watch both
shows at once
so I'm going to wait it's ni there
anyway to wait until all the episodes
are out for Arcane cuz it seems like the
Cliffhangers are very
[Music]
harsh yes yes breaking bed very cool
I've reached the part where
uh without spoiling let me try not to
spoil um reach the part
where Jesse is making some money on his
own
uh yeah poor
Jessie with the voicemail thing was feel
felt bad for him but besides that
besides the whole voicemail thing the
past episodes like it in terms of
like
suffocating pain while watching it it's
gotten a little bit more
chill like there's no crazy Tuco [\h__\h] or
so going on kind but it feels a little
bit more chill there's always something
going on of course but it feels a bit
more chill
for a few episodes a little bit more
humorous thanks for the
raid thank
you yeah he's trying really hard to fix
his family
situation um
but I must say
I he's trying really
hard and then that's nice but that that
won't
like that won't change how how badly he
[\h__\h] up and not much time has passed
since in E so I understand that uh she's
still not really willing
to you know
cooperate I feel like you can't expect
her after finding all of that out
M
no that's
shocking will poow has been increased by
two for all characters oh that's what
these altars do and
are what increased forever I need to
find more of them that's
crazy h
M Pandora's Box has been open you mean
I'm breaking bad
yeah
yeah it's nice that he's still resisting
but judging by the fact that there's
five seasons and I'm in the third one
I'm guessing he's going to go back to it
again to
cooking surely he's going to go back to
it he resisting for quite a long time
though
impressive let's going on here oh
there's a little dungeon I wonder if
it's as long as the previous
[Music]
one let me see can't believe you called
me Heisenberg you were quite ruthless
not going to
[Laughter]
lie kind of Ruthless will you join L
collab in the future I don't know right
now I don't care about
it looks very different this time oh it
looks
small yeah different but small
good and quick very
fast big reward y
oh wait forgot the
ring even though I don't care about blue
things oh could wear those right
now
nice except for blue girls yeah if you
think B it kble
[Music]
good
respawn Crow
fetish I
mean I mean maybe I have a little bit of
a crow fetish so I shall pick it
up
M I don't know who you're thinking of
there or crony
but accurate in both
cases all of
them me and blue woman yeah
it seems like they're following me
wherever I
go they want me so
bad
n hope you don't mind me walking over
there cuz there's always so
much to check out on the
[Music]
way so much
loot no stone be left unturned hey yo
there's a person there crying or what
never
mind yeah I'm not much of an empath I
attacked an enemy that was crying over
another enemy I've never seen that
before that's that's pretty cute
[Music]
sweet blue is a complimentary color I
saw this like thing today on Twitter I
guess it's another meme or something
people trying to change Hol members into
their complimentary color
people tried to change narissa into
orange
but it didn't it didn't have as much of
an impact as seeing like gigy and blue
or
so she's just like mostly
monochrome there wasn't much orange on
her
there's another little dungeon should I
go there
too yes I
should maybe it's also tiny tiny tiny
baby dungeon who knows
wait he dropped some like oh it's just
it's it's his backpack okay
o I'm a fist
fragments thank you for the raid let's
go in Buried Halls please be
small or like mid midsize that other one
felt huge maybe there's like a middle
siiz dungeon too oh that looks
big huh I wonder if there's like side
quests that make you go into these
places and I'm kind of
wasting all this
potential for side quests by not taking
them let me know if that's the
case oh my God mother's
chosen what's going on here Mommy cult
is it Lilith
or there
are not all of them okay
H hey I wish they would tell me I should
accept the side
quest
mommy this looks like it might be part
of a side quest D unlock
aspect added into your code AS of power
it depends on the icon next to the
dungeon logo okay this one had a little
icon that looks like I don't know it
looked like a
box this place is
crazy these like golden statues I'm sure
those ones were humans they didn't
sculpt
these I think those are just painted
dead human sacrif
devices don't you
agree oh no I pulled
more okay we're good we're good we're
chilling
stupid
Shaman
okay
spooky oh why did I waste my ulti on you
I don't know I don't
know what the [\h__\h] man on the left side
you see that
that thing is
huge armor
rack but that's not Lilith what is that
but wait that looks with those horns
that looks like the that looks like the
the thing that we opened
up and pulled out the
beans just still mommy it doesn't look
very Mommy to me it looks more like
Daddy Mommy sorry
Mommy blasted anyway I started
blasting sick design though cie would
like this oh wo
I'm surprised cie doesn't play Diablo
actually although I feel like I talked
about it with her before and she seemed
interested seems like something up her
alley just because of the Aesthetics
not enough
raging do you think she only likes to
play rage games I guess dark souls and
stuff is also kind of a rage game if you
fail a lot that
is CI K's pretty good at it now
you dropped so
much not enough of a challenge then she
got to play hard
mode maybe then it's more of a challenge
but I don't
know t wait that's evil
T oh
did he just summon this Fallen
overseer what's
that scary does it help me or does it
fight my
ass level
32 second one oh no
why have I freed it die die die die
die what
this this hole reminds me of the hole in
Game of Thrones where they uh killed
people you periodically periodically Dam
Dage nearby enemies okay okay then I got
to zoom zoom zoom hello enemies where
are
you
ow need more enemies oh yeah The
Veil The Veil
okay I think it's
over oh there's another one of these
Soul shots why would I free it if it's
[Music]
evil did I go back
door the power distracted
me I don't know if it's worth it looks
like it needs a key
oh yeah okay not able to open this
now can I accidentally fall into these
holes kind of want to test it
out no invisible wall once
again the
Savior people always hate invisible
walls but
they're on our side they're trying to
protect us from things we shouldn't be
seeing maybe we need invisible walls IRL
as
well minion that's not how I remember
minions looked
like w proof
holes ow ow ow ow
ow oh my God there's a lot going on
here what the
heck okay
cleared this part that looked like more
Troublesome than it actually
[Music]
was free the
prisoners h
all right oh this
one My
Savior Goblin below
you Goblin below
me
what there's goblins in here
to the right and Below wait why would I
care about
goblins it already ran away oh was it
the money Goblin
thingy My Savior I forgot about
those
no it ran
away no way my Saia my Saia
bless a door has been
unsealed it's optional as well
always H I didn't oh there it is who
that it's gone K
kill where is it where is it there
no no no no no no stay with me Goblin
CH come on come
on
[\h__\h] come
on come
on
damn he had so much
HP Focus make one war sword loot loot
loot loot oh inventory full oh
[Music]
no guess I'll
teleport
BRB at least you got an orange mhm your
left doesn't do a lot of damage you
should you should use your other skills
instead I've been trying to
mix my skill is UN Ted you'll
see all right sorry little moment of
your time to look at things
[Music]
slowly
whatever plenty worth
keeping fist Gambit
no I like the names of the items order
Peak fiend Gage what comes up with these
names ramble
Armament Doom
rigging magers
progeny vagrant
rff Soul okay this one's normal this
one's pretty
normal I'm a get them
Signet uh mental
symbol Agony
cords V vajra of biting
cold legendary Focus what what is
this what's it's is is this one of those
things I hold on my second second
hand this a
sorcerer should I keep
this not for my build I guess so like
the freeze thing is yeah not for me but
can't I even change that I can change
like everything but okay let's
Salvage I get some cool stuff for
salvaging that anyway a baleful fragment
yippee
rip work rip
work good Salvage good Salvage
indeed rip work
yay no no no chickens not rip work you
have to keep on working sorry this was
not towards
you your work is not rip at all
oh no your work is never finished the
end is never the end is never the
end got to go here
[Music]
this travel to spectral
Awakening
spicy
ooh mommy and daddy is that
you resurrected malice let's
go no my snack can't get it ooh hits
hard
I hear my bones
[Applause]
breaking
o all is okay
he's hitting hard but he's going to
die get
him dungeon
complete you have unlocked rapid
aspect yeah colx of power press
Y what what is that
really where do it go here basic skills
gain 15% what I just did that thanks to
clearing that
dungeon waa 15% is like a lot nice
reward worth
it these are all the things I've
collected so
far summons a bubble with immune you
gain 44 armor but your vade has 100%
increased oh yeah what the
heck I can get more of
these so it if I get like all 21 of
these they go up to 35% or
what oh these are things I put on my
items
[Music]
oh
oh so it's not automatically activated
now just by clearing the dungeon
n can I leave this dungeon
or
not leave yay
and
works how are you tonight thank you I am
good I am
fine I'm looking forward to a week full
of excitement and fun and rest I told my
manager on my days
off um
ideally even if you're just sending them
for me to look at it after my little
trip don't send it at all because my
problem is I'm not going to be able to
resist looking at
Discord so better to not send me
anything cuz I'll be very tempted to
reply uh and maybe solve
whatever I'm being told to do so just
don't send me anything and she's like oh
okay we'll do or will not
do and I told her just so that
she um you know
still like not forget about what she was
you know keeping for me until I'm back I
told her to just make a channel in my
Discord in my like task Discord make a
channel that uh I can't see and she just
posts everything there until until I'm
back and then she invites me to the
channel when I'm back and I suddenly see
all the tasks that were posted while I
was gone in one go genius right she was
like oh yeah that sounds good I'll do
that that way you can still go through
your usual
workflow cuz I feel like if I were in
her situation I had to keep all these
things to myself until later I might
forget about some things but this way
she can just post them as per
usual and I I see it all in one goal
when I'm back which might be shocking
but I don't think I don't think the
couple days um it shouldn't be too much
shouldn't be too
crazy big brain yeah showing my manager
side again
okay I'll try to hurry
now let's hurry a little
bit me professional I
try sturdy pants ow hopefully they're
more sturdy than this shitty
fence that I just knocked
over with my two powerful
[Music]
Paws there's a waypoint there
I think I'm going to go get
it what is that place over
there oh a whole Camp is
here and way point stay still do I have
to get
off
yay
yo feel like I must have missed
something here too or it's like more up
here Lura hello I was going to try to
come up here from the other side I guess
it's all G connected I can't believe it
Lura I know you said Swift I I I I I
totally went here straight away with no
dist actions
whatsoever I'm here now that's all that
matters oh he's sharpening his knife K
to
come pity you didn't bring an army your
siege
Works did you elas is here gone to the
Palace no doubt behind the high wall
with the gates barred behind him we
can't get
through that's how my NE and when
Zia how many messages did I send huh how
long has o Yun been missing trapped in
there with those
butchers she may be the only one left
who knows of the tunnel that place looks
cool if she's still alive if this tunnel
exists at
all you don't trust me of course not
you're a thief useful years ago true but
it's clear you have some other reason to
seek this a
you not your business why is she giving
me vi Vibes if I were to look for aun
where would I
start she has a house in the Market
Square we were supposed to meet there
before but I couldn't get close by from
Arcane tried to come back alive
not convinced this old is worth the
risk
what did I just get teleported I clicked
on
H did he teleport
me I clicked on this
here I went did yeah but did I get
teleported I wasn't listening uh I
wasn't start I wasn't done listening to
him
either what the
heck I was going to look at
this oh well I'll do it later my potions
are still fine they can keep up with my
suffering
they Mak me so
[Music]
slow it's he PE you but why did it do
that shouldn't it ask me if I want to
oh my God
woohoo I love it when it gets chaotic
like
that CH chest
[Music]
CH ah everybody's giving me slow buff
here I hate it
okay nice I found the dead
end how about over
here Chad I have nothing to talk about
what should I talk about
I could tangent even more about breaking
bed
but it never stops Breaking Bad tangents
never stop they're
unending talk about
narissa not sure what to talk about
therea and REO too
oh yeah I guess it was announced that
it's in Spring 2025 but spring is kind
of vague and
Broad I'm curious as well what they have
to offer next time last time was already
so intricate I think they're going to
try even harder to make it even more
interesting
does narissa
snore no but she's she likes to sleep
talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking just tiny little
nonsensical
words few of them here and there
scattered across the
night by the way she she never sent me
that picture on
Halloween remember I asked her for a
picture of her costume on that
evening she never sent me one
but she's getting
kitten I'm so excited Loki want to visit
her just to see the the
kitten while let a
kitten but I don't
know I don't know going to America just
for a
kitten but I'm so excited I always tell
people to get get a cat I've been
telling my mom forever too but she's
like worried that you know when she's
taking care of my cats who's going to
take care of the other
cat
true true but
still everybody benefits from a cat or
any pet at
all I will for never stand by this
sentiment even a pet rock U maybe if
your name is bi boo most of the pages
are smeared with blood the legible
entries speak of the cannibals
overrunning the city on the last page
Yun has written she's not coming I pray
that means she made it
out o
the lady we talk to no the lady weal to
is looking for ooun filled of an
assortment of knickknacks a simple
dagger a few coins and a lock of dark
hair Bound by a blue
ribbon it what does that
mean what what what what are what are
you doing with those
knickknacks
oh no no don't let them get
me I shall rescue you
yipp have you seen someone named
o i I don't know the cannibals are
rounding everyone up F that's so
terrifying if a group of
cannibals the prisons I heard invades
your city why would these monsters keep
anyone alive see I'm so empathetic I
really find it
terrifying the idea of that happening
[Music]
the thought that you're not just going
to get killed only but you're also going
to get eaten by the people who kill you
is
[Music]
just is this Assassin's Creed
now I never played that game but it's
giving me that Vibe now
oh I have to go there
[\h__\h]
H so this upper level wasn't really that
special after all I have a skill point
let's put it somewhere
there want to put it into here maybe
firewall strengthening my firewall so
that I don't get
hacked all righty ooh
sorry burn burn burn baby burn burn and
turning these birds into
phoenixes and putting them through the
Phoenix trial and see if they re survive
but nope they fail one after another the
Phoenix trial is not something for weak
Minds
help oh no you
too where'd she go she
disappeared they
fail feel like my inventory is going to
be full again very
soon h
just Diablo
things okay I'm actually not going to
stress out about uncovering the whole
map after
all not
anymore feel like it's not so necessary
in this game I'm only finding small
knick-knacks after
all okay I have a I have a talking
topic do you guys Envy me for the power
I wield over cute
girls because the other
day cute cos blare
jean11 you know the girl we talked about
before she's asking me if she does a
bunny suit cosplay of
me what
what uh socks and stuff and what what
color should the
the bunny suit be in the first place so
I dm'd her to send her picture and stuff
I took care of it don't
worry
but I am so
delighted all these cute
girls in my GR
fast I'm so
powerful I've become too powerful I
scare myself
sometimes it's terrifying to have so
much power because what we learn in
Arcane stands through too much
power is dangerous because if it goes
into the wrong hand one could do evil
with it but don't worry I will only do
good I will only do good
I'll
try I won't be corrupted by my
power yeah all the cute
cosplayers
my my fried chicken brings all the
cosplayers to my
yard nah that doesn't sound
good
my
my my Oreo shake brings all
the girl I guess it could just be
girls oh thank you for the members
message you
lurker should I go up here
no the other
way I haven't had an Oreo shake in a
while now I'm craving one God damn it
that's the one
thing i' I've already I'm kind of over
after like so many years of my life what
is this I'm kind of
over my favorite
burger from Burger King but the Oreo
Shake still still kind of has
me I can't I'm not going to order a Oreo
shake just for getting an Oreo shake and
I would have to order something else
too what are these sounds
man
oh
Punisher he you should be an Outlast get
back to outlast
you know you want that Oreo shake yes
yes I should try to make one myself I'm
sure there's like YouTube tutorials on
how to make Oreo shake
yourself step one buy
Oreos step two make milkshake well
actually not milkshake it's like a
iced
thing maybe like a
frappe is an or Oreo shake a milkshake
it's not really a milkshake it's more
ice more ice than
that is this repeating am I in a
loop you were in that same cell and I
already killed you
before
food freeze Oreos blend with milk hey y'
you already presenting me with a recipe
you seem like you know what you're
doing freeze the Oreos really I wonder
if that's a
step well we're going to have a cooking
stream uh once all of the V things are
revealed and once I have the things in
my hands could take a while I don't
know
but
yeah I bought a new microphone just for
that I mean it's not like the craziest
overpowered microphone but I think it it
might sound better actually yeah I have
to figure out something else too for the
gy stream I need to figure out
um how to use my
wireless microphone again I haven't used
it in a while I generally don't like to
use it because the wireless microphone
if I use that then I don't have I'm not
going to have audio feedback in my ears
and I'm so used to it to have that it's
like weird not to have
it feels uncomfortable but I'm going to
I'm going to suffer through it because
it will sound better probably if I don't
have to constantly stay close to my
microphone here
remember that one cooking stream when
you were using the wrong mic the whole
time I don't really remember it but I'm
sure that happened and I hate myself for
it oh yeah was it the laptop
microphone the like buil in microphone
that's [\h__\h]
up I can't eat
anymore but they won't stop feeding us
fruit and honey Oh I thought they would
bread and wine that sounds good I try to
resist but they force it down my throat
wait are you saying everything hurt the
cannibals were feeding you that stuff
I'm surprised they weren't feeding you
meat but I guess they wanted you to be
the meat that they would eat and for
that they fed you like some
stuff yeah that will make you taste
better your
flesh yeah fattening them
well I mean honey and stuff other other
prisoners would dream to have that kind
of food in their
bellies complaining
much sorry I was supposed to be the
empath why don't they
open what the [\h__\h] it is this bugged
it doesn't say it's locked it's
shouldn't this open
up rusted shut okay ail Jailer of the
weak it seems like you you must jail
yourself cuz you are the weakest prison
key can I now open this
too oh
yeah so it was locked what the heck
oh my God forgotten
Ward wait it
continues can I
peek you can destroy the wall it didn't
look destroyable but I'll check in a
moment
again oh
hello hey
they they get stronger from eating
us our
flesh isn't it
wonderful
sure you seem like you're into this no
no I I'm not ready yet I can eat more
get fatter I'll taste better right
please let let me eat more yeah I mean
that's probably the same excuses that I
would do that I would bring
up I'm I'm not fat enough let me gain
some more fat phoenixes taste better
when they're like double the size that I
am now trust me trust
me another one you guys don't want to
run out and free yourself off came a
finger out came an eye packed up nice in
the butcher's pie
great
song up came a finger out came a ey
packed up nice in the butcher
pie I'll make my next single with those
lyrics thanks man for the
inspiration oh
wait there's surely some
secret how to break
is there some some lever I have to
pull how to
open pull the onion
lever
huh might be the exit okay maybe when I
come back
are you are you
here yeah maybe on the way
back or there's something in this
[Music]
room well hello there
o you're not him who Are You The
Chopping it stopped and I thought I
thought he was coming for me
next well maybe I'm coming for
you for blood still
here you'll see her soon we need to get
through the
market I know another way it's safer the
old prison wing it was sealed off years
ago after an
earthquake
M over there yeah yeah where did the
cannibals come the wall ahead that used
to be now we can break it yeah your
memory wasn't wrong but it was a little
bit confused but you had the
spirit I'm eating chocolate
num an old damp Ledger tucked between
the pages is a folded note most of it is
illegible but you can make out a few
words earthquake damaged out of walls F
away the section leave the dead
inside thanks for nothing
cannibals now you don't want to eat us
anymore
huh be safe this
way we'll get through stay
close wait are these
also
victims that just went a little bit
crazy
feels like
[Music]
it it's empathetic of me to kill them so
that they can finally be free from the
suffering
right m
M yes I am so
merciful I'm an
angel such
Grace such
mindfulness such demure
step out of there my
friend it's
dangerous and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming and o
atin oh I just sled something up
oopsy sorry about
that was just checking if it still
works it does indeed
work I have wings you're an angel I have
wings do I know somehow I have yet to
show any kind of sign of real wings to
you guys I'm doubting it too I'm
starting to doubt it I've been I've been
gas lit Enough by my
belt I've been just I don't know I lost
sight of who I
am starting to believe I might just be a
chicken
depressing break the
seal Set Me
Free oh I wanted to shoot her oopsie
[Music]
this break bre
baby
time I
[Music]
don't I can't I don't know the lerts
anymore what the
heck I break
free even though it's one of my favorite
songs a crack in the wall a kraken in
the wall stand back no why did you enter
the Kraken
enough yeah it's what
de oh we're out we made it I can't stop
my hands from shaking nice give me a
moment okay I'll give you a
moment okay how about
now why didn't you escape
eh you wanted to be eaten at my home
when I realized she wasn't coming I I
tried to run but those monsters caught
me do we trust
her I don't know man kind of
sus H she had her own big spacious
cell SS Royal Blood just kidding ruled
guran for
Generations decadent and cruel but they
were Saints compared to Bro
[Music]
H what do you know about
Elias I I saw him at the Royal Court he
walked in
unannounced demanded the city to be
given to him crazy man the overseers
sent him to the prisons of course they
laughed about the strange man all
night that was the last time they
laughed oh
[\h__\h] are you ready yes where is
she good question follow me
[Music]
of the mountain
below it's safe now nothing will get you
up
here she's really
[Music]
here you've come back to me you waited
kept yourself in danger oh you stubborn
cow of course I waited where would I go
without you to tell
me anywhere away from here horse is mad
for some
reason maybe it's thought those [\h__\h]
humans are talking about me and their
human language talking [\h__\h] about me
thinking I won't notice I heard the word
cow help the pal I'm a Horan there's an
old Escape tunnel the entrance is in the
caverns
nearby behind an Al Cove marked with the
overseers
cross twin Sabers joined at the hilt
press the left P to open the way the
left pomel
cin could be
worse
Wanderer thank you Wanderer take care of
yourself could it be Lor all along see
the great
wonderer bye-bye horsey I think that was
the Merchant's horse best not tell
him well seemed like the horse was eager
to
leave
yippee L what's up now you know when we
first met I assumed this connection you
have with Lilith would lead you to
Darkness as it has Elias well it it has
almost bir after the good you've done
here it was a close call maybe I was
wrong we shall
see I am kind of feeling
this hand These Arms dragging me into
the to the evil
side it's hard to resist but I can do it
I can do it speak to Lor at the entrance
of the awful
pits
okay if evil why so hot because Phoenix
simple
explanation while you are in this City I
was thinking on Elias's
plans which of the Lesser evils he means
to
suon what he did to go round is a
clue he has drowned It in Blood what
does it mean is likely durial or UND
those are the less or evils you call
them that what's the difference
interesting duriel feeds off physical
pain and darel Revels in mental and
emotional thre andariel also existed in
Diablo 2 right succeeds many more cities
will share G does it make me laugh I
don't know the only hope is he hasn't
completed the summoning yet it sounds
funny to me from a German speaking
person
perspective cuz it's like their name the
Lesser EV I don't
know oh you the tunnel is in a hidden Al
Cove evil Lords of hell is that also
what one would call them
IRL uh what what is that what they call
them IRL to or is it is it a I I know I
know the choosing lesser evil that's
also what I've been thinking of I know
it's a I don't know if I would call it a
proverb but a common
saying the princess of hell it's a
Diablo okay
oops sorry Lura nice
Dodge I've explored a cave like this
before
the E and Diablo used to be one dragon
and seven of them broke off after their
war with God three main ones are misto
and his brothers and then they have four
lesser
ones and and which one of that is Lili
or does she not count in
those does she not count is she not one
of the seven cuz she was born after
that Prime Evil Diablo fist b o
b b I don't think I've heard of in the
game yet in the other in Diablo 2 as
well but probably just because I haven't
finished either of
those you fight him in the D2
expansion what does he look
like is he hot if yes then why evil
level up it's a spider crab spider body
white
head
sassy oh speak friend
saers just as o you oh yeah looks like a
pirate
base is that
actually this is I just realized now
it's making me feel like I'm in I'm
playing Boulder's Gate cuz the
POV the fact that I can in theory click
to
move this is like B skate I'm not going
to go there Lura if you can't tell me
what to
do okay maybe you can tell me what to
do yeah the graphics are the graphics
feel similar too the style Oh e drub why
do we stay here need more prey more me
and you will have it once Elias has
finished his Grand work br's the guy she
said is like really [\h__\h] up you will
see soon bro the seeds we have sown will
bear fruit ghon will be reborn can't be
more [\h__\h] up oh but work hey you
should be a drug dealer poised to summon
darel into the world her her power will
lift us to new heights and of course you
you will have more
meat meat I want to
watch certainly great brao you will be
the guest of
honor
honor uh what was I
saying oh yeah can't be more powerful
than uh what we fought last
time that is the Lesser evil he means to
Su Heavens help
us this looks quite quite pretty
though wow so much
treasure woo inventory
full
oo treasure
woohoo that is what you are woohoo I
have a
DM
oh oh
cute go team
DM okay what do we have first of all all
this goes away
[Music]
Bye by
by
bye
[Music]
bye bye Bo ooh we've reached the 100
armor but look at that I need to salvage
that that looks like it might be
interesting as a look
cute
no that got most of
it I get so much stuff that I don't
need Sinister
tradition could good Salvage good
Salvage good day
sir you are really into bers gate at the
time was fun yeah I
was I don't know it feels
like like my brakes were pulled you know
if I was a
car my brakes were
pulled that's okay but I am think like
I'm I might go back to it one day maybe
sometime in 2025 I could go back to it
if I have nothing else to play I might
actually want to I could I could be open
to
it Roman Saran oh hell no what are you
saying do you know who you're talking
to I'm not
Nissa you know I would uh romance I mean
remember remember how my playthrough
went back then what direction I was
going
to oh I was seemingly Romancing if
anything although I don't really care
about the whole romance aspect it's kind
of making me
cringe I feel like I don't know it's
unnecessary in a game like that but
okay like I don't care for it
it's not a dating
game and and it's all programmed and
they're NPC they're robots like all
these scenes they could happen with any
other player so they're they don't
really love
me they don't really love me even if
they like even if we spend the night at
the camp fire getting all hot and
sweaty it's not real
it's not real I know it they can't
Gaslight
me I know the
truth jungle forn of
efficiency casting a basic skill reduces
the Mana cost of your next core or
Mastery skill by
42% I wish I could just watch them have
their own romances yeah that sounds fine
too good
ring I
guess we'll look at it again later and
discuss our options
might want to give it some
intelligence I don't know when in
doubted give intelligence mother's
chosen wait a second the mother people
are back
again mommy
complex at its worst
M Mo hello
[Music]
guys you lik Romans and fire emblems
literally the only thing you were
excited about in
engage
engage that's maybe just because there
wasn't much to engage in in
engage maybe I that the only Reas the
fact the reason why I only got excited
about that is because there wasn't my
chance to be excited about oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] also romance and cute anime girls
is a maybe a little bit more tempting to
me
than whoever you can romance and Bowers
G even though you know Shadow heart is
hot okay
I'll give you that she's hot like
especially the cosplayers I've seen of
Shadow heart they're
[Laughter]
hot but then I'd Raab a Rance the
cosplayer me going out the cosplayers
again hey what's up Mother's
judgment low up let's [\h__\h] go
ow they never Dro Mana pots how selfish
of
them one last hug for mother judgment
judgment real women are scared
though oh I'm a real
woman I guess I'm scary
too I guess that that statement doesn't
change
anything a gruesome collection of
partially eaten corpses scrap apps of
fine clothing suggest that these may be
the remains of the royal family oh
no never be royals
Royals kind of Life aim for
us
rer I want a stream cut okay
anding for
kfp that is the way it's got to
be look at all
this an archive of the Forbidden and
picked by Elias himself what a nice
mirror planing to someone under mirror
mirror on the wall search here look
around who is the hottest of them all
sorry what were you
saying there might some clues that can
tell us where the ritual will take place
okay maybe the mirror will tell me
mirror mirror on the wall where will the
ritual take place no okay it's not
responding at
all it's ignoring me it's got me on mute
sketches of the free shrines each
depicting one of the Prime evils Diablo
Bal and
misto uh below the drawings and leas has
written only the Blessed can open the
way blessed be the fruit blessed be the
fruit the prophecy is unfolding before
my eyes I was right to act on it when
the prime evils come they will find no
easy prey we will be
ready our rebirth begins here with
andariel chained to the heart of
gulan she will feed on the suffering in
this city of Anguish and and we in turn
will feed on
her and darel's power will be ours to
wield against the other Lords of
hell if more Must Die to see it come to
pass so be it I will not fail you
mother
mommy Chronicles of the Eternal comp
some of these Toms are thousands of
years old
mag is that so search Grim search Diablo
Bale and
Mesto what were you looking for Elias at
the center of the map is the Temple of
the primes an ancient complex buried
beneath Mount
sio uh notes are scrolled across the
paper they appear to be calculations for
how much of goram's populace would be
needed to excavate the temple
here is what I found andariel chain to
the heart of
Gan her evil will not stay contained
here oh no it will drown the land in
suffering too bad this is beyond
Madness quite the opposite Elias's mind
is clear for once when I knew him he was
searching for purpose I couldn't give
him one and so he found it in Lilith I
didn't stop him I let him
become this
now is our chance to make it right
before things get even
worse yes we have what we need the
summoning will take place at the Temple
of the primes in Mount sio now to find a
way out knowing Elias he would have had
an Escape Route in case things didn't go
his
way okay behind the
bookcase I guess that's the one thing he
learned from me this one
you're so
slow oh drop the
book hidden Overlook let's
[Music]
go
oh where the hell are
we
oh should have killed him when I had the
chance well we all have regrets
holy [\h__\h]
aoni all these dead
bodies I feel so depressed by it
up sudden spawn how far is
it decently
far let's get on my
bicycle my bicycle that meows it's kind
of
weird way point I see
it thank you it's like you can see the
future you're so ready to tell me
that
Yi
uh do you sell
noow sending hearts to me
thank
you such a kind
kfp my sweet
chickens I love my sweet
chickens my chickens are the
best don't worry I would never I would
never stick you guys all in one building
like the guy and breaking
bed no no no that is not how you treat a
boil
foils are to be treated with respect and
love and
care and then eaten because then they
taste better if you treat them with
respect love and care
what oops I may have just accidentally
revealed some of my
secret
strategies what is our next step please
change the topic Paradise the Triune has
reclaimed its Ancient Temple trouble is
we can't simply walk in Elias was
researching something about shr can't
eat any more fruits and honey no you
will you will blessed can open the
way yes but to be blessed by the prime
evils damn
risky if it is the key to getting inside
the temple I will take the
risk ow that was my f Shrine is close
we'll start there
okay
oo look at that chest locked what how to
open this is there a key
[Music]
somewhere looks like a good
chance C something good in
it might be worth key from OB
balls
balls oh need to bite them in
town maybe I'll make a quick
visit special Merchant who selles the
key have have to buy a whispering key
from a purveyor of
curiosity AKA opal vendor in kilad any
major city that has an obal vendor that
sells them for 10 obals a piece what's
an obal do I have
obal
so would catar do have
one you get obal for doing events oh I
think I don't wait no events events wait
I might have
BS maybe I
do has one okay I don't know I just
randomly feel like clearing this whole
area but it's probably not worth it
let's go k
came with my
Xbox I don't have an Xbox unless the
Xbox came with the Xbox that I don't
have
uh maybe purveyor of Curiosities is that
what you
said
purveyor wait is this you
what was I what did I come here for a
key a
key I have 176
oballs Whispering
key
a ibye thank
you oh is this oh is this
[Music]
gcha it's
gcha but it won't be anything Orange
right maybe yellow at
most [\h__\h] I want to do the G
can't be orange or
better oh pretty good pretty good pretty
good oh oh oh that was
[Music]
expensive best ones to get our boots
pants and tunic they can't Blues yellow
rares and uniques you can even get
Mythic items but very rare oh
[\h__\h]
damn
no good Salvage good Salvage
I don't know I'm too lazy to like redo
the whole socket thing although this one
already has two sockets but I have to
I'd have to give it the plus 8% armor
again not worth for
now not worth my
time I wonder if these like plus free
improvements like if it's just plus
three plus four so if that's even worth
it
stream lagging every now and then what
like
[Music]
buffering ice shards
oh wait my other necklace also is not
really for me with chain lightning I
don't use chain lightning do I how sad
for arm currently is not worth it your
over 900 armor close to 1,000 armor cap
and you're only playing normal SW it's
fine as is okay good then I don't need
to stress myself out about like just
small improvements I'll wait for bigger
improvements hard hey okay back on track
I got the
key right
should in my
inventory did it go into my
secondary over
here I went here oh yeah and I still
have potions I should use
them I'll take that
one wait did I drink
it no there you go
good morning it's not morning now what
are you talking about did you just wake
up ah almost forgot about you what only
blue things bruh I expected at least one
yellow
thing oh wait Lord of Destruction
his influence has launched every war in
history never once has he tired
of two speak his true name toor BOS toor
BOS toor BOS BOS you said it so
English are you all right I'm dead bro
I'm I'm fine no I'm fine I'm good two
more shrines to go Diablo this is kind
of funny
though I'm like I fall all down burning
he's like are you good and I get up as
if nothing happened I'm
fine you can't tell me that wasn't
[Music]
entertaining but yeah let's go find
El it happen twice more let's go
ooh look at him
sheesh altar of Terror
Diablo Lord of teror looks like a monkey
gorilla mortal fear every nightmare
Diablo a gorilla
always has been speak his true name he's
always been a gorilla okay Al diabos Al
diabos Al
diabos again AL
diabos are you good girl
hello oh I'm fine at least they don't
have the dialogue anymore the dialogue
is what makes it a little bit
redonkulous
he's a big scary monster man he looks
like a gorilla in
armor pick it up
they inter this
game why do they call it okay you want
some whole life
lore because she has a really strong
grip I guess I think that's the main
reason
once upon a time when kanatan and Koko
Senai lived
together they had you know a living
Arrangement and I think she did a stream
Where She uh did the the grip
thingy and yeah she had like really
strong grip I don't know if there's
anything else that led to her being
called that h
yeah they used to be
roommates so
titty nowadays there's no
more like whole alive roommates are
there I feel like it would be fun but
for me it's obviously difficult cuz I'm
in
Austria oh wait but I don't think they
count
cuz they're related but yeah I guess
so Meo that's
meist father of Lilith huh you need to
be careful her blood is already a part
of you I can handle it I can handle it
see the power here is already agitating
you no I'm chilling what do you mean I
told you I can handle it tell me what to
say and then go search for the temple
you are so angry no what I'm just noral
speak the name do
meos but watch
yourself you watch
yourself do
mistos
oo
oh uh Lor where'd you go the [\h__\h] you're
not coming with
me yeah yeah Area 15 yeah those girls
also live together a
everybody is so far apart
nowadays we meet again do we met before
oh [\h__\h] I don't remember
misto I know who you are
now yes but that doesn't mean we can't
help each
other huh that mortal Elias seeks to use
the power this supposed to beo talking
for his own
ends no one knows their place anymore
how do
they his meddling has drawn Echoes of
the past to my refuge of
hatred but you and I can put things back
in
order once you've brought peace to this
realm I will be able to give you my
blessing
um d destroy the Barbarian defenses and
slay gorm in
here hold them
back
okay yeah he's got a good voice there's
a lot of good
voices in this
game too bad
that that one incident with the voice
acting happened
with the Laughing cries the forces of
Hell approach oh we can see they can do
better you know most of their wor acting
is good
so we we shouldn't judge them too
harshly by one
incident we will never fall to the Prime
Evil gor found
you but you're so weak
no so
disappointing hey
doggle now he's called meist oh yeah I
remember though we talked to him like in
the middle of the snow as
well I remember that
now well done oh like there was a portal
there too born for
this I didn't expect a Prime Evil would
need IM mortal's
help yes I've had some bad luck in
recent
years trapped in those Soul Stone
tricks cast back to
hell my Essence is
reforming and so my power has
limits we all have our ups and downs
don't
we you deserve far worse
all I have done is offer you help and
yet you repay me with
hatred why not focus that anger on Lis
for the time
being take my
blessing destroy
her save your
world I'm
confused the way turn
who were those barbarians the victims of
my brother Bale he laid waste to the
Barbarian lands long before your time I
wish I could have seen it with my own
eyes father of the year yeah I had no
part in it though Elias has upset the
balance at the Temple of the
primes and those shades of the past
belong in b Bale's domain not
mine but I do welcome their
hatred Dia 2
reference so what he was telling me to
kill his daughter Lilith are they not
very bonded I suppose I'm confused I'm
I'm
actually or or is she just saying that
because I
know they hate each
other
real
uh going
to why they not reacting to me okay we
got to
go all the way over
there he was telling you play Diablo 2
resurrected nah it didn't seem like a
proper
plug cuz I wouldn't have understood it
if it wasn't for you
guys they're not on speaking
terms wait why why though why
explain I missing critical points of
this story
[Applause]
okay what a
[\h__\h] the heck
it I'm not supposed to go
there oh it won't let me
anyway oh [\h__\h] I guess we'll be back
here
sometime was banished from hell for her
part in creting Angel and that's why her
daddy hates her I mean I know that part
but that's why I mean come
on don't give up on your daughter so
fast you you should try understanding
her POV as
[Music]
well maybe the real [\h__\h] is the wolf we
met along the
way didn't like her
boyfriend you'll be like that quite
often
huh family
issues we shouldn't meddle in their
family
[Music]
issues I feel like I'm about to drop
drop a ring in this mountainous
lava I'm ascending it just to reach the
top drop a ring and then be rescued by
some
birds Lura Lura Lura don't L of no I'll
do
it what took you so long I saw something
at the
shrine a wolf a
wolf Theo has been known to take such a
form it's not the first time I've
encountered him hey to the membership R
you world when you kept this from me
sorry we all keep secrets don't we and
now peace we don't have time for this
now protagonist clear your head before
we press
on the Temple of the primes is just
ahead Al so we are going in there what
whoa it's pretty
cool thanks for the membership
gift it's really cool how the the sound
effects also deepen when you look I hear
the the
lava I hear the
lava yeah yeah there's not too many of
these views but they're always always
really nice to look at oh now you're
making me walk back there bro I just
came from there what is this
map and what is this
ass hiking back no bird Taxi for
me got to walk all the way
myself a more gift thank you are you
sure you should be spending your money
on
memberships I'm warning you one more
time guys besides V there's one more
thing coming before the end of the
month I I'll I'll leave you alone and
December although the white things you
know you can still buy them in December
but you you
know I'm just saying if you want to it
might be something you want to have by
your hand it's worth it thank you will
be open hey I had this door open
already who closed it
tell the kid dad is going to be working
overtime on
Christmas yeah and no presents no
presents for the
[Music]
kids interesting this is like this like
little side mother dungeon that we did
it's the same kind of statues again
wait have no we haven't been here
before even though it feels like
it official kfp egg
boiler egg
boiler what's an egg
boiler just a
pot a cooking pot the world I'm ding
house to the world
[Music]
I like the music here it definitely
feels like I'm about to face
something pretty damning dooming
have I not warned you thanks for the
membership
gifts
bro the light it's orange light it's
blinding Hall of
destruction oh
you hear something scary
yeah I certainly heard
something yeah get back Dragged In he no
problemo jump scared me a little bit
but I haven't been jump scared enough
recently it
seems ooh
we
it's getting serious
guys getting deeper and
deeper facing our destiny
[Music]
I think that was from Destiny's Child
but I might be
wrong hello welcome to the stream
welcome to the hall of Terra also
he's got a nice
name his last name I want I want to have
his last
name which sounds like a marriage
proposal but it
isn't don't get it twisted
adoption I don't think I can adopt a
dead can you adopt dead
people wait can you actually that's
interesting I
wonder no oh what what what what if um
you know the wish of the dead person was
also to be adopted but maybe they were
in the middle of getting adopted but
then uh you know I don't know they got
into into a car accident or
something but you still wanted them to
be in your family so you kind of want to
proceed that so that even you
know in the afterlife at least like if
you believe in that kind of stuff like
your soul will be together or something
like that I mean I feel like that's
going to have some kind
of like you know can give someone peace
like I'm trying to think about it in
like
a like a sweet peaceful kind of
way
what come on stay with me chat think
think the way I'm
thinking adjust your way of thinking to
mine no only of course if
like like if it's like like I don't know
like like wholesome and reasonable and
maybe if there's a previous
understanding that that was the
intention from both
parties so okay I'm guessing it's not
possible obsid
stuff m plus
seven
heyo you think it happened
before time to
Google you do it chat Google it for me
I'm
busy got my hands
full oh
dear look at all those beans over
there look do you see
him what is he doing
they're being all serious over here and
he's
speeding I'm going to release him from
his
suffering we're too late he's still
spinning away I will deal with Elias
myself no way stay to the Shadows is it
glitching is it the same for everybody
who gets to this point I hope not
because that is um something you should
really fix oh I is not spinning
anymore oh
[\h__\h] oh my God
wait
oh don't that's not a nice
peekaboo I don't like
this it's a thing it's kind of a thing
see I told you like I can kind of see
it well brwl that was
brl oh and there he
goes more
sacrifices
yeah don't think about the physics don't
think about
it he's
cooking damn it Elias I warned you not
to walk this path
Laura have
you
Laura oh
[\h__\h] uhoh she too late in
it it's Raining
Blood oh
God please come with me she
is she
okay was she supposed to be um the like
new body
of
andariel is that what they were doing
ow he's he's such a pushy
guy oh oh there's mobs Oh
no just put my hydras everywhere put my
walls everywhere ow ow
ow ah but he's
easy he's fine
this is easy I didn't even heal a single
time
yay okay I feel like I really should
have played in hard mode or something
this is really weirdly
easy oh
well now you have some legendaries h
H I know it's at least good for like
getting through the game uh
swiftly so that the the playr won't be
too long you
know I think that is good for the sake
of the
stream I would level up faster on
hard you can increase difficulty in any
time if you visit kill that okay well I
might consider
it let they drop even more potions on on
a hard difficulty difficulty I don't
know if I need even more
Potions all
right lag
P what what
happened the is like fire crawling over
my skin this lady needs therapy for for
sure you were tattooed a ritual very
traumatizing to be the tattooed
mhm yes something for real though for
her a voice in my head that was not a
normal Tattoo
Studio a connection was made between you
and
her who are
you TAA and he walks away who are you I
am lures one of the herard
harad so so is
Elias if he told you that he was
lying I came to kill him thought I had
but the moment I looked away he
vanished if he
survived he will have fled to his
Refuge Refuge oh he has a palace oh
somewhere in the deserts of Eastern
kistan but that is all I know
can you guys talk
longer what about you we should get to
Tarak the people there know the deserts
of kistan well maybe someone has heard
of this
Palace let me join you I don't know how
much help I will be in this condition
but I owe you my
life you don't owe us
anything but you are welcome to come you
deserve venture
too level
up yeah
[Music]
oh new passive
skills I'm just going to wait what about
this one casting any skills grants one
stack of Enlightenment or grants 15 if
your previous cast skill was a different
element after gaining 100 Stacks you
become enlightened can no longer gain
stacks and lose 10 Stacks per second
while enlightened bonus damage with fire
lightning and cold are equal to them
combined and you gain this and that and
this and
that combustion your burning effects
deal 60% increased damage and an
additional 4% per unique source of
burning you may have apply you have
applied to the enemy
mhm and Asus
ferocity your fire Critical Strike
damage is increased by 25% % against
enemies above 50% life your fire
Critical Strike chance is increased by
10% against enemies below 50% life
critical strikes that kill enemies or
hit the boss Grant both bonuses against
all enemies for 3
[Music]
seconds I think I would go for
combustion combustion mainly for dealing
more burning damage AKA damage over
time as is good for
Fireball combustion is for burning
builds am I am I not a burning
build I mean I don't mind either
really have a lot of fire and bur sure
right furnace furnace
furnace I'm not
okay you do a lot of burning
yeah I thought so
too but maybe
not I mean for example the wall of
flames Burns
enemies but I don't know
like is like this one does this is this
burn damage Burns enemies for an
additional I don't know
well I'll go for this
one
Whatever but like what now is is this
tree not going to extend
anymore do I just until the end of the
game just fill up the others
[Music]
she wants to
go oh holy
macaroni that's so
far wait did I clear an act at least why
are we still in the same
act where should I go that's so far I'm
close
to okay I guess we should maybe go here
the rest of the skill points you use on
on other passive or level up you made
damage skills
okay act four very short
ooh okay
we it's best to use combustion
considering your builds well too late
now in
it got to change
it I wonder what's your side
Quest I barely made it out of
gulon I don't know if I have the courage
to carry this bloody sack halfway across
the
steps it please if there's don't
worry where
to
wait what
where does it not show me oh here do I
actually have to carry it or can I just
teleport that would be too simple if I
could just teleport
right but maybe it is that
[Music]
easy I cook a skill to get the skill
point back what
really oh my
God
what yes what's this about yes is that
are you mad Take It Outside The Walls
south of here there's a okay I'll do
that quickly I don't know why I suddenly
feel like doing a side quest but you
know
down silence please I need to
respectfully bury a body that I don't
know
digging digging digging oh you seem
scripted
die
okay these ashes will surely make it
easier
to dig oh wait I'm already done
okay let's go back to
report get sned the the body yeah I want
to read about
it apparently it's a thing you guys were
creeped out by me but it's a
thing good good I'm
sorry
Yi okay I need to Google this
now can you adopt dead a dead person
see yeah oh see for example
what can you post humously is also
important to note that post humous
adoption can only occur if the child is
an orphan or has been abandoned or if
the biological parents parental rights
have been terminated by court
order post humous adoption
w why because it's
interesting yeah that's how I envisioned
it like mostly about like uh adopting
children just
because like I don't know there there
could be many reasons why you might want
to still adopt them
H historical context the concept of post
humous adoption is rooted in the need to
provide stability and continuity for
children who have lost their parents
historically the death of a parent often
left wait is this but not about I mean
not their parents I mean like what we're
not a adopting the parent both emotional
and financial legal systems evolv to
address the vulner vulnerabilities and
post ad option became one of the
mechanisms for which Guardianship and
here are we talking about the same thing
is this talking about the same thing
that I
mean this seems wrong yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's not what I
mean okay
whatever legally adopt the corpse not
weird is that what I should
answer all right all right uh moving
on
here maybe I should check out the thing
with the potions where do I do the
potions
thing ah The
Alchemist
H wait where where am I
[Music]
going I have Renown rewards that I can
PL plain claim
okay uh
Alchemist wait this place is too
small
ooh okay alchem in
[Music]
there
JL there he
is poor Jal he will never get a game
whatever that is about his
alchemistry cuz you're not a cute
girl you got to be a cute girl for it
sorry that's just how it works I'm sorry
I didn't create the rules I just
followed
them
okay again I go
[Music]
here how has it been 3 hours 20 again I
feel like time passes really fast to
this
game the
hoorde is my paing
correct yeah
oops Yeah I feel like it's leading me
the wrong way but I guess I should trust
my
GPS for the
hord
[Music]
O I feel like I want to look around a
bit more to
find the like the other L altars
but I don't know I don't want to lose
too much time running
around dealing with these
maggots your skills cost no resource and
you have no cool down except for the
ulti you liar
Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam
[Music]
Bam no it's over
already
no no more fun to be
had you get like no XP killing these
mobs really I don't pay attention but
that's sad should I visit this
little whatever is that a dungeon a
Cellar okay then it must be really
small let me in show me your
Treasures
you is it small looks small
it's
small okay is that a pattern one two
three that was really
easy we
continuing oh there's more oh
[\h__\h] I still remember this is still
within my skill
set oh
god
um was this one twice
[\h__\h] uh not yet right this one twice and
then the other one
twice or then maybe this upper
one yeah yeah yeah Oh I thought it would
spawn
enemies
yooo
[Music]
nice oh I should have cleared out my
inventory what's
this your lucky hit chances increased by
11% while you have barrier I don't I
don't know I don't use barrier [\h__\h] but
besides that it looks really cool it's
orange
H hm
you don't have some random skill that
gives a barrier I don't
know you should only wear orange I
know that's what I'm
saying oh no you guys are back
going to get on my bicycle and Escape
you know how da says she's a car I say
this Panther is a
bicycle something about Panthers that
just makes you think they're some kind
of riding object
really nothing thought it would give me
something kind of want to almost look up
a map of Lil altars and cheat my way
through all of your hits are critical
strikes
oh does that include my hydra's hits
[Music]
YouTube do it what looking up the Lil
shrines the Lil
altars oh wait I found
one I had a feeling that there would be
one I found it on my own
yippee this place was calling to
me it was calling to
me I've got a
feeling that this place has a little
altar that this place has a little altar
that this place has a little alar
[Music]
moving
on is this an event maybe I should do
more I haven't been doing any
events oh wasted my op the daughter of
hatred demand survive the ritual en
sacrif let's go let's go let's go let's
go let's go let's go
ah
[Music]
ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's hard to see
no no
no no did I fail I don't
know did I get them all there's still
more there's still more there's still
more I think I did
it I think I did
it she only got one she got
one can I get it mastered oh wait there
it is that that's the end of
it I did it mastered yippe oh my
inventory God damn it
woohoo yeah I got a BRB YouTube what is
wrong with
[Music]
you I do think it's on YouTube not on
me please YouTube
behave be nice I've been nice to you
have I not treated you well have I not
been loyal to you I know I keep on
threatening you to stream on Twitch you
need steel work but I don't mean it I
don't mean it at
all no I didn't mean it
but lucky you I'm too lazy to set it up
[Music]
that got most of
it I'm not even looking
properly maze can go sword can
go sword can go
iron
onus now about this
one I mean I could I could just wear it
for
now win favor my friend uh I'll just
open another socket even if I don't use
the bar uh the the
barrier what am I here for uh add
sockets
why not oh [\h__\h] right these ones cost
more to add
[Music]
sockets oh well one socket
this don't know cuz like this these two
sockets give me 30 intelligence even if
this one has like four more intelligence
on its
own maybe not
worth maybe not worth then I don't want
to lose all that inen goodbye
at least I unlocked a new
aspect now the Europeans are getting hit
really Europeans
duck duck duck
[Music]
goose what the I can do it again
martal
souls for
real do I want to do it again it's kind
of stressful
so Fu focused I want to do better than
last time can I can I can I uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh it's so chaotic
bro bear of blood she will have your I
think I wait did I lose one
again is said sacrifices remaining two
that's the same thing it said
before bro but
[Applause]
where but look at the [\h__\h] loot again
I think I got something like what no
never mind but I got something
purple
no become injured while crowd controlled
grants you Unstoppable for 4 seconds
this effect has a 37 second cool
down the purple is the obal's oh ah so
so there was something purple after all
well it seems like you could kind of
farm cool stuff here or was this a
glitch that it happened
twice weird that it happened twice
how's the D4 Journey going it's going
pretty well o I've entered a
city how do I get to that
wayo I'm really enjoying it even though
I'm I must admit I'm not like super
immersed in the
story I don't know I'm not following so
well I guess but I really enjoy the game
play and the visuals
the timer just happen to
[Music]
reset
okay we're halfway
there we're halfway there you think the
story is weak well I can't be a judge of
that Diablo was never primarily about
the story really would you say it's just
about like having fun killing millions
of enemies and destroying things with
your fireballs and stuff I could see
that act one and act two were the best
yeah I was I think I was pretty immersed
when I first started out playing this
game act one was pretty
cool a lot of time has passed
so I lost my connection to it kind of
but that's okay I'm still having fun
you know what every once in a while I'll
I'll actually sell some things
maybe like
these ah why not right that's what I'm
saying need some
money why do I have
this magic Quest oh it's a it's a quest
reward uh like item thingy
ah I have yet to laugh at tragic death I
think I don't
know maybe I accidentally did
subconsciously steel work
PA I guess I'm going to salvage
this no
what would I do without you guys giving
me Diablo
advice what would I
do all right let's continue didn't not
not uh staying too long in this region
even though it looks
nice moving
on that's desolations
reach desolation of
SM a what the
[\h__\h] wait I want to go up there in that
little
dungeon what the
heck hello again hello there you're
looking so
cute fancy seeing you here
the foul
[Music]
air this has another new look
again no spiders toxic lurkers no my
lurkers are all sweet right lurkers
where are
you I ain't got no toxic
lurkers I'd like to believe so
thanks lurker oh you have given up on
lurking beautiful antidote
lurker toxic it's you says
Mo I didn't realize maa's new song was
uh like from that like like label thing
that they did with
[Music]
uh Universal Music and all of I
do I literally have no idea how that
works and how you get into
that perhaps it's Invitation
Only toxic is the most 2000 girls pop
song I've heard in decades it's kind of
amazing yeah true I felt the
same I won open
okay snake eat all maggots snack is
having a beast in this dungeon I'm sure
it appreciates it's feeding
how come a snake has a proper name with
like a first and last name who named
these snakes and who put a name tag on
them to be visible for players like
me breaking walls trying to break your
fourth wall right now we're in game for
fall who's putting all these name tags
on all these
enemies this one's called a SC live
midnight or something like that who
named you that tell me before I kill
you no answers
skiy skiy
here's the last
one the last silken Spire to be
Slade SL
fire y ever
shipped
cool very ch
meanwhile what's I don't even have a
last name why do the spiders have a last
name and I
don't does that seem fair to
you
oh Spider Slayer
yeah achievement
unlock stamping boots player t
do I want to go down here first cuz
there were two
paths
whoa okay this place is big
you know what I'd like what feature I'd
like from Diablo I to come to Diablo
4 hiring hiring people to join you on
your Journeys but I guess they maybe
they don't add it because they're just
like uh how about you go find some
friends to play the game with and they
can be the people who accompany you but
what what about people who don't have
friends or who don't have friends who
have the money to buy this
game it's in the
DLC
what
suddenly I can have
employees in the
DLC oh hello we got
separated
friends I won't last on my own
there imaginary NPC ingame
friends wait this is a
challenge so playay as many Hy waves as
you can before time runs out oh well
then they got to send me more faster it
takes time for them to spawn too
seconds quick player does
one Yoo okay I did a masters Masters I
did five out of five
I guess five
waves to keep the adventurer
alive without you I'd be dead oo thank
you that's quite a lot of treasure
please I'm surprised this person made it
so far into the cave in the first place
I guess they got dragged down by the
evil monsters wait a second could I have
gotten something cool here AG GRE shrine
what does that do again more Spoils of
of
gold should have had that during the
wave
ah it's
over too bad I'm I I I didn't go down is
this connecting maybe it is but this
path bothers
me the left path that I didn't go
to yeah the green Shrine is like when
you activate money
cheat S
mother Lo mother Lo mother Lo mother
Lo want to be a
[Music]
millionaire don't you
dare oh dungeon complete oh that was the
boss the Boss Of All Bosses you have
unlocked aspect of vocalized empowerment
yippe but they're still enemies
there still
enemy
oh I'm a c ala machine
today yeah there may be an
urge for singing within me very strong
today okay it did connect but this
whatever I finished it I'm going to
leave nice D and clear
guess we'll have a k next
week May maybe I don't know we'll see
maybe my urge will be gone by
then
okay we're pretty close to the next
point where the act and
slow slow mode turn it
off what the [\h__\h] is
that like maybe there's an altar over
there
any L
altars oh no but a silent chest I got to
go I got to go get a key I'm going to go
get a
key I'm going to get
one I need to see what's in the
G hopefully these spiders don't respawn
oh there's also a Cellar a foul Den h
by mul yeah
[Music]
yeah how big is this thing this looks
big no no never
mind really that's
it no
okay a little bit more okay
okay it was a fake chest this is the
real
one ah let's go
[Music]
treasure you sing some some of the new H
songs that came out from other
people huh you mean in the kok or you
mean
now I don't think I really am capable of
seeing any of
them of course they [\h__\h]
respawn okay good buy a key
[Music]
that doesn't even count anymore
probably I don't even listen that much
to
music what did I come here for uh who
sells the thing the the the someone with
a weird name p
pursuer
purveyor there you are
okay maybe I should have sold some
stuff oh well or
salvaged okay we got something orange
not for me but cool cool
[Music]
he wait this is this is a sorcerer Mage
what enemies damaged by incinerate
explode incinerate
incinerate I don't do incinerate do
I should I wear this
ma your burning damage has increased by
21 29 but I don't do incinerate I don't
incinerate anything
as far as I
know I can start using inate I
guess the [\h__\h] is
this the fire beam you shoot from your
hand it's a channel
ability where is that incinerate is it
like
this oh yeah so I could switch Fireball
to incinerate I could I guess I can't
have both
right channel a beam of fire burning
enemies for 128 damage per
second should I can I take this
back I can't take these
back you can have both but not
right I me I wouldn't mind switching but
do I need like some kind of
scroll resp mode
oh respect CL oh okay
so like
this I don't know if it needs five
though does it need five not five
okay something spawned next to
me it needs five for more damage
okay
exit oh
[\h__\h] mhm
uh what how do I confirm oh do I need to
spend
everything
oh every 3 seconds an enemy has been hit
by incinerate they are immobilized by
1.5 seconds enemies deal 30% less damage
while burning from
[Music]
incinerate maybe immobilizing them is
fun
so that's now my right click
skill your skills oh no there's no
enemies for me to oh there we go W what
the
[\h__\h] okay I wonder how much Mana it
normally costs cuz right now it it
doesn't cost anything of course
come on let me use it on
someone oh now we can see it go
down yeah I mean I'm fighting against
it oh that's fun to use
though [\h__\h]
flamethrower okay now I guess I'll be a
mace person uh but so what would I
combine with the mace not not a shield
right one of these
balls oh
what oh but ah the thing is I want slots
on it it'll be so expensive to put slots
on this
one but at least in exchange it's a it's
a
legendary imprint an aspect on the staff
it'll be 100% more
potent
uh no as in what what are you saying no
to
[Music]
oopsie let's go back to killed and look
at stuff and sell
stuff don't worry about suckets for
lowlevel
gear you can
Ah Ah that's what you mean
oai you what pryo said you can salvage
this for the a aspect and then put the
aspect on your
stuff
[Music]
true true true
true yeah did I get
it did I I got it
right anyway Magic
[Music]
you know what I might
just give me that
just a small Improvement but good enough
a cultist to imprint on your game yeah
yeah okay one second one second one
second I'm just going to finish my job
[Music]
here came apart nicely
ooh could replace you think this is
better use that stuff
okay you can take what's left
[Music]
so we're going to be switching
those and then putting the the thing on
it let reserve it that was a diamond and
a purple
one h occultist
hello how does this work again
wait uh
no enchant what was it enchant or was it
imprinting
enchant I think it's uh
enchanting this
one oh God what was it
called uh uh uh
uh oh incinerates listen to free beams e
wait this one's also for incinerating
pretty
cool this also
incinerate M which one's better free
beams or this
[Music]
one or is this even another
one oh yeah those two try beam whoa
you can put the free beams on Julie
oh okay let's put this on imprinting
aspect oh it takes exactly six and I
only have six oh I don't think I'll be
doing any more imprinting
afterwards is this
worth losing six of those things like
all of them
[Music]
better keep the staff for a
while
ah chain lighting can I change this one
this is an AIX right the orange thing no
wait no no it's
not an
aspect that's an aspect I can change it
wait can I change is it in
here no right
[Music]
yeah d very
absorbing sounds
good let's look at these oh oh oh yeah
oh yeah I was I was hoping for
this oh it doesn't need the fancy
things oh yeah I mean it's
a it's a level 23 necklace maybe I
should have put it on a different
necklace a little bit later but okay we
can redo it another time when we get an
even better necklace at least this one
didn't cost too many any crazy
resources
yeah yeah yeah yeah cuz it's already
legendary uhhuh
uhhuh yeah oh oh was this not legendary
before I made it legendary it wasn't
orange before
huh it became orange I made it orange it
I gave it orange
perms ah
wow nice I'm decked out question
mark lag lag
lag oh my we want to try my new
beam [\h__\h] wait I just reached level oh
35 oh nice thanks
spiders thanks for that can I improve my
my incineration I'm having fun with it
no it's maxed
okay how about
um five
five metor no
maxed Max oh wait here I can still do
something
right I'm going to add another one here
I can improve the
passives yeah this one's good right I I
don't know where the other one is that
you mean but for now this shall
suffice
okay back on track or are we I want to
find
altars Al
altars over oops what's over here spicy
spicy this might be spicy it's a big
round
area
event or maybe later for story it's
empty
now a world boss spawns here
okay hopefully not
now while I'm running through it
I wonder if the arars are always kind of
like at the
edge like the map where that was a
coincidence probably like not at the
edge of the map but like the edge of any
kind of terrain
to the bottom left of
here bottom left of here I mean that's
pretty vag too that could be anywhere
like that could be here or it could be
like here or here or here anything's
bottom left from
[Music]
me there's one in every St wait a second
wait wait a [\h__\h] second
what Stay With Me
stay with
me oh he died oh they're kind of weaker
out here hey to the Y he to the
Y stay with
me and give me all the gold like you
bleed I want to make you bankrupt C I
need
it buy my merch while you're at
it and invest in the kfb
STS where is that alar alar alar
alar how to speak English
ow oh there's one is this the one you
meant who told me to use Fireballs this
was my destiny all along
[Music]
guys that one nice good find I almost
didn't go there oh there's event I want
to do it I want to do it I want to do it
I want to do it I want to do
it ah good I found a promising or
deposit and could use some help mining
it
mhm I'll help
you but let's place I guess my things
first what's the master SL animated WF
from after I hear freeze them what what
are youing oh oh
oh
oh should be easy enough
[Music]
oh yeah all today oh yeah too easy did I
master I think I
mastered
Yahoo yeah oh balls oh balls oh
balls sick
[Music]
one of the mercenaries you can get in
the
DLC that guy that we just
met
cool I met him early we're destined to
be together I have to get the DLC now
go next go
next going to go straight for it now I
promise
ouch stop my toe stop my paw toe you
think can cats stop their toe for sure I
mean just like how I can step on their
tail I can step on their paws and that's
probably like stubbing their toe for
them poor
babies poor babies not even bernes gets
free Flame fro
yeah the power is
mine have you learned anything about
Elias's Palace hello hello hello she's
wearing clothes again the people here
speak of a sorcerer who lives in a grand
palace beyond the endless
sandstorms could help us reach it they
know the land better
than my dog keeps not looking where
she's going so sometimes she spins
around and bks her head a
andaria I hear
her I need a place to
focus keep her voice at Bay block her
look for a guide I'll get something to
help cha clear her
mind I look for guide
okay uh are you guide why are you guide
are you mad there's a a living in that
storm
okay are you guide why are you
guide no chance
okay are you good I
wolves mercenaries with a silly name
wrong person sniffing off coin why are
you good you'll find none fool enough to
accept that request wait they got camels
old man
but you look dead he spends his days in
a fog of white smoke at the
riverbank be careful it's a dangerous
place be careful too much
lesbian
cute can you get camel
mounts when you're like
here that's my favorite meme in the
world found a quiet spot where she can
focus on controlling andariel's presence
is it safe to leave her here safer than
stumbling blind through the desert at
least until we find a reliable
guide that one's pretty
cute I mean look at it looks
cute looks fluffy fluffier than the
horse does it
wins to me it
wins okay let's uh sell some stuff while
I'm
here to who wants to trade with me trade
offer I give you things and you Salvage
them you love salvaging don't you ready
for whatever you need all of you guys
love salvaging let's do
[Music]
it conjuration skill do I use
conjuration skill
whatever I have a necklace that I really
like right now so get out of my
face stop making me regret my life
choices I'm happy with what I have thank
you don't ruin all that work huh okay
let's
[Music]
go oh Hydra is a conjuration
huh not a hold all but I'm happy plenty
happy with my necklace
where are we
going all oh look at these guys they're
dressed
so
like I don't know they stand out in the
desert it's kind of slay
I'm curious about this
path sorry
l oh there's a little thing
here I accidentally entered
it can I try to look at chat whoa whoa
whoa don't forget to col oh no that was
a way point oopsy
[\h__\h] okay okay I leave this mine I will
go get the Waypoint
okay Al so L of doesn't follow me into
these optional things why is he
scared oh this is
small all right oh more
this is so sick holy
[\h__\h] I love my new weapon my new
attack it's most most amazing
thing incinerate is so good yeah I don't
know why I didn't start incinerating
earlier the things you learn in your
second half in your your life as a
pH you live and you learn all right I'm
supposed to go back here cuz I messed
up way point do
cool it's okay I can be there really
fast
M very nicely
hidden all
right just into this region
okay I like going with a Hydra build
personally it's fun watching six snake
heads
spawn what happen uh am I not also a
Hydra build cuz I speced into some Hydra
or do you mean also adding um these
things into
your like these things and and get the
conjuration
extras you can have up to 12 Hydra heads
in the end game
well I do like me hydras but it would be
nicer if I can spawn them all at once
having to always spawn them one by one
it's a bit a a
bit ooh there's green stuff here new
fools I'm not the one who's going to
roll their corpses into the river find
the drug then entrance no
chance drug dead turn around and walk
out of here
friends DEA here from the Albuquerque
Police
Department you're red show me all your
drugs and your drug dealers
now well can't say I didn't warn you oh
you want to fight all
right I don't give a
damn you will let me in one way or
another what's in here enter the back
room and search for the old man hello
old
man oh there you are wake
up should visit Albuquerque sometime
it's an interesting City really to
collect where is it I know in America
but like this can't be can it west coast
East Coast no the symbol of the
the NM you think I know what NM
means new I right New Mexico okay makes
sense it's so it's close to the border
right cuz they keep on talking about
borders
friend it's me me she no deard is
gone my name is loras we need your help
passing through the sandstorm to the
north Sandstorm eh the others must have
turned you down told you some rubbish
about a sorcerer Al
[Laughter]
wager well what can a sorcerer do to me
that time hasn't already
yes yes I'll help there's an old chapel
near there an auspicious spot to begin a
show you where the sorcerer can do that
nobody else has done it I can literally
kill meet you there Grill you like
grilled chicken this is wonderful like
I'll put those seven spices on you
though I'll make the most of it don't
worry flesh from bone perfect Quest
name meet Lor of and Mesi at The
Forsaken Chapel which is
over there how is this act still not
over this must be the end of it
right so crowded
here W moral
meter there's the Last Quest L okay no
of Mexico West of Texas and believe it
or not a little bit of Oklahoma touches
New Mexico but that do you say believe
it or not as if it should be surprising
to me but I don't know how that is
surprising nothing nothing phases me
um
so these Graves yeah um I've been sent
here uh it seems like the dead people
have spoken to me and they told me they
changed their wishes about how their
death is to be handled they don't wish
to be Graves anymore they want to be
ashes thus I have come to fulfill their
[Applause]
[Music]
wishes no I'm not going to adopt
them
ridiculous why would I do that seems so
unreasonable I don't know what you're
talking
about ah you're here de is inside with
your friend good the moment we stepped
inside andariel grew desperate but her
scream are only a whisper now this is
Holy
Ground her influence will be weaker
here here we
go wait a second is she going to turn to
andariel and we're going to fight in
this like nice round area
what does andariel say to you terrible
things mad things [\h__\h] she knows of
Lilith's return and what Elias is
planning it's coming but and not care
who wins only that someone
loses and that their suffering is
extreme extreme
suffering no I've been a burden for you
already one day I will find a way to
help
you speak of L is everyone ready I am up
to TAA whether she'll join us
though every part of me wants to walk
through that storm and draw Elias's
blood but perhaps he is counting on my
Vengeance to lead me back to him so he
can finish what he
started it is safer for everyone if I
stay no shame in that it's the wise
choice we'll bring you his
[Music]
hat oh Transcendent that's
exciting
nice awesome have
[Music]
fun are you
prepared are you I hope you've lined
your pockets with healing drops if not
help yourself to the ones I keep on
our Storm's going to get worse than you
I can smell it when it starts to kick up
we'll have to find something to shelter
us or there will be nothing left of us
but bones and
stories uh okay meet mesf outside of the
storm okay but not before I check out
this grave
he's the guy from the other to that
takes you to curse from lot gulan did I
meet
him artillery shrine
[Music]
what the heck sound stay with
me just savoring the moment I didn't
finish act two oh my God such a loser to
remember hey deard I can't it's not
deard
bro wait what follow me yeah go go go go
I'm ready
oo
ooh o it's not even on the map
cool oh it's giving me damage one at a
time L don't get
distracted M grilled scorpion
the winds are turning angry follow me oh
yeah angry storm Ang such an angry
storm wait oh my God my oopsie my health
is really
low what the
[\h__\h] we made it
what now what
now yeah make sure to take care of your
camel poor camel been through so much
[\h__\h] could it
be it is the God's favor our journey
friends what' you find sh drink with me
n let's not get drunk now that's not
good
no I uh I'm we're going to get lost
bro I won't turn down such
generosity the camel heals me
sweet seems it's dying
down healing
camel do you like them more now kfp will
you tolerate the camel now
good camel who's a good camel oh yeah
who's a good camel you a good
camel some people didn't tolerate the
camel very much from
my
uh
impression clear the way for the camel
the camel will be the God of all of us
in the future our new
Overlord I accept I for one accept our
new
Overlord way
camel flamethrower to op I'm not using
anything else
anymore Club you think it's time to go
clubbing now
this guy probably thinks
so sorry oh no no back we need to go
back why what what's wrong what's wrong
my pipe I left my pipe back in the
chapel [\h__\h] [\h__\h] Meads oh man if
you turn your back now I'll be the first
to bury a plate in
it fine but I won't forget this betrayal
L of No Mercy L of less of an ampath
than
me come on then go go go go go
go where are we
going mhm
he what if I reach the girl the girl the
goal early do I get to skip all of this
if I already know where it is like just
go there on my own oh wow what the [\h__\h]
is that
alive we're being
swarmed yes it's
massive you recognize him I don't
it's time to move
eh very much
so I feel like he's like lowkey walking
in the
circle he scamming
us Storm's not done with us yet this
way ow
oh found the house
no no that's not where you going yeah it
is do you remember the smell of the Salt
Air on the ocean no shade or devil stop
yapping go go been all across this world
since then seen things you wouldn't
believe
was never quite the same wandering
without a direction it was
just it's to have
something
one
just you done wait out the severe winds
bro it's fine let's go sounds like the
winds have C okay oh my God
can't speedrun this game with this
Quest not speedrun
friendly I'm clearing your path so you
can run through
faster oh hello
there wait oh [\h__\h] I needed to talk to
him
[\h__\h] he I'm at the camel Quest stay
close not liking
it at least Lura is hurrying
up is he moving at all
yeah Uber GPS be like barely moving in
real time I have that problem all the
time it never really
shows where they truly
are and then I'm not sure are they just
is the GPS broken or are they really
messing with me cuz that happens too
sometimes that wasn't half as dangerous
as the others made it I went to the case
where one was just like endlessly
driving away from
me for miles and miles and miles and I
was like hoping he would cancel it if
he's not planning on picking me up ever
but he wasn't canceling it I just had to
wait I had to wait like legit 10 minutes
or so until it let me cancel without
extra
cost messed up so much waste of my time
man cuz like I was on a time pressure
too so getting an Uber to mess with me
like that and not being able to cancel
for free until I reach a certain time
limit
bro how many meters is one
M I don't even know I'm just using the
word so that it sounds more
dramatic okay so we're in some kind of
Oasis wow Temple
Place speak with mief look at
this to think such an intriguing place
was hidden Beyond
oh a relic from the old days of kistan
maybe lost to time found himself on nice
palace and hard to reach too of all the
sand around it we hate sand mief don't
move don't speak to anyone there is
great danger 4.6 billion years you've
grown fearful in your old age my friend
but worry not I will stay
put nice pretty
sorry lag lag lag sorry that's on my
side game is making me lag wow there's
humans here I saw an army at the
mother's side ready to wage war against
hell and I was among her followers
reborn a new with her power are these
people ult people look how Bloody I am
why am I so
bloody is it just because I'm low I'm
not even that low on a why am I so
bloody looking CH them to join his
anointed
Circle that one in R will never survive
what is to
come you will not
survive he
beautiful not like I've bured countless
demons I have no understanding why I
look like this I don't get it
it was Master Elias's hand that brought
Lilith to sanctuary and it will be his
hand that binds a lesser evil the Lesser
evil
again all right you there
wait anointed Noble I haven't seen you
before we just made it through the storm
by their mother's Grace mother ah new
this deciples yes yes yes you've come at
an auspicious time Lilith recently
graced us with her presence missed her
again she was
here oh it was
magnificent but do not worry perhaps
Master Elias will give you a glimpse of
her through the sightless eye if he
deems you worthy I'm sure he will and
present yourself to him I will present
myself to him right
away Elias you you
[\h__\h] Show
Yourself there's a whole dungeon again
God damn it worse than I thought Elias
has the sightless eye it's ancient magic
he can see anywhere with it sross
time our flock has grown huh behold the
Wonders that the mother has in store for
you
raise your heads High champions of Li
never again will we fear
demons I saw a village the people cold
and hungry pray to a light that would
give them no
warmth but in her she just summon a
succubus a new fire was stok succub
hearts they would never go hungry or
feel cold
again
hot how did he do that he needs to teach
me I want to learn from you maybe I
should join this
cult can summon my own succubus are you
also making one he also made
one
oo
nice here oh another
one
damn what do you think guys are we
in go forth and stand in judgment before
Master
Elias but show no fear can you take off
those locks of the door though it'll be
hard to get in we
won't thanks
take bang all right Blessed Mother let's
do it I will not fail you
again the maiden will walk this
world let's go
Elias I knew you would come
Laura been spying on us with the
sightless eye have you
you think I would waste such Magic on
you you're still just as narrow-minded
as the day I left
you I will put you out of your did you
watch me though was I worthy of your
eye he don't hurt
him you should have stayed in that
little cabin your
regrets wait he already did
what what's the cat find the sightless
eye while we still have time we can't
leave it with these what's the cat hold
on I see something blood
pedals blood pedals oh
no oh
yes I melted him like butter second form
Dooku Bring It On
Fisto
Diablo
bail is that what she called her
doggy oh they look lovely together the
ruination of sanctuary is imminent
and yet you
doubt only zealots and fools are
completely certain
mother if we are to that's so [\h__\h] up
it will be by your
hand I have not come to
save but oh my God oh my God in my
shadow the strong will oppose L the
might of Hell
itself let momy fend for themselves
mommy andaria lives the horror DM
die whatever the
cost whatever the
cost her hands look weird
but they are intimidating had another
Vision Lilith thinks the prime evils
will destroy sanctuary and she's
empowering people to stand against them
that's why she and Elias are gathering
followers they're building a bloody Army
very bloody indeed
sedora the Lords of Hell threaten our
existence and we are are doing something
about it did you clone
yourself how are you still alive was it
a puppet you will never understand what
I have done for this
world all right no
problem this is the best you can
do you cannot kill me
is he dead again Bastard
die we come out of there again bashing
our heads against him like this why not
he'll wear us down nah we need to escape
but not without the sight coward if we
can take it that'll Rob him of some
power at
least
okay where is he now Gospel of the
mother at emboss of demonic ruins in the
mountains the mother and I saw a village
the people cold and hungry prayed to a
light that would give them no
warmth but in her presence a new fire
was stoked in their
hearts they would never go hungry or
feel cold
again so deep
beautiful nice
poetry where are you buddy let me kill
you
again do me the favor come
on don't hide from
[Music]
me it's all just a hide and seek game to
him oh this place looks really fam
familiar too I feel like I've been
in a dungeon that's been built like
this I sense the blood of Lilith in you
wer all right he's giving me time to
prep how nice of him blessed
communion open your heart to her
Embrace stop yapping let me attack I
prepped
everything you will give up at some
point old man it's what you always
do again we'll have a look at my Dodges
ow
amazing and once again he died
is that stench
unnatural some kind of
necromancy where did he find this
power she took me to an ancient
Battlefield where thousands of Our Kind
died at the hands of Angel and
Demon he's a good never again will we
suffer so she
proclaimed and in her eyes I saw for a
new world a paradise where we will live
free from the tyranny of the heavens and
Hell ours if we have the strength to
make it so get some
help very delusional people these cult
followers unlike us we have a very clear
mind don't we I
Laura I have a feeling this won't be the
last time it is too late to stop what
Lilith has
begun you can do better than this no
this is pretty good this is like my best
man stop holding back la oh he's doing
something different maybe this is the
last
one he changed his
tactics but still kind of weak
man come
on tell me that ain't
it
Elias the mother sat with me at the fire
and opened my mind to secret knowledge
taught me the true names of all demons
through which they can be controlled I
once we were the Lambs and demons were
the Wolves but no more we the weak will
be made strong we The Chosen will become
the Wolves well that sounds promising at
least here it is but the sightless eye
what mief can help us get the artifact
far from this place but we need to hurry
before Elias returns there's more right
that opening over there is our best
chance of Escape was that our last
Elias's
fight nah it has to be more dramatic
like I don't know make me cry make me
cry make me suffer at
least maybe maybe now this whole city
will try to kill me because they find
out that I'm not one of them
some kind of pressure here we need to
stop the
bleeding it seems I've lost a step in my
old
age I need to prove myself
still this was not any proof of me being
an
empath
hey you made it I prove it in a
different game did you kill that
sorcerer fell one of these days don't
talk the storm was broken we'll get you
out of here oh it's a
shame I got mine just a hair too
late sneaky devil poked me in the
back should I be crying like a quill
rat so it go he's still calling him
deard hey
deard
I ah he's dead so it goes well um I
don't know
man can't really feel much for a
drunker
[Music]
a well all right
P they'll be coming
I'm taking the cyclus eye we need a safe
place to stud use it against them we'll
meet to the deser is this the end of the
ACT go wait Elias was so weak are we
going to meet him again maybe maybe we
[Music]
will I feel like we
will very close to it still
ma meet Lor of at The Forsaken
Chapel oh well we got teleported sick
did you kill him uh more than once in
fact trouble is he won't stay
[Music]
dead he is more powerful than I thought
I underestimated
him so did
I but we took something important from
him at least
the sightless eye MH I think he was
using it to commune with Lilith from
afar a powerful piece of
magic and
dangerous perhaps we can use it to our
advantage give me some time to St good
luck at work
G the prime evils were
reforming hell was
coming but Elias was not the answer to
anyone's
prayers if you want to take the measure
of someone you just them by their deeds
not their words simple as that Elias
preached of saving the world while
standing at top a mountain of corpses M
then there was The
Wanderer everything Elias was
not tainted by Lilith's blood and yet
able to resist her corruption strong
that was what I witnessed in The
Wanderer
deeds and that was when I started to
think that perhaps together we could
keep the evil at Bay
must have been gruesome in that cult
never level up no more gruesome than the
rest of sanctuary's
underbelly I have two skill points now
[Music]
shees so let's put F
into 6% increased burning damage this
bonus is increased to 24% to enemies
while they are affected by more burning
damage your p man SE skills cost four
less per mana and deal 2%
damage increase damage double the
bonuses of standing still
for I might be I might be standing still
more these days now that I have my fire
my flamethrower yeah I'm standing still
for it
okay
nice I can shut out and darel's Whispers
most of the time but not
always better a whisper than having a
walk the world
again andariel is part of Lilith and
Elias's plan but how what do we know so
far Lilith made a deal with
astero a demon who served her father H
interesting choice of
Ally and she has a key to Hell h a place
where she's seen as a
traitor so why would she
go
and is she already there can we go too
we need answers we need keys Elias used
the cyclus eye to contact
Lilith perhaps it can help us bring it
here would you
okay
okay I take I take it's risky I'm done
but we haven't got a choice it already
eded
officially when you're ready picture
Lilith in your mind and G to the eye
this is the start of X4 oh
really I took off my
hood oh there's a popup I'm so
blind my eyes
M my father's Essence is
reforming how do you
know I feel
it like a thousand Old Wounds ripped
open
again he's still
weak f
I a strike who's her mommy we can resist
does she have a mommy make his power
yours the other Lords
will who is the mommy's
mommy what she saw me what
happened
she saw
me feel watched she knows we're looking
for her feel observed only a matter of
time before she comes after us not
necessarily this is really s's eye
pipping you
fool Lilith aims to take his power while
he is still
weak
so that's what you've been preparing
for all right old man
think think Laura
think
think think
or if she takes mist's power aggressive
writing on already written paper evil
herself just writing over she'll be able
to conquer hell and Sanctuary
alike I have an
idea how to stop her mhm
but for it to work we'll need the help
of an old
Ally deliver this message to Donan Donan
he'll have gone to kobad for
guidance all
[Music]
righty I think that's a good point to
stop
TBH
so wow another 5 hours of
diao
damn I'm really liking the game I maybe
didn't have much to tangent about today
but I like the
game we're in act four now four out of
how many was it again I forgot I keep on
forgetting was it eight or
six six
oh yeah this one's super short
nice Diablo is one of my comfort food
games yeah it is kind of a comy game
even though the story is
[Music]
spooky okay
nice well well well we will return to
this next week we can finish act for in
20 minutes that's cool but um I got to
read Super Chat those 20 minutes are
precious to
me
sick had a good time
today I'll read some super chats let me
move
to
here yes yes yes yes I hope you guys
liked today's
stream bit more on the chill side but I
thought you guys might appreciate that
especially
cuz
um oops oh
God especially oh especially because
I'll be gone for a couple days so you
know some chill streams here and there
would be good
do I like chill streams thank
you time spent with ba always time well
spent so wise such a wise chicken how do
my chickens become so wise they're
learning from
me audio St actually I really like the
one I was playing
yesterday in my members only
stream this
one
Jazz you like jazz do you like
[Music]
JZ so where do we continue reading does
anybody actually know GD seems to be
gone
I think I can find out just by checking
what link has been used already so don't
worry don't
worry I'll find
it I don't need your help I found it
inscription
inscription yes
yes I'm an independent Super Chat reader
now
[Music]
thank you for the support here we go ja
47 D Flappy boy with a rainbow thank you
a belated happy aie day to you T oh
coincidentally yesterday was also my
birthday which is somewhat po poetic was
I not streaming huh after all the
laughter warmth and inspiration my
cameos she brings into my life and that
of so many others throughout the year is
so much more meaningful than any
physical gift could ever be a
really what about
$500,000 except maybe that Kiana Shield
ITA bag I received in a mail today oh
that was so
nice hope I'll be able to put it to good
use next year that would be such a flex
man carrying that around as your bag at
concerts Ian concerts or so Main to cut
back a bit on supas this month quarter
four quarter four this year is doing
everything so far to disrupt my
delusions of responsible vtuber
spending so please don't worry if that
happens hyped for the special surprise
merch though a yeah you didn't know yet
at the
time but it was
white yeah happy belated birthday Flappy
boy
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in your pants
too happy birthday to you Flappy
boy and happy ooshi day to me I guess
belated yeah thank you for the big Super
Chat and the big support and and uh who
know knows thank you for wrapping the
ITA bag one of those
days I'm glad you will be repping kfp
wherever you go thank you so much for
the
support hope I can stay Yami oi for much
longer the gamer
cre will ad thanks for the pinky really
appreciate you and your hard work boss
thank you I appreciate you too and my
chicken's hard work as
well thank you so
[Music]
much H icing D River Rat D the Jolly Jam
D Tanaka from kfp D fed d delar d I got
a headache
man I've got headaches a lot
recently star thank you Quattro Kix dun
lunchbox dun L Lain dun DOR 787 thanks
for the pinky take my first ever pinky
Su would do an AKA if I could with the
new Mario and Lui came out this week you
got any plans to stream it did I answer
this I think I feel like I did but I
don't know if I did it towards
you I did answer this question from
someone at
least also looking forward to the day
you play the N64 zeld games oh yeah
those days will come I'm sure I'm sure
but yeah Mario Luigi no
nah it looks cute but I'm not really
interested and I don't feel like I have
time for it
anyway yeah sorry if that's
disappointing Mobius 0193 D Nathan coton
thanks for Pinky just wa out here being
a trans Setter again getting the other
girls to play inscription and eat an
eternal what I got other people to play
inscription
did I eat an eternal for
sure don't know about inscription feel
like I was more inspired by others
because I've seen in the past many girls
were playing incription I didn't see the
the the gam playay but I just saw the
those uh the thumbnails ah ah yeah that
could be it she did get into inscription
like days after me
[Music]
mm z d g d g D again and Bon thanks for
the pinky sorry Tel I died during the
stream due to getting tired but
continues overtime Works no and I have
to go to work now again
no man I feel bad for you hope you
enjoyed it well my Koshi still it gives
me strength to see you happy Al Z I want
to see you happy
too are you
[Music]
happy I hope so W bunny take care of
yourself
okay if you can in any way influence how
many overtime hours you're doing then
hopefully you'll keep them
low thank you
yay b d and Elie la
[Music]
next
is uh the
Mirage
stream why is the title so
weird
okay this
one I have a headache so I don't know if
I'll read much more but I'll try to read
this one at
least yeah Cruz than and Jacob for this
astical thanks for the pinky Hi boss
today I received a notification from
YouTube music saying that I'm in the top
0.25% of tak's listeners in October wow
thank you thanks for your amazing music
thank you you guys should also listen to
my music more so that you can Flex this
kind of
achievement do it do it do it thank you
as
[Music]
thank you for the red
chat oh yes Angel angle I can be your
angle or your
debil cute right I love those outfits
and I love the the
wings looking forward to making more
outfits to enchant you guys
thank
[Music]
you a TR for fun D Dax Jaden thanks for
the pinky Mirage Owns My Heart o love
this model especially the black ah I'm
reaching the completion of my rookie
year as a kfp and watching my Kami
oi your rookie year you mean your first
year oh really my day gets brighter
watching you and being part of KP hope
more years to come yes please I demand
it thank you so much for letting me be
your D
Jaden really glad to have
you and the black outfit really is
nice oh so good
H for the red super chat oh you have a
new profile picture
huh football
devilish cuteness
yes thank you so
much d tww
d thank you for the pinky now you are a
wall flat Wawa huh wait that seems like
something you would say in my member
stream yes today but what was wall oh
because I was in the
wall because I became the wall That's
why foreshadowing
yeah golden boom d space waterfall d
gold Boom D Ry Moonlight action for the
pinky camera one improvised camera 2
adapted but camera three did not
overcome what did Cam free
do what did it do I guess I was like
invisible and or
so m d I am a te beep D Al D thank you
very much Fred screw D Jim Tracy thank
you such a fun stream and the Mir was
amazing you did a great job teaching the
coral did
I cuz I might teach it
again to in two days yeah you guys are
probably curious what we're going to do
for the goo stream
um we're going to be doing all kinds of
things we're going to mix like
everything we're going to do like a
little bit of a DAT so to
say and get to know each other and we're
going to
do some dancing perhaps cuz we're in 3D
and we're also going to play
game so
[Music]
yeah probably going to be like 2 hours
or so that's probably the
goal yeah I'm excited I'm
excited I'm nervous though I'm
nervous I hope go will like
me yeah I think that'll be the first
time that we like properly
interact like in real time so she will
love you I I'll I'll make her love me I
I I can make all of the small blue
kousakis love
me I mean she's not she's not as much of
a Kaki like Kobo I would say but you
know the small blue girls they always
like
me I'm their
[Music]
mommy although her lore says which is
it's so it's so silly but she's uh I
think 300 M tall
just because very early on I was doing
my research you know and I saw a video
of like her getting interviewed very
early
on and she says like she gets asked how
tall are you and she's like secret and
and then her real answer after that is
like um okay make it 300
M even though she's obviously not 300
M but now it's like in her Wiki and
everything
why is it a
secret we'll see so if I'll be taller in
our stream then I am canonically over
300 meters
then and I'm pretty sure I'm going to be
taller in that stream so how is she
going to explain that maybe
optical illusions
there's our giant idols on stage yeah my
giant Idol
idea can work with
go forced
perspective I don't know
guys I wouldn't believe
it maybe she meant 300 mm and not meters
or 300 now 300 cm is just fre now fre me
are still too tall so she probably means
300 mm that's like the most
realistic okay not really
but 3 m is also not
realistic anyway anyway I'm going to
bring some measuring tape to the
stream I'm going to measure her with
oranges one orange
is maybe maybe 10 cm
my head is going to be the
orange by the
way orange for
scale okay where was
I H yeah unknown thanks for the pinky
you're literally perfect my Oshi is the
cutest prettiest and most beautiful in
the world I died multiple times during
the stream well unknown you always say
these kind of things but in this stream
it was very very reasonable
understandable have a nice
day GD D thanks for the red super chat
am I in heaven yeah actually wa is our
Heaven thanks for showing us wonderful
and cute 3D model T it was perfect
thanks to you I gain energy again today
let's go our Koshi best Idol
k
um so
where it
so ch ch
[Music]
thank you so
much I appreciate it thank you
everybody's just in love with me with my
Mirage
model this is only the beginning guys
[Music]
excuse M thank you
w Pap M thanks for Pinky your new Mirage
bottle is simply perfect I love it even
if it's not official it'll be for me
yeah for me too and all of us K thank
you to KI thank you K to become the
brighter star in the sky I'm proud of
you and happy to be a kfp and support my
only Koshi everybody bringing out the
Koshi words again
in these super chats I must have been
very
Charming thank you very much M yes I'm
glad you enjoyed
it I'm glad you see Mirage Wawa is just
as official as the other waas yes yes
yes she deserves it she she deserves to
be treated with
respect okay that was the Super chatos
[Music]
M I can do the next one too that's
really just a
couple the eat and eternal
ones check out for the seven TR d z KY
stamps
D chocolate Insomniac D Bruce J D Viet
Dragon d
[Music]
dun my kitty had to wear onesie but it
was because she was licking stitches oh
yeah that's that's totally like
reasonable to put her in a onesie
because of that Hulu thanks for the
pinky did you know that one lemon
contains as much as Vitamin C there four
lemons what is there a cap are lemons
capped one lemon contains as much
vitamin C as four lemons
is there a cap in how much vitamin C you
can have in one
day
[Music]
n vitamin c
cap
NY
n you just stop absorb yeah that's what
I mean you do stop absorbing past a
certain amount really
H interesting is it the same for other
vitamins or is it just vitamin
[Music]
C we just pee it out you include the
lemon peel lemon juice has four times
more
[Music]
vitamins
oh oh I see see what you
mean interesting random but good
knowledge has been
gained thank you it was so fun to see
you play with the two Hol girls I like
the most after you and froggy waa really
and that's a great combination for you
the only way it could be better is if
froggy Wawa was also part of this
collaboration
a The Mirage uh Acappella video also has
some super chats I quickly finish them
hope you guys enjoyed the
video I want to do more stuff like this
this was
fun interesting experience I mean it
wasn't as much fun for chagy
because something was weird like with
like this
process cuz I was like recording it at a
certain FPS and then it wasn't the FPS
it should be apparently I don't know and
then some other weird stuff was going on
this was kind of cursed but it worked
out
[Music]
fine
cruz7 El D and space water D thank you
[Music]
oh my
God oh my God I am one two three
four five six seven only seven streams
behind and a lot of they're all like
very very small amounts actually six
streams and one of them in a video I
guess pretty much caught up
can maybe catch up some more uh after
Holo
here yeah what are we going to do when I
have no more Super chats to read chat
what what are we going to
do what's going to
happen am I going to
disappear am I going to die what am I
without Super Chat
readings my head hurts still what the
[\h__\h] am I like what's wrong with me
what's with my head
H read food
ingredients I'll just read something
else I'll just read PC specs and stuff
like that
again keep her more names to read yes
just another kfp thank you for giving me
purpose in life
yeah if I run out of super chats I'll
just read the ingredients of my Ami
jelly like
and Sal
rainforest Alliance
[Music]
certified. that already is over what do
I do now what do I read
now well I guess I'll go cuddle my cats
and have dinner and take a shower
tomorrow's stream is pretty late and uh
it will be on shi's channel power wash
is it on
steam power
wash power wash simulator there it is oh
it's not as expensive as I thought for
some reason I thought they would also
sell this for like 60
bucks that would be
insane all right
[Music]
do you guys think I'll get addicted like
the other girls who keep on playing this
game I don't think so I need a game to
give me like more like a
story who knows maybe their story is
there it's good
for yeah know I don't I don't I don't
really think so but this is probably
better for me than an FPS
game yeah four people power wash
simulator collab crazy stuff
[Music]
sh there's actually a story kind
of probably not really
interesting but it will be fun who is
the fourth person other than ah it's on
uh shooting schedule I think it's
sha BB and me are going to play during
European decent
time 1 p.m. wa time want to play power
watch simulator tomorrow so no stream on
my
channel find me there or be square ah
damn it why is going to be on a Tuesday
Tuesday at 90000 p.m. my time Tuesday
tomorrow will be another reveal I think
it's 9:00 p.m. again should be the usual
time but
yeah another uh product reveal should uh
happen on Tuesday cuz V is spacing it
out a little bit more
now but there should be one on
Tuesday all
right
okay and then I shall see you tomorrow
in German we say Al thank you so much
for watching ify love you
[Music]