do
hello
[Music]
don't worry about it who are you all
right see
what a lovely sight you have some nice
bones
examine the skeleton
what a legend today we're playing don't
slive
together and if you guys don't know the
objective of the game you should re-read
the title because it's in the title
we're surprised not starve pretty much
supposed to see how long we can survive
for and that involves
foraging for stuff crafting not getting
lost
and working together as a team as you
can see we've already had some dust here
over on the right
i'll try my best to guide them but i
don't know
the one with the most experience playing
this game i think
we're a little fragile
this is a dog inna found it's so cute
i never seen
so pretty much you just need right out
we'll find stuff you gotta find carrots
mushrooms and when it gets dark we can
go back to the sponge
i think it's getting done if you look up
at the top at the top right corner you
can see there's a little red section
that's just like the twilight
that's like a it's sunset it's not dark
yet
yeah it's not dark dark it's just uh
dark
almost dark yes it's dark it's not dark
it looks like we're going north so yeah
if you get really hungry you can collect
these seeds on the ground and you can
eat them
mushrooms you gotta cook before you eat
them uh or else you'll get sick
oh and
i like my character he looks like um
like a tim burton character like someone
that johnny depp would play yeah
can i not
oh the pumpkins those are pretty useful
so like you can use them for
like uh torches so torches are really
important if you want to travel at night
oh what is this okay these guys are
aggro they're aggro
no oh uh so you know what happens
like around day 14 or so there will be
wolves that will try to come attack us
and we have to fight them so we have to
find wood we got to find trees uh we
gotta find sticks we gotta find rocks
the basics okay
okay it's like minecraft yeah it's like
minecraft yeah
there's a lot of uh if you guys find
locks and also
yeah the poop you can use to make farms
with to fertilize your crops
oh cool of course it's innovative
i'm hot oh my god
yeah it's a little bit like a peninsula
thing i don't think there's anywhere to
go up here
okay we'll go back down we gotta go back
down anyways we get to the spawn
can you eat what what is this you can
catch a bird and eat it but sometimes
it'll only give you feathers instead of
giving you meat ah
a kilogram of feathers
[Music]
oh we're pretty far from spawn so if you
walk on the path go faster
we can hide in the beefalo right
probably
when the wolves attack we can hide there
and then they'll like attack them
and then they'll fight back sorry
bubba's outside
my johnny depp character is saying i'm
so hungry
same oh i have berries for you if me
we'll we'll meet at the spawn
recover my heart though okay
skeleton is still just here all right
here's berries for
whoever is really gonna give you the
valley
you all take them how do i eat them do i
just click on my heart
[Music]
i thought it would be there again oh my
gosh right now
where are we both now company cali if
you if you
if you go to the spawn beacon and you
click on it uh
you can't oh you had six cali yeah i did
we're supposed to make a fire ah yeah i
got it i'll come i'm coming away i think
we're gonna keep dying
no no no it's okay we're okay i got fire
okay i know we had six so next time when
you guys have sticks and flint
you just find it right away on the floor
you can make a torch all right
my stuff okay wait now okay okay okay
i think i got it
oh my gosh he can eat raw carrots so
that's a good thing
oh and picking flowers if you find any
flowers that'll help your brain juice
oh brain juice i need a bit of paint
just wait
did we lose all our stuff yeah
[Music]
and if you pick up 12 flowers you can
make a flower hat
also cool i want a flower hat
character
you have a nice you would look nice in a
flower a flower hat i think
oh it's flowers they have to be the same
flower oh no they just be any
you guys just explore and then i'll make
a vase for us so we don't
die when it turns night again oh
[Music]
how many are we talking uh-huh how many
i think they got boy
how many are i i wonder how we make
weapons
i know okay we can't even
let's see weapons fight it's under fight
you can make a spear
so if you collect uh grass but i need to
make i need to make a
a science machine wait what i'm gonna go
back to this blind i've got seeds don't
eat seeds
you can get this rabbit to come over to
our account i guess we need to find
twists
back for kiara guys i might say loud to
you now because my audience said i'm too
quiet but maybe i'm too loud for you
guys now
now your friends get to meet me perfect
now yes
okay where did everyone go
so that we can kill it how do we gather
twigs
twig if you find uh like a twig bush
it's like a little thing
how do i kill a rabbit what a flower hat
you have to catch it so he makes grass
can you take the grass you can make a
trap and then you can trap the rabbit
and you can kill it with your bare hands
cool i make grass oh you got to go and
collect the grass and you grasp
what we need now if any of you guys have
flint and sticks you can make an
axe and start collecting wood and then
with the wood i can make a machine that
can make us a bunch more stuff
i don't i have an empty elixir do you
need that
uh it kind of sounds useless
all right i'll go back to exploring then
she's on fire i got something that's
useful
guys with fall
fangs fox fangs how did you pronounce
that
faux fangs yeah that sounds like a
halloween costume
[Music]
are these pigs nice they're nice pigs
actually some
some don't attack you you guys never
meet your friends get satisfied i got
carrots i'm scared
usually pigs are like carnivores so you
gotta give them something
okay hello
we got berry bushes nice i should have
collected more rocks
i need all right i'm giving you guys a
job
who's here all right i'm here hello okay
you you take that
you you guys collect wood yeah okay
go chop down some trees will do
oh there's a turkey can i light the
turkey on fire
oh it's dark can i come in can i will
they let me in their house
uh no that you can't go in the house i'm
gonna drop torches at the spawn for you
guys okay or i'll drop
one torch uh you guys take care of it i
think i have
i think i have a light oh yeah if you
have a lighter you you uh
might be able to use it okay i'll stick
with you and then
okay okay that's gura okay and if you
guys don't have any wigs and foot you
can make your own torch too
what does the flower do when you pick up
a flower
it increases your sanity so it's good
and you can also use it to make a hat
it helps your sanity you could use some
flint
is just random on the ground right
oh yeah yeah you can get it from rocks
too uh if you make a pickaxe hunky you
always get flip from rocks
no okay i'm gonna i think i have enough
to um
i need two pieces of wood and six more
rocks to make where is that ghost
permanent fire
oh very wait who is that ghost oh that's
like your friend
that's like your i think it's supposed
to be like your dead sister or something
wow did you see that look there's
something in the ground oh there are
many things there's sticks
i'll take them
there's a dead body over there who is it
[Laughter]
i can build a campfire so i'm going to
go back to the base and i'll build a
campfire there
can you guys go back there yeah let's go
back
okay i see it now let me open it
art style is very cute it is cute it's
all it's
mostly wait
oh another hug i think you have to kill
it i did it
nice wait watch this
you can turn that off uh because you'll
run out of fuel and you're lighter i
think
i don't know i'll still cook stuff here
so if you have like a
mushroom or you can cook seeds to give
you more oh
i have i have carrots you want carrots
you can cook carrots
you just click it in your inventory and
then
click on the fire with it oh
okay everybody stick together no i think
i'm insane by the fire right oh my god
this shadow scared me into the shadow of
the tree skate
i have one here i'll just drop what i
have because i don't know what it does
here okay yep we got a glove
there's a monkey paw what does that do
you can make a wish
i don't know i don't know actually i
don't know what that does is
tell us usually in the night time
[Music]
oh i have you cooked berries ah
i think you can you can cook pretty much
everything i'm
fleeing i have butterfly wings cooked
carrots here licorice for the butterfly
wings
oh i was about to cook you're over the
fireplace you did it wrong
if you press q and e oh somebody gave me
carrots yes
you're gay i eat it oops i thought i
thought you dropped
we survived
uh you can make healing potion but uh
it's a bit difficult so like
if you find a spider web you wanna
you wanna collect spiderweb from the
spider nest
and uh it's kinda dangerous but once you
build traps
out of grass you can catch the spiders
and they give you spiderweb and use that
to make a fishing rod
and you catch fish and then the fish
make they make good heal
snacks oh okay and they heal you yeah i
got binoculars
fun binoculars that sounds really good
[Music]
i don't think that i don't think yeah i
don't think we can use that
the tree just died i saw that that was
just
good that wasn't me that wasn't mine
that wasn't mine
that wasn't mine uh so yeah you're
probably in the swamp areas in the swamp
area if you walk by
too slow uh there were tentacles in i've
got your stuff yeah
okay maybe not yeah thank you what the
heck what is that
what what what is this oh wait i'll
stick
i'll go i guess you guys have any wood
has anybody collected some wood yeah i
have
a tent i have ten oh okay
i'll take stuff i'm gonna go we were
friends tentacles
yeah what is this
[Music]
stage hand it's like a table with some
flowers around it
oh uh don't touch don't take the flower
don't
but i did i did take a flower
you should be able to see whether your
sanity is going down actively and if it
is it might be that the thing you picked
up
it's hard i think there's a frog on my
tail
okay stomach okay brain
yes what is the other one
uh stomach brain and health so much for
no not november i can plant a tree i
found
nuts okay uh yeah
some some of the tree nuts you can eat
them but sometimes if you don't plan
okay bad things will happen bad things
yeah i have to pick them up but i have a
full inventory
i got your lighter oh okay
that's the only thing i could see from
there
all right i'm out i brought you some
wood
oh thank you i already got some um but
i'll pick it up if you just leave it
there
[Music]
rocks
as well no you got to make a pickaxe and
there's
a minute left no it's pretty easy i bet
you have enough to make it
leads to my new friend what freeze
jimmy no goddamn why did the rabbit
sound like
he died
need one more rock a turkey i found a
big turkey
kill it i'm killing it's a cat with the
x oh yeah
i won't give up i'm used to chasing
things with sharp objects uh-oh
if you guys get there and uh there's no
fire you just put grass or wood or
anything that you can burn in
in the fire and it'll work
i'll get big ones just go okay i could
really use some
fellas are the pigs dangerous
uh the ones who try to attack you are
dangerous
there are some nice pigs okay you'll
know right away
actually the pigs if you give them like
a piece of meat to eat they'll be your
friend
and they'll trap they'll chop trees for
you oh
i'll have a sweet of
if them guys are standing near this
science machine i made here you'll see
that new tabs appeared
on the left side so now you can make
like rope you can refine
you can make rope you can use that to
make traps and you can catch bunnies and
spiders and
frogs thanks for the dr stone
nice going watson i'm
literally carrying now yes i was going
to say
thank you amelia most helpful
you just put it down on the ground and
it'll like be automatic
okay i'm gonna go get some more rabbits
it's gonna get dark soon just be careful
oh these little okay mama oh hello
my mom okay oh kyrie
oh kyrie i guess we should collect some
poops
[Laughter]
i think jamaica to make farms well you
need the seeds that you get and then
stones and fertilizer but uh oh yeah
right here food you can just make one
here
oh yeah we have enough that our camp is
just surrounded by skrellingtons
we can't destroy the skeletons you can
it feels like home
really like decorative yeah they're a
reminder of
our our humble beginnings how about this
yellow oh a backpack
you can make it uh uh you gotta refine
your rope
and then i think it's under survival you
can make uh or
the other one yeah it's under survival
you can make one oh
not the candy bag no it might be grayed
out because it might not have enough
things on fire that's not rope it's just
uh
it's just grass i think there's a more
advanced backpack you can make with that
can you make things like chess oh in
this in this game
yeah you can make chests oh
the night is going to progressively get
longer and longer and so you just have
to survive
you can kind of still explore at night
if you have like a torch or something
uh but it's better to just stay here and
cook or sleep you can make a sleeping
bag and sleeping at
in the night time it increases your
sanity levels if you're getting low
yeah okay um
i think my sanity levels are always low
yeah sometimes it's hard
what was that what was that
what was that if anybody ever wants to
sleep there's a sleeping bag here but
it's better not to do it now because
it's going to turn day time and you'll
wake up immediately but you can do it
when it's in the red
the sunset time you can sleep then too
[Music]
all right i'll work on on trying to heal
if you guys want to fight stuff if you
find any spiders
you can trap the spiders you can fight
them uh
and then we can use the spiderweb and
and we'll go fishing
okay idea okay bye bye
all right we'll meet up again at night
okay sounds good i'll go follow you
i'll go do some important
i do put it down anywhere around the
pond and then go
near that frog and make it aggressive
and like tease him you want to taunt him
and and then he'll follow you
and you look ugly
[Laughter]
and walk over the chat past it tongue
looks funny
my sanity smells bet you smell like one
oh you got them
awesome now you got frog legs you can
cook it and eat them oh yummy
not raw though you don't want to eat
them
[Music]
yeah we gotta make a chest and like
store food in there or something because
yeah oh god you have seeds here
eat seeds you're a bird you can eat
seeds
yummy but i prefer fried chicken you
know
so i don't think there's any chicken in
this game but there are turkeys pretty
similar yeah i did
why are we tired of streaming i saw our
turkey you can't run i've cornered him
i've cornered him oh no yeah turkey's
scared
no it's in the water
now you can't have
next to the the sea oh and
no fish it's not for you pick up soggy
drumstick no it's not for you
i keep running towards the water and
it's not letting me pick up the
oh uh yeah you can't go into the water
unless you have a boat
kelly yeah you can make boats and we can
like sail the scene but
it's pretty dangerous so i don't think
we're ready for that yet
yeah as long as we have good eye the sea
is not dangerous for us
ah that's true
she is made for that yes oh yeah all at
the same time
[Music]
i desperately need food god damn it
uh okay i'll go back i'll have have some
food we should we should make them
we should make a crock pot we gotta burn
trees crock pots
a crock pot yeah
and you can you can put four ingredients
in there you can make all these like
different
recipes and stuff and then you can make
like cupcakes you can make meatballs
eggs sandwiches and lettuce
fried turkey how about that fried turkey
try make a turkey meal i don't i think
you can make chicken nuggets you can
make chicken nuggets really
yeah but you need honey from bees oh i
just literally ate my honey
oh it's really good for heels so chicken
nuggets they give you like a lot of hp
i did it didn't though it did not the
honey by itself
yeah ah okay oh well
oh we're gonna build something now nice
where is
uh we want to make a functioning base we
got to have like
a food source we got to have somewhere
to store the food
and we got to have defense stuff so if
you guys want to like
recipes and stuff on the left side make
whatever you want
yeah i'll help you i am not lost
i am i got to monster me dad are you
lost
i am already back i think oh yeah you're
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe i have something useful for you uh
i have a bunch of rocks
and twigs maybe i should keep them here
uh yeah you can use it to build stuff if
you want
huh cool are you okay good
we're back
okay we're good i got some meat
uh if anybody wants to sleep if you're
if your brain juice is low you can pick
up this sleeping bag here and you can
start sleeping now but it it'll take
your hunger so you got to make sure you
got like a
decent amount of your weight i think
i'll wait with that and not do it right
now
yeah i'm really hungry uh oh
i didn't notice how hungry i was i do
have one
uh chicken legs though
oh we could have made chicken nuggets
[Music]
i think uh i ate some bad meat there we
go
uh-oh didn't know i had said something
so useful
the whole time i can make a compass is
that useful one in the pickaxe
i don't think so all right i mean we
haven't we have a map so it's not it's
here we didn't need it i made a pickaxe
oh why are these lanterns lit up are
they always were they always lit up
no i put them there and the moment
why is the game audio getting louder is
it is something
it's here's something too i don't know i
only hear the flies from the poop
there we go i was like those flies are
really loud
really oh callie do you have any wood i
can make chests we can put some stuff
away i have a ton of i have logs
yeah yeah yeah there you go thank you
wow welcome i did a lot of chopping
today
okay we have you have enough to make one
now
rope chest hey whoa let's put the chest
over here pick up flowers where are
flowers
oh uh there there are some flowers down
at south and to
the east also
it's still not night right now right
it's still twilight oh it's about the
time tonight
you guys ever have any wood you can add
uh
you can add uh planks to it and it'll
like make this big fire like this
oh i have planks i can make a i can make
a chest does anybody do we need another
chest i'm gonna die
oh yeah the chest the chest don't you
know what the face is behind me
oh this is a heartbeat horror game yeah
it's like a half moon right now so maybe
it won't be
bad run what can i come meet you
there's a table following me the table
where i took the flower from
uh did the table follow me though no i
don't i don't see it
what are you talking about it was there
it was there i'm not crazy oh it's there
you do this oh
look at my table do you see my table as
well
[Music]
actually if you make a hammer you might
be able to oh
might be able to yeah
yeah i didn't know that uh getting nice
and warm really close to the fire would
do that burn
i get i have a job for you come here
okay
come on right here flowers i'm really
looking like johnny depp all right take
this oh god don't equip it yet but take
it
listen all right okay don't equip me
yeah and now i want you to come over
here
equip it and set these these scraggly
trees on fire
oh but of course wait
oh i'm happy you finished that yes that
was not edible i got them and
i'll please um
what a waste of wood yeah you're telling
me you can catch
any frogs you know have you have you
tried that before i can show you how
oh yes i did i got it
so if you find a frog by a pond you just
put the trap down anywhere near the frog
and then you
you bait the frog into into walking into
the trap oh
i look perfect now i can't
wow my ghost is so smart they killed it
killed my my frogs for me
oh yeah the ghost will attack your stuff
like
enemies enemies i love my ghosts my
ghost is amazing
flints nice i said nice
cali heck thank you i think so too
looking good
cute where did i even get my ghost from
i don't know
i don't i mean you don't have the pose
right it's like some crystal ball
i love the question kiara you don't you
don't have to you play the same
character but you don't have the ghost
right
oh yeah because uh if you there's like a
flower in my inventory and if i click on
it i can summon the ghost but i have i
just haven't done it yet i probably
should
[Music]
oh wait hungry found a bunch of good
stuff
need one more flower to make a hat
yeah let's all get matching flower hats
perfect
83 but my hunger is still uh not very
good looking yeah i'm making crock pots
now so we can make more stuff
did you want me to show you how to catch
the froggies although i i
think i got it
okay nice try a loser
that's a really daring looking giraffe
von drake what was that again
sometimes what an excellent one what is
this i don't know
why is all the audio getting louder
is something hey am i dying what
uh oh that must be insanity what's your
sanity levels at kira
which one is that hover over the brain
with your mouse it'll tell you a number
thirty
thirty oh okay uh where are you come to
me
i'll give you a present
makes me sleep i found a man racket
oh yeah you can kill it but yeah it'll
make you sleep if you eat it is that the
whole thing i mean i kind of do need to
clean
uh here you go ah where are that
they're poisonous thank you
you're welcome and oh my god
we need to kill rabbits we need to kill
frogs
and we need stuff to fill the crock pot
with
make meatballs some weapons oh i have uh
i have some mushrooms
yeah yeah yeah any vegetables or like
carrots that you find
that's right carrots i'm coming with
kids let me hunt
i just need like a few more twigs and i
can make one i need three more twigs
does anybody have to tell you i am
wings i
or control click on something uh you can
have it and then
oh okay drop it yeah cool
how big is this map like this uh it is
oh yeah it's pretty big you gotta move
your dog in the side
that i found like somebody pick up this
what is this on the ground
crystal ball thingy
[Music]
uh usually like it's
as long as you don't put anything edible
in there it should make something
exciting if you put too much monster
music
chester oh chester yeah
i thought that yeah wait who found
chester you
chester
[Music]
ah no i have a ton okay thank you
um what's it oh there's there's okay
there's no fire ah we can cook it there
now okay yeah yeah so if you put a bunch
if you can put like different vegetables
and stuff together there you go
different recipes it doesn't tell you
the recipes
why are you dying i don't know
oh it's the insanity monsters
oh yeah all right i went to sleep
[Music]
i'm very hungry as well wait do we have
anything cooking okay i'll make
something with you
yeah oh okay yes chef yeah
why am i so hungry i'm just gonna put
monster meat in there
oh the monster meets this oh does
anybody have what is this
maybe they can cook it okay i'll just
make four kids oh no
you guys can cook your seeds if you cook
if you cook your stuff does that give
you back more
more hunger bad oh maybe not actually i
think it does
i think it does what i was looking at
was hp
weapons because i feel like if i had a
weapon then i could kill a bunch of
things and get us a bunch of meat
well actually there's a spear right here
on the floor i don't know whose this is
but
you see this spirit i'm standing next to
it you can pick it up and you can use
that you can equip it you can attack
stuff
cool okay let me see how i let me try
and pick it up who's who's the hungriest
right now what are you what are you guys
hungry levels 55
oh what's the one next to i think it's
stuck in the skeleton
what
oh okay i make a uh i'm sleeping
i need rocks to make a hammer does
anybody have rocks oh flint
i have so much good stuff but i see i
see the rock
i see i'm going to take your rocks get
it yeah i'm feeling
refreshed i stopped to like really well
damn and now i'm full hungry now
i can get you today thanks let's go
oh sorry to have you make everything
watson oh it's okay
i promise i'll kill a bunch of things oh
oh this is nice
and it's gone never mind well i think
oh i have some grass
i just okay to go bottom left
i'm going for bottom left oh i'm super
hungry let's see
uh what can i eat we jumped over my
truck
yeah cool
oh seeds nice nice
no pygmy kiss
you perfect i'll go kill some things
welcome here we go
will they will they kill me for doing
that i wonder um
man i need them no leave my ghost alone
come with me ghosty
come on come with me don't kill oh i
can't do that okay
um
wait so the stuff everything like
respawns every day
uh not every day there's like a cycle
some depending on what it is it might
take a few days to come back
so yeah not every day yeah
what the
ah there you go since when are frogs so
dangerous
yeah they take items from you too when
they attack you oh you're
choking
[Music]
you're kidding me oh i gotta run i found
this factor nest
um ah anyway the pig is so nice to try
to kill the spiders for me
uh he killed maybe one i got some silk
oh nice
stuff ooh what
did that treat just like stuff stuff is
[Music]
good
i probably shouldn't try to kill the
spiders on my own right it's probably
gonna kill me
uh you don't have to kill them you can
you can make uh the flower traps
sorry i don't always have flour you can
make the grass traps and then you can
put them down on the ground and then
walk into the traps and
oh my god oh i killed all the spiders
you killed oh with your ghost no with my
ghost and my pickaxe i got like a bunch
of
and spinach and silk be careful with the
meat because
that meat you have to you can put like
one in each recipe in the crock pot
otherwise it'll make you sick
okay hey uh amelia how does one make a
trap
catch the rabbits uh you need
uh grass and twigs and then you gotta go
next to the science machine in the base
found it okay i think that's maybe the
next thing i gotta try to do damn
my ghost how do you catch a rabbit do
you just put the jackpot
yeah it's kind of hard to catch one
because like they're so
fast but what you can do is uh you want
to put the trap stand on the hole and
then put the trap like right on the hole
so then when they go back in and when
they come out
they they trigger the trap and they run
into it
damn he really hurts big brain
it's a big trouble because i'm super
hungry right now i'm trying to catch
these rabbits but uh
i'm so happy hatching rabbits is more of
like a long term thing like
uh huh you can't catch them right away
you probably have to come back and
check on the trap like a day later like
a real trap
oh my good it's fine i'll find other
things to kill
if you find um spiders you can kill
those you can kill
frogs the turkeys moles there's like
little mole wrap thingies
cool oh that mushroom is happy to see me
look at that you can't go back home
there's so many spiders
i'm gonna die can you eat spiders asking
people i have
spider meat yeah oh yeah
yeah okay i'm going back now
and we can cook some stuff so we can all
eat
let's have dinner tomorrow my ghost
keeps like putting up a fight with these
spiders but it's
like killing everything legitimately wow
so strong ah i love my ghosts
[Music]
i can't double shoot
yeah okay uh i'll make food now
cute chef puppet yeah that's
you let's go home why shouldn't eat that
rainbow
well the mandrakes are really good they
like give you i didn't know they give
you full hp and full hair yeah
sleep so wake me up completely
who's dying oh
when this thing comes out of the of the
crock pot you can eat it
thank you thanks watson uh okay i'll
make it up to you
i'll actually kill a bunch of things
you'll see okay
you'll see i will be useful
wait did my experience
oh some sort of sandwich oh it's a teddy
bear i was wondering what that was
that was nice wow
is dropping it's not too low though
goddammit i was picking a fight abigail
can we just can we just live in
happiness together with these creatures
peace was never enough i wonder if the
other way to like unsummon the ghosts
because i
i know you have to summon it i don't
know if it'll ever go away though there
must be a way
hmm
if you guys ever need more storage you
can pick up this bone and
this little chester guy this little
monster doggy
he'll follow you and if you click on him
he has a storage
oh yeah rock
oh nice i got tools now baby yes
progress baby all right so if uh
i can give you guys some tasks if you're
like what should i do what should i do
yeah you know i'll give you some tests
um yes your task is to go collect
a bunch of rocks and there's a rock area
you go to the east and then and you go
south
yes now it's a it's a whole rock area i
don't know if you can see it on the map
but
it's like a desert looking area you can
collect all oh yes
yes okay uh how do we boost our sanity
again
fish trade something about uh boosting
sanity you have to sleep but if you
are hungry then uh you'll wake up
immediately or you can collect flowers
but man picking bars really happens with
your sanity if you find anything i think
i have okay
i will do that but there's a there's a
sleeping bag it'll be in the chest
oh i'm sleeping once okay good
well uh is it when as soon as it reaches
morning you'll wake up so you just wanna
next time when you sleep you sleep in
the red time
at the start you get as much out of the
sleeping bag as possible wait a minute
more those are really
um okay
chat does it look like it could be
something uh delicious
it's time to kill things take out the
butterfly
if you guys collect any vegetables or
mushrooms or berries those are things
uh that you can put in a crock pot i'm
not sure
yeah and you just make it'll make like
meatballs if you have two meats in there
and those are really
healing look at this
nope wait how do you put it got that
jeans
to put that in the crock pot not my
mouth
i think we might um be getting attacked
soon i thought i heard it yeah
oh yeah oh what what
[Music]
does it happen to look like a giant
teddy bear
yes
i'm looking for flowers to pick and i
don't see it
run north follow the path north and go
into the beefalos and like stan
i need more berries
[Music]
okay it's gone now it's gone
okay i'm still looking for flowers i
definitely need flowers
wolves incoming oh i don't have a good
feeling about this oh
can i make with this i hear the movies
yeah see you guys just come come up
north follow the path and
run into the beefalo you'll be safe okay
can we kill the wolves
yeah you can attack them quick run into
these woods
you can make armor oh or you can make
grass armor too i'll make some grass
oh they're they're coming
it's armor huh okay i can make that oh
god this is so bad oh dear
oh run go to hide oh wait what is it
what is that now it's the
the river the wolves oh when they
started
you guys just run north i made i made
two fishing rods if someone wants to
have one another here
they're here oh
[Music]
and i dropped all my berries
thank you for protecting me
i had like two wolves running up to me
but my ghost protected me
and now i'll go fishing sorry kelly i
stole it
are you still alive
should i can i fish anywhere or should i
go to fish somewhere where i see some
shadows in the uh you also want to fish
in the pond so we have upon a
pond a pond pretty close to spawn oh
yeah
yeah you'll see how it works it's just
like fishing in the game okay
i'm coming back for myself are you here
you know
oh i'm very far i just kept running
much this flimsy rock what
nice job kelly yeah that was interesting
you got food yeah so when you make the
recipes in a crock pot you can only
put a little oh oh no i'm really not
doing well huh oh why is the earth
shaking question should i can i eat this
you can eat meteorites oh
number one meteor
oh lol okay i think i can survive on my
own
okay happy navy seats it's okay
it happens to the past only fish in
ponds okay wasn't that a pond ah
you mean the really small ones
one second i gotta get the berries so i
can make more what was it
crock pot oh yeah yeah yeah in the crock
pot
what is that oh no there are wolves at
the campsite
are you sent ah watch out should i come
to kill them
yes i'll use my ghost too
oh you also have a ghost now it's
killing chester
chester
now i get the joke behind chester
finally
because he's a chance
that's like an enoch pun ina did you
suggest that name to the game
uh your ghost looks different oh they
want to say
it was a an ineffective
[Music]
right can you cook never mind that's a
stupid question
you can put that like some food but
it'll it'll change into something less
uh filling like only one stick you can
put
oh okay
can someone light up the the crock-pot
oh i think it just goes automatically
once you put enough stuff in it
ah there we go no oh oh who put in those
carrots
me
[Music]
is it cookies i can build a shovel
or a pitchfork why did i eat it
oh i ate the monster meat oh no i'm
doing fine though yeah
yeah you're fine my mistakes
i can make a pickaxe i can make a shovel
what should i make
if i can make a pitchfork i can make a
razor oh
why would i wouldn't shave my face
though my face is perfect
that's a long shadow i think you can
shave your beard and like put it
oh oh it's here right now we need
food you know
i didn't need now sure why do you oh
wait i mean
i need uh uh i need some face
i want skins too
the server will drop you like some stuff
you can put like different clothes
okay are you talking about armor you
want armor no i want the skins
but also armor and i still don't
understand how i can make it back what
exactly do i need that doesn't look good
i only think thank you what is that okay
it's a hand that's trying to grab our
fire
why is everything what is the
where is this game like what is the
story where's the what's
the lord ah i don't know
actually i don't know what it is i don't
know maybe chad can tell us
what's the lore chad what is the lore
there is no lord
trap here all right i tell you what we
need we can
uh we need to build an alchemy machine
but to build an alchemy machine
we need electric dudettes and you can
get those by like smashing
sometimes you might just find them but
you gotta like smash some stuff that you
find like that
there's like really weird gear stuff you
can you can make a refrigerator in this
game but
i don't remember how to get all the
materials for it a refrigerator
refrigerator yeah because your food your
food has a
shelf life
[Applause]
i will not let you get away
[Music]
it's a turkey
i eat you with berries that's how it's
supposed to be
okay
wait where is everyone i am in rockland
i'm in frogland okay go hydrated how do
we stay hydrated in this game
i got it did you also just get a super
chat saying stay hydrated
at the same time they're telling us to
stay hydrated how sweet of them thank
you
all right thank you i need to drive the
rabbits away from where the holes are
i put my trap here
anyway okay i shall stay hydrated
by the way rabbit the other way
okay i'm making a bunch of food yeah
have you caught anything
i'm gonna get another flip so i can get
a picture
mm-hmm why not
oh my god oh my god oh
my god i got so much stuff
so many frog legs oh my god
walking into the wall i murdered it
i have so much food that's more that's a
pond
wait drop that finally eat can i rock
and eat at the same time
no that was
oh i'm fishing for the first time in my
life oh
i should go back i got two rabbits how
are you doing on food
murder i'm good
favorite okay i have two gloves can i
make something now
abigail chill uh some ice i don't know
you can yeah
i just oh
all right we're making a rabbit tonight
baby
identity how are we gonna go backwards
yeah should go back to my grasp
why can't i cook them i have this wait
uh cook what i'm trying to cook the
rabbits that i killed but i only have
two ah did you i have a
yeah i don't have anything to put in
there you need to fill the rest of the
slots it's got to be four so if you have
like berries or carrots or mushrooms
one monster meat or one stick you can
put those in there
okay you know you can see what i can do
yeah
[Music]
oh you can put it in the crock pot if
you want it'll make them uh
no tasty meatballs
i really want meatballs now hungry hey i
don't know how
how how does it work the fishing
yeah it says hook and then i click on it
one time or
um uh yeah yeah you uh
put it in the pond and then there we go
minecraft oh my god
i never i never even fished in minecraft
i have
i got a fresh water fish now
oh here i don't want to eat all these
meatballs myself i'm hungry
it has meatballs too oh okay me too
i'm saving my meatballs
okay if we find any spider glands we can
make like this uh
potion as a healing potion oh we need
spider glands
allen do you need food am i good for now
i'm gonna wait till it gets real low and
then i'll eat my meatballs
yeah oh cool good idea i'm gonna attend
some more rabbits
that was fun you think just like green
i brought some ice what can we do with
ice
make some tasty drinks i think you can
make
like a you can use it in recipes i know
you can put it in the crock pot but
i don't know i think you might be able
to make uh ice cream or like some sort
of drink with it too
you gotta have like a different ice
cream
yeah you can make cupcakes in this game
and you um
like look up the rest you gotta like
google the dress
oh wait a saddle does that mean you can
ride stuff you can like
uh i don't know maybe murder
now you can ride a boat yes it's
[\h__\h] not with us yeah not with a
saddle
oh my god that was that was funny
looking
yeah what what no you did like a weird
pose oh i messed up
[Music]
a gorilla i'm just eating okay
gotta turn it you're cute i'm trying to
not starve okay
i like you better understand about hey
there's nothing wrong with starving we
all have flower crowns
oh i can make some fruits yeah
it's not the team i really want to grow
the beard so i really look like a real
johnny depp camera
you can also then you can shave the
beard and like turn it into a jacket or
something like a bed
legendary science music all right
maybe we should build a boat if you guys
want to like work towards something we
can build the
idea yeah let's go build the boat
okay actually i'm gonna go catch some
more rabbits but you guys talk about
building the boat while i go catch these
rapids
okay that's good
i just
[Music]
we need a bunch of wood to make boats so
as much wood as you can collect
that you like chop the one yeah
yeah all right no not my macbook finally
in the backpack finally 10 years later
congratulations just took me five
million years
birth trap who would ever make a bird
trap those poor birds
oh you're asking how to get uh chicken
that's how you get uh some chicken you
get a little uh
a chicken legs from them no no no no no
that's not a good way
no too much they're um their area
oh wait i love the i love the chop down
there i wonder if anything got caught in
it
top
ah how much wood do we need
a bunch of wood you can get
yeah okay
now we probably need like uh
uh probably like 30 or 40.
oh my goodness if well if we all get
like 10.
that's not that bad yeah yeah hmm
i should probably store some more things
i still got all my silk and spider
glands
oh i can heal my lungs farm glands is
that for the heart or for the hunger
oh yeah yeah it's for uh healing it's
fine we can make like a healing sound
for anybody who's low hp
and you just it's really easy you just
need rocks and ash and i have some ash
so
oh
little bushes or grass twigs anything
you put on the floor will probably turn
into ash
oh do i burn it down with my torch yeah
oh just gotta make sure fire travels
like between things you gotta make sure
like if you don't wanna burn down the
forest or all of our stuff for example
you gotta do it far away
fire doesn't hurt me no problem you just
hold space
you can hold space and it doesn't okay
oh you hold space
yeah oh i didn't know i kept clicking
[Music]
the burning oh yeah it takes a while
murder damn another two rabbits
i'm starting to get that catching
rabbits
oh you caught a few yep
nice i think i have a rabbit trap here
you're kidding me
goddammit burning the tree thing didn't
work
oh yeah you gotta you gotta burn like
little things like a
like a grass bush or if you have twigs
you can
you can drop individual twigs uh i think
with
my button i see okay i got the grass
okay yeah i don't remember where i
pulled my rabbit trap oh no
i think you should you might be able to
see it on the map maybe oh
good good uh maybe i have it i think did
you find it like
oh no let me get it back to you that's
what i've been using the whole time to
catch wrap
no it's totally fine
you can have the meatballs that we that
we make with the
rabbit's like cotton
oh gosh i keep going the wrong way
i was just like man i really lose stuff
so easy
gosh here i'm dropping it on the ground
no no no no no it's only got 25 percent
if you want to catch more go for it i
don't know no
i don't even know how to use it really
oh sorry oh you're good you're good do
your thing ena
your thing i'm glad we have enough stuff
to put inside the pot
yeah i just put a lot of berries and
like meat i'm hunting because it's
simple and and i can do it give me here
i can make a sleeping bag oh okay
all right
it's under survival under the little
rope it's like at the top
it's called healing south
oh okay got it
whoa eggs
good night
wow i'm like a professional survivor
damn
almost done
wow ah i need your wood goodness can you
wake up
my what the wood oh the wood i have no
one for you
do i feel well i'm amazed with myself
i think this is because my mom was like
a survivor mom so
i think i learned it from him i have a
survival mom
really she taught me the ways yeah she
can do anything
with no tools she survives in the in the
wilderness
cool insane yeah my mom is a survivor
mom
you're probably watching right now they
have been sad you were cool
hi mom
[Music]
i don't know it's the third one four
three two one it's oh it's hunger
[Music]
i thought you needed eggplant for that
ah yeah um requires more science
oh god what is this music it's another
trap it's like the hand they're trying
to steal our fire you gotta step on them
okay hey that's where you try
yeah you will lose something i'm gonna
cut them up just like the in the german
fairy tales
is terrified by german fairy tales oh my
god look there
i have limits okay listen i want this
plain cone
oh wait it's interesting that things
spoil in this game too
yeah i gotta cook my monster meat god
damn it i need some
some very [\h__\h] stuff i have berries
i'll put
i'll put three berries
[Music]
okay i need to look for a suitable place
to put
our water stuff i think this is
no this is not the ocean what we might
make another base
by the water because that's we're gonna
put the boat ah
wait do you have my wood i took it
okay it's mine very nice boil if i leave
it at the base
i gotta try it i'm gonna build it i
don't know what it does oh
i think you can pick up land with it i
put one
one meat in the pot if someone wants to
add berries you can make a crock pot
what's that pink i just need some stone
and i can move stuff over oh i'm i'm
on my way to get some snow now i'll
bring something
stop wait yes don't you know why are you
collecting some stones oh yeah i have
seven
rocks oh can i have some oh yes
i'm on my way back oh okay
i need my potion again that's fine i'll
survive because i have my ghosts
i'll leave them in the chest oh
my god
oh yeah i have a [\h__\h] ton of frog legs i
got 16 frog legs
if someone needs food i i got too much
[Music]
oh you can make a sand you can make frog
like sandwiches with those
oh hell no have you guys ever had real
frog like before
from what i've heard that just tastes
like that i tried it once but it was at
like a really
uh shady buffet it tasted really close
oh my god
i'm not surprised it sure was really
frogly
oh snails it was a frog like it was a
frog like yeah
yeah it's like frozen hmm i haven't i've
had snails before
is it what's gonna call it escargot
oh very fancier nice
i prefer fried chicken but okay you go
with what you like
not surprised can i kill this frog so
what exactly do we need to make a frog
sandwich i got to the frog
wrap it
does someone want um some meat
like actual cooked meat
the meatballs are in the chest if
someone needs them
oh darn it what is what is oh ice never
mind i'm dumb
wait that didn't even make a sandwich
then made the same thing as before
and sitting out of the game
no no darn it
yeah that was expected give me my trap
okay
i got so much
[Music]
thank you so if i put four meats into
the pot will it still only make one
meatballs for everyone
uh yeah yeah so it's good to like uh
there's like a balance so if you put
like two meats and two vegetables it
should make meatballs but if you
put like too many vegetables and it'll
be like a vegetable-based dish
you can use filler like uh monster meat
you can put one monster meat in but if
you put more than one it'll turn into
like monster lasagna and it'll take away
hp
lasagna yeah
if you put a stick in there it'll make a
like a kebab or something kebab oh
it's fish then it makes fish sticks
oh they all sound delicious to be honest
i'm so hungry
i'm starving i'm gonna want them again
um i'm confused because i definitely
killed three things today and i only
have
one morsel in my pocket
okay that's what we need to do anyway
there are two
things in the pot so we can i was gonna
make a boat but we're not really close
to the water so if we made a boat it'd
be like a long journey with you
i bet you know what i bet i was trying
to put them into the pot and i ate them
god
bite me don't see it
we're gonna go here we go
yeah you can yeah yeah put them in
oh yeah i can let's try and make it oh
it's time to cook okay okay that's
good yeah as long as you don't put
anything like weird in there it should
make like
some sort of recipe
a lot today i don't know why
cute noises everywhere
uh well we have like stored meatballs
here too in the chest
hold on someone is at my is up my abode
i will be back in just a moment
okay don't die it's getting night now
okay i should go back oh my god oh
my god like nights oh it's still bright
oh that is okay yeah yeah
oh your sanity might go down but
it won't be too bad oh thank god i'm too
far away from my heart
anyway
ah there is an ocean it's to the north
we'd have to i have to make a new base
up there
hmm
[Music]
oh wow thank you this is smart enough
abigail
[Music]
what don't kill my ghost
what i'm over here oh yeah i i killed
them
that wasn't me that was me
it was the ancient ones i know it's kind
of hungry
i have no responsibility for what they
do
so when we make the meatballs does it
make one for everyone or is it just one
meatball
yeah it's just it's just one set of
meatballs it's like one dish
that's terrible that makes me
sad we should have enough for everyone
well there's some extra meatballs in the
chat so if people get hungry they got
food there
yeah okay well i'm gonna go catch some
more things and kill some more okay
i'm building another bank stuff whatever
how is that can i help i don't know what
to do
yeah you can you can come with me could
uh help me make decisions about the
okay where are you just up out up north
yeah by the beefalo
no it's your death no no abigail wait
can abigail die
when she's already dead will she come
back though i wonder
i found uh i found the ancient ones um
oh
oh dear bye bye abigail you're not gonna
survive that
or maybe you are well let's try hello
beefalo
i love your dead
should be fine i picked a fight that was
too dangerous to me
yes i got an interesting one i see you i
think
what the hell was all that that's not a
black rabbit
oh okay oh nightmare
it turned into nightmare fuel do you
have any wood
uh i have twigs
okay i go get wood i only need two so
you just want to treat it
oh man is there any way for me to get
abigail my best friend
back what happened to her yeah she got
killed by the ancient ones
while she she walked it on on them
how do i make this my sanity higher
because i'm unable to kill rabbits now
oh uh flowers you gotta sleep uh you can
make a sleeping bag with grass
i think you just need grass okay cool
i'll do that
thunder survival at the bottom
grass had a rope but you see we're fine
at the science machine oh okay
sure i can make a rope already i think
oh well i could
if you made one once then you can just
make one again
oh
pick a rope with grass there's a battery
cali
oh god oh god do the rabbits look normal
to you gouda
they look brown and fuzzy to me a flower
when your saturday when your sanity gets
slow it starts to change how the
monsters look
yeah oh
[Music]
sleeping and picking flowers okay oh
that's a good idea i want to pick some
flowers my crown's
gone so i'm gonna how do i make a flower
i'm so hungry like uh outside of the
game like actually hungry i'm so hungry
go get some chicken yeah after after the
stream
i need anything else i need a ton of
wood
okay i get more wood yes thank you i
have an axe i should probably
i should probably chop some darn it
sure sleeping bag i can make you one
oh thank you please
[Music]
okay i'll leave it at the base okay
there we go
here you go thank you all the flowers
are gone
good night good night
i can't type that dad in the chat
where's my chat
you
[Music]
did you forward slash dance
i thought it would chop faster if i
helped but i guess not i don't know if
it does maybe it does kind of seem like
it did
oh my axe is gone that was a funny noise
uh where's my where is it where is it
there
yeah i was able to make a rope before
i could really use a healing potion i
got like one heart left
hmm ah uh yeah you could you could
tell you had a spider gland right yeah i
still have two spider glands left yeah
and you need to work
sleeping bag with me oh i would love to
but it's gone
it's one use yeah so
i'll make you another one i'll make you
another one really wants it i'm sorry i
wouldn't no
i want to be healed that's okay i have a
bunch of grass
actually i need two more grass i have
some here
hold on here we go
whoever picked up the bone who was the
one who picked up the bone
you know i don't know
[Laughter]
okay he just appeared here he's cute
weird yes what's going on i'm gonna you
can take him
yeah i already have i already have
wobbly
yeah that would be dope
you just salute me
wait halfway i need to pick more flowers
again i wonder why the table hasn't
tried to uh
f word with us yet hey i think you have
to like maybe it's because kiara took
the flower
she has to be near it when i step on the
hands when you see them
look how peaceful cali looks yeah
nice night night johnny dance night
night
did you give me
what's happening oh what is that
what was i doing yeah
oh step on that okay i've been stopping
stuffing me
go away monsters i'm scared
i gotta protect talent from the monsters
thank you kiana i do appreciate it
i appreciate your sleeping child no no
i'm real hungry
that's not great here you're losing um
[Music]
i think i think your boy might die
he's coming to you you always want to
eat the seeds
oh yeah yeah i have the ash that you
that you're talking about
yeah real hungry while sleeping huh a
good one yeah
it looks it's like a trade-off you get
more brain juice but less
yeah you can put them in a crock pot uh
you can put one stick frog leg and then
fillers like berries or carrots
you have been fed
thank you for the assistance you're
welcome
i do appreciate it if you make an
alchemy engine
oh yeah uh well you need gold to make
the little i have enough to make it but
i was just waiting to make it up at the
base up top because uh
i'm making a new base up there ah okay
i'm gonna make one right now if you want
to follow me
uh i'm gonna make it right now uh where
are you
north i'm going north follow the path
yeah
planting trees we did by the way
reach one and a half hour yeah yeah
it has been fun we should do it again
sometimes yeah one part two
one part two is it if we leave the
server is it gonna stay like that
uh it pauses as soon as i shut it down
so as soon as i exit the game everything
will be uh exactly as we left it
so we can go back to that state that's
awesome yeah but i actually don't
remember
it should be fine
maybe she'll be fine i'd rather stay
like that
my ghost back dang i'm not gonna tango
with this frog today
dance with me frog legs
all right sounds good good one okay
sounds good a nice job today guys i
wonder what our death counter was at
oh boy
i survived 12 days what about you
i think girls probably the same yeah one
thing i died oh 13.
oh i died at the start we all decided to
start yeah we all did huh
and then another extra time well we
really
didn't do a bad job i mean i would think
i would have thought that i would have
done a much worse job but
i survived long enough yeah oh and by
the way uh if you guys ever want to
stream this game alone there's like
single player two
and this is called don't starve and
there's like a lot more content in it
and there's like a different island and
different biomes you can explore
just like mine oh cool
very art style this game too in the
field it's very nice
yeah cool i'll definitely do that sounds
good well thanks for
tuning in everyone thanks for coming to
hang out with us as we
tried not to starve together yeah thank
you for watching
thank you thank you everyone
everyone
[Music]
goodbye
you