[Music]
so
hello
happy
[Music]
everyone looks different yeah i wonder
what this is oh no um yeah when we
entered the vr universe our bodies uh
something happened into these special
forms yeah something happened something
happened
to these forums
look at this crazy staring right
straight in my eyes you look pretty good
mummy what you guys so much
order okay introduction
okay okay this is my corner okay
nevermind
okay this is my corner okay i wish you
go first this is only in my corner
okay
hi who starts you
me
okay um
hi
it's
iris i don't think you guys can see how
i look in my perspective so
yeah check out the other perspectives to
see what i'm uh what i have turned into
uh in the vr world um
yes everyone's just so cute and just
thought of being a worm and crawling and
cody is just like i want to disappear
from this world sort of
except never mind no she's looking at us
now
excuse me
[Music]
she's not even t-posing and it feels
like she's t-posing
very nice
wait okay next um
you got next we'll go around
yep
[Music]
the council's keeper of nature
i came to this costume party i got all
dressed up you can't see if you're
watching my stream but
um the elevator broke and we're stuck
here so
you can do a stare into the vortex of
time endlessly i suppose i i i can't
really look down my nose is in the way
but okay
[Music]
long neck
very nice
[Music]
i can't say anything my nose is in the
way um okay um
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're looking a bit guilty
wait wait why are you guys looking at me
cause it's your turn wait why
oh my god
oh wait oh okay
hi oh i feel on spotlight hi i'm
crony i'm the
time and right now i don't have my body
because
this world couldn't contain me and
only part of it arrived but you know
what that's okay
because
that means i i'm
what's happening
wait oh so
is this
what's happening isn't the elevator's
broken yep is it
is it something you'd like to tell us
cronie
is it
uh i mean explain yourself
it wasn't really my fault that the
elevator attendant was rushing us all in
and
i did get a little annoyed
so you annoyed it back
[Music]
don't worry about it don't worry
seriously yeah don't worry about it
don't worry about it just don't worry
about it okay
that's someone's name yeah i really
don't know wait
oh what was that as someone's name like
what i wish
karen is like uh you know that you're
overly close speak to a manager
would you like a kiss
just come here
wow
okay everyone go back to your corner
time out time out time out time out
back to your corner okay um who's next
[Music]
the guardian of civilization but i died
and everybody screwed now
everybody screw no what about the
elevator this is part of civilization
too
there are a lot of screws in here but um
guess we're screwed yeah that's true
yeah we are screwed yeah yeah good luck
everybody i'm in my retirement oh
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
remember the beat remember to be okay
are you
wow you look like a delicious gummy worm
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah that means you're sweet you're so i
hope you're she's not the sweet and sour
gummy worm i know those exist
oh
i love the salad what are you talking
about
i want to look at the sugar they just
make me look like i'm dying
all righty
i'm big tickles
hey
hello
[Music]
have long legs i've always had long legs
marvel at them i've always had a long
leg
but um oh yeah it's a model body
i don't have a [\h__\h]
you've got you've got the long um limbs
have you got the you've got the lung
lump
lump excuse me not lumps
kills me excuse me
[Music]
oh no
i'm just thinking
hey
oh no hey guys it's a mistletoe uh ben
needs to introduce herself yes
introduce herself oh oh yes
i wanted to stand originally
what's up is representing
chaos from council um i don't know what
happened to my model um i was reduced to
primitive forms
well i'm inside your head this is crazy
this actually looks oh my gosh
that was that was a wild ride i'll never
forget
why are your hands inside of your body
whoa whoa
no that's probably my nose
if it's red it's my nose one
you see one
okay i don't know what's happening
anymore
we are combining into
one
i'm very concerned
exactly
[Music]
ah
oh
yes you died
there we go we have been in the elevator
too long and now we let us down
[Music]
please let us out
my mommy's just crawling on the ground
are you trying to
[Applause]
[Music]
stop
oh
why are you in that position
[Music]
yes
these monsters
[Music]
oh
thank you
[Music]
we can find out why you look like this
i don't know what's wrong with her i'm
trying to find out if i cut her open
then
come on
yeah here we go
[Music]
i need to find out what's wrong with her
why does she look like this she looks
like a little mouse she's like hair and
shirt
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
are
oh
[Music]
this is wonderful this is chaos
amazing
oh yeah it's so good i'm glad okay i
thought you're stuck in the death
animation it seems like you fixed it
[Music]
okay
hello
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
kelly's a nurse maybe you can revive
before you
oh anymore
[Music]
oh guys look at this
look at this
i can do it
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
and observe the chaos
[Music]
you're here for the museum
[Applause]
[Music]
you
all right so this is uh pretty much like
our terminal here at the time
headquarters as you guys know cronie
over there is the head of the branch as
you can tell
um so these are our time terminals which
uh um is there a bunch of amis run them
and uh recently we did have a zombie
outbreak a zombie ahmed outbreak so we
had to close off this section here but
uh oh no we can uh unclog that soon yeah
so zombie on it
and uh we also have a few different uh
reception desks here we do have a small
one like usually i would be here and i
would help you guys uh you know if you
had like some issues just you know if
you guys wanted to know what timeline to
go to i could help you with that uh
today we will be traveling to another
timeline and as you guys know council
came from another timeline which was in
another dimension and you guys got all
messed up in the elevator somehow
it has been having some issues too
someone broke it all right
yeah somebody broke
not open concierge as well which is
currently closed as uh
holiday
welcome but we also have the elevator
which you guys have seen awesome awesome
don't make me go back in there don't
make us go back in there please we won't
be using it today do not press the
second button we'll be using that later
okay okay
you guys are welcome to help yourselves
to some drinks
[Music]
i want to sit
why is there a button
[Music]
over here
crying over here his fountain of tears
they are salt water we were thinking
about adding some fish but uh yeah some
salt water
he's got a lollipop
sweet delicious tears oh
[Music]
it's actually part of it
oh no
yeah well we've got a permanent oh nice
for you guys there's so many
[Music]
this lobby uh has a lot of timelines
attached but we do have portals
specifically for all of the small miss
members here i'd love to add some more
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's
is
[Music]
wow
hey i'll give you i'll give you candy
[Music]
thank you
how about we go over to the next area
now let's go over to the next portal
okay
portal this way guys
follow me
all right next up we will be going into
the small kiara timeline let's go check
out kiara's portal
i don't think everybody was on board
with us we're leaving some people behind
how do you reposition reposition items
everybody
cares
um
[Music]
i can't get
phoenix
[Music]
oh thank you
hahaha
[Music]
yeah it's really pretty around this time
of year as you can see the trees have
been changed we have some pumpkins for
decoration and this is like the
main town plaza is really nice kind of
reminds me of like animal crossing or
something that's really cute yeah it's
your first time in australia australia
is this the aussie night are we in the
outback
[Music]
what are you doing here
i still got a side
[Music]
we're gonna skip the auditorium for now
but let's go on into gooda's portal yay
[Applause]
[Music]
can you reach out
can we get some do it do it
[Music]
that's clearly for takeout is gonna hurt
my
really pointy object from a different
dimension
i think not much
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
and it's full glory if you guys would
like to see that add another today
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know you know when the nurse can't
find um your your blood your vein and
you just stab
yeah
oh yeah step step
step everywhere where are we going we're
getting left behind oh
[Music]
is
hey iris hey
[Music]
no
bye
is
[Music]
you can look on the windows
i hope it feels i hope your tummy feels
better soon
thank you
so much
[Music]
oh
oh she's okay
what's this one
she's stuck
i'm not sure what that one does you know
would know
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh
i lost my stem
hey just to tell you guys about this
area i believe this is inna's retreat
a cabin in the woods with inna's uh lap
here nice relaxing tea area as well as
some nice open windows with a bookshelf
and of course
painting equipment as you guys can see
up here these uh canvases that you have
painted are actually from her first uh
how do you see the game pass apart out i
don't know how to say it properly
a nice little easter egg there
oh
[Music]
all right everybody we're now gonna go
over to
[Music]
she found it over here
is
[Music]
the dinosaurs
everybody okay all right here we are
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah so uh this is uh the desert uh
some small amis
maybe some crimes
you guys can have a syringe battle you
know
can't do nothing without the juice for
it
give me
[Music]
[Laughter]
i didn't know that this is a deadly
concoction it was an accident
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's moving
i can't see my nose is in the way she's
like just relaxed but no she likes her
position right now she really likes to
be dead can sit down in a little bit
when we go to the next area okay oh yeah
that's exciting okay yeah just to tell
you guys a little bit about this area
this is where some small armies come to
rest whether it's
time or crimes uh it's a bit of a prison
it's a bit of a resting place it's a bit
of everything for each of it
um
[Music]
okay
roger
[Music]
cause i made it small you wanna put it
big
okay this time it wasn't me
[Music]
today is halloween so we have some
spooky activities planned and we are now
going to go into the spooky halloween
timeline
please press the second button here the
instant teleport button
[Music]
oh
this makes sense okay this makes sense
because i died and so i can't guard them
anymore so
this is this was that
what's over here
oh my gosh
oh no there's another one
hello what are you guys doing
um i actually believe this might be what
caused uh your guys's oh no before these
of sorts
i think there's been some
[Music]
messing around going on here
uh but as you can see there's this looks
like an evil ritual
remember this we have the time
this is for cronies
[Music]
oh you eat those no i think there's base
come again
[Music]
why are you swimming through the floor
babe why not
[Music]
on the
maybe cutting
half or something i don't know
that's a great idea i like that it's
trying to get over here
[Music]
god
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
video
[Music]
an ice cream fan nice
sure you betcha
here we go
[Music]
uh
yeah sure it
[Music]
here we go
oh
[Music]
it that way
oh it's crazy you're welcome to take a
seat we do have chairs scattered all
around this area if you like it i'll
take a look though
does anybody have the plan chad and we
are where's the plunger
now
[Music]
to do with this spirits if you're here
please give us subscribers
give us a sign what this is the prince
from the mario franchise huh
who's your favorite
[Music]
shy guys
take
[Music]
god i'm is i'm gonna cover my ears no no
no no no all right stands for
[Music]
i think oh let me zoom out a little bit
on the camera yes
[Music]
oh are you bowing down to me finally
have you finally learned your position
in our relationship
oh thank you i appreciate the respect i
feel utterly respected right now how do
you slap in this game how do you slept
[Laughter]
it's like yeah i have other scenes
there's a lot of other chairs
i like
but there's a leaf stuck in here
oh that's literally here
and i like that the
yeah i was thinking we could tell some
ghost stories but i don't think we have
anything um there's a magnifying glass
that we can use but it's in the other
map we're watching oh that's okay
i'll make sure everybody's in the spring
[Music]
all right if you guys could take a seat
please
could you guys see
[Music]
[Applause]
a virus
[Music]
stay there
[Applause]
[Music]
you can stand if you like especially
since chairs don't really work well for
you there's a chair um
she sounds like a ghost
all right
there's a chair there too yeah
[Music]
like other giraffes like
this version of bae has seen things
[Music]
crony is all right clock is is like
coming into me oh no okay sorry i'm
getting the camera that's okay
i'm being sliced into pieces right now
and i'm gonna sit cody
okay
all right um okay everybody welcome to
the spooky spooky timeline as you can
see we have a big yago here and we could
uh actually the switch report is used to
talk to the great spirit of yago but
unfortunately it seems like we've
misplaced the little planchette i
believe it's called uh so it's not here
but
uh i thought instead of talking to the
spirits we could tell some ghost stories
do you guys know any ghost stories
anybody
i know the cricket oh you do move me
stories
have you ever seen a ghost before
yeah you want to hear the story
yeah i want to hear yes
okay once thank you driving down a
winding dark road and i saw a lady and
she had no face
so i hit her and she turned into a ghost
[Music]
sometimes in the dark like faces
disappear
[Music]
i was also in the car i wasn't driving
enough because i can't reach the pedals
uh and uh i think it was with my mom we
were coming home from somewhere it was
really really dark and then all of a
sudden across the road there was this
like mist
of some sort that had no beginning and
end it was just in the center of the
road and we drove right through it and
we try really hard
to will you ever see something and it it
takes you by such surprise that it
leaves you speechless for a little while
uh-huh yes yeah like that that's what
happened it was it was it was kind of
genuine fear for a second uh but we're
trying to think of what it could have
been and there's no way it could have
been
smoke right because smoke
doesn't you would have seen it fizzle or
how would it have traveled out into the
road like that without any
well how would it have lived that long
you know it was really scary and i don't
know how to explain it or i don't have
any other way to
explain what it could have been
that is scary that's scary
at least we're in the car you guys are
in the safety right
i mean we can find ghost stories online
like us like a kind of spooky story but
it's like from a thing it's like a book
i'm not going to read it but like i can
recount it to you
yeah yeah tell us you're allowed to do
that you get in trouble
i think it's okay
change some details yeah okay gotcha
so basically here's how it goes
all right
here's here's how are you okay kiara
i looked at the chat for one second i
just had to laugh
oh
mistake
all right
so
there's this girl right
and she's at a gas station
she's filling up the gas in her car it's
just a normal day getting off of work
you know the usual
and then she decides it's time to go
home as any other sane human would you
go to work you go to home just a typical
day
right
so she finishes getting the gas in her
car settles down in her little seat
gets ready to drive away yeah i hear it
too gets ready to drive away boys that
uh
i don't know
i hear it coming from your area it's
fixed she gets what she takes a little
seat gets ready to drive away
and she heads off down
excuse me
i'm sorry
you're good fine you're fine
[Music]
musty and spooky road and she's on like
a countryside roads there's no one
around until she realizes that she's
being followed stop oh my god no way
someone is following her i know someone
is following her yeah that's right
there's a car it's hot on her tail and
it's been following her in fact for a
while she realizes that it's been
following that
ever since the gas
station yeah that's right if you
remember the gas station there was a
dude and he followed
there's a car you envision it in your
head now there's another car there's one
car here there's a car here and they're
going down the road and it's dark
outside and then the car behind her this
innocent victim starts flashing his
lights flash flash flash over and over
over and over again oh man not emotions
for flash
what could it mean
another 30 minutes left to drive all the
way home so she keeps driving and the
the dude just keeps flashing the lights
flash flash flash what does it mean we
don't know
she gets very scared and decides i need
to call the police i need to call them
so they'll be ready when i get to my
house this dude's going to kill me he's
going to jump out of his car and then
and then hold on i got i got my effect
my special effect he's going to come out
of the car
and and stabby stab
[Laughter]
no too scared of that happening all
right you can stab with the chainsaw
yeah
so so she decides she didn't just beep
at him with the car
oh no she did she gets pretty mad at him
but he like doesn't care and so and so
she keeps going and he keeps flashing
eventually she gets home she runs out of
her car the police are there they all
pull up and she runs out of her car and
the guy pulls up in his car
and he comes out and he's just a normal
dude
he says ma'am are you okay he says what
are you talking about
my man says
there's a dude in the back seat of your
oh
[Music]
thank you thank you that was amazing
i mean i got creepy pastas
i have one
tony you guys sana and then cronie
i think it's a trade story it's about
living in space australia or australia
yeah okay
sort of scary bug stories
sorry
oh okay that i mean that counts i'm
scared yeah okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
about books
[\h__\h] counties
i was thinking you would have swimming
as well uh i did but they're not like
scary i mean they're scary but they're
not scary
there's something that's not where like
um you accidentally you accidentally
step and step on the floor and you
accidentally step on a centipede or a
slug or like
like a furry spider like a furry spider
was once in my bed
[Music]
walking past my um bedroom and then
um i had i was doing something but i had
direct vision into my bedroom
um and then i was just staring at the
ground and then suddenly out of nowhere
a huge like black spider just crawled
under my bed and then
i didn't do anything
and that's it
didn't do anything behind it no i never
found it this is scary
i never found it
disappeared yeah you know what it went
inside your ear it's funny yeah yeah
inside you want me to shove it down your
side i'm gonna slap you they crawl into
your mouth
what does that mean you're gonna throw
up the spider because it's inside you
there's no other way to get it out did
you know that isn't the statistics that
like um you you swallow like 20 spiders
in your lifetime when you're sleeping oh
yeah
yeah or are you in desert
[Music]
oh it really is fake oh
yeah i'm only showing five percent does
anybody else have difficulties
[Music]
some
juicy meat um
my my
[Laughter]
sorry sorry
oh okay i was um
i was living in japan until a while ago
and
i
i moved after after joining whole life
i moved into a big big house
but the house was
very very
uh old it was that when you walked on
the wood it would make sounds like
wait wait
right
oh yeah so it was really really old that
it had a lot of
it had a lot of uh issues to it but well
it was a big two-story house all to
myself so i was like i'm just gonna try
my best to ignore that it's the looking
really old so
the first night
arrives and i'm i'm like yeah i got this
whole house to myself and i was trying
to chill but i was hearing noises
from the ceiling
[Laughter]
[Music]
i immediately contacted my my landlord
and he was like yeah there
there might be some history of ghosts in
this house but please don't worry about
it well we'll send you some ghost
exterminators
so
[Applause]
a few days later
and the the ghostbusters came by and all
those days i i heard the ghosts like
continuously only in the night but also
during the day and was kind of freaking
me out because i was also trying to
stream but it was i was hearing it on
the first floor and on the second floor
and on the in the side of the walls and
in the bottom and at the top everyone
so
uh the ghost extremities they came and
they looked into the ceiling and they
they saw the ghosts they saw the ghost
whoa really and they said that it's like
they sound like about
three goals three ghosts three no no no
and they actually had ghost poison with
them
and they put the chest that's right girl
they got the ghost poison and they put
that uh they put the ghost poison in the
ceiling and then they closed it and they
they were like okay kiara you call us
and tell us call the ghostbusters and
tell us how the poison worked
and then a few days later i did start
hearing less
so i called again and i was like yo
ghostbusters i'm calling you because who
who else would i call
right girls so they say all right you
still
that they were gonna come back and they
opened the ceiling again and they looked
inside and they found the ghost of two
ghosts
the body goes
those two ghosts of the ghosts where um
the parent ghosts of the ghosts that
survived
and it was weird because they added they
kept on trying to add poison for the
last surviving ghost but it seems like
that ghost has started to form some kind
of immunity
and uh we tried many times but it didn't
didn't work and then one time for
example i was sick
with the door open because i had it was
like a such a tiny idol meeting room
that it's like almost impossible to
close the door and i saw the ghost
myself with my own eyes
but it made itself known
like ate your food once yes it will save
my food
actually
that's horrific i don't know if you've
heard of it but ghosts are apparently um
uh
not they don't like eating chocolate
because they will kill them
[Music]
and all that
so in the end i started to accept the
fact that i'm living with a ghost and
actually we're best friends now and the
ghost's name is cassie
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
she's collapsing in on herself
we need to exercise
[Music]
oh
it might help um purge the ghost if you
want to play on desktop that's okay too
because i know you're feeling a little
sick so if you want i will reinvent you
okay if you're feeling too sick
okay okay all right
easy just get comfy yeah
yeah
[Music]
pumpy
sit down relax
[Laughter]
[Music]
she'll be back maybe we should go to the
summoning circle to summon her a shark
yes
maybe
did you leave some of the
ghost poison
pretending to be like an owl
why are you pretending
[Music]
oh
she
[Music]
she can totally hear us
oh she's awake
my
[Music]
i'm assuming she's talking about me
are we telling them ghost stories
[Music]
you know yeah i play dead you guys want
to hear another story yes please
i can tell you guys it's not a spooky
story but it's uh it's terrifying
outside
okay all right cool thank yous yeah um
all right so here's the story have you
guys heard the story yeah the crunch
bird
story of the crunch bird long ago yeah i
remember it was a crunchy bird
grandfather told you can't see i know it
sounds like that right like
exactly like you can imagine a big scary
phoenix
basically
the crunch bird my grandfather told me
this story it's been passed down in
reaper legends for generations so
basically there's this couple and they
decide that they want to have a pet
right they decide it's finally time to
get themselves um a pet of their own
because you know they've been living
alone can't have kids that kind of thing
so uh so they've decided okay we're
gonna go you know off to the pet shop so
the husband's really busy he's working
and so he tells his wife go ahead and
get us a pet he doesn't care what it is
he says whatever is fine right so the
wife goes to the pet store
and uh is kind of talking with the pet
clerk and she's like i wonder what would
be good you know a dog a cat hamster all
very cute but
hear me out how about a bird and so the
the shop clear because all right i got
some birds i'll show you some birds
takes her to the back starts showing her
the birds and she's like oh these are
all very fine birds but what's that one
in the back there's this big cage in the
back it's got this huge foul beast of a
creature inside of it he says oh that's
the crunch nothing's way too dangerous
yeah crunch bird is what it's called you
can call it whatever you want but i call
it the crunch bird and she says why do
you call it the crunch bird he's like do
you really want to know she says yeah i
really want to know he's like do you
really want to know she's like yeah i
really want no show me the bird really
really no exactly
and so
he takes he takes the bird from the cage
all right and and he says crunch bird
table
and the crunch bird goes and it destroys
the table
[Music]
destroys it
it crunches the table i see
exactly that's why it's called a crunch
bird iris i can see your hands right now
just be careful um
so
and it destroys the chair all right so
now the chair is destroyed and so the
wife says you know what this is a
dangerous animal but i think it's got i
think it's got potential you know it's
got like it's different you know it's
not just like your run-of-the-mill usual
uh pet and i think my husband might like
this potential
exactly it's got that potential real
special potential
he's saying that ten times fast real
special pet potential special pep it's
probably not that hard so so she says
you know what fine i'll take the crunch
bird and um and he he they do the
exchange she gives them the money he
gives the bird right she takes the bird
back home sets up the cage gets it all
nice for her husband to come back home
now husband walks through the door and
he sees this foul beast in the corner
and he says what the f word is that
can't say the f word we have children
watching possibly so she said let me
show you she opens the door lets the
crunch bird out
and she and he says what can you tell me
what on earth is this thing she says oh
it's a crunch bird he says crunch bird
my ass
[Music]
just in time
oh
story do you have one cronie i want to
hear
your wisdom
all right
sit in the rocky chair yeah yeah yeah
sit in the rocking chair sit in the
rocking chairs
[Music]
this is something that i experienced oh
no
um
so a family member and i were just you
know chilling out in our room and at
exactly 12 a.m uh
the phone started ringing so i said oh
wow
why would friends call you at this hour
that's really disrespectful
and then
and then she looked at me and said that
that's not my ringtone
and
the the song that was playing uh was
pretty much all about
uh like i've been everywhere searching
for you where have you been
because i see you
like
are you hiding somewhere in the crowd
and
and then we got kind of creeped out we
uh picked up the phone
and it stopped playing
and then suddenly at every night
exactly at 12
that same ringtone was happening
and that was that was not the ringtone
that she said and
later on she decided to delete the song
from her phone
and it still kept playing
and
and then we had some
interesting events taking place such as
how when i was all alone in the house i
would hear
a piano key
a single
piano key just going ding ding
i would go and check it out nobody's
there or
i'd be all alone in my room
and my dog
uh who's in the same room would
look at whatever's at the end of the
hallway and i keep trying to call their
call time lut's name and
they won't
they won't turn their head it's fixated
at whatever is at the end of the hallway
everything was pitch black
uh yeah
um
that that phone kept ringing
and
maybe something about that house was
weird um
[Laughter]
[Music]
and that same family member had
some other experience where
they would have nightmares
about how they can't move but they would
be in a fire or they would get shot some
a lot of nightmares every single day
okay that can't be a prank
sometimes a woman like crying over the
ceiling really fast just to look around
the face
that's why everything that's on the
ceiling is haunted nope nope nope not
like developing i believe like a ceiling
fan
yeah
on the ceiling
that was when she was living alone and
when she decided to live with her family
again
this time she couldn't move again in the
dream
but
uh at her bedside she saw
a woman with all her face covered
and
and you know with the hair and
everything and she said oh you know what
i see that you're with your family now
and
because of then
i won't bother you again
i hope you haven't heard me talk to you
like that oh yeah yeah and
that was kind of nice what yeah after
that she never had those dreams where
she's paralyzed in her sleep
[Music]
the ghost was just lonely
of being in sleep paralysis
and i tossed it at the chair before
take the chair does anybody else have
another story they consider this
minecraft butt
gonna tell your sleep for alice's story
my brain is dead right now gotta tell
you should i
do it
is that a scary story
i mean
yeah
we can now move on you should
you guys listen up i'm going to tell you
about the next activity
um
the next activity is a maze
so
uh we're going to split into groups and
the samples will be scaring the koha's
so the way it's going to work is we're
going to have group a and group b so if
group a is going to be council you guys
just step on over here for a moment all
the way over here to the left or to your
right
thank you and we have miss and iris over
here
yeah but she's your guy
[Music]
i want to be scared
the way this is going to work is um i'm
going to send you guys counsel don't go
into the maze yet but i want you guys to
go all the way over there to the other
side um where the summoning circle is
and if you guys could wait over there uh
that'd be great thank you guys
i don't like this i don't like this
off on your hand you know the last time
i went into a maze i came out with like
10 bruises
oh no hey hey last time i went into
amazing
yeah
[Music]
oh
did the ghost beat you up or something
oh you know you know this is actually a
story last time i went into a like a in
a haunted house thingy my bobby um there
was one part i got so scared i just ran
for the door but i didn't realize there
were like obstacles in between and i
like catapulted over them and it was a
steel bar so i got bruises all over my
body
oh
no because i didn't see because i was i
don't buy haunted houses there's a candy
once
and people yeah
your
fears to forget all your problems okay
i've never been to one okay i don't know
why
yeah because it's fun i don't know
yeah have you been
i've had a really good i've been to
really good ones and i've been to ones
where um the actor sort of awkwardly
jumps out and then
backs away when nobody gets scared
[Laughter]
oh you know what was really funny though
that was like um when i heard when i
catapulted over the steel but i remember
the person who was meant to be scary
like runs up to me and he's like oh my
god are you okay
and he had like his costume on and
everything and i was like oh
oh my gosh bae when you talk your
eyeballs move your eyeballs jitter oh
wait is it the coffee
you guys could just face the gravestone
over there face the gravestone and uh do
not look it's not it's to not spoil you
guys okay i will come here
it's crazy okay maybe they rip around
now i wasn't scared before i'm just i
have to go inside but i like the rhyme
sound a little worried
[Music]
okay
it kind of rhymes do they taste like
pepperoni
do you how about how do you rain this
gravestone out of 10.
what
you know
what a riperoni out of 10.
[Music]
as to whether that's a good score or now
i leave it up to you guys to decide
really want to look around like other
people's
gravestones
i'm just looking back stuck with this
one
hey what's that supposed to mean
it's a beautiful question we
anything else
okay
it's all right
i'm gonna scare them back i'm gonna be
like
30. all right you guys the maze is now
ready for you to explore you guys can
turn around and uh um we can do it my
way back to an i know meeting she'll be
back soon
oh okay okay we'll wait yes i still
can't say anything you're so big
i'm gonna um i'll tell you guys in
discord when to go okay just give me one
moment
okay i got this to protect me
all right all right just wait uh i will
tell you guys and discord when to go
into the maze okay
[Music]
can we turn around oh we just gotta wait
and then
wait for it
to try to you look inside connie's head
yes i i i have nice
i wanted like a mask like if you clip it
just right it's like a mouse it's like
super creepy nice to see you in here
look inside the base oh my goodness
my head
yeah your head is crazy
shorter now i don't know if that's let
me see if i can get a screenshot
i got a screenshot
all right council uh you guys can go
ahead and enter the maze please
spare me okay
okay
[Music]
that's cute
hey come on guys
are we let's go
i can lead the way don't worry i want to
watch
[Music]
oh my
[Laughter]
[Music]
i mean
don't touch my abs don't touch my arms
listen to these kids
okay okay
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
oh that's so scary oh that's so scary
wait hello that's scary scary
no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
um
[Applause]
what are you doing
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey
hold on
um everybody hold on
everybody hold on hold on hold on hold
on hold on
how do i um
wait how do you turn off the names yeah
you guys good this will work how do you
turn off names
[Music]
oh my god look at that
if you guys have seen a council member
you may now exit the maze you guys
council members may now exit the maze
do not go into the moscow
don't worry about it there's a giveaway
[Music]
oh
this way no this was not it
um
oh it's this way
okay
oh my god
[Music]
oh my goodness your belly button please
go back the way you came and exit me i
was i was chilling in the corner for the
longest time
alone
and no one was finding me i was
[Music]
scared me
thank you
actually finally someone found me i love
you thank you
this is
[Music]
back hey guys
oh my god
cancel there's still more of the maze
you guys can uh
keep going
oh okay okay
okay i thought we were supposed to exit
the maze right no apparently there's
more we got to explain more than me
please don't leave me
don't leave me
stop going so quickly look over
look right here what oh my gosh
oh my god
this is a surprise oh my gosh
isn't this something that this looks
like something that moving true
yeah
that's my creation
[Music]
i like how
the kohai's drawing is scaring senpais
oh
wait this is even scarier
[Music]
oh you're scared don't worry
god i can't see anything
i suddenly want to sacrifice my whole
heart and soul oh okay that's pretty
good heartedly that's pretty good
wholeheartedly you will give me
your big red heart queen this is queen
queen take my heart please take me like
i'm missing a hug
it's very dark you might as well take it
off come here i bow down
oh
[Music]
please
oh maybe let's see
what do you see
good i don't see anything
is that what you saw wait
that surprised me more than scary that
is being such a cute baby
oh okay what's that oh oh hi okay
it can go this way okay come here
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you like it
[Music]
i'm here to escort you back
oh hello thank you scary bing thank you
okay where are we going thank you purple
dinosaur hello where are we going we
could go this way i think crony
and fox wanna know the way on the other
side
now
if you guys follow the footsteps
the footsteps have changed here
i thought
the wrong way
wait that's this way no it's this way
what oh
yes
what if we look back i think they
figured out on the other side um nothing
happens i think
[Music]
it was worth it
i'm gonna kick you if you don't wake up
ready to lunch oh oh she woke up okay
see perfect way to wake up uh
counsel if you uh the rest of council
can go over here in this area
um
[Music]
yeah turn up the name tags yeah yeah
okay
i think it's irish
[Music]
only i didn't turn them off i didn't
know i could
i didn't i didn't go anywhere i didn't
go anywhere
okay
what was that sound
who is that
[Music]
i'm scared already was it emma now
okay time to make myself sound scary um
okay sarah left her umbrella repair
is this scary hello
it's my time
hello where did he make it
[Applause]
let's do that that's good
was that good
hold on
whenever that whatever
was that was good okay we'll do that we
can't do that
i can tell you yeah i can do it
you sound like a dog santa
yeah are you silly
my animal i don't know it sounds too
supposed to be here
[Music]
all right you guys can now change into
the avatars that you guys have the
monsters oh
i see i see
that
yeah
you guys now it's your turn to try to
spook them yeah you guys have monsters
too oh okay
hold up i don't know if i'm supposed to
show it on stream yeah i might hide for
a second oh you can show it now it's
okay oh okay um i don't
i don't yes myself
yes yeah that one looks pretty dyke yes
yes
oh i like this one
oh it's really dark here but if you
stand by the light
[Music]
face me
and we all kick this one
[Music]
just wait one second um okay let me make
sure that they're i'll be right back do
you guys wait here
a chew
shoes
oh my gosh the mouse does have nipples
what
the mouse is
okay guys stop communicating we got to
have a nice
okay come on you guys we can go into the
maze now just you know hide wherever you
like okay okay okay
okay
all right
i'll give you guys 30 seconds and i'm
gonna send them in okay okay okay okay
okay okay
um
where are you guys gonna hide where do
you guys wanna hide i wanna hide in
i wanna see upstairs
you should you should hide in the
berries maybe
i don't know where i'm hiding
oh let's hide wait wait wanna hide
something dark
are you okay
okay my voice is one
[Music]
why
i heard a sneeze
what are you
[Music]
this is actually really quite scary
what are you are you an actual rat
oh my god
[Applause]
she's just not here
oh
i carry asmr though
[Music]
[Applause]
bruh
yeah no problem
for the blog yeah i got it i got it all
right here we go all right go bro now
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
wow
is
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
okay
is
[Music]
i'm going with you guys i'm waiting for
you guys to go forward
i know
[Music]
[Applause]
come here it says come here
i can't take it
i can't jump anymore when did i [\h__\h]
tell you i'm so scared what are we doing
[Music]
it
this is why i don't eat them
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
back
just creeping on them
[Music]
becoming a oh oh my god
oh
[Applause]
oh it's really soft and smooth the
ambiance is really scary that's a good
pet attitude
[Music]
by the way
okay real quick what the [\h__\h]
what is wrong
hey
oh hello
[Music]
oh
wait i'm stuck
oh i went the wrong way okay
hello
i'm man hi
yeah look there's something
[Music]
you guys look like your names are gary
oh there's only one right here
i don't know
i'm kind of getting like a mark did i
hear stuff
[Music]
oh
yes we have a special premiere that we
are going to be watching in the
auditorium and we're going to go back
there
[Music]
hi
[Applause]
oh there we go
[Laughter]
feel free to bring some lights
yeah
[Music]
why is there a baby seat
hello ah for the baby
okay i'm gonna get another light stick
uh set the camera let's go let's go
[Music]
all right
now i think originally i'll wait until
everybody's here i'll get up on the
screen no brother to make a quick
announcement
you guys are welcome to take a seat you
can stand if you like um okay so
originally we're gonna have some
performances but uh it looks like it
didn't work out in time if anybody does
want to perform now's your chance you
could do show and tell you maybe you
want to show us you can juggle or maybe
you want to sing an acapella too does
anybody want to come up anybody any
volunteers
no i've changed all right i'm okay
okay well we do have uh for chat and for
you guys here in the crowd we have a
special music video premiere oh
yeah we're gonna watch it together here
in uh here now so if you guys want to
get a good view a good seat now's a good
time i'm gonna go russy
[Music]
it's a
here we
go on any second all right my light
stick is a sideways don't mind me yeah
all right i don't know let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
that's so good
[Applause]
[Music]
hungry dinosaur just one tiny bite
[Applause]
[Music]
that was so good
everything is amazing
[Music]
um it will premiere on my channel so you
guys after the stream if you want to
re-watch it you can go there and rewatch
it as many times as you'd like and uh
i'm going to i am too the lyrics callie
wrote the lyrics
and also
the music video animator made such good
use of everybody's models made by
seafoam hasksoff and also twilight 3d
it's so awesome so many people worked on
it so thank you everybody that worked on
it thank you so much thank you guys for
watching
[Music]
thanks for organizing
thank you where's the camera where's the
camera oh there's the camera okay got it
i got it okay there's the camera okay
we're gonna stand behind okay
[Music]
ah the
it is
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it was the berries
i love this dance
[Music]
[Applause]
not your wife i am a pumpkin
[Music]
[Applause]
good job everybody
[Music]
all right so we are reaching the end of
the stream but i have some i have one
last activity planned um if you guys
want to follow me to the reception area
[Music]
[Applause]
we're gonna jam out a little bit and
then we'll say goodbye to everybody you
guys i'd love to do some cool
screenshots so dance together waltz
together hold each other's hands hug
each other whatever you want to do dance
on the table stand on the chairs
please how do i
drink
[Music]
what's the fun to dance tonight
what a spooky scary sight hey
hey wow
[Music]
yes
what's going on say thank you guys
[Music]
he kicked out the table
i'm trying
[Music]
i don't know how to take a screenshot
either i'm just like
take the best screenshots chat
yeah i'm gonna grab them from you guys
take the screenshots
i can't
i can't multitask like that
[Music]
how'd
oh my god the inside the cronies heads
are scary oh my god i can see the eye
holes
i don't want to see it here
[Music]
oh my god is horrifying
all right thank you guys for watching
the halloween stream oh my
[Music]
[Applause]
happy at god
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
do
you