[Music]
do
foreign
[Music]
it can't go that high
you'll make me look like an amateur
come on
[Applause]
you see how i'm like missing some
chicken stairs
[Music]
time
okay okay
[Music]
hi kitty
hello
um
playing a different oh my god hello
super chat playing a different pgm right
now
because we got a little bit exhausted of
the other one
in the four and a half hours super chat
reading
[Music]
it's my original pgm there's no title
it's called
kiara underbar b
on the bar 10 minute loop dot
mp3 that's the title
the credit is in the in the description
uh he has a twitter account
he made the bgm for some of the fifth
gen members as well
thank you for the super chats guys uh
i'll say by the way
um today there will probably
oh thank you dr
today there will probably not yeah most
likely not be a super chat reading
uh because of time issues i can only
stream two hours
uh because of neighbors
nina now let's see
how much my switch has charged i'm so
sorry i'm such an amateur
this is the first time that i stream uh
switch
with with the game capture on my pc i
don't
and i took a nap after the super chat
reading
uh after watching a little bit of
senpai's stream
and then i fell asleep and then i woke
up like an hour before the stream and i
didn't realize
that it's not charged yeah i can't play
doc but at least
the controllers need to be charged a bit
right
now let's check let's let's let's see i
don't want to turn it on
oh it's great it's 20 it's green it's
green it's green
okay but can we like let it rest like
maybe five more minutes do you think
it's enough
twenty percent is enough to have the
controllers work
for like two hours
i'll i'll put i play a doc but i wonder
if that works
sure
actually uh
i hope that the game capture works
though like i have that the window open
and it worked like it showed me the
screen of the switch
i'll have to figure out how to show it
uh i hope i found the right window to
show it to you guys so i am such an
amateur mitchell
kid yeah i tried i tried i
definitely um the the game capture card
definitely worked sorry i i
don't usually this is my first stream of
the switch
my first switch stream so
it's uh yeah very amateurish
but i think i'll be playing a lot of uh
switch games in the future
so we have to figure it out
if it cuts me off at some point then
we'll just have to talk
i mean i definitely have some reading to
do anyway
[Music]
i noticed that some people are giving me
the name of tencho right now
and actually i think it's quite funny
because many generations have something
like that like
senpai or
m
yay oh that's so cool i was low-key
um thinking that that would be so cool
if i could have a name like that
it's so fitting it's so fitting because
i i already opened my restaurant
my food truck i am i am the tencho
of my fast food truck
[Music]
i already became potential papa
i already became potential very
successful daughter i must say
very successful we are on our way to
world domination
thanks for the super chat thank you
yeah good idea to make me the pencil yes
the one with the bird brain
good idea good idea
did you rest well yeah i had a really
good nap matt i was i was so
i was so how do you say
uh something something ouch
i would sell uh wiped out
i guess i guess drain no no not drain
but
i was definitely wiped out
it was a good nap it was a good nap i
take so many naps though
come in come in
and then i then i wonder then i asked
myself
oh why can i not fall asleep earlier
than 6 am
every time i'm like up until 6 a.m and
i'm like huh
what why am i still awake
and then i sleep and then i wake up and
i get
tired again and then i nap again and
then i can only sleep
like around 6 a.m uh
make it end please
relatable phoenix is our next channel
apparently
thank you for the super chat oh my god i
hope it's okay for you guys today i
can't read them because i have a
time issue
yeah a time issue i can't i can't stream
so long today
[Music]
okay let's see how much it charged
children
23 wow okay
i'm gonna dock it now
i'm sorry sorry was that till i bumped i
bumped the microphone with my headphones
i need more space
everything's such a mess i'm really not
good at organizing
this
again again again sorry
again again sorry i bumped again
okay no more bumping no more bumping
i got it
bunk bunk okay
okay now let's put you in the controller
thingy
okay switch asmr
one more
[Music]
okay so
game capture please work
turn it on okay
oh please work come on
yes the controllers have been connected
let's see how long they work
wait i should yeah you need to let me
know if you can hear the sound as well
did you hear something must have been
quiet but
[Music]
what's up
huh
am i not back back
wait okay next problem
next problem uh
[Music]
how why why is it
oh why is the game capture card not
showing on
obs
uh game capture hd
i did
[Music]
uh
wow what do i do
yeah i should it should be the right
source
it's called game capture hd
what about elgato sound capture
that's nothing oh
oh maybe no
game capture hd
hello huh
the game capture is working but it
doesn't show up in obviously
all my tech support is on my awake
um
let's see no i don't think so
wait kelly have you
streamed switch before
panic panic
yeah bye uh i wonder if if cali will
react
she's typing she's tapping she's typing
when i chose
nothing
ah she doesn't really know yet because
she didn't do
it yet
[Music]
chair not showing up in
streamlabs
close streamlabs obs and reopen as
administrator try deactivating and
reactivating the elgato source
by right clicking on the source and
going into properties
oh oh
[Music]
oh
oh well i guess i did the reactivating
thing already
i lowkey also restarted so
[Music]
bye-bye
follow these simple steps to fix your
game capture source not working delete
the capture source
oh yeah that might work
uh delete
yes oh wait i'm actually scared
oh i'm scared i'll show something that
you shouldn't see
can i like end for can i end for like
two minutes
is it okay two minutes please two
minutes
okay ah
i did it though i did it okay i did it
let's
all ignore it just everything that just
happened
just ignore what happened let's just
ignore it
okay but i did it i did it
i'm sorry but let's go
i'm really sorry
let's go though
okay okay now
let's do this
yay
this should be japanese
[Music]
here we go
[Laughter]
louder
does it have to be louder and it's too
loud
[Music]
how about this
okay what are the others a template oh
yeah i can play this right now but
[Music]
i'll let you know um i i have
kind of played this years ago
but i don't really have a memory of it
i don't have much memory of it
oh
[Music]
the audio is a bit weird for me double
audio
oh [\h__\h] how do i
how about now
we will get there my friends we will get
there
okay oh
this is so nostalgic
for reasons i am playing this in
japanese because for reasons
uh but i'll talk in english of course
don't worry
is the audio fine other than that
because i can actually hear some weird
popping in the sound in my headphones
okay
[Music]
okay i hope everything's fine now
you have to pop in too that's so weird
why is it doing that
world record i'm coming for you
you hear the popping er
old game might be the reason but this is
the the reloaded version the collection
version
that just came out today
oh oh nice hiragana
pizza
[Music]
fight fight who you fighting who's she
fighting
wow wow
oh my god this is my childhood
[Music]
yellow
i have to tell you guys i'll be very bad
at this game i
know it already go go up go up
why is it where is it go
outside okay
ah no
okay now we start the world record
of the longest gameplay ever
listening i'm not really listening to
what you're saying
[Music]
let me see peace
no i will not go this i need to do
i need to do this i need to play okay
what's the first thing we gotta do
do we just go into a door already and
play already
[Music]
which one which one which one i i
remember this one i think
i remember this one very well but we
can't go in there yet
shut up bowser shut up
they all need one three
very left okay you guys will get very
frustrated with me here
[Music]
oh i see we have trains later in the
chat
i hate this map this is the one thing i
remember
i hate this map what do you want me to
do
what i should have probably read that
emanuel what do i need to do
do i talk to them i saw only akai
wait the first one is i have to go to
the top right
blah blah blah blah blah
he's panicking oh my god be calm
[Music]
this is so amazing like i don't really
have
like i was so small when i
i lowkey played it i never played it
fully of course
because i was too stupid but it's so
weird how you still like
remember the the way i know that way
i know that way and these these bowls
always reminded me of a chocolate called
a malteser
i don't know if they have it in your
country but do you do
do you know that those my taser my teeth
are
oh
[Music]
just follow me guys
i'm almost italian did you know that
italia
[Music]
we need to um okay oh no
beth is coming kelly stop it
[Applause]
how do i get back what do i do
okay
okay here we go again from the beginning
oh backward jump bonjourno
i forgot all my italian i used to study
[Music]
italian
italian gang where
[Music]
i don't want to die kelly please don't
kill me
okay okay hello hello
okay don't why did i even ch
[Music]
will i ever reach my goal will i ever
reach my destiny before dying
i need coins where the hell are coins
except the red one
no wait how to camera
can
ah coins are on top of trees huh
but i can't really walk on
[Music]
everything's so slippery
where are you there we're there we're
there
so i'll be singing along a lot
hi friend hi okay
[Music]
the good thing is i refreshed my memory
of this game
by play by watching a certain senpai's
stream
um
i'm scared i'm scared we have to we have
to
grab him like that right or is that
grabbing too
okay we try to get him from the back
side
oh that was not it
[Music]
no wait how do i do it again
when you try your best but you don't
succeed
when you get what you want but not what
you need
okay wait was i i i did try to grab him
didn't i
here we go again my friend here we meet
again
fight me
[Music]
round two fight
okay oh okay okay okay okay we got this
how do i how do i throw him with a
how do i throw him guys how do i throw
him
how do i throw him hey
no ah okay the same button okay okay bye
bye
was that it oh wait
was that it oh not off oh i thought i
have to throw him off
there oh yeah that didn't count did it
we do it again
round three
i thought that would do it
skill that was some skill did you see
that that
jump okay
okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on let me touch you
i know you wanted to
[\h__\h]
don't don't move so fast
[Music]
mario runs so fast oh my god he needs to
chill
mario
oh i'm sweating my fingers are sweating
this is a really tough battle my friends
okay i would say i'm already better than
a certain senpai
addicted
[Music]
a
nice whatever you say okay
can i go to the can i do that can i i
wanna
i wanna do the one the one the most
nostalgic one
[Music]
that is also something i have a deja vu
with going into the door then trying to
move on but you keep on going
through the same door this one is the
one i want to do
yes slide slide slide slide slide slide
imagine there this is the right one
right
yay is it this sideway
that was the funnest time i ever had in
my childhood
okay first try
[Music]
that i don't i don't i didn't remember
where the secret path was
[Music]
how many years ago that was i think it
was probably like
[Music]
12 12 12 30 mom even more
probably 15 years ago or so the last
time i played this
[Music]
well how would you know how old i am can
i do one is there anything else that i
was supposed to do in here
what i'm eternal how will you know my
age
[Music]
is there anything else no was that
it
eh yes get below 21 seconds
oh and then i have to use that that
shortcut right where was that shortcut
dad
where was the short cat again was it
here
oh no was it here
coconut
[Music]
come on
where was it
should have gone right there
wait am i losing lives
was i supposed to go right at the
beginning
too early there's um
[Music]
if there is no shortcuts what don't let
them in
or maybe maybe maybe a rhyme
[Music]
uh only the snow level has a shortcut oh
so this is just about speed
why don't you tell me earlier i keep on
looking for shortcuts
and you just keep on laughing magicka
okay well then let's do the speed later
let's um where's there's no one um
where was the snow one there
this one i'm so hungry
yay let me in
this one no that's not it but this one
is fun too oh no wait is that it
yeah could it
that's not it right
opposite oh whatever whatever
oh i i know which one that is ah
let's go
wasn't there something in the flower
fields wasn't there
something you could do in the flower
fields
no hello my friend
okay let's go what actually what is the
mission do i just get to the top
eh you can tell ah yeah
i am correct do i have to like look up
or something
[Music]
are are you trolling me guys are you
trolling me
what is the mission anyway
yes
i was a different flower patch okay okay
the ones with the coins okay now let's
show
you my professional skills
i'm not even that bad wow
[Music]
i love this music
sleep slop isn't this
beautiful
punch it in the face oh my god wait wait
wait wait wait
wait i almost slipped i
almost i almost slept buy coins i don't
need you right now hello
who are you again i don't need to fight
you right
[Music]
how am i doing i'm not doing that better
oh i'm already at the top
okay how do we do this i just let him
like fall down right and i jump on him
how do i do the the thing with the thing
[Music]
oh yeah yeah hit me come at me
fight me
[Music]
though this is so close camera hello
come on how close do you have to get
okay okay okay so we don't do this
and then we
the camera is so close
okay
okay guys please tell me how to do it
oh how about it set that where is that
where is that what's that i have
a b y x
jump l r double double
double jump set oh
okay
[Music]
i need to do this after i jump
this one ah
okay now you can fight with me
round two
come at me bro
[Music]
one more come on come on
god damn it do we have to start from the
beginning again
why don't you put fences there
[Music]
point for me oh round three by the way
hello
and there we go point two for me up
but did i count around there
yeah oh my god i'm not even that bad
[Music]
big stop
i'm not as bad as i thought
[Music]
guess it's over
but that one is three stars is it the
three star one
bottom left dora
left oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
again we have entered the wrong door
let's go what's the mission
do you do you tell me what the mission
is here in the under on this one
chewy
[Music]
okay
uh what is the mission wait wait this is
i don't think i'm good enough for this
mission yet
[Music]
okay wait what is the mission just go to
the end okay
and we need those coins we'll probably
die
wait where do we go
[Music]
oh the controls here man
um
do i go for that is that a hole or is
that a stone
oh where do i go probably gonna die now
is that a hole no go up go into the
shipwreck
eel
wait get into the boat yeah
let it you're aligned
i'll wait down there right is that a
hole
that looks like a hole
okay okay okay okay okay this is ready
to go
touch eel no i'm scared it will kill me
i'm pretty sure
that i will take a lot of damage if i
touch the eel so
i think i remember that from my
childhood
[Music]
i think i remember that hmm
what do i do do i jump on this
is that a different mission put a bit on
me
oh
no
[Music]
this is fun are those super chats
what is the right order
what is it yes
okay i would say this one
[Music]
i figured out your riddle
so much her singing is so amazing
here we go
[Music]
it was easy yay
why so much fun
oh i remember that was what was there
again
[Music]
a back flip wait wait or two
back foot hold that and jump
[Music]
oh how cool
look at my skills oh my god where am i
what is this
oh red coins oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay
i'm not sure if i can make this
let's let's keep those coins for later
for emergencies
[Music]
is the camera really that shitty or am i
just not used to it
no no go down go down go down
[Music]
no no no no no i hate swimming
i only like flying so i'm looking
forward to that flying level
[Music]
i'm gonna get you i'm gonna get you
yeah i'm gonna get seasick here where's
the next one there okay
i don't remember this level though i
mean it's not a real level i guess but
i don't remember this one hello
[Music]
i'm coming for you but i'm not even
dying everything's cool
and you how many are there and is that
the last one cause i got
i'm not so bad at this game
[Music]
nice i'm so proud of myself
okay how do we get the star my friends
how do we get the start
[Music]
no no yes yes yeah
here we go
nice you guys mind if i get a talk dr
pepper from my fridge
dr peppa tony gonna
[Music]
peppa
okay this is my last one from my stock
[Music]
cheers my friends
i love dr pepper so much
um oh that's so good
wait is this one the same like a similar
thing
is it also swimming i don't want to swim
anymore right now
[Music]
is it the same thing
one second
okay yes no level where is the snow
level
doko you guys you guys said left
so this one
[Music]
here we go snow i can't wait for winter
yes intellectual drink very much indeed
[Music]
what is the mission i guess i can do the
the the slides the race first
if i want to i guess the mission is to
get the little baby penguin there though
[Music]
that stupid coin man oh my god
shortcut oh shortcut that wasn't even a
pepper
my neighbors love me
and when i try to get the shortcut i
will not be able to get it
what does that blue coin even do
i want you no [\h__\h]
shorthand
no not backwards oh my god
ah went backwards was kind of
unfair
still
[Music]
two lives left oh my god okay let's try
to not
do the shortcut now but i don't know
that
it's so slippery kind of leads me there
no
no shortcut now no shortcut now oh my
[Music]
god
yeah wait there was another shortcut
there right like in the wall
what happens when i die completely
[Music]
good advice
yeah bye this can't be that hard
let's go let's go
[Music]
to tattoo
last chance i am scared
[Music]
so much fun
i did it
[Music]
we did it after like five million tries
now don't slip no no no you
goody thank you
here we go nice
congratulations to me congratulations
what a pro gamer
yay again snow snow snow
and now we save the penguin right
no penguin
[Music]
iguod
how do i what is the best way to get up
to you
this way okay
all right or left
[Music]
okay no why not why not
we're doing this quite nicely
no not backwards okay i think we reached
a good point to stop thank you
oh we're clearing this so
quickly i love this mission i love this
mission i want to save this little
penguin
the way mario walks though he also walks
like a penguin
okay this one we just go under
the snowman
no problem no problem come
come little baby don't go back
okay
we're almost there we're almost there
i'll probably have to wait until he
turns around right
[Music]
okay okay and then we go down we're
almost there your mama is there
your mama is there
i'll bring you to safety oh i'm scared
of this dude no
don't don't hurt me
[Music]
that was close that was very close
don't lose your child again or i'll call
child services
thanks for the super chat
those are
[Music]
[Laughter]
should we go in here again or do a
different one
what do you guys think
do we go into the same one
no no no why would i eat the baby oh my
god you guys are crazy
[Music]
one extra life
really
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
look up okay ah then we can fly right if
i look up we can fly
hey my my i think my
controller's batteries are not working
anymore
what no i i was just too stupid to
control them
let me fly time
huh why is that working
let me fly i want to fly oh i need more
stars oh
okay okay okay okay no problem i can get
more stars which one do we go
let's go to this one again
ah what is the next mission in this one
what what do i need to do just go to the
top again
look like wait come on
wasn't i already at the top
wasn't i already at the top before
climb to the top climb the tree
there's more okay
game over no my first game over
no
well we can play with your face now
oh where's the mouse ah there we go
huh i wanna play with your nose
mario you have such a big nose
is that the only thing i can touch i
think the mouth you can touch
[Music]
thank you mario
okay here we go again
no problem oh i really love this this
outside place here
it's really relaxing the birds and the
sound of the water
this is so relaxing i just want to take
a a vacation here
which means i should probably play uh
super mario sunshine if i wanna
go on a vacation like that
[Music]
right
okay this time i will not fall
yeah i really love super mario sunshine
so i can't wait to
play that one too but it will take
probably a long time until we clear this
one
if we want to clear it actually
[Music]
be careful here okay guys
oh be careful be careful
you could
get 120 stars is that a mission
i don't want to die at the same point
again
[Music]
and then
i need some dr pepper
no
indeed this is good training for fall
guys as well
don't worry we can ah we can do it we
can do it this time i will not fall
why did i go through here so easily the
first time
eh
okay calm down i'm just too excited
i need to come
[Music]
foreign
i need to go slowly right
[Music]
la la la la la
that's that surprised me oh my god where
am i
can i get back up here
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay maybe i'll just go here
hello sweet dreams my beautiful
beautiful plant
piranha planter hello
i hope you sleep well have nice dreams
no no you can't go that fast can a fire
can you
and asleep again wow
am i that boring my friend
am i not entertaining you enough that
you have to fall asleep
[Music]
okay almost at the top again
again
[Music]
i'm still a bit
bad at the controls
come on no
oh please something's coming i hear it
okay okay oh
oh so oh yeah they they added something
up here
oh something came out of there
okay aha
i vaguely remember this oh
okay
[Music]
i wonder if i can first try this come on
come back come back
oh don't i get something if i uh crawl
climb up that pole
that paul polo that we just saw oh my
god what's up here
hello oh that was easy
yay
[Music]
here we go
you kicked the pole
what's with eight stars it said
something about having eight stars
uh can i do something with eight stars
bowser time oh no
no no where
where if i was 10 big door
no i don't want to go this door
[Music]
i'm scared
no i'm just scared this was such a scary
i have this as a really scary memory
no this scared me when i was a child
no i'm
[Music]
no
for real i have like a traumatic
experience from this
okay we gotta go i just closed my eyes
am i here where am i yeah
where am
[Music]
i hate this i want to go to the back to
the happy place
[Music]
yeah the music is really good but
i'm really scared like this this gives
me like the feeling of ah
i'm too weak for this
no no i don't wanna see his face hey
what
i can just go from here okay
okay okay okay go slowly yeah that goes
slowly you can do it
all these viewers are behind you
protecting you
what does that thing do again though did
i do
are the red coins okay i don't need them
now
panic everything's okay
everything is okay i know i can go up
here i think but
i'll go to the side
i'm not scared of death no no
uh
[Music]
maybe i have to go down here so it's
easier to jump there
okay three two one
no that was hard why can't i jump on
there
okay chill everything's cool i can do
this
all these people are with me
we just have to connect our powers
okay go up and now here we go again
any tips guys backflip or long jump how
do i do a long jump oh my god bronx
thank you so much again
i read all the super chats tomorrow
jump higher how do i jump
jump um
i have to try it okay one more time jump
stop stop stop stop stop
i don't wanna fight bowser
[Music]
i don't wanna fight bowser please no
he's so scary he's
[Music]
why why why why you do this to me
come on
i was so excited to see spongebob
[Music]
i feel like we're gonna fail again with
this jump
yeah that was spongebob and here we go
okay okay no worries we didn't fall off
the cliff everything's cool
yeah that cheese block okay three two
one
and jump
jump do i have to get this again
[Music]
am i doing well guys
oh hey what did what is that i get
something here
okay hi spongebob don't do the same
mistake again
oh what's this oh thank you
okay here we take care i don't want to
fall down again okay
i don't wanna i don't wanna fall down
again i've come so far
[Music]
i'm just scared of bowser but i don't
have to be scared of falling
down i can i'm a phoenix no matter how
many times i fall down
i get back up again
jump jump
jump hit me
spongebob hello
wait wait one more now we go together
[Music]
mario
mario mario
mario because of your stupid moves
people will get sick of me and leave the
stream
could you please be a good boy
and just hang on there
or hang in there whatever
people are going to leave because i'm
not doing progress
[Music]
thank you it will be a long journey
a long long journey
a long journey with me spongebob
okay okay okay don't
don't mess up here don't mess up
jump okay okay chill everything's cool
oh no oh no eh
[Music]
foreign
i'm getting i'm getting too nervous now
i'm getting too nervous
[Music]
god dammit
my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god
fire shouldn't be able to hurt me
i'm a phoenix
[Music]
see now i'm getting so nervous that i'm
messing up the parts that i already
know how to do
[Music]
no
oh more god jump okay
stop jump
get that life i need it get it no
they are ganging up on me they're
ganging up on me
oh my god that was scary
oh my god oh my god oh my god my fingers
are sweating
okay spongebob
[Music]
huh
do i have to switch the camera there can
i even
thanks for the super chats
come on stop
jump get the life don't let them gang up
on you
[Music]
if you gang up on me i'll send callie to
kill you
[Music]
better be careful she's on hiatus but
she'll do anything for me
the first time that one got me
okay spongebob jump
stop get this
now go with it jump stop and now
focus focus
focus oh my god
oh my god what now
what now i don't want to fall down
anymore what's
what's happening what's here eh
i don't need to go there right
only here but do i have to jump on those
or can i go on the side
does it make a difference i can get the
life if i go inside it just takes longer
time right
but it feels safer it feels safer to go
here
[Music]
okay okay chill chill chill chill i need
that life i desperately need it
you have it
[Music]
thank god what now i just keep on going
there right
camera is giving me anxiety me too my
friend
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god
i don't see [\h__\h] nam mommy in it
okay safe now don't [\h__\h] up for real
hello friends jump
hello okay now how do we get up there
i don't want to mess up can i just jump
normally
just jump up normally why do i hear i
feel like i hear double music but is
that just
the soundtrack
am i almost there please tell me i'm
almost there
[Music]
how do i get up there how did i get up
there
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
how did i can i not okay
oh my god oh my god
why was that so such a short time
frame oh my god
[Music]
okay oh
that was so close oh my god okay
it's time for bowser oh my god
what happens if he kills me do i have to
do the whole thing again
[Music]
yes no
oh no i have to grab his tail right
oh no i hate this so much
all right i got you my friend i got you
basically told me everything
else okay easy
wow wow and what now do i just oh
yeah nice i think we can do this i think
we can do it i just gather
up my power of the phoenix
you can't hurt me your fire can't hurt
me
i'm resistant to fire
[Music]
oh that's difficult it
how do i do that
[Music]
did i do it did i touch the spikes
i thought i missed them again i did it
accidental win
[Music]
hey was there a spike there
there was nothing there
here we go my first king
[Music]
no run away i don't want to be in this
room anymore
can i enter that room now
is that what i can what i can do now
with that key
but do i want to go in there
where was there again
i'm not okay it's not the same i have to
keep for the for the
uh basement we still have like
18 minutes or so so i shall continue
where do i go ah this one
do i really want to go there already is
that an hour another bowser fight though
[Music]
ah it's just uh more levels oh no that's
another buzzer fight i don't want to go
there
no thank you i probably don't even have
enough
uh yeah i i don't think i can do the
flying it where am i even going
[Music]
should i be here should i even be here
oh no that is so scary
[Music]
that is so scarce
go in what was that again lava level no
no no no no what's there
catch pekura yeah there was a bunny here
right
where's the bunny
[Music]
not now ah at 15 stars
okay i'll fight until i can save her
until i can catch her oh how did i get
back here
where am i even going
[Music]
okay i think what is that
is that where i came from
[Music]
oh no do i have to go here no 30 stars
i'll just go outside now
[Music]
okay let's do something easy
because we don't have much time left
oh i remember this place
what was here again nothing
i love the walking sounds
hello isn't this where the ghosts show
up
l is real what
why are you referencing a death note
is that even that note
okay there's nothing here huh
no death notes oh luigi
how did i get the idea of death note i
didn't even
read the manga where did i come from
oh okay you know what
let's go
here let's do more swimming
yay i think this is the last
level no i also didn't watch the anime
do i have to what do i do
what's my mission
[Music]
you also thought about deafness okay
that was not the other only one haha
what do i do eel time uh oh
you know the eel really reminds me of uh
super mario sunshine do you know that
that
that level with that was it an eel where
you have to brush the teeth
that's so nostalgic okay what do i do
though
i did what
[Music]
what was i supposed to do what was i
supposed to do
go in front of it don't bump into him to
swim in front
okay will do
got you thank you dear kfp employee
i think i'm getting better at swimming
i hate this i hate this view though
[Music]
can i eat the eel you know what i really
like
so what do i do now hello
hello i'm gonna die
what do i do wait let me get the coins
it's the coin point quick
don't touch it swim in front of him
then back down wait i
i don't even understand the controls
[Music]
collect coins yeah wait
hey i don't get it he comes out do i
have to wait
give him a hug no way oh my god i'm
gonna die
ah coins [\h__\h] i go up i go up first oh
my god can i make it
bait under him okay okay
okay okay wait that wasn't even all
oh what now why don't he came out what
do i do
what do i do
i do i go into the hole
[Music]
come on no no are you going back in i
hope not
okay wait wait
[Music]
now dammit the controls i swear
do i go in yes
wha wha wha what's happening what's
happening what's happening
what's happening do i have to say is
this some play from marin senpai again i
need coins or i'm gonna die
are they these electric again i need
coins
coin ma i can go up there
air please air i need air
thank god okay what is the thing that i
need to do
[Music]
puzzle time electric chest okay okay
well
i might die can i open that
how do i open that underwater
[Music]
please let me open you huh
does it have to be this heart come on
[Music]
ah
okay wait let me come up
go again where is where is up oh my god
oh my god i'm going to die here this
will be the end of me
chill okay now open the boxes
marine senpai are you doing this again
you want to play with me
this will be electric i swear oh wait
how do i open them
uh-uh wait wait this is too hard for me
no this is so frustrating
[Music]
wait it's not electric though
okay that was definitely not not the
right one
what was that what was that
no no no no
no oh my god oh my god this is so
stressful
okay it was not that one must be the
right one
mickey dicho
hi how do i open
hello
[Music]
touch the lock okay that was also not
it
let's try the middle one let's try the
middle one this time
hello is it you
please tell me it's you before i die
how do i no
let me touch you come on let me touch
you
oh it recovered me thank god
okay what now which one now i shall
choose you
yes yes yes
now maybe you is it you
no i have to open them again
yes okay okay i'll open it again no
problem no problem please give me a life
again though
please give me life will you give me
life again
no no no no no no
oh my god these swimming controls are
the worst
you're not gonna give me life no no i'm
gonna die
no i don't want to die
no no no oh thank god hey why are you
not no
no no no no no no
[Music]
all the bubbles the bubbles
okay that was a lot of fun though i
really enjoyed it
it was super nostalgic and i love the
soundtracks and i thought i wasn't even
doing that
bad for like if you think about how how
long
uh it has been since the last time i
played this
i hope you guys enjoyed it too hopefully
as much as i did
i really had lots of fun i think
tomorrow i'll try to stream
at a time um earlier so
around the time possibly where
i did the the super chat reading and
we will play for a few hours and then
i'll do the super chat reading of today
and
that's so much fun man ah
i really enjoyed that finally we're
getting like into some real good games
huh
because until now we only we only played
the egg game and fall guys but
these are all just like small games for
in between i would say
and originally i was gonna play fall
guys today as well but i i
realized uh today was the release of
this game and i ordered it before so
that's why uh it came in the mail today
and perfect timing for a while we'll be
playing some mario games i think
i hope that's okay in between we still
might do some stupid
fun short games as well and yeah
so tomorrow we'll do the uh continuation
but i'm actually not sure if i can
actually
clear this game i feel like i'm not good
enough for actually clearing this
i feel like i need more skills
and but yeah let's see how far we get
and if we get like sick of it
yeah i also start playing minecraft
sometime soon
so
yes
see you tomorrow everyone and at the end
in german
we say goodbye three
two one
thank you everyone so much i have so
much fun today
and also thanks again for um hanging out
with me during the super chat reading
today before this stream
i want to apologize for getting so
emotional and i want to make clear again
that
um that comment itself
the person who wrote it is not is not at
fault it was just uh
i was just too emotional you know it's
been so much going on
but all in all you all have been so
supportive of me
and i really appreciate it thank you so
much
see you tomorrow hashtag
please follow me on twitter and
subscribe to the channel
bye bye
[Music]
bye
i love you
bye bye tomorrow
i'll probably start uh around the same
time as i said but maybe like a little
bit later maybe one
one hour later than uh today's super
chat reading
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
you