questions
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
friends
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
hello
sorry for the way
wait
ah
for sure the window size always the
windows
ah
it's nice that you can make it any size
you want but okay I think I got it
I think I got it
Thank God now there's a little bit down
there
oh there we go there we go maybe that's
good a little bit more
alpacas are spitting at me already
they're like why don't you play for so
long where were you kiwawa
oh my God this is so nostalgic
where are we what are we doing
who am I what is this 2021
[Music]
first of all how do you open the chat no
wait at tables
okay can I write
because I know like good I had issues no
okay I can at least on This Server so I
added the other server
only
I added the because I think we have a
new server right
but I thought we were like connected
anyway so I don't know why we need a new
server ID
um but I still went into the game with
the old server idea because it showed me
the same amount of logged in people
on both servers
so I am very confused
yeah apparently I don't need the ID but
who knows I'm not even like you know I
don't know if I will
Kyla
it's the first time I see Kyla on
Minecraft which is an interesting thing
to say because she's always on Minecraft
right
um
I was trying to find the the slider
thing but wasn't it didn't it used to be
here am I just blind
oh wait maybe it's no
where is the sliders shaders I mean
wasn't there like a Shader thing here
that you can NPC or do you see an NPC oh
it's Kyla the NPC
I need to install them I don't
understand I downloaded an updated one
but does it even I don't I don't get it
I don't understand how this works
anymore I want shaders though because
this is so ugly
I need help to find I do have a weight
different OptiFine huh wait what up to
find do I have
ah
what what you need to install them for
this version so I need to look for ah
OptiFine 1.19.3
can I just because gonna be a little bit
of a longer stream anyway
can I just can I just can I just do this
really quickly
okay I see OptiFine
1.19.3 I wanna cause like I want
something nice to look at
us okay what version did I have what
version was it when I last played I
wonder because my game I guess obviously
updated to
1.19.4 on its own and now I had to go
back to 1.19.3 which is why I was I was
late
okay I have to I have to jar data will
you do this again do you like double
click it is that it is that it
oh yeah I think so
install
or extract I think install
1.19.3 OptiFine successful in style okay
I'm sorry I have to restart
um
I mean I think I have to restart
[Music]
I saw that fauna was like streaming
Minecraft yesterday and I saw she had
like Animal Crossing style bgm running
and that got me in the mood
so now I have a playlist as well I don't
know where fauna got hers from oh
no it must have been replaced okay play
please work
is she also using audio status you
figure out how to get Animal Crossing
POI ish music from uh audio stuck
because you can't type in Animal
Crossing you have to type in the
Japanese name atsumori because we our
audio stock subscription is for a
Japanese one oh
oh
oh okay I'm in the in the like login
screen
it shows me like it's endlessly pinging
the new server ID but the old one is
already ready so I guess we're good
oh I see shaders let's go
okay is it gonna you know
you want to capture it OBS eventually
come on there we go upstairs
oh okay say that listen that didn't take
so long and that's much prettier
[Music]
oh my God it's been so long
Hisashi booty
oh did things change I have a feeling
that I logged in once
for some maybe I dreamed it but I have a
feeling I logged in once a million years
ago okay not so long maybe half a
million years ago
to
do something I don't know what maybe
just to check if after the server update
if my character was like still alive and
if I had my fangs
oh no
the after that was after the weather
prep I think um
maybe it was a dream
okay
oh God it's been so long it's been so
long
what is this game burn your house down
and start a new maybe I should I know
um so first of all I guess I should take
a tour
maybe I it's Kyla streaming maybe we
should hire her to give me a tour
streaming if not then she probably
doesn't really have
priorities
no she's not Kayla
then she can lead me to where it is and
I don't have to follow like the
coordinates right she can also give me
um like give me a tour of the ID server
she's on the break
what no way what are you talking about
she's not gonna break oh only could show
me too
why not why not answer
um
could ask Ollie Too
or Ollie
a medical checkup oh
does someone oh maybe both Wanna Give me
a tour uh
well always probably streaming
spontaneous tour
of the ID server and then
show me the portal to the new world
[Laughter]
oh he's swimming even what's going on
what what
skunky I would love oh
yay
that's awesome then I don't have to do
anything so we'll get that first and
then I want to see if I can find an ally
um
only flare is streaming oh
let's meet in in collab you see
and
I am at my house
do you know where it is
I'm typing such long sentences it's so
it feels like it doesn't fit into
Minecraft like this is not what you do
in Minecraft you don't write long
sentences
okay where's our we have this Co-op
thingy there we go
uh
okay
okay hey I'm getting a pickup service oh
but since I can't do oh hi hi
okay okay okay okay oh oh you have an
every verb
oh
hi hi hi
what's up why are you like in Minecraft
but not streaming
oh uh I'm just working on my house a uh
off stream oh it'd be easier to
concentrate well on the ID server or on
that new server
everybody left their old servers or what
oh no no no no it's just that um the
hype is all in the new server I guess so
I'm just kidding the hype guys there's
all these volume okay or should I make
her a bit low okay okay
let's make her louder
I'm on my way by the way thank you so
much for accepting my spontaneous
request
me it's been the first time in forever
oh yeah she is right now on medical
leave I I am I in the right timeline is
did I like enter some weird portal where
Kyla takes breaks
um
to be honest I'm not sure she just
suddenly decided that she wants to have
a medical checkup she decided she wanted
to have a medical check and that what is
that to just today
uh that's for a few days I think what I
think she's on the oh hello I see you oh
hi hi ah I I knew I saw something flying
up there hey Ollie you're looking uh
Kylie not like how I remember you but I
guess it must be my imagination wait
there we go oh you got the ninja outfit
right yeah let's go oh you're missing
the big ass thing oh wait that's is that
another outfit the biggest thing over
your head oh yeah the the flower too bad
you can't do that in Minecraft huh yeah
I wish we could use mods but anyways
where did you want to go again well
first of all are you sure you have time
like it's late over there right
nah I mean I stay up until four anyway
so you have no streams planned nope okay
wow thank you okay I I never went to the
ID server before so seeing that would be
cool and then from there really yeah
never and I thought we could go to the
new server together because I don't know
where it is and I'm too lazy to look at
the coordinates
hey come follow me oh my God I'm so
lucky I'm so lucky should I bring
something oh my God wait I have a bunch
of things that maybe I should leave here
just one second oh yeah yeah yeah take
your time okay I have a shulker box if
you want to borrow oh no I have stuff in
here too no problemo how do you do this
again like this am I not wearing armor
oh well it's cuter my guess
it's so nice to hear your voice it's
been a while and it's nice to hear your
voice too only
I haven't been able to catch up to your
streams oh no no worries about that I
stream too much I've been streaming like
I've been catching up with streaming
why is this not going in oh can can a
shulker not go into a shulker I forgot
oh no it can't if you want it'd be
better if you uh carry another another
an Ender true true yeah I have one down
here let me put that down there so since
when can you not put a shulker into a
shulker
was that always a thing
that's crazy
okay let me put this here let me put
this here and this year and I really
need nothing I don't need anything just
put everything away if you want to just
put everything away
okay I'll keep that okay okay I'm ready
I'm ready
this is so perfect I think I might have
to put you on my thumbnail because this
might take like at least an hour
oh yeah for sure for sure I'll put you
on my phone afterwards
back in the days when I used to play
Minecraft more often uh no one was ever
online at the same time as me so it was
really depressing it was so sad
that is pretty sad not gonna lie I feel
you
but hey you feel me really because like
your time zone is way closer to Japanese
time zone so yeah oh are you in Japan
right now no
no no but like at least your time zone
is closer so you can you know hang out
with some Japanese members in Minecraft
I'm in Europe like nobody plays when I
play
true unless I start super early then I
have like Japanese prime time which is
like 3 P.M for me
oh shoot
I can walk too
have they still not invented a double
double mine cards that would be so cute
if you could ride together
it'd be really really nice if we could
just roll our coaster together
yeah also but the answer for you guys
don't have the uh the portal to directly
to ID so we'll have to go to the JP
server we don't send the ID oh man
not that I remember okay okay so maybe
I'm mistaken can I get if we go to the
ID server can I get a free electron
you know you could ask Kayla right now
like she she would be like oh you can
just take one from the shelves can I get
a free Elijah from you when I reach IDs
I mean I've heard it from the Legends
and everybody who visits you know gets
like presents and there's so many light
trust I want to say that with my own
eyes
oh sure
be careful to be Smitten by the
blacksmith
I've been um smitten ever since I met
her in Indonesia yeah ain't she Charming
I hate it
no it's so funny though because I first
really I thought she was a manager
because like why why would the manager
be here they're all in Japan
can I be very honest with you um I
didn't recognize her at first
well yeah I guess I guess she wasn't
wearing her usual clothes and stuff yeah
yeah for sure
but you Ali you're unrecognizable
because you come with a voice a very
loud voice and what I mean you are you
cannot be not recognized that's what I
want to say
thank you
[Music]
it's like a new server IP right
do because I I didn't actually use it
though can I still go into the new
server
before
to be honest
it's not sure okay maybe so that you
automatically spawn right away in the
new server as a new character no do you
wait if you use that IP you come out as
a new character right
like with no stuff in your inventory
right
not really oh last time I input the IP
turns out it's kind of like the same oh
my God I don't yeah I don't know
Minecraft anymore
so knowledgeable
he burned I heard that it's her uh
tradition to actually explode yago's
face what
yeah that's a good tradition Thomas
invite did that
once in a while I guess yeah
[Music]
we have viago in the ID server too if
you want to explore that of course you
do have Yago in the ID server too
don't you have everything in the ID
server oh we go up here wait how do you
go up again space space
I need to get warmed up because we're
actually gonna try to kill the weather
with the uh weather yeah on I think
Thursday or so
God dang yeah
so it's been so long and I don't even
know the controls anymore so I have to
have to learn it again
it's like riding a bicycle you'll get
through it I guess we get into the D to
get to the ID
[Music]
kind of difficult to read it
oh
cozy in here already what is this place
nothing what
place be
well I mean since I just like come and
came in here I'm guessing it's like just
a welcome area but
well how about the restaurants
wow wow wow oh I'm ready to be impressed
by everybody's oh you're actually on the
ship
what this is a ship a ship oh it's a
wait
is there a reason why it's a ship
uh because you know
um uh how do we say Maritime uh we
travel to the waters usually so
on the ID server you mean
I'm not like uh traditionally and uh
according to history we travel via boats
so we decided to make a ship wait so am
I imagining things or didn't uh the ID
um 3D stage have a ship
yeah right right exactly okay I thought
that was like you know connected
yeah awesome so now I guess oh
I don't hear myself anymore I
disconnected oh there we go I disconnect
my headphones ah so so so so so the the
same reason applies to why you have it
for your 3D stage that's cool that's
cool I didn't know that yeah I thought
it was like random pretty much
associated with chips mmm potato chips
yum I I'm also associated with potato
chips
yeah okay so there's quite a lot of
places that we can visit first you want
to check out the current place that
we're in do you want to go
um
do you want to go right do you want to
go left uh because we have like
different volumes here
um
I wanna I guess
follow whatever Ali thinks is best to
see in that order
so I guess we'll go with the mainland
first you know it will take Kayla's
place okay do we have shaders on
this place is so pretty when it rains at
night oh my God yeah right so pretty
yeah so right here is the ID Harbor we
first arrived oh my God from afar it
looks even nicer oh we all built it
together
whoa what's this there used to be a map
here but uh oh we had like some bugs
going on so we're still fixing it oh oh
no okay so that's what that is
[Music]
you guys all this already is cooler than
everything we have in the en server but
don't say that don't say that
okay oh pretty there's so much detail I
think we're going to show you the jam
yes is this very big clock tower oh who
built it yeah
all of the ID we built it together and
it's the first ever monument that we
ever built in the entire server it looks
so so so cool
yeah does it go ding dong ding dong wait
I'm faster here is it because you guys
have a beacon
yeah right in the middle did you kill
the Wither together already
uh uh I think it was muna's and by who
did that oh wow yeah so it wasn't
together you can go up too if you want
to like see the whole View
okay let's go up
yeah
yeah tender from here and then there's
like a bunch of Soul Sand elevators oh
several levels I see oh yes
okay
we're like sick at all
no no I might just drown
what am I drowning this kind of elevator
but at least it's really fast
[Music]
yeah very cloudy today
yeah so
we can you can uh choose which which way
you want to go because there's a lot of
C
what
I want to go to the direction where all
these houses
ah my direction is nearby this Castle
okay okay and we'll go there next
skyless House close
this is over there by the desert oh okay
okay she made her house black so she
wants to make it as visible as possible
so she build it on the desert
um
is it far
uh we can dig the railway oh we have a
railway okay okay well we have a railway
too
it's all good oh
I gotta do something about this this
just hurts
right
you cannot have your your visitors be
burnt alive can you
we had a few casualties before
wrong side
I think it's this side yes
uh Crouch oh yeah right you can Crouch
and then it doesn't hurt ah remember
yeah
I never won wow even the view in the
elevator is nice
right
y okay so would you like Kayla's house
first or my house first uh I'll be your
house first I guess okay um
so my house
is over here it doesn't have like a
secret road that leads to it this is is
is Kobo online for some reason because I
think the rain maybe is caused by her
can we tell her to stop
anything I feel like cowboy is lacking
in her job
where are you
this is the ollie area oh did you build
like this these paths as well
yeah I terraformed and everything whoa
what a nice view indeed she's already
telling giving me a script on what to
say but I I wouldn't even need that I
would say the same thing wow oh I like
this I like this Pond oh you have a
turtle in the in the in the boat
it looks like a part of the boat
yeah it got stuck there I don't know
what to do with it
seems cozy in there it's I think it has
it's using it as its own New Shell like
a because it has a top shell the green
one but now that the boat is the
basically protecting the bottom of the
turtle which is normally not protected
so yeah yeah double shell wow
[Music]
I got terrorized with stones what I
moved the mountains and islands for you
wow that's so romantic
oh oh she was making space because you
requested it or what no uh so there's
this project called borobudur and it
requires a lot of stone so she decided
to annihilate a whole amount of stones
for me
to finish the pack when all these chests
are not normally not here
no they're not I must say I'm quite
disappointed in Kyla because these are
not even shulker boxes what the hell
[Laughter]
these are just really cheap wooden
chests I mean come on what your
reputation oh do you have like food in
here no it's empty
um
we'll get some later though oh no no
need I don't need with a nice kitchen
design oh thank you and then we can just
go here and take a little nap
guest room
oh oh
nice
I like how you made it basically into a
tatami because it looks like it's on
like you know on the ground yeah pretty
cute green wow nice to see I'm pretty
proud how do you have so much like
patience to build something so nice man
I mean it's relaxing to build stuff is
it not maybe this is like
maybe maybe because like what I can what
I can enjoy a bit more than this in
terms of building is like building in
Sims 4 or Sims generally I guess this is
just another SIMS yeah is
whoa what's upstairs
this is my actual room that was the
guest room we go upstairs we have like a
little study room
that is so nice
the guest room somehow looks nicer well
it is for the guests I don't need to
sleep in a fancy you have a closet that
is so cool I'm sorry if we're playing
fast with phobia right now we can hide
in here and hide from the ghosts where
we could just Place seven minutes
[Music]
[Laughter]
safe safe these walls look like
chocolate bars
yeah yummy they're pretty cute dark Oaks
Noise Okay we saw all these cows very
pretty I like it
I like uh I'm actually The Decorator of
hollow ID oh I usually am the one who
was in charge of like making fast ways
and whatnot oh I think you you actually
also made the our like entrance area
pretty pretty I mean the one that leads
to my house that was you wasn't it
there's also this uh
this castle that I'm actually very proud
about you made a castle
yeah I forgot I think we sold it to
someone but I don't remember who owns it
anymore
oh oh a little fountain
horsey High horses a horse stable
and this is supposed to be like a
storage slash a farming crop even the
storage is so old but I can't open them
all right they're just decorations and
then this one I can open oh was it a lag
oh it was a lag
oh lag okay
oh nothing's being stored
yeah cause no one's using we forgot who
we sold it ah okay it makes sense makes
sense gouda owns this Castle I think
said someone oh mume or bae or something
you guys have no idea either
none of us know Bae I think babe bought
a floating island and forgot about it
uh-huh oh yeah the floating island
from over here
I'm really lagging right now it's the ID
server where are you here okay oh I'm
behind you I'm right here oh my god oh
my god wow
sorry I might be lagging just just keep
on running oh and that's the floating
island
damn yeah how much does it cost
um I think it costs like one kiss or
something I forgot oh come on come on
who can you guys sell these things for
so cheap
because it's just so fun to build stuff
or is that just you know the conversion
between USD and I IDR
yeah we just want to be noticed man wait
the upstairs
Castle no
nothing much though I want to see it's
mostly this oh there's a little clerk we
can go up uh you can go to the tower
maybe I should buy the castle
does it come with a title
um the castle owner title sure I I guess
you can see that
no I mean like because for example in uh
uh where was it guys where do I have my
title
and what country do I have my lady title
oh you have a lady I have a lady title
yeah it's a Scotland oh yeah cause um
some viewers purchased uh some land for
me which is really tiny but it comes
with a title I mean it's just a joke but
I even got like a whole certificate for
it well you could be a baroness okay
fairness of the ID Castle or something
oh I'll think about I'll consider it
I'll check you know with my with my
accountant can I just re-log in really
quickly because I need to fix this oh
yeah sure I'll be waiting okay one
second
oh
don't joke don't joke let's see
hopefully it is better now
maybe it's inevitable with the ID server
although I mean the Japan server also
pretty crazy too so it never happened to
me there
don't worry a lot of members have been
experiencing lag anyways wait I forgot
to show the game again
okay all right let's go let's go yeah
so I think it's about time we show you
our Subway a Subway okay yeah
and I think it's better if we go towards
the uh Kayla's house okay sounds good to
me
yeah whoa
that is
so much better looking than ours
somewhere entrance
[Laughter]
oh you guys actually put like effort
into it I mean you girls also weren't
forced to build it so you know you went
in there with a different mindset I
think oh hello oh is that a Subway in
the subway
[Laughter]
but this is more like a you know in
subways they sell like little
oh yeah Subways yeah
Subway
we can we can eat here
I haven't eaten at Subway for a long
long long long long long time oh Subway
actually sounds really good
yeah and this is the subway too the
Kayla area well okay literally Kayla
area but the desert area where's this oh
we can just get in
did you just spawn and you pushed
yourself yeah
oh
[Music]
so go he's so good wow oh my God I feel
like I'm riding a Disney ride
you do yeah oh hello we put a lot of
effort in decorating it's a bit faster
than a Disney right I mean the not the
roller coaster but like uh you know more
like a visual ride oh it changed because
now we're in the desert
yeah wow
whoa
so cool
it's so pretty oh oh that's it no I want
to see more
don't worry there's still more we have
like one more Subway I think you'll like
it because like this one is not made out
of diamonds
because we made this like uh this is
like the first Subway we've ever built
oh
yeah and oh do not be shocked when you
come up these stairs you'll see our
nether portal ah okay oh okay yeah
oh holy
macaroni that thing over there is so
cool like out of that world is that the
never portal yes oh the nether portal
what
sick
this doesn't look like Minecraft that's
so stylish oh magma vlogs
yeah and lava
sheesh
sheesh that is intimidating and
threatening and really cool I can step
on this huh okay oh yeah one of our
pride in Hollow ID you guys are insane
patients were needed when building this
that is so cool oh
that is so how how do you girls like
decide on what design things should be
when you build something together
oh usually we just look through
Pinterest and go oh yo this looks cool
let's do this and that's what we do whoa
whoa Pinterest like other Minecraft
Builds you use as a inspiration
yeah uh in the original Minecraft build
this was a prismarine and it was used
for the uh what what was it called The
Guardian
oh the guardian what was it called the
one that's underwater Oh yeah
into like black and red so that it
matches the nether yeah that is so much
cooler oh my God I love it man what
what so insane okay wow and the
materials you all collect together like
on your own or do you spawn the move
like creative or so
um we have like some leftovers from M
Chan when we first started off oh oh wow
so we used what M10 gave to us some we
still had to look by for by ourselves
but it still built it like in survival
oh good job damn damn a lot of debts
next is also one of our main attractions
oh
[Laughter]
or so
what was it called it's her like Memory
Lane
whoa whoa whoa
what is that her lore
uh these are like her uh memorable
moments in Minecraft and she likes to
store them here
what the [\h__\h]
yeah that's two values every single
moment
very romantic isn't it what
oh my God let me read this
August 26 2022 I had Japanese class of
Louisiana at August 24th she taught me
how to say
she said she would give me the kinoku in
Minecraft later on I finally met her
while she was finalizing her booth in
natsumatsuri I typed kinokonohoshi and
she gave me this mushroom which is
accomplished
cute isn't it cute I hate her
ah I love how you say that oh there's a
monster
leave it to me
this is so cute I love the the heart
shape and the lightning and the
decoration oh my God yeah crack her
recent ones too
now I saved you thank you
with your toes
no let's focus on the Kyla house
what is this so
um
well I mean it's a blacksmith house
it looks cool enter at your own risk
what does that mean are we gonna die
we're not uh I mean in a way kind of why
are you getting rid of the lights
no I I accidentally put them down okay
can you go first please oh don't worry
we won't die as in die and lose our
items okay that will die in a different
way oh yeah because it's so impressive
what
oh she moved it so Kylie you're my
inspiration I love father
she removed it I wonder why
removed what
mind break warning it where is the Mind
break
ah there they are yeah that's what I
wanted to see
um
you can make the move the the heads move
yeah with the red block hmm I've heard
there is something I've heard many
things about this room oh wait the boxes
are not even filled with the light runs
what the hell
no it's because he kept on giving it
away yeah someone dies okay and also
this floor used to be shulker boxes oh
but it got too laggy so I think she
decided to like take it down and a lot
of people ask for a shelter
using all of her fangs
ah I see I see she found the city wait
what was that
oh
so oh yeah so yeah so do I just take one
off of the wall
yeah that's that's usually what she does
she'd be like oh yeah just take one and
he is okay it's just that I haven't mend
them yet ah
ah okay okay okay I'll take I'll take
us
okay well I don't want to use it yet
because I will break it
don't want to break it okay
yeah so that was Kayla's ass what
what that's it
speed up speed up
people
[Laughter]
I mean
I mean okay yeah I'm very
shorts were really
um yeah
impressive but I I don't know I thought
this would be bigger oh wait there's
something down here where does this
bring me
he has
she has this um
she has this real railroad that's called
the free talk railroads oh basically she
has this place called the basugihan
um there's a lot of fancy stuffs diamond
blocks Gold Blocks what whatever you
name it and um to get there
um you'll have to write this at Sudan
Railway that takes about like 45 minutes
oh so is that where she keeps all her
really impressive things or what
oh I mean she has more impressive things
I feel but wait aren't the rails cut off
here on it oh not here I think it's
still down there oh wait it's not over
here it's in her room yeah that's the
railway
okay okay
if Kyla will see my reaction what she's
gonna say she she will feel challenged
to you know make something way more
impressive what the hell is this I said
a broken elytra is that what they look
like
yeah what is this thing
here it is you go down uh through here
oh
and if you go down I think that's the
zatsu railway
oh chocolate floor yummy yummy yummy oh
Ollie what the [\h__\h] what what
where did you fall
I stand corrected oh
I'm glad I didn't follow you oh right
here oh no oh no oh no
[Music]
um
interesting uh maybe that one
maybe it was that one
do not fall no yeah no I I'll say it on
top here why are you respawning where
are you my house
hurry I'll get there in the juice okay
I'll I'll see what's around here maybe
something more impressive or skeleton
horse
I didn't know any better
I guess you never went on the 40 minutes
uh that's a rail of her
I did once but I forgot which part it
was
God damn it how could you forget this is
what you get for forgetting
I'll play in the ID server more yeah
yeah
everybody's leaving to new servers
because it's so fancy you know new
things always so fancy
is that the what is that I wonder
do you guys know oh God it's so dark now
no darkened darkened rainy again is this
like England or what the [\h__\h] I thought
I was in Indonesia feels like I'm in
England it's because it's Indonesia we
live in a tropical country ah is it
rainy season right now maybe if it's
rainy season then where is Urena
are you gonna like pick up your things
somehow like maybe drop some water or so
I guess
you know what no it's okay but you had
another
I can just ask and I can just take
another one you guys treat fakes as if
they're worth nothing
oh my God
yeah I'll take one I'll just pop one up
from her
well and and yeah
all right okay let's move on to the next
thing let's try to not find the whole
yeah better to not find it or attention
okay
okay oh wait I think I can use in the
lighter to descend I'll try oh okay be
careful
don't
oh
she's doing it oh I see you descending
you know what I'll stop
Kayla I'm sorry
um
I mean why does she have that hole what
also it's light down there is did she
like
um
did she did she dig all the way to the
other side of the globe is is Minecraft
a globe and she came out on the other
side
what look at me because it looks it
looks bright when you look down as if
there's like you know you're sitting the
other side of the of the
Earth
oh don't worry I made sure that I fell
[Laughter]
could have at least
saved uh your spawn spot here by
clicking on the bed
yeah
let's just continue wait what
find the correct hole there is a hopper
chest on the bottom there's a hopper
there's a hopper Ollie
apparently if you go for the right hole
and there's a hopper that picks up
everything from the wrong holes
again
oh yeah and they say get water bucket
you know I would drown before I get
there
no not to have the dream uh SMP skills
to just water bucket yeah but just just
if you touch the bed you can do it right
here you know cool
do you really want to be wasting Kyla's
electrons huh
there she is
I've touched it
no oh is this the right hole oh no this
is the
the going up coming back up
why is it so complicated
oh
I found it really oh yeah I looked at
that one too
um
I did it yay is there a hopper
is it safe down there
I accidentally went up again
[Laughter]
why is this thing
maybe I should go down too I want to see
two is it safe to fall down
yes there is
wow oh
is this the path
yes
I found it
cheap I think if it takes 45 minutes to
go down this path I will know how long
it takes to build it no no I don't want
to take it now guys no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
where's the hopper located
um
so there's the amethyst room
Where Art Thou
you guys know
I thought you could open this hmm
why is there a cat stuck here somewhere
I hear her
that one Union torture you need a torch
or something to open really
go back up and see the corner
I think you have to place a redstone
torch down on the right spot ha it's so
complicated maybe maybe oh you found it
I think I found it
a little redstone torch
there's nothing here though wait maybe
Kyla will find it if it's got collected
by a hopper then she probably has it
somewhere then yeah she probably has it
so I think we can continue okay
yeah I'll ask her later
okay oh
well at least you know it was funny when
you died so
it was good content
and then you died again that was even
better content
I feel like I'm wasting your time
and honestly I had no idea what to do
today so
the only the only thing I I was like
thinking of doing is finding an ally
Allah
yeah yeah
but I'm gonna do that after I'm done
with the tour
oh do you want to sleep
yeah okay
good morning
oh it feels nice to wake up with you
right by myself I thought you were gonna
leave that uncommented and just leave it
there
no of course not I gotta take my shots
it's okay Ollie I I get you I get you no
problem what are we gonna check out next
uh next we have the there
is that a bonfire we could check out the
risu island
okay yes what is this see ya what's this
thing over there
oh that's it I think we've told you
before it's the the the rice don't don't
get in though it's a trap oh no oh my
God thank you for telling me
yeah it's a dumbbell is used for
celebrations right and we decided to
like make a
yellow rice
yeah the yellow rice
Indonesian food again
wait have you tried Nasi Padang I think
so yeah pretty sure
the the rice stats wrapped up with paper
ah
yeah
[Music]
did I did I maybe I don't remember
eating something that was wrapped in the
paper but I ate like Indonesian rice
dishes
oh pretty sure and then you know the the
peanut was it the peanut sauce chicken
or so that was so good
[Music]
um
foreign
I know how to do this
Oh I thought that would spawn
are you lagging because I think I saw
your avatar just standing still oh okay
probably lagging yeah because that
button is supposed to lag
okay
that was scary that was scary I thought
it was like crushed
to death
only it doesn't oh there we go finally
let's go oh did you hear me
yeah hi
hi
I'm coming now
you explaining how you lost everything
yeah making excuses
I mean I really did die
feel like for us to dying is just it
doesn't really affect us much does it
and that makes us too risky we do risky
things because we can afford it
um it's I'm not I'm not saying that our
lives don't matter it's just that we'll
get resurrected here yeah
oh we're going through a different
Subway Okay
subway that I built only Built holy [\h__\h]
that is beautiful
that is incredible I love it wow oh
wow wow I feel like I'm playing a
different game when I'm on the idea it's
a different game
oh my god oh wow
very nice Ollie you did a good job
so fancy
I feel like I'm in a medieval type of
game
oh yeah because um you see in her ID all
of us kind of uh uh we had a like a
little meeting a little discussion and
we decided that we wanted our server to
have like a certain theme hmm
so we grouped up everyone has like their
own areas they can build whatever but
the theme is Medieval okay honestly the
way it kicks you out of the the minecart
and then collects it immediately that is
so smart
right you girls are so small my Empress
I'm very sorry but do you have any food
yeah how do I throw it again
for the Cutie some kfp chicken oh
delicious
thank you 10 out of 10 review guys
[Music]
the thighs especially yeah right yes
in case there's too many people queuing
up I guess
cute I think I saw the lights from far
away
from the ship right yeah the floating
lines
all this Lisa sent by both by herself
can we enter everything
yeah why don't we have full access to
everything except for one thing oh bad
it's hidden oh the ship is there oh yeah
you made Subways even for like pretty
short distances
oh I like this
[Music]
where's her actual house
but her actual house is this way the
lanterns so pretty
so pretty
soon
wow nice bee also I think I I keep on
lagging
oh where did Ollie go
here hello hi
don't worry I got you I have your stream
up oh oh oh Sakura area
yeah that's the Onsen if you want to
check it out later you have an awesome
tool
Lisa Senpai has an honor oh wow wow
such a huge area oh my God yeah and this
is her house
[Music]
I'd say it's quite the house it's cute
it's like yeah oh you guys work with a
lot of wood with like flower decorations
and stuff I like it it's very pretty
natural she hasn't done anything to the
interior though
oh nice cozy and warm here
[Music]
man
oh this damn so organized
I
need to hire you girls to do something
for me
we were nearly hired it's just that we
didn't get our payment kid so we're wait
did you receive a lot of emotional
damage recently
uh through Kayla yes oh why
um she gets [\h__\h] I don't oh don't
worry don't worry I I I'm I I can be
your [\h__\h] I guess you
I am happy happy I mean I don't know
what exactly that entails but what does
it entail being a [\h__\h]
it it this it just means that I I I'm I
got one point away from Kayla
I have to say your house was cooler than
Kyla's
I mean she has lied to us but you know
but that was her old house you haven't
seen her new house in the new series oh
[\h__\h] okay and I'm a little bit scared
oh what is what is this place is this
like a farm
oh that's just a decoration that this
isn't by made it's cute
yeah and if we go up ahead we can see
zeta's house oh
okay
I think I saw a sign that said that the
house somewhere
yeah you see over there the gray uh
modern looking ah she went for a modern
style wait are you guys
why do you guys have so many biomies so
close by why is there a mushroom one
right here what the [\h__\h]
yeah we're pretty lucky
[\h__\h] it's not actually a mushroom volume
it's just uh this used to be like a dark
forest with lots of mushrooms oh okay
wait that makes sense yeah um those are
I guess not that rare
I don't know I don't know anymore what's
rare and what's not what is this
oh
that's a Zeta Subway so if you ride it
you'll arrive in one of the uh train
station whoa hi horses one kind of
escaped baginda
okay that means you're uh your highness
oh can I enter wow oh interesting oh so
Santa likes a more modern style I see I
see oh I like it she also has where was
it wait this looks like a like a cow
pattern interestingly
yeah and over here is the cap dungeon
captain
[Music]
Roblox
wait wait a second wait
a second
please wait I
don't
this is not as wholesome as I thought it
would be what's going on here
I remember this is it that we're talking
about
it wasn't kind of semi-psychopathic I
guess I don't know because she's like
one of the two members who I haven't met
uh in person yet but
wait save the cats like what the [\h__\h]
some of them are alive why would she do
that what's her problem what the [\h__\h]
said that what the [\h__\h] what the actual
[\h__\h] I'm gonna break this open I'm like
how the [\h__\h] can she do this to the cats
she's a cat herself so how how can she
do this to her own people what
yeah
huh so what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm gonna
I don't know if I can ever consider
collabing with her ever after seeing
this like what the [\h__\h] but but you guys
are kind of kind of Sammy cats right
yeah but apparently she hates cats what
the [\h__\h]
what's what the [\h__\h] like that's changed
my impression of her very much I'm
sleepy
sleep I I am shook head
I was gonna invite her to girls talk but
now I changed my mind like what the hell
no I should have showed you
said I'm sorry
oh you can't just show this to me this
is terrifying terrifying
didn't want to see that
okay what's next show me something more
happy
um we can see the Japanese Onsen and
within the Japanese Onsen we have you
sent by secret house okay okay yeah if
you say my secret house does she also
have a non-secret house
um she has a non-secret dumpy
no like literally uh she built one
you can see right there we'll see her
dump you really good I see a big
eel-free figuring out
cute
the dumpy then
she probably stole from me
I will I was trying to get my butt
buffed and it's still not as good as
hers
I don't understand
it's probably she probably has pads in
her pants
other people pad their bra but she pads
her panties
all right so what is this this is the
this is like the this uh you know how
like in nonsense they have like an
Indian
[Music]
yeah oh
over here we have a changing room oh
[Music]
nothing in there so I guess I gotta get
naked
that's what you're doing an Onsen hmm
oncensor right here oh
that makes me want to go to an Onsen
again which is a great thing to say for
me because I hate that like idea of
getting naked in an onset of strangers I
hate that but I had a good time with
Cali in Hokkaido
a winter trip to Hokkaido and first we
went to Sapporo like the big city and
then we went uh to like we took a bus
right into the mountains and then the
mountainous area we had this little
beautiful special ryokan which was
surrounded by a [\h__\h] ton of snow and
they had so many different little Onsen
like baths
and and I had to really
overcome my you know my my fears where
did you go I drowned
but yeah we went in there
okay it was nice the snow was so nice it
looked so pretty oh man
uh memories
for real where'd you go where'd you go
for real for real nearby this there is
there's going to be like a little hole
you might want to go in
within the water
nearby the stairs
I think I see you
wait how do you go down
oh there we go oh oh [\h__\h] I accidentally
drowned that's scary that's scary whoa
that is cool and scary
oh wow whoa whoa whoa whoa what the hell
her Secret Garden what the [\h__\h] that's
insane wow I don't know why she doesn't
want to show it but she also has like a
really cool looking house that's so cool
that's so pretty I like that it's so
secret
um
so hidden away
oh what kind of tree is that because
it's like so orange so it's nothing
so uh something like a world tree hmm
yeah and these these quartz
quartz oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's a really bright tree I like it
pretty
shiny wait eofi built this
uh I kind of helped out
only always helping when someone needs
help be always there just like for me
oh shots
yeah her house is right here oh
you go here wait let's go through Divine
in the secret area there's another
secret oh fishies hello fishies well
they're pretty what fishes are those
what are those tropical fishes damn
pretty pretty
oh
oh in the cave oh
yes right
right split up so nicely
I wonder if she never gets like visitors
over here no she never gets them I mean
I mean in terms of like zombies and so
on maybe those are the only visitors she
gets sadly
wow it's pretty spacious in here
right she's actually pretty good at
building it's just that she gets motion
sick a lot
[Music]
a lot
oh
[Music]
yeah oh
really Airy Airy ceiling so that it
flows through
hmm
what do you like me thank you for
showing me
all right and the last one is probably
cobles last one but it's pretty fun
got a visitor all right you got no armor
her I I have armor I will kill him
well he got he got uh
golden armor
I'll distract him
[Music]
I love your sound effects
[Applause]
you are amazing I am a part-time Warrior
after all
she is she is this is so cool oh my God
I like the ideas you guys have and you
put so much commitment into it the only
aspect I like of Minecraft is not the
building aspect but the adventuring
aspect so I normally don't build things
you know
I could literally never have the
motivation to do this kind of thing
foreign
that's a big ass crack wow
damn wow
how do you
laughs
we have to eat the scaffolding for it no
scaffolding I has no it's okay it's okay
let's go please maybe
a cool little space I forgot that Cobble
space was actually really really far so
oh what about Wayne in place
weenie please Winnie please is very
close to the portal okay okay
you think I saw everything that I need
to see already
please
all right there's no place want a place
we're actually going to her Direction
right now okay okay
this is such a great tour I will give
you 10 out of 10 on Google reviews
wait yeah I think that's that's five
five out of five actually
Stars
it's the most I ever get the last time I
got eight out of 100. oh what the [\h__\h]
who gave you that
Kayla what
you gave Kayla a tour
yes of what
of the ID server oh when she just joined
yes what so she was new and you're her
Senpai and she gives you eight out of
100.
brutal isn't it it is brutal my God I
didn't know she was super maybe only two
ID members and then to Japan and Ian
remember she's really nice
[Music]
this is she has a lot of stuff in here
is it lag on your part a little bit yeah
wow wow but I can see
an automatic farm right beneath her
house
it's a bit spooky this house yes all
right let me let me let me log back in
one more time
ow what the [\h__\h] okay
I'm back
looks better now I think maybe it's the
automatic farm that's killing me right
now
whoa a little Onsen so you can look at
the ID while you chill the flower is
kind of cool it's like constantly giving
the the bath like a special scent and
all that I suppose like a bath bomb all
right wow
pretty nice you can just look out the
window and you see Yago
oh
there he is
[Music]
fancy wow
oh nice views here yeah very outdoor-ish
you can see Yago wherever you go
and don't get it wherever you go
ah funny I didn't get it first
what's the what's the um the thing in
front of the Bee by the way
to be um in all honesty I don't know it
might be an orange a pineapple I'm not
sure or or a carrot deep in the ground
before being pulled out also be a carrot
okay okay is there a second floor that
we should see
there's a second floor but I kind of
broke it what do you mean you broke it
uh there was a villager and I needed to
get it down so I had to break the stair
on the floor oh no that's her room right
there oh
oh
what oh wait so there was actually a
floor here before Oh [\h__\h] yes
now let's put cooler okay
oh yeah wow wow
that's so detailed yeah amethyst she
also has like an amethyst Farm down
there
it's killing me now too guys sorry I'm
feeling starting to feel sick by my fov
somebody in the chat set of tubes
yeah I think maybe we should skip out no
no no it's okay it's okay
I just had to turn down the fob it was
like making me feel sick it was so cool
damn does she not get legs when she
comes to her old house all of us get
legs when we go to her
the reason being down here oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
wait this is like this reminds me of
crony
oh no yeah it was
by bunker when he actually oh whoa
what is that
Flappy slime zillion carrots because you
know pecores didn't buy it
I thought it was like a little bit more
greenish a little bit more turquoise
carrots carrots oh where are the carrots
where are the carrots oh we sold it
we're having a whole ID inflation right
next door we sold it to all of these
Traders
oh
scary
this is scary this is not let them out
oh no this is a Trade Center this is
their home no no no this is not
they need more space to live than that
this is like the tiniest Japanese
one-room apartment ever that you could
find it's cool
it's cool no they're just mad because
they they haven't gone their room
colored unlike these people they're
pretty chill about it I can't see stuff
like this this is like
terrifying this just shows that
there will never be any other race than
humans taking over the humans because we
are just too crucial and we will we will
torture everything that threatens us we
will even torture our own people
into your farm right next door oh and at
least they have a little bit more space
in there
wait look is there like at the in the
carrot room can you not like Harvest
them there's so many
oh uh it gets out of sorted over here so
whenever they're right
whoa this is full by the way let me just
clean this up
oh
oh yeah automatic farm a tech stack
carrots
um
wow oh my God there's an Enderman here
hi better not look at him
don't worry it's true to glass
oh does that not
can you not get out
the what can can an Enderman get out of
the glass
oh they won't be able to see you through
glass really
yeah
oh I hear bees the
stuff
I hear them but I don't see them
troubling
oh troubling oh flowers for him to
feel like they have something to do but
they can never reach them instead of
what's going on
you're screaming so hard I can barely
hear you yeah this [\h__\h] Discord is
cutting me off so much these days
they're so cute
[\h__\h] Discord
wait are they the Harvesters or the
foxes the Harvesters
um
I think maybe I'm not sure I don't know
how it works Holly Holly you know an
example of how Discord is [\h__\h] me
over at the moment is I had this this
Easter VR collab right the other day and
and I was like you know we started the
stream and I was like introducing what
we're doing and I got excited and I said
uh that we have many eggs eggs and I
hope I didn't cut it off for you right
now but this skirt cut it off so it cut
off the first egg and it sounded like I
just said things
and everybody was like yeah what what
the [\h__\h]
I said eggs eggs
the hell
[Laughter]
uh can you say eggs like countless of
times it'll it'll start to sound like
you know six right yeah yeah exactly
was glad to really quick
okay
Mia
I love my eggs and milk oh yeah
what are you saying
let's leave this place this crazy crazy
place but really well made oh my God
yeah and it's all automated so it'll uh
everything will be you know it'll be
um submitted here chess is there more
down here
oh there's a spider farm an amethyst
Farm oh you can Farm ah I guess because
they like grow these Little Flower
thingies huh yeah
yeah so while she was making the house
he found like a spider spawner oh if you
just stand here the spiders will spawn
oh hi
High School spoodle come here can we
fight them oh they're coming yeah oh my
God it's kind of cute oh a little little
tiny comfortable exp Farm yes
and she got it all
though yeah it's better than nothing and
you don't have to go so far
well come here come here oh they're
doing their best to swim over here oh my
God that's so cute
oh
yeah and you can take their strings and
eyes
in the chest I mean
cute cute cute they're not they don't
look so scary anymore when they're just
doing their best to swim over here with
the little legs
why is it that it's so cute for you to
kill all of these spiders that's trying
their best to swim but it's not okay
when we have Traders inside their hold
up houses
because spiders are evil and and Traders
have human rights okay
the spiders they don't even have to swim
over here if they don't wanna they have
plenty of space it looks like if they
want to they can just go somewhere else
but no they want to hurt me that's why
they're coming towards me but the the
Traders they're not attempting to hurt
me and or anyone and yet you hold them
up in a one by one space
their economy is [\h__\h]
have you ever seen a village that has
like a really thriving economy without
us
helping it out
you girls are just making up things to
torture them
yeah I'm spinning facts that's all I do
all day
oh I see so how's the economy in Phoenix
then
it's pretty good I mean and they have
plenty of space well I would say we have
some good stuff yeah but then but then
fauna wants to replace it and she'll
think she already did so now now because
my Phoenix Sun is useless
bad memories
where is the exit
exit right here exit exit oh and while
we're all we're added let's go over here
there's going to be a lot of stuff that
I'll show you before we go to the next
portal okay it's taking so long are you
it's fine but maybe today's stream will
just be tours
we'll see we'll see where did you go I
don't see you
[Music]
oh that's fine that's okay I'm fine with
that fine with me
okay they say it's fine I say it's fine
we say it's fine
so
over here oh we have and we're very
proud Stadium this is what we used when
we had the sports festival
whoa
[\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
wow oh my God wait what kind of games
can you play here
also we can play uh we have like an
eating cake competition where you have
to jump whoa and then there will be like
a cake up there daddy oh
that's so cool I love that yes and then
we have uh uh what was it called where
you have to like pull one rope and the
other one tug of war oh there's tug of
war up there but instead of like using
like actual ropes we used fishes and
fish each other out oh that is genius
can we can we try that
we can if you want to but before that we
might want to touch the bed first okay
okay hi
Tom
one second let me change my PGM
don't want to be too repetitive
okay
all right all right wow wow
we're going to go to this side I'm gonna
go that side okay should I put my
fingers away
I guess I'll just pick him up when I
fall down yeah
uh
[Music]
how do you get up
oh
sorry I'm blind I'm literally blind
yeah and shelter boxes behind you should
have like fishing poles
time to fish Ollie with a good bait
let's see a good bait I have some good
baits to fish you
like getting married
Ollie Ollie do you want to see do you
want to see the color of my panties come
here Mommy come here
come here you want to see it don't you
oh okay can I can I sniff it though
um you will see what I will let you do
with them once you get over here come on
I'm in the air
am I hanging on you oh
what where am I what whoa
[Laughter]
yeah
you won't let me sniff the panties
no I said I will you will see what I
will let you do
wait is all of this yours or all of this
one didn't die right okay
that was the thug of War yeah that's so
cool
I didn't participate
yeah well maybe maybe
um not giving I'm not giving any
information but maybe we'll make another
one let me be part please I want I want
to be part of you tell your best we're
still making the proposal okay well then
we'll have another one okay [\h__\h] wow
look more
what what's with the cow
um just a random mob
it's bouncing
yeah why is he bouncing
is that a viewing platform
yeah no one uses it though it's
basically just decoration I mean from
here it's hard to see but
[Music]
it's so nice
and this is like we had like a relay
race also over here
oh
so you see all of these things they're
all obstacles
from where what where
listen we can start from here and we can
start and we can just race oh okay uh
starting line oh it looks just like
decoration
okay okay go go oh now oh I guess so
oh oh berries
that's by the webs
can you like jump over them
[Applause]
God this was
oh where does it continue
down the water down the water what oh oh
let's see oh no I have Advantage oh
she's confused
I'm still I'm still ahead I think and
then and then and then and then here and
then
no no thank you
okay see it's not very obvious
you're supposed to go
decide over the cactus
[Laughter]
[Music]
dying is there a trick
maybe [\h__\h]
that was I had half a heart left oh my
God
[Music]
even though I left the the race so many
times and came back
good at this
maybe you let me win on purpose
you know I was just being a noob it's
been so long since I parked
I'm wishing minigame there's a fishing
mini game are you fishing the turtles
no so basically we're going to be given
like water buckets and then fish will
automatically spawn and we'll have to
catch the fishes and throw it into this
little little Hopper over here oh okay I
don't wanna have a fish now though I
don't wanna
I just want to fish you
oh
fun I'll be like oh
okay what's next
[Music]
you're so cute no you
so other than that we're heading back to
the jam but you might want to see our
you know how in JP they have like their
shared house
oh like I saw Generations had like a
shared house you know yeah we have our
own community house that people can like
take stops and sleep until oh did I like
this early big house zombies zombies
this house
does it say something here oh yeah
some raids Americans powered by whole
Avenue
oh
entrance from the side again yes
you must have wow
stones
planks wait how much is there actually
in those
oh there's nothing in there yeah we
haven't been using it
okay I thought maybe I could take some
things from here when I need them
what's this dirt iron plants
[Music]
armor no
there's some amethyst still
Diamond there's no diamonds in the
diamond chest no wait that's the wrong
chest
there's diamonds in the diamonds Diamond
I don't know whose diamonds that is now
they're mine
they are in the free detection I guess
oh
and he can actually sit on it and you
can actually eat cake too
oh because it's in a in a in the
minecart
yo oh does it keep on the respawning the
cake two of you are done eating it oh no
no we don't have that magic okay it felt
like it was happening
free food free food wow
haven't been restocking them
oh no there's some stuff here wow oh
there's some stuffs over here
yummy on this one oh wow I'm gonna take
[Music]
so long
thank you wow what a feast
all the good chicken in my tummy
in her tummy wow thank you chickens
oh that's a nice chill area by the
fireplace
yeah so cute
I like it is there a second floor oh
yeah I went to here yeah
uh on the second floor we have like a
lot of rooms that you can sleep in
oh
oh wait oh sugoi sugoi
can I have The Mending book
it can take one there's only one yeah
[Music]
she's having fun
oh
I need to remember this place
um
what was it mending and I'm breaking or
was it something else
hmm I'm not future I'm I'm just taking
what I'm being given oh
sorry we have to take separate beds this
time
yeah your bed has like their a different
theme
if you want to see fifth chill I will be
fifth Chill on Saturday I think
Saturday yeah I'll be playing 50
simulator you will be yeah have you ever
played it before
oh no actually it fills me with anxiety
ah yeah probably it'll fill me with
anxiety too but it was on sale on Steam
so I got it for like pretty cheap almost
free
it was like 90 off or something
rainy's place in kobo's place but
hopeless place is a little bit far do
you mind yeah no problem let's go yeah
we'll start with trainees please okay
wait now I'm coming when I haven't
talked with Wayne in a while at least
not like via voice chat
this is her Library
yeah
oh yeah she has a fan fiction
really
yes
what was whoa you
what oh okay uh should one of us be
United one of us being you
I'll I'll be you okay okay
silly this is only the second dose of
the the gws pills you need to take them
if you want to get well soon
[Music]
sorry but you have to do this I have to
do this don't
because you have been bad you leave me
with no choice
then it reaches for the rope in her
backpack and ties you up she throws you
into a room looking like a cozy car
that's at first glance but the color in
your face strains when you realize there
is no way out
gorsh like seriously I didn't think
there'd be a you know a room like this
sorry you're now trapped here forever
what the [\h__\h]
this is
I didn't know you were like this
sometimes
is this what you think of at night
sometimes Ethan always the only things
about that something she doesn't show
the sides to me often or ever this this
little Hollow side I guess
go down there
um
what's down there's more fan fictions
down there oh
[Music]
so I built her like another Library just
a little gift and she made fan fictions
in here too it says pavonia's secret
Library totally not only it doesn't mean
that actually you wrote The Fan factions
in here
no I just built the place oh wait I can
sit down can I sit down now okay let's
read this
oh Ollie and Evie
one of the others
Muna and Anya based on a true story
[Music]
what does that mean
it's the lyrics from Identity voices Oh
wait a second 14 pages
the advantage of Kyla oh why does she
have it here
doesn't she have her
oh wow I like this design of the library
okay let me read the the moon
basement true story one oh wait it's in
Indonesian
no partially only
oh
stream men
couple
young line what does that mean so
basically they're building a ship
um
okay trapped in venom ship
um I'll I will be I'll be Anya okay
I can't believe all the others remember
bailed out anyway thanks for
accompanying me this late
it's no problem I admit I do have a
morning stream tomorrow but I I just
can't let you do this alone
we only need to seal this part and we
can go home
Muna places her last Oak plank sealing
the ship completely
Senpai what's the exit
but that's the exit
really
tries to ask the newly placed planks to
get out but her ax breaks of old age
do you have a spare ax no but can't we
use our own hands
you see I wanted to make the best of the
best so I got ourselves special quality
Oak that cannot be broken by bare hands
oh then that means
we're stuck
God
what an interesting ship
thanks we built it ourselves
anyway you want to outright it's very
easy
all you have to do is
reconcile
cute why are you guys so cute writing
stuff like this what it's just rainy oh
are you sure
I feel overall you guys are so tainted
having this huge server where you build
so many things together
I put so much work into it ID is so
tainted like I literally witnessed it in
person you guys are just too tater
thank you
that was worth it we'll be going that
way this is the portal so we do not want
to enter it yet oh supporter oh okay
okay
[Music]
foreign house
unfortunately no she really wanted to
like build it in a place where nobody uh
but where it's really hard for anybody
to get there honestly really cool what
the hell I'm so anti-social what the
hell
what's the matter of cobalt
you can probably see it from here
whoa whoa
whoa
wait looks like a
tropical
plant Glass House thingy
it's a greenhouse a greenhouse that's
the word
[Music]
me
okay all good yeah
oh
that's very original unlike the other
thing I mean I mean the other things are
also original but I mean like it stands
out it's kind of different than the
other things
oh it really is a greenhouse
[Music]
gold
and wait there was another one
where the panda
don't pandas like attack you oh was it
only when there's a baby close by right
yeah what does that mean
uh
tahia I believe it's like from jahaya
which means light it's like an
Indonesian name come with you I forgot
what it means he wants to cry oh
see and this is how you keep cats
correctly those stray cats are in the
glass house and having a great time I
think
wait is that an arctic fox
oh it sounds like crazy yeah the fox too
cute
preemie hi
I don't know where she got all of these
animals it's honestly shocking
good
wow she did such a good job here though
whoa whoa is that like a desert cat
yeah oh hi
hi I need to eat
oh
wow
wow what's on the other side
some more animals here
Axolotl and it's a blue one oh
right here
you keep missing it oh
it doesn't want to be seen by me it's a
white axle
oh there's a blue one also oh blue blue
blue
yeah
whoa
he went without me
where is that way to do right
where is it
they swim it is so dark now too can't
see ah wait a seat it's out of the water
oh it's back in the water
oh whoa whoa it goes all the way up
[Applause]
he's such a happy people cute oh there's
so many oh yeah cute I will build this
all by herself good job couple why are
you not want people to see it when it's
so pretty what's the meaning behind that
and I have it all to yourself for what
she never really uh formally introduced
us to this place too so yeah
I like it oh we can't let the foxes
Escape but they're going crazy here
okay okay yeah Marshall has a lighthouse
over there oh
it's like couple designs oh it even says
couple cool
Speedo hello
Nice Nice kill
oh he's planning on making something
over here too but she kind of abandoned
it hardly plays Minecraft anymore really
does she play more in the beginning
a she played she played a little uh
after we introduced her to the server
and then she just stopped playing I
guess it's always
what was it available no Apex did you
play Apex or Valor and I don't know
Valerie Valerian okay
yeah oh let's go on top of the
lighthouse
yeah don't get dizzy oh
oh this gives me rust Vibes because of
my
my little that's a lot of people said
too yeah really oh
yeah I thought it was just me now
can run run oh somebody said that helped
with the designs also
Jerry Jerry who is Jerry
uh her Fox who's dead no
no is it a snowball
I believe it was like a normal socks oh
or was it not
[\h__\h] cherry
did he fall from the Light Tower oh no
that would be terrible
[Music]
okay now that's pretty nice
this is what your child made
my child
um we are not bad I mean ID it's like
you guys never disappoint no matter what
damn
but you can also see it from here that's
the the TPP that we try to replicate but
we for uh yeah but it's like an ID oh I
was wondering about it does it work
I forgot if it works now
hardly ever use it
because we have our own too and
everybody has one I guess
yeah
excuse me let me through thank you
oh okay hi Dogo
it's cobra
dog personal cat person uh she's a dog
person isn't she she told me an anime
Boston
yeah that's why there's so many dogs
here
are you a dog person or a cat person
Ollie
I like dogs but I can't be near them or
cats in that matter oh wait you have
analogy
yeah I just figured it out you just
figured it out what yeah
uh but you girls like keep on visiting
each other's places so now you can't
like
visit oh no it's still a visit it's not
like the a really bad allergy is that
it's just that I'll keep on sneezing if
I'm around them okay but you don't get
like a rash or so
okay that's that's decent
that's not so bad you could even take
medicine if you ever want your own pet
yeah as easy as that okay okay all right
did we miss something important
I don't think I think that's everything
we went to everyone's houses
oh I guess we oh
I guess we did huh huh are you tired
no no no no no no no no no I'm never
sleeping no no no let me take a bite of
my mom and did you see the muffins I
made
I did no it's really good I really like
I really like blueberry muffin really I
had a sudden urge to make muffins and
then I went out and I bought the muffin
thingy oh
um
oh there's a zombie coming for you
[Music]
hurt me
no no
oh my God why does she take so much HP
from me
how thank you harrisoned bye I don't
have any money to repay you so I I think
I'll have to pay you another way
there's no need I was just protecting
myself
[Music]
oh
mind if you go for you oh because you
wanna guess family
oh
[Music]
maybe maybe that's my cousin are you
like staging all of this is this like
you got them when you come here to make
a dramatic situation between us
what I I'm not that slighted
a bite slip
nothing good very good looking really
good
be careful do you ever bake
uh my sister bakes I I usually cook are
you good at baking
what do you cook
I cooked I'm very good when it comes to
like uh stir fry curry soup yeah
Mmm Yeah well next time I come to
Indonesia maybe you can cook something
for me
or is there yeah where's the best
cooking idea
Lisa sent by hands down
has she cooked for you before
she just cooked for me yesterday we had
barbecue what oh my God is that drowned
what the [\h__\h]
what are you doing here
because it's a lot of water and what did
she cook for you
she made me like this beef uh beef
skewer with like onions and paprika and
bell peppers and
um
leeks and whatnot and then she made me
steak she made me Burger everything meat
basically no
why so much did you have like a mukbang
yeah it was a Me risu Senpai and Zeta we
had like a barbecue party
just for fun
was there an occasionally
[Music]
I am jealous
then then let's have another one in my
house next time you come
[Music]
I will come and then hopefully I can
I can get my my last two ID
um
meetings you know the last two releases
and set off
these are the only ones I haven't met
yet
because just
there they were in Japan
worst timing
a really really bad timing ow oh what
the [\h__\h]
but
still that was it was a really cool
experience I'm so happy I went
and we're so
constantly miss you I'm gonna go again
do you plan on having like any vacations
this year
um it's not possible with the schedule
that we have so what
not it but this is still only April you
have the whole year ahead of you oh no
uh I have the whole year already planned
it's very hard to escape what the yeah
but I mean I'm busy too but
no vacation you can't even do like a
free day Bali vacation or something like
that
uh no that's why we actually had a
barbecue party because it only takes a
day
yeah what yeah but yeah the year has 12
months and you guys already have the
whole year planned out
well at least for me okay
[Music]
yeah sad sad sad very sad oh I think
that's all okay thank you so much for
showing me I'm so glad I finally got to
see it so spontaneously you're the best
always yeah
um
let's go
does it work oh my god it works well so
instantly I've seen this I've seen this
I mean I guess I don't know do you know
this place well too
[Music]
yeah like the back of my hand oh wow
okay then maybe you can give me a tour
here too is it as big as ID already
it's um yeah oh my God okay okay we
don't have to end everything maybe just
like a rough overview of what is what
oh so this Beetle minutes I know
I met her Beatles before can we like
oh yeah there's a shared house right
over here I forgot who built it though
[Music]
yeah I met in person I met Dennis
Beatles I I you actually did yeah she
showed them to me
they were quite something
I see they're huge they're like oh
insanely big I was surprised I didn't
expect them to be so big
like hand big yeah now and then they
have like funny horns and stuff like
that
oh she must be an avid fan yeah well she
they're pretty stinky too
more like the never portal where you can
like see that there's something there
yeah that would be neat oh well okay
where do we go where do we go
this is the truth and lie detector oh
what
what yes so you stand here say something
and then you press the button we'll see
if it's the truth or if you're lying oh
well what question do you want to ask me
you can pick like a question from here
well there's like a question generator
oh if you press this oh I think you got
it here
are we talking about Yago now or are we
talking about uh oh okay so the question
is are you aiming to steal the CEO
position yeah
I mean I've had a lot of good ideas
recently that I would love to have
implemented in like whole life concerts
and so on and I guess being the CEO
would be helpful for that at least for a
day
um but generally no
oh I'm telling the truth I always tell
the truth why would I lie
do you know what my idea is I'll leave
it here I wonder what you think about my
idea
what is it so so imagine I mean you've
surely been to a concert a big concert
before right have you had a good seat
not really Ryan that did you see the
people on the stage really small
yeah yeah it was kind of like rough
right like man like I wish you could
afford a ticket in the front seat
but they're so expensive doesn't that
absolutely suck don't you wish you could
get the same Big View as the others well
here's my suggestion how about since we
have virtual Idols uh we could size
ourselves up to the maximum
oh yeah so that even the ones in the
back in the very back can see us so big
they can see all our pores and then you
want like struggle seeing us right
right so like we can be like little tiny
antsense
yeah exactly you can imagine even them
stepping on you or so I guess but
oh my God we gotta get this on the board
yeah nobody will be disadvantaged no
matter where you sit all the viewers all
the all the people in the in the far
away seats they will all have a great
view no matter where you are
do you need someone who can make a
proposal
I mean I mean I I I'm just I'm not very
hopeful that they would implement it to
be honest
but I mean we gotta start somewhere
right yeah I guess so I mean I had some
more ideas that are maybe a bit more
serious
um what was my other idea that I had
I think
oh
just recently guys what did I say oh no
I think one idea was that we should have
not uh like two days of concerts we
should at least have minimum free days
we should also have a tour throughout
all of Japan uh like not just like one
weekend but we should tour from from
north to south uh with all kinds of
venues also I really understand the
makuhari
um oh this is what the hell really
understand that we want to use makuhari
because it has the concert venue and the
convention venue but I think we need to
move on to bigger venues so it's time to
give that up so the question is do we
want do we want what and um question is
do we want like the convention part the
Expo part and the concert part to be
just on separate like far away venues or
just or just on separate days completely
but either way we have to do something
to be able to have more people enter we
have to move on to bigger venues we
should go for Budokan at least let's
call Budokan
[Laughter]
I'll take one from here oh okay
are you an enemy
of course I'm
[Music]
Chris I'm yeah you are you could never I
mean I don't know enemy of what that
would be but I think you'll always just
on the good side you know that that one
legendary clip of Surah Senpai and aqua
Senpai being the whole life resistance
I think so
yeah I think that was a reference
hey was it in English
yeah okay I can get English ones here
let's go to the next one
okay
oh let's say you want like a quick uh
iron you can get it from this little
iron farm
oh I take I mean we have plenty of iron
too though but I take I take I take what
I can get
dripping
and then over here we have Migos and by
his house it looks pretty good doesn't
it oh it does it looks like a typical
Japanese traditional house
yeah we enter from here
okay
wow pretty cute
open oh
yeah he's junk in here
the dungeon is actually over there not
over here no okay there's also the Mikko
Senpai Castle dungeon
is it like you you can die in there
you can die which is why there's lots of
respawn and they tell you to uh put your
items away first
okay so cute maybe another time what's
the this one over there the the
turquoise one
um I believe that's
in pies
floating Castle
that's where she stores yeah Castle
oh it's the PPT school it's not a castle
it's cool that's cool I like it
yeah never been there before though
what else what else
oh here here's a very useful place that
a lot of us go to
It looks interesting it's the Kayla 69
Temple oh
uh-huh is that like her house or is it
just uh like a farm or
it's a it's a temple where you give
offerings and Lego at Kayla will try to
uh make your uh request come true
yeah you see over here
um these are all currently full right
now but basically
through the barrel you write down what
you want you put offerings in the barrel
and after a few days all your wishes
will be in the chest
oh wait you write it down where do you
put it
uh you write it down in a and you know
how in the barrel there's like a book
yeah
yeah you ride it down there but
currently all of the places are taken
all over the booth
oh ah so her commission slots are
currently closed
one commission is then you can just go
back though
put your offensive the number of rhinos
can be any number all is acceptable what
if I say
ing diamonds
write your item request nah no way
and you finished writing please put the
book in the barrel
ah oh you put it back into the barrel
what
[Music]
yeah
cool I write down in the book and you
put it in the mirror
I don't I wouldn't even know what to ask
for at the moment but I will remember
this oh
I was cooked into the delicious Lamb by
the coaster but very nice I'll see you
in court by gouda why I died why
everybody left Clark and what's going on
very interesting coaster cycle not safe
is dead
oh
oh roller coaster there's a safe one and
[Music]
safe one because uh I kind of it was
kind of my fault ah
and she's getting bad reviews because of
you
I I mean we are arch nemesis
there's no stars on your Google review
are you manipulating her things
that's funny wow okay okay cool I will
come back here when I have a certain
request for something
yeah should we sleep
oh but we can sleep inside yeah yeah
okay
don't wanna sleep outside in the rain
orange don't go there's no orange why is
no orange
Brown like the orange no you were on the
brand I think
oh no orange so unpopular what the hell
okay let's go let's go
okay nowhere else I can pick you though
there's a lot of places we can take out
well I mean you don't have to show me
everything
it's okay I'll just go on my own quest
to have the words oh what is Dad I'll
try this thing that grass invite me she
made something
she actually did see is it finished it
looks finished I'm not sure if it is I
haven't been paying attention what
yeah maybe here not is it no I guess
it's supposed to be floating oh she not
finished huh it's not finished it looks
pretty pretty close at least to being
finished I don't know what she wants
what's like the end goal is
but it looks good right
yo gura
what about the other things have
priorities
what does this mean oh wait you can go
oh you can go down here yo you can
actually go down
wow I didn't know this
oh yeah okay that looks like a lot of
work wow wow she's doing this by herself
wow
see her Ambitions now is Atlantis on the
way
she abandoned the old server and it's
just building it here now what
it looks similar to what she was trying
to build in in our server
just never saw this part damn no it's
just it's just temporary storage her new
home part seven
part seven hey it's take two at last 2.0
oh man I guess I guess sometimes it's
good to start from scratch
yeah all right cool yeah I didn't know
that that was happening and I saw that
she played Minecraft quite a bit
recently
cute
I don't know who built this though
uh Instagram uh picture taking place
[Music]
oh I like it
I'll just look from the outside
[Music]
empty I mean there's no furniture so
it's just storage okay looks good though
yeah I mean it doesn't have to be it
doesn't have to be complicated or
detailed and so it's just efficient
efficient enough to play the game
that's I think that's more my style
[Music]
what do we have
and then there's so many things there's
coil Labs up front coil labs
oh not this oh oh curious invite I think
you really I think you'll really like
this it's a stage oh
oh
[Music]
yes you stand here I stand there okay
okay
yeah where's she going oh check this out
oh it's Gonna Come From Below
[Applause]
yay
but no it's actually a boxing ring oh
have they used that doll I wonder I'm
not sure what the missing people did
looks better than my boxing ring
well you know it's all about efficiency
for me
okay where to go we're still in the like
very center of everything
yeah there's oh do you wanna oh oh I
know we can take you to the guild The
Guild okay yeah we have a guild the Sora
Guild
what kind of things do they do
uh you know when guilty have like those
request boards
oh yeah yeah
yeah you can you can make requests and
people will do it or if you want to do
some requests and you can also do that
too wow why everything so helpful now
like back in the day I don't think there
were so many ways of asking people to do
things for them
will bring you all the resources you
need and I guess the guild will get like
rid of mobs or whatever for you
maybe you could hire them for uh
fighting the Wither or so together with
you
oh it looks nice
oh here's the bulletin board there's a
lot of stuff
who's part of the guild
uh soda signify is definitely the
Headmaster we have
I don't know if coyote is a part of the
guild but she has like Koyo Labs oh
okay if you have like map part you can
put it here
what if he wants to build a cockroach
house with someone
why aren't you helping her huh
it's a damn cockroach do you think I'd
be helping that I mean I have seen
people build some weird things on this
new server like the the beetle that
energy built but also the pecula tower
which is just like what one huge block
of cobblestone what the [\h__\h] speaking of
the pecora tower
can I see it for myself
yes okay because it's actually right in
front of the guild and they're having
war they're having war
right there oh the head kind of changed
oh for now what the hell is that it
that's it
oh when I saw it like in screenshots it
looked like really really lame
oh it was really
it was a real start whoa that's
impressive what the [\h__\h] did she build
all of that on stream
I don't know if she actually built
everything on stream
oh it's a cannon
no yeah
yes
what the [\h__\h] it is I can't and then and
you see to counter that uh so the the
lore behind this is that they have the
pecora tower and then koyori you see you
see those
scene you need like mini cannons
responded with the bigger
responded with like a magical uh
platform underneath yeah bunch of
cannons yeah oh yeah I I I've noticed
that the coil is like doing a good job
at like entertaining and challenging her
two things keeping her not so bored yeah
yeah helping her
did it change in Queen there's the
Subaru
to keep things at peace like that bird
guy as like a peace symbol but oh gosh
that's a lot of stuff
it doesn't really seem to be helping
though
people vandalize it a lot like the can
you see the titties and the armpit here
[Music]
wait there used to be like kintama too
what I don't wait on which one this one
or this one on the dock I don't see I
mean okay I guess that's what's that
supposed to be
um
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh golden ones even damn they're
protected with gold oh God I thought I
thought that was actually both on Senpai
but both on Senpai with like like Duck
legs chicken legs this is what that
looks like whoa what the heck
oh
no button Senpai now it looks more pink
now looks more gray before the sun eh
it's a kissing boob when you stand on
there
no I didn't know
I didn't know
you're showing your your otaku site
again
[Laughter]
well I mean I mean I guess she's asking
for it I mean he literally says here you
can kiss me if you stand on this
pressure plate
[Music]
[Applause]
hello a moment ago wait did I you did I
also always call uh her Senpai
specifically her by accident
I think it's because she's like so so
professional and serious and she's like
so into it and generally like like
Japanese Senpai and Japanese members
they're just I don't know something
about them that makes me want to call
them
she's the one kissing me I was listening
oh yeah yeah you had no choice Ryan you
had no choice but to step on it because
she was she was the same
okay let's move on okay
um a lot of these stuffs are idea oh uh
so there are two other spots that I know
of oh uh which is the Kila Island and
the Holo ID Irvine
which one do you want to see
oh let's see if Kayla Island will
impress me let's go okay
[Music]
I noticed you say it you say Kayla I say
Kyla
ah
how does she say it herself does she say
Kayla
hi she says oh it's like an in-between
it's like how people often call me
what do they say Kiara Kiara and I say
Kiara about myself I always pronounce it
Japanese
but also some people say what do they
say
I don't even know
wait there's a portal that we have to go
through I want to go into the never
quite far no hello
[Music]
okay we
and we'll have to ride a train
okay okay at least it seems relatively
safe okay
as long as I don't die let's go
Press B let's go oh just W okay
it's also the German Way not only
Japanese I guess so yeah no German would
be a bit more are unless L but I
generally say it with a little bit of L
that is too much l
ol
wow even the never looks cool here
I think he just never go to the
Netherlands
not to this I've spent quite a lot of
time in our own never oh this why is it
so fancy why did they build the
oh I guess because they're diagonal so
you have to use curves
oh
and it's not they It's Kayla
Kayla made this by herself if I remember
correctly
Kayla Island oh only for that purpose
oh there's also a Muna Island
and wait Mikko and
this is Miko islands and Kyle Island
they share an island
um Miko's Empire recently became like a
neighbor to Kayla
[Music]
I mean she must see the advantages of
living with or close Canada it must be a
good service and good help all the time
whenever you need help support items
I hate her
I mean if I would request 1 million
diamonds from you would you get them for
me
no I'm okay well there you go that's the
issue
it's okay though would you get 10
diamonds from me yes okay that's plenty
I'll just ask for 10 diamonds a hundred
times
or maybe a thousand times
separately you can pay them in rates
no I we live in the material world but I
am not a material girl don't worry
oh
oh do we have to go through again
so can you see it oh
oh
what a what a flex
what is that
this black one
you're the thing inside
oh that's a beacon and the one
underneath it is a netherite block
oh oh whoa that's never right I don't
realize
the um damn okay
[Music]
request for Quest so welcome a RICO spot
has been created in the guild you're
welcome to make rickets for everyone
huh
[Music]
grapeflex reflex I probably was gonna
attack us okay
no nobody saw that right nobody saw that
he had a weapon I thought he was gonna
be is he living here
he
[Music]
what no I really had
to wait why was he named what what about
four what four no no no I'm so sorry
Ollie do you know who that was I don't
know I didn't even know it was named I
thought it was just a random NPC I
didn't see the name either what the [\h__\h]
huh no what was he for
hey
well I guess I guess we'll have to go to
Kayla and apologize for this
first Kyla's neighbors no no I'm sorry I
wanted to protect us
no why am I here his name was why am I
here even he didn't know why he was here
he was the janitor he had a family I'm
so
Minecraft
no it's okay if we ask for forgiveness
she will surely
it was my part-time Warrior
if it's really from Kyla I'm sure she
won't forgive me too but right now right
now I feel like I'm in I'm in danger
Chuckles I'm in danger
oh [\h__\h] hey I'm ready to go to the ozone
funniest sure sure if that is finally
the one string that broke and gets me
there I'm ready
um
ah okay where do we go
down first or up first I guess I'm going
down
is this hell is am I going to hell now
this is her story true okay it looked
like hell to me uh oh wow
oh
[Music]
Chris Marine
oh are these What potions are these
water breathing
damn I still never got into a potion
making it I don't really know
oh healing healing potion would be good
for the weather maybe oh and slow
falling potion would be good for the
warden oh and night vision too if I ever
need those I'm gonna ask Kyla
Russian mention suppose you mention not
a motion mention
um
what is this oopsie that's so pretty
uh eyes
oh so glowy
check never right
um
is there is there a box for never right
only you good
mentally damaged right now I can never
win against her
oh it's okay it's okay this is this is
not impressive to me this is not at all
no no this is so lame
wait sorry Kayla no that's not even the
full chest of that that's not impressive
don't worry about that is not impressive
that's also not a full chat no no no I
expected one
oh lame lame so lame
[Laughter]
she's not like under girls fella
it wouldn't be funny if Kyla sees this
and the other reactions I had and she's
like damn I need to impress her and then
she just like starts this whole gifting
Arc of giving me everything I could ever
ask for
trying to buy in my love you're kind of
like putting danger of like all of her
fans because you know she likes making
endearing streams right
she likes making what
enduring streams
endurance streams oh yeah yeah I mean
I feel sad for her listeners I'm just
giving her a reason to play Minecraft
which everybody loves seeing her play
don't they
[Laughter]
'll be the next time that I log into the
game so I don't I don't need anything
foreign
okay and let's go up what's up
uh her Island and the most furious
volume ever
the the most what by All Me
rarest rarest no
which one is that
oh oh what's up there
what is that
is that excellent am I being graded by
accident
weird Flex
oh wow
wow she built it ah I mean I have access
to one of those too
um was it something like that there
can't be any enemies spawning on this
kind of Wyoming yes right I just heard
that
oh hi cows
excuse they're fine wait why is there a
brown one I didn't know there was brown
ones too of those two yeah
yeah I guess so oh that's super rare
don't worry I will not kill this one
don't worry I mean even if if you killed
that one come over here Senpai where did
she put them here's a carrot
I hear this see shocking milk chunky
milk strawberry milk and turkey milk oh
yeah so so you do know why I hate her
now I guess it wouldn't hurt hey but
like what's so special about them that
their their mushrooms too is it better
than the other one or what
I don't know
why is it this is like much better
Freedom not super rare anymore yeah
she's she just she's killing her own
economy her own Flex by making so many
so it looks less rare
they make suspicious stew
oh they're just a much rarest one yeah
because suspicious steel is like who
wants to eat that
yeah yeah
oh gosh what is that thing
what is that thing
um
someone's building is someone trying
to find laser
laser you think that's gonna be a laser
you see the one on the right the right
one that lights up oh yeah yeah I'm
building a laser to destroy her house I
don't know who who's building the one
next to it oh wait oh so the right one
is yours
the the only the top part
and the left one is probably Kyla
you you you started building a laser to
destroy Kyla's place here
yes
Ollie Ollie I'm very Petty only what
what
you I thought I thought ID was like all
super tainted
that's what you think yeah it was wrong
you guys have a lot of issues maybe you
should talk it out
no we can we can resolve it with
violence have you ever tried just like
sitting down with a cup of coffee or
something like that and just talk
talk what your issues are
maybe if you say it to Kaila that you
want some pictures too then then maybe
she will like include you in her credits
and so on and say hey this is this these
five million diamonds are not just from
me they're also from only partially 50
and then you get you get the love to I'm
sure Kaila would be selfless enough to
do that don't you think maybe would she
that would hurt my pride
well then I have a lot of issues here
well then you just gotta get good
that is the only other solution then I
guess
[Music]
stop it you're gonna get the the people
pooping here
is there bed to sleep
wait this is new oh inside the mushrooms
stinky I hate mushrooms see I don't even
like this by only because I hate
mushrooms only
oh you don't feel so bad yeah I hate
them
oh let's disconnect real quick okay
eight in five four three two one it
should be morning
yeah you really are Mario oh yeah right
that was one thing only did you see the
Mario movie yet
oh not yet oh oh I don't want to spoil
you is it an ID uh theaters
yeah it is it's just that I haven't
gotten to watch it you gotta watch it I
was so like surprised I didn't even know
that Mario actually doesn't like
mushrooms I didn't know that he doesn't
like mushrooms yeah he was like forced
to eat them uh to get stronger you know
without spoilering too much that is like
just happens right in the beginning
pretty much but no it's not spoiler
there's way more things I could spoil it
I'm not gonna spoil I just wanted to say
that because that reminded me you know I
was like damn I'm just like Mario for
real for real I don't like mushrooms and
all Eva
[Music]
ruined the movie forever for everybody
no but you really gotta watch it because
like it's it's been
it's been quite some time now it's
really good I really recommend it
I I will once I get the time for it go
go go go go go you guys you guys can all
go together except I guess you you
should go together with Kaila like
bonding bonding time together with my
arching nemesis
ah what's this
this is her house
her house
yeah if this is her house
wait
I I have I'm bad at this
time there we go there we go oh really
this is her house
yes I mean it's kind of cool I guess
[Laughter]
that's that's pretty decent
people
oh [\h__\h] oh man
it's always happy at least I can cheer
up Ollie with that oh wait that is
wait so wait don't wait was there a
Temple here
I think there was and she got rid of it
or did she no I'm not necessarily she
might have just built this
because the conduit you can build
yourself I think
okay she did that herself ah okay okay
that would have been a crazy coincidence
if right next to the the Red Cow by all
mean there's like the temple as well
yeah that's a crazy seed
but no it's not not like that but damn
yeah that okay that that view is cool
but the inside of her house I mean
oh I like this this idea though with the
handles yeah
um
I'm just you know you know when I well
for example uh
what are those examples when I
um eat uh
uh something
um
no what are the examples what have we
had before when I try to make something
feel better about itself guys what was
it
[Music]
swim outside and you'll see
make a better one I can't
a hot chocolate I yeah when I drink
totally not hot drink and I go like
obviously doesn't care about hotness I
can't I cannot feel that kind of thing
in a negative way well I just react like
that to make the hot chocolate feel
better about itself so basically maybe
me reacting to Kyla's things who knows
maybe it's just me trying to make Ollie
feel better
no no no no no no no no no no it's cool
you know but but I I I you know damn
well what is that
that's her uh you know Sandy from
SpongeBob oh
I just watched a SpongeBob tier list
video
did she rebuild it
yeah she made like a half Globe how do
you go outside wait I guess I would die
if I try to swim there no wait you can
um you
she has that thing yeah oh let's
let's how far can you go
okay we have to go back up
don't be sad Ollie I'm outside
I just
just just on the water stuff is kind of
cool just that though not nothing else
the rest is lame
like my head you can put a chest on a on
a boat
oh
Coolio
okay swim
oh where is it you're kicking in
where is it
where's you
wait she has two conduits oh there where
there's a 69 let's swim through the
circle yeah
whoa
throwing up the Shader
yeah okay just for this uh
[Music]
uh off
I'm not drowning
yeah on the water I'm gonna turn it off
oh spooky sounds
oh but there's nothing inside
no cool floor though yo those those um
patterned floors
maybe that's a thing I should request
from her
oh there's an axolotls stuck in there is
it inside or outside
are you good you good buddy oh they're
inside definitely oh okay
wait so there's water inside I thought
this uh place was supposed to be without
water there's water
say Ollie like they're so unhappy
they're like almost killing themselves
in order to get out
so what does that tell you about Kyla's
builds huh huh don't feel so bad about
yourself
your axolotls are happy aren't they
I don't have any well that's because you
don't purposefully like steal them from
their homes and their friends and then
bring them to your own place for your
own entertainment
yeah you're a good personally remember
that
[Music]
don't worry about it
oh well
[Laughter]
from outside her place looks pretty cool
oh really well pretty cool pretty cool
oh the corals are nice oh I guess she
placed those herself there those weren't
there to begin with probably
so fake
fake corals
[Laughter]
all he needed is
not no one else said that ever
like I know that I have to get good but
nowhere
it's okay Ali I'm I'm on your side
until until I'm convinced otherwise
are you saying that you will backstab me
if you were convinced otherwise it's
really in the end basically a skill
issue only
haha
so it depends on you and Kyla I guess I
have an honest person but so far I'm not
that impressed you know wait
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is she doing with
those frogs look at them panicking
what is that like look it's your speed
are they necessary in order to keep the
Allies up there or is that unrelated
I think it's unrelated I don't think oh
oh my God what they're so cute I've
never seen them more all right let me
turn on Shader
uh
uh which one was I using this one right
allies allies whatever
oh
cute I wanna get one I wonder if Kyla
would get me one but no I want to get it
myself
[Music]
want those poor beans they're like so
magical and mystical and you know they
just want to help and she has them stuck
in here
I guess you gotta keep them somewhere so
that they don't fly away
what a glow
hey glow I guess and also originally
they must have been like in that jail
right that's where you get them from so
I guess she freed them just to put them
in another jail
that is so sad yeah they think they get
they're getting rescued and they're like
Wow Let's Help Kyla because she's
rescuing us wow she's like holy our our
holy rescuer and then Psych
putting you in another jail
oh wait there's not again no bed here I
thought that was a bed
okay wow uh there was one more thing
right the ID or something the idea
Ravine ravine
so we're building houses in like the
edges of a cliff hmm
yeah
people want me to see the Miku Island
though since we're here I guess
oh is it okay if we go to the mix I have
never been there is it finished
yeah because last time I went there
people scolded me for giving spoilers
apparently oh is she building it off
screen
oh secret is it it's okay it's fine it's
okay not ready yet it's not ready yet
mixed mixture opinions
[Music]
it's okay streaming is fine now it's
just not finished
okay
I mean yeah okay this is yours if it's
close
do you know what it is
what what is what do you know where it
is
I think we just need to follow the rail
right okay okay
coming soon
[Music]
let's run
let's run oh with the Shader like
looking into the water from the outside
looks really nice
mmm
and also very creepy at the same time
nah nah
oh gosh it's not lighted yet
don't say stuff like that it's so dark
it's so dark
will we be okay this is scary
there's a skeleton
it I have weapon
you fight I'm poor Tech
oh wait maybe I should
um put on my shield and maybe I gotta
change the batteries to my headphones
okay
this is why I only use wired things
oh I didn't even get damaged I'm weak
even Kyla's enemies here are weak
I was trying to do okay yeah let's
disconnect
I'm wired again yeah
over the bridge now it's pretty oh
holy [\h__\h] this is really pretty I love
shaders this is why I need shaders so
worth it right oh hi burn burn
motherfuckerberg
I normally don't like using that word
because it's lame
but I have to say it to get it across
wait am I going the wrong way I'm going
around because it was so pretty
[Music]
you're breaking off I can't hear you
[\h__\h] disco why like I even have my
sensitivity to like zero so that it
should pick up everything
I think it'll be faster with both oh
okay and also we're on a boosted server
too I don't know man recently I'm always
being cut off I don't get it
let's go
let's go more support wait do I have no
expression
I shouldn't normally but let me see
where is it
uh
wait where would that be in in who is
seeing the sensitivity setting is it
somewhere else
I have it no no I I I made it like the
lowest it could possibly be the other
day because it was cutting off I thought
it would help
it
oh wait wait a second
wait it's like I hear
let me turn it off
um although I think
um
ah what the [\h__\h] is that what is crisp
foreign
[Music]
yes tell me if it got better I'm gonna
like scream and laugh and all that okay
okay
oh I can hear you
yeah yeah oh
yeah no surprise let's go are you loud
and clear yeah oh thank God finally no
more
zags only eggs eggs
eggs eggs
[Music]
eggs
wait this is cute this is why is the eye
not what
because it looks Derpy cute also oh yeah
this is gives me this gives me Derpy
funny Zelda and Animal Crossing Vibes
for some reason
cute this is such a nice Road actually
oh wait that's it
that's pretty much it oh but there's a
there's a little Bridge
yo that's so cool nice that's perfect
what's the oh so high up guess some
space problem but damn so is she gonna
like build a lot of stuff on here
like like Lisa's Lisa's Place like she's
gonna have like a a lot of things here
too huh I think she's building like palm
trees too look look oh
I see
palm tree I didn't even see the light
house tower thingy
Los Santos eyes are inspired by GTA
because she plays GTA I've played two I
see I still want to play GTA with Mikko
senpai
but I'm too scared to ask
oh there's a trainer what's that
what's your third about oh no I mean I
already asked one time but you know and
she said yeah sure and then you know
well the tree looks a little bit naked
maybe we need some coconuts and stuff
yeah with the with the Coca-Cola but
from far from far it looked really good
really nice
nice Tower too yeah cute I'm I'm looking
forward to what this will turn into
yeah
this thing reminds me of I know it's not
supposed to be that but it reminds me of
like in
um what's his name like in Wind Waker we
met him for example the the little the
little
small uh green dude
tangle yeah tingle not curvy I'm talking
of Zelda yeah tingle why does this
remind me of tingle maybe the derpiness
even the the pool is actually a face
oh I guess so yeah yeah
[Applause]
yeah chill guys chill I guess I'll ask
her again I do miss GTA I want to play
more GTA okay let's go to ID land I
should take the boat again yeah okay
only you're such a good um person to
have around
no I mean you thank you for uh prep
talking me too anyway
it made me feel super good
did you did you um free not feel bad you
know how I first um asked
for Kyla and then for you
I'm a little bit disappointed I was like
there was lag it was lag I it took me a
few
since there was like I actually actually
I wrote Ollie first and then there was
lag and then
yeah
really is that true true yeah
like really really yeah it was the Ping
really uh yeah
laughs
oh don't cry don't cry no unless it's
for happiness yeah yeah
like like I I really thought because you
know Kayla is a very famous in Minecraft
right now so I thought oh yeah yeah then
said he'd ask Kayla first you know yeah
no I I think I mean the number four was
I think that I already knew Kyla wasn't
streaming and I just assumed you were
streaming
and I just thought when somebody's not
streaming then they probably don't have
like a goal right now in mind that like
they have to do this or that you know so
I thought I wouldn't be disturbing them
that was the you know the real thought
of train so so you know okay
oh
[Music]
okay
let's see oh my God the cow
let's see the ID thingy and then maybe I
also gotta check out fauna's tree
oh I don't know where that is actually
we should be able to have been there
before I should be able to see it
because it's so big
somewhere I
does that mean fauna can show it to me
um I'm like can we do the weather we
gotta fill up again God damn it
God damn it
we're here here here yes hi hello thank
you for waiting
are you guys enjoying the bgm by the way
I switched it again it's nice isn't it
oh Crossing b gym is so good it makes me
want to play Animal Crossing but every
time I like try it play Animal Crossing
I feel like it's so
I don't know I immediately got sick of
it
oh but I want to be entertained by
Animal Crossing
but everything's so slow you know what I
mean
because it's more of a my uh a pace game
yeah that you play like every day slowly
slowly
do your thing but hmm I played
pretty much every day for a while in the
beginning but the whole like once it
gets to the point where you like you're
ready to decorate your Island properly
that's where
I kind of like I don't know I'm like
what the placing the tiles on the ground
takes so unbelievably wrong along I just
don't have the patience for it
I just wanted to look at other people's
islands and
and maybe do a few like collecting
things
but
yeah
after a while let's just
um I wish I really want to be the type
of person who can play Animal Crossing
every day for three years or so I want
to be like that but I'm not that kind of
person
you need dedication for it mm-hmm
so true the updates are just so those
aren't so fun anymore so I could have
stopped also oh were there some updates
recently
yeah like there's a cafe in the museum
now I bet that's a long time ago already
I saw that
um
I haven't been playing since that update
how often is there like how many years
apart is there a new Animal Crossing
game guys do you know
which is the their main console they're
probably not gonna release a new one and
they keep on saying they don't have
plans on getting a new console yet so
even though it's been so long
every five to six years
um
you just have to wait right if it's
every five to six years and it's already
been like what at least three years
right
at least I remember like when I was not
in whole life yet I was like watching
as a big fan and that was like right
before the the spring before I joined
the whole life
was when everybody was into Animal
Crossing everybody was streaming it and
then we I joined and I wanted to play it
too but then all the other Japanese
members they already stopped and I was
hoping that I could like get into the
same kind of Rhythm as they did with
like everybody was visiting visiting
each other's islands and all that but
but by the time it was over it was just
over
it was that lockdown game yeah oh sorry
I went somewhere else because I was
scared
are you okay
I'm okay all right you're being followed
by the spider and a kaboom
yeah
oh don't worry watch this watch this Pro
Gamer move
you're gonna die what are you doing
no no look Pro Gamer move I have the
creeper killed it almost
and the temp was made
I'll do something about it
I'm the one who terraformed Subs anyways
okay okay okay
[Music]
it's going to be quite a walk from here
because usually uh it's better if we use
a cart
I hope you don't mind oh no problem
only before you joined a whole life you
are also watching lots of whole life
weren't you
ah who was the who did you watch the
most back then before you joined
bye
um
really wow only Japanese members you
didn't really watch the uh ID members
oh I did watch them but uh back then the
clips were mostly them so ah true true I
wear you like watching translated clips
oh
oh like many others hmm
[Music]
hi guys if you haven't seen yet my
schedule for this week is out and we're
having coolness Senpai as Holo talk yes
let's go
[Music]
there's so many monsters
there's so many monsters there's usually
No Monsters what the [\h__\h] yeah it's not
really lit up well here
yeah so this is the whole idea Ravine oh
nice
yeah right there is house and this one
here is my ass
yeah
okay Sam I'm getting some some fighting
practice today too very good oh should
we sleep
good um
oh this is connect
is Lisa trying to sleep
she's not she's streaming like how do
the people know
she's not sleeping she's not streaming I
think she's just surviving
one of these uh houses oh yeah yeah okay
oh she's already sleeping huh is there
two beds oh yeah okay I'll go out
there's no no bad at all
oh I went in too fast maybe did I no no
burn burn
[Applause]
crawling onto your skin with the hotness
of hell
I still kind of did him a favor by
ending him quickly with the blade
okay let's see
Blue Roof is is my house in progress the
barn looking one is muna's house in
progress and there's a little bridge
over there that leads to risu Island
part two uh version two
yeah another Island for lisu
yeah
this is nice you can like jump on the on
the roof and make some noise up there
yeah
we can party hard and annoy the heck out
and wake her up and yeah and then she'll
check she'll go outside after waking up
and she'll be like what the [\h__\h] and
then we hide somewhere wait they brought
some of the cows here
yeah I believe that's a present from
Kayla from winners your arch enemy
Nemesis
oh this is cool
yeah uh I was the one who built the
bridge and this is everybody was the one
who built the entrance y'all Ali this is
cool you did a good job again
it's cool are you sure you're just not
saying it no for real like I was
thinking damn this is this looks really
cool like the the darkness of it and the
the design of the the sides lunches or
whatever it's really nice too
yeah and the gates are nice too
really cool if I made the gates wow
yes
oh okay so this is what it looks like
before you guys transform something into
a big big crazy thing here oh no wait
there's actually oh it's already there
never mind
there is no before there's only ever
after
[Music]
oh
scared the Hickory heck out of me
welcome she says
really cool builds
I didn't know this was such a good
Builder too
well she's a she really likes building
uh
we can stream her building
what what's the tower over there
yeah with the with the magic floating
what is it like crystals so cool oh
well this place is really like it looks
dark it's dark side welcome to the dark
side
[Music]
that's your storage room what
what do you mean that is your storage
room
I said what I said
why why would someone build such a
crazy storage room intricate why not
what the [\h__\h]
why why
what what
oh
geez I feel like I'm in the Zelda game
yeah she's really cracked the building
this is like I'm in Hyrule I'm in Hyrule
I think I'm in Hyrule
still in a work in progress she still
has the scaffolding on
well I don't see it out there
water slide
[Music]
one more one more one more one more one
more one more
oh slow it's so slow gotta go faster
can we turn sonic mode on
issue
water slide is too slow
fix it please
It's gotta go faster
[Laughter]
[Music]
increase the half of me
[Laughter]
wait
Quake Pro
am I walking I think I'm walking in the
water we'll probably make a new water
slide oh oh
nice soup
is this what I had it on before
your storage room looks like
Zelda's
Palace and high roller song
so nice and yeah you used to laugh at
some point can you do like a Lisa
impersonation
oh do you want like the normal laugh or
do you want the wheezing laugh wheezing
[Music]
damn there's no more mushrooms over
there
yeah it's the dark woods
yeah what is the normal laugh then
ah cute lately she's been laughing like
that but if you're going for like her
old laugh
I
think I can hear it yeah
are you hydrating ah this is listening
listening
[Music]
do you have a sound effect for that
no I only have you're listening mom
s
that is actually perfect timing perfect
timing
actually guys she dm'd me she said
if you're still playing later I'm gonna
try and join and help with whatever
you're doing when I'm back so
now she's here
and she is probably show him what what
she's ready to help me
with what I'm gonna do now because it's
perfect because I I said after this I'll
go do my own little thing and we're
pretty much done aren't we we just want
to see if Ono's tree I guess
I think they'll have to leave yeah
that's understandable I kept you for
three hours
yeah I don't know if I'm gonna do much
more though I
don't worry I'm a real man I chase my
woman I don't follow them
I'm scared
I'm coming for you
I get [\h__\h] I think the other things
I'm just gonna have fauna show me the
her tree because we don't know where it
is and I want to do something else now
also I've seen fama's Tree in her stream
a little bit anyway
yeah I only see her uh tree from streams
okay can you just bring me back to the
answer of all
right
[Music]
oh I'll see it when I head back really
will we see it when we head back
really
we love you ollie they say
you guys are making me blush you're so
mad so mine for helping me because
otherwise I would have probably tried to
run around on my own and I would just
like had no idea where to go and what is
what and every time I would have asked
who made this and then five seconds
later because delay well then they would
say this person made this I think and
I'm like oh but do you still have that
anyway
I mean I mean no I'm
I'm really glad you were here to help me
today no
no also because we don't
you know we don't do much together we
don't collapse much so this was a great
way of getting some time together
actually thank you for calling me
because uh I've been wanting to ask you
on the collab oh but I always get too
intimidate it don't please no online
please ask me nobody asks me please ask
me
any game doesn't even have to be a game
we can do something else too
like I don't know what
[Music]
no
oh actually maybe I'll also end up
inviting you to something
oh
I think I have an idea
you guys want to collab by holding hands
okay
actually mama
I have Mommy I have something I need
your help with maybe
um
so I'm now free for sure
okay
yeah we didn't even hold hands
when we were together but we gave hug
hug is even better we did yeah remember
I told my viewers that um we made yeah
the others laugh by holding
hands weirdly but I think up to this day
they don't understand how weird our
hand-holding was
okay so competit bluntly while we were
holding hands uh we accidentally made
like a scissoring motion
you had to say it that bluntly I I
didn't think you would say that word man
um
I mean
well I I I yeah I guess it was yeah that
kind of that you know that's what I
thought really
is that really what you thought why
would you immediately think that that
was what it would be you you're thinking
so badly of us
[Laughter]
having a describe was it
yeah and like you know there's the space
between your thumb and your pointy
finger
what happened was uh I don't know if
Kiera Senpai is comfortable with me
actually uh touching her skin right if
she's not comfortable with me kissing
her then I wouldn't want that so what
happens is that I put my uh middle
finger and my uh pointy finger above her
Palm so that when I do kiss it I just
kiss my own fingers instead of instead
of her hands oh and then I was like yo
you're kind of holding my hand weird
like why do you do this and then when
she holds it up we accidentally scissor
each other's fingers yeah
people got like how it really happened
but I guess that's how it happened
[Laughter]
it's moving listening I think she's
listening
okay I will go to the Ian world only I
guess this is goodbye no totally not
yeah goodbye Ollie thank you for free
wonderful hours with you
my pleasure
to you thank you and don't worry too
much about Carla okay
thank you that kind of makes me happy
I I'm gonna talk to you another time
okay talk to you later
bye thank you whoa
I'm back oh it is
oh okay she left the VC as well well
well well I am all alone again oh no
that's awkward that's awkward
okay where am I I am okay I think
maybe I roughly know
[Laughter]
it's like when you say goodbye and then
you're not actually
leaving
so my problem is
it's been almost three and a half hours
and the other thing I kind of wanted to
do
I feel like it might be a commitment for
I don't know how long it would take I
want to get an LA
l-i-e-l-i-e but I know they're like in
these like Pillager places right like
stuck on the ground
sounds like quite a challenge right like
first of all we would have to find
something that's like spawned after an
update right
because
It's gotta be fresh otherwise the Allies
wouldn't spawn right
yeah Pillager Outpost
I would have to go pretty far and then
I've never really raided the Pillager
Outpost before
I know how difficult it is
has
an ally Ally Ellie
mummy mummy you can join me in VC
uh I'm in the collab one
I'm gonna call her mommy now
the collab the h e c b one
who
me
that was by accident now that's my new
nickname for her
mummy
mummy be moving
[Music]
um
you should be hey where is she not
no you're in here you're in that PC
let me tag you
uh
me
[Music]
no no you're still in it I see you in
the members list
mommy mommy
yeah
I it's enough it's in its own folder I
can see yeah
you are hiding it how you doing mummy
[Music]
what
I'm good how are you this is like
unbelievable I whenever I used to play
uh Minecraft back in the day no one
would ever join me and today you're
already the second person to join me and
there's a possibility if possibly later
that someone else will even join me as
well
it's the power of me not having
civilization duties oh magical I'm
suddenly free at this time so what does
civilization do when it's not being
duted by you
um it's put on hold
but doesn't that mean that I'm being put
on hold right now
um but I'm getting I'm getting special
treatment now yeah yeah you're you're
special civilization wow oh my gosh
fashion
yeah are you already in the game
yeah but I'm in the en server uh I am
where am I I think I'm near PPP
uh took over a village I'm there is
there anybody else here at all hello
um I'm just gonna log out to you also
want to log out for a moment
oh I will sleep my only one here yeah
you're the only one left okay I want to
go up and sleep
God damn it oh I sleep okay
okay okay Mommy
do you
think
you too
I have heard and if it's true that you
um you are in the ownership of an ally
Vinnie
oh is that oh my gosh what did I name it
silly blue or something I do have one oh
how did you get it I found it and then
lured it with my charms did you found it
at the Pillager Place thingy no I just
found it in the ocean what
well here's what I was what was I doing
I had a boat and I was in the ocean and
I saw it and everyone was like move it
be careful be careful then I took it
but dude
random randomly
I think they can because I found I've
seen two before
what and I didn't see pillagers
one that someone lost people say
somebody maybe lost it someone must have
brought it there they don't seem to be
missing it
what yeah it was on the en server or
Japanese let's see a missing report it
was on the new server oh
do I have a right here in my
um
yeah Finders Keepers
that look what I have set up in OBS I
have a moves
set up
[Music]
perfect I'm
oh you're next to me but I'm actually
gonna put you to the left side
oh my god I've been push out the window
by this villager I hate them I hate them
so much hey yo Revenge Revenge if I kill
them then I'm gonna just like something
bad happens I think I get killed
so
what are your plans for today are you
streaming or so afterwards I don't know
I'd like to hmm but it wouldn't be for a
while okay because I I want to get an
ally but just like relying on randomly
finding it somewhere that's like I can't
do that like I wouldn't know where to go
because I guess they don't spawn
randomly after all because you just took
it
um
I guess so
go somewhere far away find hopefully a
Pillager Outpost raid it and get the
ones that are hopefully stuck underneath
it
but that's like such a big challenge I
haven't really really like thought much
about it
do you have to find a new one or can you
use wait what do you need what happens
with it
when you use it oh is it I want it just
because
it's a reason to go out and do something
oh okay I thought you needed it for
something like you needed it for no no
oh you just want one oh
okay I wonder if we could find a stray
one again but
is that what you want to do they say
I'll help you maybe better to do it in
the new server yeah but like how
difficult is it to raid a Pillager
Outpost oh I feel like it's tough
because like I saw uh
is gonna come too
I don't know I mean like you might want
to have that adventure with Lana because
she knows what she's doing oh she knows
how to do things you see I don't know
how to do things I just don't have one
that tells me to do I mean that might be
fun too
and I already rated one on a whim before
my first episode of whole talk
I guess so yeah I did something like
that before
all right we shall do it I shall take a
strong bow which is then I wonder how
lucky we have to be to find one a new
one has to be a newly spawned one
I see
and okay
um hold on let me get stuff what should
I bring weapons and armor
weapons and armor okay
I don't really have because I wonder if
Kyla had any tridents that would be a
good thing to request from her
trying to suck I should probably go home
um
but if you don't use it then what's it
even worth
you don't use your Trident
I need a good uh bow
also what do you need to learn how did
you learn it
was it a music block
I don't know I don't remember
I think I oh I think I threw something
it took it
I think I leashed it
you can leash it need a lean okay okay
okay
let's think about what we need um I will
bring my lighter do we have an elytra
I do have an elytra okay I also have a
lead I can bring out oh please do then I
don't have to leave for it
um do you have fireworks for your
lunchroom
I have 30.
30. that's probably not
um enough because we want to fly far far
far far far far but most of the prep we
can go with
um my on another uh
thingy
um
oh wait I found a good one flame mending
power I'm breaking okay I'll take that
one
why do I have so many totems since when
[Music]
string any uh give them any item and he
will follow you any item
yeah I gave mine a sword it looks pretty
funny I guess the thing with this with
the music block was that you place it
somewhere and then they stay around
there and collect Whatever item you gave
them but around that area
is that what that was
oh
shoot I need more string
more string string string string maybe
if I want to make a powerful bow what
enchantments do I put on it I have
personally I have one with infinity
because then you only need one arrow in
your inventory Infinity
okay and then I also have power and
Unbreaking on it and I have one more
with flame mending power and I'm
breaking as well but like as high as you
can get it let me see I don't want to
lose them look at my hot wings infinity
and power
um
need the books
infinity and power okay I'm gonna go
shopping okay get out of there's a line
get out of the way I hope it won't take
longer than like two hours what the heck
what do you think villagers kissing on
top of the entrance to the store oh
no I need to get in there no PDA stop
okay
oh I have some strings by the way only a
few and they're looking at me while you
do that
fireworks oh wait there's more strings
do you need strings
I do I need one I have 42. do you need
it for a bowl
yeah you're making it from scratch I can
give you a scratch bow as well like a oh
okay I think you can give me the bow yes
okay to mend it a little bit I'm trying
to get to the how good are you like in
in combat in Minecraft movie I don't
know
I think the bow would be my best bet
okay just just wondering if it would be
safe to give you one of like good bows
I can make a good bow except there's no
there's no does she ever Infinity down
here do we have a good sword
no
although well fauna collected swords for
us
um I'm sure it wouldn't be a big deal if
I yeah she said she could get her hands
easily on new equipment as well
I feel like she would be really good
with an ax
would I be give it an ax actually I have
a diamond ax well ax is not really meant
for comment but it is good for combat
like slower hits but strong more damage
oh shoot there's no are you an ax person
psychopath ax cycle ax
[Music]
if you can't find an Infinity
enchantment I'll give you a couple
arrows
maybe it's outside
why do I have so many what the [\h__\h] I
guess I'll take one
hmm
hey why did I get so many totems
no wait no they're not outside
they're from fauna
eh did she give it to me personally
what I mean I feel like I could have had
like two or so on my own but this is too
many
um
was it maybe I should give in to
everyone
check your new house too um
am I being gifted something
um
I can't get good bow
[Music]
perfect okay I'll bother you one of my
bones
okay
and some arrows
um
okay is this from fono
okay and then I just hope when we find
I'm Pillager Outpost quickly is there
like any
any way to stumble upon them faster guys
oh
do you have at least some proper armor I
do have proper armor okay
I also have a totem baby okay hold on
baby you mean the total just a totem of
undying right yes
okay I think I'll also I'll bring an
Ender Chest
so we can like set it somewhere
just in case wait there's some more
stuff in there
okay wow thanks for everything
's empty so I guess I did see it before
okay see my house isn't even that bad
you placed that there
are you where are you now Mommy
I'm your PPP
um oh yeah okay previously peckwell's
property okay
um guys any advice on what I should
bring besides
Two bows some arrows
fly fireworks do I have more beds
okay
I wonder if I have some
food I think I have plenty a spare bag
okay
[Music]
you make it so bad
I don't know
I should have wool ah I do have walls
and I have wool here yeah
I make a brown bed for moment and I make
yellow bed for quinoa no I just take my
bed no no
oh wait there I have two I have an
orange one
okay
also if you can sleep now I sleep
in the way of the elevator milk and
Leash okay you're bringing a leash right
yeah maybe if you haven't any chest
somewhere put it in the MHS to keep it
safe okay
um
sorry guys brain slow
[Music]
um
okay
thank you
how to make bad God how to make how do
you make anything at all it's been such
a long time you go to this table
you got maybe wool oh
and three plank
I think
yeah like like you're not like oh yeah
it works wow mommy wow I totally didn't
just look it up a second ago
oh
where is
okay she did not have a furnace
oh the furnaces are
here
goodness here
okay
um somebody said bucket I guess I'm
gonna bring some buckets
um
yeah
I thought it only works in the left hand
no no yeah yeah I remember okay okay I
mean I'm gonna make it so that we can
spawn right next to it once we find it
so
be okay
but hey don't I have more fireworks
somewhere did I not see them
I feel like I need more
fireworks or
powder right powder with paper
oh I hope I hope I live
you will live with me believe me
you have to
okay you're like scared I'm scared of
losing it
you have manding on it right yes okay
I think that's enough okay worst case I
mean we might not make it back but
that's that's another problem that we
will have
okay when was my
I remember
to my house because I have my material
there I just forgot how to get back
uh and you have to take the subway
oh yeah oh yeah what has it been a long
time for you as well I've never played
Minecraft
me neither it's been a long time
I only played to talk to people
that's what you're doing now yeah
you you got the lead
I put it in my in the Ender chat nice
okay perfect
I guess I'll just wait for you here and
the the main hub
okay I am on the way
let me tell mysterious participant on
the frame what we're doing just in case
she wants to join eventually
mysterious number three
I now trying
to find a Pillager uh what's it called
Pillager
thank you to read it
song
let's try to see this and wanna join
favorite
Outpost
no friend G she actually yesterday in
her stream apparently said she if she
can she wants to join maybe do whatever
I'm doing I guess
um
yeah yeah but no pressure no pressure
oh please tell me there's a cart oh
there's a card
all right yo I just came from the ID
server
and it's insane you've seen it too right
yes when did you see it
ah oh I look good with Bae Kyla showed
us it was a very humbling experience
yeah
um
[Music]
thank you
Make Way for Mommy
[Music]
the subway that's not as pretty as I do
yeah but my my argument was that it's
not as pretty because we were forced to
build the subway
because good I had us on a leash and the
ID members they weren't forced to make
it they made it out of their own well
okay
I see yeah excuse us for not building it
with flowers and all that around us it
was a
[Music]
um
so the build represents the feeling
inside you had exactly pure enjoyment
that's what we were feeling obviously
like
by the way
okay I am
it's not a loop is it uh no no okay what
is this but I can't see okay
it goes too fast I can't read
I think I'm on the way still hopefully
why do I have potions that have Coyote's
name
huh wait it is a loop
what
it's a loop now
what it wasn't the loop before
does it have stops or do I have to like
oh no
Nani there's no stop no
me you're lying
wait did I already ask you if you have
fireworks for yourself
yes okay okay
HQ where I am
[Music]
this way this way Tucson I will stand
where you have to get off so you see me
or is this Loop shark mine oh
um this way but what's this way I'm just
gonna go up you cannot possibly drive
past me now
I'm leaving to fly
oh okay
okay I'm not gonna get lost though I see
where I am okay I'm going to just fly
now okay I'm going to go to another
portal okay
do you have something golden
no
if we go to my house and the new server
I have gold and stuff there no I'll I'll
borrow you something
oh okay something gold
something pretty
something oh
let's see
a gold sword probably doesn't count okay
make something
another an En server right uh yeah okay
okay uh I'll make you some boots
there we go
oh can I how do you do I have an anvil
oh I have no Anvil anymore
no whatever I will just be for walking
around
pick Rockets again
I think you need paper and the the
powder the thingy the thingy powder I
have much paper
I might make some more if I can just in
case that would be good you know it
would be at my house though
in the new server oh okay well my house
is close to the portals okay good the
server oh go go go go go my basement
oh it's in my basement I'm gonna get
water real quick I got gunpowder I'll be
right back okay eye around the water I
assume yes yes okay be right back
guys this is the first time today that I
I have now a moment just with you guys
hello
[Music]
I've been talking constantly with others
I missed you guys
I forgot what your voices sound like
hi
do you guys think I can find the
Pillager Outpost quickly relatively
quickly
oh mama is here
I will be a big challenge we're just
gonna fly far far far far
but then do you think it will be a
challenge to to take over them
to kill him
[Music]
unani
you learn something to someone you
borrows are you correcting my
did I say I I'll gonna borrow it okay I
should know that that's just I I know
that I just
you'll be fine it's not as well it's
easy okay okay okay okay they just my
viewers just gave me confidence for our
mission I feel confident now
oh I was trying to scare you yay
impossible mummy I cannot be scared
I am the challenge I'm fearless
you still have candy from Japan which
one what kind of seasons are
drops drops it says drop
are you sure that's all it says no
there's like other stuff but I can't
read okay
you gotta you gotta go now
succeed to the Merit of handmade as the
old time Spirit still now
that makes no sense
[Music]
I'm gonna go get you and go get your
powder or so powder right no what are
you getting fireworks
uh yeah I wanna make fireworks but it's
in the other server okay
should I follow you I'll follow you
because I didn't see yourself anyway I
guess I'll do because otherwise I'll
just be standing around my house is a
shack let's go can you fly
yeah I think so
um okay
[Music]
fine
I feel so good
doesn't it how can you play Minecraft
any other way after you get an Elijah
right so hard oh this is new I didn't
notice the the new sign
above Army
interesting
uh this oh my gosh where's Mommy
oh I'm going to the portal you see where
you know where the portal to the JP
server is
um
I just kind of came from it but oh my
gosh oh there you are okay I I I'm you
don't know no I can I can land
ing still has to be practiced huh is it
this one
um yeah nope come wait where where are
you that was it no oh you're on the
other side okay go to New Hollow live
world we
[Music]
in a great neighborhood near the
transportation system to the other place
this is my house it's very
um
this is my shack I mean it's my
temporary Shack there's an Olay in there
be careful well I think it's tied there
though okay I want to go to my basement
that's where my stuff is oh okay oh my
God
yeah
does it not like Fly Away
um it's leashed up right careful so I
lost you where are you oh I'm in the
basement go around the side there's a
basement
um I must have gunpowder somewhere I'm
looking for it
oh yeah but it's Clay
well I gotta I can't have like
expectations to Ian builds because this
is different this is not I can't build
things relatively organized
where's my gun palette it was working
nice I could find my gun powder there is
oh I have a golden shelf like in brain
anymore we don't need a golden shade
oh yeah but gold man I have to I think
it has to be armor
where the heck is I thought it thought
it okay I don't have gunpowder never
mind
[Music]
he'll get it by burning things was that
cold oh
gunpowder I think you have to get some
like creepers and oof maybe there's
something somewhere in the en server
uh ID and Japan
but wait I mean
I mean
I have uh like a hundred
you have a hundred oh maybe it's fine I
have 29. okay I'll give you a couple
more and hopefully that'll be enough
whenever we can I guess we'll just jump
into a boat or so instead we have a boat
I do have a
did I leave it
I had a bow I can make a boat okay
you make the book
oh is that base
looks like it says
take my stuff I'm so like
is it right next to you
I definitely had more stuff
oh
happy mume and my team will 100 be an
advantage and will help me get my my
goal and and yeah defeat the pillagers
for sure
um
huh
okay well I've even less prepared and
it's not on a leash mummy also it has a
sword
yes
that's a sword it's not a leash
be careful don't leave the door open now
leave me
stays in there
it's so cute
I can't believe Minecraft destroyed the
current meta by giving you like a pet to
help you with collecting things
what a patch
unbelievable I am so I give you some
here
oh
you can use these ones too they're
different ones because they're different
speed
ah thank you okay all I have is an iron
sword I have good arms are you kidding
me
I have
um I think I think I'll give you this
bowl it's even flaming with these arrows
there you go oh
so okay yes try to stay away because I
didn't bring a sword now hmm
um we can go quickly back and I can give
you maybe a sword I think I have maybe
one day since one one more I'm a bit
concerned because I swear I had more
stuff unless the stuff is in the en
server like I have diamonds and stuff so
I'm
gonna fish the pillagers with your with
your fishing rod oh no that's for you
thank you
I'm already with you
I basically fished you just in case oh
we fish each other
oh yeah yeah I do have I do no wait no I
don't have one okay let's go Mommy
uh to the end server again where was it
oh that Kyle my stuff's my good stuff
that Kyla's place right she opened a
storage unit for me
boots boots boots for you
oh thank you mine are about to die thank
you golden boots I mean they're really
just foreign
to wear Ian
to the end oh this way okay
and then we'll go without further a duel
because I got [\h__\h] to do I need to go we
got to do it I have to do it I have to
accomplish something
wait ah here
yeah I knew that the end world let's go
I follow you okay I'm your backup yeah
think of me as your backup okay okay
my my second chance in life yes okay
your insurance we will go through the
Never
um and then we will take my train
okay and then we will come out at the
Mesa by Omi but we will go even further
wait did I actually not after going to
the Mesa fly out to find the like Azalea
stuff
was that
did I go
from my Mesa by Omi
or
yeah I did
I
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] mummy oh
that means
[Music]
that means that was before the patch so
oh was it the same update wait was it
the same update
was the Frog did they come did the frogs
come with them they want to say
all the chance because I already
explored that area you know I've already
flew there so it already spawned a lot
I didn't see a pillage I'll post on the
way but oh well
okay
there might be Alice inside the pillow
management that was ages ago there's no
way that there were allies in there now
that there that they spawned in there
now right
frog is recent yeah
okay okay
hope for the best
where'd you go they can reach they spawn
they spawn in Pillager outposts that
have already been uh like explored
before the
update
am I at one guy am I being one guy who
am I doing one guide a lot I do get I
get like one guide and two guide like
it's usually two because like I I'm wary
of you know being one guide but it ends
up being two guide then I don't blame
you
um
all right I don't know I don't even know
where the old one is so we're just gonna
fly out far and see what we'll find
when we come to the other side I am on
the way come to the top side what oh I'm
here I've been here
guys I don't think I can read super
chats today because this is some
with my second Quest today I'm doing
more than I thought I would be doing
people still have to cook afterwards
oh you know what you're gonna make love
me I saw you replied to me by the way
and I tried replying back like a million
times but Twitter kept on crashing on me
to what uh you you wrote something to me
I think to a a cooking tweet that I did
you can get into the boat
like we can support
the potato wedges yeah and then I was
replying because I thought you were like
like not real moments I was like oh you
look like a fake woman to me I had to
check your profile did you not believe
that I would like French like potato and
no it's more like first of all you
didn't have the check mark and you
changed your profile picture and you
normally don't reply to me so I was like
is this really
[Music]
I don't get many replies from other
members so that was like really weird
for me
I thought I must reply to potato oh you
like potato I like potatoes what's your
favorite like form of a potato
wedges or I like french
fry oh I did too
[Music]
Destiny
perfect to advertise my kfp travel
agency
huh let's get out of the boat oh okay
and uh okay wait so what what's your
favorite type of potato like I like what
form but oh bones I like potato wedge
uh wait like a mix of french fry and
wedge it's mostly a wedge it's just long
wedge oh what about mashed potatoes
I like mashed potatoes but I don't know
how to make them and I very rarely have
had them because
mother Al didn't like cooking them
because they were a hassle
I see oh this is so scary mashed potato
it's mashed potato
wait is mashed potato common in Europe
you know I have escaped I have escaped
oh dear wait don't die
don't do anything stupid I didn't die I
didn't die I lived welcome to my many
never portals um whoa
are you
did you spawn for the back one
no I spawned through the same one I just
went around oh okay okay
and yeah have you been here before
probably not right
to this area no okay
um I always forget which
way
is the ah [\h__\h] why am I strong oh
[Music]
okay um
thanks for the help you're welcome I
watched
which one is is it that way
nah
I always forget why did I not make it uh
why did I not make a sign
South
South uh how do you see the
F3 every thank you
I helped facing south
is it really South
is it I guess we'll go south
let's go how many how many guys said it
I mean it could be normally I am here
with a boat so I guess we didn't break I
have your belt oh you brown
accidentally picked it up but I also
have my own belt so I'm prepared you're
thinking I said I use brain wow I'm
impressed
yeah that's it okay I see it now
beautiful so we'll Traverse through the
water a little bit no I guess we'll fly
over the missile
this is the beautiful Mesa by Omi that I
found mumi
oh
I mean it doesn't look good in in the
night you don't really see it's Beauty
we should sleep oh oh yeah I need to
give you your bed I think
yes please I have no bed
here is brown bed
yeah yeah thank you now we sleep this is
my little room
very luxurious I oh don't
it's comfy it's just
big enough for us too yeah but it wasn't
really built to have guests always up
funny we were smelling each other's feet
oh
it's so pretty yeah like everything
looks orange and brown just like us
we're also Orange Crown it's like it
matches our hair
okay so
um which direction should we fly just
south should we continue South and then
we fly waiters this page is right there
what the heck oh you're right does that
mean there's an outpost
what oh [\h__\h] oh that's scary oh
did they see us
that's just a ray that's just Patrol
okay oh okay mommy try to follow me I'll
try not to be too fast but
let's go
how do I fly I forgot
double spacebar right click okay I got
it just just fly straight let's just
keep on flying straight
okay
um
but I wonder if we fly two different
directions and somebody finds a pillow
job post we can give each other the
coordinates and then just
I don't know what those look like but I
I worry that you die but I think when
you see it you'll notice it's like a big
tower
relatively big
a big tower I could look up a picture
too
oh yeah you should okay should we where
do we come from I think that would be
smart to to go separate ways than just
for finding the Outpost okay you look at
the picture
okay and then one will fly uh
removed we're going south
so the post is back there
um hold on let me write some stuff down
I'll fly a little bit left South and you
fly a little bit right South
okay
[Music]
I like your cape by the way how do you
get berries on your cape I have no idea
oh wait no I already gave you Rockets
left hand isn't it not is it not in my I
guess it's my right hand villager
Outpost
yeah yeah I have an off the phone kit
but mine is not berries
mine is like a really cool Phoenix
look this is so fitting I was like what
the [\h__\h] OptiFine this is
we're just looking for this and hoping
for the best that we just stumble upon
one exactly wait can I want to take a
screenshot
perfectly let's go okay all right
uh keep me updated on what you're seeing
don't get lost
um okay try to keep on having like south
of you as your direction but uh yeah you
go left I go right
like oh I got almost almost West
somewhere between South and West and you
go somewhere between east and south okay
okay
you you know where you see that right
yes okay okay
all right
well wait I'm just going over ocean now
it's almost like a a challenge now
because
um who knows should I find it first fly
slowly don't spend too many
um
um Rockets because I'll have to go to
you if you find this person you have to
go to me
um okay yo what is that
what
[\h__\h] it's a Mesa Mountain spiky Mountain
by oatmeal what
what the [\h__\h] I never saw that before
oh it's a Mesa Village
oh so pretty oh it's not here I
shouldn't look
is there like a area where Pillager
outposts often spawn like in like in a
desert or so I think I saw it in a
desert before but doesn't matter
chat let me know
anywhere okay that's what I Bond
slowly flying
often saw them in the desert yeah me too
but I guess it doesn't matter okay even
in the jungle
could they be
um
new chunks is it new chunks oh I think I
saw a burp
third yeah oh snowy snow right in the
jungle Shore makes sense Minecraft makes
a lot of sense
I saw snow
wow trees
trees you like snow Mommy
yeah yeah I like snow
I think yeah I like snow do you know how
to ski
no I haven't skied since I was very
little oh
so if you go skiing now you would
probably get into an accident like me
I know the pizza and french fry
wait it'll actually only generates
environments that let Villages generate
so it won't be on top of a mountain okay
okay
anywhere where a village could be that
makes sense
what did you just say about the French
fry
Pizza french fry
um
saying the same thing I never learned it
like that because I guess just because I
I didn't learn it in in English oh maybe
it's because I like the only time I ever
went I was like pretty small I want to
fix my chunks what the [\h__\h] was that
crazy
[\h__\h] oh
the game oh yeah there's like some
snowball oh yeah be careful I don't know
what you're supposed to do I can't get
out of the water Dig Down
I can't die okay I don't want to die I I
logged out of panic shovel the snow dick
dig the snow in the snow in front of me
or below me below me what
the [\h__\h] make sure it's not one guy oh
no they're all saying it oh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] I didn't know about this
that's new
yeah I think it is new because it
happened to me
and I didn't know what to do when I died
oh no
I want to fix my my chunks uh I should
render more right more chunks
because while I'm flying it's barely
loading in
okay
it was new long time ago but I never saw
it before that's cool it's kind of cool
though but it scared the [\h__\h] out of me
okay let's see here
oh
I'm gonna die if I do like stuff like
that
[Music]
okay okay come on you know how to fly
Chihuahua
yeah
this is snow or snow
oh okay let's go
What on earth oh someone been here
maybe what do you see
I see a floating Rock
um
that's weird weird it's very weird
guys scream when you see something you
know
um
okay I'm going to use seven more Rockets
I'm going to be what no one
no no no I'm just saying what a U7 more
because I'm worried okay well what is
that I have 47.
one did you thanks that looks like one
did that am I so [\h__\h] lucky
like I found one
I found a village we don't need a
village
no did you find one at the same time
hold on hold on I found one that's for
sure what's your coordinate what if I
asked did I I think I went Southeast
wait what what what's your coordinate my
coordinates are uh minus
wait are we looking at blocker chunk
it's been too long block right questions
minus 2532
and then 71 and then uh one thousand no
000 for 163.
the first one minus two thousand uh
minus 2530.
did I hold on how do you zoom in to look
you know I have the shaders and I can
why can't I not [\h__\h] land
I can't let I keep on floating around
looks like I don't have a bed oh no it
was lag that was leg I could have died
okay okay should we sleep uh yeah oh I
definitely found can't sleep yeah
how do I zoom in
you know although the screenshot
I might look so empty from here but I'm
sure there's people there
let's
do something let me sleep okay sleep
for sure okay sleepy time
[Music]
yo yo
I'm going to check real quick if this is
one
no mommy but I have one but the village
you mean that's right with you
yeah I just wanted to see if there's one
around here not all of them have allies
that's okay that's okay I'll just check
this one if it doesn't I'm only gonna
look a little bit more but so basically
you have to first like like kill
everybody right and then it's probably I
read that that it's like you have to dig
it's like under it right like would it
be here
Jack
they respawn
would they be nearerville I'm just
keeping no they don't have to be near a
village okay then I just found a village
I guess we're outside there
hope you have milk it will be a cage
outside
oh
so I could see it if I go like around it
a little bit
maybe if I fly a little bit land on top
of the Outpost
oh will they see me if I land on top of
the Outpost
invisibility potion I would be good but
I'm not that prepared
okay and I'll try to fly on top of it
I'll wait for you to confirm if
oh if I see a cage okay yeah oh God
too many arrows or uh Rockets yeah yeah
okay
I can't control
I got I lost my connection
oh
it was too laggy what's going on
no problem though right at least I
didn't uh do it while while flying okay
all right
slowly slowly slowly slowly slowly
slowly
I think I oh no oh
[Music]
sure okay
I see pillages I see some weird things
oh God he saw me ah but he can't reach
me up here
that dude definitely saw me
is this why they would hide it now or
more cagey right
can't get up okay okay
what if this has doesn't have a cage a
wooden box a wooden cage
how close would it be
more left and closer
[Music]
oh wait that that
is what I have one oh yeah
okay okay
what were the coordinates again minus
2500 uh no what what yeah minus
2500.00 and then uh well the middle one
is blah whatever and then the third one
is one a 13 500.
okay I'm kind of far let's go try to get
there okay fly carefully and slowly
don't die and be careful of the spawning
chunks don't fly into a mountain
okay let's see let's go
don't try to announce it okay my
connection is like so shitty
I got kicked out again no it's raining
is it because of the did you increase
your
okay
[Music]
I'll decrease this
um
now maybe just the chunks would be okay
will my loading new chunks make silver
lag oh okay I'll just I'll just uh stay
still here
oh it's because I'm finding new chunks
maybe yeah overall that stuff that's
okay I'm safe now as long as I don't do
um crazy
should I put the cards in the chat for
you does that help
sure I think I remember two negative
2100 500. yes and uh negative 13 000
something I'll write it down anyway so
you know yay you can always check
I have to hold myself back to not
already start the combat I feel like
from the top we can we could like use a
strategy to just shoot a lot of them
from the top
and then go down and see what's left of
them
but I feel like I can find a lot of them
from the top
yeah I put my bed down I already slept
in it
positive
[Music]
uh did I write it wrong
yeah positive yeah I wrote it correctly
yeah yeah I'm getting one guide
I can't how do you change this okay
there we go
yeah my shield but I have to call the
totem
this is right there so honestly dying
here wouldn't be such a big issue
um I'll hold it before we start just in
case that I fly into a mountain and then
get kicked out again
um
[Music]
yeah yeah I was thinking there's one of
those trees here does that mean there's
a lush cave right here too
probably
ah you are correcting roommate not me oh
okay okay
oh did I say negative apparently oh well
I knew it was positive
yeah oh yeah yeah did you see a latch
cave before a moment
yes okay with the azaleas yeah because
apparently there's one right here as
well I went to quite a few
did you get four walks oh God
they definitely you know I'm around
I should fly away sorry it's taking a
long time not even in the negatives yeah
like a memories uh like like how long is
their memory that I'm up there how long
can they remember
I'm too famous
yeah it's safe but how well are they at
shooting me
foreign
yeah how long do they remember they will
never forget me
should I open the fire because I can't
hold back
I can't see them yeah they're probably
like gathering in the tower trying to go
up because they they feel that I'm there
oh
let's see I need to this is good warm-up
someone shot me from somewhere I think
that's so slow oh no worries
I must have gone did I go far
East or did you go far west
was that my own that was my own ball
um
I went
um I think Southwest
oh yeah
we weren't very far away wait we're both
of those arrows my arrows
did nobody shoot me
did nobody ever shoot me
oh
oh well I didn't need to scare you you
scared yourself yeah
[Music]
oh higher AC doesn't know this
there we go
shitty weather to start this fight but
yeah it is
oh I got it is it the same weather all
around no no I got him
oh they're going crazy now
but they got no time maybe
you don't need me you you you're giving
me confidence I'm not alone in this you
yeah there's plenty of enemies I think
for us to fight how many pills are there
usually yeah
I have The High Ground party started
oh
Okay negative one thousand two hundred
I'm getting closer
yeah buddy got him
good look at those emeralds the heck
they keep on running once they see me
they run like
so far inside that I can't see them
anymore
gotta go down
they respawn
how fast not that fast
good practice they will restart your
practice what I mean but how fast like
how could I like get time to maybe Mulan
can be my scapegoat
oh God
I'm so dark I don't like it I'll light
it up here
down and fly it you can go inside
filling them yeah I guess one can you
like go
um inside and then shut up now but then
how am I gonna exit
hey how is the best way to do it
[Music]
dig under
I guess you could oh yeah we could dig
down and go
yeah always invade from the roof really
I was thinking barricading ourselves if
they really spawned that endlessly
oh this looks like [\h__\h] without shaders
man
[Music]
oh
Mommy how's the flying going how how
many fireworks do you have left at 36 of
the regular ones okay I also still have
plenty I think we'll have enough to go
back to
me
mommy can you sing me Something
ah
[Music]
if you don't mind the coughing yeah no
problem I mean just like you know a
little little
[Music]
oh yeah
okay I'm nearby
um
to me oh I see it okay where are you oh
you're on the top yeah maybe come to the
top okay
I must perfect this Landing he did yeah
really slowly circles yeah nice nice
eyes ah
[Music]
I did it I did it hello now if you look
over there straight over there I put a
bed and a ender chest down there maybe
you wanna or I guess you could put your
bed heat up here and touch it up here oh
yeah
okay
so I kind of want to do this at least a
daylight I think but my bed is over
there will they shoot me down when I fly
I'll try
I'm too fast oh I can't rest here
because there are enemies oh okay and
better make it over at my
my bed okay
okay okay
um I don't know where you went oh is it
where that light is yes
okay
circle circle circle circle
I see you circling good job
cookie
all right okay
they saw us wait wait oh there's a lot
there's a lot of them I'm going back to
the roof
to the roof yeah okay to the roof
and then we will you have an ax right if
we make a hole here will they see us
through it right away or
I think I messed up my spawn
oh did I mess it up if I if I took my
bed oh yeah then yes yes
we are back
I'm wasting arrows um I'm going to set
it up somewhere else
not there because they they went there
I'm gonna go oh yeah I want to go up
here okay
[Music]
there's a bed here that's a sheep that's
a sheep that is a sheep
I mean it's you take to make a bed nice
job
okay I'm coming back I'm not sure he
didn't even realize it
well man are you ready for the Wither
[Music]
what
did you not did you hello I'm here okay
okay okay
uh so you have an ax right
yes I'm scared what what if you make the
hole under all underneath because I hear
the whole but I guess they're kind of
far away they sound like they're not on
the floor right beneath us
are they are they here
look down first what do you mean look
down
and just shoot them through okay you
make a hole and be careful be very
careful stay back okay stay back
foreign
[Laughter]
nice nice nice ow
but like this is never gonna end right
if they keep on spawning I just hope we
kill them faster than they spawn and
then once we take over that level I
guess we can go down one level and then
block it off or so
there's a thing over there I think it's
good now ah there's one more coming
clear oh
I saw one oh but they're not he's not
coming up
don't worry I heal
okay in a moment we will go down and
we'll try to block off the stairs okay
do we have a block to block it off I
don't have a shield
wait I I'm in a blog okay I have a Blog
I have a Blog I don't know I only have
one block though
I've got a shield wait there's more
okay
I snipe
yeah Fox uh one block do you have more I
guess we could take
um
quickly get some can I do you want me to
take from this roof
uh yeah maybe from The Edge or so
oh God I'll run out of now now we won't
do it that long
but my boat dies
I'm going to get
oh nice voluntary Exile oh because I
killed the boss or what
huh should I go down should I go down
I'm scared I'll go down blocks for you
hold on
uh yeah yeah in a moment we just just
when we go down there you see the stairs
right just this block off trying to
block off the stairs completely I don't
I'll I'll do it I only have one block
though maybe it will be there
there's so many movies
yeah they all came back
maybe we should oh God I hope I don't
run out of arrows I have 55
okay I have the infinite one so leave
the shooting uh to me but now I mean 55
it's enough it's enough
let's try to clear the area again
oh they have weapons we can grab
let's clear the area
I I might go down and you go with me
let's go okay okay let's go yeah let's
go let's go down oh yeah okay cancel you
go first
um
okay okay
[Laughter]
bottle of enchanting there's some stuff
here a goat horn
is that useful okay okay wait do you
have your elytra on uh yeah
you might you have other armor
uh oh yeah I should switch maybe right
or red okay so use the gold one why oh
to play it there's no oh there's no time
for that now okay once how do you do
that
[Music]
this is our tower now the sound of your
doom
there's some downstairs
should I make another Hole uh I don't
know what to do because
the lower we go the more they will spawn
on the ground ooh the thing is the the
cage is over here we can't just set it
all on fire we have to
I didn't bring fire
that's okay block tower entrance
I'm shooting them is that okay yeah I
guess okay now let's make another hole
try to clear the area and then with a
banner is that bad no that's good okay
oh that one has probably a good reach
um let's make another hole
another hole Yeah okay how did I get up
to this level oh because there were
stairs okay okay we're doing the same
thing again but I think the level below
us is already the lowest level maybe so
then we have to
make sure to close the entrance uh
quickly what the [\h__\h] that was me oh
that's what a burning nice Mommy
they're so fast yeah
oh my gosh chill guys I'm just trying to
kill you oh we have a bad Omen now
wow
I like the shooting part of this
yeah
[Music]
this is also why I prefer um Adventures
over building in Minecraft
oh nice shot damn that was a good
headshot
is it sounds relatively empty now we're
getting there
I can't hear so I'm depending on you I
can turn my volume up I turned it down
because the villagers noises make me so
much do you have blocks ready
yes let's go down okay
[Laughter]
nice okay
Maybe
could we should we um should we open one
in the middle again let's open the
middle again
hi guys
it's us again
well I guess if we had lava we'd kill
her we'd be killing ourselves too ah and
I would probably end up in a very
chaotic situation oh you're lining up
the the place with me
skeleton
I thought that was your fight okay oh no
I thought the skeleton sounds really
really empty again you can go down soon
maybe
okay
oh I see that one more come here come
here come here oh I'll kill them I'm
going down oh God oh God
okay well my mama come down help me Mama
come down here
to help
let's block it off let's block it off
I'll kill whoever comes
okay okay
let's see why are they not coming
they're not coming Where'd I okay I
guess they didn't see us the new ones
the new spawned ones didn't see us yet
where are the blocks moving where are
the blocks I see
it I guess they can't come up here I put
the blocks down oh I guess that's all
this one oh sorry I missed one no I
thought they could enter Through the
Windows oh no problem then okay okay
I thought we were already like at the
level is yeah they can be ours mermaid
oh but we only brought
okay one more level I guess
okay
hello hello
are there anything down there I don't
maybe we heard of them oh no I see one
oh is it okay
and I heard him too oh there he is he's
running frantically
they're not even out here got him
I think that's it let's go down
shut up
and use the axis I use okay nice okay
got it nice
[Applause]
down it's ours we took over let's go
but now how do we get to the allies
[Music]
um we're outside they're outside in the
cage right there like
right there just have to make like a
safe a digging oh I guess we can dig
yeah oh okay we'll see okay I don't have
a shovel but I have this ax you want me
to dig yes for the wood and I have a
pickaxe so I'll I'll dig through the
stone or whatever we find I wanna oh uh
do we have one more block
oh
nice denied denied entrance but one more
time
[Music]
do not disturb us
we're on the Rescue Mission
but how do we know where to exactly to
dig towards
I guess we'll just really roughly assume
it is somewhere this direction or Fern
cool
okay I blocked the windows math memory
uh okay I'll
I wish I had the shovel now
it's okay
what okay you maybe you go first which
way should we just stay on the dirt
level maybe that should be enough yeah
it just does I think more or less
straight and then sometimes maybe dig up
maybe dig up
um
this way yeah straight oh somewhere
there we go wait oh I'll get rid of this
how about here
oh I hear them
I hear that I think it's a little bit
more
maybe a little bit more yeah give me the
shovel
I give you the shovel
thank you
[Music]
did I get it
I'll see you oh wait take it back sorry
here from the distance wait thank you
got it now I got it
I hear them that's a good way of finding
out where they are
Hoards the sound
oh yeah it's like hot cold hot cold it's
getting hotter
now
oh
oh there you go there's somewhere
there's somewhere there I mean we're on
the ground so I'm not sure how loaded
loud it can get but oh they must be here
I hear L.A yearns okay yearns the
Pillager murmurs though they're still
some pillagers be careful I'll I'll peek
yeah I hear them
um
I make
the yarn I'm saying
[Music]
uh wait
uh
[Music]
e e
that was um that was not quite but it
looks really close it looks like there
was some wood structure there
what it was uh what I saw was just the
outside maybe maybe here
Mimi
[Laughter]
and I saw an ally
are they do you think we already
respawned like a lot of them or surely
surely but we just have to
um we just have to spawn inside the Ally
building the cage
what if I go out and shoot from outside
like I snipe them can I do that or no no
it's okay it's okay no okay okay we'll
be fine
um
[Music]
um I just it one size
and maybe a little bit further I saw it
like in ahead of me I think
[Music]
tricky kind of tricky
I'll try
here
what I can see oh [\h__\h]
oh
okay
uh I'm okay okay okay
I'm practically in the cage it's uh it's
here
okay oh
[Laughter]
my God
daylight out of the cage too the
pillagers were in the cage too how do I
get it to be mine here take this wait
wait okay okay
wait wait wait wait wait where'd it go
there it is it's in the Box okay give me
something uh what do you want what do
you want do you want fish give you fish
no
there's a hole there as long as I have
one I'm happy but this is really awesome
I need the lead oh I need the lead
wait though uh don't uh okay I'm going
to block this hole hold on
they they saw me and they were like oh
she's my my hero and they immediately
they they hurried over to me I wonder if
there's still another one there
is there like one per cage or so because
we saw two
[Music]
oh my my mind is trying to fly away oh
okay if we only have one then we'll just
bring one that's okay
I think if you give it something that
follows you really it's okay
it started straight for the opening it
right
wasn't gonna follow you it would have
left by now it would have gone through
that whole I'm pretty sure
I don't know he will follow me really
even if what if I like fly
no I think if he fights too fast
like I read a tutorial and it says like
uh it will
it will like teleport but
don't fly
um all right it's flying around because
it's looking for items for me what if I
give it a camera how do I give it
another item
penny
I don't know
how do I give it a different one
okay
it'll fold but it might straight away
keep an eye on it
eh okay let's test it if it will come
with me I
I we're done
let's go
it's not okay I put a I blocked it off
but I taken these
to block the windows and it darted
straight for the opening of things ah
but maybe it's still floating around
there maybe we can still say that
if you want it I already have mine you
know just because we're not much of a
hero if we leave one like out there but
it's free go to the roof okay let's go
to the roof okay
okay
you have to ask maybe you might get rid
of the the yeah cut off there yeah wow
that was so cool the way they flew into
my arms me
oh it's scary
where is it oh I see there's someone in
the cage
what if we what if we just quickly run
over there try to open the cage and Let
It Fly freely
let me try to shoot oh we keep it there
maybe oh God oh God scary scary scary
woman be careful
the dude is there
where I saw him I should oh he should
wait no
um I think since we only have one leash
and uh anyway though maybe we keep this
last one in the cage just in case I need
another one then I know the coordinates
for the last one
[Music]
okay let's do it that way
whooshie brush he shot me
yeah because it's still there's one in
the cage and I guess one we just freed
and I'm happy for that one it can
hopefully find
a happy life yeah can you open that up
please oh yeah go upstairs
where's my baby
it will come to me right
I heard him I heard it giggle
baby
[Music]
stick by you
drop stones
hello
what that's why I need a leash
we're gonna get my leash I mean the
least you have the one leash
where is it
oh
honey
don't fly too far away ah it's looking
for stuff don't don't go away no just
stay here
hey
thanks
I make me so happy
I'm shooting now
no baby what do I call it mommy oh
um I called I forgot the name I got my
name on silly blue silly Bloom that's
what I need
I'll name one mine after you move me
yeah I will be mummy
mummy hi mommy Mommy come here
oh not too many I'm going to leave okay
why are you fighting them because I
wanted to
okay so I saw there's one more in there
I can't see it now but yeah okay there
it is
uh
huh mommy mommy
okay so I have the coordinates if I ever
need another one I will come here
now how do I know who you're talking to
are you talking to me are you talking
about it
both oh I see let's um do you maybe want
to fly to your wherever your leash is uh
the under chest is over there where the
bed was my bed oh okay I'll get it and
then come back here so I can give it to
Mummy
[Applause]
oh my God it's okay I'm safe
from water you forgot your wings
oh
fine
I'm fine
I'll protect mumi and mummy oh God he
gave up get a leash he gave up he's
coming back look at all that yummy EXP
[Music]
o
yeah I don't want to shoot the by
accident does it only have one HP the
Ally Ally oh yeah
I wonder how much okay I'm coming back
this time with wings maybe I have wings
noise
okay do you want to read
uh yes
we have been on an adventure moment
let me test if it comes back come back
if it's on the lead won't I have to be
like pretty careful with bringing it
back
yes
you will have to protect me I guess
[Music]
ah drink milk before coming back yeah
oof where's my baby
Mommy
[Applause]
but how do I bring it safely
[Music]
oh dear oh my God it's so cute
oh gosh there's a lot of them
if you fly with wings rolling slowly it
does with leads it doesn't work right it
won't be able to
catch up right go buy boats and we'll
have to find some water oh wait oh
it's down there
too fast little break yeah no more
arrows
uh yes
uh seven more of them they're all oh
dang it they're all here no no no then I
mean I could how about
um how about I give you the the infinite
bow oh yeah and you try to protect me
while I walk over to you okay yeah can
you give me it you're killing them okay
I'm also setting this maybe you may give
me the other one back then
okay this one thank you
all right oh wait I need a I need one I
have one here uh you can have these oh
yeah this is this is another challenge
getting mummy and mummy back safely hmm
I think I can I killed the ones outside
just now okay wait there's some more
here
oh they're coming they're coming all
right
[\h__\h] hell
Mommy okay okay I'm I'm gonna run for it
let's go
oh [\h__\h] I don't want to fly
I lost the lead I think oh she's she's
following you I think okay then I just
gotta I guess without the lead go
carefully Mommy
Mommy
maybe on the way out you can pick up the
leash if you find it okay
broke on my fall I think maybe it's like
just um when you go fall down the holes
good yeah yeah perfect okay
so leave the other one there
uh yeah yeah for now so maybe we'll find
uh I'll I'll get it when I need another
one when Mummy dies or so mommy Mommy
come here
okay I wanted to fly over there now okay
um I think because I don't have milk
maybe I'm happy if I just can go over to
the Mesa by Omi for now I think
[Music]
uh yeah
here if we make it to the mess up oh you
know where we had the never portal then
I think oh I'm happy I'm plenty happy
then
oh got the lead okay
ah
it's so cute this is way cuter than the
axolotls like who cares about axolotls
and this one actually does stuff for you
yeah
I would like you too mommy
I'm here
Mommy
I hear her giggle she's over there
she's so cute all right all right mommy
let's pack our fangs
oh and oh shoot my bed
what'd you do it's up there
oh
I mean you still have it closed off
right
it's like it's on the mountain
do I need it
oh
oh you you can probably click on my bed
are you taking your bed
[Music]
we can leave it here actually just in
case we're done we spawn here and then
take the second Ally
um wait I didn't bring up
no wait wait what does it need for an
Ender Chest
[Music]
does it need silk touch
oh I do have sub touch okay okay no
problem no problem
oh
I got it all oopsie
perfect okay uh you got a boat right but
for now I think we have to walk a little
bit
okay wait I don't have a bet we don't
have a bed to sleep on
um when it gets dark yeah that's me I'm
gonna find my bed yeah better to bring
it I guess
we have to go by foot and by boat maybe
if I find that sheep again I'll find it
um
also I don't have the coordinates for
the Mesa thingy oh I have the
coordinates for where we split off okay
shoot where is my bed
oh where is my bed did you not leave
I know I put it in a random spot on this
mountain
I am
[Music]
I mean you could sleep and I'll just log
back in okay what happens if I sleep
with the leash it's uh I have to put it
on a on the fence Maybe
it's fine
okay
[Music]
this is the cutest thing ever I'm so
happy this might be the reason that
makes me play Minecraft again
the thing
it's so cute yeah okay and I got mine by
rescuing it so it will be forever
grateful to me
yeah oh yeah mine's mine's just
I kidnapped mine yours is yours is also
rescued they totally spawn randomly
somewhere
oh no zombie
don't don't hit my Ally
can you can you kill it but without
killing my Ally
I'm scared of that why isn't it paying
attention to me hello I got one hit I
got another okay okay okay okay all
right let's um I'll take the bed
do you have the coordinates
yes I have just for where we split off
okay one second
one second
this makes me really nervous it was 326
and 11 533.
my Ally is Invincible to my attacks
really
almost can't kill out really okay okay
okay
it's just far away it's kind of like a
porch like a lamp for us
it's glowing oh
okay 11 500.
oh god well if I went South West before
does that mean on the way back we have
to go north east
okay
so
okay do you wanna do you wanna get the
boat yeah do you want to take the the
lead I mean I don't mean the leash I
mean take the I will follow you mostly
not too fast not too fast because of
Ally come on
baby good baby
it's like it looks like it's being
dragged it wants to go the other way
alloy friend oh
which way do we go maybe we should be
able to go by water because the Mesa
thing is surrounded by water even if we
go a little bit around mountains maybe
eventually we will reach it
to find the ocean
don't be don't we only have one lead
Mommy we have to we have to leave the
other one behind okay
look at the other one another time okay
yo it's accepted it's fake no maybe I
don't think I should bleed because I am
[Music]
we have to go
what was it again 300 oh God it's far
it's far
um don't we just just try to
um
go south
north we're going well we have to go
this way and if we go this way it's
going to take us to actually you know
okay we'll go this way first this way
first this way first this way first yeah
maybe we'll find the big openings of the
big ocean and then we just try to go
around everything
South north
South
now wait what
let's go up here are you sure you gave
up on the opening of the ocean yes let's
get high ground okay
I'm scared this will not take us to an
opening for a long time okay
oh
uh
[Music]
new member of hollow Tony it's not quite
a bird but we'll just say it's a bird
mushroom up here
mushroom all right I lost the lead
oh where's the lead I just went up a few
steps you little [\h__\h] you went somewhere
to collect some [\h__\h] didn't you all
right let me find it it must be
somewhere I just went straight up
you will follow me even without but
still where's this leash
I hear
don't unleash yourself
you here
do not
I want you to bring you home safely okay
I'm going up
I'm coming
you coming
you coming hey Alex
[Music]
where are you
mommy
oh over here I see you go to that
mushroom
we're right there oh hi oh hi oh hi okay
let's just go this way okay
a little creeper
all right
we good we safe
um
[Music]
God damn it man I should give up on the
leads leash
you'll follow us if we just walk I got a
date
I would hope so but I will attempt to do
it with the leash as long as I can okay
you know when walking around the trees
it keeps on losing it
[Music]
um
if the lead Falls somewhere down there
on the trees I will not grab it I think
I don't think I wanna jump down there
just go slowly but surely it will take a
while but we'll get there
yeah
[Music]
jump up mummy jump jump
where are you don't go too far away
I mean you yes me
okay
I stopped for a second I see you okay
okay after well we're gonna want to go
down here maybe I shouldn't have named
this movie maybe I'll uh okay I'll name
it um you could just call me no no
[Music]
like when we're in the same room okay
that's that's a deal okay just
temporarily okay you go away
yeah aggression
all right should we go down to the water
yes okay to the water
[Music]
thank you Mommy for doing um do it for
doing this one with me thank you I like
the adventures
not having to do it alone is quite nice
yeah I realize remove some stress
perhaps
it's fun
being alone
bless you it sounded like you were
coughing and laughing
I
um oh
I think I dropped the leash
oh no no it's still there it's just kind
of going into the dirt
[Music]
um
mommy Mommy
come down
you little [\h__\h] okay I'll drop some
Stones here
is it gonna try to collect even with the
leash on
me
let me let me come on
I don't see it in the dirt
oh
Mommy
I see I see you see it yeah it goes I
think now I dropped the
I dropped the leash for real now okay
okay uh
it broke
a broke
can we do it without because I don't see
it I got mine without I don't think I
had a lead when I did it another month
okay okay
all right
leash is gone
just uh Gonna Keep on here Mommy
what's your calling to
come here
okay let's go okay ready
[Music]
just every once in a while can you okay
no it's following us it's not following
I think it's focused now and following
us if we keep on going
oh okay oh
go back go back
guys
okay okay okay there we go there you go
okay
[Music]
can we make it both can if you I can put
it in a boat with me wait can we test
that really quick like how would we do
that
is that really possible
it can't sit in the Box
all right we should probably sleep once
oh I'll log out
okay
and then I'll try to make uh
a boat
okay
it's daytime
You're the Reason me and my partner
always refer to mume with that
pronunciation
but I normally don't call mume as mum me
this is just today
so if you're pronouncing mume as mumi
that's not my fault
it's always been mummy
wait what oh this is new cool okay
um
I have just enough
uh
for a boat okay do I have to force it to
sit like you know
while you do that I'm going to go to an
idol meeting okay
snack just in case I'll be right back
thank you
okay put up put it on the land okay
throw a block in the book oh interesting
whoa
oh
so cute in the boat I'll get into it hi
perfect oh why didn't we do this
straight away now we're just gonna try
to go by boat mostly
yeah yeah
[Music]
because
look at oh
wow we gotta get mummy on the picture
too she's like the aunt now or the um
what the God God Parents is that what
you call
those
she'll be the Godparent also my left arm
today my wrist and everything
feels really strange today the Godmother
did they say godfather oh no I said the
Godparent godmother
um
fairy godparents isn't that like a TV
show
she's my fairy's godmother
cute
yeah it feels like I don't know I have
something in my on my hand arm in the
wrist area today
ever since I
uh came to the PC today
the Odd Parents oh oops
close enough
and that's all all getting close to
midnight I know I have to cook I wonder
what I'll be cooking for this week I got
to choose my recipes properly
yeah I'm trying to massage my wrist
right now
Odd Parents is a pun of God Parents ah
makes sense
I get here right as you and I'm not
ending I'm not ending we're gonna go
back I want to go at least to the Mesa
also hey am I no I still haven't
does the curse go away over time as well
maybe
how do we get milk oh maybe someone can
bring us milk worst case hi
hi where's the Milkman oh you got it
yeah nice wait I want to take a
screenshot can you can you look this way
too ah you're now my fairies godmother
mommy I'm
not there oh yay okay okay let's just
try to do to Traverse everything with uh
the boat now even if we have to go
around mountains let's hope this works
okay but yeah I'll probably be faster
coordinates wise I have no idea right
now of what we're doing
so I'm trying to make another portal
there oh there's ocean oh I think oh
there's the jungle broken broken portal
[\h__\h] portable
I wonder what's in the chest
but I will resist
you can fish a boat to move it not
really for you you can fish a boat yeah
it's almost midnight
I didn't think I would
um really play this long today
but I basically did two big quests the
ID yeah toured and I did a Japan new
server tour and then I'm now I'm doing
this with you very productive today very
productive you got yourself
[Music]
all right well now we're in the big
ocean I feel like we can
find it somehow
are you going the right way
oh wait that's a I think that's the Dead
we have to get to like block 300
something just to get to where we split
off that wasn't even where the portal
was true but pretty close though
yeah we can use this let's just use
these open ocean
this is exactly what I want from
Minecraft actually
um wait when is it coming out there's
this Minecraft Legends or so coming out
okay
okay uh Minecraft Legends I think is
called
this week next week or so
it's out now today oh I kind of really
want to play it but
um actually what was the what was the
verdict I asked jenma if we were allowed
to play it because is it from is it from
moja
reviews haven't been good really I want
to play it though because it's like RPG
base basically right
I wanna at least give it a try I wonder
how long it is though
man did you see the the like RPG
Minecraft
I don't think so
RPG Minecraft
it has it has like a Dungeon Crawler
Diablo esque feeling to it
I might fly to see how long it'll take
us to get to oh okay ocean so we can
turn so we can start going west
already going west according to my oh
we're going we're going Southwest but
it's taking us further RTS
RTS let me see
okay
oh it's literally just it's just this
corner oh really oh okay yeah then we
can start going
[Music]
hi Mommy you like my partially my taxi
now
I'm the Navigator Minecraft dungeons is
the Diablo like one oh Legends hopefully
I navigate well they look so similar to
me but I guess they're kind of different
yeah yeah I just wonder if we can get
permission for it hmm
Okay so
I don't know what you're talking about
there's this new Minecraft thingy
it's like not like this one
but it looks like a totally different
game I mean it's like you have quests
and and goals and so on you still build
some things but it's kind of automated
wait I love more or less whoa whoa
okay
thank you
and I'm confused but this is fine this
is fine
this is okay this is fine it is an RTS
what does that mean again real-time
strategy this way
well this is the first time start I saw
some gameplay it didn't look like a
real-time strategy to me but then again
what is a real-time strategy game
um
[Music]
oh I think we had a turn up here I made
a I turned too early maybe
did I oh I'm so bad at this okay we'll
reach it eventually
okay because like AOE yeah
why really
I just saw like the beginning of the
gameplay I guess but hmm
mummy are you gonna play uh the tears of
the kingdom when it comes out
I have to finish breath of the wild
still which I I was playing on stream
then I started playing on my own so I'm
gonna finish it hopefully before it
comes out how far are you to finishing
it
um I haven't played in a while I have
and I forgot the names of the things I
have one more of the big the big guys
you know
the big guys yeah and then
I don't know I've I've watched the end
of the game I'm gonna follow a guy that
says how to beat
breath of the wild fast enough so that
you can play
there's a guide for it oh really he's
the Divine Beast yeah yeah okay okay
there's a guide
well well
I wish you luck I actually I never
played for the wild but I watched full
hundred percent playthroughs like five
times five times yeah they're crazy
this is this one specific YouTuber that
I watched it off several times because I
just really like how he narrates and
reads everything it's like a German
YouTuber
oh wait wait were you talking about
speed runs or no the normal runs full
100 normal runs
yeah you know I watched several times so
I know the story and everything and how
it works and all that but I never played
it myself I felt Satisfied by just
watching it but this time I'm gonna play
it myself I guess
um
watched it is it difficult for you Lumi
breath of the wild yeah it wasn't
difficult but
I can't
I don't oh shoot wait go out here okay I
don't think it's a difficult game but
I was getting I don't know
it's it's long as I was cat I think I
was getting burned out of playing it
when I was streaming it and then I kind
of was like you know I should probably
try playing it again when I wasn't
streaming it then I ended up playing
amount I feel like it's kind of like you
can decide how long the game will be for
you
yeah you can really explore
and do side things
collect stuff I like to bomb the fish
okay did you see the latest trailer
no I haven't oh it's built up extreme
hype like I wasn't even that hyped
before seeing the last trailer
couple days ago you should watch it it's
so hype I will watch it
[Music]
do do they know where they're going do
we know Mommy
kind of it's probably not the fastest
way but I know we're making some
progress okay good good are we
though we're going this is all these
obstacles if it was true open ocean yeah
that's fun look out there we'll get
there
combining sticks to go
did you see any uh trailers at all from
the new one
me yeah yeah I saw like the very first
ones okay so you you saw that you can uh
did you play it did you see the gameplay
one where the developer was like oh sure
it was like
showing how to craft things basically
no I haven't seen that one oh okay
because there's like even more like
crazy crafting options now it's kind of
weird it's like Minecraft now you know
oh you don't just hold stuff no like for
example if you see like a simple rock
and a simple stick you can combine it
and it becomes a weapon
Oh weird there's a lot of those foods
and then you can make yourself like a
car by yeah if you see like a rock
that's shaped like a flat surface you
can use it to make a car you can have
wheels and stuff and I don't know all
kinds of weird things you can you can
make yourself a boat with speed boats
with like wind turbines or so I need to
watch the trail but there's like no
recipes like in Minecraft no you just
gotta freestyle it and hope that it
works I guess
I want to watch and you can stick things
together
this is this is a this is the good way
this is the way to go okay I'm trusting
you until we find another obstacle
this way
the way
sounds like the car from The Flintstones
oh yeah yeah basically your car will
look like the one from the Flintstones
this is your feet
yeah I guess no no no no no no no
it looks really funny the stuff that you
can make looks funny but I don't know I
don't want to craft too much I'm more
the adventurer after all
[Music]
I want to this is the way they say this
is the way how do you know are you guys
just guessing
this is the way does anyone know the
coordinates of my base by the way the
the master base
says the Riser player well that's again
I'm only taking us to where we split off
yeah that's okay for now oh is that
really it but
what is that here we go this way or
another portal
let's see
um keeps on giggling
I call it silly can we go wait maybe let
me check let me check um really quickly
if I have a screenshot of my base I
should have it somewhere
um it wasn't again
uh app data
uh
I can also check
um if it's still open ocean up there
[Music]
I I eat drops
oh my tablet oh I have I have the uh I
have the portal coordinates at least
what should we bring us there
okay
they now I shall try to take the lead uh
let's try X 270
what uh that went relatively close with
that well let's do that
um
in German we say that that yeah I know I
think
most places like even speak English
outside America say Zed oh this is the
way I think because X is going up and
Zed is going down but really slowly
uh
one a 10 10
000 and
270 okay
Mommy tell me something tell me a story
what's up recently with you any updates
on something I don't know
let's see
um I can tell you about today because I
remember what happened today okay okay
all of the the drowned people
um okay today I took my animal out
and I crossed paths with an old person
wait a second I shouldn't well X
shouldn't be going up it should be going
down too right okay
you might have to focus on one and then
like just one at a time just because of
the open ocean okay oh is that you oh
okay
uh uh wait wait wait let me just really
quickly uh understand where the hell I
need to go
um
okay
this way uh please continue
I saw I I crossed paths with an old
person
do you ever cross paths with old people
no I wouldn't sound like what is that
like
across okay they love to talk oh and
they're like retired and they don't have
anywhere they need to be
they live in the moment they are not
worrying about what's to come in the
future because
that'd be sad for them to think about
um so they just talk and talk and I'm
not an old person I have places to be
and I was thinking but okay in Minecraft
and wanted to talk about the old person
animals
perfect new animals you know the thing
or two about animals can I go through
here yeah
laughs
yeah lots of they're like oh yeah my
animal did this thing my animal has this
personality and is that another Tower I
see a village and do you see another
Tower oh my god there was one here let
me take a screenshot just in case I need
another baby who knows if they have one
though
okay uh where what is there where am I
going uh
um
uh
I'm nothing else nothing's going around
it's all going up now uh
what if I have any stories
yeah if you start usually if I hear
other people tell stories they start to
remember
apparently we may have brought a really
big Misfortune upon that Village Now by
passing by
it was already close to an uh Outpost I
mean they were doomed for Maddie
so here's uh unfortunately here's a dead
end
[Music]
maybe here
okay
oh
still open worst case I guess we can
walk a bit but am I even going
yeah yeah yeah
that is going down when I go this way
okay
we're like in a you know what do you
call this kind of area
slots what do you call it
um I don't know
whatever I don't mean River [\h__\h] that is
really a dead end should we walk
I don't mind walking okay let's walk a
little bit
okay
I don't want to hurt my baby
the baby
oh
it's enjoying the the chickies
you more shake me more
is it night time right now
huh
I think it's just raining okay
which way which way which way this way
I think wait wait wait which way oh I
see it okay okay but I would like to go
the way where it goes down on both
um
no okay we have to go this way
mommy I'm trusting you to stay close
both of you
oh
all right awesome I almost died
um be careful here
oh my
oh my all my movie blocks wow
sunflowers and chickens and horse while
titty
[Music]
and there's water again should we try
and get into the wall into the room oh
sure I took your boat oh
okay just place it there and I'll throw
blocks at it
oh wait I'm getting the Box hold on
for me my mommy blocks Come on Mommy
right here
for me
don't be a pain in the ass where are you
where is it
where'd it go huh
who's a good baby you go baby all right
let's go
yoga
you're going to be
you were actually helpful so yay
on it is this oh no oh no oh no what the
[\h__\h] yeah what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is
this is this water that goes down there
let me get yeah kind of no but we don't
wanna we don't wanna go this way
um oopsie [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] what am I doing I
just want to get into the boat
and go back somehow
here
um [\h__\h] oh it do go down it looks kind
of dangerous
um I vote against going down no white
yeah no there's water the water just
kind of ends there
why are we doing
I guess I'm taking out of the boat again
until I get this thing home
let's see oh my gosh
oh Turk ages
oh
okay
um I will we will go we will go I will
try to get X down now let's go this way
X is like really far
[Music]
um
okay where's the boat what are you owing
about
do I need to worry no I'm just looking
at how far it is
[Music]
we're getting into a boat again I guess
because we can sit
[Music]
sit sit
yeah there we go good job I knew you
could do it let's go uh
okay this way this way this way but how
long how long can we go this way
um
Maybe
it's hard to see there's more water
there right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's so
difficult how do I get my pixel home
German always works
okay [\h__\h] [\h__\h] the boats
we're walking again
okay
oh I think you took my boat oh did you
okay maybe yeah I got two I got two okay
okay
[Music]
um
it's gonna walk a while until I see
really a big ocean that is reliable
um
or
I could fly ahead to see oh I mean I can
see you from the mountain first
oh [\h__\h] this is a very mountainous area
I'll go down here again
let me are you already flying
me oh no I wasn't do you want me to oh
no no no no
I will I will jump into the water
refreshing
you are you a good swimmer roomie
yeah I'm gone swimming in so long I have
no idea if somebody was drowning in the
water AKA crony
would you be able to get her to the
shore to the beach
probably
depends is she drowning because she
can't swim or she drowning because like
there's so many waves and it's so
intense because then I'll probably jump
too
the current or is she just like no
because of the because she can't swim in
this situation in this video okay then
yeah I could probably save her wow what
a hero
I really don't have the stamina and the
the strength I think and I'm not a good
swimmer either
I've never it's been
a while since like when swimming with
other people
but
I feel like it's not well I don't know
would it be that hard to bring someone I
feel like it is because you can't use
your arms really you have to have an arm
around the person right that's a good
point it's like mostly swimming with
your legs
cows
let me I have buckets let me get the
milk also what's that Village it's hard
if they struggle oh it's just one house
was that multiple houses really oh [\h__\h]
yeah where are the cops here it goes
if they Panic it can be very dangerous
for both people
I feel like crony would be chilling damn
it it was like drowning long long before
you got to her yeah I got a milk bucket
for you mommy oh
I have I get milk yeah drink drinks I
drink it okay
now we're here yay we're no longer like
really what is that house let me check
really quick I'm curious
now it's safe to go there's a village
over there oh it's a whole how close do
you have to be with a curse to bring the
curse upon the village I hope we didn't
do it because we went really close
but then I saw a bit more
oh well oh well it will say right up top
ah okay okay
oh are we going through the right way
yeah kind of yeah oh
I think I'm getting both down now that's
noise
oh scary scary me looking at the
coordinates makes me not look at the
holes in the grounds this is a holy area
careful what time do you wake up Kiara
um most of the time if I don't have any
reason to wake up early y'all around
like 11 12
12 most of the time noon
um
I was just wondering because you stay up
really late yeah I do
[Music]
the other day my family my my bro when
my mom came by like two days ago and I
told them please don't come too early
because I stream for way too long I
stream fire emblem for way too long
and then they still ended up waking me
up and I was like
and then I I wanted to get myself
water and I looked for a glass uh in the
in the plate drawer and then I looked i
i instead of ah instead of orange juice
I took out the milk and all that it was
like really I was so out of it
I was not there I was not amused and
they were like oh we brought you a
croissant and I'm like huh I couldn't
even laugh at that yeah they even said
to cheer me up you know to be like hey
we woke you up at a shitty time but at
least we brought your crossbow
and I was like um
someone brings food I feel like it's
worth it let's sleep really quickly oh
okay I log out
oh
um
I can't do it you know the meme though
right well the quantity
you can come back by the way
[Music]
awesome
try harder for me
[Music]
say like you're suffering yeah
you I think you have the perfect voice
in theory you have you have the
potential to say it the way it should be
yeah I just don't have the skill
um no no you have the skill you're just
missing the commitment
I mean
I need to watch all right listen the OG
yeah but I I think I sound basically
like the Uchi
don't worry about the croissants anymore
as long as I just want don't want you to
die
in an awkward area here how do we get up
for me we might just have to go around
real quick okay where's my mommy oh
there okay wow it's pretty
um reliable
[Music]
is there a way to get down here careful
be careful my arm my wrist hurts so much
it's so weird
be careful do I have some illness now am
I not too young
do you have
because your wrist hurts yeah
my left wrist yeah wow that's a fluffy
alpaca man
dude
am I abandoned
you left-handed oh yes I love tennis
now this card is cutting you off quite a
bit
maybe it's because I went like are you
acting
I got wrist pain sometimes too but it's
weird because like it's not after it
would make sense if you've been on the
computer for a while they'll notice it
when I'm not on the computer but maybe
that's because I had on the computer for
a while like yeah before but
nah I feel you okay
[Music]
okay
okay but that's just a little bit of it
where is there there's the rest yo that
is already very good looking
nice yay
but that's interesting because I'm still
like X is still on on like 3 000 and we
need to get to minus
three thousand and we need to get to 270
um
uh
can you hear ideally we want to go maybe
into a ocean soon that would be nice so
we can be faster
there's water down there
before we go into the water
oh that looks like a big ocean
okay let's go
[Music]
mountains look so funky
funky oh
shoot I forgot what order the German
flag colors are in oh well Austria is
red white red
um Germany was
um
gold black and something like that
it's reverse I was gonna say the
mountains are German but it's black
yellow oh that was easy no it's black
radio black line reverse black not right
black red gold that's it yeah
something like that I I mean I I
recognize it when I see it but now like
suddenly if you ask me to describe it
then my mind will go blank and
but I I know what the German flag looks
like I know it
I know I don't know
but oh my god
do you ever watch uh Clips do we get
recommended clips and watch them
yes I saw this clip like yesterday that
I am so
talked about Mommy would you mind
telling me uh all the continents of the
world
oh
[Music]
Europe's not a continent can't you see
that one hey I can watch it I recommend
it to me yeah good almost like
accounting the countenance
thing here's the thing I kind of can see
where a girl's mind went why
as maybe she was thinking of
land masses that stand on their own more
in Europe and Asia
Eurasia I mean there there are some
countries that think uh like yeah it's
Eurasia and not Europe and Asia so some
countries really like teach it like that
and then say it like that but which one
for example but America doesn't do it
like that do they even America thinks of
the continents they think of Europe on
its own right
America we're taught there's seven
continents and yeah so it's North
America South America Europe Africa Asia
Australia and Antarctica okay okay okay
so that's not really an excuse that she
can use
I understand if it's like oh yeah she
learned it as Eurasian but I mean
apparently not
but here's here's the thing though like
it's actually kind of debated on so
consonants
um there's not like a hardcore
definition for it because some people
also see like determine consonants based
on like cultural differences but I also
checked like the tectonic plates that
they sit on but it's
I feel like there's not so much
leeway there
there's either the one with the with
Europe or there's the one with Eurasia
it's
I don't here's I
um I understand what did you learn in
school
I learned this oven in school okay
so with with Europe right with Europe
yeah okay there you go that's all we
need to know
but like
I was I'm just wondering
where if if we're not good I think I was
at I guess she she heard of Europe
before on its own but she didn't think
it was a what did she think it is then
oh there's another one there's another
one oh yeah maybe she thought of like EU
sort of thing maybe we're just like a
get-together of countries I guess and
yeah I mean yes like the European Union
yeah but yeah
maybe like a region sort of thing oh
wait we can get around maybe can we
[Music]
um
well she couldn't have found that Europe
was a country but then let's say she
thought okay Europe but the thing is
like she she counted uh all the
continents besides Europe I think she
said them all and then
she thinks like oh what's left but then
wouldn't she like think okay where is
koalas uh at like where what continent
would kiwawas Austria be part of and
then wouldn't that make you think like
wait a second there must be something
else there
maybe she's implying that you Europe
isn't real
that maybe it's all an elaborate scheme
to make you question where you where you
are it's just I think it it hits the
Europeans very hard in that moment
because it's just at the time where a
lot of Europeans including me are very
confused about why we're not shipping
merchandise to Europe and then glasses
I know it's that you know on purpose and
Elder it's just I'm sorry Europe I'm
sorry I'm one of you I can't even order
our own merchandise
I can order it I didn't realize they
weren't shipping to Europe yo that I
mean the at least the like I think maybe
it depends
um
like the our official shop ships I think
absolutely nothing to Europe geek check
does but the our official shop doesn't
ship anything to Europe I think
which is so sad not even to like the
bigger countries mean but that's not
it's not really I keep on saying that
please guys don't blame it on cover
because it's not necessarily a cover's
fault okay yeah if they yeah it might it
may have to do with the shipping company
yeah
nice nice Village it's just because
Europe's not real and why would they
ship to somewhere that's not real
yes pour more salt into the wounds
oh well it was funny
um this is Gouda has many Pawn moments
moments
she's just opening up the space for a
debate
to really die to really dive into what
is a consonant
continent what is a consonant what is a
continent
maybe exactly what Wikipedia says it is
but it could also not be
um
sorry I'm doing everything I can not to
Google
confidence so I bet even Wikipedia says
like there's some disagreement on what
defines one no no no no no there's no
there's no substance agreements only the
only thing that it says is that there
are some places that consider your Asia
as a continent
but what about Australia because
oh no Australia is a con okay we're
gonna I'm gonna look up stuff in a
second okay let's let's try to sound
smart let's try
like I guess there's Australia versus
Oceania or what yeah
hold on let me clarify before people go
it seems already too late
[Music]
yeah I think
I would probably and this is maybe a
moment where it gets embarrassing for me
but I would probably in German at least
call it
Australian
uh can we say in German do we say like
let's see onion
I think it's a term but I don't really
think
in German would you decide I would
probably just in English
oh I don't know
um yeah
[Music]
um
yeah we say in German we say Australian
so in English I just would probably
quickly think oh it's Australia
have things that confuse people there
where am I going where I wanted to do a
stream or like with maps like filling in
maps oh
filling the country names in a lot
countries or like states in the US too
but I tried that too I failed miserably
wait what did you use because I was
totally oh I just used the graphic of
Australian in paint I painted it in uh
America I mean America yeah America yeah
I actually just have to make my own
um oh
my map is Canon now I'm just gonna sleep
really quick oh hey okay
oh there we go
you can come back and now I guess we're
pretty close I think so we can walk now
mostly over the missile
okay
can I get the boat
yeah
and but I uh my I want to see your map
no no it was absolutely ridiculous I it
was no no I just guessed like and I have
no idea and I never claimed I would have
an idea yeah that's how even people in
the US like I think for most people it's
like you know the state like where you
live and then the ones around it maybe
hmm and for the most part like I don't
know California Florida
Texas is probably
people will recognize even outside
of the stage oh yeah Texas the shape is
really really easy to recognize the
shape yeah at least yeah that's the only
reason why I would know where it is not
because I know where it's like in the
map no just because I recognize the
shape like I don't think I can
even place all 50 I can I can name all
50 but I'd probably struggle will you
name me all 50 states remember let's see
if you're if you really okay
oh there's a song like the ABC song yeah
I want to hear it yes
Fifty Nifty United States round 13
Original
Colonies
something for every state in the USA
Alabama Alaska Arizona Arkansas
California Colorado Connecticut Delaware
Florida Georgia Hawaii Idaho Illinois
Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky Louisiana
Maryland Massachusetts Michigan
Montana Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire
New Jersey New Mexico New York North
Carolina North Dakota Ohio Oregon
um wait wait is there one between Ohio
and Oregon
oh oh Oklahoma
Oklahoma
Oregon Pennsylvania I don't remember the
melody
the Melody's throwing me off
Oklahoma Oregon Pennsylvania Rhode
Island South Carolina South Dakota
Tennessee Texas Utah Vermont Virginia
Washington West Virginia Wisconsin
oh that's so many that's crazy
a nice song I never heard of it before
ever
thank you yeah I heard it in like the
first grade just somehow remember okay
so could you say all the states without
singing the song
um in order
not an order no well I probably didn't
order because I'll probably forget
Alaska Arizona Arkansas is an
alphabetical order oh
Alabama Alaska Arizona Arkansas
California Colorado Connecticut Delaware
Florida Georgia Hawaii Idaho Illinois
Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky Louisiana
Maine Maryland Massachusetts Michigan
Minnesota Mississippi Missouri Montana
Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire new
New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico New
York North Carolina North Dakota Ohio
Oklahoma Oregon hence I lost you where'd
you go Oregon Pennsylvania
uh uh Rhode Island so no yeah South
Carolina South Dakota Tennessee Texas
Utah Vermont Virginia Washington West
Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming
Oh Come to
um uh uh I'm currently at uh x minus 15.
and then
10 900.
I'm over a river
oh you're over the river
um
[Music]
you have proved yourself to be
relatively knowledgeable
states can you name all the countries in
Europe
I was I I was scared that you might ask
that um
I don't think I can uh how many is there
I can try but I don't think I'll I'll
make it
[Laughter]
uh
just tell me there is 56
what really 56 dear Lord
um
56 44 eh 44 what can someone keep 45
yeah can someone make a list
okay what's 44 to 50. what stays like uh
we not an exact name 44 according to un
okay okay
um I will not get all of them I don't
think so
let me try Okay Austria
the moment you should be counting okay
counting oh but I want to try to
remember one thing okay okay okay okay
okay Austria also Germany
Spain Italy Hungary
uh switch no wait
wait I mean wait I was speaking of the
continent or of the uh of the Union
[Music]
yeah but
the outside Union
continent continent continent in the in
the content in the continent
yeah
no let's film a union let's do the Union
European Union okay otherwise I don't
know if I can do it
if I do if you do consonant then you'll
need more countries
no we'll do the Union
okay okay okay
um okay okay uh wait my my bird um wait
oh God I wanna I wanna count two though
wait bird uh mummy
here what do you want me to look there's
my
[\h__\h]
what if I just drop it like this
here
where are we going oh wait uh no not you
I'm still trying to get mummy in here
oh okay I was gonna write it all down
it's okay all right all right well
um uh all right okay I guess that's a
challenge for me
um
okay here we go I want to come too let
me let me use my fingers
I'm on my boat let me just really
quickly check the number for real
European Union number of countries 2020
27 only all right all right okay okay I
should be able to do this
otherwise I will be in shame
okay
20 20 what
27 okay 27. uh Austria one Germany to
Spain Italy Hungary
um France
um Finland uh
um uh Sweden uh Netherlands
Belgium crew wait that's that's ten
Croatia yeah 11. uh not Sweden short
Sweden of course Sweden Croatia Denmark
um
check
uh when people are saying no Sweden what
of course Sweden
wait now people are saying yes Sweden
yes of course Sweden
people Google stuff before you tell it
in chat
oh check uh that's 14.
um uh God oh God Bulgaria
[Music]
uh uh
in school
what of course of course wait uh I need
to see the map at least
I didn't say Italy yet Italy 15. I think
you did say Italy did I
yeah did I I think it was the fourth all
right let's start from the beginning
I did I didn't I did maybe I should
write it down I should write it down I'm
gonna I'll write it down for you you'll
write it down
okay oh God ah okay okay
um uh Austria Germany uh Hungary uh
Italy Spain France uh Netherlands
Belgium Denmark Finland
that's 10. Sweden
um
you missed one
okay Austria Germany Hungary Italy Spain
France Netherlands Belgium Denmark
what about least in uh
what's the what's the English name
Luxembourg
is awesome that's the capital no no wait
no wait oh there's uh Liechtenstein
what was that
listen English Liechtenstein oh
Lithuania
I'm looking at Chad they're saying
Lithuania oh wait this is on its own
this is not in the year that could be
true that yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's right that's why I heard
that okay never mind that
um uh Portugal
God I stopped counting I think that's
now
12.3 four five six seven eight nine ten
okay
Portugal
I don't know
you don't have a map too
what what has a map it's hard to do and
you don't have a map yeah poor Portugal
um did I say Croatia yet oh [\h__\h] yeah
I don't know this is too difficult to
say without knowing what because I guess
for you you can go alphabetically but
I'm not even I'm not even doing an
alphabetically no okay don't go
alphabetically then you're gonna lose it
because I'll be like wait did I say this
state 40 40 States ago no Switz guys you
keep on saying Switzerland Switzerland
is not in because Switzerland is in the
European continent but not in the
European Union
uh just straight pretty much
I'll go back I'll go back later straight
increase yeah I was gonna say Greece I
was gonna say Greece I think I see you
okay
I was gonna say grace of course I was
gonna say grace
I think we're gonna do it with a map
guys with them just so I can know which
ones I said and which ones I didn't
let's do it with a map eventually okay
uh let me focus on where we're going oh
my god
um 270 2070 let's let's get to the
270 oh no do we have to get off the boat
I got I got away
okay we gotta go online again you know
the Animaniacs song that where like they
really quickly say all the countries
I don't have that of the world of the
world yeah
oh my boat
is lost in the water we can't we can't
go by boat
okay got it it's so hard to see with my
Shader
wait I don't know that song
oh it's older I wasn't even done though
guys I could probably name a couple more
oh
I could probably name a couple more I'm
just ah who's shooting you
shoot them back yo my lady oh you got it
you got it I got it I got it should we
sleep we should sleep
I leave
[Music]
come back
that Melody sounds a little bit familiar
just a little bit maybe it's a common
name
[Music]
oh God oh God and lots of spiders
can I shoot it
yes I lost you don't then don't shoot it
just run oh God uh I don't have any more
arrows yeah the creeper is a problem
I killed the creeper no
[Music]
no there's two
um I just run away from it Mama you will
have to um find me oh I'm going to kill
it okay oh I don't see it run away I see
it you wait run away from it run away
a creeper hit with probably one hit my
Ally
yes don't want that
yeah wait wait we're almost there mommy
and mommy we're almost there
sorry for dragging you through this at
least I will make you I won't make you
get it with me to all the way back and
just just uh my mess up base is fine
and then before the weather collab I'll
get myself back to the base I'll just
actually I guess I can just like lock it
into my Mesa base for now and then we'll
go back together like normally
oh no although starting from there it
shouldn't even be much of an issue to
get it back anymore
um
[Music]
yeah this one this one that sounds
familiar no no no no this thing is way
easier to get back I think than I don't
know other things because it follows me
so so well
[Music]
there that will be clipped all of that I
think there will be clips of that yes it
will be very embarrassing
well well the Clippers just look silly
it looks silly you guys on my back right
you'll come and say actually
you have to type it like actually
well actually
it sounds okay meant to say that
Australia isn't real actually we may
meant to say that Australia is
[Music]
um
is spreading propaganda that continents
don't exist at all yeah actually
according to umumi the guardian of
civilization continents it's just a
concept yeah they're con they're well
well they're just
yo we reached it for me we're back
[Music]
do I have a leash here no
okay I need to get this thing in here
um
a rock
come here
and if I log out and then I log back in
does it still remember me as its owner
so leave it on a boat oh I guess I could
do that too
prison
it's over there
it's on other side oh hi I was trying to
get into the house you're almost there
there it is
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
nice
I'm so happy accomplished thank you so
much for helping no craft did I help
I was helpful in Minecraft 100
couldn't ask for a better helper yeah
[Music]
thank you so much I think I will leave
it here because it's like half past
midnight so I better go I am starving
I'm going to go eat food you go eat food
I go cook food
good luck yeah I'm so glad I ordered
food yesterday oh jealous
okay see you at the Widow fight mommy
yes I'm going to be ready I'm not ready
right now but I will be ready I think
today was kind of a warm up for you too
at least
yeah
yeah we had some combat no yeah you know
uh improved my aim here yes aim will be
very important uh did you give me uh can
I get like my my bowl back yeah do I
have something from you
probably not do you want your boots oh
no wait I'll leave those in the yeah you
need them to stay safe okay do you want
this ominous Banner
um no
okay I'll keep it throw it away
I don't need that
all right
okay I go eat now bye bye Mommy
thank you I'm just saying goodbye to my
tread as well oh that one too I see
bye bye bye
guys
I did not expect to be accompanied for
the whole stream but tomorrow we can
talk a lot okay
I actually didn't think I would do so
many long things
I thought I would have time for reading
super chats
um
sorry sorry sorry guys I need really to
go now to cook but I had to accomplish
this thing I had to finish what I
started so
um tomorrow we're playing passport 2
right
at uh I think an hour or two later than
today
let her cook let me cook
yeah at least we have lots of rare
interactions I don't I don't uh you know
in in Minecraft I used to always be
lonely this was so weird for me
people telling me they wanna hang with
me and stuff like that actually like is
there no one else streaming Minecraft
right now because originally I saw
someone putting Minecraft in their
schedule
and I thought maybe that person would
join us but I guess that person changed
their mind or so
um
but good I did mention that she might
um join me she didn't and that's totally
fine must have had something else to do
that's totally fine I had movement so
I'm I'm more than happy
um
um yeah but but good I had the interest
in it and and that already counts like
so much for me I saw when she talked
about it when she said quinoa you know
with a blush on her face she said I
haven't talked to chihuahua in a long
time a voice
we do write
um
still after the whole Japan trip even
after that we still write uh quite a bit
way more than before that's for sure
just not really many opportunities to
get into voice chat you know no but like
I I check up on her
I sent her just like yesterday I sent
her the aikodoba video because I was
listening to it randomly and I was like
oh damn this is so nostalgic and as I
was looking at the lyrics
and like oh this is this is really
fitting for us isn't it and I send it to
her I'm like isn't this so nostalgic and
then she was like yeah it reminds me of
us going to karaoke and want to go again
and she's like yeah let's go again
I say let's go again she says yeah let's
go
because she she missed that too
um
yeah
let's go again
yeah we got we got definitely so much
closer and don't worry just because
we're not like collabing every week or
so or not doing anything that's visible
to the outside doesn't mean that that
has changed or so it's like I have this
I have this
I think many people have this
um way with friendships that even when
you don't communicate
um
like every day
or even every week
then you're still friends you're still
like it doesn't change it your
friendship status at all you don't feel
less connected them to to them or so at
all
[Music]
um
yeah yeah and I I have that with all my
friends like you know
sometimes sometimes when I make a new
friend
and they're not used to that and they
kind of have a different way with
dealing with friendships
I had that before
um recently
they expect
so many more interactions
and I'm like oh I don't know if I can
like give that to you though I don't
know
but like apparently
apparently what I heard from this person
when I met her again and talked all
about it with her
apparently an acquaintance of mine
who does indeed follow me on social
media and all that we just never talk
because we don't really have
I wouldn't call this friendship we don't
really have a connection at all but this
acquaintance
did like
like kind of [\h__\h] talk me to this like
Loki friend like
they talked about me like oh she doesn't
she doesn't reply and all that you don't
need a friend like her she said to my uh
like Loki friend that she doesn't need a
friend like me because I don't you know
interact and all that that makes me a
bad friend and all that so don't and I
in general I kind of get it but my Loki
friend at the time
um I think she didn't know yet
I think
what my current occupation is and that
that is what makes me so busy and
eventually she found out and then she
was like oh I get it now I understand
now and now she she's okay with it but
damn I was like shook it to hear that
I'm being [\h__\h] talked by people I don't
really even know but I guess okay wait
that's interesting this is this is like
I get [\h__\h] okay we all get [\h__\h] talked
we're like you know well known so we get
[\h__\h] talked everywhere on the internet
all the time but that's why people who
don't know me at all
um which is also makes no sense but okay
this person like is an acquaintance okay
it's a friend of friends and so on and
how dare you how dare you what do you
know you know nothing I I have plenty of
friendships who are plenty happy with
the way I deal with my friendships and
they're also the same though it's not
like they try to spam me with messages
every day either no we're just living
our life
and living our friend to them and I I
feel I do feel a little bit bad
sometimes that I don't you know
interact more with them have more time
for them and all that but but but but
especially my BFF she's very busy so she
gets it too this is just how
how we are and all that and we're
totally fine with it and and there's
there's no need for others to judge that
and be like you're both bad friends
because you're bad at having friendships
no this is what we call friendship and
we have friendship feelings about each
other so that is enough for us that is
not we don't need anything else yeah
that's how adult life is exactly
like Ugh
man
I just felt like I felt kind of insulted
to be judged from afar
um
have have myself be [\h__\h] talked to
another friend
what what do you know
um
[Music]
yeah it feels like High School drama
um
and all that while still following me on
following me on social media
[Music]
huh what
yeah it's so uncalled uncalled for hmm
[Music]
yeah I mean whatever I think me and
Dad's Loki friend after you know talking
all about it where she she gets it now
and she's not angry or so and you know
we're fine I'm fine
did you ghost or something no like we're
not even like in that kind of
like relationship like I don't
Maybe
maybe senior IRL a few times but I don't
know she's more like a friend of a
friend so I know her through that
you know
and I guess we see each other's social
media posts but at least I realize yeah
yeah not the [\h__\h] talker but the the one
who you know
has been
you know fed that information or that
advice
yeah it's just it's just I mean it makes
me feel kind of bad and I I wanna do
better but
it's not like I give anyone special
treatment I basically everybody gets
this treatment for me my family too so
uh
if you want to be friends with me you
gotta you know deal with that you're
gonna accept that I I don't see you any
uh I don't see you as like
any less of a friend just because I
don't like write to you daily
I still see you very much as a friend
what I what makes me see you of less as
a friend if you stress me out about this
kind of stuff when you know that I am
very busy and stressed out
you know that's why I'm like okay then I
don't need that friendship because
you're not understanding of my situation
yeah
yeah I need friends who understand my
situation and who are reasonable and
accepting yeah and don't Guilt Trip me
yeah don't pressure me and so on don't
guilt-trip me um
yeah and my current like my close friend
circle is very good at that we all I
think they're also mostly like that at
least
at least like yeah
towards each other
who's who's with me who's like me and
those terms
I feel like a lot of you guys said me
too
there you go see so many I mean no
judgment if you for a proper friendship
if you need like a lot of
like uh no
signs and the conversations and all that
then that's that's what you need and
that's totally cool that's fine that's
fine it's totally fun I just
I just can't give that you know
[Music]
um
at least not
currently when I'm so focused on my job
oh yeah high maintenance I am very a
very low maintenance friend
um
I hang out with my friends at least once
a week damn
that's good I mean that's not even that
much
it's good if you're like able to do that
would be nice if I could do that at
least like twice a week but me and my
friends we meet
like in a group maybe once in two or
three months
one-on-one with like hand-picked some of
them one one maybe once a month
which is really low like sometimes I
mean day they probably they meet more
often without me I think on their own
they just know that I'm extra busy so
you know
sometimes I do feel like I need
I probably should
meet them more and get more social
interactions because I am drowning
myself here in my apartment basically
in
I mean I don't feel lonely but
maybe subconsciously I am maybe oh no
um
so I probably should meet a bit more but
I don't want to see them like every day
[Music]
remember me with text we text a bit more
than we actually meet and yeah that's
fine
just introvert things yeah that's really
another reason why I don't understand
why people think I'm an extrovert I
don't
I don't want to go out and talk so much
I don't like that at all and
the Japan trip was like draining me so
much trying to get so many off collabs
and meetups to happen because I needed
to make use of the chance the time that
I had there but then at the same time
well I was training my energy and my
batteries so much
yeah I tried my best
I'm sociable not extroverted
huh
I'm just I'm just I just know how to
make a a conversation or interactions
and and meetups
um comfortable and like you know so that
somebody would feel like
good about it I know how to make someone
feel good about being around me I guess
yeah I have good social skills
um
unless you put me into into a club
with people drinking alcohol in that or
bar no no that's that's where my social
skills immediately disappear poof Into
Thin Air
as long as it's not that I can deal with
pretty much any situation hmm
[Music]
anyway why am I tangenting I really
should go I just wanted to give you guys
attention before I go
yeah the setting matters very much
because that's like the most
uncomfortable you could possibly make me
probably
now
that's the only place where you have so
really
seafoam boy
is it because of the alcohol that helps
you I guess for a lot of people the
alcohol really helps huh
like loosen up and then don't think
about [\h__\h]
um
seafoam boy a clubber
oh a social drinker
what did you say social lubricant what a
weird way to describe alcohol a social
lubricant
what
I also enjoy existing at bars that's
good for you man I don't know how to
enjoy bars I feel so awkward
blah
need something like a nerd bar but even
there
then I feel awkward to
oh well in the end I guess I'll just
stay home
okay I'll go cook now guys I hope I have
something simple and quick to whip up
um
[Music]
I ate my frozen pizza yesterday because
I made all my hello fresh dishes but I
didn't even eat the whole pizza because
again this new tuna pizza recipe from
the pizza that I always go to the frozen
pizza they've changed and so bad and I
thought I'd give it another chance but
no it was pretty bad again and I was so
disappointed I only ate a couple slices
and
why did they change all the recipes it
was so stupid everybody's criticizing it
why don't you change it back I'm going
on another tangent but I should stop
no no I like you know there's a
difference like frozen pizza is its own
category I see it differently from like
good Italian pizza so sometimes I want
good Italian pizza like fresh ones and
sometimes I just have a cravings for the
the cheap uh frozen pizza but they
changed it up so much no it sucks
so anyway I'm gonna go
bye bye guys thank you so much for
watching and thanks to ollie and
Moonlight I gotta put them on the
thumbnail man
I was never alone today never
so happy bye bye guys
tomorrow pause for two
children fine fine secret magic burp
keep your tangents no find magic burp
keep your secrets no tangents
oh God my face is exhausted bye-bye from
smiling so much man
okay bye-bye and keep on saying that
Alfie does the endangerment
[Music]
bye-bye have fun today yay
while we're not alone for once ah it
feels so magical I feel so magical to
not be alone wow I didn't know this is
how it feels
well I'm so amazed oh my god wow
[Music]
foreign
European member
man I would die for that I would die for
that
please
[Music]
give me a European member please
I need one
[Music]
there can only be one no don't say that
oh
can I just say it because I saw some
rumors uh yesterday
[Music]
please do not get your hopes up I will
not be um invited to Japan Expo okay
just
reconfirming that with you guys
unfortunately
[Music]
it's all about the budget guys
thank you
cries and chickens
didn't even know what that was uh
biggest European anime convention or
like Japan anime convention
[Music]
oh
I'm not sure about stream but I don't
know
um
yeah it seems like it has been like
low-key announced the World of Warships
one mm-hmm
collab coming anyway I should go bye-bye