[Music]
foreign
wow
wait
hello hello
[Music]
hello
yo yo yo when I wanna introduce first
yes
okay let's go let's go
[Music]
oh you got it hi more is here
I'm excited
oh sorry it's okay no problem
no problem more is here hi Jessica
happy death Grim Reaper I'm here I need
to do my best for my team ID sports
festival let's go let's go
yeah dude I don't know it's been a long
day oh Ralph
[Music]
Ralphie not Lo-Fi but you can call me
your p r e l c but it's not love I am
sure I mean like um FYI I'm I think
probably I'm not the only uh I'm the
only one who doesn't open stream so
you're free to watch from whichever okay
[Music]
hi hello everyone my name is
wait um
okay um I'm the black sheep from whole
life ID three generations
about your introduction no I've never
done any introduction in my own stream
yeah
[Music]
again
oh okay
Indonesia generation one I am
part two in these guys I'm actually NPC
right now
I can see your forehead yes
be careful with my forehead
slime
I have I have been chosen as the produce
team leader
leader leader
a good good day good morning good
evening everybody I am participating in
the soccer match and also in the
badminton with a teaming up with Kaela
[Music]
is
my name is
[Music]
good English
[Applause]
okay so before we start I actually have
a little bit of uh
yes before we start so
um
will not be here but but they are a
really diligent member so they already
practiced
um in the afternoon although there is no
stream yay also later on at uh one hour
from now uh hopefully sooner Senpai will
be able to join
[Music]
yay
what uh I think Mona here tonight will
help us as the mod for uh several uh
some games nice PC okay
and also
[Music]
so I will also explain about the game
first uh for each game okay but maybe it
will be better if we go about the
teaming
we have
um nine members including me and then
there will be iyophy
Kiara Cali and fona yeah
[Music]
we are strong all of you are great
thank you you're great
yeah
Pink Ladies
I think
there will be one two three four five
games five games
the first going to be a a catch the four
third floor capture the four thank you
uh and from our team it's going to be uh
Kyla me uh yeah
and what's it called again
two more people to kind of like join
um
because they aren't here
try it before you can just join in okay
thank you
[Music]
and then there will be potato sack race
so basically it's a race
uh basically you insert like like you
you go inside of the potato sack and
then you jump
so basically it's not it's not the the
normal race it's like a race while
jumping you have to jump okay yes and
yeah whoever uh complete the three laps
uh within their member
first is the winner okay okay
the team will be me
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
you're playing against the blue the big
the big blue yes so basically it's the
pink team against the blue team
[Music]
because it's going to be me coyote and
Cali okay
[Applause]
[Music]
pressure right now
and then there will be badminton so
badminton will be like we'll have two
rounds basically A and B
so in badminton a there will be Kyla and
Kiana yay
and in badminton Bay there will be eofi
and Sona senpai
[Music]
and then last there will be soccer yeah
oh yeah soccer is really fun
[Music]
yeah you're saying soccer and not
football
[Laughter]
no we were playing football okay
so
basically uh uh uh initially it will be
me but it's going to be changed yeah so
the team for soccer will be elfi Kaira
Cali coyote
and before before we start playing I
would like for everyone to go here
cute
that's amazing
wow
so amazing
I would like to teach you
the calling response of fertility okay
ready ready cap let's see if this is it
I'm looking at the let me look at those
grapes
I will I will read everything first from
the from the top to bottom okay and then
we'll practice after that okay okay okay
okay so I will I will give example first
um
foreign
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
we got it so no no problem what does it
mean oh okay okay so basically uh that
one
is like the the best sometimes
whatever okay like the strongest team
ever okay
is like uh whose team yeah
foreign
and it's like yeah
let's go
again
I'm ready I'm ready
probably uh I wouldn't say it's probably
like most likely
um the MC will tell us to do that before
the game starts later
so yeah if you'd love to practice I
already
put the
the example the audio example we got
there so feel free
you guys can listen to me right
kind of
you're kind of gone
really
they cannot even um
foreign
so uh which game do you want to try
first
soccer
I'm ready for football let's go Kyla
you're good yeah let's go let's go
soccer
[Music]
not you
why so yeah
[Music]
oh my God
interact so yeah you are not
participating in the next games
should we should we
um split how many people are here how
many people here I mean this is
three and three see
[Music]
all right
okay
what should I do as a roll what who is
white you can win for white okay so you
want to be a keeper or stalker
I feel like we should practice what we
will really be in the end okay so
basically who wants to be a keeper
because keeper is the only one position
Minecraft
okay
okay I'm just oh bro okay I'm just gonna
be standard too wait
okay I'm just gonna be I'm just gonna be
cold keeper six minutes please
already already
six minutes
right now one team Striker I have to
explain something first okay so
so there is uh like three items uh if
you are on basic there is like two shoes
green and yellow and if you're the
goalkeeper you will holding this
yay yeah I know this one yeah yeah
so okay uh for the goalkeeper
um if you want to get the balls you have
to click it so it's gonna be on hold
and uh for the
basic one uh there's like two a green
and yellow the green is like a regular
cake and the yellow is the long cake
um and there is uh if you are on the uh
some special occasion that you have to
kick to the goal what is the name
I forgot the name
it was like a final decisions kind of
thing so make sure 11 meter shooting gun
the eliminations the elimination the
final elimination
yes
there is there is like uh
you cannot use this one you cannot use
the yellow so you have to use the
regular the green one the penalty you
mean where you stand in the corner and
then shoot or no no no not in the corner
and the center in front of the goal in
the center okay ah where they line up so
it is 11. yeah okay yeah they line up
and they try to get a goal until yeah
they can okay okay
okay
oh that's all uh have fun okay
[Music]
okay
yes okay
at least I can't be out of breath here
in this game
[Music]
thank you
that was a good kick
yay no no no no
no no no no no no no no yeah
[Laughter]
try throw
ing up
I think we're allowed though I don't
know because I don't know
as close as possible
don't worry
[Music]
do you even think about it
no don't go crazy
let's go let's go he's there let's go
yay
yeah if you were holding it it's gonna
be like that oh
yes
and why do you keep there no sorry oh my
God
nice fry nice try ladies okay okay white
team let's go
you must
listen
[Music]
I will I will
um
wow a long kick
yes
my new Talent yes
here is very good
like the pressure
okay
no no no no look at the ball I think
[Laughter]
yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
foreign
ah
okay let's go okay
[Music]
I don't think we can pass again
oh it doesn't look like it oh you want
to pause the game yeah
King a bit or like a few seconds yeah I
don't know yeah I don't know
apparently additional Pals in the game
I think
is still opening the door right now so
she yes
[Music]
that's it
finished
and this one this game is only six
minutes as requested by risu
regular game will be on 20 minutes
[Applause]
done in Pokemon unite I'm I'm excited
what are you talking about
remember
are we gonna practice this again or
moving to the another do you want to try
this again
be prepared
[Music]
foreign
okay
come on I'm gone I've just fell through
the world oh no
yes
you switch because it was switched to
elfi so that she's controlling the girl
and then switches back
[Music]
like that
let's go okay all right good good good
all right I'll do this
[Music]
and I'm gone
oh yes oh me again oh my God
okay
spectator mode
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
it's gold
here we go let's go The Spectator
[Music]
that's very good it's hard to be close I
used to have to be up closer to it say
it I can see it
ready yes
oh
my God
grab it
[Music]
oh my good night oh my goodness
I'm gonna hold it
let's go bring it easy
come on
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
nine nine I don't think I should be the
goalie
I think wait is is eofi
um in the soccer are you in the soccer
game yeah I'm in a soccer game you
should be the goalie I don't wanna
oh okay yeah that's the only way I can
we can win all of us okay okay
[Music]
once more yes yeah I'll always try for
this time next one okay
I think I'd get a white again okay
wanna try and
okay I'm gonna be Striker you'll be
strike keeper
I'm the best soccer player in all of us
because we suck in Austria we never make
it to championships or anything
okay okay okay okay okay
go the keeper
please please goalkeeper on red yellow
oh okay should I go okay okay sure
okay I think I I think I pick it already
I cannot change it
oh can I wait wait wait wait you can
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay okay let's go
alone I'm gonna make sure again
oh yeah
yes well no time wasted
okay okay
let's go
Holly let's go
[Music]
are you going
there I was going there
[Music]
nice nice nice nice wow
that's cute
yeah leave it to me yeah okay
please
[Music]
okay
okay no
[Music]
no no no
no
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
Kyla is so strong
okay what no
try
okay
[Music]
no no no no no no no no
[Applause]
[Music]
the song
Mitsubishi let's go let's go
come on come on let's go
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
okay y'all are aggressive
we are gonna be gotta be aggressive
[Music]
nice wow
okay okay
okay okay okay here we go
oh my God
[Music]
okay also it's a cracked goalkeeper no
it's just beautiful
okay we're good we're good I'll see you
too
we're good now continue yes continue yes
you must
continue
starting all right now
yes
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's freaking go wow
you guys are getting stronger oh yeah
practice practice
[Music]
uh
everybody
rigged
absolutely right no no
yeah
nice one Kyla hey
oh God oh my God everyone is getting
stronger and stronger okay okay
oh it's over there I see gotcha all
right all right let's party let's go
[Music]
let's go cycle
oh wait where is it
yeah I wasn't prepared
[Music]
Get Ready Get Ready Get ready ready
no no no no no no
no no no no no
my advice
come on
yeah
[Applause]
yeah I touched
[Music]
yeah
this game good game
and so you want to go back go just
slowly okay
what is the next one
I am with Kyla and then uh yuffie
okay but if you want to try it's okay
though
[Music]
thank you
we can take turn what color are we gonna
break let's go red red okay
okay I'll do white
okay
can you guys give me a left-handed uh
bad place
okay everyone's good everyone's good um
okay everyone's good okay for the
badminton one I think it's gonna be
easier if you press F5
yay
okay ready ready
let's go NPC let's go
okay uh just make sure that uh when you
want to kick the is it
through the ball through the ball uh
make sure you don't go uh don't look up
because when you look up it's gonna be
sword sword oh
yeah it's gonna be short it's it's gonna
stuck in your place it's not gonna be on
your opponent please okay it's almost
more straight
yeah it just looks strange focus on the
streets
[Music]
foreign
you know
how do I know
yeah
good day
[Music]
no uh I see I see aim for the red
oh I can fly oh my god let's go
[Applause]
if you're not playing the game you can
fly don't worry about that
okay oh no oh because you look too far
up oh I see
tournament
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
wow you guys are strong
[Music]
I think I can trust my teeth you guys
are really strong on every game I'm
sorry this is difficult it's fine it's
fine we can practice more later it's
fine okay yeah nice nice
okay
this third person is better Chad they
said first person's better because you
see the shadow
really I didn't know that she said So
Right girls you said F5 for third person
is better
it depends on your preference no no okay
I'll try this one um okay I'm trying F5
okay okay
a good day
[Music]
one more yeah yeah another time we
really need to go back to someone else
want to try no you guys can try it it's
fine I need to stay in um
[Music]
yeah
we need white one more
white one who is it oh white white
okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
yes party man
okay okay let's go
[Music]
company
let's go let's go oh let's go let's go
okay okay
right right oh yeah
what oh okay what okay they kill you
okay
nice
come on nice
[Music]
one Kayla nice one nice one is the
tournament it's on Sunday
right we spent Sunday for me
good morning
[Music]
Saturday for n a okay
okay you're on the left yes got it I'll
be honestly nice one it's nice nice
nice
oh
shoot yay oh he hit the ball out yeah
okay let's go
oh nice nice way oh
okay out no no no no
okay let's go I think it's out right
it's great yeah just let it hit the
ground yeah
yeah um if they're shooting over to your
side for the first shot you should just
let it fall down to the ground if
they're gonna if they're not gonna hit
the red what's here
yeah very cool okay
let's go
what
no it did it pretty far yeah I felt like
it yeah
where is it where is it okay okay
but I don't see the shadow but at least
I see the ball
okay nice
let's go hit it hit it
nice on you
on the ground for a second it's still
sorry I'll get back to my side
[Applause]
okay
okay because it looked like it was
already on the ground it was it is
kidding I'll be left it's fine it's fine
just follow whatever yeah just follow
the band
no okay
you guys
bring it on on let's go let's go party
oh my god oh no wow you guys are strong
is it out
yay
nice
you guys win yeah
we have good badminton players
[Music]
okay which game grenade
Grace
[Music]
okay
this is our is our potato sack Team all
here oh no I guess not no it's not
Senpai and fauna okay
[Music]
isn't it now midnight
already practiced the other day so it's
probably yeah okay
so everyone can try oh
we can all try this one it's okay sure
yeah
three and three
yes because it's like three versus three
I'll join white the white okay I mean
two versus two is it good though why I
guess
[Music]
one time just one time okay
it will be over before before you before
you realize
[Music]
it's so cute
berries faster than those
oh no there's lava thank God I'm not
participating in this I'm never good in
these races I think
yeah there's no way that I would be good
at this
[Applause]
[Music]
very wait what
are you are you going the wrong way
Kelly yeah
I went the wrong way
[Music]
you'll be already in her second round
now I know I'm not
no I'm not because you passed me already
but that was okay because you were slow
[Music]
honey what's the best route
slimy yeah so try it the best fruit
[Music]
s
to go so fast
okay
[Music]
oh my God okay the bounciness I can see
how yofi gets sick from this yeah yeah
emotions thickness
oh [\h__\h]
okay I'm gonna get sick from this too
being stuck in the bedroom
you get through the berry bushes there's
like no path through them
oh no I'm glad I'm not doing it again
[Music]
you can get through the cobwebs that's
about it
Queen
just kidding I lied I'm not in sync with
my potato sack
s
[Music]
you can you can actually just just stand
there waiting for the other team to
finish it
flying
I don't know I'm done if everyone is
already gave up just tell me I can just
stop the game yes
okay
okay okay
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
but I have to say it's a very cute
original way to replace a normal
Marathon relay yeah
[Music]
let's go let's go
okay okay I need to practice this one
for sure
what's that
oh
hey
okay
okay okay
you should be in one team and we'll be
in the opposite
[Music]
white yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
she stays up late
thank you
thank you okay
who wants to join my team
[Music]
hello yeah we need one more uh
um
tell you okay
[Music]
okay he just said she's bad at it
good morning
ready I'm ready ready okay I'm ready
find out your finger Queen
uh you spam right quick
the lever
whatever
right right right right right I can do
anything for me
oh this one
oh my God
[Music]
it run okay Speed Run nice nice uh
basically you need to like spam clay
with a right click okay
you haven't joined yet hold on I'm going
down
okay I'm going down
leave it to me
let's go okay macaroni
the whole architecture is insane I know
who built this okay
magic magic
[Music]
on my fingers
yeah
nine two
again again again again again again
[Applause]
we have to win let's go let's go
[Music]
practice practice
we have to win
also tips from me you can actually pick
uh the furthest lever so you don't
really need to like stay on the front
lever okay
so you don't fall off so early I guess
okay okay
[Music]
if you want to focus more we can like uh
divide on different level left or right
yeah
okay and everyone needs a different
lever right yeah it is yeah
the most part is
foreign
[Music]
buttons
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay well you know what happened okay
what actually I started doing better
when I changed fingers when I changed
fingers
actually
my fingers
oh man
this time I'm gonna try okay with the
other finger oh you guys never give up
practice till you make it okay nice yeah
basically and you can actually lose this
first with your
um pointy finger yeah yeah that's what
I'm gonna do with the finger you'll be
with your finger yeah I switched Midway
through so that the other one gets a
break but team the current team red
lineup is our homeban lineup our real
lineup so you girls gotta win against
team white go go go go
[Music]
okay I'm ready
everyone ready
I use my middle finger man it's good
yeah best finger Ichiban skin
[Music]
seriously
Beauty UV
that's freaking out
[Music]
because also you can you can press shift
so you can you you barely move I think
oh that would be nice
hold on hold on hold on uh I messed up
I'm still moving I'm still moving even
holding shift yeah me too yeah it is
kind of but smart life
you keep on moving forward like while
you're hitting them um I see what's in
small steps ah wait hold on because I uh
because I hit shift it messed me up
it's okay it's okay we can try again
after it is no worries it's okay fine
[Music]
even more stats like who uh who did the
most pulls each member I want to see
exactly one one versus one
if we were using a game controller it
would be a different situation
so you know on the button matching Queen
click to like space bar
I don't I mean you can do it right
okay yeah I mean you can do it if you
want okay okay yeah yeah
okay let's just try without Kyla okay
okay
two versus two okay oh okay one more all
right let's try
foreign
[Music]
okay
you don't have in heaven
kidding me by herself I'm gonna stop it
I don't know please pick the start
wow
awesome
red
okay
I mean if you want to one versus one
it's okay though if you want I'm gonna
try white team okay
so white and Chihuahua white okay
[Music]
let's go okay that's good that's good
let's do it okay
um
[Music]
she's so true
oh yeah yeah we're gonna be against
Cowboy imagine that and then you'll be
so much stronger okay
[Music]
right you're still right
the Box
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h] it's so close
[Music]
finger finger
the problem is
the numbers then it takes so much longer
and now ubis have to hold out longer
[Music]
as long as you need me to
strange
I may not be as fast as quicker but I
have stamina
hahaha
um
[Music]
oh my God it's so close
kind of lose it
[Laughter]
[Music]
my finger
white team leading
what happened with red team tired
already
but but we're still leaning okay okay
[Music]
videos
[Applause]
I don't know man my finger's giving out
one minute one minute
[Music]
hahaha
oh my God
one minute left one minute let's go
finger endurance
already
30 seconds
30 seconds I mean if Greece is doing
well is the Sprint's still a good thing
for us is it not no I don't know
okay okay
15 seconds
yeah I don't know about this
let me try it really hard
five four three two one
foreign
[Music]
I'm never doing this again
no problems already
yeah seems like we played them all looks
like it we did it one left one left one
guess oh one game left the library
yeah can I take a break
yeah
let's see I think Moe is actually gonna
have to leave now I gotta go to bed but
that was really fun maybe good luck to
you guys thank you thank you
well fight I will rest my fingers at the
time yes thank you
[Music]
maybe maybe while we're taking break we
can try to the the yellow elephant face
here sorry Senpai is here yeah
[Music]
foreign
okay
let's download okay okay
foreign
[Music]
take your knee
HP simple kids
[Music]
oh okay
um
okay okay
[Music]
oh okay
um so
this
[Music]
Metallica
on the day we're actually gonna play
please
and also there is another thing as you
can see
yeah
okay okay
[Applause]
hands up here I want to tell you guys
that be careful uh if you're on your
opinion land so as you can see this is
the center of the place
one that I am sitting right now is the
center place and this is the red uh the
Red Land and this is the white land if
you're white and you're going to Red be
careful uh if you meet your opponent
because you if they get you you will go
into jail immediately okay
and it's also vice versa with the others
but your friend can help you to get out
of the jail
okay please explain it in Japanese okay
okay
[Music]
um
yeah
okay okay
let's go
okay
[Music]
um
Canada
oh
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
thank you
[Music]
come on
here
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
awesome
[Music]
foreign
be careful of motion sick be careful you
can try once I didn't really mentally
listen to the instructions though it's
okay
just run yeah it's a team so if you pick
white you see that uh White laser like
to up to the sky yeah yeah you need to
go to the red one
okay okay yeah
if you are red you need to go try just
try to find a way
um okay to the white and then if you see
your opponent just punch
okay easy easy
um easy very easy
yeah all right I'm back in okay
[Music]
who wants to go with red
lettuce
yes you you practice oh okay I practice
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
let's go let's go okay
[Music]
let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
should we go together
it's up to you
it's up to you yeah it's up okay
separate is better because we have
higher chances
hi
[Music]
do we have HP
yeah we have the the in the middle one
the red red bars above your items
oh
okay
can't you like remember yeah if you if
you really if you if you can if you want
to remember you can do it I mean I'm not
in this but can the people who are
actually participating remember yeah
maybe yeah maybe maybe maybe maybe
you just gotta remember the pattern and
you win yeah but but but there are mobs
right there are mobs that gonna disturb
you ran all past all of them they didn't
hit me once yeah you can do that you can
do it yeah
[Laughter]
foreign
maybe you can bamboo them and just
change before the real match just change
put one door somewhere
oh
Hi how are you going okay
okay okay okay
we're gonna see we'll see we'll see okay
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Pikachu
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay
okay
yes
um
[Music]
you're okay you're good yeah should we
practice the badminton again yeah like
because we are here right yeah
so you guys
[Music]
okay we're gonna go to bathroom let's go
um
okay so three versus three
not two words only can play by two yeah
who wants to play
you play
I mean if you want to play treats it's
fine to eat scan okay yeah Kyla Kyla
um
since uh you guys will no longer need to
practice Ben 10 and soccer then I think
uh you can actually lead this uh start
game and the stop game okay
okay okay thank you so much thank you
thank you
okay let's go
okay
all right
let's go let's go let's go oh
[Music]
Focus concentration okay
should I stay more in the front
yeah yeah okay
okay
[Music]
let's go let's go they don't expect us
what kind of car sure
okay I didn't think about that one all
right that was good
[Music]
oh thanks
toy
[Laughter]
too much power
laying too much power
everyone
[Applause]
Queen
Auto
[Music]
wow
okay let's go let's go
[Music]
hell yeah
yeah go let's go
okay I like badminton but it's easier to
uh in Minecraft
you be sweating potential
wow okay okay
[Music]
oh
protect the front yeah
so far
[Music]
it's okay
oh my God
we need to run faster okay yeah all
right it's out I think it's out yeah
it's out
foreign
[Music]
nice it was fun that's fun wanna
practice again oh yeah of course that
was already good much better you're good
yes
[Music]
Kyla I'm up for more practice yeah okay
okay we can one versus one yeah we can
one versus one yeah
thank you
[Music]
talk to me
oh yeah
guys
[Music]
listen please
all right
makes the Minecraft screen really really
short for the potato sack game because
it normally you feel sick for these kind
of games
and it helps it's actually really smart
life
[Music]
where should we go
training
training okay yeah okay I am Chihuahua
gonna go training
okay
hi
hello are you ready
oh yeah I guess so you appreciate me
hold on hold on I'm setting up the PNG
but either way even like
they have on the team so if you were
good yeah yeah yeah so I'm good and you
lose both ways it's fine yeah we just
need to practice the hitbox I think it's
gonna be fine yeah
let's go are you ready yeah do you wanna
for the actual real game also be mostly
in the back and I'll stay in the front
yeah sure sure okay good okay okay
all right okay
but practice
like this is kind of hard because the
field is like kind of big yeah it's okay
so far so good yeah yeah it's good it's
good no okay okay
oh my God yes that was almost out yeah
it was on the white line okay ready
ready ready
we need to go
to the the opposite side you cannot go
straight if you're passing the the first
the first one
I didn't even know yeah so if you if you
if you that's if you saw the opponent
like hitting yeah yeah
so you need to go like horizontal wait
not horizontal XX you need to do like
realistic badminton yeah yeah sure sure
yeah it is
alrighty okay but after that is anywhere
it's fine right yeah
wow
okay let's go
I mean you're good and we're fine I
think yeah I think together will be yeah
we will be fine
nice so fun I want to do this as a
collab stream Just Dance
even after the tournament
I think it's out
yeah it's out yeah I didn't even yeah
realize I was hitting it
okay okay
[Music]
yay yeah it's kind of funny
okay
nice nice nice whoa
[Music]
oh no
okay let's go
okay
new collab game idea yeah but this
server is like disappearing afterwards
right yeah true so sad
can we keep it up I don't know we'll see
about that because it's a different
Surfer right so yeah
um can we move all of this to the I
don't think so
uh I I will pay for the server to stay
up it would be such a so such a waste of
beautiful buildings
it must have been spent to make this red
Kyla that was so close yeah to the night
right yeah yeah yeah
but good job okay
okay we can pull such close ones in the
real match then we're gonna bamboo them
through it through it through you can do
that
hey
that's almost that's almost that kind of
Yeah question for you yeah in in Pokemon
unite uh-huh did you
did you actually always go for me
because you knew I was weak as [\h__\h] not
really I think it's because it's because
it's this hey I don't think ENT is weak
like you know it isn't but I was the
weakest link and I feel like you no you
know what you your level is even
uh rainey's level even under your level
uh like like the Character level I mean
and our Pokemons or the character the
character ah yeah but still like I think
because you were you were looking at the
um japanian match right spectating yeah
yeah maybe you saw oh Kiana no
so
I I say to him I say to my team the idea
team that Ian plays so need
like yeah yeah of course of course you
you guys defend so well yeah yeah yeah
true true I I really I really saved it
to them
you're too nice no no no I will
literally say that like like when when
we
um analyzed the the match I really I
really say that like not not on the
stream but I really say that yeah uh the
en team
it's wrong oh we're gonna practice
Yeah I mean you know that was our first
match so we were still really really
nervous but uh I think we were really
careful in the first match but it's
super good it's super good like the enjp
one is super good
um even when we saw that we were losing
we still thought that okay this isn't
this isn't even so bad this is not as
bad as we thought I mean there's Ian Ian
was winning at first we hear the ray
before the records are right so it's
always Rayquaza who turns around
everything yeah yeah yeah yeah
but yeah I think
uh then in we at the after the first one
even though we lost we thought okay this
isn't so bad maybe we can
have a chance against ID but I was
really scared because I knew a lot of
you and idea also cracked not really you
know like um I I and rainy started
practice the Pokemon like four days ago
before the tournament yeah that's
literally four days practice YouTube
yeah yeah yeah I rank and it was really
high yeah because yeah because I
practiced like yeah you know but it's
literally like you usually do yeah yeah
but I mean I literally just practice
just play the game like four days and
I've never okay um if you played MOBA
games before right yeah but it's on PC
and on mobile so I think I'm you know
like I mean I got the micro macro one
and the knowledge but you know
um I've never played on switch too so
it's like the controllers kind of hard
for us like for us so that you can play
it in on the phone no we cannot we
cannot we cannot I asked already we
cannot oh for the tournament we could
yeah okay uh because generally I saw in
the world championship I was watching
the world champion yeah yeah yeah and
they play on the phone some of them yeah
we cannot I asked I asked already okay
but yeah can we start yeah let's go it's
chill
and but you were so scary with your
especially you and the combination of
you having a scary looking Pokemon scary
looking yeah
suddenly and you're like
like I did a lot of I did a lot of
blunders here and there but yeah yeah no
you also when I was watching the Japan
the Japan versus ID match we were
spectating all together and I was like
constantly watching ID and I was
cheering for you guys and you were doing
so well all of you
thank you thank you look so organized
yeah Ian were you guys not really like
organized and well communicating because
to me it looked like you guys must have
been communicating so well
um yeah but I mean we we literally did
um
blunders here and there so yeah
but it's fine things happen
um
it is what it is like here what you guys
were talking about but it's probably
Indonesia yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I wanna hear what's going on like it was
somebody giving instructions in your
team yeah
we have giving instructions
um on the practice most of it gonna be
like Kobo but on the day it's
mostly me because uh yeah because that's
just happened
[Music]
was Kobo the most experienced right
um no actually no I don't mind the net
wait I think it's wait sure okay okay
yeah I saw it was Chad wasn't it behind
the net and I hit it anyway maybe it's
the hitbox and I shouldn't have hit it I
don't know
that was weird okay
right
it happened I'm just reading chat oh
okay okay let's go
hey
yeah yeah
okay okay too high yeah don't look up
too high yes
[Music]
okay what happened what happened there I
saw you I saw you hit it
I was like right next to it okay
again on the top of it I see yeah
that's very lucky move yeah this week
there's so many exciting weekends right
this tournament and Pokemon
yeah so many things to practice for you
know Pokemon unite ends and and then
yeah for this
never-ending practice yeah no next week
ending
no more practice next week
well ID is still very very busy
yeah oh yeah we have the Independence
Day coming ah yeah yeah what are you
guys doing for that
oh
um we have the
the costume refill I saw yeah yeah I saw
I saw you talk about that too yeah oh
really yeah yeah yeah
your silhouette looks really cute to me
no it's gonna be cool
we'll see about that yeah sure
I thought and cool books looks so extra
to me again yeah yeah as always yeah
[Music]
I'm excited is that on Wednesday or when
was that
um 15th
um 15 GST
[Music]
15 15. yeah 15th but that's that's not
the Independence Day is it no seventh in
seven because 17 we're gonna have
something else
that
that view oh yeah because you're waiting
for me yeah because we have that kind of
rules too like we need to wait for the
opponent to be ready before we hit it
oh really yeah yeah we need to wait we
cannot just like yeah
should we be giving each other like a
like a announcement and oh I'm ready I'm
ready are you ready yeah maybe maybe
it's nice to us probably
or maybe we can just something very
sudden like oh that's why I was still
still in my brain uh thinking about what
just happened
oh that's all okay okay hello here hi oh
hi guys we're done oh that's fast how
did it go
yes we actually I tried twice and
it went
really good great
we are practicing really great too yeah
yes you guys are really
um
passion passionate
that's so close that's so cool it's not
so close very good yeah that's very good
that's very good oh okay
no one more Kyla okay yeah yeah
practice you want
the gold shoes no yes oh here I can see
it I see it just thinking about hello
Cure All the Time by the way like are we
against on the badminton from the SRI
candy who are who are we gonna face
okay
sure sure sure
I wonder how good they are yeah I'm
doing a practice stream I need to watch
it yeah yeah they they actually did it
yeah in the morning I need to watch the
VOD yeah I need to check it too we need
to know our opponents right yeah yeah
that will help it's out no it's not I
should have rely don't rely on the auto
I should
okay okay so yes Kylie serving Kiara oh
it was very very close I ran for myself
[Music]
oh no this is bad this is bad
okay
[Music]
yay that's the big fields yeah ready
ready Let's Go Frozen I think it's
pretty pretty big okay
oh Kyla is catching up ready ready okay
I'm getting a feeling for it when it's
out though nice
oh you you already yeah we practice for
that yeah for the outline okay what
happened there
[Laughter]
okay
nice nice
wait what I passed through it it was too
close
okay
I like the Smashing sounds
[Music]
oh
my legs are too short both team are
equally strong apparently which is good
it's good because we're on the same team
yes and it's actually a good thing
nice I love this oh wait is that a dog
is that Alex yeah I need to look up yeah
okay okay okay okay okay got it got it
okay
oh this is so close
okay five five oh the scores oh no is
that for both things
that's supposed to be out I think I
don't know
yeah I think it's my mistake for still
hitting it even yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh
okay
[Music]
okay this is so fun is that Alex
I'll talk
oh my God okay I'm ready
mm-hmm
okay okay what
what
to look up and make short shot
um
no because they don't expect it okay
[Music]
okay hi
oh no gamers
this is catching up guys it's catching
up
oh
[Music]
my God just one more one more Chihuahua
one more
um
[Music]
is this gonna be a comeback
this is going to be
I thought it was more in the front than
it really was okay nice nice I think we
should be fine I don't know if you want
to practice again I we can do that can
we uh for soccer we have two three
people is not enough I guess I mean we
can do oh yeah it needs to be like at
least four like at least four yeah but
you know right you can dribble the ball
so by the time that's the very important
one so you just can walk and dribble the
ball you don't need to like short shots
yeah you don't need to just kick kick
like that no you don't need to do that
you can just walk you can actually hit
the ball yeah you can dribble the ball
oh without clicking
as well yeah I didn't know that that's
secret knowledge yeah that's why because
if we kick we lost the ball
okay soccer
don't forget to press anyway if we can
make it move
[Music]
me too
okay nice shoes
okay ready all ready yes
bison
okay okay
we will not have goalkeeper yeah it's
okay it's fine
okay hold on don't kick okay don't kick
first don't kick just oh but I think we
need to take this first no no no okay
just walk over it just walk don't kick
okay okay yeah like that yeah yeah go
yeah yeah yeah you you just need to like
turn left turn right yeah
yeah like that so this is not cool how's
this not go go in
yeah so you you need to like do that
I want to think yeah okay uh let's let
me see how far I need to go until I
should until maybe let's say I'm here on
the line and then ah too far let's go
back
I think that's yeah that's kind of okay
I think if I do a lot from here is it
gold it hits it hits the post I think it
hits the post
does it also have to do with like if I'm
looking up or down no not really
anything not really
yeah so we can do like this like this
like this like this
[Music]
try try try try practice the dribble
part durable durable durable durable
yeah you don't need to okay because if
you kick you lost the ball
oh that was a score
apparently what's that
you can actually go that far like I ask
and and moon has be like yeah you can
actually just like go there I guess I've
seen that in soccer before yeah but I
think goalkeeper doesn't stop yeah I
think the goalkeeper gonna it's easier
for the goalkeeper to hold
rather we dribble the ball like that I
think the goalkeeper gonna catch the
ball if we got close I think I want to
finish I I don't think I'll I'll try the
the dribbling but I want to finish my
dribbling off with a good cake yeah okay
okay yeah practice that yeah try try you
can yeah so
can we have like maybe at least
you should try to stop no or maybe or
maybe I will be the goalkeeper okay
let's stop first okay let's stop first
let's stop our actual goalkeeper is
gonna be
gonna try to stop the dribble okay
yes yeah do it okay
okay so one goalkeeper the goalkeeper is
either elfi or Kyle yeah I think
I think I'm good I think it's better for
me because I think I can dribble quite
okay
[Music]
I think
okay so what team should I get yeah
maybe white so you can you can be in the
opposite goal yeah yeah we'll try to get
a vote against you
should I be the goalkeeper I'll be the
goalkeeper no no no no no no no no you
you need to be the standard so you try
to uh take the ball from Chiara because
Kiara is like trying to practice the
dribble right now
okay okay okay
I'll be the goalkeeper
wait I will be the goalkeeper for the
white for the white man hold on do we
need a goalkeeper yeah to try to stop
the yeah oh okay you're both against me
now okay yeah yeah okay yeah yeah I'll
be just trying am I not a goalkeeper no
am I a goalkeeper no right
I'm a goalkeeper
we want there wait what
you can just you can just try to pick
the ball but don't hold the ball
don't catch the ball mommy yeah yeah
yeah just try to stop the dribble
okay
I'll go around here
okay I'll go around here I'll be giving
okay
yeah but you got it right you got it
nice nice nice okay
try
[Music]
no
oh that was I was pretty far and I only
used yeah the normal kick yeah at the
end
so that still went in nicely okay
because the problem always was that I
would hit the the top of the goal a lot
yeah don't don't use the long cake yeah
just use the normal cake one
let's go buy a goalkeeper
[Music]
okay okay okay on goal
foreign
try to catch up no
no no no no
man hey you want to play Real Soccer
I never actually play Real Soccer
um
I on a plane when I was little and I
never really played anymore
how little was little weasu
little
baby no not baby actually
this is like little little bubble bubble
we do
[Laughter]
[Music]
smacked it at me I smacked it back oh
yeah nice
nice okay
Lisa
[Laughter]
five seconds
oh no
okay break time I will talk to my
teammates
and I'll talk to them I'll talk to
Esther both goalkeeper do you have
anything else
um balls balls
maybe try to go from the side Kiana can
I look at your gloves do you have the
goalkeeper gloves this is my glove okay
oh
you both have it yeah
and what we are talking to each other we
are we're in the team right now
team light trust me trust me
why
I'm wider I'm the widest person
let's resume the game yes
okay here we go
[Laughter]
the problem is I have to go around the
ball because I I don't want to shoot it
in the same direction man okay okay
so no this is not listen no this is
Well normally I would have someone
behind me to back me up right to help me
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
is going so far away I'm gonna keep her
now
goalkeeper prison oh I said
I was pressing the one thing I was
scrolling elsewhere okay
you don't need to scroll by the way you
can just use like one two three
like just press
okay
you know
Nice Shot back into the middle
not for you this is not for you is
[Laughter]
I think for the goalkeeper it's also
easier to use the F5 the third point of
view oh yeah I'm also doing that oh okay
no this is the first time
nice nice so fun I'm feeling so sweaty
and hot
okay
[Music]
are you playing the software no right
like no on the day a change with eovie
oh your figure okay okay wow you're good
you're good at it
laughs
[Music]
Kiara is feeling the pressure no
I was close if I would have angled it a
little bit more to the left and I would
have been
oh it's almost all okay okay
what I want to try again do you want to
try anything
um
no I don't play no stop it
oh yeah she is this is me
you could do Kyla versus Lisa because we
we actually did we actually did a lot
already
took
um win against Tyler
is fine I mean Lisa is fine hey but I
want to see it once how many how the
point differences I want to see it it's
gonna be a long one I want I won't I
won't be in my uh top performance
because I already did it but I could try
once I want to see it
entertain me
nice okay that's a request right there
you're you're entertainers it's your job
we have done like 1 800 before
my child say it's 1800.
yeah it's like five minutes ish yeah
five minutes and it's like one on one
one match
my team
I know okay let's see I don't know if I
can still do it but yeah why is wait why
is Kyle and in the tug of
[Music]
because I do not Bank she's not picked
by the um staff I don't know why did you
see what I've wanted yes you guys it's
fine real soon I wear that clothes so
it's fine the score is closed yeah
my my hand feels sore already
now you're running in okay
I'm not ready for this one
I'm here
okay
am I red or white
you're red oh red yeah okay yeah we're
we're actually that clothesla like yeah
yeah we're that close so I mean it's
fine
Oh I thought it would be a big
difference but maybe in the late game
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
who gets tired first
oh my god oh yeah so far it's so pretty
it's pretty much the same
sorry
for giving you this challenge it's gonna
be five minutes like this but yeah I
mean we have done this before so
[Music]
and she's creating a bigger and bigger
lead
it's only a matter of time until she
pulls the first wait up oh yeah she's up
no she's already right because I feel
better
six red and four uh White so pretty soon
wait what I'm I'm red right I'm red
right oh wait for that never mind you
read okay no no I don't know I don't
know which color am I yeah you are red
oh okay okay
on the top is like switched with the
yeah the place right the place right
yeah yeah the place
[Music]
producer is still doing very very well
yeah I mean we got the same spit like
yeah
[Music]
don't worry about it
so yeah basically our difference is like
20 to 30 yeah on average yeah
on average
one one laughter tap is like
um one point or two points or what I
don't know I don't know actually I think
it's three three points every lever
I don't think it's one burn
you're going okay
yeah and and I don't really know like
how well they do it like the blue team
yeah yeah I don't know I haven't watched
their practice yet yeah is definitely a
speed clicker I think because she's a
Zoomer she goes fast
[Music]
I'm pretty sure and and gura yeah is you
know a master at Rhythm games so she
clicks everything really fast and she's
not she she doesn't just click
everything randomly no she's very
coordinated with where she's clicking at
what timing so she should be pretty fast
I will see the practice after this then
oh my God yeah Allah please report me
later yeah yeah I will I will I will I
will I will yeah because that time when
they did the practice I was doing
something else I'm mostly touching
across all
right yes yeah patching grass
work related who work related I need to
touch some grass not because I want to
touch the grass
oh touch grass you know I saw the clip
about
um
Polo cure
yeah Easter egg where the
grass for perfectionists oh yeah yeah
completion is completionist completion
is
wow yeah I mean well wow on Monday or so
because I don't have time this week
on this uh Minecraft then thank you so
much thank you so much for your effort
no don't worry I have this problem this
uh starts for me at six a.m oh Pokemon
tournament I had to be there at 4 00 am
oh
oh it's it's I'm Zone I don't know if I
should stay up or go to sleep to sleep
early go to sleep super early it's the
best chance
yeah also I have I have hold a talk at
10 p.m
at midnight that's six hours before the
Minecraft thing I would be done with
holotalk six hours so that's not really
enough time for me to sleep because I
need one hour at least to fall asleep
yeah yeah I'm just so excited
understandable yeah ah God damn it what
did I do with I didn't think it through
I didn't think
I wanted to do a whole talk on Sunday
instead but then
take a nap I'll just take like a free
hour nap or so and I'll be fine
okay looks good all these matches
looking good
um I think I think we are ready
I think I'm good I'll practice maybe me
and Kyla can practice tomorrow a little
bit Yeah you can yeah yeah you can we
can just do it off stream too it's fine
yeah yeah yeah just just call me anytime
it's okay or even before uh you know I
have to hold a talk until the actual
Minecraft Holo cup will I look up I
don't know what to call it
oh yeah between those I have like you
know some time probably so we can play
yeah sure sure I can actually uh
accompany too so like whatever okay so
thank you definitely make my uh but
usually it's gonna be midnight
like if it's midnight I'll I'll leave it
to guy
like morning time for you girls okay
okay yeah
looking a great job at organizing this
and I'm I'm really impressed at
everything that has been prepared for
this turn this ID Club so good job thank
you
um
okay I'll go read super chats probably
yeah me too I think me too me too see
you later
thank you so much thank you thank you
for a great practice bye bye thank you
okay hold on hold on hold on
[Music]
ah
I don't know it's really weird the mic
is really weird like I mean I don't even
change any set up settings on my mic but
it's really weird like it's happening
all the time right now
okay
okay let's RTA really fast
[\h__\h] back maybe from the audio yeah
maybe maybe it's because
um you know um
the feedback that I hear is like too
loud maybe on my ear so it's like the
fit back entering uh the mic so from the
headset entry the feedback that I heard
from the headset is like entering the
mic too so it's like
yeah yeah because this one is I lower
the volume and it's fine I think I just
need to like lower the volume probably
okay
small layer of volume yeah
so loud because it's like so loud and it
like hits my
head
painful
oh
okay
okay okay then
okay okay
I got hit by the name
so many times already
okay
hold on let me RTA first
okay I see here got it
smile thank you uh
thank you so much
practice
thank you good luck for practicing we
know you got bad from Tao
get some help
it doesn't mean you can bully or senpies
in practice I didn't bully anyone
I didn't bully anyone okay I just play
Talk of War when I got the chance okay
hmm
I I'm just too excited every single time
I do talk of War because no one wants to
play tack of war with me
I mean you know what actually right I
can I can borrow someone's account and
then I can log in and then I can play so
I know like um which one is better my
left hand or my right hand and then we
click click click click click but cannot
lie because it's like pulling each other
and so
yeah like I mean
[Music]
there's two possible answer one you have
got finger two you have smooth Mouse
no my Moss is broken already
this is this is not even
um a new mouse I have a new mouse right
where's it
because this one is kinda broken already
right half broken
yeah
half broken so maybe I need to like use
the new mouse maybe probably but yeah
[Music]
okay
what's this uh you want to break your
new mask even better
but I don't know like you know what I
mean I got no idea because because okay
yeah you know uh we can actually uh uh
change the team members
if we have the actual reasons for it
I don't have any
um specific reason to play in The Talk
offer and it's bad
motion sick and she got a yes she got a
yes
from M10 to do that and then when I say
to engine like engine can I and then
like no
you must say my hand cannot handle
badminton I mean all of the practice
right all of the practice M10 was emptin
emton was watching the whole time the
when when SRI candy team practice party
within practice just in case if there's
like technical issue buried um like yeah
um
technical issue here and there so Amgen
is like I'm trying to monitor it helping
Munoz and Pie and I mean
I should have known
I should have known I should have known
probably I should do something like M
Chan I got motion sick from playing
badminton
I don't know
hmm
I Really Wanna I really want to play the
talk of War but I can't
so yeah
Jonah Ryan finger coin in that all hail
Kyle amiibo what finger
Yama bro even bed in practice now even
better
yeah three
it really hurts like I I literally
didn't expect that I think it's rhesus
and pirate I think it's risu Senpai it
is a senpai right when when Riso Senpai
said
I was like what
oh your vision pie it's no reason Senpai
is senpai
I was like so happy because every single
time practice you know
um I say to I say to uh risu Senpai
please please invite me to every single
practice even though it's off stream on
stream whatever please just invite me
because I know if it's a practice time
then I can I can play the top of her
that I really love but
it's fine
it's okay
hmm
it's fine
kirikov it's Lonely at the Top Kyle
it's not even at the top I need my
monkeys
go hard around what
nice yeah it's really her
I didn't expect that
I was like I was like so excited when
Kali Senpai said we need to practice we
need to win and then and then I was like
so excited and then
um I have to say to myself like yeah
this is the time for me finally I can I
can play like many many games of Sparkle
four and then
Kyla it's better to for you to not to
plan and I was like
head by the truck
it's fine
fine
St icy waffle here Pepe for the finger
Quinn
Andrew get some help thank you rain or
some say bully I say master trainer
those finger muscles have to that flop
you also meet them to learn the sacred
finger switching techniques
amazed
[Music]
Source QR thank you so much
hunger or I mean I like it nice
I will always try to edit it after the
stream so oh yeah so um there's gonna be
a trailer
short shorts it's gonna be a short
Thriller like um what's that what's that
what's that uh similar to the kimono one
if you watch the the what the
kimono trailer want
yeah it's gonna be tomorrow
individual trailer yeah it's gonna be
individual trailers on our Channel I
think I don't know but mine gonna be
yeah tomorrow tomorrow
how much it will it showed again
we'll see yeah it's three more days
right it's three more days
so yeah
um
tomorrow tomorrow
yeah
it's gonna be on 12th
um
are there any practice after this one
maybe the on-stream one maybe there is
not going to be any on stream one but we
will do um some of the off the
off-screen one two like the small groups
probably like um we're gonna practice
for
um each mode
okay
Naga thanks for the training our extreme
Kyle it's really fun thing
and then Chris Gala for the tournament
I'll be rewarding for partially thank
you
okay wait I I gonna I'm gonna do my own
yell because I really love the yellow
wait where is it
please what Ella please please what
please what I really love the yellow
because why not right yeah
cheerleader Kyle I have new drawing idea
even better
lumayan
I can't why you can't your throat good
yeah my throat is fine literally just
fine yeah
it's speaking okay okay I will I will
definitely put the reefer you just need
to wait okay uh how how to even put the
reform hold on ah
Reverb
oh I think there's something wrong with
my OBS no worries
because I cannot even press anything
hold on hold on
I'll just do it manually then
laughs get some help
check okay
for the way fight fight fight fight
let's go ha
[Music]
is that good enough
yeah I don't know if I appreciated that
when now you're being confused
oh okay okay backgrounds
okay okay bgm
gone
okay I spilled my water because of you
don't do that
uh
wait
check check
s
[Music]
oh
get nice
uh my fears drop around 400 because of
that but it's okay
I really appreciate it
it's fine
foreign
nice
so it's a spoiler about your new
children leader outfit even very nice
it's surprising only 400 oh
nice
okay
um
400 people don't have mute button
I mean you can you can definitely say
that you're muting the stream but I know
that you guys gonna go to the field over
and over again for that moment I believe
so
it's okay
you don't need to be maluma you know so
yeah
yeah thank you
and then
no place done Place done what Legend you
eat it then before they could find
laughs
foreign
I didn't know what happened
on the opposite theme okay
I was just too excited
okay
um
nice
then
or maybe I know
can I practice with um can I practice
with srikandi the tuck of War
Zeta
any any of your members
La dot dot
I just
I just wanna play and I cannot play it
by myself
nice
even very nice
the general Ryan yeah really is your
Kryptonite lamal no I mean you know what
amjan and I are both uh
uh the kryptonites to each of us like M
Chan Kryptonite is Kyla Kyla Kryptonite
is M Chan so so it's like uh both of us
is like kryptoniting each other
does it make sense
yeah
sometimes I lose sometimes and then lose
perfectly balanced yes
Kryptonite only works one way no
oh yeah
I will practice with average and I'm
just fight me
M Chan if you're still watching this
fight me
do you have time for that fight me
yeah Evanston let's try some other time
fight me
[Music]
that's a yes right
that's that's a yes right yeah that's a
yes
that's absolutely yes
happy happy happy happy
nice
and even there this weather this weather
will be legendary Adventures
[Music]
not meaning join joy and that's joined
half time break exhibition match
I'm taking that personally really
yeah
I will remember the day of Kyla not
playing in the talk of War forever
forever it's gonna be forever
every single Holo ID cop if that happens
every single year I'm gonna definitely
remember that moment
Yama bro usually I say skill issue now I
can say skilled
yay Channel yay thank you 12 months
let's go
and then
enjoy Ryan nice
green Arco 9.5 out of 10 on your
cheerleading very passionate thank you
so much oh yeah
if anything's still here
listen to my yellow oh I know I know I
know M10 really proud of me yeah mjang
will be proud of me
for that yellow
yeah
or maybe Amazon also the one that I'm
closing the stream when it happens we
never know
but yeah or muted yeah maybe
it's part of the 400th year
so pretty I like it yeah thank you thank
you
only an M will Loop that Galileo it was
amazing though thank you so much Jordan
Ryan I know I know thank you
thank you
eh no matter what you say right I am the
coach of yeliel remember that the one in
the press conference
I'm the coach yell
hmm
yeah
um
thank you thank you thank you
and then that lemon just want to say
thank you for all of your Hardware in
the past week like you did amazing and
I'm glad I chose you as my oh she dude
thank you thank you for being here thank
you for uh staying uh uh in my stream
and then
no no not gonna be like that my bed is
[Music]
yay let's go oh it's 14 months
13 months
that's super nice thank you
okay let me see let me move on to the
social bus we'll see
you guys did well in this practice I
think particular team is ready to fight
in Hawaii cup yeah we are ready I mean
that's pretty good I can say I mean I
haven't seen the second d one
but I have some confidence
so yeah
yeah
Aussie are you a fox why are you
thank you
then
hello Mazer after I see it hi this
morning got news Grandpa sorry if I not
active seeing you happy helps a lot
Gambar pagu Maser no
no deep condolence for your grandpa
stay strong okay
stay strong
yeah sorry to hear that yeah
I mean your jokes yeah Halloween history
jokes always lights
the situation up every single time so
you know
you're a great
person
so yeah
please take your time
as much as possible
stay strong
um suspicious that was loud I'm going
black
that's the spirit that's the spirit that
we have okay that's the spirit that we
have we we need to be like in that kind
of spirit to do that
okay
and that's all for now I think
tomorrow stream
tomorrow stream tomorrow stream
um
tomorrow tomorrow gonna be a stream but
it's not gonna be at night I think Kyle
is always so good the cheering gaming
and laughing nice
touching grass time the touching girl is
gonna be
um
on the evening so
I think I will be streaming
um
in the morning
not really in the morning it's use
um probably it's gonna be
yeah morning and morning around 11 to
afternoon 11 12.
yeah because I need to post the shorts
first
I need to pull to post the shorts first
because if uh if I stream in the morning
and then I post the shorts
maybe no one's gonna watch that
I so I need to post the shorts first and
then stream yeah so maybe I'll post the
shorts around nine ish yeah
or maybe eight nine nine ish yeah
so yeah
then probably I'm gonna stream 11 12
around that time so yeah
stream to promote sure
do live commentary and watch
okay then thank you so much for the
practice it was fun
um we have a pretty solid team I believe
in particular team no matter what
happened it happened so yeah
let's fight
yeah let's find GG
thank you so much for now I'll be seeing
you soon adios
[Music]
is
get some help please take your rest
please
don't do that please
[Music]
thank you