[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
nice to meet you
outside
[Music]
everyone as I fix what I have done what
I hath brought upon all of you
for me
can you guys hear me okay yes yes
wow okay the mic is pretty far but they
should do this should be fine you guys
this
hi everyone we had uh some issues and
those issues I like to call
um I was getting ready to stream from uh
stream Labs OBS little did I remember
slash no slash mostly remember
um I can't do that to other people's
channels
and so yeah so I decided okay let's
learn how to export so I tried to export
and then I clicked make a new because I
thought that it would save the one that
I had up on my screen instead it deleted
my entire setup and went ha ha ha
apparently Kelly your your volume is
quite low
you need to hear your people voice and I
have a reverbs
I think they're [\h__\h] it is echoing
hello I don't hear anything like that
I'm building myself there okay
[Music]
it's fun
Buddha and Kiana are echoing apparently
I don't know
when I tune into the stream I hear that
too it's like a me me me me me me
it's like four four times echo or so
though foreign
yes yes yes
maybe I think that usually gets fixed if
we re-enter I think but hey but how is
that possible when Kuda is in a
different room
maybe I'm just hearing it from good uh
wait let me see hold on mine's not muted
but I need it okay I'm gonna mute mine
now
shall I rejoin
okay hello okay you know what how about
I think it also gets fixed if I just do
the re-muting
but but but but do you guys only hear it
in the Stream or just Kelly hear it on
her side too
I
oh okay now it's no Echo
oh yeah the echo is gone okay go gone
how about now
thanks for the feedback in the chat
thank you we appreciate it
oh I know why it's happening for
whatever reason your audio is going
through my microphone
oh
who is it because I could have
um and I'm echoing again
hold on a second
[Music]
hey guys we're experienced and
professional streamers here okay chill
yes chill yeah I got it Laurel though
Cali is not streaming with her usual
setup so please give her a break
myth Breakers man
yeah
and she's that I know the struggle I
think some of us do this know the
struggle to switch from your usual setup
to a one screen laptop setup
it's quite quite stressful sometimes hmm
well
uh well well Kelly's troubleshooting
shall I tell a story yes so today I had
like a low-key day off and I met with a
friend to go get foof and
[Music]
food food food
and we were gonna we were gonna go get
Ramen so we were gonna go get to go to
this place that uh has Ramen and I
haven't been to before but I ordered
Ramen from there before so I knew it was
good so I was looking forward to going
there and and and they don't have like a
website or anything but um they're on
Google and it says they're open so with
my friend we're gonna meet up there and
then I arrived there
and oh my God they're on freaking
holiday and the same thing happened to
me just recently so it's like the second
time that happens I arrived there and
when I am there I see that they're on
holiday and I can't get the food after
all I
because they don't like ride it anywhere
like on Google says they're open and
they still really have a website so how
am I supposed to know man
yeah so yeah that was stupid and I had
to find a different place but actually
it ended up being better because we went
to a different Japanese restaurant that
I didn't know existed until today and
they have even more than just ramen they
had the they had katsu curry and and
mochi and all that kind of stuff it was
really good yum yum yum yum
for my life
what oh it's just so they would decide I
should look at it
but currently you're not in the same
room unfortunately so we're outside we
went for a quick walk we'll be back okay
that sucks though that sucks I'm happy
you're able to get food anyway though in
the end yeah yeah I had for dessert I
had melon bun with uh Yuzu ice cream
inside oh got my hands all sticky
um
say I don't mean in trouble one more
thing are you using a are you using a
Blue Yeti it sounds like a
yes
I know that sound
no that's the big mute button on the
front that sounds like plastic
for whatever reason it's picking up you
guys's audio uh even though I'm using a
headphone
that's so weird happening on uh stream
Labs uh OBS
um God damn it what what is the audio
going through on Discord like
input
and my FF might be going through the
microphone then that might be the echo
problem
possibly yeah the wires are all crossed
okay
[Music]
oh yeah
uh uh
[\h__\h] it's still picking you guys up why
yeah a little bit
damn son
because we could keep it like this but
all of your audio would be super low and
there'd be no music
let me see let me see hold on
if you go to the sound settings like
um and windows
and double check where the output input
is and then you can also set the input
output for each app okay
[Music]
yeah sorry guys sorry
anybody else have any stories
probably do
I just need to look into my story drawer
now I mean you go first
come on Twitter stories sweet oh yeah
what about that sweet what happened
oh yeah one thing today and it was about
how lovely of a day it is you know
spending spending the day with friends
yeah relaxing
uh-huh
[Music]
uh
wow what's your thing with she on
oh Shion I'm I wrote
um
uh yes yes go on I was in the JP server
yesterday I was having a grand old time
by myself and I I happened upon I
happened upon xion's uh ice castle and I
um I just I have I just I realized I had
some extra
signs laying around and I I figured I
would write a um a little message
letting her know that I've been there
did I call her hand in marriage
no she asked me and I agreed
um
I don't I don't know yet but but yeah in
the karaoke I went to her karaoke stream
today
and and and and yeah that's where that's
where she proposed
um marriage
I need to work on my on my
speaking skills I need help I'm really
bad at it you might want to be careful
though because of alcoholism but I don't
know how she thinks about that
what I called I called Shield my
powerful cute garlic wife that means I
win right
healthy it is healthy and it keeps uh I
don't know the immune system
yeah true
I want Sana as a new member hello hello
Council uh Sana tsukumosana's new stream
uh first first stream after her W The
Bridge Street yeah I was having a great
time so I'm brioche one of you guys
uh
[Music]
I don't even know my stars
always
Gemini I was I was streaming at the same
time I think so I didn't get to catch it
yet but didn't I
ah Chad do you remember what was Gemini
Gemini better be breadsticks
endless breadstick the kind that you
leave pretzels you're a pretzel right
the Gemini too apparently according to
the chat so she's a pretzel too
star science tell me Google a kind of
pretzel like one of those ones they get
all twisty twisty tangly pretzel wait
that makes sense because yina has
tentacles and they can get twisted wait
I'm like at the very edge of Taurus yeah
it's very last day so technically a
Gemini right right yeah well both maybe
not
I don't know
let's talk what
what bread was a cornbread horn corn
corn bread
yummy
cornbread corn is delicious I like corn
but I don't know if I like cornbread
like a stone-ish
you make it with cornmeal and water and
cream cream
mice yeah yeah it's not really a thing
here
delicious this is a German word for
cornbread it's my my sport but that's we
don't it's not very common here
not at all but you gotta make it in a
cast iron pan and you want to make sure
you you grease the pan with Crisco and
then you got to put it in at 400 degrees
and then you only pour the batter in
once the pan is absolutely send your
skin hot
honestly it looks like cake though it's
delicious hi Jake hello uh did we
eat it
I do not know
it's still echoing yet foreign
no Echo okay do they hear music though
do you guys hear music
turn it up a little bit I do
yeah stay here music oh so everything
should be fine
[Music]
that's the voice of I'm sick of
troubleshooting I'm very sorry
[Music]
not more
sorry everyone uh that shouldn't have
taken that long and hopefully maybe we
can put that out actually no you guys
told a lot of really worries in there so
I would prefer not to cut it out it's
fine I'm sure people will put time
stamps to when we actually start yeah
that's good uh I want to say again sorry
everyone this is my wish
[Music]
earlier do you remember earlier before
you started the stream I was like hey
can we can we get some time to like chat
before or after the stream when you're I
don't know I don't remember what you
said but hey I got my wish okay
oh no it's okay
um
yeah my apologies for this everyone I am
far away from where I usually am uh I am
doing this with one screen with many
many many tabs open and this is my first
collaboration away from home uh so this
was not anticipated to happen please
excuse the late start we're still going
to have a good time today I prepared a
lot of fun stuff so
hopefully we can still have fun together
yay
all right no matter what yeah well I
mean I'm always having fun if it's with
you guys
[Music]
um
plug I can't
um yeah so guys from now on I think I
mentioned this before but the training
wheels went off okay yeah
I let you guys get away with quite a few
things quite a few
um and now it's time for that to end
um I'm gonna talk to you guys about a
little something called breaking points
uh to hear about breaking points
yes all right if we mess up Cali
literally gets to punch Us in the face
oh no
very close between left side and right
side
[Music]
the GM gets to give you a black eye each
time you anger them
can you boost Amy's audio a little bit
yes
[Music]
oh God
you should be better now just to be
extra safe everyone let's first do a
final leveling check just to make sure
that we're good to go from here on out
and no more problems first Ena give us
an introduction to who you are even
though this is your Channel
uh hello my name is
my name is Steph no I'm kidding uh my
name is
I happen to be the owner of this channel
uh you might have seen me around uh yeah
part of whole lot of English yeah yeah
all I've made yeah how's the volume
it'd be fun I lowered you down should be
okay now though
um
um I have acquired uh I got rid of two
skills uh and no merits and added one
Merit we changed a few things uh if you
want to know it's um for the people who
want to follow these kind of things I
now have the Merit Gunslinger uh with
three dots I got rid of subduing strikes
I got rid of a little bear and for
physical for firearms I changed my
Gunslinger specialization into revolver
and also I added thanks to exp gaining I
added one dot in stealth Euro School
[Music]
you guys made any changes in your stats
definitely let everyone know oh yeah I
sorry uh I'll do it after since I
already went everyone else
how about gura
oh okay
I'm the shark so today
I don't know exactly what I did I think
you know I think you actually filled
mine out for me accidentally and then I
filled yours in oh
but uh I added a skill I purchased uh
one skill merchandise I asked for
athletics because I'm tired of scout
getting stuck in scenarios where Cali
says all right I'm gonna need you to
roll Athletics and I have absolutely
nothing in athletics and I uh I don't
know so I got some Athletics skill uh
Boosty purchase
nice nice
and it's yeah that's it that will be
helpful yes
the Escape working on those abs
yes crunches in the gym yes
okay sounds good oh yeah nice uh I can't
be good as homework uh so I also got
plus one in athletics
uh and I came in a little late but
uh hello testing uh Amelia Watson
did you also have zero Athletics before
that
I don't think it was Zero but I think it
was pretty low
I already had two points and I have some
other stuff so I felt like I just put it
somewhere else yeah I never really had a
piece of Athletics yeah yeah a team of
couch potatoes no longer
yes
[Music]
yes the getaway will be easy now maybe
that depends please please
yeah
[Music]
I just got uh I got some cookies that'll
be fine she's she's already got the tone
I can already hear it now it's okay it's
okay I mean a lot of folks were worried
that I was that I was gonna be too harsh
on you guys but then a lot of folks were
worried that I wasn't being harsh enough
do you know what that means guys it
means training wheels off you got your
friend no we have a bunch in
cheeky freakies in the chats same people
that say you forgot the homework I mean
you're being too easy on them it's time
to go whatever okay yeah get ready for
get ready for a fun time guys we're
gonna talk about breaking points
okay so you may have noticed that on
your on your sheet you have uh something
called Integrity or morality I think
it's Integrity
um
it's one of those goodness gracious
morality yes that's the one then it's
morality
I mean they're technically the same
thing and I I do them the same way
regardless of Ever Getting playing
essentially essentially
um if you want to do something again uh
like for example uh pushover a hobo
steal a shopping cart
um if that's what you want to do I would
do that
aha I'm happy you asked listen
um here's the guide when your character
has done something morally unacceptable
to themselves or modern society or they
have witnessed something truly
terrifying they stand to lose a point of
Integrity this is called a Breaking
Point
break oh
basically this is how it works when you
experience a Breaking Point uh the
player or Storyteller I'll have you guys
do it I'll have you guys roll you roll
your resolve plus composure with a
modifier based on your integrity rating
for example I think you guys read seven
correct correct me if I'm wrong is
anyone not at seven
we have a seven all right so that's good
A plus one modifier not willpower uh
wait
resolve plus composure
you roll your resolve plus composure and
then you add a plus one to that dice
pool okay and that's your roll
um if you succeed uh depending upon how
well you succeed
um the result changes so let's say that
you get an exceptional success you do
really well with this role so the
character somehow manages to not only
survive the breaking point but also find
meaning in it to reaffirm your own
self-worth and to pass through the fires
whatever
um sometimes I think you might get a
bonus for it but no we're not doing that
over here don't do that in this game no
bonus good for you
um now uh yeah actually I think if you
succeed exceptionally usually you take a
beat and get one point of view power
back we don't do that here
um none of that you just don't descend
into madness uh same with success pretty
much good job
um now if you fail
the character's world view has been
shaken and he probably questions uh his
sense of self the ability to relate to
people moral Worth or sanity you lose a
DOT of reality
and choose one of the following
conditions the other two guilty shaken
or
all right but the biggest thing here is
that you lose a point go down that's bad
since you're more likely to do
bad thing
um and then dramatic failure that your
worldview has been damaged perhaps
Beyond repair and you suffer a you
suffer traumatic stress
[Music]
and you choose from the following
conditions
um or I create one for you
um either broken or Madness and you also
take a beat that's the nice thing hey
you get a beat exp yeah like mind broken
or body broken what do you mean broken
Minds
oh yeah okay get ready for that fun
stuff guys if you want to do some kind
of uh
questionable things I'll let you do it
but uh just be ready just be ready to do
some rolling
okay
[Music]
huh
well I'm happy to explain for all of you
Lads at home and you ladies as well
hopefully you get the picture so hey but
don't let that hold you back from from
making fun decisions you guys
oh go where the fun is
um I don't think I'm gonna remember that
uh I'm sorry if I make a mistake oh
don't don't worry it's funny don't work
through it together I'll just remind you
guys don't you even worry about it
yeah so I guess we should go ahead and
get started because we've kept everyone
waiting for long enough
um let's get moving then so the last
place where we left off you guys had
gotten a ride you hitched a ride on the
open road didn't you
yeah yeah
I like that we remember the repair truck
is the taco truck now
same thing right technically they didn't
repair everything anything but you guys
did get tacos and a lift
[Music]
it ended up being pretty lucky guys
does the food like help us heal the
damage that we already took nope but it
tastes good okay okay feels the soul
tasty points yeah
in terms of damage that you guys have
taken in the past we're also going to be
a little more strict on damage that you
have taken everyone
okay so in terms of healing talk about
healing okay uh you will heal with time
you can do medicine checks as well to
kind of speed it up that's fine but
essentially the way that it works is
bashing damage heals one point every 15
minutes so if a day or so passes like
right now on this road trip a day is
passing
um you should have no bashing that's no
problem
however lethal heals one point or two
days
remember this takes a while
all right
now that we've gotten that out of the
way oh
you guys have been traveling on the open
road for a while now it has been a whole
day enough and the reason for that
despite the fact the place was only
supposed to be five hours away
because taco truck friends have to make
a bunch of stops you know they're still
on the clock they still got to do their
work but lucky enough for you guys that
is a day that you get to heal
very nice well
from remember the day when uh
uh I got hit on the Hedge that didn't
heal yet right because it's like a bit
hard to tell how much time has passed
since then we slept through one night at
least does this mean that I get to heal
the damage now because it's two days you
should hear one point of damage after
the next night has passed and thankfully
you still have one more night before the
party you guys still have to shop for
your dresses or talks
okay
yes in
ah no two guys make your way down the
open road and eventually your friends uh
who have been repairing trucks along the
way the whole time while you guys sat in
the car and kind of did nothing
eventually drop you off at the contact
point
[Music]
oh no the contact Point happens to be a
bus stop in the middle of nowhere
but I think they agreed to take us to
the closest town what's this
technically the bus will take you to the
closest town
okay it's not great oh no
bye-bye they let you off
not at least we had tacos
we have to walk all this way
they go off laughing and screaming into
the distance
may I know we shouldn't trust the banjos
perception check to check uh if there is
a time schedule for the bus sure oh nice
idea
foreign
Plus
composure
weights plus composure that ended up
being afraid for me and one two yeah
it's gonna be a bus schedule but it's
gonna be written in a language like
Russian
wait what I have I'm bilinguals I can
read it
I can choose that language
like that okay that's right yes ma'am
ah right you got one success not bad not
bad at all with your one success you
kind of Snoop around the sign a little
bit and you see that there is indeed a
schedule and it looks like the next bus
is scheduled to come
in two minutes
oh my God tomorrow
to search for change on the ground sure
your perception
what is it again
roll your wits plus composure Dash roll
forward slash row
did I do right yes you did and you
remember you can do a greater than sign
eight uh count all your successes but
this is fine I can see that you got two
nines so that's two successes we'll have
to tell you find 50 cents in a bus token
lucky you what to tell very nice
all right how are the rest are you gonna
pay to get on this bus
I still have some money no
you probably have a couple well since
should be fine
um anyone else have money
wait what if I use my resources does
that count
I'm glad you asked yes it does
okay buddy it's for everyone I'm sure
bus tickets aren't that expensive all
right sounds good I'll I'll let you do
that
your with your resources and that's all
you get to do today uh with that okay
that's fine wait but no way
it's fine it's fine hey you guys still
got another day till the party no need
to worry well that's true that's true
yeah you guys are still out on the open
road and what's important is you guys
get to the nearest town and meet the
contact Point So eventually the bus does
roll up
doors open and it looks like the
jankiest bus you ever did see but hey
it's a way to get into town I guess
yeah what
better than our van as long as the
wheels are spinning you're right
I'll be sitting wheels on the bus go
round
eventually you guys do board the bus and
thankfully uh you was able to buy you
all bus tickets
thank you
you're welcome
[Music]
so you guys settle down on the bus
and the bus uh starts right back up that
old creaky engine gets moving rumbling
right up again
hey you speed off the forest
as you continue forward into the forest
you realize
someone sitting in front of you
seems to be very interested in you all
a rather dashing look
and by dashing I mean little wannabe
dashing Shades flicked back hair it's
like a business dude really a bit pale
has something of an umbrella over his
head real weird
like a hat umbrella yeah a little
umbrella head
[Music]
like those ones it's just a headband
strap around your forehead with an
umbrella on top a lot of straws with
beer candle pop yeah you get the feeling
that he would look kind of Dashing
except the umbrella hat kind of ruins it
there you go he looks like a fool yeah
big old clown looking back at you guys
what up bro
yeah pulls down his sunglasses looks at
you all and says Ah
it would appear that uh
there are four of you
you do match this
are you perhaps
a team that's supposed to be
[Music]
it depends
you have to know
a note
the one
I didn't sign it
a tip from me surely you have it how
about the invitation oh who has it again
[Music]
I've got a lantern
[Laughter]
oh okay well surely someone has a shovel
Callie's microphone cutting off
apparently uh
uh uh uh check one two hey
check one two check one two
just a little bit they said yeah it
sounds fine now okay I hear a different
microphone in the Stream compared to in
Discord like in Discord you have a
really shitty microphone oh yeah
partially difficult to understand you
but yeah okay
no worries no worries
alrighty then
can actually change that it's okay ish
now yeah
they say it's fine
okay sounds good as long as everyone
else thinks it's okay
all right
um but this dude kind of looks back and
forth at you guys and said surely one of
you has
quotations yes
well maybe if we got your name sir we'd
be able to tell if your note had your
name on it
sir
all right all right fine fine I'll play
ball with you all
my name is Cornelius
I won't give you my last name just
Cornelius Cornelius cornhole
he looks shocked that you have to play
cornhole Cornelius carnal you know what
cornhole is corn holes when you throw
the bag in the hole on the board I'm
sorry
Cornish
hmm
God he says he says God
ah
um
yeah I really don't know who has our
invitation though
oh and it's like your pockets okay uh
I have a wrinkly receipt uh
note
right
I have a note
[Laughter]
[Music]
yo we might have to go back to the Hedge
real quick to get the invitation lost it
somewhere the bus stops one kind of
jerks to a stop and it looks like
there's someone in front of the bus
waving their arms around
[Music]
pumpkin over and over we hear you now
[\h__\h]
[Music]
the boys
like we are in the room but you're not
in it
[Music]
I think you can re-enter
yeah hi stream people hello
[Music]
it's fine Taco dadd cheese what's up
what's up Taco dadd cheese how slippery
are you today what how slimy are you
today
what
they're not slimy
I know it's like they look very slimy
you guys are good for the skin it's a
good thing it's they look slimy in a
good way
that's how they fit in all those weird
tiny places I like rats yeah like bats
are slimy
[Music]
a dime oh I see I can't
liquid
yeah cats are not slimy though
it's like tacos
the tacos are slimy cats are slime
no no no no little tacos more furry and
they had like hair eel
yeah excuse me
yeah fur actually make would probably
make them more aesthetic to me
personally because I like everything
that's fluffy
I'm thinking about like the somebody
with with a 3D
program that can put the photo on the 3D
model by like a high texture high-res
texture oh my God images
[Music]
I think we did it yeah
yeah we're back we can figure out who
the dude was
ah why isn't Kiara moving
oh there we go I'm moving oh God you
scared the [\h__\h] out of me oh she's
scared oh I was just calling we're
getting into this game if it kills us
let's go that's right we will do this
I I take out my mind
oh
[Music]
man I'm sorry Kiara what was that
nothing
I'm not doing anything
oh
um
I really don't like oh
I see I see something it's not moving
sure isn't give me just a moment
[Music]
Sally's losing her mind
I don't know do you think we should want
to play Minecraft yeah
I don't know maybe
in any case Minecraft when in doubt play
Minecraft Minecraft
play
um wearing Jack box oh we have a boy
almost dead we have permission for worms
yeah I think we do yeah I'm back guys
yeah what
yeah I think wanted to be boss
and we
you can do a chat stream we could just
set it out you can just chat about stuff
that happened you know yeah yeah a week
or so is that okay
of course of course
yeah whatever you want to do Kelly
we're just here along for the ride
you've been the brains of this so far so
whatever you're comfortable with thanks
guys I want to say I do feel pretty bad
uh really bad actually because uh it
probably would have been a better idea
to just move it until I came back from
vacation but I just wouldn't want to
leave everybody waiting so long you know
because I know this is something that
everyone really likes a lot and a lot
falls on my shoulders to make sure the
quality
guys and so I really wanted
like apologize
everyone I'm very sorry uh especially I
told all of you guys as well I know you
guys
um sometimes things get in the way
uh
I want to make sure that it's high
quality for you guys so I do really
apologize and I won't let this happen
again
um
yeah but we can maybe still have fun
together if you guys want to do
something else
let's do it is that cool
that's cool can we I mean we're only
streaming one point of view I guess
right now so we could do jackbox games
yeah or we could just chat we could like
uh oh yeah I like one of those word
games or something I don't know board
games
White games oh
my god oh what is that thing where uh
you're supposed to say the first thing
that comes to mind
oh I like the word
oh
like a I say a fire truck and then
somebody else says I don't know
association game yeah yeah
okay okay
[Music]
yeah or we could do shiratori I know I
said it like super
like
cheers that's not really work in English
that well then I guess it doesn't that's
a good point
laughs
um
oops what's been going on recently guys
well we have new members
yeah I know that I I kind of gave all my
thoughts already but uh I just want to
say real quick I really love everyone
I think everyone's super cool and super
cute
what the
hi what what hello hello
yes went into the void I couldn't hear
anything I'm sorry I'm sorry I feel good
going on
[Music]
I'm back
I'm big
small
even my internet died I don't know
what's going on I'm sorry it's all right
today's just a scuffed day you guys
it'll be fine
[Music]
I don't mean to Rend your bodies
here we go
[Music]
oh my God
oh my God that scared me
um
like being in the room with you guys
like a like a nice rainy day where you
can't go outside to play yeah relax
inside chill
yeah can we play worms
worms I don't even own worms right now
what's the code
wait look at the garlic phone that's a
browser game Cali and this is free
that's a good idea
okay well yeah
but whoa yeah
because I mean we have that too but
worms I do not own right now currently
and I don't know but if Cali owns it on
her current laptop
into worms another time good on
the game is really nostalgic to me too I
played that like a million years ago
when I was sick really I just I know
lots of line to play it I'm going to
play it uh oh yeah yeah sometime that's
not a bad idea actually
fine
[Music]
if you guys want to
oh okay so should we do a poll or
something about it
or whatever is easier for Cali to set up
right now yeah okay again oh we could
also uh like you know I could
um do it on her side since if Cali stops
and Eda started it would be like the
stream didn't end oh yeah
hop on over to the other other side of
the bees
but that'll be like like uh
5-10 minutes
music
okay here that too monkey music
yeah yeah it's coming from you Kelly I
hear monkey music yeah
[Music]
you guys can hear my my uh desktop as
well very strange and I don't like it oh
oh okay heads up then
um
it might be my garlic phone addiction
but I think garlic phone would be the
easiest to set up for Cali very true
I like all the noodle emotes you have oh
it's like a noodle Kusa
noodles
I asked Sana if I could chew on her
forbidden gummy worm and she responded
to me
please tell me she said no
said only if I can sit on you and then
she sent a an email called Sana
so I I think I'm in trouble but I get to
chew on yeah crushed
but I get to chew on a forbidden gummy
worms so I think it's a fair trade it
looks like I think you should run I
think probably
[Music]
like fit like in the crack yeah in the
crevice
[Music]
I didn't finish it
please
on it it'll be like the amusement park
right where you're like right inside the
cup and it like spins around
yeah
hammock between fauna is like a little
uh sticks
and yeah
apparently she's a kitten yeah from
right here
those aren't Atlas
no there are branches they look like
Birch but I don't know what they are
it's like Karen was supposed to be like
golden and like glowing
are apples
oh golden apples like different you know
it's not there's enough antlers
and she said it's also not carbonated
and it's also
never mind I think I think somebody
asked her if uh if there was sap in her
in her branches and she said she didn't
know so maybe one day we can find out oh
maybe we should just ask her she has an
apple maybe she doesn't Harvest her
sweet nectar okay don't say hold on if
you say it like that wait a minute
serious sweet thick nectar a what
[Music]
yes what do you think I said
stuff today
just shut my mouth until we figure out
no please continue talking this is the
joy to hear you speak
this is where yago's dream died
I think it died a long time ago it kind
of looked again you know what the what
the console tape is kind of but for two
for point two seconds you know we would
just put the nail in the coffins that
that's the that's the phrase right I
think I think it's about it's about done
four now
if we're lined up like this we're like
uh we're like a council Council of
boneheads don't say the dummies
hey don't understand
we are more than just boneheads okay we
have a combined brings our account of
one and a half on a good day I said
already I know that the council's got
like god-like avatars and stuff like
that but myth hasn't even really begun
to show our full power yet
yeah like this done oh my God
oh my God
look at that I'm bad
didn't you think that like when you
first heard console you thought it was
gonna be like a student console yeah
yeah yeah that's exactly what I thought
yeah but yeah the council will be
joining you and I was like huh so
they're like yeah but honestly
you know you know our way you know our
big brain management they wouldn't do
something like that they need something
more chunibio powerful that's gonna top
our power even though I know how to top
a Shinigami how to talk
how to talk a time traveler how's the
top of Phoenix and some girl that says
she's human but she's definitely not
well we gotta make Gods next so
students yes
what you're saying is that we're all
bottoms
exported me
[\h__\h] or something cool yeah yeah
there's a fan art of like like
uh like like Yankees and then like yeah
that's cute oh I like that
um
gangsters versus the gods apologies
couple of Goody Two-Shoes that still
need to they need to be they need to be
introduced to the way of the home
I can't wait I mean I'll get the duct
tape I'd never do that what
no sorry
are you good I need to go
say So reading on my channel just went
down by a lot today
[Music]
I kind of want to bite hungry yeah I I
could go for a bit yeah
a bite of some garlic
we can go to kfb together let's go yeah
aren't you gonna make lasagna this week
yeah or tomorrow tomorrow
I am I'm nervous because I never made it
myself before I only have eaten uh
ordered or a frozen lasagna before so
this will be the first time I'll make it
myself but it'll be so difficult
yeah you stack some stuff
on top of it because like it's difficult
to get the right
um texture and stuff yeah yeah
lasagna lasagna
it's all right it's just spicy instead
of what I love the ketchup sauce you put
in the Sriracha
ketchup in lasagna tomato
lasagna are you eating yeah
something did something oh you mix in
some spicy stuff with tomato sauce and
you get spicy spicy lizard when are we
all gonna cook together
oh
my goodness yeah wait one day I'll feed
you guys
spicy food we should do a stream where
uh three oh okay wait remember bitching
kitchen what if the three of us the
three of us will cook a three four
course meal for Ina and Kiara and they
have to judge it I like that idea oh
okay before before that idea how was
your rate your cookie
cookie
with or without the microwave
um we're assuming you have a microwave
oh eight
okay okay maybe seven
okay okay
I'm gonna say seven yeah what in half
nothing uh six and a half
well you know you turn into a cat
yeah when did that happen
[Music]
where'd you get those drumsticks
can't Pina
Tori go
chicken she's no longer with us yeah I
want to go use the litter box
[Music]
Finders Keepers
what are you doing yeah that is big
oh God
there she goes oh
I think so yeah today happened did it
happen I don't know
can I eat can I eat enough
I'm behind you oh no that's the right
ways
how to get rid of a big cat bring up
some tentacles I don't like it
you know
my girly am I growing it
what are you doing on my head yeah
now why are you behind me no what are
you doing back there what are we doing
I'm not behind her what are you doing
back there don't worry I thought I was
sitting on your uh
what the lyrics
sorry about it
wait what are we doing are we just
hanging out or are we gonna Oh
I thought we're gonna play a guard phone
but it's okay we can just talk that's
fine you can just talk okay
I mean it'd be yeah
I have to say I have to save everyone
I'm honest
so I
wish I was just kidding I fooled you I
have to I have to go in this
[Music]
yeah you guys we can keep playing while
I set up a brand new world for us to
play in is that okay oh
yeah okay
will it be a big open field if you would
like you can imagine
it's gonna be uh it's whatever you
imagine a bakery oh hey
what kind of Bakery what do you think
the heart desires one filled with bread
croissant
question
I pronounce that really
awesome
[Music]
I thought you called me musty
I was speaking French you mustache
wait stupid what you know French curious
speaking French yeah that was me oh
speak French
thank you
[Music]
you can do it
guys are hairy it looks like Harry oh my
God every day and tell me Hey listen
nice hey Nathan hey hi
[Music]
hey
are you making fun of I will punch you
why we go
[Music]
vacation mode
oh oh that was just the the music
okay I will be playing yeah I'm setting
it up right now
yo gamer time
yo oh I see the link oh my God it's
happening oh wait I gotta I gotta be
done gotta find the right we don't even
have to play that long I think one round
would be enough because we always stream
for one hour or something like that and
yeah for longer I don't know we can do
one normal round
or two
me a girl you want to scoot a bit closer
to Amelia
okay yeah don't be shy get real close to
gonna get real pick up on your face
um
smelly
[Music]
all right I make myself normal again
here's some space
[Music]
gotta be careful okay let me move over
here time you washed your mustache I can
smell it from here
let's watch it what's that why it's
called the most uh
actually yes hide it smells like
oh
watermelons cereal
[Music]
cereal
okay Lucky Charms after this
blue ski Shamar maze
have you guys had the the Lucky Charms
where it's only the marshmallows why
why not is that really
I just wanted to be uh artistic I just
want to draw some questions
I thought
[Music]
hello
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
everyone knows who you are are so live
your life
[Music]
it shouldn't be anymore
came back
[Music]
yeah that thing pokes my eye man anymore
bye now
it's fine it's it's a it's actually it's
not really a brush it's like
because it's a pokey Ellie decided the
room smells kind of fishy
[Music]
I gotta do what we gotta do
say it again
well it smells good over here
try the animation one
really
um I don't really know if we if we could
do this but we can give it a try if you
like knock off was really funny too
yeah
I like the knockoff one
I don't know any of them before so
knockoff was like oh my God I was dying
from laughter my eyes I'll chat if
there's a taco blocking my face because
of the uh you know Channel thing you can
just turn off annotations in the YouTube
settings there's people who don't know
that I think
they want to see their sweet sweet salty
I I think I show you now
I need to learn
wow
[Music]
okay yeah I'm ready always okay
ladies would you like to get started
yes okay yes let's go you guys want to
play normal or knock off
[Music]
knock off
focus try to replicate okay let's go
party time
no no text from do you actually just
have to draw but the time after eat like
now you have a lot of time for the first
one but later on you will have less and
less time to copy it and yeah oh did we
try this before
no I don't think so you you girls
probably didn't
um
maybe maybe you could like if you can't
think of anything maybe Draw Something
RPG related drugs that's a good idea
oh I already Drew someone else okay yeah
me too whoopsie doodle
oh we should do like uh we should have
one where we draw the new Council oh
that's great
yeah good idea that is a very good idea
I'd kind of like to do more than just
fun so that's okay we could maybe
yeah that's okay
yeah yeah yeah definitely okay yeah
what is those transparency BS
[Music]
I forgot what my bird looks like damn
I just make something else out of it
usually
[Music]
wait Watson what were you just humming
oh that's a lovely song
it is it is
gonna put on that that silver tinfoil
outfit
[Music]
mine takes too many brain cells yeah
yeah I have to agree you know I don't
know how you don't think we only have
one brain cell right but you draw all
the time oh
I don't do anything else oh I'm
incapable of doing anything else gotcha
yeah no gotcha gotcha you know
gotcha yeah I I understand he has gotcha
[Music]
I'm sorry I don't mean to bring back
painful memories
it's fun it's fine all right recently
recently my money started watching my my
clips on YouTube randomly and she was
like what is gotcha they say you spend a
lot of money on you I'm just like I
don't know I don't know talking
[Music]
I need to know
wow yeah of course
[Music]
my art skills are not here today
I can't cheat with my friends
I know
yes really
I think so
I don't know
uh
um
I
[Music]
forgot I don't know
right
else
ruining the fun oh I'm ruining the fun
it's okay I cheated a little too we're
all allowed to cheat just
good luck drawing this
[Music]
I understand
foreign
[Music]
make something out of this
no Panic
speed
[Music]
trying
beat stop the time
[Music]
no
okay I guess we'll just
a lot of sense
um mine might not make sense but
what is
okay I have to draw this this is
round at the end you only have like 10
seconds time also why are you looking at
it the time passes too so oh
um what for our drawing as well
yeah
oh
what was that
[Music]
oh no
oh no oh it's already halfway time you
know I hope people watching this archive
don't I mean they won't but I want them
to
this is not in a drawing this no it's me
drawing it tallest
no it's cool
oh
I forget the whole drawing
me too man
oh God what is so hard about just
remembering a drawing
so
what is this
I was very abstract it's like Picasso
yes
oh no
um okay
easy
[Music]
um
a line
again
[Music]
oh God oh God
oh my God oh my God oh my God
what time foreign
yes yes
I
this is your drawing that I got I got
yours
I don't know maybe it's not oh it's
[Music]
no man wait yeah that one's wrong
there's no way
is
[Music]
uh oh no
oh no
okay
[Music]
and then
that was good
should I do it manually and it's a
manual yeah manual is better
automatic voice over of the sentence the
rest is fine yeah the lady yeah I can't
wait here we go this is my album one
oh I know I decided
um as like hey this is supposed to be me
as a gamer well here
over time now listen first it was draw
whatever you want so I started to draw a
gura I wanted to draw a girl it's like a
big gamer with like Doritos and
mountains right and then we decided to
do OK ttrpg and I'm like wait I forgot
TG RPG okay fine Scout I guess so Scout
asgara is a big game it goes in Mountain
Dew and uh that's Mountain Dew I didn't
know what that was okay
[Music]
come on
time was like what is this
um
[Music]
oh that's cute
as always
everyone
I have saved mixed up okay
I just like did anything that came
through
not a mushroom yeah
that turned out so good
I love the girl theme Here
laughs
my dog Kiara's art was Watsons for sure
what does that mean
it looks like I'm sorry
there was an effort there was an effort
a good effort too
um
you're eating eating the space Cheeto
yummy
that's mug I didn't know
[Music]
I love that face good face
you guys have similar teeth
back to the one before I couldn't save
it all right thanks
we can move on
what the hell
I'll add red hair at the end because you
thought it was Bales yeah
[Music]
so this is
working at ksb and having just a really
angry customer is actually
yeah I don't definitely know what I do
oh my God it wasn't any corn wait
[Music]
what happened
[Laughter]
turned into a [\h__\h] cold
what is the situation man I love it oh
that's good
I like this game oh man
[Music]
oh God
acorns they at least like talk to
now what do we have here
[Music]
um
[Applause]
yeah
Mama really turned him into it
Cali ran out of time I see
it disappeared
get here
where did we come from where are we
going England
that's great I love it see that's why
not love is funny
good game
you go come on
guys a surprise Facebook I'm
light-headed from laughing that's good
that was a good round that's a good
round shall we do one more
you guys want to play again
I wouldn't mind
quick and smooth in fact right okay uh
yeah
oh dear okay okay that's the thing
all right here we go
[Music]
um
okay I know what to draw hell yeah let's
go
[Music]
this will make one of the members here
very happy
I wonder if we're trying the same thing
I don't think so the way
no way
[Music]
of course you can
okay you just need to have you just
gotta get your message across that's
what matters that's what that's what art
is you know
you know communication tool
[Music]
all right
problem yes
to you
oh God
I like this
no probs
stop the nightmares
oh dear
I don't think I'm gonna show all my past
drawings as well it's not fair
that is the most interesting thing about
it the process of the creation of your
Picasso art
oh no
[Music]
so that we can get into that shark brain
real deep
um caution turn back
and turn back
[Music]
okay okay
oh still so much time yeah let's go
let's make this beautiful
yeah with so little time you always get
this this brain freeze where you don't
know
how everyone looks like even yourself
sometimes even though you see yourself
always
[Music]
forget what I look like
I like need to pull up a reference
yeah no time I know I know
yeah you think after we stare at
ourselves so long that we get it uh
ingrained in our brains but I guess not
no I don't remember myself I remember
you guys
[Music]
you guys might hear squeaky bed everyone
on my bed
you're on your bed now yeah I was in a
lot of pain
oh no
are you okay yeah I don't have an
optimal setup right now because I don't
have the setup popping off yet uh
supposed to be in the future date
supposed to go to the lake
[Music]
almost oh gosh
yes but when is your stream starting
approximately
I don't know whenever we're done here
why okay
I'm gonna I need to no no I just want to
know when I when when I will give you
the thing is
what I've already done
okay
[Music]
okay I'm proud of it I'm so proud oh my
God
I should upload this to the fan art
hashtag
mine also portrays a very important
message mine too
[Music]
yes we are
we are a team of artists
you can do it beautiful
[Music]
yeah I'm watching what what uh
um
okay okay
can you smile for me Watson I need to
see what that smile
smile
there you go thank you
[Music]
okay Todd is ticking everyone time is
ticking
keep it in mind
[Music]
um
someone can properly
after me yeah
someone can save it and someone can say
especially if Ina comes afterwards yeah
definitely I don't know about that
video oh they're good
oh no
oh God
uh oh I'm [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
what is this what is this okay
[Music]
uh can I look at the picture again I
forgot what was there
[Music]
uh
oh my God there's no time I wish I could
add color
um
[Music]
I know what this is
no-brainer
[Music]
uh-huh
what the hell
oh man
that's beautiful
okay
[Music]
oh no
uh
[Music]
I don't know what's being wished or here
's mine let's see what we have
such a short time
you know how do you save this how would
you say this you know
[Laughter]
Russell originated from a cat
caterpillar pause the blade
you know why yeah
um
beautiful hair thank you gorgeous hair
beautiful
uh
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
Corinthians
yourself
I went from Orange candy corn to corn
cob because I was thinking about the
Cornelius from tgrpg
rest in peace I guess
that was a carrot I see
did you think it was a carrot Kelly
oh oh oh that was Kiara after my bed
getting I always thought it was a corn
Watson's the one who thought it was like
a carrot
[Music]
it just I could I don't know how to draw
the the top yellow carrot no yeah yellow
carrot
look here
and that's a carrot
yeah
oh yeah I'm very proud of this one oh
wow yeah it was really uh
bad with this one sorry about that I
tried definitely knew it for someone
yeah
got a lot of time though
it works
[Applause]
to make it simple
I love it girl what is that I love it I
thought it was a pair of butt cheeks
I'm dying man I'm killing me
yeah my definition and he's your your
pair of butt cheeks
I know
something special
[Music]
the crash
right Watson
um
oh
and this works
oh thank you that is what's gonna happen
to you boy got across the point got
across yeah
well done
you ladies
I will never get enough of this game
I will say
mm-hmm
holy cow I needed that
wow I needed it that's not your Apple
workouts
one of those definitely on Twitter
[Music]
I needed a left
yeah there you have it yeah
I don't know let's be real though if we
would have if we would have played TT
RPG our sidetracking would have
frustrated you anyway today
I don't know I just I'm gonna get all
I'm gonna get all stupid and Matthew I
don't know you guys are the best at me
you guys are just I love my Den mates
too
creative smart
I love you guys
from Cali I'm trying not to y'all Safi
[Music]
because I
I get it
but yeah
your boy your boy did wake up extra
early to prepare the whole scenario so I
guess oh yeah I'm sad about that
personally because I had a lot in school
guys but you know what that I can attach
to that he was ready two hours before
and we were going through things like my
character sheet and my skills the ones
that I should eat out and all that so
she was there she prepared so it's just
some things you know when you travel and
you stream abroad it's just not that
easy yeah I should have also offered to
just stream on my end with like all this
stuff too so yeah okay no problem I'm
gonna make a new thumbnail for you where
we just slap on the garlic phone
logo over the myth Breakers look yeah
let's put the logo on top of it it'll be
fun yeah yeah let's just slap that bad
boy I'll make it I'll make the session
even better uh for when we Zoom again
when I'm back home that's okay
what yeah no worries
let's take it easy
you guys too yeah enjoy your vacation
Kelly don't care enjoy your time with
your stairs
yes
shut down a little bit and stuff as
you're having a big group
wait I can do this though wait hold on
uh
oh my gosh
oh let me who's purring I feel that how
was that
hello
[Music]
I want to go cuddle with my cats now
um
yeah
okay we are a big happy family
you guys are the best I'm kind of
ruining the picture here so guys
I'm back I think
picture time family photo everyone's
screenshot
now where are you okay
I think they're our adopted too yeah
[Music]
Victor I just wants his face look so
weird and your face always gonna do that
does it always do that though
hey get that broken limb out of here
I bet it's wooden it's not even real
there are just like try like Spanish
children and like pull it out and just
like ah and then you're like
poke my feet yeah
pulling my fingers sorry oh my God
I can't reach it wait no we're looking
good now we're looking good
oh my God
I pulled her finger as you wish
ascending
this whole picture
left or right everywhere every heart
desires
foreign
[Music]
laughs
I think they got it
nice thank you thanks everyone
collab I had a good time talking with
you guys if
yeah can't wait for the rest of the
story to continue
um if anything you guys remember where
we left off and I guess
and Cornelius has an umbrella hat and
sometimes that's all you can ask for in
a session
yeah they don't know the person in front
of the bus got hit by the bus tune in
next time
[Music]
exactly I'll see you guys we'll catch
you on the flip side and continue the
story in Prime setting later on bye
everyone
bye bye
I'll see you soon