[Music]
do
sorry for the
hello
welcome to my state
welcome welcome welcome welcome
how are you guys
should i move a little bit
uh over there
now maybe over there
so we see the chat a little bit better
nice background thank you
so i mean i've already showed it before
but this is the first time i really use
it on my channel properly
so let me introduce once again my new
background for karaoke concerts and
stuff
and breakdance dance parties whatever
and
[Music]
[Applause]
dj looking sick yeah he's having fun no
actually he thinks
you know
he's a chicken so
he um i gave i gave him a dj uh
table
he thinks he's like controlling the
music
but he isn't don't tell him
he's not actually controlling the music
but don't tell him he will be sad
we don't want to disappoint him
he thinks he's doing something but he's
not
let him dream yeah we don't want to
destroy his dream uh
[Music]
see that's a meme that i can get behind
uh off
so today is a very special kind of okay
because i'll be uh
i'll be singing um
oh i have original songs
and
uh they are not gonna be the original
versions though because i'll be singing
remixes
that are officially released by whole
life
as you may have noticed
since a lot of the whole live members
have been using it in their backgrounds
as bgm
uh in their streams and there has been
like an official release of remixes the
first wave was uh
lo-fi
low-fi remixes
and the second one was which is recent
very recent it was like bosa nova
remixes yeah
and i've been digging them for a while
and everyone like i've been using them
for super chat ratings mostly and every
time i
um
was like trying to read super chats i
was vibing so much along with them that
i just felt like
singing them
even even the first time when i heard
them i just wanted to sing along and we
did that every once in a while
but today
i'm gonna probably dedicate a stream to
those
jazzy lo-fi versions
uh they're really chill i really like
them
low fidelity offbeat
so
and i i've noticed the pattern and the
lo-fi remixes
the melody
and the verses and all that are not
really changed
uh they're they're pretty much the same
just
a slow one
um but with the bossa nova
versions this is why i was so confused
when i first started jamming out to them
in the bosa nova versions there's
actually
um they took out usually the second
verse like after the first chorus they
would like get rid of the second verse
and then
replace it with an instrumental solo
that's why i got so confused so before
the stream i was trying to like i was
choosing the songs and trying to figure
out which parts got uh rid of and then
where it would start
again to sing
so i think i think generally i got the
gist of it
generally i think today
and i know the flow i can go with the
flow
[Music]
eh put it
your hand hurts looking at me because i
have my hand up what
what doesn't look weird or anything
looks natural don't you think i can do
this too
is this better
alright so are you guys ready to
i would like to say ready to party but
this is gonna be a chill singing stream
it's not gonna be so much of a like a
party
a little bit more like yeah
you might at the end of it you might
feel like that chicken there
all right so let's start out liv
the first song a lot of these uh
um especially the bossa nova ones
are really really long because they
added a lot of instrumentals so
yeah
it's it might be a bit awkward but
i'm not i'm just gonna we
will just have to listen for it i'll
till the end and i might just be
reviving and you can vibe with me are
you ready for that
mhm
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody clap your
[Music]
foreign
is it okay here okay
swimming swimming
hiki no
no lightning
maybe
[Music]
[Applause]
no music
what what what what what
i heard i saw two comments saying no
music are you are you are you
are your ears like broken or what
okay you really confused me there
i was trying to fix it isn't this uh now
it's still too quiet now i mean now
there's no music but is it self quiet or
two
wait let me see
oh my god
it was fine
okay
okay this is okay now i think
i think the balance should be okay
if it's really like too quiet let me
know let's start again
[Music]
clap your hands
clap your hands today
[Music]
hey
uh
[Music]
a
you guys are really really confusing me
[Music]
go
clap your
[Music]
foreign
actually i wasn't sure if i should rap
here i think yeah
can meanwhile crazy
[Music]
lazy
noodle
[Music]
everybody clap your
go
[Music]
me
okay seems like we're still having i
don't know different opinions on the
audio but i think generally should be
fine the balance
i at the very end i also turned myself
down one more millimeter in obs so huh i
hope i hope it's fine
yeah this yeah low-fly versions are just
like really
b bassy so
they're based thanks to the memberships
thank you thank you for clapping oh this
song was so much clapping i hope your
hands are not tired yet guys
because there's much much more actually
um the next
song i
learned today
i practiced today for this show for you
guys
and i wonder what the song could be
[Music]
sure if i still have it in my memory
properly but
but
it should be fun yeah use your
headphones um i think especially for
this kind of music should be better with
headphones
if you really have issues you okay let
me
change my thingy okay no spark stairs no
unfortunately there's no lo-fi or bossa
nova version of sparks yet
as far as i know
yeah i think if you have headphones
you'd be fine yeah and no but no sparks
unfortunately
unless if you guys know that there's a
low-fi sparks version that i don't know
about then let me know
not no not violet i'm only singing
remixes today guys
i don't know of any violet remixes
either
i'm singing hola
lo-fi and bossa nova remixes yeah
but the next song
is
from my dear dear orange friend
uh
but
for a long time i didn't really um
take the time to practice your songs
but
in the new bossa nova remixes one of
mega's songs
is part of it
lunch with me
it's such a fun song
so
you guys are welcome to vibe with me
lunch with me
[Music]
la
my
[Music]
i already stumbled over my words three
million times meant to
come can i do it again
[Music]
la
oh
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is
with me
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
is
la
[Music]
with
with me
[Music]
such a cute song
man i love dennis voice she's such a
cutie pie
i i wonder if she'll ever listen to
me sing this
i hope she doesn't
mind
but
forever i need to collab with nancy
again for the people who don't know me
and um
me and anything
have a quite quite the bond yeah we've
been uh collabing a lot we've been we've
done some some um
collaborations when i was in in japan
uh karaoke collaborations
and other actually two yeah you two in
person in-person karaoke collabs i
really really love ninety
so next song
i want to sing
this one
say
senpai
[Music]
that was not it
violence
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
a
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
dance
as you might have noticed the
instrumentals are really long
but they're so chill so nice to listen
to i love them so much
yeah
i love these versions
and like in the low five versions they
mostly went for like the whole live uh
original like the bloom songs but with
the bossa nova versions they've been
doing like some solo songs from others
as well
but
let's go back to the lo-fi versions
and sing one of the low-fi versions
low-fi
a song that you all like very much
sing ahoy i'm sorry you guys but i can't
sing songs that i that there are no no
remix versions too
a specific
list that i can go from
where there's already remixes from so
sorry one day i'm sure there will be a
remix of ahoy as well
i mean how could you not remix it
officially from her life side let's go
alright let's sing suspect
[Music]
thinking touching feeling
why you know
[Music]
i know it looking thinking
feeling
understand meaning
meaning of love
are you ready
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
thinking touching feeling why
thinking
touching feeling
understand meaning
meaning of love
are you ready
[Music]
oh
a
[Music]
so
me
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
this song is already so like
censure oak like the sound of it is
already so essential like in the
original but like the lo-fi makes it
even better like oh my god
yeah
but every time every time i sing those
those lines that nobody sent by sang
like
i always have to think of her voice the
way she sings oh my god it kills me
every time
all right
next song
yeah that super high energetic song it
has a bossa nova version
version it's really cute really fun
a little bit more chill than the
original
let's let's go
[Music]
that was a mistake
a
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
m
[Applause]
[Music]
a
uh
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
my
down
[Music]
can you hear me
yes
i don't know if you noticed but
i i sang this song before in the
previous catalogue the original one not
the remix one and if you heard both then
you might have noticed i try to sing
this
more
like
adjusted to the remix like more calm
with more feeling
even though the lyrics are
the lyrics are just funny
but i tried to give it a bit more of a
groove and a smoothness
have you noticed
something yeah
the lyrics are really just funny
so it's like the lyrics don't quite fit
the the style
perhaps
but bosa nova definitely fits better
than the lo-fi version if anything
well there is no low five version so
yeah
oh
yeah these songs are really really long
so just one song takes up so much time
so let's go to the next one immediately
after i take a sip
pickle random super chat thank you oh
thank you also for adding the red thingy
because yeah uh i wrote it i wrote it in
the pin message for everyone who wants
to send the super chat please if you
don't send it in usd or euro please add
red or pink to it if you're sending a
red or pinky so i can acknowledge it
properly because the super chat window
is still broken so i'm doing it for
stream elements today so i wrote read
them today but yeah it just it on stream
elements it all converts it to usd so
you know even in countries where the
value is different uh
i i wouldn't be able to notice so please
write it if you are going to send
something thank you
[Music]
this is one that you guys
liked a lot previously when i sang it
this this kind of started
this whole i need to sing these songs
thingy
candy go around
yeah you know it
[Music]
uh
everybody clap your hands up cool
[Music]
utani
you
[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
dance
[Music]
[Applause]
stand up ring a
[Music]
my
me
[Music]
oh
i
[Music]
foreign
these are so much fun to sing
so much fun
let me let me uh switch uh outfits a
little bit
for no particular reason
i want to be a cat
oh wait
oops
i'm back
yeah
it's kiara field [\h__\h]
oh that lasagna yesterday was yummy wait
that was not yesterday that was a monday
but it feels like it was yesterday
it's just i have always lasagna on my
mind
and next song
i might mess up a little bit so bear
with me i'm not i just tried it out um
if i could vibe to the
remix version of it before the stream it
seemed okay-ish so
should be fine
water first
[Music]
cookie
whoever
my
[Music]
you
foreign
[Music]
a
oh
[Music]
yay
that one is actually like pretty
confusing because the
the melody
is not so
obvious in this instrumental so it gets
like am i really
allowed to sing here but
you just gotta be confident and go
through with it
yeah
have confidence
everyone have confidence
[Music]
next song as well is another one that i
give a first try and have not tried yet
in previous super chat readings or
whatever
and bossa nova
we're back to bossa nova
we signed two lo-fi songs now i'm gonna
sing two bossa nova songs yeah
all right
you guys have confidence
already over now yeah cause these these
take these take a while
okay
let's go
daddy
family diary
[Music]
wait one more time
take free
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
so
oh
[Music]
let's
is
[Music]
our daily diet
is
[Music]
um
oops
[Laughter]
cute song isn't it
very cute song
well
i have
one one more song
maybe two more
depends on you
oh well the next song is a last song
give me a give me a very loud
no
[Music]
is
no
[Music]
me
do
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
you
me
[Music]
thank you everyone for coming to this
concert from atakanasi kiara from our
live english
we hope you enjoyed this concert
on your way back home please don't
forget any of your belongings that you
brought into the concert hall
like umbrellas or
pen nights or towels or your pants or
your jackets or your shoes i don't know
what the hell you took off when you sat
down
thank you
god
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
thank you thank you thank you
thank you everyone wow wow i'm so
popular but yeah i can't believe it wow
wow
wow all these people asking for uncle
even though i was supposed to go i'm
i'm so unprepared i did not expect this
at all
oh my god what what should i sing i have
nothing prepared at all oh my god i
don't know what to sing oh i'm so ah
if only there was a song
that fits this whole theme perfectly oh
that i didn't sing yet uh if only if
only
please listen
[Music]
[Applause]
tell me i can hear it clearly tell me
[Music]
till
tattooed
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
don't break i will never give up don't
break
[Music]
is
oh yeah right it doesn't have this pipe
oh wait wait wait oh yeah it just ends
there i forgot that
oh
[Music]
i've totally forgot that i thought this
was a full version
[Laughter]
oopsy i haven't listened to this whole
uh track in a long time
even though it's my ending song but i
haven't muted normally so
on my side oops oops well maybe yeah
maybe one day uh although let me give
credit by the way because this one is
not by any like
whole live official people or so
and this is a fan made version by umi
busy it's also in my credits because i
always use it for the ending song these
days
yeah
i wonder let me see
nova
spikes
yeah
is there anything that i don't know of
yet no
nope nope
no heart challenger either
well if anyone wants to make something
please do i want to do this again
because um
oops
i left out a lot of uh songs today
anyway because they all take so long and
i still have to practice some more oh
but i hope you enjoyed these and if you
did then i might do this again at some
point soon
[Music]
um
yeah this will be aircraft of course
because it's whole alive originals one
of the ups
and merits of being of singing whole
live originals is that i can archive
them
that would be so cute
i can i can feel it i can see it i can
imagine it it was super relaxing really
thank you
well you know what super chat is also
really relaxing so i think you'll enjoy
that too
i guess i can just play some more of
these
uh bosa nova and low five versions while
i'm writing the super chats hmm
it was super chill about the whole time
thank you
yeah i'm glad you guys like it some of
these songs i
i prepared uh today and wasn't so sure
yet about but i think i think it was all
right all right all right
oh
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you for the
sweet feedback thank you soon
yeah
i appreciate it thank you oh thank you
the dj chicken
yeah he totally made all this possible
totally me yeah yeah yeah give him some
good feedback give the chicken
here some good feedback so that he'll
feel better about himself
[Music]
yeah it's a nice
nice uh chill
version of karaoke normally it's always
very exciting and energetic songs but
today it was more like let's relax guys
it's been some tough weeks some busy
weeks
let's just
you know vibe together
[Music]
it's actually like
really fun to sing these because i i get
to like play a little bit with my voice
depending on the song
i get to like give it some some more
feeling and and try to mix it with some
some whispery parts and some
it sounds weird but like moany money
parts
yeah
all right let me put these uh
[Music]
no more singing sorry guys let's go over
to the other screen
let's see what's what chaos awaits me
today
oh my god ah music oh
well there we go at least there's no
chickens making up today
they like this they like this
in the chat
no chicken's making us
i always just felt a little bit awkward
hey he still has a party hat on from
from the party we just had the loki the
lo-fi loki party
okay so i at the moment wait let me let
me check in again maybe they fixed it
although i doubt it but let's see if
they fixed it by now it's been in the
beginning of the stream and it was not
fixed
[Music]
yeah it doesn't work what the frick
all right no problem
no problem we'll read that we'll read it
from the stream elements although this
is like really not not i'm not used to
this but
we'll do it like this
[Music]
yeah um what the hell youtube it's been
like days this is like this since like
sunday maybe
ah the stickers on my laptop
they're not being sold as far as i know
currently but they would be perfect
stickers right yeah they're by christina
manzanita
on twitter
and i i use her art a lot uh recently
and she's also the maker of my new um
members only emotes
please check out her twitter
i take her entire stock me too
come on
is little apple in spanish oh really
that's what it means christina little
apple
you're a little apple ringochan
oh manzanita really actually speaking of
spanish
i've i've i've started watching a new
netflix show
uh
new as in for me neil not not new on
netflix
uh
jane the virgin
is what i've been watching uh the past
few days
it's quite all right it's um a little
bit exaggerated here and there but
generally i enjoy it quite a lot it's
really fun i'm in the first season right
now
um
yeah i like it i'm hooked because
with every episode it gets more and more
complicated
and deeper and deeper
jane the virgin
is the
name of the show
that's no valence point but but that
itself is not a telenovela it's just
like i mean i guess they're kind of like
trying to add a little bit of a
telenovela feeling to it but but it's
not supposed to be a telenovela i mean
from what i've seen in the show they
show telenovelas and that is not really
like
doesn't match up i mean i've never
personally seen them tell novella but
from what i see in the show
where they show telenovelas on the tv
and so on it's not the same but
yeah i i see how they like maybe add a
few elements of it you know there like a
the tackiness of it
a little bit but generally no that's not
a terrible villain
anyway i'm feeling a bit hot
and ideas are reflected oh
i can see some inspiration yeah
i feel a bit weird right now i need to
drink more water
[Music]
i cooked today unbelievable
i made the hungarian dish called goulash
i just drink more water i feel weird
i don't know what the english name is
where does it have an english name
but it's called grass in glass
glass
in germany
the more often i say it and the more i
read you guys saying gouda
gouras it confuses me
yeah these are there is a there's a few
types of gunas
um
like um there's a type where you put a
beef in it um
and like it's always is there that's
really nice beef beef glass
it's really nice but then there's also
like potato and um
sausage goulash which is also really
nice
the the soup sauce thing is a little bit
different
it doesn't exist
anyway it was quite decent but i kind of
used like
like
like a powder
um
like base for the soup instead of making
it from scratch
so
in theory i also
can't do it from scratch but this made
it much easier and faster and more
efficient yeah so
yeah
i'm happy with it
so
and we haven't read super chat in a long
time i'm so sorry guys i know a lot of
you guys look forward to it and i also
felt shocked
the past two days that i wasn't able to
read super chats because i wanted to
talk to you guys
um and i really want to
read the ones from uh
the
from saturday yeah i really want to read
the ones on saturday
but we're still fine it would have to go
to like i don't know 20k or so in order
to
make the previous ones disappeared i
think we're fine for a while
no super chat's no life youtube stole
our tangents they [\h__\h] did
i missed so much readings oh really
oh man
it's post-traumatic non-super chat shock
uh
well well well
it's okay well at least
in exchange i streamed minecraft really
long yesterday
no flash chats
huh
the chat readings are fun i'm glad you
guys think so
i'm glad i can make it fun for you guys
because i know like it can get very
tedious
and if you just go for it like
then well you might finish it early but
it's not really fun to watch is it
so i always try from from the very
beginning on i always try to make it
somehow interesting for you guys
i mean there's probably still things
that i could add to make it more
interesting but
um still i think the current way we do
it is okay
i hope
remember the one time
let's go remember the one time when
reading super chats was so tough on my
voice i mean it still is but um what i i
i recorded my donkey shin
and just said the names and then played
the dangations
after it to save some of my voice
we only did that once because i felt bad
like how
how automatic it sounded uh
and only the name was live i just felt
bad about it even though it would save
me a lot of voice trouble
oh
no i have never done it since then
so this
foreign
robotari
robotoni
[Music]
you mean you mean the the recording
thingy
record every single viewer's name then
oh my god i'm so sorry but this is
roberto
piano text to speech oh interesting that
would be useful too
it always hurts i know
sorry
roll botory
self-automated super japanese but but
then yeah i mean that would be great and
um super efficient and all but then
there would be nothing personal about it
so
yeah
oh it's just just now i kind of like
realized this
this
bright uh
reflection spot on my glasses
never really kind of like paid attention
to that
oh
yeah
oh should we get reading
[Laughter]
sure read it
okay
let's see let's see how this works on
stream elements i'm at the very bottom
i'm just going to go to the top
to the top
i'm excited for tomorrow tomorrow's
stream
is a
garlic phone two times
i'm starting guiding phone phone two
times tomorrow
oh
okay okay i need to read the super chats
mr cat's biggest action
this is really like
not so pretty to see but i hope i
please bear with me if today i
like
not acknowledge
like reds and pinks sometimes because
it's
it's not that pretty
on stream elements
so
[Music]
it's a little bit of a mess
okay
which super chat uh the ones from today
because the other ones i can't access i
you know i i thought on monday i was
like oh youtube's gonna fix it until the
next day right
um
and
on monday i wasn't even really aware of
stream elements just yet so on tuesday
it was still unfixed but i was like okay
it's been two days so sasukani
you we would be able to expect that by
the next day they should have it fixed
right right so i was like already aware
of stream elements on tuesday but i was
like ah they'll fix it until the next
day for sure
so now is wednesday right
name wednesday yeah today is wednesday
and it was still a fix so i turned on
stream elements i'm sorry it was kind of
late but
i i thought that you two could do
something
what the hell man
um
so did i yeah what the hell men
can't like i want to like i'm so close
to tweeting at them but
i don't know man
i still go on twitter and be like at
youtube what the [\h__\h] are you doing turn
on my super chats again like i want to
read them what are you doing
but i'm sure they already
work on it probably
i really want to tweet at them though
but then
i don't want to like
like do something
bad i don't know i feel like maybe
that's a little bit of a karen move yeah
i know my rights
you guys coming up with colors that
don't exist on super chats
[Music]
thank you
the attention today is my birthday and
my birthday wishes that i wish all your
dreams come true and also i wish i could
witness every moment of your dream
coming true
well then
well you are already witnessing a lot of
them
because uh
this is a dream come true being able to
have so many people here watching me is
definitely a dream come true
yeah
happy birthday to you
thank you thank you for supporting me
thank you soon i hope you had a lovely
birthday
and uh
please take care of yourself yeah
thank you
that is a pinky i guess
i'm not guy is that a pinky because like
it uh
it should be a pinky is it like a
um
is it a red
in which
in which thingy in which uh
canadian dollars see it converts it
to
yeah eighty dollars so that's confusing
okay okay so that's the right one okay
no it only shows us dollars here it
already converts it automatically that's
why i asked you guys to like
write the um
color of it inside oh well
uh
thanks for the great minecraft stream
yesterday have you guys thought of where
you're putting the portal to the japan
server there are so many great spots
like the torii gate the giant kotoni or
and maybe hatsuma will let you use her
tower lots of possibilities actually no
not at all um yeah
nothing
no idea uh still also something that
uh
i uh
don't
uh don't i can't i can't say much about
it
it might be happening but i was told to
not like specifically say it's
happenings but i already did so it's
kind of too late for that
uh
that's why i tried not to mention it
anymore
but i already said it
like i don't know i didn't i i didn't
know it was like i don't know supposed
to be a secret or something but i
mentioned it like ages ago and then
weeks weeks later
after i already mentioned it like five
times
weeks later like maybe two months later
or so after the first time i mentioned
it
i was there was like a general message
like yo um
please don't talk about merging the
servers because technical blah blah blah
[Music]
now then i was like
oh yummy
oh
ah
yeah
about that
yeah but well now i mean
yeah so that's that thank you tanaka for
the red super chat
thank you
yeah i think we all talked about it but
i felt i felt like uh
anyway uh
isn't it if it's a bit awkward it's a
bit awkward
um
definition is subjective any time review
is a party to me
if that is so then i like parties out of
uh
all of a sudden because generally
parties are like
nothing to me
i don't know
why but like like ugh
like this goes and stuff like that is
absolutely not my thing i hate that
stuff
[Music]
i once had like a friend um
who did like djing
and and um
i don't know i i really like that friend
but it kind of feels like we're like in
different worlds you know
but even then like i love her and i want
to support her so
um
she had this we had this dj
gig in a relatively small like life
house underground life house
and um
yeah i was like
for once i don't want to be the lame one
for once i want to be
like cool and
hang out with her in her world and join
her
so
i went there and it was first of all it
was like
like a little bit empty so
you stand out more
if you were not cool
so i was like i came in and the first
thing i did was just like
stand at a table
and like
i was like really really stiff and my
friend she already knew like everyone
she was like yo what up hey hey hey you
you how you doing man dude yo what's up
and like really like socializing and and
connecting with everyone and already
ordering alcohol and everyone was like
really cool and i'm like whoa it's not
my world
and um
then uh the thing is also i don't drink
alcohol so
like when when when
i was offered like alcohol i was like
uh-huh no thank you
and they're like really what about this
what about this what about this one come
on come on you don't like this one even
i'm like no i don't i don't like alcohol
in general
and then they offer like drinks that
have like only a little bit of alcohol
in it in it and they're like oh come on
you won't taste this alcohol come on
come on you won't taste this one this
really barely tastes like alcohol at all
and then i'm like no no even look like
zero zero zero zero zero point one
percent
alcohol i still taste it and i still
hate it so
yeah
at some point they finally understand
and let it go but it's really always
difficult to get to that point and
anyway so
um my friend was having all this fun
and i i literally just came to be there
and like kind of support her and i don't
know maybe for once let her think that i
am i'm cool
and not [\h__\h] lame
and then at some point so she has her dj
thingy
and
well
i i made my way over to the very very
front
and uh
instead of like standing somewhere in
the middle of the dance floor because
that's absolutely absolutely impossible
i i went to the very front where the the
fence is and just clinged onto the fence
really really clingy
and the the only thing i could really do
because i'm just shy
i just well sometimes the stuff like
this yeah
woo hoo
hey
that's about it but there was also like
a lot of the songs i didn't know that
she played but there was one song she
played ariana grande once i think it was
break free yeah that that's the only
time where i was a bit more like
[Music]
this is
when there's finally a song where you
know the lyrics too then you
suddenly out of nowhere
get really loud and like yeah nobody's
so [\h__\h] yeah
she played this one for me for sure
uh yeah um
but besides that that there were like
all these other people i mean it was it
was really not that full but there were
the other people who were like really
dancing and doing like cool
cool moves like break dancing and
and i don't know shuffling and every
damn shuffling
and i looked at them and i felt
damn i mean in theory in theory i can do
like choreographies and stuff but first
i have to learn it i can't do like
freestyle
so i i wish i could do that man but i i
can't like i mean no actually you know
what in my room if i'm in my room
listening to music i dance freestyle on
my own
in my room with no audience but if i'm
in a club or something like that no
[\h__\h] way
no [\h__\h] way i'm gonna just show my my
my private freestyle moves
no way
i'm not gonna
embarrass myself here
although there was one point where the
cool people who were dancing like cool
people um
like tried to get me into it and it was
actually successful because they
tried to show me like really simple
steps from one side to science i with
some hand simple hand movements really
really really simple
i don't know what i just swallowed it
must have been
air anyway so that
that kind of like an idle step but an
idle step i can do it it was a little
bit more of a cool version of an idle
step
yeah and that that i was able to follow
for a while and i felt really cool when
i was doing that with the cool people
like yay
yay
yay i can dance to the beach as well yay
i'm part of the cool people now
and they even gave me a flag i think
they had flags like tiny flags so then i
was like waving the flag in in revlon
yay yay
okay but generally i was mostly clinging
on to either a table or a fence and
did not feel like i was supposed to be
there at all
so i was very happy
when it was over
ah
yeah jenna's a popular one now
uh
i guess i don't know man
just because i have a lot of audience
here doesn't mean that i'm like
strong in social situations now
outside of this
stream thingy i mean
it depends like okay
generally i would say i'm strong when it
comes to social situations if i want to
but um
not in like you know these
club thingies or so
yeah
if it's like uh
just like getting to know strangers
uh
yeah stuff like that
or like having a dinner
uh uh then yeah oh hi
mom nerds your elite
pretend
um
we can't i think you guys can relate to
my story right
that was once in
four or five years now once in eight
years maybe that i went to a club
and it wasn't even it was a club in
japan so
i think
that is already like
very different from clubs in like europe
or america or whatever like
i don't want to say
it's labor but
um
i have to say
they are already like
more calm
uh
it's just calmer
yeah more reserved yeah tamer table yeah
tamer tamer yeah yeah yeah yeah i think
yeah every street yeah yeah yeah yeah
thank you
yeah more on your level yeah if anything
like that's also the reason why
the only
the only like
festival music festival that i've ever
been to
ever was not in europe or so but it was
in japan
i could i cannot imagine
going to a festival
overseas like outside of japan
music festival
because
i don't know it scares me
and
yeah
even in japan i still felt like i'm not
part of this these party people
kiara imagine
[Music]
oh my god can i do another tangent
oh that's kind of awkward
one more reason why i don't like going
to these kind of places
like big festivals
was like really long because it had like
a lot of artists
so it was like i don't know eight hours
long or so
with lots of different sets so i went
from the very beginning because there
was someone i wanted to see in the very
beginning and then there was also
someone i wanted to see in the ending
so i mean somewhere in between
you want to go somewhere right
and i i i i checked it out but i don't
know just it disgusted me i couldn't go
i couldn't go
and also like every every freaking
one of those boxes was a traditional
japanese
one
squatting
no
which actually i guess makes it better
if you think about it because you don't
have to touch it
but still it'll look disgusting and if
you don't okay
let's change the topic
uh but yeah i just think that's that
says probably a normal a norm in like
festivals anyway
you won't see me in those kind of places
anymore
you won't see me there anymore
how was dokami watch my stream for
monday i talked a lot about my dokomi
experience
i showed pictures and everything talked
about the podcast and the meet and greet
and the dinners and on other days and
and the concert everything so check that
stream out you will not regret it
i got dragged to edc one time
uh electric dance something oh my god
it's a nightmare for anyone that hates
those kind of scenarios
yeah
it was fun experiencing it like once
um
because i just really the artist that
order i really love them
so that was really special to me
but thank god it was in japan and not
any other country
now
the only kind of moss bit that i've seen
before is at idle concerts
uh
i guess that's also a mosh pit
i i like that kind of moss bit where
they run in circles they they like even
though even though the whole concert
hall is packed
with people and everyone's like sticking
to one another when it gets the point
where there is uh where they do the
circle
they suddenly have so much space in the
middle
and everyone runs in in one big circle
and i was once part of that not only
once probably several times
yeah
that's fun
that's a fun kind of
mosh pits
that circle
different kind of mosh pit
they don't crash with it ah they
actually do
as well
it depends on what kind of idol concert
if it's like a
more underground idol can't say that
they do they do
they like jump like they attack each
other with jumps
[Music]
but it's still very civil
uh
because i haven't been testing for a
while huh where was i
here maybe
i definitely read this one no did i
where the hell was that
i'm somewhere here
okay
no i read this one yeah this this is the
one this is the one i found it
if i got my niche because he was like
party definition is subjective any time
of you is a party to me this is how i
went into this huge tencent
oh man
god of amiibo thank you sir and
every time i hear a blue clapper i just
imagine a white lion riding a roller
coaster it's so weird
so you imagine
empire riding a roller coaster or an
actual white lion
white lion
that's an interesting imagination you
have there
errone mcnugget duncan
[Music]
what's his name um
so it's a i think it's a korean silver
chat
but it just says
oh this
circle circle circle
circle circle circle circle
[Music]
i wonder if he's here
i don't i don't see him here
okay okay okay okay
apparently it's red is okay okay okay
okay
oh okay okay okay okay okay okay
i think this one
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
fruity as hell noise
alex dankessen
there's something about the white
castings oh oh that blesses my ears
what do you mean oh
fc8 magic face duncan that's really not
very specific
at least not without context
looking for the top document
oh wow
[Music]
for the red super chat
just a pack of random super chat thank
you
[Music]
thank you for the support thank you very
much i appreciate it i hope you enjoyed
today's karaoke
especially the piccolo song that's so
much fun to sing
unknown
thank you for the pinky
yay
no text of it apparently
but still thank you for being here today
and watching my song thank you
midnight thank you and after most prime
thanks for the pinky
this chill karaoke is exactly what you
need right after a stressful work day to
come down and relax thank you shin boss
because of your wonderful voice i can
feel all energy coming back already to
be ready and fully charged for the next
day
sweet
really
thank you optimus prime
i'm glad that you get some energy from
this
you will need it because tomorrow we
have two streams
and you
might want to watch both of them
also i'm still wondering the garlic
phone
collab
would probably be fine with just one
point of view
but i'm actually not sure what's planned
if we should all have it at one point of
view what do you guys think
because
in the end even if there's only one
point of view you see
what everyone's drawing
afterwards anyway but i guess it's yeah
you can see the thought behind it
and yeah i guess
everyone's point of view would make
sense too
um
yeah i think it would be fine too
both both works
difficult difficult choice multiple is
excessive
one is probably you know what let's make
a poll
it's not really like
it's not gonna be my decision i guess
i'm gonna ask the other girls what they
think but i'm gonna have your input too
to make my own
decision a
guiding phone en collab
one pov
all pov
[Music]
got it
if it's only one then it would probably
be on iris channel
it's a first full collapse
oh point of view 70
69 nice
68.
um okay oh yes so
more people say
all point of views
you mm-hmm it would be on my channel the
one that i do with the artists is on my
channel only yes
[Music]
one sounds good because it adds a
surprise it kind of does yeah
[Music]
but like if we're all in voice chat
um
at the same time and like five people
are like struggling with whatever and
you don't know what they're struggling
with
um
i don't know it seems like like they're
they're they're trained or flawed or
whatever i feel like maybe it would be
interesting to have their point of views
but i don't know i i am personally when
it comes to big group collabs i'm
personally
i personally prefer to only have it on
one channel if that is
possible
i prefer to have only one so that
the audience
gathers at one place
instead of everyone spreading all over
the place
but i mean if it's a game that
should be in more than one point of view
then of course that makes sense
anyway okay oh i see i see you guys
i'll ask i'll ask the girls
thank you for your input
okay where was i oh yeah optimus prime
thank you
for thanks for the pinkie duncan you
always managed to bring me back down
after a shitty day at work i'm melting
on my chair from how chilled i am at the
moment
thank you
kiara thank you for blessing my ears
once again you're the best i never get
enough listening off listening to you
sing thank you
i'm happy
to hear that i'm glad you like my
singing
and i hope your work is not always that
shitty
i hope you generally
don't have shitty days that often
hmm
a soulmate yeah youtube kind of wrote a
similar thing
are you guys working at the same place
are you do you have the same job perhaps
you too
thank you fro fro
owl jin donkey
thank you thank you
she saw the gondra thank you for the red
super chat
thanks for singing to us thank you your
voice is really soothing after stressful
day again
why are you guys all so stressed out
today what happened at work
oh no
i hope i i hope tomorrow will be a
better day for you i'm sure of it
tomorrow will be a better day
oh if today was [\h__\h] then just look
forward to tomorrow eat some lasagna or
whatever
work
i'll always be stressing yeah for me too
though for me too a little bit in brazil
so much to do
i have so many tasks on my list hmm
it's difficult to get to them
[Music]
unknown
thank you for the pinky i got into a car
accident today no one was hurt and was
feeling down then you started the
singing stream and i felt so much better
thank you as always for feeling my heart
healing my heart wow
i'm glad nothing happened oh my god you
get the first
the first few words scared me but i'm
glad everything's okay gary garza
um
please uh i don't know you may maybe
have absolutely nothing to do with it
but please always be careful
with uh
cars
cars are dangerous even when you're not
driving them did you know that
cars are really
dangerous i hate cars
a car once hurt me
when it was already parked
even though i was
in it
i almost lost my eye
because of a car
true story
yeah
although you could say it's my stupidity
um
all right well i will i will elaborate
so i was i was in a car
um on the passenger seat
it was raining and it was dark
it was dark and i was wearing uh i was
wearing um
color lenses
for fun
and i don't generally wear glasses or
anything
or
um lenses contact lenses or anything but
on that day i was wearing them
so
well we arrived at our destination
parked
and
got out of the car
and i hope i
i i
i put my legs outside
i don't i really don't know how exactly
this happened i don't understand either
i put my legs outside i stand up
[Music]
how did i do that and for some reason
the edge of the car door
of the window so the top part the edge
the corner of it the corner of it
somehow
bumped into my left eye
the corner of it the corner of the car
door
because it was so dark i don't know man
it's
bumped into my eye
literally into my eyeball
and i felt it
and i lost my lens
because of that it was so dark and rainy
that i couldn't find the lens on the
floor anymore but that's how i lost that
lens and almost lost my eye
and i was shocked like what the [\h__\h]
just happened
and it was holding my eye i was like oh
my god it actually like kind of hurt
what what the [\h__\h] was that
and i was scared that like my eye was
like dead
but nothing happened and i still have
very good eyesight um but i will always
question myself
oh i did that
can you imagine what you have to imagine
though
what
is there like a
you know it has to be an illustration of
a car door
of an open open car door
let's see let me go through
i want to make it easier for you guys
try to try to understand even though
there's it's not going to make it better
i guess
the lens safe i maybe it did maybe it
did i mean the lens is thin though like
it's not like the lens is like
five
centimeters thick or something like that
it's not
it's like really thin like i don't know
one millimeter thin
like a normal lens a normal
contact lens but i don't know man it
might have saved my life in my eye
i almost got a pirate verb
i could have been a pirate boob
could have been so cool man
no i'm glad nothing happened i was
really shocked in that moment this is
another like stupid accident like this
no this is even stupider than the skiing
accident
i mean the skiing accident is more like
shoganai can't do much about it it
happens
was the door not fully open and no well
i opened it i opened the door and then
poked my eye
with it
so [\h__\h] cars
[Laughter]
um
it makes the cringe like nails on the
chalkboard
this is like a humming story right kind
of
are you going to attack all car doors
now
oh man so everyone be careful you can
never put you let your guard down even
when the car is
stopped and it's your car
and even if you're in control of the
situation
ah
i don't have a problem with our kfp car
though
i was not in control in that moment
all right continuing
i hope gary garza that this um cheered
you up
the story
i almost lost a finger closing car a car
door oh my god
were you the one closing the door then
well this is again our stupidity i'm
stupid you're stupid we're both stupid
we're both stupid
how about scooters i i have one
um
sky
not very visible scar from my childhood
that i had from a scooter
although it was never song soon song
song
it was never sued son
it's just healed on its own and i still
have it but it's like really
not very visible well i have it from a
scooter
yeah it's ages ago
no stitches
[Music]
pinky oh wait that might be
might be a
red one because it's converted
i don't know you didn't add red or pink
to it tai chi so it's your fault if i
did it wrong
but i appreciate it nonetheless whether
or not it's a pinky or red one or a blue
one or a green one or whatever thank you
thai tea as always thank you soon
if it's a red one then you would get a
kiss but
now i don't know if it's a red one
hmm
here is a questionable
questionable kiss
was it red i i'm pretty yeah i can
imagine it being red
thank you for the membership
i'm going to
cars um sand two incarnations of true
evil
thank you
pineapple
i love pineapples
and thank you
that could be a pinky but you didn't
mark it either i'm just gonna assume
it's a pinky
thank you for the pinky thank you for
chill vibes and
a beautiful performance thank you very
much
thanks for listening and supporting
i appreciate it thank you
thank you hopefully i'll see you in the
next
as well
i was blooming to you because of the
collab stream oh
i wonder if you've been liking it
well i guess i guess you are liking it
takasana
always nice to see you hope you're doing
well thank you for supporting me every
time
i proceed
yeah jim tracy down get your naked
chicken dang i should pull down some
clothes for god's sake
thank you for the pinky
yo kiana okay streams are my favorite i
had a great stream today it's a great
time today thank you thank you can't
wait for the next one thank you
thank you very much i'm glad you enjoyed
it
how could you not these versions are
amazing i love them
sean uh free one for uk dancing
thank you for the pinky one of the best
candle okay your voice is so perfect i
love it so much
i'll use this later in bed it will help
me fall asleep i really love you kiara
okay and this one especially my oh she's
a top idol indeed
thanks so much for everything thank you
tom thanks for listening tuning in today
on this lovely evening
hello smoovie this movie has been so
freaking clingy i don't know what to do
with her she used to be like more
um the opposite of clinky
that is a red super chat dell style
she used to be more tsun tsun way more
than
but i don't know
she grew older
and now she's super super
super
sweet hi baby
[Music]
the way she looks at me
it melts my heart
no
she's just lying on the ground on but
next to my chair looking at me
go pet her no it's okay i already pet
her like for five hours today
honestly she gets like hours and hours
of petting each [\h__\h] day
and while i sleep i also like hold her
for hours like i have my hand on her on
her belly for hours
i mean i i could pet her 24 hours if i
would if i had a third hand hand
i wouldn't mind petting her for 24 hours
per day
yeah stream so much
but
five hours is not enough for
motivation once more
[Music]
um
speaking of
speaking of you
speaking of cat
[Music]
gummies movie
you sure
[Music]
she wants my attention
you just want attention
you don't want my heart
all right
i don't know where to help john chris is
but that's okay junk is also being cutie
pie every goddamn day
changes
[Music]
and where was i here looking for the top
foundation
max duncan
um
need some advice trying to make amends
of someone yet it's just not working
seems like they hate me what should i do
like if it's not going to work then why
bother
well yeah
um i would need more details of the
situation but let's okay let's say you
had a fight the person is mad at you
because you did something if you
apologized for it
and tried to you
know improve whatever you did
and
the person still doesn't give oh
slowpoke is back and the person still
doesn't give a [\h__\h] then well what can
you do
yeah what can you possibly do but i also
think you it you don't have to feel
obligated to
apologize or anything
if you feel like you were right i mean
often people who think like that are
often not right but you're always gonna
leave some some space for doubt
because you might be right in that
situation maybe the other person was the
ridiculous one
and maybe you were actually right yeah
so
in that case
the other person is being ridiculous
so
i would say
don't do anything
uh
but it really depends i don't know your
situation i don't know the details
but if if like
if you really try to make amends and the
person still doesn't appreciate it and
doesn't give a [\h__\h] then the person is
not really worth
your friendship anyway
yeah if you tried and
she or he doesn't
want to cooperate
then it might be better to be without
that person
there's just some some kind of people
who are just really really troublesome
for example my best friend
she's the least troublesome person i
know
and i've had other friends in the past
who were really really troublesome who
were always about the drama who always
needed to like
create some drama out of [\h__\h] nowhere
and those are the kind of people
you don't really need
you don't really need them and i'm glad
i already got rid of some of them oh
hell yeah
hell yeah oh my god don't even get me
started
drama
i'm i'm really happy with my print best
friend
sweetie cutie pie
hey duncan ghost phantom duncan a ghost
phantom duncan skye thank you for the
pinky
oh
a lovely chill cutter okay but this
super chat is not for me it's for the
2500k discord member jimmy fryer penguin
that stands for jfp for some reason
sus
i mean you can't abbreviate it with jfp
that's kind of sus
and this name is serious he sent at
least three red super chats on monday
because his birthday's on the 8th august
oh i still couldn't read it oh no
happy birthday
related but still
happy belated birthday congratulations
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear jimmy
yay
sorry i caught it so late youtube is
being a [\h__\h] right now
but i hope you're having a great
birthday or you had a great birthday and
lots of cake
got some presents
and lots of love for everyone from
everyone that can't speak anymore also
please stay healthy take care of
yourself
yeah and thank you for the love and
support
i'm happy to have you as part of kfp
hopefully not jfp
oh no wait that was a pinky but you say
he sent red superchat so here's a
a bit delayed but also
early red super chat piss
del star duncan blackfridge and duncan
gman1514 thank you
one uh
i look forward to a stressful day next
time i suppose
hey if you miss this room then you
better watch the archive
thank you for a red super chat
reddish green super chat maybe it's red
might be green who knows it's a mystery
now i know
you can't hide that from me
that's in us dollars anyway so it gets
converted into us dollars it doesn't get
converted at all
you cannot fool me
you would have to bamboozle me with
another currency
as long as it's us dollars you cannot
hide from me
i see what you're doing and trying to be
funny
can't play any tricks on me here
ah
a habit to shout del star
i can see right through you
thank you for the support
is
it was so beautiful i'm joining the
kiana fan club looking forward to voting
for games with investors
congrats for your new mic it's so crazy
i can't imagine it getting better
investors
back in the days you guys were not
employees but you were investors i don't
know when i kind of changed that when
did i
like i don't know it kind of
it feels like that happened so naturally
smoothly that transition
in the beginning i was asking you guys
to invest into kfp
i'm still an investor
i mean you i guess you guys are awesome
yeah still kind of investors because as
employees you're actually paying
salary to me
i improved my marketing strategy yeah
i don't know when i did that how did
that happen
technically still investors perhaps yeah
i don't remember like officially like
being like okay from today on you guys
are employees
but very interesting slowpoke thank you
thank you
oh my god what is it with these last
moments red super jets
we're close to the end guys
have some support oh wait why don't we
do the name first name first this one
maria thank you for the red super chat
have some self-respect movie and stay
standoffish next thing we know you'll be
joining chongas in the nowhere food club
no she will never it's movie aussie no
more dd chunkers movie club
what
why she's just being more
clingy there's nothing bad about it
although i
the difficult
i don't know who to pet when both are
being clingy
i try to
um pet them both
it doesn't always work
thank you though um
yeah this movie will
never not like wet food she goes
absolutely crazy over it every goddamn
morning
every time she sees my eyes open i
already told this before but when when
i'm on band and she's of course also in
the bed
and she looks over
the moment i have my eyes open she sees
me
and she's like meow meow meow meow meow
you have feet can i use them
sometimes i use my feet to pet them as
well yes sometimes but generally they're
fairly close to me i prefer to pet them
with my hands because it gives me more
of a petting sensation than it does with
my feet
i want to feel it i want to feel the
fluff between my fingers
softest fluff ever
that meowing summoned my cat if i would
do it two times more so mine would have
also
charged into my room probably
toes
also like they if i just do it for a
moment they respect it
if i pet them with my foot
but if i do it more than just one moment
they attack my foot they feel like it's
a toy or something so it's dangerous
the headbutt and per combo said that's
the best when they give you headbutts
oh
it's the cutest thing ever
no
spanking of being heim
thank you for the red silver jet welcome
back i just got back too my cats are all
over me like velcro
i don't understand the velcro reference
but
but i get the i got the cat reverence
a fellow cat person
dan kitchen thank you for the red super
i'm not a cat but
i hope you still
like me
i know velcro is uh i know what it is
but
it's devil still i mean i guess i guess
i guess it's so
okay
reference
[Music]
i get it but i feel like magnets or
something would have been a better
reference
my cats stick to me like magnets i feel
like that would be better mm-hmm
yeah
thank you
dark attack thank you also
great concert at dokomiya while she is
the greatest thank you did you watch it
on twitch
the role reversal in the manga reading
was a wonderful idea ah
role reversal
i don't really see it as a real reversal
because
we rather than i mean
they're they don't perfectly affect our
personalities but we read it in the most
fitting way i guess according to the the
viewers
but
[Music]
i look forward to your future streams
especially with phoenix mom yeah please
be careful on conventions but of course
you will viva la chiang aviva hot wings
thank you
yeah i'm over cautious anyway so don't
worry
don't worry
i cannot not be
careful
at this point so
yeah
thank you thank you for your support
and your concern
thank you
thank you for watching my dokomi
performance
everyone even though it was not on
youtube everyone who came over to twitch
to watch it and support me there it
really means a lot to me thank you
thank you you guys are the best
it was a special day for me very special
black friction thank you also for a red
super chat
this is a membership renewal no it's not
it wouldn't even cost 100
anyway
membership's very cheap uh
please join membership thank you
you don't have to know you don't have to
we have guided phone this week with
members only
you can't prove it no i can't because i
filtered everything
and to show me only simple chats
and it says here black version sent a
hundred dollars super chat
you're telling me stream elements is
lying to me
or are you lying to me why you lying to
me always
i thought i could trust you
thanks for the listen
welcome
also yeah
black fortune kissy
and delta thank you for the super chat
what's behind you a chair
yes
i know what's behind you
the back of your chair
surprised you didn't think i would see
huh
oh i see you though
i got my eyes on you
i'm on the stool no [\h__\h] way
how did you know
elvis thank you for the rest of the
chat i hope you had a lot of fun and
doko me it must have been a pretty
tiring weekend but you deserve it i know
you work hard but don't push yourself so
much i love you gentlemen
[Music]
i really love gemma
oh man elvis
i'm not gonna give you a kiss because
you sent the super chat to genma you'll
never get a kiss from genma eva though
so
was it worth it was it worth it
i don't actually know the song and
there's a high chance that that is not
in our
um list of songs we can sing
but yeah i don't know it
jay frosty thank you and this look
around thank you for the pinky that's
why your catnip platform a while back
would be great for like two seconds then
a terrible idea slash regret for a
lifetime
that's why wait what's
with what what's that
what did i say
i will because they attack my feet
when my cats are high on catnip they
they rarely are because i really give
them catnip but they um
they just they don't really like attack
things they just
like like roll their back on the ground
so much the whole time they go really
crazy about that
they cuddle with the floor
yeah
really intensely but they don't really
go aggressive they don't attack anything
they just i mean they aggressively
cuddle
uh but no harm is done
thank you
stan dewey
thank you gets better and better all the
time thank you
gd thank you
for the pinky
thanks mate
thank you mate thank you soon i
appreciate it
meme dude
don't worry i'm reading them and elm lee
duncan thanks for the pinky my greatest
achievement this year would be pushing
my friend to the rabbit hole and make
them a kfp as well
it's double happiness towards your
stream with friend love your attention
yeah
i can see that would be fun and like
having someone to
like
talk about whole life and be like yo did
you see her stream today that was so
[\h__\h] funny speaking of funny streams
today uh mannin's
show was
[\h__\h]
amazing was a blast
she's a genius i don't know who
i don't know if she wrote the script for
all of that but
if she did then she's a genius
she could be a professional writer for
something like that
[Music]
if if you understand japanese fluently
then you myself
had the time of your life during her
show today
was amazing she's
she's such a comedian
such an entertainer she has the blood to
be an entertainer like it's her destiny
so glad she's in her life
what would the world be without her
it would be such a sad place oh man
yeah surprised luna didn't pass out yeah
surprise she got number one
yeah japanese style tv show
guess know what to watch later you have
to
probably there are already clips out
anyway so you could even watch like
translated clips too
it was so much fun
since last saturday you're in the rabbit
hole you're very new
wait last saturday doesn't mean you
doesn't mean wait where
i wanna know now what because saturday
was dokomi did you find me for dokomi
or
what was the reason you found me
i want to know
i'm looking at the comments
please tell me
[Music]
watching since day one thank you
interrogation time
no reply yet
where is my reply
no definitely pressure
where is he
tell us
how did you find me
he's probably writing a whole paragraph
right now
how did you find me
[Music]
i was in the audience
okay even and supporting you with my pen
lines not me why it was actually
impersonated they'll give me your skins
thank you soon [\h__\h] cool
let's point me for duncan
thank you
penn right gang yo
yo
what's good
nice
so cool yeah then biscuits had
conflicted
you cannot leave kfb anymore once you
enter there is no exit
thank you for the support
yata
wow that's that's even more special like
finding me not for like the internet or
finding me like in person at a
convention
uh
at the at the concert yeah it's even
more special
your first impression of me is a concert
of at an in-person convention
nice
thank you
er
where was i here elm lee
thanks for the pinky no that's the one i
just read thank you so thank you
that's how we talked about rabbit holes
thank you good job of putting your
friend into the rabbit hole
black christian thank you for a red
super chat
you just want to tell me you love me
i love you too
[Music]
thank you what's wrong
so lovey-dovey today
must be happy because i have been
haven't read super chats in a long time
thank you
thank you i'm getting a membership that
i guess that means i'm a chicken now
if you're just getting it now know that
you're first an egg but thank you you
look forward to becoming a chicken
and
and something else in the future thank
you
i don't know if you already remembered
but thank you for the membership if you
already did no no you didn't do it yet
i see it
but whenever you do it
look forward to being an egg be careful
someone might drop you
but that's i guess nothing that you can
be careful about the person who handles
you has to be careful
we are very careful at kfp we handle our
eggs with great great care and love
eggs are our everything
we'll just sit on you mostly
yeah trying to hatch you
minimal juggling
unknown thank you for the pinky
i said this many times before but your
voice is seriously so beautiful
words can't describe how much i love
this dream it was divine exquisite
thank you for this blessing tantra i
love you so much i love you too come on
come on
[Music]
foreign
a specific part of that statement
i understand now you are going to the
usual room to the usual room on my
ho
for life life sentence
life sentence usually
where's my button here
[Music]
no mercy
live sentence
until you're ready for the bucket
wow
wow okay
evil chicken
you have angered me
[Music]
chats guys unbelievable
i wish i could read the others let me
try to open them again
come on youtube don't don't disappoint
me
i can't help it
yo is there any way to like open those
there's some special did someone find a
trick or something
[Music]
come on
okay that's it i'm sending youtube to
the usual room too
[Music]
bye bye youtube
you'll you'll never get out of there
unless you fix the super chats how about
that i'll let you out with super chats
i'm just on the usual room
yeah
if you if you fix my super chats
midnight thank you yes you may
yes thank you everyone for watching
today i hope you enjoyed it i'll go to
sleep now because i have two streams
tomorrow and thank you everyone for
watching
ah
black friction
thank you so much
and yeah yeah yeah yeah until chill too
i will come to document 2022 if the
organizers invite me mm-hmm and
blackfish
susan hates kiana love
it oh don't take that away from midnight
he asked so nicely
motion duncan looking for the tough
my nose is so
itchy with cat hairs
this movie was that your hair was it
wasn't it i know it was you i know it
was you
oh it was you
sky thank
that's not a red
elvis
you're walking on thin ice today
and you know what never mind i'm sending
you to the usual moon dog dancing elvis
elvis one month usual room
[Music]
bye-bye bye
thank you for the
pinky that's let's be real that's a red
one thank you
more flies with honey and black friction
what
susan flattery kiana appreciation you
want to flatter susan so that she's
nicer to me yeah that would be probably
a good idea
boohoo seven two three duncan i don't
know you guys don't want me to leave huh
i'm gonna go now i'm gonna go now
you can't catch more flies with honey
than with vinegar
huh
everyone please post the question market
mode now
fried
[Music]
thank you thank you oh my god dude
against monkeys
language and dynasty action
oh my god
everyone's so confused right now
because i told you to be confused we are
not a cult by the way
all right i'm leaving now also thank you
for the
thank you for the pinky
the moon this shirt the moonshot is
pretty tonight
wait are you trying to tell me something
specific rock is done soon
[Music]
um tomorrow super cool people come into
my garden club you will actually not
[\h__\h] believe it it's gonna be amazing
bye especially
everyone
i don't know how i want like a i want to
make like a thumbnail it looks like
avengers something but i don't know how
to do it so i'm just gonna make a normal
thumbnail i guess bye bye bye
[Music]
no like if i asked on twitter you guys
gonna use copyrighted material i can't
use a picture of the actual avengers on
my thumbnail
[Music]
oh also i'm saying avengers but it's
probably avengers right
[Music]
bye bye
i love you
thanks
for
[Music]
oh