[Music]
do
kitty
[Music]
sorry to keep you waiting i had no time
today i was so busy
so i was trying to quickly eat something
before stream
uh
[Music]
oh my god i want to take off my pants
and get into pajama pants
ah okay no i was yummy pepperoni
pizza pepperoni
merry yummy i added some corn though i i
is that
shocking to you guys trust me coryn
is the bestest
yeah okay guys today
for the first time in a long while we
are playing a mogus
killer
[Music]
um there is a new map and i um haven't
looked through it yet i opened like a
solo game
so that i can uh check it out a little
bit um how do you
tap okay so from what i've seen it looks
really huge
i want to first like check it out a
little bit and then we can get started
uh
let's see if we can like figure our way
through it
electrical okay so there would be a task
uh over there okay
uh i should
[Music]
pizza is weird you are weird there's
nothing weird about corn on pizza
okay what's the other task this one
okay so the tasks are like familiar
[Music]
yeah i have an angle in my head that's
one of you guys sorry i dropped you
and then there's one over here hello
dummy you know what i like about this
map
already like this there was one issue i
had of the you know the first one that
everyone played
um my problem was like whenever
like in discussions whenever people
would ask like
oh kiana where were you like i would
have
no idea like i would never remember
because like i don't know the names by
heart of each room
but for these ones it's kind of you see
where you are like this looks
like yeah a medical room and the other
one that looked like a kitchen and all
that
and the weapon room and all that so it's
kind of like easy to
remember yeah do you
agree with me guys i could never give
them an answer when they asked me where
i am i always just said
uh bottom right top left whatever
that's the only thing i was able to say
okay well let's make up a little tour
where are we cargo bay on the very right
so from medical to cargo burn you could
go through here to the showers
huh oh no you can't uh you can look at
someone else over there ah
you say hi okay there we go there's a
there's a thingy uh what do you call it
a safe
i can't use it though
it's huge this thing is huge is that a
banana
this map is huge lounge
is something oh the toy oh my god
i like the way they open the door like
done i'm here get off the toilet
how long are you on the toilet getting
back to class
oh are they close they close on their
own again
oh now it's not closing ah because when
someone's inside it's not closing
trash can billiard oh i suck at billiard
and a dart i've i've tried like i once
played
dark with a friend for like hours and
i i wasn't even drunk or anything but i
was
so bad at it even even after like two
hours of playing it
i could never hit or pencil
never could hit the
goddamn middle not even close
tennis no i'm okay with dennis at least
like on switch as we have seen when
oh you slide down and how do i go up oh
okay okay
oh wow top notch animation
but i'm stuck here ah unless i i can
vent okay
so that means there is no connection
here ah
that's another one of those gap rooms
wait so how do i get back into the
middle i have to go down from here
is this the discussion room where
everyone starts
so we go down here wow it's like a lot
of towels all
over who left all those towels on the
floor
they're free starting spots oh my god
what
wait does everyone start somewhere else
see them started as a group somewhere
wow what is this is this like is this
like uh
like the pictures that you put in like
like
some liquid yeah yeah yeah
i don't know why you call that in in
english but
dark room
a hole wait there's a lot of small uh
rooms here
what's that room it's just okay looks
like a usual room almost
oh treasure chest let me open what's
inside what's inside i can't open it i
cannot deny a bunch of there
you can't do that to an rpg player like
me
dad bothers me a lot okay now we're in
the engine room
where and there we have a task you guys
gotta go easy on me when you play
together
after this because i really need to get
used to this mouth
okay then we go out back again and
yeah then we can go down here there's a
weapon room
armory that also leads
all the way to the right side oh there's
also there's a task
oh down there as well let's check it out
a viewing deck oh it's noisy here what
is this
what
what ah oh that's funny
hey well you're like holding the phone
like
i can't get reception here what the
walk the plank hell now
wait can you actually fall down no
okay that was noisy hey i almost got all
the tasks
well nobody did the dishes unbelievable
what is that big golden thing what is
that
all right and then wait did i check out
that room
is that like the the control room where
you can see the cameras
no wait i can't i cannot check out any
cameras
maybe that's not it oh i guess it's not
that
okay and then i've seen that i've seen
that on the screenshot
it's the cockpit oh ah
oh interesting um
the admin wait did you see the i forgot
do you see that
because i never checked the cameras do
you see the no wait what is that what is
the admin even for
oh wait oh ah
it shows you where everyone is wait was
that always
a thing security
is in camps what go to security security
security security security
security ah down there ah okay no more
no i'm gonna go up to the last task and
then we can get started
[Music]
security and comes showing you underplay
i never what
i've never seen that i only i thought we
only have like the cameras
i didn't know there was like a whole map
where you could see where everyone is
but i guess not with the names only like
roughly oh this is the emergency room
thingy
and then we have another task oh
what ah six
two eight three two six two eight
three two wonderful tasks complete
normally the crew would have just one
because that yeah okay i know i know
okay understood a
little game not a huddle let's
play together online and i'm gonna
create a game
um and i'm gonna first hide
the number
and we're going to change the number
after each okay wait should i
i need to tell you guys the rules let me
let me make a pinned comment
server i think oh let me see uh
north america right now
let me let me make a pin comment server
and a quote
each round different
and please only join
one time
any other rules ah and don't i
i would think it's obvious but don't
watch the stream oh i chose public
really create game there we go
don't watch the stream if you
uh are in okay so i'm gonna pin that
no screen looky looky hey also obviously
don't kill me
no you can't kill me but maybe go easy
on me the first time i want to
like find out like if if you're the
imposter i'm not
please let me give me some time i need
to get used to this whole
map okay so airship imposters two i
think is okay right
okay
one second i don't i don't see a code
now i see the code okay
okay i'll say the code you guys type
with me the thing is the last letter is
always an f
usually it's always an f okay it's
always uh six letters and the last one
is always an f
um so i'm going to say the last letter
as quick as possible
yeah uh i wish you luck guys
haha v like
vista why like
york
n like north pole and f
we even have a perfect emote for that
check out a tanning mode go go go
go go welcome everyone welcome oh
we see chat hello
rules i can't type
i i can't type
why not
can't i keep type settings
huh sensor chat
i don't know
i forgot to turn oh yeah why i also
didn't change anything on the left side
do you think those settings are okay
i mean isn't this the same as i did it
back
before i need to sign in what the
okay
but i need to use the chat
wait can i not change it now what
eh that's a new feature isn't it
you need to create an account chat well
can i log in now
uh oh we need to start again ah
guys i'm so sorry i need to get out of
here
ah goodman i have to get out of here and
make an account it seems
wait a second i'm so sorry guys
sorry okay
i has left okay one second let me try to
make an account really quick
back i hope those people get in again
i'm so sorry
come in uh
where account uh sign in
it you successfully signed uh
what do you mean i didn't even make an
account but i signed in it seems
signed into one okay
it seems to have worked so let's do it
again uh
airship let's go
making new code and that was easy
a fruit steam okay thank god that was
easy
uh ah the among the server could not
authenticate you you must have an among
us account to play online guess
what the what oh no okay it didn't
work
ah
can i do how do i do it though go
offline please it doesn't give me the
option to make an account
um
why does it give me this these weird i
did i never put in my height and my
weight
keep trying you'll get it restart game
go to the menu and
offend fighter
oh i closed the game okay
sorry for the slow start
i don't even know how tall 36 is can you
tell me that in meters
i don't speak your weird language tell
me in meters
they don't chat type quick chat only
free or
if i change it to free or quick chat
does that
does that work where's the difference
yes that's it okay okay okay
okay making room hopefully that links
free i can tap okay then i don't really
need an account do i
um one meter that is so tiny
wait it says again the servers
could not authenticate you
why where would i even log in
it doesn't even like show any way to
login
because when i go to account see
is it i can say you play as guest
what what the who's philosophy
ah randomize the name
see and then it says you're successfully
logged in
what who i'm not frosty
but now you would think i'm signed in
right
okay
let's see
okay now i'm in okay okay
okay you like unicorn
and v no m like
master v like
victory you like universe
g like g string and f like f sorry i
said the only thing i could think of was
just
hey some of the same people made it in
okay okay and now i can show now i can
show there we go welcome
everyone
that was the that was because of gura
it's her influence
okay let's see if i can chat hello
no i cannot chat with the phone
unblock me please i don't know who you
are
hey i can't chat
click button on the right
what
what that's how i have to chat no yeah
what question
are you for real
try changing language to something else
and then back to english and it might
work since it happened to someone before
go into settings and change to free chat
what what
okay wait
i'm so sorry guys i have to leave again
change my age under 18 what
i don't get it okay so
wait i i changed it to free a quick chat
but it changed
back to quick chat oh my god this is
annoying i'm so sorry let's try again
well now now it should work right
ah after i logged in i think it switched
it back oh my god
okay good luck again everyone
what an annoying starting why did they
change it
dude what the okay i can make a
account but you told me i am
logged in
you told me i am logged in and you don't
even give me an option to make an
account
no that's something else try switching
service
you really think that'll do the trick
okay you see the code now
i can type now what how the did you
get in that vast what the hell
okay whatever then you know what let me
change the pinned message
we're on europe server now i don't know
why it didn't work in n.a
europe
okay uh
hey there's a hush hello
okay is censored as always thank you
thank you watch humble talk on the
weekend okay guys
uh be easy on me
and mute stream
please be nice oh i would i would be mad
if i would be um
imposter already in the first round
please no
i can't i couldn't
so please give me a break game i need i
need to get to know this map
even up until now i never was able to um
i never was able to actually get to know
the other um
maps i only really played the first one
i don't know why but this one looks
interesting
so let's get to know it okay let's go
let's go let's go everyone ready
ready ready
change task numbers and cool and kill
cool down
i can't do it now i think oh can i maybe
i can i'll wait
how should it be oh no wait oh ah there
we go
oh
[Music]
emergency cooldown how how long
emergency cooldown
wrong comments
20 for me one second
okay now now it should be correct okay
uh thirty
discussion time more right
voting time 120
discussion time 30. um
one meeting okay confirm now
okay okay let's go with that let's go
oh wait wait there's short and long
tasks i couldn't change those
ah scroll down
okay what about the test click quick
common tasks how many long tasks how
many
crew vision interesting
why is that crew vision
three two three two two four
okay just going with that let's go
stacking
we can still change those up
oh thank god okay there are two
imposters and moguls
what what uh where i wanna be
oh main hall maybe
hello hello hello okay uh
uh wait tasks uh i have one here
oh my gosh what you take a shower
that is so cute okay first things
wait he watched me take a shower oh my
god
that's not cool that's not cool don't
what the hell
that is sensitive sensitive
where do i go where do i go wait there's
also one on the right side
and i'll do that one why did he not do
that
why did why was what color was that blue
oh i was too late wait i don't know i
don't even know
wait was that even the right task i
don't know what i'm doing
and that was just my normal task huh why
is all those
that wasn't even the emergency thing god
damn it
oh well uh cargo bay downtown okay
don't kill me i need to learn this what
six
[Music]
is dead
ah wait there's two people dead who's
you me and the blue one
rip i have capsicum
okay now it's good rest in physics wait
i never thought of that
who how when why
why is someone talking do they not have
accounts
why was no one talking did they are they
they were talking so much before
so my last near the cockpit near green
uh huh
that was two emergencies ago yeah
i i i haven't seen anyone
i don't even know who was the person
that was doing a task with me right
there
i don't even remember what color that
dude was
who was standing there when i came there
quiet groups us
do you want who who won was mommy
i think i was with white
uh now so he's
cool
i think but i'm not sure don't trust me
i'm not sus but i i'm also not someone
you can't really
trust today i was a purple
oh wait maybe purple
i don't know oh my god
i can't see colors
but it sounds exhaust
i don't know this map i even played one
yeah i mean everyone everyone's gonna
use that excuse now
i haven't seen yeta well you're stupid
you're stupid why are you saying same to
you can't see colors or you haven't seen
me i'm
i am i am opening a safe
right now
i have it okay well skip
skip around me skateboarder
skip skip skip
okay someone voted for green
interesting why
oh no one was ejected
oh i can choose again oh oh well i guess
let's go to the kitchen
wait okay i need to go
up here go to the cockpit once
and then to the vault
like this one okay downloading
those sensitive pictures
it's a good stream for welfare isn't it
yeah i was
feeling like though the wealthy style
kind of reminds me
a little bit of
[Music]
the i mean it's at least closer
to the a manga style than uh
my normal looks
[Music]
there it is oh that's so
i told you i told
you to not kill me what the i was
just
she was legit waiting there for someone
to come
oh my god
[Music]
it's really noisy here let me go
somewhere else oops
can i oh can i can i go somewhere else
right now
do i have to listen to this it's really
noisy out here
i am only ashes
feel my rage when i rise
rise like a phoenix
out of the ashes
[Music]
what actually like around my debut time
i was uh asking if i could sing that for
my debut stream
but i couldn't get permission because
it's like a
well overseas songs well not really for
me it's like in my country but oh well
anyway she had to start playing so i'm
gonna just say what
how huh
how does he know i said plank
what
trench what what is it yeah except where
actually yeah how does
ah when i explode but yeah why would i
what is that what is this conversation
i don't get the point but anyway vote
green out
vote green out what about
great
[Music]
i need justice to happen
[Applause]
that is depressing oh well
okay i wish i could haunt people okay
i'm still back with the wi-fi back with
the wi-fi good research noise
what's the what's this guy always red
look at this what the
of course i told have not watched the
stream and that is uh
good they are not supposed to watch the
stream oh now i can ignore the walls
nice i forgot about that let me go up to
the vault quickly
let's help them with the tasks yabby
oh there's a big diamond what do i do
that
huh
oh i have to i have to rub it what the
hell
no he's so dead all right
hello hello
oh greeny little bastard
nevermind anyway i was saying yeah i
wanted to sing that song for my debut
stream but i couldn't
and then i forgot about it i need to
sing it oh at some point in an
unknown craft stream because it's such a
perfect song because that singer
is also from australia wink wink
uh just like me and he sings about
rising like a phoenix or she she
as a singer conchita is a she if i
understand correctly
and as a normal person he is a he
oh wait the other way around
quick what the hell oh there we go
oh how long do i have to do that
[Music]
only once uh
i have to turn the dial around one time
what is it body check
yeah oh it looks still the same green
hasn't been able to
kill more people
thank you thank you for that information
nice
just like like uh ghosts like to do
they like to haunt toilets and stuff
don't they
i know chill
i didn't take it any other way so what
are they talking about does she fix the
sabotage
two of her tasks red purple clear then
it's probably you light you and
green i don't know about maybe not
okay maybe it's uh maybe it's red and
green and one more time to do a thing i
just need to
find where why am is on the map such a
a they're skipping again
soupy sauce
no one was attempted again okay but
we're still only free dead people so
uh okay let's go
to electrical electric bugaloo
uh
i can't do anything else it seems but
it's leading me over there which is
something i can't do right
oh wait i got a new task
noise yay
no i'm not ah
oh i can fix that as it goes i thought
that was kind of emergency i couldn't do
as you go see i haven't played the
mangas in a long time
i'm i'm already getting used to this map
what what trash do i take it out
what do i do with that
what what the
freak is
i like those new oh this is my enemy
like that oh
two
out to the other side
i up
what okay let me do it again
one
one three to the left
oh come on i want to finish this one for
once
ah damn it oh wait
oh one more dead people per person
well good luck good luck
it was a bella rip
bella i'll never finish it no i won't
finish it next time
i will i believe i believe i figured it
out now i understand now
but i feel like if if we were ever to do
like a collab with the
japanese girls again or like even
without a collab i feel like a lot of
people
a lot of the whole live japan girls
would have lots of troubles with that
task it's like the new um credit card
swipe task
he's he's acting like stupid
how does how the does fixing
lights work i don't get it
i just said about the flesh and press
what
the hosting of me asking questions well
hold on
question submissions are closed
wait what what is it though uh what's
her tampa is she's a huge bleach fan
and i'm pretty too knee so i bet she
made one of
i have no idea what that even means
well i gave you guys enough time to ask
questions you actually you could you
could still send questions in on twitter
and youtube
i have to go through them after this
stream or like tomorrow
morning yeah i really don't have much
time i've been super busy like today
the whole day been recording something
something very special and
tomorrow i have a long stream a long
riser stream
and whole talk preparation
and then i have her talk like in that
night it's like
technically it's sunday but it's still
kind of like saturday night for me
thank you this is just like me having
conversations with my
fans focus on being a ghost focus on the
game
so what are they talking
wait why me or what oh they oh thank god
they did vote for him
oh was he a little bit too sauce
nice nice they got one down
but i don't know i don't even know who
the next one is
can i even i can't see them as a ghost
can i okay so
one to the right okay
three to the left okay that doesn't
count i need to go
do a whole one okay
and why does it not work
what the
huh
oh open
oh finally that is the worst task ever
give me a freaking break okay what is
that ah
there's a diamond in there are we sure
we want to throw that away
okay let's see what they're doing
because i think i have all my tasks here
okay there's red and white together i
think
that can imply that they are uh
good they're safe
i'm tearing you apart how why okay i
hope they don't get killed
where are they imposters ellie
they're scared i'm scared for them too
i don't want them to die we need justice
justice
huh calm sabotage okay this one i cannot
do someone quick
but the door is closed the door is
closed
don't get killed in there okay
where is the where are they
oh they're running over there now
quick quick you almost have a task
finish
task complete almost
better not be one of the ghosts who's
missing okay
oh no that is uh probably
not the imposter because
[Music]
or maybe maybe he is the imposter i
don't know
he's running running around alone
be careful of guru be careful
never forgive never forget
oh let's follow the imposter
ah he's under pressure
revenge for last time i did nothing to
you
[Music]
run run run run
run the channel can't bear
i need to protect where where's everyone
else is everyone else dead oh
okay
okay oh there is a pla oh you can't go
over there oh
no no no no quick yep
no no
i was following you
trying to protect protect you
there's one task left one test
come on
oh yeah okay now this is important
this is let's see if pink and white can
figure it out
oh my ass killed purple oh he saw it
hey she saw it
i was walking up and saw him dash
huh maybe maybe we get a happy ending
okay one voted okay pinky obviously
knows that
he himself isn't it but okay he dressed
white
[Music]
that is that is good as last words ah
nice i mean almost all of us dead that
was really close
okay we are uh sorry i'm leaving
uh i'm opening a new lobby
uh wait this time i will not show you
the code i will tell you
yosh okay new code are you guys ready
no zumbiva okay
w like washington are like
restaurant
m like mama
and like norfolk f like f
welcome welcome
hello hello
welcome
er rules okay
evil perfect we got some medicine in
here
in case someone needs a painkillers
yeah don't give up guys don't give up i
know this the everyone is so
fast i'm sorry about that
short you have some you want me to
change
the the settings just for you huh short
kill distance and 30 seconds cool down
short kill this is i guess is uh uh
something i can do
oh he'll cool down ferdinand okay
carelessness short okay it sounds like
sounds reasonable
done oh i didn't ask
rose okay in that matter i actually
meant if they understand my rules
is stream closed
that's understandable i also still don't
know where the map really oh my god i'm
probably gonna be imposter next oh my
god i feel it
okay be uh
be nice to me
please thanks maybe what do you mean
baby
what do you mean by me i mean yes okay
okay
let's go
okay good good good i'm relieved
[Music]
i'm gonna go to records okay
oh my god there's so many tasks here uh
wait how to get there
done oh wait there's one here
i have to pick up the towels
[Applause]
that's it wait that one
[Music]
cool clumps are sabotaged by the way
let's go get them probably gonna be too
late anyway
but i'm running welcome to the stream
thank you for the red super chat felix
ah see it's already over
oh weapons
oh i have to pull on here
oh oh oh
cleaning up i see i see
and then go quickly quickly
here are you guys learning something
from this
this is uh for everyone
who wants to play the new among us map i
will
show you how there we go
you can learn from this and then tell
your friends hey there's a new among us
map
okay if we represent okay
what is that burger what the let me
make a burger i'm busy
tanjo is busy
what the is that reasoning
stupid reasoning but okay
uh i am where am i where am i right now
i i am making a burger right now
but it's vegan for
some reason yes i'm still in the kitchen
did you see that that was only salad and
and
onions and onions it's like double
onions but no
meat or anything
what are we skipping so is anyone anyone
here uh was a science and he's with lime
so they're covering each other could be
that they are
uh both imposters
let's keep cyan and green
in mind i was with no who's null
are red okay uh so dark green says he
was with red
and science says he was with
green light green okay
i will i will forget that information in
five seconds
kitchen okay
oh it's different now okay that that
that still has no meat what the hell but
okay tomato
salad salad huh
it changed again what what i don't
understand
oh wait oh okay now it has no bread
salad onion tomato onion salad
oh god wait no no no no
okay what the salad
meat meat onion salad
salad ah oh
it's the other way around oh
uh onion
meat meat
oh thank god not isn't it
that is so difficult
what a burger i mean at least it has
meat in there that's something
i'm not following you outside no way
okay what is that i take them all
right and put them here one
two ah wait
[Music]
i don't know the quickest route
sorry i was trying but okay
green and who else was that green and
someone i feel like green is safe
so dark green and no i think are are
safe
maybe at least that green because he's
not killing me right now
three nine seven okay
okay let's stay together
batman
i need to go over here my friend when
will it come
i think we're coming inside no
i have to use it okay i'll just i'll
just go the other way
it will never
okay it won't come until how did it come
when i saw it coming to the other person
oh wait no it's not here
oh light green is dead
um dark green is safe
other than that no idea
we died 10 seconds ago at the very
bottom
i can vouch for green okay then okay if
he vouches for green
and green watches for red then i also
vote for red
because i can vouch for green
informative web yeah i shared the little
little information that i have
that's kind of sus brown
i was electrical figuring out the funny
one to six tasks
ah funny funny funny
you're he's trying to be funny by saying
it's funny
sus prepple says
purple sauce purple brown sauce
lebron says grandma starts off the first
death
why
i passed two people some place but i
can't i think i saw a red insecurity
for now we are mostly done with tasks
and only two are dead yeah
kind of sucks that you say that though
sucks he's trying to make us skip
um i trust
red and brown
skip
who do you guys think is it
i feel like yeah probably probably
purple
and maybe brown
and yeah you guys seem to all agree on
brown huh
yo okay really close nice i thought that
i had some missions here are they
no no no don't i will kill you if you
kill me
stay i'm
[Music]
maybe he's just you know not killing me
because i said don't kill me
uh something is up there
can i get there how
how i know i can
why is it over there now okay stay
together guys
i'm going down bye bye so much for
staying together
[Music]
if i go here
wait there's something something's
red the lights are off someone turn the
lights back on please
i'm doing this
i'm helping too i don't know where the
lights are
okay wait that was that was that the
lights
did i do the right thing yeah the hands
are kind of weird
got to stay down what there we go
amucos the platform is here
but i don't need to go there i'm acting
sus
no i'm just i just don't know this map
hello
hello oh they're sweet they're like uh
coming to help me
oh let me turn that back on
hello everyone okay i think these are
all saved oh black joined us as well
okay
then i think it's white and
huh
i mean i i didn't suspect brown the
whole time
but but
oh my god but but green covered for red
and red color for gray and green was
okay but green was just
betrayed by red and
and and brown was alone with me for a
while
but he chose to not kill me but then
later do a double kill with
red what what
what
i am so shook oh my god that
was what
damn that was insane
that was insane
oh my god
i am impressed dominique you died so
early i'm sorry
no no no wait i didn't try i trusted red
and dark green
brown afterwards after he didn't kill me
but i still was like he probably is only
not killing me because uh because he
likes me and i told him not to kill me
oh my god okay opening a new one guys
wow
wow impressive oh
that was okay damn it sorry guys
the fastest one will win hello
welcome i wanted to hide the chat but at
the screen what whatever
we're going to switch i guess hello
hello next time i hide it properly don't
worry
damn you dancing sorry okay
and kill attention
only at the
end if necessary please
trying to do a smile oh i can't wha
what what
i actually accidentally opened discord
oopsie
ah what the
can someone else come in it says to
nintendo
oh molly how rude kicked them
now we're starting okay let's go
ichimos
am i imposter oh thank god i'm not okay
but but okay next maybe next round i
i wouldn't mind being imposter um
these things change too interesting like
it's not a whoa holy the amount of tasks
wow
oh you know reveal code diamonds
coin diamonds emeralds
yeah what now huh
what what
other side oh
wait that's annoying and mendoxa
well be there diamond coin diamond
emeralds
maybe i need to go i was trying to
remember that
diamond coin diamond emerald doors don't
kill me
don't no no don't kill me
diamond coin oh diamond coin diamond
emerald
a help
huh i'll just go somewhere else then
i'll go up door is closed here what two
what the
no
oh you have to open those doors on your
own
oh no but it's already open though isn't
it
what i haven't even done a single task
yet
it's not oh my god
oh my god i keep on running into one
still
oh my god every time i get so
surprised ah
okay purple is dead and cyan reported it
now i'm going to standing there what i
was in the toilet
but he says it's in the kitchen
sis kitchen is like top right
and toilet is a bit far away i was with
piano in the library
really really
lime green was just standing there
kitchen oh wait no but eh
he tells us he was in the kitchen but
that's also where the body was so what
is his
lime green what's your defense hello
what what's his argument then he's not
even trying to say anything
he has no alibi
silence
oh
no answer connoisseurs is he still
typing
take lime green and like vote
he's like literally saying nothing
though maybe he can't type
okay
let's do it oh he has a dc or something
i don't know
weird orange didn't do anything that's
kind of
shut up shut up
okay he's not voting i think he's like
afk or ah yeah what maybe he was afk
what the hell oh wait no no that doesn't
say sauce is made it meant seriously
means cute
bye bye bro for frau
for frog i wonder if it was really him
where should we go main hall maybe
i still have like a million oh it's
closed again oh
yay okay finally why did you not open
the door for
me the lady
okay
that one coin
[Applause]
i got it oh man i
have too much time passed and i honestly
had no more idea
like i was close to having no idea but
hey i remembered i remember didn't i
okay i'm going good we even had a
discussion in between the whole voting
you guys should be impressed with me
wait for super chat
i can't chat i knew it was it should be
something like
needed to it must have been something
like that ah then we kicked out the
wrong person
probably or did we
maybe maybe not maybe he was an imposter
shut up what is it for the doors
stupid doors uh
okay here download
sensitive data
nice going down oh no wait that's
nothing is here i go
here here here
here here i
have a task here hello white don't kill
me now
i told you i told you
potential must be killed last so
hold your horses i'm showering get out
of that light
bad guys what if someone kills me in the
shower oh my god is that possible
hello why are you waiting for me i have
a task here
okay white seems kind of safe
she know what
i thought it was closed again there's a
lot of closed doors today
okay and yeah maybe if we can finally go
bottom left somewhere
going down
where is it where is it though i don't
know where it is i don't know it just
shows me like a rough
rough marking but i don't know where
that even
[Music]
can i actually go there i want to use it
bye bye see you later
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god went across bridge
see dead body
will be
with a million people behind me though
white white i know you i was the only
one that dressed it
was the only one i dressed
i'm scared now
i would just light blue in my life and
would let them watch my past
i was security marking making a switch
test that's really annoying
well that sounds again green again
sounds sesame
um he sounded test to me already
in the very beginning get dark green
i don't know i don't know why
wait how many dead people do we have
free already
oh well
i don't know
uh i ain't left my vision two seconds
before their body was supported
ah there were so many people on the
other side of the bridge i honestly
don't remember everyone
ah on the other side of the
bridge there were like four peeps but
i don't remember all of
them i went over there
i went over the bridge alone
and everyone left behind
don't tell me i'm obsessed just by
saying that
ah oh yeah our memory was
there yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh oh my god so it was blue
black yellow me
that leaves green it's green
it's green it's green
green and red green and red
green and red
i don't trust green that's that's for
sure that's that's for sure i don't
trust green
let's go engine room oh god red i don't
trust red either though
don't get me i'm scared
no no no don't follow me no no no no
blue stay with me
[Music]
ah
i knew it i knew it where is
who is the other other one
green oh my god
okay now i'm gonna do tasks lime
wow
[Music]
oh
i was like panicking and then everyone
left for a second and then
he killed me
is gonna clear it up he's gonna clear it
out i i
i believe in blue cannon and i spawned
an engine and we were arriving for a bit
and then the reactor went off
bodies and kitchens and they stayed a
while while i went
yeah yes please believe blue
yes please believe blue
they have to trust him
i was just with black and red at the
moving bridge i'm glad you're not dead
yet
wait zion wait light green
so furfur was the other imposter right
funny i was on the right yeah
that's okay that's okay so what what
does what does red say
red speak uh maybe he's also has he has
has read ever chatted
maybe he can't shout
then maybe he's one of those people who
can't guys if you
if you want to participate please uh set
it so that you can chat
otherwise we're gonna have a problem
[Music]
uh two impulses and we
no not necessarily it could have been
frozro who revolted out first because he
didn't talk
yeah please vote out where did we go
when do it do it
go go go go yes
yes this means we win no
come on come on come on bye bye
head taker he really did take my head
oh
[Music]
why didn't you leave me alone
why why why
i was so scared i was so scared is there
any explanation man it's not red
i'm a money did you already know he's
still there
i thought red was a friend but he was
not
don't trust any anyone
all right leaving this room
okay next time i now i will uh
hide the screen and tell you the code
[Music]
telling you the code guys
are you ready
i think my roommate is going to try to
get into
huh
she doesn't know the map so she's not
gonna try she said she wants to try but
you know the thing is she would have in
advance because she hears
the code like two seconds before you
guys probably
but yeah and you can learn the map now
by watching my stream have fun
okay the code is and like north pole or
so
i can't think of any other word hotel uh
k like kilo alec
do you like tango d like delta and f
go
welcome
okay hello welcome everybody oh
oh i already started i'm sorry
i accidentally clicked couldn't even say
hello everyone turn on the streams turn
up oh
turn off the streams everyone
i mean not the viewers only the people
who are playing with me
oh i said do the tests automatically
always pile up like no this time no last
time where i
um spawned at it had like a ton of
tasks right there but it has nothing to
do with where you spawn right that was
just
was it just a coincidence
i
yeah this was mostly the towels i guess
oh
no it's a europe server check the pinned
comment
uh okay got two of it
it's coincidence okay two over there oh
what
there we go i did it i think
whatever that was um cockpit
what is that huh
what's the task to left of slider
oh yeah anyway
someone has to fix the lights but i'm
already here so i'm gonna do that one
light green dead
eye queen is dead somebody using that
why not i use something else in between
two but today i feel like this one is
really fitting
where was it is everyone saying hi
wait
what the
see now everyone's using this excuse
like i haven't played for a long time i
don't understand anything
which can be very true but it also can
be just a
excuse from an imposter
free dog what the hell wait
so black
green like light green and then light
blue cyan
oof holy i'm scared
that's a typical excuse even though i
used that excuse even after playing the
mangas five times
because i didn't even lie i still didn't
know what i was doing after
playing in five minutes
who it says pepe why is paper sauce
because he said impossible welding gotta
say if she was in the
cockpit
well yeah i am safe indeed
i'm having trouble oh yeah which party
did he find
can white even chat he did say something
didn't he huh
i've seen black on top with me but we
got separated yeah which body did he see
i want an answer
answer the question
[Music]
hello
i was kind of alone but like what which
body did you see
what the what
that was
[Music]
okay i'm still in the cockpit
i have a bad feeling about this round
like there is no communication
wi-fi i'm not well not the wi-fi it's
the other thing
europe is bugged what do you mean it's
bugs
is it really i thought those kind of
issues were fixed
hey green
did you already fix it
hold it
you green
where did he go
unbelievable where did he okay i gotta
do tasks i gotta help i gotta help
oh there he is again why is he waiting
there now
i got reported
it's so noisy here again
oh my god oh they have to oh yeah
so it's green on too
so i was doing the smartphone wiper
things
he was indeed like kind of doing it yeah
oh so white and green
oh man
yeah i mean oh wait why actually kill
someone
well that's why he wasn't wait that was
self report oh
he reported it by himself
oh those people are like the most
sus people ever self report is like so
such unbelievable
why kill being self-reported oh my god i
can't believe it
that's like such
that's the sausage of the sauce
i i i from i have played the mangas of
you guys a lot
but i think this might be the first time
i've ever encountered someone
self-reporting or at least like only a
little second or so
[Music]
he reported an accident ah i guess we
couldn't think of
any excuse he should have told us which
question was which body he found and he
was like oh i was alone
what what you reported though
maybe he didn't realize that he was the
one who reported
what was happening are they going oh god
i hope they can do it
up until now it's been one win for the
imposters and then
uh four wins for the crew i think
wait who was voted out no what the
you got stupid
no oh see i told you we have
communication issues in this
run you guys need an emergency run or
something
emergency uh meeting this is pretty yeah
bye
okay ghost taking out the trash here we
go
did i do it
oh man i have a i think the imposters
might win this one
yeah oh ah
that was because communication issues
okay i don't even have anything to say
about that
i'm going to leave thanks guys for
playing with me
okay wait i changed to north america
again when no all right it says no for
america but
it's actually europe what the hell okay
um no i'm gonna stay in europe and uh
we're doing one more
last one last game today
okay last one
let's have fun guys are you guys ready
for the code
do your best and also everyone who is
already in don't try to get in again
okay
mango oh like
oasis s
like s
synthesizer
what do you mean chicken what the
chicken oh okay that's okay
oh welcome phone fave did you steal my
phone
wait because she thought one of his
names let it burn
what is his name
wow crispy
uh crispy chicken is best
i love those names
rise like a phoenix soccer chicken what
the no
no soggy chicken
okay uh close stream
my echoes hero person watson
i don't own a tv like i don't know if i
can watch it can you watch that online
like on the website
nowadays does it do i play it when is
that even happening
are we actually having a eurovision song
from this i never watched a revision
concert sound contest it's like the
biggest thing in europe
but yeah i don't watch it ever i feel
like yeah they're probably streaming
nowadays now there's so many people just
don't own a tv
anymore so there's a lot of streaming
going on
okay let's go so last round so let's see
if i'll get to be the imposter
impossible
oh we were only nine people that was
last minute nice
yeah okay well that's at least i feel
safer
in some way like i know what to do
oh okay there's a of tasks actually
down here let me go there first
[Music]
now oh okay pink hello
what is that
was it okay oh no what are those tasks
three the other one said five hey do i
wait
like three seconds or what did this go
away
are you okay pink what the pink is
like bugging
in order oh my god what are these
complicated is it already done
oh where are these complicated tasks
pink is he like
okay so this one was five that one was
free
but wait how doing ah
oh there is pink that was four
and that is one okay one
and then two must be there ah is that
is that two oh yeah that's six
oh that's that what a riddle is this
okay two
one two this is the one that they said
one two six
okay frame was over here somewhere
uh maybe that one no well the crumbs are
sabotaged but i don't give a
okay someone has to give a
pink is like broken yeah but i saw him
somewhere else running around too i
think maybe that's just the graphic bug
maybe he is actually running around no
more
yeah he seems fine uh
wait who's then purple and brown is dead
and rant reported
purple brown dance red deported and read
the porch
sorry i didn't want to deport you
report it now i
read the paint comment i'm on you server
yeah chicken chicken is a meat chicken
is with me
yes chicken could have killed me too
right at the start but i'm not sure
about him yet uh-huh
it was pink and yeah pink pink looks
bugged though
thank you looked like you
were booked at the lad
there for minutes so are you
okay
yellow i'm safe because kiara and pink
doko is the body that is a good question
yes where is body oh cargo bay
okay cargo bay where is that i don't
even know
yellow pink yellow and i save okay
uh well then that leaves us with cyan
it must be cyan cyan
maybe he's also one of those people who
can't chat that kind of sucks that they
change that oh no he's talking
oh who sounds sauce to you guys
he reported oh yeah wait
which of those two bodies did he find
yeah
orange shut up i'm orange
lime really really
no no no no i don't know really
wonderful
man sorry if you're watching the archive
later on i didn't really feel like
wait someone left the king did you guys
see the name i didn't see it
[Music]
no he know stream had challenger
okay wait but there's those tests oh the
tasks are gone because of the other
thing
wait where is that where is it do i have
to start all over with that
what
oh now there okay do i have to start
over don't have to start over
at six eh was that always six
start from four you can't continue where
you left okay
i think four is here oh wait i can't
no i can't activate that
oh what this test that's the way
sayaka
four was that right
then we need five
let it burn wait
seven
it was what is scion doing
what is sign doing avert crash course
where is it where is it where is it
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
four seven two nine
six go why it saved the world
hello hello yellow okay yellow was
trying to do it
sian was serious there
right emergency meeting
come on
cyan kinda says why didn't
you run to the uh thingy
you were standing at a door
chilling while while i ran to emergency
okay seems legit
those doors suck
i mean i have to spend some time opening
those doors too but he could have gone a
different way
stupid doors
anyway i did the emerge
so yeah the bodies are still the same
body count is the same
and where was black i guess
i was alone and i'm pretty sure it's
safety car doors blah blah blah
black is not talking red where were you
good questions hello yellow
yellow white is doing good job no both
of them actually
i don't have any more clues
i don't believe that what do you mean no
clues yet why win
no one covered for black in the first
round evil in in the first
discussion
flat blackberry sauce
skip okay i guess i can skip one more
round
one more round maybe it's okay black
vented what
did he say oh it was a joke
i vented throughout the whole ship why
would you say that even as a joke
why would you huh
i don't but if you were the imposter why
would you say that
right
reverse psychology
okay back to my stupid tasks let me move
other i can't move
what i can't move i can't move
oh no okay
quick what i can't open the map
the game is bugged how will i ever
finish this game
you have it i have to use my mouse okay
where were we
where did we live off where did we leave
off seven not
seven wait five five five we need five
five five five five
five six no no i'm not gonna be the one
fixing this again i'm gonna i need
to fix this
wait that one that was pn no
five okay let me fix the lines nice
uh then this must
be six oh finally
well yeah i've been doing this the whole
round oh my god okay i'm finally done
uh i can't open the map anymore with for
some reason
ah why
okay anyway there's another one here
okay what do you mean i have the memory
of a chicken that's busted
okay crash course
uh wait how do i get there
i went the wrong way can someone
else do it
is it can i get there from here
can someone else do it
love it
did that work okay okay okay
someone did it oh thank god
ah what what
are you kidding me no
way oh my god
i cannot believe these tasks
is the thing here i want to go over to
the other side
i have it i feel like there must be a
lot of dead bodies now
what's what happened now fix the
lights
wait who was that who was that just now
where are the lights
that's not it
oh someone fixed it okay
that was white oh you make chicken hello
okay he's safe we should stay with him
eh oh
oh thank god
oh wait wait no
those doors i didn't now there's
nothing here
oh yeah i'm stressed out
anything else in here i can't open the
map anymore with tab oh this one
uh here and then like that
right okay
and then engine room
who keeps on closing the doors
it must be in plasters
yes yes okay
okay cyan and white i think are safe
no i can't really ah where do we go
chicken
second where do we go
i wish it would stop doing that when
they're already open
someone is glowing right can i do
something else
oh only one more dead body
interesting
uh yellow is dead now they didn't kill
many people in that time they were
trying to drag it out
interesting
well
i was trying um do my test shut up and
don't back suit
what else would you think i've been
doing i've been trying to hang handle my
way around the games
shut up kiara white and me were together
and can confirm
[Music]
stack kill stack hill only one person is
now
oh i can't let's go what do you mean it
was free
dead already and not just one more extra
what do you mean stack kill
okay are we killing are we uh doing red
okay
probably black as well right yeah
because wait where
it could only be pink and black
but probably black i hope it's red
interesting
interesting are you
[Music]
oh the white chicken is not voting yet
you still got something to say
he's waiting for red's defense red has
no defense let's go
let's go why are all these
impostors so quiet
today
honestly
don't be scared
i don't bite oh maybe i do
let's just vote go go go wait who are we
waiting are we waiting for phones
oh we're waiting for red oh or maybe
he's the fk
workplace harris but no no i didn't
no they they like it
or did he not vote at the end he didn't
tell
was he's just like well whatever
this game i'm gone i'm out
okay now um i think we need to quickly
uh eliminate um black
oh i spawned with black
i still can't open the map uh properly
which kind of sucks so
let's go oh
who's coming uh what
uh how did i get
this doors
they didn't have that in the in the
normal uh
one right what how do i okay
i gotta go to the other side oh wait
there it is there it is
nice that was a vent sound
only the new map has those they are
really annoying i wish is there an
option to turn them off though at least
that would be nice i feel like i'm kind
of safe up here and no one's trying to
get up here i think
i should stay here
[Music]
now
should i turn on the emergency thingy
and just vote for black
because i need to go all the way down
there
i can't i can't do it now
ah is it right down there can i reach it
oh i feel like maybe not
[Applause]
it was not that it was pink
no i understand why you would think that
no
ah black reported into things as a
self report now
oh
they're obsessing black how though why
oh yep
i thought it was black but i actually
was alone with black two times and he
didn't kill me so actually
oh a bridge i love that i love that
that was so funny
washed out bridge
oh no
pink killed me i was coming from
security the gap oh my god
the way he got me the moment i climbed
down the ladder
and i was about to about to call an
emergency meeting but i would have
tried to kick out black so i don't know
maybe it's good
that i stay we shouldn't vote
three versus one hmm i think it could be
pink oh nice
there's so many times on pink fk okay
okay okay
he's smart this this mac chicken is
hella smart
shiro atamayi
i should okay now that i'm a ghost i
have to do one more task
quickly and then maybe task finish
oh
oh my god i'm so sorry black for
thinking it was you
i don't know what got me there hey
thank you guys for joining that was
fun wow
impressive not bad not bad guys uh some
good rounds in there even though we were
all i think or most of us
beginners um i still have a lot to learn
but i think um i want to
[Music]
you know that now that this new map is
out wouldn't it be nice to have another
among us hold on
and collab with with either the fifth
gen or
or someone else because we did a
halloween with fifth generation collab
um among us at the very beginning no not
very beginning but like soon after
our one month anniversary wouldn't it be
nice to
do something like that again not with
the new map i feel like it's time it's
time
yeah i'll
i i know i will think about it
i'll i'll try to i'll i'll try to
organize something
[Music]
okay it's it's time it's time for kiana
come back i have to organize in
a manga's collab but first of all
before that uh this end of the week is
still very busy because
whole talk and i still have to say
is very soon in about 25 yeah 25 hours
so actually i still have to prepare a
lot so i don't know um i'm gonna read
some super chats i'm going to read the
ones from this stream only if that's
okay for you guys
and the others i will read on sunday or
i'll read on sunday i don't know
what should i do i was thinking about
um doing a super chat stream on sunday
but actually this stream i could i could
be done quick
i think it shouldn't take too long for
the super chats from today's stream
i think
oh let me let me give me a little super
chat intermission time i'll be back in
one minute or two minutes okay
and then we'll be quickly reading the
super chats from among us and have a
little chit-chat
a cookie a cookie okay
okay see you in a second
[Music]
did you heard the crack
wow
[Music]
you're just trying to get me to stay
longer aren't you
hello everyone i'm back tai chi what the
tai chi
tai chi dostano
[Music]
what's going on with you you're trying
to tell me something
as always he's not writing anything in
his super chats
sending foreign
what's wrong dancing four reds with no
text what's going on
what what happened is it like an
anniversary
are you telling me happy and uh happy
900k
or something
what's going on
i
oh my god okay well
well i'm chad
well okay wait that's one of that's one
of the very few times
where taxi actually wrote something in
his super chat and still
only two words ah
thank you arigato thank you you know you
donate
in in um yen but i never know
what language to answer in but you wrote
in english now so i guess i'll just
always
write to you in english but if you ever
say you don't understand it and you want
me to answer in
japanese let me know you could just
write something in the super chat and
then i would know what to say you know
um yes
what a chad okay
we'll be reading the ones from today's
stream only and i'll keep the rest for
sunday
okay let's go i don't want to spend too
much time because i want to do a little
talk prep so let's go
you forgot about that do you did you
guys forget about it i hope you didn't
eliza no no no
no there won't be any super chats for
um
thank you thank you for supporting the
razor stream hi
froggy why are you calling me froggy i
just want to say that i forgive you for
never using me in the party
hotel it's still why you thought was
why is hell calling me froggy honestly
i'm just glad we got to go on our
funny little adventure to cover stay
saucy hot wings
is this mr caspegs
wait that's so cute thank you
well it's not over yet it's not over
but soon it will be over
[Laughter]
gotta be him soon maybe i have a like
i have a feeling we'll finish it
tomorrow but that kind of depends on
whether or not i'll have some time to
make some web
some armor or before the stream i kind
of wanted to do that before the stream
but i don't have much time i need to
prep whole talk oh
and something else i feel like there was
something else i needed to do but i did
i did my recording
um i was recording all day as i told you
guys in the beginning of the stream i
think
i was recording all day and my roommate
helped me
very very much and we're done
i hope it will turn out good
it was uh it did go i think well i'm
just really curious about the
outcome i hope i hope it will be okay
because it's going to be a bit of a
special
cover not a normal cover oh
it's okay if this doesn't end up being
the final holocaust priority
yeah but i kind of like even like
imagine i would start
like if that isn't the final i'll
probably get like super close to the
final and then
would only have like what an hour to
stream left
or so an hour of content to stream left
that that will be lame so i hope we can
just finish it rather than ending it at
a real
really weird point you know
one hour of ride the four hours of super
jets well no because ryzer doesn't get
any super chats
um you wanted shorter streams anyways
yeah that's true we might get a lot of
short streams next week i don't know
dlc missions i'm not sure if i will do
that depends really on the time i hope
we can finish it before hello talk we
have to finish it
um we should have enough time
starting from the beginning of the
stream tomorrow until whole talk we have
like six hours or
more seven hours six hours i think
oh that that should be in
no wait wait no no no
wait no we have 10 hours what the
can't do math what the hell and we have
10 hours 10 hours that's enough
yeah yeah okay okay then i think we have
enough time
although i would like to take a little
rest and i will try to prepare
everything before after they arise our
stream
yeah and i gotta do it before the stream
because i don't know
how long atelier riser will go
[Music]
okay anyway
okay
so i've been wondering the baby has been
around for a long time
listening to my streams but never saying
a word isn't about time that the baby
learns its first words and
like says something like mama to me
i think it's about time that we hear
some words from the baby
say mama to me but oh god but if it's
like
learning language from my stream by
watching my stream then it might pick up
some bad words like
and what if the first words of
the baby are
or or like or something like
that
[Music]
thank you not a donation expect at least
two good cultured riser screenshots on
twitter in return
oops you are uh
pressuring forcing me to make a
screenshot
we will see it's the finale so we have
to
hmm wait my chat's gonna stop what the
hell
chat
my chat is kinda dead
oh yeah
maybe it will come back soon this just
because i
unpinned the comment now it stopped
moving
how do i even refresh that window
reload
meanwhile i'll be reading subjects
yakuma yumi thank you
didn't even get in today thank you
i did like the burger task it was cool
that they had that
we're always here tanjo thank you
jules had the bug uh you're up oh
i'm sorry
maybe next time but you know has already
gotten a lot of times before so
uh yeah next time
we'll try um different server we'll try
asia next time
ring clean ear thank you for the
thinking
from the midwest you mentioned corn i
donate
someone who likes corn yay i'm glad
i was actually like shook when a lot of
you guys were shook about me
putting corn on pizza like what the hell
that's so good i put corn everywhere i
love
corn corn is so good
like also in in ramen um
[Music]
oh i would say i mean i like both but
grilled is better with lots of butter
and salt on it
uh ark black or arch black 45 thank you
thank you for the pinkie hi kenna first
of all
i really really enjoy your content even
though i'm always just lagging oh
thank you thank you for coming out of
the shadows
second of i kind of wanted to ask if
paul live has permission to play all
capcom games now if so you might want to
try the ace attorney games they're
awesome
i think we do have permission for all of
them
generally but i'm not sure i haven't
looked into it that closely
maybe i know about the ace attorney
claims though
objection i know about them but i would
probably not play them on stream
maybe privately but not on stream sorry
thank you for the suggestion though
thank you
it's that cuddle thank you thank
you
your friend russia's birthday happy
birthday rachel
t r apostles
yesterday my two week sentence in the
usual room finally ended well that was a
long time
do i have your permission to meet santo
yes
it's your usual room graduation
congratulations
how was it will you be good now will you
be
a good cat now will you behave
really i'll give you this chance we'll
see what happens
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat love
frosty
oh yeah that random name in the
beginning that was really random
sorry about the trouble in the beginning
guys i didn't know that they added such
a function
where you have to log in now to chat
sorry i didn't know
[Music]
i'm sorry about waiting so long in the
beginning we wasted some time there
but now i know but yeah but the thing is
oh
it only worked for me because i joined
the eu server
i hope we can figure out a way to make
it work in the na server too and
possibly the asia server
hmm
oh has some issues yeah when did they
update and add that that function
i wonder if they'll fix it na0 was dead
for me too
didn't work in na or eu for me okay and
then where do you actually live though
asia no way
when they added their new map that was
really recently
right i might but i'm not the only one
having this issue right
asia didn't work but eu and n.a worked
asian bros can't join dna and the eu
service oh
that's sad
[Music]
you aren't the only one okay well at
least that that's something
okay okay
nintendo games no we generally have
permission for nintendo games we do
i've been playing a bunch of them
um i guess like the
the region block the region lock
might be um on purpose but the chat
thing i don't understand
a pokemon no pokemon unfortunately
that's something
else that is a different story
another fire emblem stream yes i did say
before
i wanted to do that other route so
maybe at some point yeah if we have like
a maybe if we get like a phase where
i'm like i don't know what to play
or possibly for members only as i
mentioned before
but it's been a long time since the last
five emblem stream and i feel like maybe
a lot of
new people joined and they don't know
what the hell go uh
happened and they didn't watch the
archive um
anyway uh daisy
looking for the top packaging frost fish
dust fish
why didn't you change your name like
that changed bad grassy daddies
and know who you are
[Music]
thank you
guys it's my birthday today would it be
okay if i got a birthday shout out of
course
hoping the among us games are super fun
today they were fun and
um i'm glad that um i kind of like got a
good feeling for this map
the one with the snow that's like
partially outside i never
really liked that one i don't know i
didn't
i tried it a few times but i never
really liked it
but for this one it's kind of different
i liked the new one
happy birthday agreed oh
shut the first deck i didn't build it
yet my stream on that is i think next
week maybe
attention even though i've said it
before i'm so glad that you became a
beachbody and that you were the first
eon member i decided to watch oh
thank you i love your energy and overall
craziness and wouldn't have you any
other way
thank you that's so sweet thank you for
following me
peter brett thank you
star fox christmas bob one thank
you
i can't ignore that message i have to
read it pinot bread
can you give me praise for my grandma
she's in coma from shock and i don't
think she'll make it
it's been a week but i think she'll make
it if not then just pray as for me and
my family for
hard times and to you see i can't ignore
such messages
i can't ignore them um i wish i wish you
and your grandma all the best i hope i
hope
it will go well
but if it doesn't
then well that's
the time will come for anyone on this
world eventually
and that's something inevitable but i'm
sure your grandma lived a long long long
and happy life
so cherish and pressu treasure these
moments
that you have of her the last ones even
if she's in a coma just
stay by her side and hope for the best
i'll be hoping too
foreign logical paradox
felix now thank you for a red one thank
you
sorry i'm late no problem thank you for
still coming i slept in and i didn't
wake up in time what time did you wake
up
wasn't it like a decent time over there
but hey
i guess i i always make you guys wake up
at
weird times and then mess up your sleep
schedule sorry
i go watch the archiving glad you're
having fun already thank you
have fun with the archive and thank you
for coming and having fun with me
and for one watching me even though you
might be tired or
or don't have much time thank you for
spending the time with me
don't apologize for our wild addictions
[Music]
i missed brown in the showers there was
a dead body
huh i didn't sit down
you're also reporting his death
thank you thank you congratulations on
getting into the game
from production also having issues but
still so thank you for participating
forever
uh unfortunate that you couldn't chat
with us but still
thank you oh thank you for also
participating in the game thank you soon
bryce please thank you for the rest of
the job
[Music]
uh good luck to y'all i'm sad i work so
i will need to catch up on the archives
and i know it's late but congratulations
on
900k here's to so many more yay thank
you
thank you thank you better better wait
than never
right thank you and have fun with the
archive
it's no problem i really um
don't mind if you guys watch it live or
in the archive as long as you watch
everything hashtag will catch that yolk
road to one million tantrum yeah let's
go
but i feel it will be a
uh a slow and
chill way to go
let's take our time i guess
but soon everyone from halloween will be
over 1 million isn't that crazy
that's crazy um
i'm glad i'm glad everyone is like
doing so well
dominic what's heart challenger with my
blood when i died in the last
game
thank you dominique
head taker so many of the participants
are super chatting thank you
i can't talk and chat and defend myself
i'm so mad such an easy win if i could
ah see a lot of people had
problems with that i guess a lot of
people didn't know
because it's so new damn it
that's kind of unfortunate um
[Music]
thank you for joining and i hope you had
fun anyway have another call thank you
for your time brown thank you
heart taker again no no please please
don't worry about it
i i had to take my win by killing you
[Music]
thank you can't wait for future streams
like this thank you i often do
streams like this like mario kart as
well among us and slivered on io
so you guys are always welcome to join
whenever i do like streams like these
they're lots of fun i love interacting
with you guys
magic thank you thank you
hi kelly you were just talking about
collabs there if y'all get permission to
there's a free game on scene called
scribble it it is
a pictionary game that works with
different languages together
oh scribble it
huh okay
thank you for the suggestion are these
dreams oh another one who was in the
game thank you thank you
tai chi thank you for the crazy red
super chats thank you oh my god
wait why why what is the occasion
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you that's crazy but thank you for
being so
generous i don't know what i did
to deserve that but thank you really
hope you had fun in the stream tai chi
see you tomorrow maybe maybe maybe
and uh yeah thank you for always
supporting me
and having my back thank you thing
laser blaster little
little refresh time
actually next week yeah
next week i'm so fine but the week
afterwards
i might be very busy moving although i'm
gonna try to prepare it well
early on yelping
i still didn't decide if i should do it
with a with a moving company
or uh just on my own with friends
because i don't have that much stuff and
i'm actually leaving
almost all of the furniture
here i could i couldn't even leave all
of it like if i have i
have this one one bookshelf
which which i want to bring and that's
the only big thing i have
so i don't know if it's worth it getting
a whole moving company
um
i feel like maybe it's not worth it
maybe just i have friendzone to help me
probably
it's more expensive than buying a new
shelf yeah i was thinking that so let me
just
uh keep the shelf here and then buy a
new one
and then get like uh
free not not free it's not free but get
get them get the
them to like build it for me the people
who deliver it
what do you guys think should i get a
new one but i like this shelf i want it
come on i kind of want it
higher movies movers it's way less
exhausting yeah
i don't know i kind of wanna hmm
i guess the less things i have the
cheaper it will be anyway so
[Music]
i never had like movers uh
help me moving in australia before in
japan i had it before but not in
australia so i'm a bit worried about it
because in japan they were really really
like polite and
and proper and clean and all that
and i don't know it was it just seemed
very well done
and very well organized and quick and
all that
but here in australia i i'm not sure if
i can trust them
and if if they'll do a good job for
what i pay them
but i'm thinking about it but i gotta
decide soon because
the moving is soon
i did i already did a little bit of his
research and found like one
um official
somewhat of an official page that did
like recommendations
uh about movers in australia and
so yeah i i i would i have a lot of
friends that would probably help me
with moving but i don't wanna you know
it's heavy and it's exhausting i don't
wanna
annoy my friends of that because they
probably would it would be hard to turn
down right
like if someone would ask me if i could
help them moving to be honest i would
like to turn them down because
i'm weak i have noodle arms and
i have asthma
i really wouldn't want to help anyone
so yeah um yeah maybe i'll get movers i
don't want to annoy any one of my
friends with that
but but they'll they'll help me uh
color my walls paint my walls
i'm getting help with that i'll not ask
you then don't worry thank you
this longer yeah thank you for the pinky
thank you for everything this little
korean
somehow cute oh shake my wait shake my
head shake my head it's not somehow i
always read that somehow
shake my head cannot trying to dog's
tightening
no no
no i'm just wondering i'm curious about
you guys
anyone else i want to learn more about
you guys not not
not to stalk you just to understand you
guys i want to know
why you do these things
i want to understand
well i mean if you don't want to tell me
that's okay too but if you want to tell
me then that's that's cool
pineapple pizza thank you soon thank you
p 1 2 3 4 m thank you soon
50 not eight what the hell daisy don't
play yourself down like that
why would you do that you can't deceive
me like that
i know how much you donated it's not
eight dollars
ah after all the cuts oh yeah sounds
about right i mean i can't do maps
but sounds about right
no well i think it does so
i supply suction siren crispy duncan
flores
from
i look at this for one second and i know
what this is
you can't fool me hi mama i hope you've
been doing well this is my first thank
you and i wanted to put something
special for you and here starts like a
japanese
a big wall of japanese text i know this
is a rick roll i know it immediately
ah
it goes on and on i can't really fit the
lyrics to the melody because this is
probably just deep
deep l google translated
you guys try and try and try
but the thing is i don't even care like
i don't mind being rig rolled because i
like the song
it doesn't even bother me
thank you for the pinky deep frying
thank you for the support thank you for
the rick roll
uh rs thank you soon reggie steele thank
you soon patrick chen thank you
this looker thank you for another pinky
what the hell
this look area
corn is fine cantona is a crime against
humanity
why i love both the best thing is
tuna pizza with corn
tuna is yummy but okay you wrote canned
tuna okay i wouldn't just eat it out of
the
can i mean
i would obviously put it like i don't
know
wait you say can't tuna but is it okay
on pizza
tuna and pizza is so yummy
especially like from straight from italy
um tuna pizza from italy is so good in
other countries they might it up
but
the og from italy is
so yummy so yummy
you like onions and stuff on it too
you order it from italy yes i mean they
are my neighbors so yeah i totally
ordered directly from italy
i mean they are my name
no but like i've eaten like good real
italian tuna pizza before
many times like all kinds of pizzas from
italy
and yeah they do it well
plate tectonics sure are crazy
shut up
why is it good why spanish tuna
i generally don't never and i
never eat food that's like out of like
cans
really really rarely the only thing i
would buy sometimes is like canned corn
and then put it on pizza or put it in
i don't know with some eggs or whatever
anyway you're not prepared for the apple
apocalypse
yeah because i don't give a if i
die i'll just get reborn in a different
dimension if it's the apocalypse i don't
really want to survive it
it won't be really nice afterwards so i
might as well just say okay bye-bye
i'm gonna go to a better place who wants
to come with me
sorry i'm going alone
i'm only 89 thank you for the pinky
everyone who doesn't like corn here's
a four yeah who is uh
what hey here's is that a joke
here is
what it's a bunk oh i don't see the
emotes in here
did you pause the bunk there wait let me
see oh yeah you did
oh oh that confused me
oh thanks for bunking them nice one
emily
and zero two thank you and happy
birthday
chaos ex function lucinda have a night
thank you
happy birthday to your mom
happy birthday lucinda moms lucinda's
mom
so many birthdays what's going on
and bring help for three intern tree
internation
thank you for supporting the riser
stream
you're using an anagram
what's an anagram a bring help for a
tree
intern um
what does that mean
letter scramble i don't get it though
first one over yeah but it only it turns
out to be a b
h f a t i
that doesn't mean anything a combination
of what is mixed
rearranged wait okay wait what is that a
b
h f a t i
[Music]
a b h f a t i
look at the proper pick it's so small
help me oh it's a car
[Music]
is it harbor
okay
huh i love corn also i'd be super
excited to see kyla collabing with the
girls and monster on the rise maybe
maybe peko namuna and kiara hunting
lagombi
lamborghini
i would hunt down a lamborghini why not
no i've been thinking about um playing
monster hunter a little bit like at
least look into it
because i already bought it so it's a
bunny
whoa now you got my interest
[Music]
okay maybe next week actually um
probably next week we'll look into it
[Music]
and looking for the top dancing thank
you
love to see my collab queens come back
everyone will need your translation
skills too
everyone except inna and and kelly
if they speak japanese with the japanese
girls but if the japanese girls want to
talk to them to amend
and kura well then then yes
we need some translation i'm always
always
ready to help
okay um
sorry
i'm glad your day is better thanks to
joining the game
jesus more wellness thanks in skydiving
thank you
peace light thank you thank you for
congratulations
what's your fault on vr would you ever
do a vr stream i don't really like i've
been
i never really did much with vr i don't
own like one of those thingies
um i don't know really if i could ever
do a stream like that maybe if i get 3d
one day
we can do a vr horror uh game stream and
i'll get a heart attack and i'll die
and i'll yeah well that's okay because i
turn into ashes and then i'll just
revive again but i don't like it
i don't like it
well we will see
that was supposed to be i don't really
want to cough right now
outsourcing don't be pennywise pound
foolish
are you making some jokes with money
cute pretty cute pretty cute
are you just laughing if chad is
laughing then
then that's a good one
is it yeah it's advised but there's a
joke at the same time though
hey it's an extra actual expression
do do english speaking people say that
it's actually a phrase oh i didn't ever
hear about that before
no don't be pennywise pound foolish i
don't get it
pound foolish what
so weird i know that's money but i don't
know it sounds kind of weird listen
it doesn't sound like a sentence to me
thank you thank you for the pinky as
well moving fee thanks mate
thank you thank you hopefully it will go
well
hopefully i can still book someone
thank you i will report on you guys i
will tell you
if i got someone to help me or not
actually did i did i tell you guys
when i came back to australia
um i had like i paid
my friends i paid two of my friends
um
one of them i paid him uh like 50 euro
to build my pc back together
just because i i i felt bad asking for a
favor
so i was like do you want to help me
i'll give you money
and the other one i i also gave 50 euro
for um building um my furniture back
together
but in hindsight blowing the furniture
took like
three hours and building the pc
took that person um
10 minutes so one got 50
euro for 10 minutes of work and the
other one got
10 year 50 euro for three hours of work
or so
not quite fair i didn't expect there
would be such a huge difference in
in time
but hey the the the pc
person got done early and help with the
furniture so it's all good
i don't know i didn't wanna i didn't
wanna you know like especially when it's
about
building furniture and helping me like
bring bringing it back
upstairs from the the
um i just felt like
that would be like something that again
back to the topic where
friends maybe feel forced to say yes
because you're friends
but don't necessarily want to help but
if there's money
on the table then it's another different
story
tax it i don't think i can tax that
i just wanted to like like help out i
guess
and i know at least actually both of
them told me they kind of
like don't have like much work recently
and can actually really use money so i
was like yeah okay
then that's perfect i'll help them and
they help me
awesome
anyway 67 you are
thank you thank you for supporting the
razor stream this long area
thank
thank you for the rise of support
and
ultra new kitchen so many australians
what up you guys are what's
up so early what's going on
thank you for waking up so early what
the
uh ultra new wait i already read that
one do you love 67 dancing
have you ever had an asthma attack from
your own ashes
yeah actually i did and i i died like
right over
oh like again like at the moment when i
was reviving from my ashes
i like breathed them in
and then died like in the middle of
reviving again
so now when that happens i try to not
breathe
while i'm like reviving i try to like
hold my breath
kind of tough that's so cursed yeah it's
like an endless loop
death loop yeah
ah
iron high thank you shannon this look
area danke thank you for another pinky
it's an english thing ah that makes
sense because of the pounds
being short-sighted and saving a few
pennies short-term
but losing out long-term
but kudos i'm slowly spending money on
important stuff now that you're no
longer broken
hell yeah is it important stuff
this is important stuff i don't even
know i mean
it's at least not super unnecessary
things
i've been mostly spending money for you
know new equipment for my streams
and stuff for my skin like skincare
and uh now furniture new apartment and
all that kind of
and obviously yeah cat cat things
that's basically all my expenses
[Music]
recently
good gravy yeah like really really good
gravy oh yeah and i
i bought i bought the new wacom tablet
uh cable cable i hope it works with the
cable
otherwise i'm like what the i'll
try it out
tomorrow or so okay i i am tired
i woke up quite early i didn't sleep
much and uh
then i was like up all day recording
so i think i can sleep early today if
i i could but the question is
will i i must
like last night i was also like tired
quite early but
something kept me up like my my brain
was suddenly like
i can't sleep now having that
knowledge i cannot sleep
oh my god what the
what the sorry my phone's just
vibrated i was like why what the
[Music]
uh we will confiscate your phone to get
your sleep early
you cannot do that i need it for my
alarm i needed to wake me up
no it was mirrorcast i i
downloaded that once
and it downloaded like a million apps
that like
like um cast your like iphone onto
your pc
i tried a million of those apps and not
a single one worked
there was a time when me and callie
tried that out
when we were in uh hokkaido and some
things didn't go well
so we tried all these apps and
uh
kelly even bought subscriptions for them
she paid money and still didn't work
we were so like like like frustrated and
like what the
why is none of this working
yeah i don't know i'm sure that
that in general those apps maybe work
but i don't understand why they didn't
work in our case like
what we're trying we were trying a lot
of things but i don't know
i think it was a problem with the wi-fi
though in the end
um anyway let's finish the superchats
i'm pretty much done
cd thank you for the pinky more movies
life
thanks mate thank you but not necessary
thank you dolce d let me give you
let me give you a kissing
[Music]
kiana's dream chicken thank you soon
you're looking sexy
oh my god i love that super chat
[Music]
oh my god that's super chat
australia or australia
it's australia
right there you go last super chat
you gave me a little heart attack for
one second
what is it hello mrs takanashi this
message confirms your order of
58 kilograms of premium catnip and gold
plated water damage
yes gold plates for my cats to lick out
of
also can i have a golden golden toilet
please
a golden cat toilet not for me only for
the cats i don't want a golden toilet
i don't know obviously i don't use a
toilet anymore but
i want a golden toilet for my cats
however you order of debarker chicken
feather
over is an available i'm gonna pause
this please
you
all right i ordered that because of you
guys
i have uh taken one chicken half page in
my apartment
and i've been trying to torture it
so
if you don't want that to happen to you
you better stop calling me a chicken
understand do you
understand me
who the said that i will ban you
i'm scrolling up where did he go
where the said that who said
joe
there smoking x uh one one one
x i i i let me give you a little time
out so you can reflect on yourself
you are now time-outed i am not angel
if anything intentional
and you better remember that
who is trying to keep me from going to
sleep
with more super chats black friction
jesus morales
and iron height
okay guys this is it
iron height uh i didn't know that shiela
does bring me under this service but
i don't know such a thing take me
seriously
black rich in language in no one banking
[Music]
thank you
i will um do my super chat reading
stream after that
not during it so just so you know that
and take its monkey dancing what is your
post
also your order of pink colored cat ears
inside polish
has been sent to one two three ghost
street on the world japan we thank you
for your patience why would i
maybe thank you for watching
jonathan what the from striver
thank you
[Music]
exactly thank you at least someone is
acknowledging that
foreign
shane thanks for the membership okay
okay
okay i've already no more super chats
after this lunch box duncan
no more no more no more jcd
no more no more good night guys and see
you tomorrow during raiza and then whole
talk
and then super chat reading okay
black person daisy
no more bye bye bye bye love you and in
german we say
[Music]
what the
see is soon guys let's finish rising
tomorrow finale
even if you haven't watched my raza
series i would still appreciate it if
you would come to the finale
please
you
[Music]