[Music]
ah wait where's
the where's the gay
one that wasn't the gay one I have a gay
opening
right uh
no
no ah I think I got rid of the gay one
oh well
[Music]
he
oh
oh I
was I was just turning
on
my my PlayStation 5 thinking I
uh was going to play on playstation no
steam so
[Music]
confused
he
[Music]
K
hello hello
everybody
uh I realized the gun with my swimsuit
is like the perfect
combination holy [\h__\h] the trailer
already has 70
million
views and I am not one of them because I
waited okay I
waited I was a little bit disappointed
to see it got leaked and then I had to
be careful going through Twitter because
people were talking about it people were
posting screenshots people were
retweeting or liking or reposting the
video on Twitter so I was like
h a lot on my timeline then I had to go
around cuz I still wanted to um wait
until we can watch it together I'm
guessing a lot of you guys already
watched it you impatient little
shits yeah 6 69 million right now to be
exact
mhm how many did
know
7.6 million likes does that video have
macaroni holy
macaroni yeah I already got spoiled that
it's in
Florida and literally the day before I
was saying like two days ago I said I
will never go to Florida
so I'm not going to play the
game I gu guess I'm not going to play
the game I said I'm never going to
Florida okay guys I'm going to post a
link in the chat it's one and a half
minutes we're going to watch it together
unless you're already side and you don't
give a [\h__\h] but yeah it's uh
here y y yep
Y and I I I think I heard that it's
coming out in 2025 which at
least uh already early on killed my
hopes that it will be in 2024 oh well
okay uh we
would
stop uh we will we will watch it on on
zero okay uh you will not see it on my
side so you have to play it on yourself
shut up shut up don't write anything in
the chat I don't want to
[Laughter]
know 3 2 one zero
make contain content inappropriate oh
no ah the
colors Lucy
h
[\h__\h] Rockstar
Games
oh are we playing a girl I got a I got
spoiled a little bit about that
too but that's amazing if that's the
case oh the
water oh wait was that a Louis
Vuitton swimsuit alligators oh
twerking can we twerk in the game can we
play an alligator in the
game naked man the many naked men oh my
God
oh my
God no the the bike gangs not
again who is
this her partner crime
oh Grand Theft Auto 6
2025 it better be January 2025 first of
January it better
be Bonnie and Clyde Dynamic oh but I
don't really know what that Dynamic is I
never really I don't know what couple in
crime
right so we're playing we're playing a
girl is that what you're saying like oh
my God [\h__\h] yeah [\h__\h] yeah I prefer
playing girls let's go
oh ah let's [\h__\h]
go that is oh two playable characters oh
I wonder if you like choose yours or if
it's like switching around depending on
the
situation yeah interesting but that's
really exciting I don't think you got to
play a girl before in the GTA
games wow I mean graphic everybody was
talking about the graphic on Twitter and
yeah it looks amazing holy [\h__\h] yeah the
cars there's a lots of sports cars I see
and where are the where are the muscle
cars I don't
know lots of uh very like
modern inspired like things of the
current uh World culture I don't know
how to
explain like Tik
toks
uh oh that was not a Louis Vu swimsuit
I'm just going back but it kind of looks
like
it oh rooftop pools are we getting
rooftop
pools
nice sheesh oh now I'm looking at the
beach
again wow wow there's literally is this
a realistic depiction of Florida because
I don't see a
single person on the screenshot where
you know the beach the first one at 22
seconds I don't see a single person that
doesn't have a smoking hot
body feels very authentic no no I'm I
don't mean like the city the landscape I
mean the
people do they all have
like smoking hot bodies nobody's
overweight
the real beach is way more crowded I I
can
imagine speed bow let's go definitely
not oh my God my my R screen is like
[Music]
twitching there are is not on the beach
oh so only only the hot skinny ones go
to the
[Laughter]
beach don't forget the alligators yeah
where's the alligators on the do
alligators not go to the beach
discrimination I see a dog why is it not
why is not an elev elevator alligator
allowed if there's a dog they should
allow alligators
too it's kind of discriminating but
okay as a Floridian is that really how
you say it there's a there's definitely
a lot of really good looking women in
Miami
m
even though I'm not there
really I will never go to
Florida uh but uh yeah I guess this with
this game I will be going isn't this
like the the the naked almost naked guy
running through a uh gas
station isn't that like something I
heard about in the news
before why is my OBS and my chat
everything on the right side is
twitching I so that is that is a thing
right the Florida
man oh so that's that that happens every
every first
[Laughter]
day I mean I guess it's hot enough to be
naked all the
[Music]
time and the only funny story I'll have
about ending up in Florida is me playing
this
game yeah
[Music]
um it's just your average
Floridian tday is going to be Florida
man
simulator excuse me Florida woman
okay yeah I mean I don't know I I can't
get so excited about it yet cuz it's
like so long to
go 2025 could be 2025 winter could be
autum could be 2025 summer could be so
much and like what the [\h__\h] like
um so I don't know like stuff like this
that's that's so long to go hard for me
to get very excited
about or even like think about so far
away like
toy that's got it N Things to fix before
it actually
launches well what's there to fix I
see is that muscle car I'm not
sure oh well oh well well at least it's
like a lot more colorful because now we
go to our G
actually okay the gay the gay thing is
not so gray it's more gay but uh we now
go to our beloved GTA 4 which is gray as
[\h__\h] I think I was somewhere like here
usually can I open the game please
Rockstar game launcher thank you
don't they always have issues with
capturing this
game why did we not finish this game yet
anyway I feel like we did I know why I
feel like we did because we're already
in the
DLC
what where is there it
is there it is
G let's turn turn GTA down a bit here
okay I mean the main game I totally
finished the main game oh right I play
this game with keyboard right yeah let's
go controllers are for babies
no oh wait oh you still don't
see Tab out
okay it should show up there it is ah
but let's make it full
screen something like this
maybe where I don't know where were you
guys where were you when wa was playing
GTA
four controllers are for helicopters
exactly
you are
[Music]
here let's
go I have no idea where we
were
I couldn't find this opening I'm
sorry at least I still had the other GTA
opening
yay okay
uh let's go I have no idea what we're
going what we're doing what we're in the
middle of doing what we did before does
somebody have like a recap for
me game do you have a recap for
me uh oh yeah we did something that made
us able to like drop off everywhere U
for base jumping I guess there's a tri
where where do I go
uh to the to this m perhaps to
Mor you C A Blog guy who was talking
mess um should people drive cool cars
sure game pretty quiet really
okay
uh wasn't this after doing the diamond
Mission from this perspective yeah
yeah yeah the tracking the car of the
helicopter ooh that was so difficult I'm
a new KP employee
welcome thank you enjoy the stream
remember some
anime yeah we were watching anime on
TV it's my mom sounds pretty close it's
an obligator obligatory uh this
one true okay let's go there wasn't that
like what I kind of was was like
planning to do
anyway oh yeah and I I I I last time I
kind of like just started cheating my
armor all the time right cuz it was so
annoying that after every single Mission
I had to run to the stupid ass that's
not the
way to the stupid ass armor shop so
we're going to do that again if
necessary this time but you guys got to
o o o you guys got to tell me what the
cheat was cuz I don't
[Music]
remember ah it's saved my
phone all right all right all right nice
noce cheats are part of honestly yeah
that's like how I remember it from my
childhood too that cheats are like the
way to play it but now as a as a gamer
when gaming is my job it just feels
wrong to cheat myself for games same
with AOE though too right AOE
too like there's no meaning in playing a
game when all you do is cheating hello
baby can I
pause is this pausing when I Tab out I
need I turned it down too
much I've stop cheating on GTA 3 cheats
are part of the fun
right that's not what you you said last
time you always taking care of the down
and outs I mean it's a beautiful thing
but you got to let him into the house a
these are my boys baby just like you
time I watch them grow up yeah well
apparently your boys and your real son
got some work to do so ladies we got a
roll crime let's go come on let's
[Music]
go Melle you still the best cook I
know
damn so much left over food here you go
Mommy take this okay take care I got to
go that makes up for it take care son
dealing drugs people getting killed
nightclubs you take care no you go to
scho new reverse card be go somewhere
it's not too late my baby I me but you
got it all wrong I mean it's not like
that anymore you know I I know good
people I know bad people you know but I
know the difference I mean I know I made
mistakes but but things are better now I
mean how many times we got to go over
this if things are better now then why
are you always like this but you take
the money right you take the [\h__\h]
money every time get out of my house
what choice do I have I lost my job yeah
well call one of your other kids the one
you ain't ashamed
of Are We coping oh yeah chill out
bro
mommy wait so what did did she tell me
to do
something oh yeah go to the go into the
car okay how do I enter the car again uh
e
f
f okay I don't remember anything yo we
heading to the docks in
Bohan okay can I get a GPS on that no
yeah thank you thank
you I I I do not know the city very
well she RIS me too hard man hanging
down toown made you forget who you is L
what you mean I mean you a [\h__\h]
Dominican all Dominican e like that you
think me and R don't get [\h__\h] too damn
right Turk I'm
Dominican was asked to go to college you
know the Dominic song couldn't even
spell sat let Al on G D I thought he
could even spell ABC only thing I can
spell is DV D she's not what she's
Dominican what was it she's not
believe it bro she was always a save the
world special needs helping type girl
special needs to jump on my dick yeah
but oh wait your boy going to tell me
what's happening here yo we doing some
she's not Mexican shment for some people
I going to be some unruly [\h__\h] bro we
need us another set of eyes I'm your set
of eyes don't worry there going to be
too many people under our purview to
cope on our own and considering your
experience as a man manager we thought
here we are we thought here we
are dialogue too long I cannot wait for
you to finish your dialogue dude talk
faster they're bringing the stuff in off
that boat we going to bring it up here
to get in these cars then all we got to
do is get them back to the heights easy
peasy lemon
squeezy
okay o you two head down to the boys and
loading the boat I'll cover these cats
up here meow I want to cover the
cats follow
Enrique down to the
Pierre
my he I watch new girl but I don't
really like it as much
as like everything else
friends what's going
Seinfield
uh uh look oh my God I watched so many I
love sitcoms sitcoms are my life is g
girl a sitcom I don't think
so I'm on that
[\h__\h] I'm on the
[\h__\h] what are we doing do we shoot I
have no gun how do I shoot there it is
the [\h__\h]
that I don't like being attack what who
is the
enemy keep loing that [\h__\h] this don't
yeah a
[Music]
dram are you enemy oh oh no way no
way why is the whole world my
[Music]
enemy what did I do to them what did I
ever
do is it because I abandoned the game
for too long you guys mad
they're so
mad oh yeah I love I love mockumentaries
too the
office parks and
[Applause]
[Music]
R is you friend
noed [\h__\h] I'm
dying why are they lying like that
I'm dying I'm
dying
what uh gun better
gun [\h__\h] I'm going to die uh what to I
need to cheat how do I open my
phone they can handle this a while until
I figure out je
right I got a little lost
I I I need some I need
some time to get back into
[Music]
this what's up
ke which one these
[\h__\h] out
there oh thank God okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay so I normally wouldn't do this midf
fight but uh circumstances are desperate
oh my God how is he still
alive desperate situations call for
desperate
meos how I get myself into this [\h__\h]
amand dead ah man now we have to redo it
anyway
probably [\h__\h] so they actually di when I
way too
long going to do
man Moy Moy try
again oh
I well what can I do they need to make
it more obvious which one's my friend
and you know like [\h__\h] that inspection
on the
way okay I don't know who my friend
don't you guys also confuse enemies with
friends
sometimes y'all act as if this is so
easy to tell foes and Friends apart but
this is one thing I struggle with in
life so much okay can't don't know who
are my friends and who are my f that
like the [\h__\h] all the phones be
acting like friends sometimes and all
the friends be acting like f sometimes
it's to real it's so real what can I
do no [\h__\h]
[Music]
way yeah you got to wear team colors but
even then it's like kind of like
[Music]
ulous is this my friend yeah okay I saw
it now on the
map let's not shoot the guy in this
second who's not doing anything maybe I
should should shoot off his gun off his
hand cuz he's not doing anything anyway
what is it with this
[\h__\h]
this I need to e we can't
get careful going don't make me shoot
your head this [\h__\h] is why you left the
he was it yeah one of them reasons
bro hey it's like everything is smooth
as butter again after that first uh bad
try now I feel like I'm doing
wellu nice to be back
again in New
York New York New York did you guys see
before my stream it was announced like
not there was some some details about
Fifth Fifth Fifth best
right uh and uh so yeah some details
announced and the title right was
announced four stages yeah this is like
what I was asking and begging for uh
last time I don't think they did it for
me obviously but uh ripping
[\h__\h] my prayers have been
heard more like not not more days but
more stages and also uh
bigger bigger venue I didn't even know
that which one is my
friend I didn't even know you could do
that with that venue
like I can say that right that is also
public now right the the venue the way
they use the venue is is public now
right R run R
run I can say it right giant frd Idols
yeah that's not happening sadly although
it would have been like the
perfect time for
it it's now you little [\h__\h] get out of
here
like [\h__\h] help yeah yeah they they
said which Halls they're using right
they're instead of using using the usual
intended uh life Hall
oh was that a police officer oh
[\h__\h] uh uh which I thought that was the
only option no no you can also do a live
concert in the Expo halls and we never
used all the Expo Halls
before anyway so there was like Still
Still uh like
possibilities to expand within the same
venue when the police are showing up
that's the one cons that's pretty
awesome consolation the paycheck is
going to console my
ass for this and divide about how many
bodies you had to drop back there and
see if that shit's real money [\h__\h] that
math Stu you know I can't divide nothing
hey all I'm saying is you have to take
down a lot of people to earn not very
much money ain't a good business B man
they came bro one our thought they gone
now okay man fair enough this may be
[\h__\h] but at least we work for ourselves
mean someone's [\h__\h] everyone's [\h__\h]
I'm sorry but you ain't got [\h__\h] got
even bro I just like saying
it Indie GT you ver G tubers GTA G
tubers Indie where did they come from
yeah oh my God park in the garage why do
you change the
camera okay now we're in we're in yeah I
guess my shooting was more important
than my man management skills on this
business trip for real we going to get
paid
bro okay yeah dude GT for
why uh uh
uh
yes look at that Oo we got two
goals accuracy 32%
[\h__\h] no shut up go away go
away go
away H all right one Mission done how
many more to go does anyone actually
know how much more I have to go can I
even finish it today is that realistic
of
me
eight more seven more oh that sounds not
too bad surely one of them is like more
intricate nice car not so nice car but I
mean that please no muscle car muscle
car it's a muscle car right [\h__\h] I I
don't have like the the whole controls
in myself
anymore oh how you doing ah helloand at
your club I'm Ray bulgarin oh yeah
you're the wor who was was asking about
Co cookers and corpses yeah I'm sorry we
couldn't accommodate I didn't take you
for the sensitive type I'm spending some
time here while I'll catch up with some
old friends and I need help with some
things told want to talk to listen man I
got a real busy schedule this is not an
opportunity you want to miss out on
especially as I hear that Gay Tony prin
ship is sinking I don't know you heard
that just come to my house we will talk
can you pay can you send me an
Uber uh yeah let's uh get into how do
you call a car a taxi normally again
also
nice oh this these cars are nice a uh
see this this why would you not
want uh a car with the option you have
the top down
H how could you not want this did you do
what the [\h__\h] did you do I was like
showing off flexing your
car where you
going that one over there oh my God
ow ow
Mommy okay
where can I take
you so yeah anyway back to the topic of
Fest I am as I just tweeted also I am on
stage one which is day one and I'm also
on the honeywork stage but then this
time you know normally we were split in
like two days right like half of us one
day half of us the other day but now we
split into three plus the honey workor
so it's kind of like four but honey work
isn't really split it's just like uh a
certain amount of members so yeah yeah
but free main stations which I
mean I don't know if that's the ideal
solution because if you have more OES
now like let's say you're free OES and
they're all split across the days I mean
it gives you a good reason to go to all
of them but at the same time you have to
spend so much more money to see all of
them m l i saw that nice man Mr Santo
again
nice man I mean he's a lone
shark he helped me with my
sh gentleman you could learn so much
from him stay away from him mommy listen
to me on
[Music]
this but um don't worry if you're just
kfp you only have to watch two the honey
Works sent in the day stage
one now I'm excited for it let's go
let's go
33 30 oh come on come one more these
suckers again why you got to be such a
[\h__\h] oh I'm sorry oh [\h__\h] you myy [\h__\h]
me
[\h__\h] me you can't [\h__\h] me baby b name
one thing you have ever been able to
[\h__\h] me at one thing huh I lift more
weights I fly better Choppers I have
better cars I screw better women hell I
screw women my bling ain't CZ and my
paper ain't a photo copy what's up Lou
so again one okay we have C re got on
this one man you're [\h__\h] annoying me
I work in nightclubs I hang out with
gangst I me [\h__\h] 24 hours a day but
you you take the cake man I'm sorry we
sorry that I'm trying to toughen up my
little bro here my little bro who I love
more than life it's Su and you think
that you can interfere with
that I think maybe you're taking the
tough love thing a little too far man I
mean I got sent to juvie when I was 17
years old for shooting a teacher who
felt up my sister they tried to tough me
shot a teacher didn't [\h__\h] work too
well
[\h__\h]
approach I mean there was a reason yeah
but sheesh I think you might be right
holy [\h__\h] come on baby b let's hug it
out yeah let's hug it out okay I love
you I love you it's just the truth is
I'm I'm jealous I am I'm jealous jealous
that that you are dating such a
wonderful guy as Lou here it's l calling
him kidding come on
Jesus you guys are a couple of penup
Queens I swear come on let's go have
some fun huh you too be come on stop
soaking Jesus you're
pathetic I love you but you are such a
[\h__\h] come on there's nothing wrong with
you know a man being more of a [\h__\h]
okay nothing wrong with
that let him be a p take these head said
so I can be in your ear all the way
[\h__\h] oh no thank no no please thank
you no I don't want you to be in my ear
it's good to hang with you I'm really
happy you're Along on this
ride are you [\h__\h] with me come on
little bee hey what do you take me for
it's good to have Lopez right hey The
Three
Amigos y two men and a little
[\h__\h] yeah you hear that Brucey he called
you a little [\h__\h] yeah I wasn't talking
about him bro very
veryy Lopez me and my brother are having
fun today yeah man we are we should do
this more often
bro oh B [\h__\h] before I forget there's
this email that I got that I thought
you'd be interested
in what's that oh you see it's this
doctor he's a [\h__\h] genius yeah he
says he's made this
pill Poli problem you [\h__\h] off this is
having fun you being cool bro no no I am
bro I to can extend your hose by at
least 2 to three in hey call me an
[\h__\h] but I'd be really backing a 4in
punch how's that for cool shut up Mory
the one thing you do got going for you
is those roid ravage
be anything would look big hanging next
to those peanuts right am I right shut
the [\h__\h] up
ory pathetic you see this guy Lopez what
did I tell you this guy see to stop
listening when you open your mouth
remind me again what you pay for that
place in broker Brucey huh oh and a gar
I love how they're running exactly by my
route and oh oh yeah yeah what are those
proper left bye bye good luck that I
don't want to talk about okay [\h__\h] you
see Lu I wish the best osed like a
stripper only thing more useless than
that little pecker of his is his
portfolio ain't that right Brucey hey
leave him Al Mor you're even more
annoying than usual he's a bit like you
and big okay I don't remember his usual
annoyingness should start anous circle
jerk
together yeah you can sit around crying
and hugging and talking about how you
lost it all H at least we don't know you
[\h__\h] anymore Mor remember that that guy
eras in that vet [\h__\h] genius oo
little Lopez got his in a Twist she
string on too tight is it you guys
should lighten the [\h__\h] up come on
no it's not a mother car it's not wide
enough is it even my car is kind of
wider but the
shape it is okay okay okay yeah the
shape confused
me the but it looked so small look kind
of like a baby muscle
car a low rider yeah the low rider from
me up
honestly makes them look so innocent
oh he's got a gun on his
car oh you got to watch those
[\h__\h]
bazooka my car looks like a 2005 charger
the one I'm what this is like such a
basic car it's so
[Music]
boring
I wonder how big the world will be in
GTA 6 GTA 5 was like
huge
[Music]
already they they got to go big all
right go big or go
[Music]
home I wonder if it'll be as wacky as
GTA 5 I really really love GTA 5
experience the wackiness of those free
story lines
I mean yeah in the train line looked
like like like everything looked
wacky in terms of like aligators and
naked people but I mean like that's just
like the surroundings I wonder how wacky
the main characters story lines are what
what will be the story
line
hey buddy thanks for the tip off here
you go oh thanks bro hey don't go spend
that all in one place chump all right
you guys said you think it would be like
a bonny and Clyde thingi but like a
wacky
version fla Man the game use the button
to lower the
platform what I don't I I don't have to
punch it I don't have to punch the
button a too bad that's a nice car there
you go bro h
wait let me drive what the [\h__\h]
Brucey what about
me use a
button
what what about do I get another
[Music]
one do I get my
own s what I'm pressing
s and I think he's done Ling the
platform bucked or am I supposed to get
wait are we
racing what what are this do I use this
one the dot is like still
here so that's confusing press
e oh oh okay it was saying s oh wow what
is
that
see funky
the front looks
interesting okay a Ford GT okay moving
out ladies follow me follow or race keep
up keep up
okay gas gas
[Music]
gas over us how they know what's up wake
up
panties [\h__\h] just got intense
I don't want to make this car blow up
because I'm trying to escape from the
cops
please I want to keep this one this
one's a
[Applause]
keeper come on Lopez we're waiting
they're coming down heavy
bro oh I already hear helicopters really
why why do we deserve hel what the
[\h__\h] did I shoot it they got an air unit
on us now we really got to turn
toat how did
I what
no bye-bye suckers I'm out of here we're
redoing this I did not trash the car I'm
washing the car excuse
me that curve was
mean very very mean nice
[Music]
boat we are living in the yellow
submarine yellow
submarine yellow submar was a white
submarine though but we do live in
it is that a water
car is that a old car is that a
submarine that curved though anyone who
played this game tell me you did not a
little mess up that curve and [\h__\h] up
like
[Music]
me [\h__\h] bro why the yeah man how they
know what's up wake up pities I caught
them [\h__\h] just got intense huh are you
alpha or Omega you think you can handle
it [\h__\h] hate you bro you little s
bastard [\h__\h]
[Applause]
you
H got to catch
up okay I am catching up I am catching
up hurry it up Lou stupid taxes man
that's why everybody uses Uber nowadays
for us man
you
[Music]
inferior I don't think I need to shoot
so I guess I I I'll focus on this curve
now not
cool
okay
dangerous he's also dangerous yeah you
take this
corner they know what they're
doing leading me through this
area
oh what's up
view why did they force that
camera Haven press
anything O Let's
Go what oh come come on physics guess
I'm going backwards for a
while yep what choices do I
have oh now's a turn turn turn turn
Point Turning Point yeah bye I'm too
[Music]
stupid N I don't have my license you
know Drive bro shut up and drive drive
drive drive shut up and drive drive
drive drive do be Co speaking of license
I I had a talk with
crony in the middle of the night like an
endless talk wow I don't think I ever
talked so long with her ever
before kind of started with me asking
about her
license you want a
TR
woohoo wo go easy on this one you don't
want to over another one woohoo can you
do this show me what you
got that twist that twirl like a
ballerina [\h__\h]
intense can't do
this come here I'll teach you check it
out bruy you
know might be even slightly bigger [\h__\h]
than you we're done right I mean we're
Square
you got your cars now insan St sit here
listen to your tiny man [\h__\h] at
least on your side I get style points
the game doesn't give me [\h__\h] you're as
dumb as you look o excuse me you got an
opportunity here EXC watch my lips move
I can teach you things come on think a
pred intern minion yeah think a squire
boy you following me all around learning
to become a business Mastermind no more
clubs no more tony
Queen you my friend could be free that's
not free is this a joke man I mean
you're the guy that needs to learn
something [\h__\h] you're awful bro I mean
maybe someone can teach you the most
basic human behavior M bruy please do
the sky favor PE princess me you want to
be my present guy in family with some
manners you think that I could learn
something from Little Bee here the
marshmallow man more this pale piece of
tur all right cut it
out man is nothing but beyond pathetic
that's it boy cut it
out oh I don't want to see these
prophetic idiots anymore can we kill him
oh
god what the [\h__\h] man what the [\h__\h] are
you
doing I'm sorry Moria I forgot man never
never in the face oh come on this is top
work up here you'll know that I got we
can just just just don't tell Mom okay
okay okay okay okay just you're going to
take me home can you take me home yeah
[\h__\h] okay yeah [\h__\h] come on let's go
okay okay
come okay hey I'll see you ladies later
okay yeah uh I'll see you at the club or
something okay I hurt so these [\h__\h]
are so
obnoxious oh my
God oh my top speed I got a reward for
time and top speed I didn't follow close
yet that was um a bit unfortunate this
time would have could have been better
but oh well that was another a mission
down hey wow we're
like we really don't have much left to
go did I really need to start so early
today oh
well why is everything so gray right
this game is supposed to be the gay
DLC why so gay why so
Gray yo well I found found where they
store some F620 or bullet and bullets
and you need you
need uh I
need
this eh although yeah wasn't this DLC
actually
surprisingly more colorful than
the main
game now that I look at it for the first
time in a while I can't really I
wouldn't really know hey I want the car
I
[Music]
have give me
car no not the
[Music]
polia get in that's a score hey I faster
go man faster oh [\h__\h] let's
[Music]
go is that green route my next thing
yeah okay well
then I didn't do anything I just
accidentally shot the back of a car
okay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay Stay go
away go away go away go away go away go
away Circle go away Circle
yes I am too good at escaping the
police why is everyone going up there oh
there the police car the
glitches the glitches this color is so
nice damn it's like a sparkly it's like
a like they put nail polish all over
this car
oh desie who's desie desie Deo my man
masonet what's going
onys but we could do with your input
things never run as smooth as when
you're on site me next me next okay okay
bro I'll put some hours in real
[Music]
soon yes drive
safely same color as your
car but is it this
sparkly I think it's hard to tell maybe
from the Stream
quality but it has like this like
graininess on it can you
tell it's so
sparkly to be a good color
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah but I I don't know while this is
really pretty I feel
like uh matte
cars are pretty sexy
and come on if you want to stand out
with your car and make everyone go like
oh [\h__\h] then you go for a mad car
maybe maybe
maybe and meanwhile prare
to let me thr please oh sorry thank you
sorry I don't know why there was such a
why why it was so busy
[Music]
there thanks little the
tip wouldn't you feel the same if you
see ooh nice
car same car if you see a mad car don't
you like also feel like M damn that's
nice
[Music]
man
spy not really for ma depends I mean
yeah still it kind of depends on the car
bottle too but you
know you
[Music]
know anyway anyone Here Wanting hoping
planning to go to Japan for the Expo and
the
concert I know isn't it like even more
expensive now so that's too bad but
uh
me not Fast 5 for
six so far I wish I wish I could I can't
I wish this economy here we go please no
way I can do that all right that's fine
you can watch it on suu let's stream it
guys
we can do an afterwards watch along
again or the days where I'm not involved
we can do watch
along maybe
maybe don't know how how the rules will
be this
time yeah Y is low Hees want to sell I
it's just expensive in Yen but if you
how you offer the last time if you
double it are overse million and then we
see it might be a
Ste if this banking is not hanging on my
wall your hat will be okay think about
that yeah the flights I guess you got to
swim should pay visit to his children at
this school not yet I think there's
always a prize in this
city oh Louis excuse us we're been rude
no don't worry about it I like the set
up here no just looking around gu are
all collector's items celebrity Rock
memorabilia okay man good for
you
Mr for [\h__\h] I got it for my sister hey
you bring me to this [\h__\h] country and
you keep me in an ugly no one on TV
lives in [\h__\h] duk then you come and
move all my stuff into hallway and play
with [\h__\h]
guitar shut up [\h__\h] take your pills a
friend of mine is here h you don't have
any friends you don't even have a
business here they're having a legit
conversation my sister she's still
getting adjusted with all are so how can
I help you [\h__\h] you Ray you have ruined
my life yes
yes a difficult
situation it seems I'm been investigated
by the national office of security
enforcement there is a particular unit
that has a heart on for me and what why
because
Mar won s the
Rampage you'll get rid of them I will
own this [\h__\h] team hey the problem
may just going to disappear why do I
have to do this for him leave this do
iow to me if the money tells you take
the [\h__\h] leg you'll do it because the
money is better than the [\h__\h] leg the
money is making the plans that's the
American way I man thank you I like you
I rich I make you man maybe I'll make
you a man with one leg but I'll make you
a rich man with no he'd still have two
legs there is this tracing a carow mine
take out the whole team no exceptions
okay man if that's what the money wants
you're a bright guy Louis I still like
you you made a good choice coming here
not Christmas chocolate just normal
chocolate good
go roll the [\h__\h] but I
have I have
ch
tangerines tangents tangerines for
tangents take us to the basement Park
lad in the middle
par in case I'm feeling
[Music]
fruity you're your bombs for the
party [\h__\h] that I got explosives already
and over that mg of yours and I'm ready
to
go it's good to have you with us L yeah
yes must been nice for you to get out
from
the I don't know what you're implying
bro Tony and me are Partners steak in
the
Enterprise a steak sure retrospective
and and dark box REM you C up your [\h__\h]
going hand in hand together unless you
enjoy working for such love C really bro
I don't know when I was left with my own
devices I got locked up at least with
Tony's guidance I ain't doing time yours
this is not perhaps but do think you
achieving everything you could a man
with your talents in your condition you
could have anything you want I didn't
get to where I am without being able to
see the a war of man that's real
flattering Mr Bugatti but whatever it is
you're offering I'm going to have to
decline me and Tony is a business
relationship like and and a good guy
help me out I'm not a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] bus
relationship what are you talking about
I was saying that I may be interested in
investing in your like for real for real
until as what as a businessman I'm
looking for someone here Liber to sit in
with the correct
relationship I already got one of like I
said he's been good to me of course but
what is he he is a draged dict a Madman
you are useful to him but you think that
is all he wants from you n don't come
out of your car musle bound Pretty Boy
comes along he will forget I'll go first
I'll go preious steak in the tny prince
Empire whatever bro can we talk about
something else what am I doing here you
are helping me with my business this
don't seem like legitimate business to
me man nothing can be achieved here in
Liberty City with ashal pigs rooting
through my Affairs for anything to
happen they must be eliminated okay man
you really can't buy these people off
sometimes a price is more effective if
paid out of lead not gold this is the
first lesson I will give you
than okay you done talking now now I
have to talk to Tony Mama M what do you
mean what's up where are you look man
I'm taking care of some personal
business
you the [\h__\h] up how long you going to be
I don't know way to
hell yeah man I see and do you know that
you are here with us kinky
interesting I guess
so okay now now they're done ACDC k i
put karok on my schedule I I actually
didn't decide if I wanted it to be
unarchived or archived but I'll try to
make it archived maybe I can
sing some whole life
songs maybe
some maybe some archivable anime songs
and stuff I'll see what I can
do over
there why does it have to be there I
don't like this parking
space we will conceal ourselves a bump
where they will not see it uh okay put
the bump on the front of the the
front of my car
what
my car this one good good you shouldn't
say that until it's too
late how do I crouch again things are
about to get sorry I didn't want to get
into the car no no
doubt don't speak I know what Ste bro
you ain't talking much you nervous [\h__\h]
you bazooka let's not use the Bazooka
why they are here by
bye
that's how do I how do I let around the
car I have to blow it up right how how
do I how do I do it
again what's the button
again what's the button again what's the
button again
G are they are they around
enough now is the time oh there it is
this ain't right
Yahoo They even the game told me it's
okay okay
party head shot no no you press me on my
head shot who's
alive
friend no not friend friend uh yes
friend yes friend
I oh
put come on don't be in my
face my shots are more important than
yours I don't see anyone
oh
oh my God I need to reload so
often someone's here
oh oh my God I'm
dying [\h__\h] it I'm not wasting any time
today is he
dead oh what was
that
hacks it's me or you more more more more
no yeah let's
go can we get a corpse
[Applause]
counter all right all right all right
all
R let's go
more
assh oh be careful
there the FIB is
here so famous let's go
oh head
shot and last but not least officer
goodbye
say at least five
that that that's uh I think a bit more
than that so credit where credit is due
please lose
the what if I kill them
though now we need to drop
these
now okay do you want to use the car or
no go that way
[Music]
I feel like blowing up something
but no it's not really the
right [\h__\h]
youo stop hurting my friends oh oh oh
God why you guys here why are civilians
here you really shouldn't be here take
bulgarin and teamour back to bulgar
house oh they're still kind of alive go
for them go for them must have had a
high defense
stat uh how we going guys are we taking
a
Car Any Car Any
Car you go back to my sister
[Music]
house you want is that my
sirene I still have smell of meat nose
oh no my tire is true you are the one
who blew them up that unit
lose job most competent how I get myself
into this [\h__\h] man you yourself into
this I Choose You I pick you out because
I see potential in you you're lucky to
be here all right but if you need more
cops taking out crooked or otherwise you
ain't choosing me look at this the
sensitive modern American World you need
to home and explain your mult may as
well cut them off what the [\h__\h] is this
I don't like killing government agents
you down we got no more law enforcement
to exp Mo those were the only
guys you think he will sell he has no
choice but to sell have taking away his
protection it's that simple is it it
should be Mak is a whitling he lives
here in Exile like all CS but he has
been here for a long time so he has B
connections that others of us have not
been able to acquire I need a tire
should have sever good my tire has
expired and we'll keep others
involved before they continue their
Association okay perhaps I will buy
clubs home you as well you sell them to
me them gloves is levers to the max
already man I don't know if there's
anything left to sell I don't care about
other invest they will forgot about
deaths if I'm involved I [\h__\h] some
these investors aren't the type to go
away oh my God what are they talking
about I can't listen it's not my place
to sell them I have a but Ton's got the
controlling sh head empty brain
empty and the little puppet man dance
for him the sirene in my head going
we
D [\h__\h] man what's wrong with you you st
is [\h__\h] you think you run the club
but you're still just reach reminds me
of going to skip and you won't admit
like that one ampper clipping me all the
time recently when I say something about
am you think this is enough to to get a
clip
[Music]
too I'm man
sounds like
[Music]
her now he went maybe I don't
know greetings greetings Amy Clipper I
enjoy your
clippies think about what I said to you
turn off to be fair turn it off okay I
will send my regards to Big T what's
happening like what's happening what's
happening like what's
[Music]
happening ah shut up oh look at that I
got like most of the targets
oh oh I did not cheat no no you're
making that up let me get out of this
shitty car oh my God all right and
another mission down are we like ending
super early today or what oh I think I'm
getting a call because there is no
mission on the map which is a good sign
guys we're getting to the
Endy just waiting for a
call no what nobody's actually like
uh no no no nobody's mad at me right for
cheating a little bit right
right I played GTA so much without
cheats okay I've proved
myself okay good I'm
living yeah I love that camera but like
why don't you try and me where where's
oh there's a bee
now there's a
bee
it it's right there
I was just there hey get your guess it
needed some time to move on to the next
step that can it be
oh more clip
content
EMP I was looking for fan out I had
saved the other day and I found this
froggy Wawa and am fan art and it
reminded me I need to do froggy waa and
am
collab
urgently something stronger huh I'm cool
bro you know how to play the drums we
need a [\h__\h] drummer I guess I do your
man bro sorry you Spanish have the rythm
I know how to play the drums as good as
you guys know how to play the guitar
drown B you dance don't you Lou dance I
can dance man but not with you and him
that's a shame you dance Mr
B Money froggy wa is very very popular
dance my friend there's so much
possibility with froggy waa wait wait
[Music]
L this is it this is it hey can you ask
to stop playing for a second look at him
in the back jamming you want I should
stick $50,000 guitar up your ass no but
I got some friends I can intr ruce you
to if that's how you get your kicks oh
funny guy all
right all right
okay you have heard about Liberty City
Rampage the owner still will not accept
my offers I have been more than
reasonable you mean after you killed the
special team of cops it's weird you want
me to negotiate tangerina now while
listening to this T time for
negotiations over do what needs to be
done in his boardroom send a message hey
I ain't a Hitman bro I mean I'll fight
anyone do whatever but I ain't a
contract killer I'm not the offices feel
like are in the me TV buildings oh get
in it will not be easy you'll have to
find someone else man I mean it's not my
thing I Ain qualifi for this I'm going
to end up doing it though am I not I'm
sorry I wasn't discussing you Career
Development I was telling you what to do
no [\h__\h] off and
go
see I do everything what people tell me
to
do I
am wait for I
am team more is joining me we must pick
up Chopper go to elport
no not the tip Chopper not the whip
Whopper hey I'm sorry to break up your
party man you look like you were having
fun Mr Ray wanted me to keep watch on
you make sure you do are told hey I
don't need no Watcher no Mr R think you
do no
way [\h__\h] you think I want be here
whatever okay one tangerine SL so so
[\h__\h] what so what's up Bro [\h__\h]
off chill man I'm just trying to
converse with
my job is Hospitality my job is as for R
bul bro I like to think I can talk to
people I try to put them at ease make
them open up sure they open up when you
shoot in their head you put people in
the ground my friend you killer like me
that's what
Bulgarian so that's what you do
hospitality is for
weaklings cuz I don't I don't feel like
switching around my controls right now
you're hard work Bro [\h__\h] You you are
hard work don't even know what you are
hey I know who I am sure I do bad [\h__\h]
let see how going be forever I've heard
this before [\h__\h] off you want me to shut
up good good yeah the checkpoints are
Silence from here on
[Music]
in all
right let's give it a try oh this is
not
what's the point in learning English if
you're going to be such a miserable
[\h__\h] just like me for real for
real learn language connect with Z you
know knowing more than one
language gives you so much more
perspective listen to the radio on these
trips they ran out of dialogue
already nothing to talk about awkward
this is not a good passenger princess
that I have do you guys want to maybe
jump in be your better passenger
princess my lips
seal where did you say that
for what you say that you see
fing
right he like uh faed through the seat I
just noticed when falls
[Music]
back police car what are you
doing where are you trying to
go you're [\h__\h] terrible
conversationalist Al so they do like
pick up on that okay okay what the
[\h__\h] you've got no game
team
total [\h__\h]
silence so true I like it though we can
we can keep it like
this he's so mad that he's not talking
though wow I would appreciate
it you ain't getting a peep out of me
you want me [\h__\h] hit
[Music]
you
why even though I started driving late
it would have still not been enough
dialogue to cover this whole drive if I
were to start driving
immediately I [\h__\h] shoot this
guy please
[Music]
move five star Uber
review but I'm I'm I'm the driver think
the dri driver is complaining that the
passenger is too
quiet that's kind of
weird all right I have arrived oh we've
been here
before take command of Chopper ah the GP
Chopper the whip
Whopper I don't know why I say that now
it's kind of fun to say you starting
something yes starting the big
one H I don't remember how to
control the we go above star Junction
you can go I better bring us up over the
H we going to get the altitude
a oh numpad eight is forward I will tell
you what you must W is
higher great thanks uh cap you tell me
what the plan is Ash office what we're
going to space not going to get oh that
[\h__\h] up my Japanese keyboard let's
switch to German from ground so you
coming from above out the chopper great
he's not so tough I would do but there
is Chance Ash's people come for my
family back in old place and you ain't
worried about my family no tell me why
we can't just land on the building I'm
here you think you would not noce
Chopper building going silent when you
get in build building I will give
instructions through headset you kill
Ash send message and leave building I
pick you up on ground sounds real t for
you that's so high what the
[\h__\h] can I make it
[Music]
yeah next one next one do we really have
to go so
high team War be like can we get much
higher
please I want to see the stars show me I
want to go above the fog so I can see
all the
stars together with you my
love so
romantic oh we're
parachuting
right so far like this is not no no
issue just flying up high as long as
it's not a Chase or
something
okay okay okay
okay okay you soon need jump I will jump
not flirting no jump out I know how to
jump out F [\h__\h] this right and then what
did I what did I press to uh right click
maybe you're going to Splat if I don't
know okay it was left
woohoo Fu going to be very comedic if I
wouldn't have gotten a reply from chat
until I landed but I randomly figured it
out where are we going I see something
on the map but it's like far I have to
land on top of a building or
what [\h__\h] what which building which
building all right how you manag to miss
that big I don't know which one that one
but that's so high how about this
one I'm
redo n Mr lus Mr B you might have heard
that I didn't make the land you floor to
run like some [\h__\h] [\h__\h] fairy
maybe you did on purpose it wasn't on
purpose man I just missed it I'll talk
to you soon
[Music]
okay
where do we restart in the middle of the
flight would be
nice before jumping out ideally
yeah jump out it already says jump out
where is it we're still so
far let me get a little bit closer I can
get closer
right
you see the
ring I see no ring I see the a pink tip
of a
building on the pink light okay on the
very top go back e no I want to jump
here I'm going to swing out over the
broko bridge we'll gain some hide and
come back over the City Light Start
Junction as high high as possible okay
but can you like change the camera you
little shits like
what I have headset for you this is so
we communicate when you in building just
what I always wanted a hotline to a
[\h__\h] charmer you like to parachute
it's an occupational hazard what's that
mean it means I don't like doing
anything that could easily kill me but
sometimes you got to to why you tell Mr
Ray you are not killer you scared we
nearly here when you go I will take
control too high I
guess please I want to I need more
leeway
please push push up lower lower
lower look at these precise movements by
me can I jump
now go a little bit higher St
sh oh
[\h__\h]
a turn around turn around there we
should could be here [\h__\h] now I know
where to go but that land is is like
he's sinking so
fast how can I make
it the one on the right not that one a
a guys you said pink of course I'm going
to look there but I was thinking that's
kind of
impossible okay
all right that one's
easier that's a helicopter landing pad
why don't we just you know land with the
helicopter uh
oh okay go go
go made it
move I'm
here no I'm not there no don't look at
me
it's fine they accepted
it there is someone on roof find out
what is
up this [\h__\h] die
now we have I'm not on a
roof I'm going to shoot this [\h__\h] in
the
balls okay party party
time I'm in find Ash and take him out
let's
[Music]
go where are you guys oo vest but I
already have one but it's nice of them
to put one
there are we going through this
door I thought I was ready mentally
but not quiet where the [\h__\h] are you
man you good oh is that gas or
something oh my there
alive are they on top of the
elevator that's why I have to take the
helicopter to the top because you guys
are blocking the elevator man
[Music]
you there what you doing te I wait for
you to kill this is this team more bet
please my teammates really have to be
like more clearly indicated otherwise
I'm going to kill
themad you enjoy yourself I need these
are F your boss a lot
of
I like how the pipes can be
shot you done yet chill out bro I'm
lucky to still be alive
mhm I'm I'm me I see the Min map
but approach I'm moving
in
hiding I hear that are
[Music]
going we' got
you wiy Wicky where are you at I'm still
in here cutting through these [\h__\h] I
tell you when I'm
done nobody saw
that you
finish
you go
down nice though through the ledge I
mean come on got to give me credit for
that are we going for this door no it's
a fake door
okay f
someone
hereu oh [\h__\h] oh the fire
alarm is that scripton did I do
that
[Applause]
boy
M no [\h__\h] reload interior decoration
just get job
done wait how do
you how do you
stand oh
well I got Target [\h__\h]
he some othering ass want dead don't
shoot
the you hey are you my thought was
E I need a
okay it's hard to
see this one too much looking
for you're in the
bag oh he had his hands up
oh I didn't do
that yeah that sound is the and suddenly
we're
here I would like a suit oh
my can I go can I go can I go too
oh okay that was the plan anyway okay
land on the truck which truck uh blue
blue blue blue blue blue blue truck this
truck
truck land on the truck they say as if
it's that easy a that
thing how the [\h__\h] how am I supposed to
land on that no time to wait it's not
worth the risk good luck buddy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
what uh take them out or Escape okay uh
we're basically
done goodbye that was close oh oh oh
H
uh no problem no
problem it was
bugged hey what's going on they're so
glitchy
[Music]
fuing ugly
[\h__\h] it's okay I mean this is just a
small amount of enemies I don't have to
run hey he
oh okay interesting Mission I mean the
controller wasn't
necessary didn't need it I'm told you
didn't good job thank you where' you
hear that from Timmer that guy left me
to get killed bro some getaway driver
[\h__\h] him patient man he does not suffer
Weck how can you land on the truck so
what you had to drive yourself away you
are still alive I'm still I think much
of your abilities there will be a place
for you in my new Empire please come to
see me
soon
okay I don't want to see any more of you
what's your TT a what's your
GTA what's your GTA what's your
GTA did you guys Noti this the title
it's a reference to new jeans which whom
I love very
dearly K-Pop group they have a song
that's what's your ETA what's your
ETA and every time I think of GTA I
think of what's your GTA what's your
GTA
really love K-pop fans dropping in to
praise the title let's
go I am one of one of you they are one
of me yourself L my man how things bro
yeah not that great my father he is a
very passionate and angry and very
disrespectful man but listen can you
come and meet me at the construction
site I have something to discuss yeah
okay man I'll try to come
by okay
whatever he wants from me first we're
going
here yeah yeah yeah I talk a lot about
new jeans they're so good they're just
so good it's still like So Fresh So new
where's the one man Ben is working
okay can't afford new jeans but we'll
always support new jeans ha shut up so
I've got for some people I know that
maybe you have some diamonds for sale me
not me my boss Tony my other boss yeah
yeah you got them from the fat cook Ray
Ray what are you still doing here anyway
I'll stay as long as I like you think
you're a big man where's your house on
Middle Park East where's your big sport
team huh shut up you
C [\h__\h] you shut up you [\h__\h] C oh calm
down B is she okay big gun next to a big
man H your thingy was Tiny even before
the wrestling coach make you take
steroid only
had the diamonds tell me I got to talk
to Tony you got to talk to Daddy I
thought I was making you a real man not
a r Bo well I can't sell what ain't mine
bro plus with all the work I put in for
you I don't really feel like a man yet
okay soon man soon I want you to cover
timur's back he's going to talk to some
people I need you there okay man I got
it but you should chill out
bro let me decide want to chill out
go
dude maybe call the
ambulance y
y go to the building and protect teer I
have to protect
teer you're for real
bro can I take this car thank
you calling my
[Music]
car oh well oh well oh well did you guys
see the schedule for this week do you
like it do you like it tomorrow we're
playing the fan game I know I said I
don't really feel like it but I decided
I'm going to play it anyway because it's
now or
never let's see if it will be
fun
and what else are we doing we're having
a member stream that'll be just chatting
and I'm thinking of you know I it's like
it could be a get ready with me stream
because it'll be right before the Mee
and green and I said it'll be a short
one this time right so I squeezed it in
before the meet and greet there'll be an
hour of me getting ready for the meet
and grade and like I don't know maybe
thinking about what to wear and what to
say maybe maybe put on some
makeup you know um um you
[Music]
know just get ready for you guys
yeah and what else what else what else
oh yeah the cookies we're baking the
cookies also by the way uh so turns out
my stock puppets are in
Japan they're I have I don't think I got
them
back JMA is now looking for them
because since
the uh
Expo we're not sure about the
whereabouts
yeah I I hope I can get them back in
time I mean shipping shouldn't take too
long but I hope that I hope my suck
puppet wouldn't get lost in the Customs
can you imagine every single [\h__\h] that I
get sent from Japan gets stuck in the
Customs there you you you can't like
have my sock my selfmade shitty scuffed
sock puppets imagine a customs officer
opening it up and and it's like oh my
god what the [\h__\h] is this oh but hey
it's for takanasi yeah let's let's
[\h__\h] bully the [\h__\h] out of her and
annoy her about this and and be like oh
we need we need an invoice for this
please uh a payment uh confirmation oh
oh it's not that okay then you know
business blah blah blah no no no not
this time not this time you can't [\h__\h]
with me this time these are self-made
socks okay don't touch
them you will give me my socks no matter
what if they make a drama out of it out
of this too I swear I'm I'm going to
[\h__\h] riot I'm going to go there to
the customs office in person I'm going
to say who the [\h__\h] do you think you are
to stop the Christmas Joy from happening
huh huh this is all all hypothetical but
you are ruining the Christmas Joy of
thousands of people in the whole life
English
Community yeah they the Grinch in
position do see backs in front of
you yeah open it the mission of
retrieving the
puppets have you open it yet no give me
a sec looks kind of bloody in
yo holy
[\h__\h] do
you
[\h__\h] I I believe we parted with him in a
diamond
d y what the [\h__\h] is this the guy we
brought the ice from you colluded with
him to steal from me yo we just got some
rocks off him okay look listen no you
listen I offered you an opportunity yet
you were pling against me y I ain't no
[\h__\h] about those rocks but I believe it
doesn't matter I will do everything in
my considerable power to drive you in
your [\h__\h] master from this elf
goodbye
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] great who home
[Music]
home what the [\h__\h] is going
on take the snippity
snipers try to pin the location take him
out okay he it imagine imagine you're
just walking on the streets of New York
City and suddenly you see someone
falling down with a sniper
gun this an accurate reaction I felt
something I felt the wind
what what were you thinking
Lopez I seeing something on the map you
are dead but it disappears after a while
oh
oh that one will never be found I
imagine no one goes up to that roof nice
blood splatter though take the [\h__\h]
time and
[\h__\h] ah
I see
you beautiful
work Flawless he'll feed the pigeons
yeah give the pigeons some good [\h__\h]
food they deserve it it's locked pigeons
get bullied so much man with kids
running into them and be
like surprise
[\h__\h] just stop giving pigeons
heart attacks man can we normalize
leaving pigeons the [\h__\h] alone
huh
stop running into
pigeons it's not
cool they have weak Hearts
yeah what the [\h__\h] is going on what
the uh find a way off the roof oh but
what if I use my bazooka
mine oh God it's going to be a little
bit slow though why it's moving so
much
no goodbye building uh okay
uh I can't
move
off what what do mean what do you mean I
can't go through the
door wait wait wait wait where am I
supposed to go where am
I why am I why am I I hate I hate this
okay where where where where do we want
to
go do I just I just kill
him
now I mean we can do it like that I
don't mind it oh oh that's the
helicopter
right yeah I'm going to die I'm going to
die H just this door is close to oh my
God I should shoot the helicopter I'm
going to try it
again now
they
no
y sa you right bastard [\h__\h] oh there's
a there's a there's a
thingy nice don't have to cheat oh my
God oh my God oh my
God are they
dead I have made the
helicopter
shut
up was
there was there a [\h__\h] bomb
there hey I felt so safe but I heard
something ticking and I was like what
what's every everyone's dead what could
it
[Laughter]
be grenade why why why why
why of course it's locked is
okay oh my I I start by getting head
shot like what the
hell cover
me
moving
[Music]
in yeah all right all right all
right now it's
quiet
everywhere off that
roof oh they don't com
I got to be careful before they shoot
another one of those at me getting close
watch we have you surrounded
up oh what was that was that the
helicopter
crashing I got you oh my God oh my God
oh my
God I will die
guys tell me tell me when they're
throwing a grenade at me okay you tell
me I I hear a lot of things blowing up
man oh oh oh
oh hurt me I was climbing I can't climb
faster than that the [\h__\h] who was
that
how do I get
them
goodbye who who where are
they I'm going to die I'm going to
oh oh get in there I don't know get in
there
I was down to zero HP oh
Mia M Mia I get out of there I'm
stuck I'm just trying to keep the the
Stream flow smooth for the viewer
experience you
know come
on behind yo it don't
stop wait I heard a I heard a grenade I
think run run you little
[\h__\h] I feel like I heard someone
throwing a grenade at
me I don't know I'm really paranoid now
I was in the bunker yeah what what am I
what's my mission right now kill them
all cuz like they're not on the map
so what do they want they're not
indicated on the map the
enemies
are
Escape I feel like I escaped already I I
left the building
here
oh maybe that's why they don't indicate
them because
uh they'll be endlessly spawning and I
should just leave live the area
Okay the streets are so empty
wow beautiful if only it was always as
empty what's this
building it's quite nice is there a
hotel in there
let's get in
here my house can I
visit GTA 6 is the second GTA game with
a female protagonist yeah cuz the first
one is me like I am the protagonist
right right that's what you're trying to
say right right
right which which one is the other
one
I wish I was the protagonist
man GTA 1 was that on like the Game Boy
advancer so
who the graphics were probably so bad
you couldn't even tell it was a
woman it's just a pixel so does that
really
count Playstation One ah
L [\h__\h] I've been looking for you listen
tonyon I got something to talk to you
about you remember that Ray buling
guy you think he'd lend us the money we
need to get out of this [\h__\h] he's bad
news I hate to be the voice of reason
here but I don't think we need that kind
of stress in our lives oh yeah man we
already got it I talked to him about
some opportunities and it turns out the
diamonds we bought were stolen off him
in the first place he cut that Cook's
head off man want story short he wants
his de de poor old Chef what were you
doing talking to these guys without me L
I'm sorry man I [\h__\h] up kind of
refreshing though for me to be the one
getting a in [\h__\h] for once don't you
think yeah a real
relief that was
Japanese let's go to
YF cuz cuz we're in Asia town oh
[\h__\h] that actually sounded
um uh
authentic so uh maybe they actually
hired
someone Japanese oh just for a
background voice
sheesh I kill these cows myself I kill
these cows
myself says the guy from what what hot
dog stand or
so well how reassuring I mean I don't
know it could be kind of kind of
reassuring because if you do it yourself
it may be more in a more hum humane way
I guess so maybe that's a reassuring
statement
yo [\h__\h] would you shut the [\h__\h] up man
what's wrong with you who yo yo easy
amigo I'm just pleased to see you yeah
come on baby give me some ski can Dude
well you know it's my father
uh hey you know my ancestors we built
the pyramids baby we built the
ziggurats very M and [\h__\h] I'm here I'm
not afraid I get my hands dirty well I
can work whatever man how's it
going epic homie this [\h__\h] is epic
people r a bobble about this [\h__\h] in the
future baby I'm talking luxury a whole
new level place so expensive people
won't even be able to afford it it's
going round in Gold you know it's like
uh yo yo yo is that a diamond in your
pocket you just pleased to see me and
[\h__\h]
who know the Sal Sheet's going to say
ah Impossible Dream Priceless
Indulgence Style by yusf Amir Timeless
classic Timeless classic yeah sounds
perfect man just what the people want
right now but what are you doing
here I'm crafting this whole thing with
my bare hands okay cool man listen it
was good catching up with you okay I'll
see you soon yeah not so fast homie yo
could you uh give me a ride to my
helicopter I can tell you something
along the way but I thought you was was
busy building the pyramids all work and
no play makes use of a d boy come on
baby be
[Music]
fun that'll be 1599
please
homeboy yeah okay that's a nice egg yolk
car wait for it I'm
[Music]
waiting are we back because OBS died for
a
moment
we back okay you ready just [\h__\h] tell
me bro a
[\h__\h] subway train yeah baby the
prize of the fleet the ass [\h__\h]
Flagship of the LTA give it up what you
want a subway train we're taking that
[\h__\h] out to the gulf for a new Liberty
City theme development out there check
this out genuine LTA submarine we're
getting the submarine of our Dream going
through a precious and delicate coral
reef perfect Del aside from how [\h__\h]
dumb that sounds how am I supposed to
take that thing not going to be easy dog
no one likes people [\h__\h] with their
public transport in this can't you just
buy yourself a subway car bro no man
[\h__\h] we need the genuine article the
real deal you think we could put the am
name to anything but authentic [\h__\h] yo
how am I supposed to pull this off okay
we just need the front car of the train
you jump on board you climb to the front
and you unhook the car I'll handle all
the rest Real Simple Man I don't know
why I hang out with you bro cuz you
[\h__\h] love this [\h__\h] homie that sounds
like a difficult Mission boy and I'm
going to put your clubs on the world
stage we have a lounge on the Moon by
the time we're done for real your
me believe it baby pinch yourself you
ain't dreaming this is no film the city
is our playground homie if it's our
playground I come I'm the only one
getting dirty I do like his enthusiasm
I'm going to look after you you and Tony
your problems man youf can make them go
away you better be able to bro cuz
you're about to owe me big
time damn yeah if he has so much money
why does he not just like buy the thing
that he wants why do why do we steal
it
why stop ring on the
right offense yeah but he can buy the
real thing then it's still
authentic here's where you B the
train get in position above the tax man
I'll see you soon well I don't like this
what am I supposed to do
what what what do I jump onto it what
that will not go
well a
oh I hear
it oh my God I made it fight your way
along the train who am I fighting and
disconnect the front Carriage okay what
why am I
fighting oh there's
helicopters
where's oh what it's weapon I have holy
[\h__\h] oh okay now I can handle
this
yo what is
yo here we
go you
at auto shotgun
Yahoo how do I disconnect this
thing or is this currently oh God oh
God Sho Sho shot
shoot why 1 2 3
4 I about a chocolate
more oh my it's getting a little bit
bloody [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
uh oh
reload you treat all the commuter like
this oh my God the boom boom
sound boom boom
insane it's like a
subwoofer you [\h__\h] with the wrong
computer press left Ctrl duck oh he's
ducking for me anyway holy
[\h__\h] I'm just going to continue fighting
until they oh my what is right next to
me too close too close too
close this connect well I don't have
time I he doesn't even move like I
can't why does he not he doesn't move
though he's like stuck in the spot am I
doing something
wrong oh my
God why does it suddenly appear right in
front of
me what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
kind of sick yeah you were there for 20
seconds that's so weird I didn't see
like any button to um disconnected what
why are you
[Music]
screaming they meleed me with a [\h__\h]
helicopter
but them telling me to duck underneath
feels like they were like that moment
was scripted and they wanted me to get
to that point and I just got to the
front too
fast I don't
know I thought like this now I'm just
riding the [\h__\h] menro
okay so I'm here but like he he get
stuck there and then I then it won't let
me move
anymore Dominican oh I think my ears
broke from that keep moving I can't I
can't I'm pressing forward but it
doesn't
move no I restarted without
armor leave me alone but I also can't
get it now I [\h__\h] hate
helicopter yeah I can't cheat now yeah
it's scripted like it doesn't move I
swear they want me to get to the point
where I have to duck I
guess what was the button for
ducking uh left
Ctrl oh oh I'm ducking I'm dhole what
the [\h__\h] I don't know that didn't seem
really helpful can we UND duck thank
you wor through this
train oh here there's something
fun shoot treat all the commu like
this okay I don't think I can take this
one down they want this moment to happen
happen don't explode on top of me that
was close
woo okay I'm going to die the wrong
commuter there we go I'm going to die
please let this end now I saw you
guys don't shoot me no no what can I
do oh we're doing it we're finally doing
it what the [\h__\h] is that that's not even
the real helicopter up
there oh that's him okay okay it's a
lifting
helicopter damn can you really do it
that
easily just
one one flip with your
finger that was really close man I had
one
HP
he so stupidly
unnecessary this
Heist do you really need this in your
life I love you don't drop me like that
I'm low on HP with it you C
fool get rid of the stars for me please
I don't want them five stars is a little
bit too
much
[Music]
there we go
25,000 let's go o terrorist I Should
Have Cheated afterwards wait but I got
all
four oh well cuz yeah okay play a damage
I just
uh if I would have cheated one second
later then that would have not counted
mhm so I did did pretty
well uh going to
towy do I not get to keep that cool
Weapon by the way like holy
[\h__\h] that was
insane where where are the CL hello
hello where the [\h__\h] am I Central
Park
but you can buy one
oh oh this a pretty strong and useful
weapon especially for the helicopters or
any big bulky thing listen man I told
you I didn't know [\h__\h] about who own
them diamonds then maybe you should have
asked instead you ran around this city
making a full of me you're in your
[\h__\h] boss we'll be killed for this I
will do everything in my power to I
think the singal's dropping man later
[Music]
bro okay we're going to
Tony that's like a taxi taxi we are L
abiding C citizens after
all as you can tell hey
buddy
mhm here we are oh what
the what are you
doing this is one good thing about GTA 4
being more scuffed than GTA 5 confident
we have a good it's good SCU hey you
want to list yes no yes you're not
coming in oh wait a minute man we're
relatively important people we're going
in bro I don't give a [\h__\h] who you
coming in come on man I'm a VIP we we
come here all the time hey DES hey man
tonan I ain't seen him hey man Lou bro
can you get us in hey Brucey yeah sure
up Tessie take care of
[Music]
them I I've never been in a club like
this before some vagina tonight just
seems like a realistic thing to happen
never mind
so I'm going to go get the
drinks the way somebody who's first
denied of getting him so SM once they do
get in listen can I just say the way you
dealt with B I was really great you're
welcome hey don't mention it man unless
you want me to kill him maybe Hey listen
you know you're like me that's right
you're like a alone wolf and Advent
tough but with a
sensitive like
yes yes I know but that's just your
thing oh he likes me what's your problem
man I'm not gay cool man just don't do
it again man hey look I [\h__\h] reg girls
last night man one of them can't even
see I got those vibes from the beginning
now she could walk before she didn't
need a wheelchair or anything look I was
just checking to make sure you weren't
gay
bro Hey listen hey Louis come on man I
say youen gay no homo man
no totally totally totally
bro
swag thank God you showed up bro never
thought make things feel more
heterosexual yeah
totally pret didn't hear thatwe to man
dude
dude I
totally I'm so so hard into [\h__\h] you
know yeah to totally that's my thing
yeah let's go Pier
45 he it wrong to kiss your homies right
exactly good point back she's coming
home you mean taking her back or this
going to be trano God I hope so they're
getting the diamonds for her so they
better behave [\h__\h] wait a second slow up
man what if the diamonds got to do with
Gracie what the [\h__\h] have we got to do
with Gracie shouldn't her old man be
handling this apparently the kidnappers
have asked for these rocks and we aren't
being given much of a choice about it if
you catch my meaning oh great angry
moners kidnappers Maniacs sounds like
another fun
day are we like I feel like I've done
like already 10 missions since I started
the stream why is there so many
taxis how how many do I have left this
doesn't feel like I'm close to the end
to be
honest three more and you're done for
real doesn't feel like
it the the buildup I don't feel
it h but okay okay okay three
more that will be a quickie
[Music]
today fast
stream W wa fastest game
finisher not not only the only Ian to
finish GTA 5 on stream but also the only
end to finish GTA 4 on stream oh my
God can you imagine GT GTA 6 sponsoring
me when it comes out could you imagine
how [\h__\h] dope that would be please
give me early access please please you
know what I will tell cuz like uh not
not it doesn't guarantee anything at all
but like we can like give like hints on
what kind of sponsorships we are
personally looking for or hoping for to
the management I'll I'll tell them I'll
tell them does Rockstar sponsor anyone
at
all they already know I I don't know
like even even big famous companies with
big games they still sponsor people you
know not necessarily mean you
know not something I've seen happen I'll
make it
happen nice boat nice
boat yeah they don't need it exchange is
on charge Island they're com by land
we're on the water it still happens you
know big companies still sponsor people
you know
no oh even Early Access would would be
cool yeah not being sponsored just
claiming ownership he's got some serious
res Early Access like maybe should think
maybe how about July
2024 to the
Russian don't have to pay me I can be a
game tester I'm a perfect game
journalist fig out I got nothing figured
out City I'm very well vered in game
journalis
[Music]
Don I'm too much of a gamer to be game
generous really what a
[Music]
compliment I'm better really I'm better
time to bankrupt
ourselves oh wait what I'm [\h__\h] I'm
missed my stuff cuz of you guys cuz of
you guys praising me
[Music]
wait
over
here uh there we
go
this was a bit more difficult than doing
it with a
car but I did
it if you can beat the cuphead tutorial
you're over qualified I never played
that that indeed looks difficult sure
I'm sure father's going to kill us if we
don't yeah makes it nice and simple yeah
lends a lot of clarity to my
thinking
[Music]
a his
stance
oh the boys the bastards didn't hurt you
did they you can't speak we got a gag in
her mouth give her back you animals she
suffered enough hand over the stuff hand
over
Gracie I'm here for you sweet hand over
the [\h__\h] stop all right calm down both
of you oh yeah we put the ice in the
middle we walk back then you send over
the girl I've seen this before somewhere
up the stuff
an sure show us the goods this feels
very
familiar but I don't remember the
outcome come back to me
honey let her go
oh oh so
peaceful I like this it's very peaceful
with the birds in the
background
what's going on what's going
on you right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
babe you okay where did you [\h__\h] kill
them you [\h__\h] nothing huh you
[\h__\h] oh wow
go W that went
well
you
[\h__\h] don't hang on to my
boat is there a word for like a
passenger that's not supposed to be on
board [\h__\h] Chomp off our boat hey I'm
trying okay Tony you're [\h__\h] pathetic
I need to drive and curve our Bo sway
yeah yeah yeah a world of his
own who someone told to kill can you
guys not just go back there and then
[\h__\h] suffer get his off the getting
to know what tip we sit out here [\h__\h]
oh my God that reminds me where is my
daddy he oh my God that reminds me I saw
this video on Twitter of [\h__\h]
apparently it's like really famous and I
just died now like people in a boat
[\h__\h] gun give me a [\h__\h] iron
and the guy just like he drives so
recklessly like for real and then the
cute girls and the Su and and all the
the cool dudes and everybody oh he's
gone [\h__\h] to kidnap me you know that
video like suddenly like everybody's
just being like found around the boat
and it's insane and you see how they go
like and BK their heads on the boat and
she had a voting accident make sure old
man understands that I don't want to see
her again okay sailor so long that's
insane like did no one they must have
gotten like really injured oh another
mission you're telling me I only have
two missions
left that video killed me the first time
I was honestly very concerned when I saw
it and I didn't even understand like
what was going on but uh I thought like
it wasn't like the fault of the driver I
thought like maybe some they they like
bonked against uh
something or malfunction or something I
don't know it turns out must have been
the guy just wanting to flex too much
okay okay and going too hard with his
boat I guess I don't
know the people were fine yeah I I I I
hope so yeah I think I read like in the
comments like usually when I see
something like this I get when I get
concerned I I check all the replies and
look for an
outcome don't [\h__\h] Lou have you heard n
lives are falling apart no yes no sort
of the city's closed down the clubs you
serious those [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and we forgot to pay off the
Citadel [\h__\h] D maybe this is a good
thing at least we can concentrate on
getting off every gangster's headit list
we better do it quick there's no more
money coming in it's only going to get
worse for us [\h__\h] me I need some
blow oh
another I hate the way he goes
downstairs uh we still don't have
anything marked do we okay then I'll
just get a car and wait sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry
sorry
it was a racing boat they all knew what
they signed up for but they're like if
they knew what they were signing up for
why would they stand like you
know they should sit
down do do these boats have seat belts I
guess they're too cool to put on a seat
belt
but Luis Lopez what could you possibly
have to say that I'd want to hear Rock
time to face the facts Jack frankly
you're [\h__\h] there's a rich Russian
having a powow with the old man about
you and the [\h__\h] FYI they ain't talking
about handing you a special Commendation
well what the [\h__\h] are me and th
supposed to do about that let's leave
the homo out of this for a minute meet
me and Uncle venzo in the public toilets
in Middle Park we got to talk in purse
Middle Park Central
Park okay let me
get a cab we don't have this
deal
[Music]
this car please this this taxi can I get
this taxi no no this can
I oh there's someone inside oh well well
don't mind hey why why why you leave
what's your problem with me little Park
I know F we can drop you off first and
then
me I don't know what the fascist won't
let me drive there but I can let you off
nearby if that's
okay f sh won't let you drive is that
what he said l r listen you [\h__\h] with me
Louise no no not at all that's how
things seem but trust me that wasn't my
intention you [\h__\h] with me and now I'm
going to [\h__\h] with you you little cun
you are dead dead dead
dead you understand no could you say it
again please [\h__\h] you I'm still not
getting it what about a third time bye
excuse me who was that I don't know who
that was I have a new phone new phone
who this I I should really just reply
like this like act as if I don't know
him who who who's this sorry who what
did you say who what a nice
flower in the middle of nothing this one
Little Flower it gives me hope in this
dark and gray day and
age it gives me hope especially because
it's two and it's a sign I think it's a
sign from Heavens that I have two
missions left and after that I'll be
celebrated like a hero the true hero
that I
am
yeah better times are coming for
me new jeans are coming for
me careful he's got sex sexophone the
sexophone made a on the ground are
youself youself you staying out of
trouble man you better believe it bro
totally guilt free it's business
business business with me yeah why that
make me think you're about to ask me to
do some dumb [\h__\h] Dam what do you take
me for I'm a giver not a taker I don't
need anything from you I want to make a
gift of my car to you a special machine
but you know what you have done for me
recently the the yolk one thanks a lot
bro you didn't need to do that though I
do want the yolk car there's a little
bit of fun for you in the glove
compartment I think you will enjoy it
all right man I'll check that out no
glove compartment
what what what could be in there that
fits in a glove
compartment H that's what I told him
first we do this never happened back in
a
day what's up ladies still living the
high life I see [\h__\h] you what you doing
here cruising very funny you Mr
ancelotti still blaming all that diamond
[\h__\h] for Gracie's kidnap well you did
bring the heat down on the club so I can
understand why they blame you and those
chinks they're still [\h__\h] pissed at
that dispute of ours again fair enough
whatever it don't matter all right what
matters is the Russian has come to Mr
ancelotti and said he wants the head of
anyone involved with the diamonds on top
of all that Gracie and [\h__\h] [\h__\h] the
old man is pissed he wants blood I think
we can cut a deal we give them one body
all right basically it's you or Tony one
of you has to die no me and Vince would
prefer to work with you in the clubs
over the [\h__\h] not another Choice
ending you kill Tony you get to keep the
clubs you and us together Partners now
we protect Tony right is going to send
some serious people round to whack you
and the [\h__\h] with ancelot sanction yeah
you both get whacked you're way out of
your leap kid and you you're a [\h__\h]
loci hanging out with children living a
fantasy life I ain't killing Tony but I
may be about to kill you two [\h__\h] though
M then you're a dead man you and your
family and those SP drug dealers you
hang out with you're all dead it's your
choice I'm loyal to Tony [\h__\h] you think
about it I'll be in touch [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] it's the DLC of Tony we we got to
stay
[Music]
loyal oh oh [\h__\h] that's
accident make
bom oh [\h__\h] how do I deto it
[Music]
what about the the inside one didn't
detonate I don't see a big
boom not
satisfying
yay somebody just had a really
explosion
like business in the
toilet kind of
disgusting wasn't me I know it was the
last one to walk
out but I'm just I'm just cleaning the
toilets okay that's all I
do
explosive barrier
yes this is
explosive
diarrhea let's
go disgusting puns let's
go take me
home
let's
please stop
talking no please
talk
I love you I love you I ran out of
dialogue yeah they didn't write enough
dialogue for me I'm scripted guys yo
what's happen can you get them like
maybe maybe they're on strike I don't
know do something I need more dialogue
okay boss I'll inity room if you need
me
Tony oh there he is thank God you got
here these [\h__\h] guys I talk to them
tell them we can figure it out it ain't
that simple D sure it is we got money
coming we can expand we don't have
enough script writers I'm a Survivor
I've been in this game since
1987 ouch lack of
resources you better tell him Tony man
what things are kind of [\h__\h] man mhm
these guys man these [\h__\h] guys you
never should have bought them in man now
somebody's got a
you know the Mex is with us now you got
to be [\h__\h] kidding me times changed
Tony your brand of charming
homosexuality it's kind of run out of
steam someone has to pay for what's gone
down do it CH sorry do it I'm sorry man
after all we've been through
L I'm sorry th he's just acting as if
you was family man but I see going shoot
the other
men the Russians are coming man we don't
got time for this gay [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
problem
already
nah
yeah you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] hey I had second
thoughts man you [\h__\h] killed yourself
just then the Russians [\h__\h] everyone
that coming after you the old man you're
[\h__\h] dead the both of you they're
coming any second and they're expecting
corpses we better not disappoint then I
keep your head Lou he's a maid guy [\h__\h]
him all right get out of here Rocco this
is for the old man and that's it you're
a dead man Taco get out of my club you
[\h__\h]
moo you sure that was smart you should
not shooting me with smart I don't think
so all right we're going to operate
we're need some some Goodwill here what
now I don't know didn't he say the
Russians are coming doesn't stop does
it uh let's
go oh my oh my God you will die oh my oh
my
God really hoping that he will come
through wish to K me now oh my God one
of out oh my god there so
many I bing my club kid who
disappeared maybe that helps a little
bit I don't
know oh oh there's someone there get I'm
to get
there's so
many the camera W locked me in I was
turning
around one more time oh but ah [\h__\h] my
armor [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'll
start right at the
Battle can
I okay ah
okay I got it I got it get
[Music]
down okay okay uh yeah this is not the
best position to uh start this fight
in this is a better position maybe I bet
you wish to kill me now though one of us
goes
out I don't like this I don't like this
I don't like this at
all
[\h__\h] take cover somewhere oh oh
I don't need that yet the know that's
there I know where the first aid is I
wonder if there's
a a vest
somewhere don't always want to if
there's a vest lying around I'll take it
a legit way drop you [\h__\h] he's got a
[\h__\h] Army there's more of them here
more tell your bom to settle this in
front uhoh making me I might die I might
die
[Music]
it's okay it's
okay A little party never killed
nobody except me cuz I'm
dead A Little Party Never Killed
Nobody except for me cuz I'm
dead
the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] no can you go here thank
you thr my
club I bet you wish to kill me now
L one of us goes out we both go up
checking my back more often now because
it PES me off
ah I'm the unluckiest [\h__\h] on
the
[Music]
planet [\h__\h] there's even more of
them get out of
my
you son of
a Happ me again okay a I hate this are
you joking more of
me this is my club you bastards I buing
my this I love you
now
on they're behind me again oh my
God should I just stay at the stairs I
don't
know yeah there's with heav waves I know
I know like I've been trying to keep an
eye on it
[Music]
but let's stay on the stairs okay okay
must
be no more they're not at the stairs
yet suddenly suddenly suddenly so
sudden
time to
die [\h__\h] Army there's more of them
here W this one's so close me
and
suddenly so quiet now eh I get myself
into this
sh [\h__\h] how many of these guys are
there you want to De you [\h__\h] try in
here me W serious gaming now please do
not disturb the WWA you know how much
thatw cost
[\h__\h] you got me angry
now nice head [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
indeed [\h__\h] you too [\h__\h] there's even
more of
them Rocco wasn't bullshitting about the
she hit body must have been the first
time in his life you want
to okay can't wait suddenly suddenly man
show up out of nowhere as
well are you joking more of these
bastards
more nah come on come on
BOS fight oh [\h__\h] it I'm sick of
[Music]
it you turned out to
be
behind position come on you little
[\h__\h] I would use more bombs if the
switching around wasn't so messy cuz
there's so many things in my menu and I
don't know where it
is oh that's it okay I could have done
that without a cheat I
guess yeah
more of them are arriving outside then
we're going to have to go meet them boss
it's got to end
[Music]
sometime really did I not even leave
like a vest here for people who don't
cheat really
really Tony let's go [\h__\h] Lou not buil
to handle these [\h__\h] me neither
uh do we go for the toilet what's
where oh dear oh dear [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] can
you get rid of
these
uh up your we'll [\h__\h] you up
too [\h__\h]
reloading why does every gun have to be
reloaded more guys what a [\h__\h] h
killing him always at the worst time
time to die die you son of a
bitching who saw that coming the moment
I was
aiming I have a feeling the checkpoint
is kind of nice
[Laughter]
J uh
D what's happening you're [\h__\h]
kidding me get out of here yeah yeah
yeah that's
after okay okay
okay thank you thank you thank you I
know I know I know more of them are
arriving outside then we're going to
have to go meet them boss okay let's go
it's got to end
sometime oh but this way this way
everything's cleaned up no weapons lying
around I'll be no good to you out there
come
on I'm ready I'm ready and I'm
steady Bring It On are you [\h__\h]
kidding me bring it on even more of it
bring it on
ouch Bring it
on Bring it on
baby
goodby goodby
get back
Tony I don't know where this enemy
is I think we clear okay we
cill me you want to [\h__\h] kill me easy
man what the [\h__\h] we got through it we
beat them we did it sorry taxi but you
know I wasn't sure where the enemy was
It was kind of hard to see I'm ping up
and I'm leaving town spot spot town in
the desert can I you swing you don't be
stupid I'm to come with you please don't
be stupid I'll just come find why he so
mad I saved him does he not remember the
moment where I was supposed to shoot
someone and I didn't shoot
him does he not remember 13 head
shots all that we've been through
doesn't matter to him he's so
moody why Tony why Tony and yousef's
super
DD let's go to you
s don't know what his problem is
man all I ever do is protect him and be
loyal to him
man take me to yeah let's get my egg
yolk a fun way to go there it
is oh it's so cute it's so pretty I
don't know I think it's supposed to be
gold but to me it's just yellow it's
just a really pretty clean
yellow I like it it's my
car will be available here this
apartment whenever you need it oh okay
okay also it wasn't the mission at all
it was just dropping buy to get the
car I'll probably destroy wait is this
when he says available whenever I need
it what if I crash it move it or lose it
godamn it does it
respawn
last
mission what that was that's so short it
will respawn okay
okay but last mission so hopefully we
don't need it
anymore how did you
last
Tony come
on don't was that long but like we've
we've been isn't this my fourth DLC
stream or is it my third one
we've been on it for a
while but like now it suddenly feels so
so sudden probably because it's the
first time I play in a while and then
it's not even that long so it feels
like I'm not really in the it's ending
kind of Zone you know Lis hello my
friend uh did you like the car did you
like the other gift the gun oh yeah one
was a short stream too yeah solid
go always is the best for you thank you
youf stat this is actually a sick ride I
like it we are brothers it is
nothing myself is gold just glorified
yellow guys is it just a
cope why not just say yellow
huh cuz this really just looks like
yellow I mean you could have done a
better job at making this look more
golden this is just
yellow like for real got me all anyway
I'm
you oh [\h__\h]
son okay we're here Tony let's go to the
spot together let's go to the
sauna vodka
bottle hey
C [\h__\h] off L iir haven't we been through
this already been through the fact that
you wanted to kill me been through the
fact that you're far from Al that
this is over it's over it was I said it
was a second father or something I think
but it was never really to die I lived
it I lived it hard and now I'm ready to
end it oh shut up you hysterical [\h__\h]
Queen get consider silly me silly
[\h__\h] me the Russian mob want me dead
my best friend just contemplated
murdering me it's just as crazy ranting
as in the beginning of the DLC and I
just lost $2 million worth of diamonds
any other man would just dust himself
off and carry on look okay I'm sorry I
thought about killing you I really am
but if you keep up with the [\h__\h] I
might have to kill you for real [\h__\h] off
l no you [\h__\h] off bony I didn't kill you
I wanted to why because you've become a
useless junky [\h__\h] that's why but I
didn't and now it's You and Me Against
the World okay and if your brain ain't
working right then I'll make the
decision for us okay we got him or us or
you can shoot us both and make his life
easy for
him
look you're kind of clever aren't
you I only hired you cuz I thought you
were dumb yeah thank you very
much you're welcome very much are you
coming now a he's
dead yes I'm coming
now I don't think you can take the
liquid into the let's go come airport in
case you're going
there probably not though right all
right that he's taking on a
what about my yellow car that was so
much
[Music]
better last mission guys we're going to
Croc see we find them what are we going
to do then we're going to take out their
income stream and then we're going to
take them out in this [\h__\h] okay I'm
armed I'm dangerous let's [\h__\h] do
this come on T give me a break what
we're in this
together I love you but I shall handle
this alone I don't want you getting
yourself killed then you're going to
have to punch me out again L don't make
me man you know you just going to Slow
Me Down bro and kill us both I want at
least one of us to
survive look don't go home don't go to
the say like don't go nowhere anyone
might conceivably think to look for you
there aren't many places like that left
in the city I'm afraid come on where you
think you can hide that no one would
expect I have no [\h__\h] clue does I ran
away from there when I was a kid and I
swore blind I'd never go back apart from
to catch a plane okay cool hit up like
uh that monog Monument thing in Meadows
Park hang out for a few hours if I
survive this [\h__\h] I'll find you if I
don't show then I'm gone move to Brazil
Who somewhere Brazil back I thought I
was the annoying drama queen in this
Parry I'm serious T this is my last
Testament yo send some money to my mom
sometimes
I [\h__\h] fine [\h__\h] knowing this whole
crazy town is crazy enough Crazy Town
you
down crazy
town all I can think of is the pink
[Music]
girl later the [\h__\h] blue come to Brazil
after yourself byebye going to Funland I
am in Funland wow I'm I'm having so much
fun let's go oh that was lazy town
ah true true
true now we own junk trade in Liberty
anyone need package they must deal with
us destroy the
heroin uh what is it in the
trucks do I shoot the
guys
now let's keep my bazooka for a little
while
later
[Music]
Ang if they have an HP bar visible that
means I have to kill
them but like what what do you mean with
how about how
about come out [\h__\h] like
this your marin oh that seems to be the
way to
go
oh [\h__\h] youo I saw you what the [\h__\h]
I'm don't get so close you're not a
phoenix done not again no I feel like
I'm in Sims
no I'm on fire get up
dude wait where's the other
heroin wait is it this
thing this thing you guys tried to kill
me one too many times maybe no that was
not
it judging by the map I thought that was
it that one is one oh that's the one
I was like that's not even a car like
why would it be there that's what I was
thinking but you
know let's kill the people
first fun music
it I'm so out in the open
man come on come on come on you
[Music]
what where you at
[\h__\h]
birdie
what it's so fun wait put
cover while I'm looking for the right
weapon where are the people that are
shooting me
oh hey hey I'm out
[Applause]
you he's literally too far I'm aiming
correctly
but y
byby should
I
a little bit too
close oh my God where's the last car oh
hi this is a really nice
location for this nice team outing
having a good
time good background music it's me or
you bro me or you all right where does
the bump need to
[Music]
go I don't see a
car this end of the Year party is
great Oh Come Out [\h__\h] oh I'll
show you a greater end of the year party
supposed to be on the other
side soon
TM there's a first aid but I really just
need the
armor okay
oh yeah this is
crazy J Scrat the
MEK
okay F man so fun man these rides are
amazing oh hey there's the vest
yo so hard to find these things they
placed it so that you only find it on
the way back destroy the remaining okay
oh
[\h__\h] oh
where's why they all
Bol why is the Bol ratio so high you
kidding
me oh to kill me one any
time you know who you [\h__\h] with
now maybe crime makes you lose your
hair but don't do
crime
pee on [\h__\h] no more head shot
the cool thing to do is the pee
shot welcome to the membership
oh come on come
on come
on you are
all
oh I just noticed that
here why did I not see that
earlier
oh stop me there 26 Moms
come come out
you what is it with this
[\h__\h] oh trash bag I ain't de yet [\h__\h]
oh that what you
want oh there's so many of them you
didn't want
me
oh oh is that is that a the whacker Oh I
thought it was um come [\h__\h]
thought it was darts he's ugly I'm so
[\h__\h] at
darts I'm really bad at like any kind of
game or so Sports where you have to
throw something especially balls this
game too we played this with with with
myth
IRL I think we played this in the that
that
the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] Game Center thingy we
played this yeah I think Amy was really
good at it am
oh Cali too I think cie a beast at
it that was the first time I played
something like that so I was not the
best okay where where does this bomb got
to go huh wait this way where's this
car haveed you will die soon no please
let me go to the car first I got you
you turn around turn around turn around
[\h__\h] around they still won't let me
go no I see it on the map I see it and I
see
[Laughter]
this I spy with my little
[Applause]
eye oh oh this
thing oh
[\h__\h] we got him mistake [\h__\h]
mistake me
dig oh me dig [\h__\h] did I just do
that that's the right that's the right
good thing they don't blow up right the
away huh
away
now [\h__\h] you you think he will forget
about you you and all your friends are
dead yeah that ain't happening
timy shot him sh him you killing your
whole family get to the airport in two
hour go go go
go where is he where'd he go take down
the oh
oh what
come
on he went
straight run run run run run run no time
to
aim aim is pain to kill your
ass
Hospitality we all got ay man and you
don't cut
it go go oh is this is this
him he's
dead get on the bike the
bike uh uh 2 hours 2 hours in game 2
hours is like
nothing this is like a [\h__\h]
maze wa it's over
there what what
bike
bike oh there it is oh can I make it can
I make it
biking let's go back to the routs the
first
DLC L what's Happ I can't talk bro just
really coming apart what you need let me
help you out there nothing you can do I
don't think you can help crazy Russian
[\h__\h] manages to leave the country it's
over at home I got to get down the Douce
Expressway without any number of Russian
Assassins taking me down oh we're done
why am I even saying this I mean would
be pretty cool if you can help me but I
doubt it you
Expressway lot of controls on
this a bike controls so
[Music]
wobbly
oh hey I made
it this not the airport
though
nice
she youf let's
go wait does the time even still matter
now that yousef's like part of
[Music]
this is he taking care of all oh my God
you is an A beige helicopter you
probably call it golden I'll just just
for now I'll I'll comply
totally
gold uhoh oh what the hell what's that
supposed to
hit don't blow me up
[Music]
bro that was kind of
weird we're pretty much
there
and I have no checked in
luggage just boarding the plane with
nothing on my
hands imagine that I couldn't do that I
always need to bring so much [\h__\h] you
know yesterday my day off I spent uh
Cleaning Out My Closet uh switching out
my summery clothes with the winter
clothes I went to the basement basement
seller and oh my God I I found my my
window coats and they were like the
window Coats were in
a in a a suitcase sealed off
perfectly and
still there were like Mo uh like empty
shelves of m
v and [\h__\h] like that
do I shoot this
thing get close
okay yeah
by so now like I'm in the process of
washing all of my winter clothes because
yeah you ain't getting away from me Yo
cool fil
scene PE let me
in yo what in this game
who's flying the plane is is he okay
with me being the passenger now I hope
so cuz I don't think I can fly it wait
what this is still going on
okay [\h__\h] you we have to deal with the
[\h__\h] inside here to see you
Louise yeah cuz I came here looking for
you I'll bu trying to leave without
saying
goodbye is he
wait who fly fly the you kill me all die
oh I guess that's fine you can't shoot
me you'll blow a whole plane up I'll
take my chances
yeah the way he look to the side like H
oh
no oh no e are we going to die no
parachute out parachute out now oh oh we
got the parachute I'm back
wo
hey smart boy such a smart
boy hey I didn't even have to activate
the parachute myself all right let's
tell you this more of my more about my
moth
problem like one of my favorite
Cod one of my favorite window coats from
Zara I looked closely at it
and I I saw like one little hole mostly
it was okay mostly was intact but yeah
so I think they really some people said
they they they're not at fault for my
jeans but I feel like they might be cuz
you know I've got this huge issue with
them everywhere the clothes that I have
hanging they're all pretty much fine but
the ones that lie around somewhere for
longer than 2 or 3 weeks without being
touched those always get affect
but I thought my codes would be fine cuz
they were in the suitcase what the [\h__\h]
they must have made their way in before
I closed it or something so weird where
are we
going am I going to mess up this Landing
cuz they want me to land very
specifically somewhere like not here
[\h__\h]
well
wow he this a [\h__\h] I hope we were going
to make it over
that why did you have to step why
couldn't you lift your
legs he's
fine
yeah have you guys seen the holes that
Ms make though what we start from here
no
way no
way cuz like the the edges of the
holes is like really
smooth that's how you see sloping M
holes really small
too I don't know if you can fix those
though but they only made like a hole in
like the top layer of the coat and it's
really small so behind the top layer was
still like the same
fabric so I think I can totally still
wear
it go go go go go
[Music]
no yeah it's like they dissolved the
cloes it's so
[Music]
weird yeah but just washing them once in
the wash
machine basically got rid of all the
[\h__\h] and I cleaned out the surfaces of
all my closet which they were a lot of
surfaces yeah
really
[Music]
dirty I have grenade you kill me we all
die got to be careful when uh you can't
shoot meing your Co plane up I'll take
my chances cuz they're really
really
[Music]
sensitive try turning on the music or is
it not copyrighted there's a special
music for the parachute
segment oh what what I have to land
there that's like so
far hey I
just you mean just my own music cuz I
guess
it which one's my own music The
Independent
overk and
under that do not do it yeah that that
sounds not like my independent music and
I don't know it is copyrighted
okay where where where are we
[Music]
going it's so far how can I go there am
I not supposed to like press W cuz I
feel like I lose more or do I should I
go forward with W faster
but oh I can just take a car okay so I
don't have to land there
specifically do I hold
[Music]
s oh okay okay so we don't have to okay
okay roller coaster
let's just not land the way we did
[Music]
before it's cooler to land by Parachute
but can you actually make it
though we
are
uh N I think I'm going to have to take a
car
would also be pretty sick to land on a
train with no train
inside me go this
[Music]
way
y
okay let's get into into the
car get get this one get this one that
one's nice
looking wait get
in
polia no no no I should be immune at
this point no I got other [\h__\h] to
do right behind me sure yeah yeah yeah
now I'll just go this way oh
[Music]
man don't they know like this is my last
mission this is like at the end of the
at the end of high school you know high
schoolers play a prank on their teachers
and on the school or so and they're
forgiven because it's like the last day
or so for them it's like their their
final prank
yeah I feel like just this one St should
just shut the [\h__\h] up and let me do my
thing school did you go to I didn't go
to any just kidding I did go to a school
where there was a high
school oh now I see what's going on here
ah [\h__\h] oh well I think I'm losing them
now and while I was not involved there
seems to be that kind of
[Music]
tradition Justice wants to celebrate all
the things I have done for this city
I've kept the city safe you know totally
totally oh oh yeah right I turned it
off oh my
God ah I was looking at the chat yo I I
was watching
um I originally turned participation
down because I thought I don't want to
like join a stream at like 1:00 a.m. I
don't want to commit to that but I was
watching the GIC phone collab from O's
Marathon for quite a
while and then they were talking about
if anybody's ever been called to a
principal's office and cie said like
many many many many many times and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] for what like Ina
said never honestly I would have said
the same cuz I I also never was called
to the principal's
office what did Cali
do I want to
know I want to
know I've been called so many times what
did you do same got called there L what
did you do guys what did
do why why did you all get called
guys so popular with the principal what
okay yeah so many of you guys yeah
thanks you criminals okay stay away from
idiots like
me [\h__\h] you I'm armored oh nice thank
[Music]
you he's your pal your
prinel cuz I threw a rock in my Bull's
Head oh
wow Dam wait Diamond where did you get
the dam did he take it from my pocket or
did he have it
already nice good for him good for him
yo is have to make a scene don't you
problem with me you know I wish I was
more like you subtle shy retiring it's
time for some orange uh slight orange
flavor cookies I used to play right
there when I was a kid dreaming of the
world wondering what it's like that
place just or that little island over
there you ever go that thing nah went to
Al gangin instead waiting for the world
to come to
me you did it
man you did it you saved you guys got to
tell me all these stories business you
[\h__\h] did it hey man I did what I
could bro I'm proud of you man this such
a peaceful ending thank you sweet but I
don't want you to get a big head I don't
want you to go uh change got a mega star
got a Vinewood write a block of course
not you're a pill popping o Queen man
I'm a never write a blog survive we
survived we more than not in these kind
of days we prospered we took on his town
and we won we took on his place and we
gave it the [\h__\h] finger [\h__\h] you all
I don't care what people say Tony Prince
and Luis Lopez could not be stopped huh
oh jeez who's this what's up my
Niger oh my God man you [\h__\h] made it
man that was some serious Gangsta [\h__\h]
shoot shoot Cheo them up I said shoot
shoot Cheo them up y t t give me a hug
give me a hug not too close SOC the
wrong
impression Luis I love you man I love
you I love you I love you come on let's
get out of again well he helped me in
the end so way my father he's redeemed
himself in my eyes I no franchise is not
the way to go he gave me the Yol car
from [\h__\h] the people [\h__\h] them all we P
your dick piss all over them you're
going to go a long way in Hospitality my
friend no what a sweet
[Music]
Trio why was that so T at the
end TB OG GT complete what does that
mean Rockin North oh is there supposed
to be bgm right
now
let me play
something
[Music]
um
that was GTA 4 my second GTA Adventure
on my stream on my
Channel with the DLC we did both the
biking DLC and this one which was the
actual
real how to say attraction that people
wanted to see m
I got to say this I I I unnecessarily
dragged this whole playthrough out a bit
because of breaks in
between so I can honestly not really
rate the game so
well cuz I barely remember my feelings
about it the but I think I can say the
DLC was way better than the main game of
course because of stuff like the
checkpoints being
nicer mhm
uh yeah I really can't tell like if you
watch me play the main game you probably
know what I think of it cuz I don't know
anymore
but generally I I prefer GTA 5 I think
that was
the the general
consensus uh but like going back from
GTA
5 from what I've heard no matter what
like the game games are fun and all but
if I go back if I didn't start somewhere
in the first games but I go back from
the latest to the older ones then the
older ones are all going to seem bad cuz
they just all you know improve
themselves after each each single
game yeah yeah GJ San Andreas next I
don't know um I mean until GTA 6 there's
so much time so there is a possibility
for me to play another one I I bought um
in a in a package I bought GTA 4 free
and San Andreas so I do own the
games and I think I have permission but
I feel like if anything I would play Red
Dead Redemption thir next up sometime
sometime in early
2024 and also we're going to play Yakuza
of course
yeah yeah I think I'm I don't know GTA
[Music]
4 I I had my fun but compared to GTA 5 I
I had way more issues I think of like
connecting vibing and following the
story and the
dialogue had some funny scenes and all
but for me everything was so
disconnected in my
brain it's probably my fault for not
being able to follow along but I just
have this problem in general with GTA
games I think like the dialogue is so
fast and then it's while driving and I'm
trying to focus on the driving and uh
and read the subtitles because sometimes
it's hard to understand what they're
talking about and it's like just ah my
my attention is just like
split yeah and then they use so many
weird ass words that I don't understand
like and they swear so much I I have no
idea what they're going on
about I'd be even more lost in all the
GTA probably
yeah probably
probably um but I I still like the silly
humor and the missions were fun
especially in the DLC I can attest to
that to
that uh so yeah graphic Graphics were
nice if only it was more colorful
because the grayness is like [\h__\h]
depressing
well it was nice to see a different
city this
time very local jokes and reference what
do you think of playing a collab of
other
members I I I keep on bringing it up
like every now and then like to them
even in in person you know um I've
brought it up to like am before but you
know if if I don't don't actually go and
follow up really really really intensely
things don't happen and I just didn't
have the mental
capacity uh up until this point
still yeah
[Music]
um oh yeah that's also the thing like uh
finding out that mikoi has the console
version and I have the PC version so
it's like oh got to buy if I want to
play with her got to buy the console
[Music]
version that was also a thing I
think
um but I mean it can still happen you
know there's like always many ideas in
my head
and you never know when I might you know
make something happen bring it back from
the back of my ideas that I mentioned a
year
ago yeah one day yeah cie is trying to
get something to work or like she she
asked management so management is
currently looking into making like a
server for GTA online for us so if that
happens I'll I'll most likely be
joining look at that lady dancing
the oh she already
stopped such a disco
[Music]
dance I need to
s oh it's the homeless man yeah
oh was he drinking out of this oh it's
bubbling I thought it was burning like a
Molotov
cocktail thank you thank
you so yeah it's it's really hard to say
to rate this game say anything about it
at the moment it's just been too
long I don't know this was fun though
thankfully it didn't drag out too
long so that's a good thing we've done
some we've done some good uh
pre
preparation oh yeah dance dance dance
dance you got here just in time you just
arrived oh
man wo wo so many men without shirts
woo oh they got some
[Music]
moves wow no shoes on he's rocking the
socking hey hey hey hey oh wow damn you
can really learn some moves from these
guys oh he's doing that disco disco
disco point up Point down point up Point
down
[Music]
there's something for everyone there
yeah no shirt no
shoes no
pants whatever fits your fancy tickles
your
fancy well well
well I thought it would be playing
longer today I thought this was going to
be a really long stream but I guess I
can catch C up of super
chats you freaking Terminator in GTA
what are you talking
about no service what what do you mean
no service no
[Music]
what oh what because what everybody's
dancing so you don't get service what oh
this was so [\h__\h] this mission was so
[\h__\h] oh I hated this Mission I think I
really hated it did I not tell me did I
not oh that
terrible like I mean it's probably just
because I was playing with the
keyboard yeah when I swapped to the
controller it was
okayish but still even with the
controller I think the first time I
failed
mhm yeah there were a bunch of H
helicopter missions that were just [\h__\h]
but with controller surely it was easier
and in the DLC at least the the the the
checkpoints were
forgiving cuz otherwise I would have
thrown my computer out of the window
yeah one mission in GTA San Andreas is
Rage inducing I I feel like uh I was
told there's one rage inducing mission
in GTA 4 as well and I got over that
one like pretty
smoothly more or
less don't know what that
[Music]
was I can lift my
computer you think of all the cat photos
I don't have my cat photos on my PC I
have them on my phone
[Music]
mostly oh following a
train I got to be honest with you guys
if the previous games are more
scuff than this
one a lot of time will have to pass so
that I forgot I forget completely about
my negative emotions and can be um
convinced to play
them a lot of time will have to
pass yeah I do want to experience the
can I get a
uh you know number nine
whatever uh I want to experience
that but but is it worth the pain you
know I don't
know you could just use cheats
again maybe maybe yeah that could be a
nice get around uh to make up for the
scuff and the rage we could uh from the
beginning
on just play it more
Loosely just have fun with eats a bit
more more freedom less getting sweaty
and
[Music]
salty
maybe cheats are not that easy to
use in San
Andreas
[Music]
no sheats don't help with the rage
mission is there no cheat to just like
typee in mission complete and you get
like an okay you just skip the
mission that would be great that would
be great if only if why
not why
[Music]
not one DJ salad will would get me all
the memes or is it really early
on HM H yeah I mean since I already own
the game we could just do like one or
two streams like without completing the
game
oh all the memes are very early okay
okay both things are early
[Music]
oh flying really hard in San Andreas
let's hope we don't have to fly early on
then
no need to finish it okay okay but first
as I said Red Dead Redemption and also
Yakuza you know I feel like Yakuza is
basically as I said Japanese
GTA I don't know if I'll actually play
that short one by the
way oh
oh oh because from what I've
heard if I don't if I didn't play
whatever game is like I connected to
that then it won't make much sense to
me so I'll just probably be waiting for
the oopsie for the long one
oopsie shut
up main story has not been completed you
can repeat missions via the phone no
thank
you no thank you I had fun though thank
you for
today you sure want to AC the game
yeah I was good oh we're really out of
it okay
okay ah so n we're going to uh Read
Super chats I guess this is such an kind
of a lowkey antil climatic
ending sorry guys I I shouldn't have I
completely forgot about it recently when
I was making my schedules I never even
considered that we still have to finish
GTA
yeah
[Music]
yeah I played uh Yakuza zero and uh the
the the most recent Dragon one like a
dragon
[Music]
yeah how's tales off going for perms I
don't know I'm waiting but I guess I
might even ask like uh cuz I've just
I've just been waiting for them to say
on social media that you can play Until
the End now or you can stream until the
end now but uh maybe I'll just ask like
personally my
contacts oh the toe the pinky
toe that was
literally it wasn't I guess it wasn't as
as crazy as people thought it was cuz it
wasn't just a single pinky
toe strutting its stuff in my dream no
no no it was it was a pinky toe attached
still to a foot uh but like the the most
of the foot was fine it was just a pinky
toe that was absolutely squashed and red
and bloody and gory
and yeah it was
terrifying yeah but it was just like 1%
of a bigger dream you
know but I just had to mention it when I
saw when I heard Shi and narissa talking
about
it oh by the way so far how you guys
liking the Advent
calendar are you liking
it so far it's going pretty well with
like submissions I I got a bunch like
even early
on yeah everything's been on time so far
except for my
tweets
yeah you're liking it are having fun are
you guys checking it out no matter like
you should always check out you don't
you shouldn't wait for Twitter to tell
you who the [\h__\h] is on the Advent
calendar the the it's about the surprise
you open the website before getting
spoiled you open the door and no matter
who is it no matter if it's your Ashi or
not you watch the video
you love the Christmas Market thank you
it was a good excuse for me to go to the
Christmas
Market and and buy some overpriced food
and drink
yeah I want to go
again it inspired me to go to a
Christmas Park myself nice did you like
it did you go where are you from where
did you
go tax deductible no no I'm not I'm not
trying
to do that
no food looks yummy really I want to go
and eat those those spa the K Spa yum
yum yum yum yum in Oslo oh Oslo surely
has great Christmas
Market is my first Christmas with whole
life the Adam calendar is awesome thank
you for organizing oh really thank you
you should check out the old one on the
same website there's a uh a link for
like kind of like an archive of last
year's Advent
calendar you should check it out if you
haven't
[Music]
yet you know my lips are so [\h__\h] up
right now I ripped off so much skin
yesterday and
then cuz I have this shitty habit when I
feel something standing off I want to
rip it
off and then overnight it was like
growing back and I was like waking up so
often tonight noticing that my my my
lips are struck together and then I P
open it and like every time it it kind
of
hurts and that repeated itself like 10
times during the night I woke up like 10
times ripping my mouth
open so
bad and I put some I put some
um some lip balm on top of it before the
stream so it's it feels better but it's
like
H did you guys never have this before
when something like when your lips grow
together the humidity I need oh yeah
maybe yeah it's probably really dry
mhm even now I'm picking it
off
[Music]
H I've never needed lip balm damn you
live in Florida or
what happened to me okay not only me
then I had like that
really I use my teeth to pick it up oh I
don't want to do that cuz I don't want
to have it in my mouth and also it's not
as accurate with the teeth I think than
with your
fingers H anyway let's play
some
[Music]
isn't this
nice I love this music oh
[Music]
God pink gun on my pink chair I'm such a
gamer girl let's
[Music]
go ah I should go to the night version
maybe the night version suits the winter
time a bit
better maybe maybe we can
have I don't know if certain someone is
listening right now but maybe the the
windows could just be you know like like
like how Windows get when it's really
cold out are you out
here like in both of them just just
changing the windows to be like Anish
lagin what's it in English
like uh of course you're here I'm
surprised yeah the trees like I don't
want to see the tree
leaves doesn't have to be snowing but
like maybe I can be like
[Music]
frosted you always say thank
you thank
[Music]
you m oh yeah so while we're I don't
know while we're chilling here and we
have so much time let me show you the
schedule in case you didn't see it also
for members I uploaded the members only
wallpaper which is a really snowy one
it's in the community board on YouTube
in case you didn't get
[Music]
it you know when I get early today when
when I get done early today I can um
sign some Polaroids I wanted to do it
yesterday but then yesterday I went to
an IRL thing meeting kind of
thing um and then afterwards I I came
back and I I I I came back and I I I
remember I was like kind of freezing cuz
like I was wearing the only coat uh the
only winter coat I had
out uh outside of my cell basically so
then I came home and I was like you know
what I'll check my Celler if if all my
other winter Coates are there cuz I have
like like a skiing jacket and all that
so I was trying to find that and I found
it and I brought all the Coates up and
then then I open it and I was like what
the [\h__\h] it's full with moths
everything uh not really moths but like
the it looked like the the REM remains
of mths hanging out on my clothes so I
was like [\h__\h] and so I started washing
things uh and then I I switched out all
the winter clothes summer clothes this
and that just did that kind of stuff
and went into deep cleaning my closet I
went for this whole process and that
that was actually fun for
me yeah the other day I deep cleaned my
kitchen I've been cleaning a lot and
it's not even January
yet yeah probably the MS that ate my
jeans I have like a moth um trap you
know the sticky ones and it's it's been
working like there's a [\h__\h] ton of moths
on the Trap
yeah and just cleaning every all the
clothes that are that look like they
have like the the remains of the stupid
ass moths on there [\h__\h] moth Arc it's
like the Casper Arc but with the
moths something therapeutic about
cleaning I have to do it when I actually
have this motivation for once that's
really rare cuz normally me getting
started on cleaning like getting to the
point I I I I'm so
lazy so when I actually get started I
get rolling and it's easy but getting
started is is the problem for
me but yesterday it just over overcame
me The Moment I Saw the moths on my
beautiful winter coats my favorite
winter coats I don't want to buy new
ones I I have like
six maybe six winter coats guys and
those are not cheap right I mean I don't
buy from Gucci or whatever they're just
like Zara and the the skiing jacket was
expensive though I think but you know
you know witer coats are not not not
cheap so I I don't I I want to use them
I don't want to buy a new one each year
unless they're really cute and I really
have to have
it it's Z is pretty nice yeah like
I I would say like zawa are you like
most fancy clothes I buy most of the
time I don't really treat myself
to luxury clothes uh besides
that I I do have one pair
of I have one pair of Louis
vuon
Loafers because they were so pretty and
I like these
loafers but that that's pretty much
it
normally I don't make such
purchases they're so pretty
yeah but they really hurt to
wear cuz like I don't wear them that
often right cuz I don't want to overwear
them but when I wear them the the lever
it like I have to stretch it out again
cuz it's
like getting so small and then I I rub
off my skin on the back of my foot
H I'm holding you hostage you don't want
to be here huh you don't want to be
[Music]
here oh yeah I was going to show you the
schedule schedule schedule where is that
uh this one yeah we're back to the left
side schedule the art is on the left
side cute art I noticed I had to cut off
quite a bit for the schedule because uh
the character was pretty
centered and I didn't even realize when
I was like monitoring the creation of it
so we finished Tuesday on Wednesday
we're going to do Holo
[Music]
parade and then Friday Christmas cookie
baking going to start pretty
late Saturday the promised members
chatting stream that will be shorter
because I'm doing weekly members streams
and the previously they've always been
like pretty much on the long
side I've realized one thing me doing
weekly memb streams that are not even
that short
now uh my public streaming hours will be
less no I realized that they you know
those like top streaming hours whole
life
English they don't count the member
streams
so I'll I'll be a little
bit further behind than I should
be well whatever just keep that in
mind oh I see a all
flying ah [\h__\h]
you go somewhere else but don't go into
my closet actually go to the closet
there's a trap waiting for you
there [\h__\h] hate that
and then K and sleep talking mvy the
sleep talking mvy is basically finished
uh I I told jenma
please
what told JMA please get get it to the
legal check I don't know if she
[Music]
did
told her now
[Music]
again yeah
um Buffs Ms are drawn to
Flame am I am I so bright do you get
Roes there no thankfully that's one good
thing about living one of many good
things actually I mean we just talked
about
the fact that it's not humid enough and
that's why my lips are trapping but we
don't get cockroaches I would say
cockroaches are more common in places
where it's humid and
hot AUST is roach free I wouldn't say
it's completely roach free but I have
never seen a roach in Austria ever
before like Japan was the first time
when I ever saw a
cockroach
yeah at first I thought it's kind of
cute
when I just saw them outside I thought
they were cute but once I saw them like
inside a room then they were not so cute
anymore of
course
mhm uh I remember here you get a random
story I
remember uh this was a long time ago I
was just in Japan for a
trip um this was before whole life
and I had not much money so you know I
would normally go for like the cheapest
of the cheap
accommodations um but I found an
accommodation I wonder maybe it was
Airbnb I'm not sure
probably uh that had a pretty neat
location and a nice location in
Tokyo and it was like tatami so Japanese
style but I I feel like those kind of uh
Japanese apartments are
more
prone oh the m is on the wall oh let me
let me get
it ah I got it but these Ms when I kill
them on the wall they leave always such
a disgusting Mark oh my God but yeah I
feel like they're more prone to uh
having roaches
um the older Apartments so I I was going
to go to one of those and it was
summertime and I I uh it was a weird
apartment like I was welcomed by the
first it was so weird oh my God I
arrived and like I was not sure where to
go it was like kind of a
shady area looking shady and the
entrance looked shady I didn't know
where exactly I was supposed to go in
and I think I I eventually
finally reached someone the owner and
they came and they like showed me around
and explained the the bathtub to
me it needed explanation because it was
so old like 50 60 years old kind of
bathtub where I had to do several things
before getting the water running
and I was filming it so that I could
remember it but I don't think I ever no
I only yeah the thing is I never used it
cuz first of all I was disgusted by it
and confused by it and frustrated by
it um yeah it was so confusing too was
like what did I get myself into no
wonder this place is so
cheap
and then uh I guess the person left and
I was more more or less ready to sleep
but it was just overall kind of spooky
the
whole that area even though it was
Central and close to the station of a
pretty cool area the corner I was in was
like shady and the apartment was scary
because I would I it I would hear so
many things from
outside and everything was old
everything was like creaky making creaky
creaky
noises
um yeah
and then I
uh oh yeah I was so terrified I uh it
was like pretty spacious living room and
all that but you sleep on the floor so I
roll out the tatami
mat and I was just uh trying to sleep
but but then I see cockroaches running
around and I freak out and I can't sleep
especially cuz it's a tatami met and
sleeping on the ground where the
Cockroaches are running
around so that freaks me out and then I
remember also that I was
hearing like knocking noises I think and
it sounded like it came from the door
but I was so terrified cuz it was like
late at night and I was like freaking
out I couldn't sleep I was scared of
this place and I was I was
crying I never found out like what what
the knocking was what that came from but
I I ended up like canceling my stay and
the next day spending a bit more money
to get to like an actual Hotel not a
shitty broken down Airbnb that scared
the [\h__\h] out of me and I was so relieved
I could not stay stay
there mhm it was so
freaky it's so scary like just me saying
oh Somebody's knocking on the door and
oh crock roaches Maybe maybe that in
itself isn't that bad but like you don't
even you can't even imagine the spooky
atmosphere of that place
man I talked about this before
really yeah it was spooky and
uncomfortable and scary and H it felt
haunted
yeah mhm they probably had box I I don't
know I wouldn't say so the Tatam me was
the the bed the mattress was fine
but like I don't want to sleep on the
ground when I know this [\h__\h] is running
around
yeah oh see okay if I talked about this
before that means I was able to bring
back a really old tangent
yay
yeah nowadays I
I I I I
can you know stay in normal places
although my last trip I was trying to
save money so I stayed in like
relatively cheap airbnbs but they were
pretty nice they were somewhat somewhat
Spacey
spacious so they were pretty
[Music]
good I woke up with a spider on me once
why did you remove it did you scare
yourself by reminding
yourself even if you had a normal bed
doesn't help knowing I can fly yeah even
with a normal bed I probably would have
felt uneasy
um there was like they actually had um
cockroach spray standing around in the
room I was like okay so this seems to be
like a common issue here you know about
it can't you like before you let people
stay there you obviously know about it
can you like do
something but well cockroaches are very
common in summer in Japan
so I guess it's just a
thing nah just lower the price
exactly fight your own battles yeah it's
exciting it's an
experience should try for the exciting
experience it's like playing a horror
game yeah never seen one in the UK yeah
same same I never saw one in Austria
before
[Music]
ever and then me living in the beginning
of my whole life
career although that was the second
accommodation already me the third
actually in some way me living in the
house with mice or rat rats we will
never know what that was cuz I don't
really I can't tell I think it was rats
actually now that I think about it
recently I saw
mice and realized how small they are so
it was most likely
rats cuz I I only ever got like quick
little glimpses at
Casper but when I think about that he
was pretty big
yeah and mice are tiny
so it was rats
yeah but since I couldn't get rid of
them and I was kind of forced to live
there I was forced to get used to them
and eventually I didn't even care that
much anymore about it and as you
remember I felt bad I started feeling
bad about trying to kill these
[Music]
[Applause]
rats I got I got got I got gaslighted
gaslit by the
rats I formed a bond with them but it
was freaking me out especially in the
beginning when I moved in and it was
like I heard these noises all the
time somehow like it's so it's kind of
ridiculous if you think about it I also
know like obviously they're not going to
attack me what are they going to do
they're not going to attack me it's
[\h__\h] rats they're scared of
me so I don't know why why anybody
really get gets that freaked out of same
with cockroaches they're not going to
attack me
either they can bite you think they
would bite me steal your food they did
steal my food they did steal my imported
beloved favorite uh chocolate that was
supposed to like give me a Taste of Home
in my one year of Japan where I was
stuck because of Corona and I couldn't
leave the country country because I
wouldn't have been able to enter
again yeah more on the
[Music]
hygiene yeah it's kind of like the the
imagination that maybe they could climb
on me or maybe they would be right NE
right next to me while I sleep like just
like sniffing me and walking around my
mattress just that
thought while it probably never happened
and never
never not really realistic but but
that's that's the the thought that is
stuck in my
head needful company I don't really have
any idea what that game is I just heard
the name a few times recently and
doesn't really seem like a game I would
play would it I don't know maybe other
Ian
members they like
chicken
uh I'm just happy like in my apartment I
feel like like a rat or cockroaches or
so would never even be able to show up
because I don't know how it would be
possible with the way it's
built and where they would come from and
like I don't think it's
possible
logistically for rats to infest my
apartment or mice or
so the scene I don't think so like
everything feels so thick and sturdy and
closely cut
off
yeah I I I don't see how they would show
up
here
mhm nah and even then I have cats here
that's right in Japan I didn't have my
Kito Catos but here here I do
I've noticed chunky wonky like more and
more staring out the window so
cute I want to take her out for a
[Music]
walk
wait is the thing today is there L thing
today for me like
tonight I think it
is I don't have it like it's so
confusing because it's like after
midnight oh yeah it is yeah I'm just
calling in into waya stream just a short
call in probably just 5 minutes or
[Music]
so then I called into all stream and
into Way's stream well what's with Ana I
would of course not call into Ana's
stream whatever she's doing because I
hate her we hate each other
obviously but it's funny because that
really seems like uh I have no idea did
she already do an anniversary
stream Anya was doing K oh she's done
did she do any anything where somebody
would be able to participate at
all I yeah the joke is that we only do
Callins ever yeah true true
true few hours ago
damn no to okay
well then I had no
[Music]
chance there never was a chance for me
oh yeah yeah right I saw the thumbnail
it said rare
kok Anya's
rare
your words to Oli was sweet yeah I could
like even though I didn't
really hear much or know much about
what's going going on I could pretty
quickly assess the situation honestly I
feel
like as as I am also in whole life and
I've been
also having a lot of struggles
um this year and last year that have
made me felt a feel pretty lost
or uh yeah pretty down so it's it's easy
for me to just say the right things
because I feel like the same kind of
works words work for most of
us cuz yeah similar things so I know
what to say cuz I know those words would
probably help me if somebody said them
to me I feel like those would
be about the words that I would need to
hear
mhm so I just applied that to
ollie yeah I hope she feels
better I hope she can stay strong and
even if if she can't like for her it's
also what 3 years now
right after 3 years I I think if you're
as active as someone like Ollie or
me you bound to reach a point
where it's just hard
to go on the same way like acting as if
everything's
okay is difficult acting like
fine
no you get burnt out and and it's more
than just being burnt out I don't know
how far how much Ollie cares about the
same things that I care
about um but yeah for me it's like the
burnout combined with issues that I
just eh don't want to accept and things
that just don't
seem you
know and that's been very stressful for
me and I've been really trying
to combat
that uh on my
[Music]
side so I hope you guys can understand
if maybe sometimes I try to keep my
streams on the shter side these
days or even do something like this
taking two days
off it's just for me to maintain my
sanity right now and also I mean I I I
do get told here and there that my
streams are so long and that's why
they're hard to follow up you know like
you guys even like when I have a long
RPG series running and we just finished
uh
Mario I think it's uh fine or smart to
give you guys some time to break uh uh
to catch up and by doing some shorter
streams
so so yeah yeah this is catch up time
for you guys and just like a Brea a
healthy I'm still streaming this is not
a break I'm still streaming but like I'm
I'm I'm just trying to uh keep a good
balance right
now
[Music]
mhm I'm previously on yeah I would like
that
too I don't even know what was was
previously
on why
you thank you
Miss thank
you you part G on me on on the other
hand there's the wow there's just one
wowa I don't need a briefer from you but
when you need a briefer It's always
important to take one thank you for
understanding
yeah but I will be taking a break in
January after the vacation which during
the vacation we will very much be
streaming um but after that there's some
private life stuff that I have to take
care of anyway and I will also take the
time to toxic detox detox from the
internet and work and all
that
yeah a little
break yeah thank
you thank you slime thank
you I haven't had like a proper break
where I don't have to work or
so since I
joined cuz even even on my vacations I
always like
communicate and play plan things on on
Discord like I check my Discord like 20
times a
day if I'm not on the computer if I'm on
the computer I'm like constantly
checking there's always something going
on and yeah like remember the the
Greece uh vacation like there I didn't
stream really cuz I felt awkward to
stream while rmt was there but I still
did a recording I brought my laptop to
do a recording there
work recording and stuff like that but
this is this might just be my first real
break even when you were terribly sick
yeah last year last year so far I'm
doing fine I've been drinking actimel
every
day even though I I I I hear it's not
effective it's kind of a scam I don't
care it says it has vitamins and St up
Stack Up acate
do you guys
know it's like a little yogurt drink
that has you know it's it says it it
strengthens your
[Music]
defenses I'm sure there's actually
vitamins in there so I can't see how
it's a
scam I will stay yeah probiotics and
vitamins I will stay healthy this year
okay I will not get
sick
yeah Yak could is something like your c
a little bit a little bit
probiotic it's a little yogurt drink it
tastes so good I really liked it when I
was a
child might as well take Vitamin C
somewh hey I'm eating tangerines right
now I bought a whole bag of tangerines
it's Tangerine time Tangerine Cho Tang
Jo T Tangerine
[Music]
Jo I'm not threatening you it's my cute
accessory I have um I bought like
supplements that are like uh like
multivitamin basically multivitamins
basically and uh supposed
to
uh how to say supposed to keep a cold
away but I haven't been taking them
regularly at
all cuz um sometimes I
forget and sometimes I don't take them
purposefully cuz I don't like the taste
the moment they're in my mouth even that
short moment I don't like the way they
taste somehow they're not
tasteless and it gives me like a little
bit of a
shiver m
don't like it don't like it don't like
it don't like
[Music]
it you know what I
mean but now is a good time to take them
because yeah it's cold
season could you take them with
something like you no I feel like I'll
choke it's okay e
okay you guys really deserve a moment of
Peace of your thank you thank
you starting to run low got to have to
buy some more oh yeah stay healthy Stay
Stay keep your defenses
High powdered vitamins that you can mix
them with tea yeah I guess I could do
that
too so this anyway anyway anyway I feel
like we've uh did the Chit Chat long
enough let's start reading some super
[Music]
chats ah for everybody or anybody who
lives like in LA or in the area there is
apparently a shop right now that sells
our merchandise I did not know about
this and honestly I didn't know what
they were selling selling until Kai youu
posted
some
stuff
uh
here they have uh quite a lot of
stuff they're selling like plushies and
some keychains and figurines and all
that Plushies are cute from Ian and
Japan and ID I think
too so if you're there maybe check it
out it's uh Southern California the
Tokyo Japanese
lifestyle Glendale store in Glendale
Galleria until December
31st as uh reported by whole life
production English Twitter just in case
you wanted some merch cuz like normally
I'm just saying this because overseas
you know I know you guys uh wish you had
easier access to merchandise and there's
quite a quite a few things
there just so you know there's also some
um what do you call them uh tap
tapestries I think the tapestries I'm
not sure if there's a Ian tapest
maybe yeah the friends of you plushies
is so cute so
cute what else what else
else what else was there to report
on as you know the the concert thing is
announced
now as we talked
about please look forward to my
involvement with honeyworks I really
love honey Works since a long long time
ago and I I do think my voice suits
honey Works quite a
bit so so I will let you be the judge of
that but yeah also look at this the
dates are 16 to
17th March in makarim Mesa
again and as I said I'm like I'm I'm
surprised and excited about us expanding
with within the same venue that's
exciting
and and they posted the image and I'm
also really excited about that that yo
it looks like it's like beach themed or
vacation themed or
so I wonder if they're going to put like
um if they're going to plaster the
ground with like uh not wallpaper ground
paper floor paper whatever cuz it looks
here in the image it looks like they're
going to put like a
beach thing printing on the on the
floor I think I've seen whole the makani
Expo
halls in like like having their own
floor ring depending on no I don't think
there will be actual sand I think if
anything they will put some kind of uh
printed out floor paper on the it will
not be sand I
think that would be
crazy that would be insane I wonder what
the trees will be made out of look at
this will there be actually a hot air
balloon I mean if they put it up there
it's got to be
there
yo I can with full confidence say that I
have no idea what the booths will
be I still don't know if I can exhibit
my
nails yeah I wish I hope I can I want to
exhibit my
nails it's an Airship
sogy oh but uh yeah look at this it says
there's a town area a Park area a cafe
area an entertainment area and a market
area yeah that makes sense Park area is
probably like a chilling area maybe I
don't know where where are all the
booths I wonder what kind of booths will
there be I have no
idea I wish I knew guys I wish I
knew
yeah
um also I I'll say it again I'm not
doing a pioda concert watch there's
already uh I think bals and fuu doing
one so I felt like there's no need for
me to do one I know it would make sense
but I know people especially Japanese
nulis probably expect me to do one and
that's why I was thinking so hard about
it but I don't want to like you
know yeah I don't know
[Music]
man when there's already so
many I don't know join in one of the
others I don't want to self like invite
myself you
know I'm not the kind of person to
invite myself to a stream that
somebody's planning on their
own cuz I don't I'm not sure if I would
want that happen either to myself like
if I planning to do something on my own
and I have a reason why I want to do it
alone and I don't want to be cuz it puts
you in an awkward position when when
somebody do does ask you can I be part
of this and you're like
well I guess like puts you in an awkward
position sometimes I don't want to put
anybody in that kind of awkward
position
mhm yeah yeah
yeah also Ena has her
Freddy uh really really late birthday
life this
weekend ah I wanted to ask you guys
about that um we know that eventually
waa will do one eventually eventually
eventually because I went to Japan to
record
something H here is the
question what time should I aim
for should I go for Japanese prime time
where I feel like when there's a stream
like this happening in Japanese prime
time there's a high chance that Japanese
viewers will like they're also loyal you
know that they're they they love
watching any kind of like whole life
important 3D stream so I feel like many
would show up uh Japanese Prim Time
would be like middle of the day for EU
which is not bad especially if it's on
the weekend for na it's not so good I
saw uh I saw ena's
time Ena is like 5:00 p.m. PT which is
not exactly prime time but I guess it's
like a a good time for na so I could do
na prime time too but like I never
stream at na prime time and I I I'm not
sure if people would come to watch My
Stream I don't know I don't I'm scared
I'm scared of everything actually and I
I don't even consider EU prime time
really to be
honest cuz I feel like yeah I always
stream during that time but it's like
give I'm I'm giving
myself a disadvantage just by doing that
just by choosing
that youa time excellent for
na yeah so I I'm like na prime time for
na viewers hope that they will come or
Japanese prime time to hope that
Japanese viewers will come and hopefully
I mean also other viewers but like I you
I would get I would say either the na
boost or the Japan
boost H but even the na prime time that
Ena chose for example isn't bad for uh
for Japanese time zone cuz it's like
10:00
a.m. it's not
bad
but
yeah but uh really shitty for
EU so if I don't want
to uh [\h__\h] over my European viewers too
much then I should probably go for the
Japanese prime
time there's no merch up there is no
merch
[Music]
drum would you guys be okay with
Japanese prime time would you guys come
watch
[Music]
live I will say I have
also many guests
and they may
be the you know
maybe no I mean there's a balance I
don't want to spoil anything but
um there are Japanese guests
[Music]
so are they allowed to
overlap uh generally anybody can overlap
these streams but I feel like the ones
who would appear would probably not
overlap it even if it's uh pre-recorded
I think that is the one courtesy to
[Music]
follow I'll definitely do that for a wa
thank
you okay then maybe I'll go for Japanese
prime time yeah
weekend stream would be
much well I already have the date but I
just don't have the time I feel like I
think the time is uh for me to decide
the date was for them to decide I will
let you know when I
[Music]
can
it will be a
weekend
[Music]
yes
yeah then then it's
good then whatever
fine weekend for Japan too uh
uh
yes yes
yes
yes weend for
[Music]
anyone elevated music's nice right what
is Japanese par time 8 or 10 I don't
know anything in between that I could do
I could do eight I could do nine I could
do 10 the later the better so I might
even go for something like 10:00 p.m. go
like really late so that it's later for
Na and later for EU makes it a bit
easier for you guys but it's still still
good you know for Japan
too yeah might just to 10: p.m. if I
can yeah that's good that's good
right okay I'll ask staff too if that's
okay
[Music]
and then we'll see what
happens I won't say the date yet though
cuz I want to announce it
properly my birthday is on the 25th of
December will you sing on the C Orest
for me and kfp all I want for Christmas
is you the upcoming one no the upcoming
one will be probably archived so no but
I probably do another Christmas uh K
closer to
Christmas and I might just sing that
song there's not many Christmas songs
that I know I know that
one okay Super Chat
time finally finally wa is going to read
the super
chats where were we uh here super chats
from emergency
meeting the [\h__\h]
thumbnail I'm really really happy that
chy gave me this thumbnail
afterwards uh I didn't even ask for it
but chy made me a thumbnail it was quite
[Music]
nice wait which one is it this
one oh look at that face look at that
face
[Music]
oh
no this was very important to me this
stream okay [\h__\h]
Ms I'll shoot them with my
shotgun I really want
[Music]
to Persona empty wallet I the 20 Wet
lightning cable D Bruce J
D Marcus menes D Gary ktoo D res 4 for
One D thank you what do you mean I don't
need ass surgery I need jeans
[Music]
surgery junk chunk thank you for the red
chat is this a new fashion
trend don't say that I was so
embarrassed I was so ashamed I was so
shooked man
but it spawns so much fan art oh my
God but I don't even know if I can
really use all that fan art like I can
only use the head part I got I got to
cut off the bottom because like what am
I going to do put like my open ass out
on my thumbnail
like how is that going to you know I
usually like to use fat uh fan arts that
kind of suit whatever game I'm
playing what game is it going to suit
when I have my ass open
HH we'll see if I can make use of any of
them but thank you junky chunk M Tunas
thanks to the pinky sorry for your loss
thank you like at least someone is
taking this problem
seriously rise
up maybe I'll you know in Photoshop
there's a there's a fixing tool where
you can patch up things maybe I'll just
fix my ass like
that I wonder if that
[Music]
works thanks for the shop I love you
Ponto soon thank
you okay that's already it let's go to
Mario Cart super
chats Mario Kart is here
cute cute cute
cute
yeah if it was that easy to fix my
clothes I would fix my my my my my my my
coat Sky D Cruz d tny d Psy danash SE 47
danash game 8910 D so many people
sending me new pants
fund Tanny thank you for the red of chat
my first AA here's my birthday tag still
got one year left till I'm able to
legally go to kfb Convention drinking
After parties
oh anyway I just want to say thank you
for being such a large source of
motivation uh sausage Source enjoy my
life W love also B pants thank you yes B
pants oh you're welcome I'm glad I can
help and oh happy
birthday so wait does that mean you're
20 now cuz I'm guessing 21 would be the
legal age
cuz you're donating in
dollars you're such a baby you were born
in
20 2003 such a
Baby
Gaga but sorry you probably feel like a
real adult right now right I also felt
like an adult when I was
12 congratulations on your birthday
happy happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
pants too happy birthday oh yeah not in
your pants cuz we band the pants happy
birthday in your skirt I don't know uh
SC um happy birthday in your in your
shoes whatever it's hard to I have to
change that
song happy birthday to you
tny yeah
enjoy enjoy the time well you still have
the number two to boast about
man there's no rush to become 21 or any
older than that so take it easy and
enjoy every day every
year like is you last one yeah dramatic
I know but do
it no rush only love
rash so
[Music]
true I love that song it's kind of grown
on me love brush is really grown on
me I feel like um I don't really care if
love Rush is like the least popular song
in my album because I think it's it just
has such a special meaning and for kfp
it will always be an important song
because of the meaning and I feel like
in in let's imagine I would give like a
real life venue
concert I feel like I would sing Love
Rush at the end
and can you imagine how
freaking deep and emotional that would
be and how everybody would probably cry
yeah it's just
[Music]
a and you know I kind of did create the
album with like a concert in the back of
my
mind and does I think love Rush is very
very necessary on my album mhm to create
a story and to create a timeline and and
to cover all my bases everything that I
need and that for me is like the perfect
thank you song to put at the end of a
stream or at the end of a concert you
know to just express my gratitude yeah
so with that gratitude I say thank you
Tanny m kfp cile thank you for the pinky
comes on hello K after a long wait the
music album has finally arrived ooh
pineapple yay rest in peace G pant thank
you yeah ah is pineapple your
favorite thank you I also really really
really love pineapple thanan I hope you
can listen to my album a
lot as we just talked about it love Rush
too every song deserves love so please
listen to it muchos
muchos fim Mo thanks for the pinky hello
that certainly was an interesting
emergency message to watch when I got
back from work today I also got my date
for my Fury exam and my driving license
soon I'll be able to race like you guys
oh so many people getting licenses you
and qu
quason is it time for me
too I I said to myself myself I will
only get it after Holo cuz I don't
really need it now most of the time and
um I don't really trust
myself with like being able to focus on
it I want to I don't want to stress
myself out about it
so I don't want
to it's not that hard I think it is I'm
stupid I'm stupid you've proven your
driving skills today I I prove them
every
day prove them every day I
do I don't know now is definitely not
the time cron is so smug about
[Laughter]
it she did tell me like I should come
visit her and she'll drive me
around she did invite me
basically
yeah we talked a lot like oh my God I I
I never talked that much to her before
but we also like opened up to each other
about some things and um we
also
uh ranted about some things
together yeah so we had a good time
talking should talk more
often what prompted it oh me just like
uh
like she just sent
me uh her Advent calendar video pretty
early and I just thanked her for it you
know and then I asked her perhaps to be
in another
one yeah yeah she's been very
very um motivated I think that's what it
feels like to me very helpful oh my God
can't believe cron is in the Advent
calendar because waa totally did not say
that everybody is in the Advent calendar
be careful now I have a shotgun in my
hand yeah
[Music]
um so cimo be careful on the road yeah
that is the most important thing and
never drunk Drive
never del d d d thank you
ah what you're so nice I will never be
number one what the hell what are you
saying but you're so nice thank
[Music]
you oh really have a confession I think
I'm addicted to eating the Cy chicken
platter at the ANL Cafe in Singapore is
that one still ongoing I had been having
it multiple times and I still think
about really I was worried like um with
something like that
like from the photo that I saw I felt
like there's not much sauce so I was
wondering hopefully the chicken isn't
too dry so even when you run out of the
sauce you can just still enjoy did that
not bother you the chicken is great
really oh
good
really
it always sells out
[Music]
y like chicken is like fried chicken is
such a go-to food for collab cafes or
whatever for me I don't even choose it
like they suggest it usually and I guess
it's like quite popular for even if
you're not a kfp fan if you look at the
stuff and you're like hm what should I
get I feel like it's it's a popular
choice generally just people loving
fried chicken and it's such a reliable
trustworthy kind of food
usually the drink too it's not as sweet
as I expected it to be damn I wish I
could try the things
man like I went to the Korean collab
Cafe but I can't just fly around the
whole world all the time and test out
all the collab cafes man
sad I mean I could but the time that
that would take up just to go to a
collab CFE for Korea I just had a
general good reason cuz I generally
wanted to visit Korea not saying I don't
want to visit Singapore I do but there's
not as much motivation there as for
Korea and in Korea I at least had
someone to show me around and
Singapore I don't think I know
anybody so that's also like kind of uh
an
issue
H so this unless somebody would go with
me but uh yeah it's hard to convince
someone to do a trip like that oh but I
did I did remember when I said in oli's
call when I said oh we should go to
Valley next year so I I did get that
ball rolling I wrote uh to the ID
girls in uh like a group server yo who
wants to go and it's going to be a big
big big group uh vacation I think so
many ID girls are up for
it so
exciting yeah I got the B
rolling yeah yeah yeah I don't know when
we're discussing when but like in
general just generally yes I want to go
I got like so many
[Music]
yeses it already got me so excited yeah
Bali Hol house yeah yeah yeah
yeah we can rent like a big big Suite or
a big house or
so and I was saying we should do off
collabs and all that too and we'll just
we'll just be having so much fun oh my
God oh my God oh my
God oh my God oh my God oh my
[Music]
God I won't confirm or or so any any
participants because I mean it's it's
still still might change depending on
what time frame we're actually going to
choose but so far everybody's really
interested yeah b b b
b i I think you know I wanted to go to
Bali because I I thought it might be a
good Meetup for ID
members it might be more accessible easy
for them to get there and I I hear it's
relatively
cheap destination like at least for
accommodations St should be relatively
cheap and you
know now if I can go to some beach
Paradise that is also close to ID
members why the hell
not just combining the two things I want
to
[Music]
do so yeah back to the super
chats I guess for next year so there's
males and there's probably another
couple of Japan trps but
that's and and and Bali and who knows
what else I want to go to Korea
again
[Music]
ooh
hello where we
gone are we we're already back okay
I was just saying like oh next year I
can already say I'll be going to Bali
I'll be going to Japan I'll be going to
the Maldives I'll be going to oh I
already have like an an certain Europe
trap trap trip uh
fixed mhm
with Holo Ian member and then I want to
set up another one with a Hol
member uh you know this n this and that
this and that this and
that it's not a trap it's not a trap if
anything I'm getting
trapped it's actually a trip I was
invited to wink wonk wink wonk wink
wonk
Legas somebody asked
me to go
somewhere let's
[Music]
go yeah here it was blackout D NTV
D George Martinez
oras what are you doing here
hello Ellie Smith thanks for the pinky
you kept begging management to give you
bigger assets and now that you have them
you're upset you ripped your pants
somehow I don't understand
[Music]
woman you know that's not the
issue it's the [\h__\h] moths I have a
moth
[Music]
problem
man you know it and you still teasing me
you little
[\h__\h] Amigo 265 fre your second time
racing with a vtuber nice
Freak video
gamer n you're welcome a thanks for the
pinky after reading into why there is
almost no lsf 100 in the U seems Kiana's
getting scammed by the higher number is
much better mindset she so she will need
this money yeah yeah yeah this kind of
um like made me wonder when I saw the
Super Chat uh on stream and I I Googled
about it but I didn't really I ended up
like checking out those American
sunscreens but they they said SPF 100
and then lsf 100 like both of it was
hundreds so I'm
like so I thought they were different
but then they have the same numbers on
the same product for both things is that
even
possible it oh that's what you mean 100
is only 1% better than 50 what why
how can it be like
that I'm praising you for managing to
rip your jeans at that point excuse
[Music]
me that's so
weird oh
[Music]
well I will um
what's the word for when you think
something
works but like it doesn't but you like
just imagine
it oh yeah Placebo I will placebo effect
it and I'll be happy oh I won't be I
won't be having a a a sunburn and I'll
say oh it's because I had the 100
SPF it worked
it's okay it's okay A than thank you oh
thank you for the sweet words
[Music]
than that's a cute profile picture is
that
Amit no
is
enhance oh no that's
hatam oh I mean they're sisters of
course I can make a mistake there Jimmy
Russ d g d thank you with honey
mustard golden i d thank you Barry G D
oh yeah col let's go am
a
[Music]
shal black out thank you oh wait that's
the bastard [\h__\h] him morally immoral D
unknown D Pride Z thank you it's okay
don't worry about
it thank you for watching anytime you
can Ms or M miss miss miss Lulu
than thank you I'm glad to be your
favorite Wings CV
than
R Bruce Jen Clips
D Wing Jackson Wing Captain D pant
thanks the pinky
sadly I'm going to be VOD gang for a
little over 2 weeks because I'm going on
my first trip in 5 years for vacations
in Japan but I'll make it up by getting
as much V mer I can get my hands on oh
well I feel I I feel like for me at
least those two weeks will be over in an
instant but I hope they will not be over
so quickly for you I hope you can savor
every moment and enjoy everything as
much as you can wa merge in Japan huh I
feel like you'll find it here and there
you should go to the gacha machine for
sure
the catam machine with the small myth
thingies besides that oh maybe I guess
the Tokyo character Street
thingy is probably also still open while
you're there cuz it just
opened oh it's until January 18th
perfect then time for you to go there I
watch the video of uh Quicky going there
there's a lot of stuff it's not just um
the three ambassadors so there's
something for
everyone yeah maybe go to places that I
visited before like enoshima I really
recommend enoshima but although in the
winter it's not as nice as in the summer
but you you could still go so please
have fun enjoy see you soon Wings CV d
space waterfall D Ryan wood D James
Jackson
d
yeah that that's super chat take care
the Great Ghost D Wing CV D Ryan wood D
thank you for racing with me Bruce J Le
dang and the Great Ghost thanks for the
pinky if you ever come to America
there's this Trail ah called The Man
incline in Colorado I we looked this one
up right which basically goes in a
straight line up the side of a mountain
it makes for a good L like day workout
yeah we talked about this one already so
thanks for the recommend Foundation
though
yeah Bruce
Jones
the an X Monkey D and the Great Ghost
D sorry that I'm not probably not going
to go visit your
Trail don't recommend hik to I I
wouldn't need them cuz I'm going to get
myself a running machine
treadmill
yeah
okay
next that was fun this stream was
fun I really like the fan game Jim try
thanks for the red super chat c to think
it's my first birthday in kfp already I
feel so lucky to be part of this awesome
Community some of the best chickens out
there an amazing Phoenix I'm proud to
call my own she love you boss thanks for
all you do don't forget about
yourself you're part of what makes the
community awesome thank you so much for
being you you're
amazing love love love love you too love
you too happy
birthday hope it was a great
birthday you're so sweet Jim
Tracy you're so sweet love love love
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your shoe happy birthday in
your shirt too happy birthday to
you that doesn't sound as enchanting as
the pants
version what can we do times
change so
sad so sad should I unbend pants just
for the birthday song I can't do that I
have to show them who's the boss I can't
just go back and forth with my
statements you know that'll show
weakness and they'll they'll make all my
pants break cuz they think they can just
like [\h__\h] with me like
that yeah then all all my pants will be
[Music]
broken
that's how you feel that I'm out what do
you
[Music]
mean are you
pants man what confusing Tracy thank you
jacob7
Ricky thank you yes more and more people
are getting POV and I heard geek Jack is
sending it out
[Music]
nowar mp53 G I am a beep you should
change your name at this point cuz I'm
not even cuz of my stupid
new uh mixer I'm not even using the beep
anymore cuz it's too loud you should
just change it to I am a chi
beep and thanks the CH heyel another
year another birthday AA
oh you should have a birthday party with
Jim
Tracy yo but this time I got a nice job
to back it up o you mean your job at kfp
though because of sad job I can't always
catch your streams live I'm glad to
still catch the occasional stream I will
always be proud to be part of kfp and I
will always be proud to have you thank
you thank you for still being
around I'm I am happy to have you don't
ever leave or else
I have this gun just
saying
y I may or may not go yand on you so
yeah happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoe happy birthday in
your shoes to oh no we already had
shoes happy birthday in
your underwear too happy birthday to
you and I might have more than yeah true
true but it's kind of
weird
congratulations please tweet yourself to
some yummy cake I wish I had some right
now yum Yum Yum
Yum stay healthy and happy and good luck
and uh fun at your job too don't forget
about me the
greatost taco
Brek looking for
[Music]
top
P you're
welcome and Di thank you for the red
chat here's for no money issues o de I'm
fine I'm fine I'm
fine thank you so
[Music]
much I appreciate it I hope you you have
you know plenty so that you don't get
money issues yeah be careful be careful
always put yourself number one
prioritize yourself y know and then
maybe prioritize some some other things
too before me I can't
I don't think I should be a number two
if you have like some other things you
know to take care
of don't neglect it you also fine don't
worry about okay yay we're both fine
high five high fine
[Music]
hey good for you good for
me good for us we're
[Music]
fine
but have you ever had a massage before
treat yourself to a massage yo and then
treat yourself to a spa day and then
treat yourself to a high tea afternoon
tea and then treat yourself to a day in
the cinema I want to go to the cinema
right now because I want to watch the
newest
um
P what's it again in English
Day movie I want to watch it but my
friends don't give a [\h__\h] about it so I
have to wait for uh rmt to watch it with
me yeah the Hunger Games there's a new
Hunger Games movie which is so weird cuz
if it wasn't for one
single Instagram story of A friend of
mine then I wouldn't know that it's
currently happening why is it
nonexistent in the social media and all
that there's new movie and like nobody
talks about it nobody advertises
[Music]
it it's better than the last ones oh
[\h__\h] yeah but like where is the
marketing maybe they just thought people
will come
anyway it did pretty well in US box
office that's good for them did you
watch the others I
did and now my my my friends don't want
to go so I asked rmt and she said yeah
but she's uh currently not available so
I'm waiting for her and then we'll go
watch
it yeah it does have Tyrion from Game of
Thrones yes yes yes yes yes yes yes was
it wasn't his name Peter
dingl I think so yeah that was the thing
I saw that and like when I saw the
trailer I was like what the [\h__\h] there's
a new Hunger Games movie coming out I
was already confused there H didn't they
end the story was it an open ending
in the last movie I honestly don't
remember I should probably rewatch
the movies before I go in there cuz I
don't really remember
much it's a
prequel oh that's
[Music]
cool oh that makes sense okay
okay but I might still rewatch it before
I go so I can get into the mood yeah
although it's pretty
[Music]
sad oh
yeah if I rewatch it I'll see my beloved
Natalie Dormer again because she's in
the SEC I think only in the second one
though but in the second one she has
this hot hairstyle she looks so good no
who gives a [\h__\h] about Jennifer Lawrence
it's all about nalie
Dormer
mhm
who cares about Jennifer Lawrence when
there's Natalie Dormer I mean please
come
on sorry but I
mean I may be a little bit
biased they're both hot so I'll take
both no you can have Jennifer Lawrence
cuz I'll be taking
Dormer you can't have both cuz I'll have
one of them
[Music]
I love her so
much I love her so
much
Min could I shoot
you but whatever you don't have to find
her you know any good because you don't
have a chance with her anyway I am the
only
one who gets a
[Music]
chance is she
married does Natalie dmer have a
boyfriend is she
[Music]
single uh
married
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] David Oaks he's British of
course he is of course he's
British since 2008 18 5 years [\h__\h] why
did I not act
faster they have a daughter since
2021 the couple entered into a civil
partnership wait what does that mean
what does that mean what is a civil
partnership does that mean that they
kind of broke up but they're still
together because of the
[Music]
child do I have a chance
again is there a chance is that
basically a
divorce
what what is a civil
partnership oh [\h__\h] it's the opposite
kind of it's like a marriage for people
who don't want a marriage do it a
legally recognized Union with rights
similar to those of manage marriage
created originally for same-sex couples
but they're not a samees seex c
is jur jurisdictions where they were not
wait why did they do that
they're why did yeah I guess it's just
marriage that's not religious yeah for
people who don't really want to do like
a I mean even non-religious people do
marriages but I guess it's for people
who really just don't really care about
the the church aspect of it or
whatever yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
okay okay [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] ah my
wife my
wife God damn it she's so cute she's so
cute I'm looking at pictures right now
pictures of you pictures of
[Music]
me pictures of you
pict of
me a it's a [\h__\h] Vikings actor a damn
it
Vikings oh
man oh she's so cute without makeup on
this
like
picture oh she's so
[Music]
cute
VI Viking is awesome I mean it it was
until the last season or so but uh this
one's from Vikings Valhalla which I
haven't tried yet I want to get into
it oh why does she look so pretty
without makeup
too wow wow what a what a woman what a
woman they have an interesting beautiful
dog but I guess that's where we wouldn't
have worked well cuz I'm a cat
person it's a pretty dog
[Music]
sheesh there's so many pictures of them
walking their
[Music]
dog is still like dogs do
beagles the Beagle the Beagle that was
sniffing
me
oh my God okay back to Super Chat
[Music]
sorry and where was I did I read any of
this did I where where am I where am I
who am
I ah here post wait ziply postcript Ang
congrats to you and my for the conert
Blu-ray I watched it live and it was a
lot of fun you mean at the venue or in
the Stream with New Years coming soon if
Ian wants to do a shuffle mle who would
you like to switch with a
[Music]
n yeah I know that I know exactly who I
would switch with
ly yeah first Flora Flora thank you for
the red super chat comes on
me been 2 years working for kfp I will
keep supporting you as a fan for my role
model thank you it's 6:00 a.m. in Korea
I have to go to work IRL I'll watch it
in the archive after work thank you yeah
V Watchers are very
strong I made a poll the other day cuz I
was wondering about some things but uh
yeah
wow I'm not even surprised at the amount
of clip Watchers
because yeah it it just makes sense
looking at everything uh and it's fine
it's fine to have so many clip watches
it's totally fine but uh uh I was more
interested in the balance between vaud
Watchers and live Watchers that was
actually the one thing I really cared
about I only put the clip watching
option cuz I thought there's certainly
some people who don't watch either and
just watch Clips so I'll give them an
option but I really just wanted to know
about
uh how many of my viewers wish
they could watch my streams live but
they can't catch them because of time
zones or um my streams being too long or
whatever so those are pretty even yeah
but uh I I I don't I don't
know I wish I wish uh we could
get them to watch live but you know it's
a time zone issue I would say mostly
yeah it is what it is it is what it is
I'm just happy that they're watching at
all hi VA Watchers how you doing how are
you
[Music]
doing your friends think you're insane
well that's kind of mean it's just like
watching any other
streamer like they probably wouldn't
think you're insane if you were just a
fan of some twitch streamers or YouTuber
like a non a flesh tuber
right it's no no difference hi Aura a
sorry a I need to reply to you I saw
your message but like when I saw it I
was not really I don't know I was either
in bed or some
somewhere I like your ideas that's what
I wanted to say
though I like your
[Music]
ideas
flesh streaming is a niche
too yeah but I I feel like they wouldn't
call you insane if they call you insane
for watching a vtuber
then probably the anime aspect of it
frows them off but yeah anyway back to
Flora 6 a.m. yeah so I I was talking
about B watches hope you enjoying the AR
Flor comes an and good good uh luck with
your job every day keep on fighting
thank you for supporting me and for
being here for two full Years
thank oh she only
streams at good times for you
really really really I didn't see her
streaming while I was like awake I I I
feel like it just doesn't show up on my
YouTube sometimes rarely yeah I feel
like you you're mentioning Ki Ena and
Shi I think it should be Ki Ena and
narissa sometimes fuu especially with
their morning
streams and sometimes they start their
longer their RPG streams are so
early
mhm yeah it's not just free people but
it's just like they're all over the
place they're not
always except for Ena but Ena for me
starts at 11:00 p.m. which I wouldn't
say it's convenient for Europe
but
[Music]
yeah yeah sh streams and a prime time
right I
mean but there's there's some some mix
here and there sometimes some stream a
little bit earlier some sometimes do
stream a little bit later so it's a bit
better than before Advent I would say
like there's a bit more spread out
now from what I've
uh witnessed a bit
more
yeah she is borderline late for a lot of
people in na oh
Nar you watch more Japan and I details
in danen apart from me because of the
time zones yeah I'm assuming you're in
Europe so that makes sense
yeah
am has been streaming pretty late now
yeah and I miss her every
time what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm I miss her every time
like and she doesn't do schedule so I
can't even anticipate
it I don't know what she's up
to oh I got to plan my there's a collab
where I wanted to have her and um I got
to I got to plan that there's so many
things I want to do right
now I got to set something in stone for
the
Advent
um Advent uh Clothing Design stream cuz
we are planning on doing that I just
have haven't been able to find a good
date
um I I will throw a
date at Ena after the Stream
yeah half of Ian dropped schedules it's
so true and I I think back of the times
where uh I was the only one in myth who
wasn't doing a schedule I think and
people were
like
really in like they were I don't know I
want to say mad but everybody was like
please make a [\h__\h] schedule I'm like
I don't want to like I want to stay free
and and and and spontaneous and all the
Japanese members aren't really doing
schedules the only reason Japanese
members are doing more schedules now I
think is because they saw Ian doing it
for like one or two years and we're like
hm maybe this is pretty nice to have
like a
schedule I'm fine i' I've been making
schedule since but like I I was kind of
forced into making them
[Music]
pressured didn't know you were like that
yeah in the beginning I was I think the
only one out of us five who didn't want
to make
[Music]
schedules yeah but I I've been since
making schedules consistently so unless
I want to hide on which day in a week
I'm traveling that's those are times
when I'm not making a schedule or when
I'm really when I have no idea cuz the
week is going to be really spontaneous
and I have no idea when I'm
streaming which is rare a rare
[Music]
thing
yeah I like making schedules
though I like it I enjoy it cuz like I
can um get a good image of if the week
is going to be balanced cuz if I just
decided randomly on the day before or so
I I can't really get a grasp over the
balance of the whole
week and also just looks nice to look at
it and I like you guys' reactions when
when you feel like oh this is an amazing
week then everybody freaks out I like
that I'm like what do you mean it's just
a normal
[Music]
week thank you thank you yeah it shows
up the cute wallpaper
exactly yeah and thank you
Flora D Brandon D Super Snake Mario D
thank you for listening to the album I
appreciate
it thank you oh when you find some free
time you probably found some free time
by now right
right okay
okay I might leave it at
that was so early but I think I should
be
cooking uh tomor I wait wait I'll be uh
in waya stream at like 1:00 a.m. or so
for call in I can't forget about
that yeah let her
cook I made oh I didn't post it on
Twitter but I made some decent
food that on the photo actually looks
underwhelming but the taste was really
special it was some rice with
like
flattened meatballs and some just some
Tomatoes uh and some sour cream or not
actually yogurt with like herbs but the
the meatballs and the rice they had a
really special
flavor I feel
like it's probably the way those are
flavored was probably inspired by some
some countri is cooking I don't know
what but they were uh quite
interesting not like the meatballs
didn't taste like normal meatballs that
you put in a burger they were a bit more
intricate than that and the rice too the
rice was really yummy on its own
even yeah today I'll probably make some
pasta I still have this like last uh
today my new hellofresh box is coming
but I still have the last dish from the
previous
box if the herbs are still looking good
I should make that
one
yeah chab no not chab
te it's hard to tell what it is just by
looking so I don't know I thought the
picture was
underwhelming not as appetizing looking
as it actually tastes was surprisingly
[Music]
good
H the flavor will still be good I have
to check the one thing that annoys me so
much of the hellofresh stuff is like
when they send herbs for example if they
send two different herbs like let's say
uh uh what's
uh
schnit chives
and
uh that was the thing they sent parsley
chives and then they but they put it
mixed in a back totally
Tangled in each other and it says uh on
the recipe cut them chop them separately
because they're going to be used for
different things but then the parsley
isn't even already like separated from
the stem I have to like it has like
smaller stems on it too so first I have
to like I I I swear every [\h__\h] time
this isn't even considered in the recipe
they say like oh 30 minutes to cook this
this but then I always end up with like
50 minutes because for 20 minutes I'm
[\h__\h]
detangling all the
herbs and then I have to rip off the the
stems and all that which is fine that I
would have to probably do that normally
as well that's fine but the entangling
please put it into two separate bags or
or give me um for parsley don't give it
to me like half ass chopped off give me
the full how to say the like the the
bunch with the longer stems cuz then it
doesn't tangle with the other things you
know what I
mean instead of half asked cutting it
off where I still have to cut off things
in the end and then mixing it with the
other stuff and then I have to like cuz
everything's so small I have to spend 20
minutes to entangle everything yeah just
a full plant a full cut of the plant
Mama
Mia
I don't care I'm not getting sponsored
by them anyway unless I like go like
apparently it's really easy to get
sponsored by them like you just go to
them and say hey sponsor me apparently
but that's for like normal YouTubers and
all that whatever it doesn't quite work
like that for us so it's kind of
different so whatever I'm like
whatever I don't need you in my
life I mean I do I do need you in my
life cuz otherwise I'll be cooking the
same thing or
[Music]
nothing Captain meow
nine
me andies I think I know about
that raisins are the best yeah this rice
was supposed to have raisins in it but I
don't like raisins so I didn't keep the
raisins
in anyway uh considering how much I need
the time to untangle my [\h__\h] herbs I
better go now
uh yeah raisins and rice right that's so
weird right so I was thinking that that
has to be from some other country's
Cuisine cuz that's not like a normal
thing you come up with in in Austria
Germany or so I think oh I'm just going
to put in some raisins into this rice
just because for fun and Giggles no I
don't think you normally think of that
you do it in Mexico it's Oriental that's
what I thought cuz overall it tasted
kind of Oriental I think I'm not sure
but or in I don't know I don't know what
it was oh you guys are mentioning all
kinds of countries now so it could be
anything but yeah okay I'm going to go
in German in sorry it was kind of short
gaming session today but uh hope
hopefully made up with lots of chitchat
goodbye see you tomorrow Hol parade
[Music]
hey m
5 and 1 half hours excuse
[Music]
me P it P it P it
I love that
[Music]
song