[Music]
what is this where am
I
B antic
collection it seems like this might be
the start something
new why am I here
how did I get
[Music]
here no
doors stuck in a corner
[Music]
there where were we
right what is
this
what what are you doing here she look
like me
[Music]
what's going
on what are we supposed to do here how
are we supposed to get out of
here anotic
recollection a recollection
[Music]
I don't remember
much
B
B I don't
[Music]
know is that
I getting
[Music]
punched is see an
anim I
[Music]
remember what
try to sniff them to see if they're
good con
con where hav
CRA not
good smells like a bir it's not too bad
I guess
who are you
people hello can you say that
again oh my
god oh you guys can talk of scared
what's
happening what happened to my hands
they're
so I feel weird you know I don't know
why my body looks like this it's so
Square what happened where am I oh my
God what happened I think I hit my head
what happened who are all of you yeah I
that's what I want to know I think you
all have some to
do I my head you hit your head too I hit
I just hit my head I don't see any
cracks sure I'm very durable but it was
trauma damage very
[Music]
durable are you guys also hear us from
another did you see the lights did
anyone see the
lights did you see the
lights I'm not this
I don't have
but I don't know did you see I where are
the
best
oh I'll be right back ba
[Music]
I don't know I thought the corner would
be safe but maybe it's more
the corner is the best in the
end there's a lot of violent things
going
[Music]
on the
enic I don't know white it
[Music]
was I can't stay as a blank stay forever
you I sound crazy talking to myself I'm
not talking to
myself there's a lot of room
here excuse
me you were punching me before but could
I have my corner back
don't punch me otherwise I might have to
punch you
selfdefense don't attack me
[Music]
then scared I'm sced
you'll be okay you have a tail
too yeah but I'm a demon
dog what I'm a Dem
dog don't do that
un I am a
big I'm a big demon dog
nice to meet you nice to meet you you
still have my cor then you're the first
nice person I
met it's scary here do you know why we
here
no maybe we should try to SC or
something yeah do do you know how much
Mel
either that's
odd well maybe we can find a way yeah
[Music]
I don't have
fish I want fish
[Music]
did I don't know why but I'm so
must be
[Music]
the I wonder what color
all I don't know
[Music]
Aon I don't know I
am remember was like maybe a big truck a
big
truck b
b that go a forgotten memories sneak key
sneaky
who am I the world I live
[Music]
in I'm more than
anything the people I hold most
dear peace with Oblivion I feel empty
[Music]
relieved perhaps
Destra I do not
[Music]
know Papa so much I don't
know
mysterious so much I don't know and yet
I know it
don't
it I hear voes again so much I don't
know go toward the light toward the
light hey I'm walking here let's go
towards the light let why if I fall in
the
H actually yeah there's a lot of
lights the lights all together blue and
white those ones are the yeah don't fall
there's a oh wait it looks so Co
oh this looks
dangerous I can't do this this place
must be
like all the lights together though
they oh thank you than go to the
light are we going to shoot up do we
show up like
it say
[Music]
have take
me so
many can we go up can we go go up should
we go towards the
light what's that that looks like an egg
this is much better
[Music]
Big Egg it's a
egg egg
but oh it's not a hole I don't know I
don't think this is an
egg connect
[Music]
going what is this what is
this the bestel
[Music]
castle what you doing here what what are
you doing
here you have a look of the outside is
about
you
oh wait could it
be
Majesty the H the H of drive to the
sanctuary wait
away Royal audience
chamber welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of Rob besto and I am its king
the God who brought you here have
informed me that you remember not but
your own names I
foa aside effect of travel between
worlds and
[Music]
no this must all come as a surprise to
you but herin as well it was I who
summoned you here he speaks funny you
see an unprecedented calamon now
threatens our
world it has swn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our homes
oh King L this lighted land now gives
rise to creatures Shadow know as
[Music]
stands this Kingdom of leesta and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
leest but should the Calamity be left
unchecked it's only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world but
should the Calamity be left uncheck it's
only a matter of time before it consumes
the entire world
[Music]
what I can't
move
oh why is he getting out of the chair oh
face with this Prospect I scouted the
ancient t for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found
one the
ritual of hero
summoning you who H from another world
have been summoned here by me to become
the saviors of the best a
savior okay only you have the power to
save our
world and so I ask Will
you who's
this we
is is it a great host of St has broken
through a defensive
line I I don't know ready to be a hero
yet we are rushing to mount a defense
but the situation is dying Your Majesty
we must get you somewhere
safe strangers Str
B what you here will you accept this
destiny
there is a power within you will use it
to save us save this
[Music]
world I have a
weap the his name is
normally
but know I'm ready to
play Celesta the ancest blessings upon
you my name is Celesta notate to call
upon
me your heart be a
okay you thank you for
letting you may call me a
[Music]
I didn't
see you yes I do Myer
my you I'm no f i fight to the last okay
let's
fight I don't see anything yet it's good
to be
prepared all it hasn't even started yet
sir are you okay Elizabeth is my
[Music]
name I don't know every time I get it's
what is this why
[Music]
does scary
to
right this over here are you cat I am
I'm a big cat I'm very first and is such
a beautiful castle yourness could you
maybe go back
to you the power of
[Music]
show them okay I'll you in my are you
more I'm ready I think I'm
ready it is a long and tedious name
isn't it it's a pretty
[Music]
long
don't she's nice okay oh oh
D built to you a king of faces
unprecedent
crisis the Calamity befs leaving it of
Life infested with the mon
know not even the might of the castle to
be safe anymore a land of simple words
Perhaps it is too late to save this
world from destruction
nevertheless it is our duty to defend a
king and a
[Music]
country on me
the back is the same as
[Music]
[Applause]
light oh no no
no I need to eat something
eat
more
[Music]
oh
the oh my gosh
[Music]
keep on spawning the little
guys get the
[Music]
king am
I I
need going
[Music]
oh there tiny ones
too there's so many
stains okay the cake the Kake is at the
gate I have to protect oh my
gosh
B did we do it b
ball
revolation revolation
Revelation
[Music]
reation
reol bu
revolation re this is the
left reation revolation
buff Revelation b b reation
[Music]
B am I missing something
B he's de right the stay
King where is
everybody
[Music]
B oh my gosh B
guys did you know we we failed to save
the world once that was that was the
that was the world did we not do it oh
my God wait so is this like a
different I think horses have turned
back the
[Music]
time what's going on I thought we did it
finish you can get me out of here thees
they're not telling me to do
anything still here maybe I'll just find
a
[Music]
corner Mar I'm going
toour that feels a bit better to have
some
[Music]
I don't know what
to I guess you
[Music]
know it we almost did it maybe we
didn't do you have bread are you SA
[Music]
I have I'm
good my only friend
here let's hope we can get out of here
for good
[Music]
is that what my name
is I don't know the last thing I
remember is that I got hit by a truck
byck it's a good thing I had my
[Music]
snack
B
clothes well I I feel like you need to
go to the
[Music]
shoppingall but we can go shopping for
clothes are going shopping for
clothes I feel like I might have seen
this before I remember this though
Echo are forgotten memories Who I Am the
world I live in world
[Music]
I more than
anything people I hold most
dear oh face with Oblivion I feel
empty relieved
oh a lot of
emotions I don't
know
Pap so much I don't know
yet
yet the bright light I don't know and
yet the light don't go toward the light
the bright light
there a this absolutely what I will call
it it says you took the
word thank you madam it's
just I'm trying it's it's the first step
into a gaining my thought my head told
me to call you B boo I
I
I'm what is have no idea where they that
from a I'm never heard that's what I
thought too yeah they said that you were
my
wife I don't see ring on you
[Music]
either bad happening over
there I'm going to stay towards the know
it's a first meeting I'm not ready
[Music]
I for
do
I is nice to me too you say B bow just
like the pink
one I don't know have you talked to her
a lot
moo yeah Moko was her name she was cute
just like you and then she said that I
was sweaty and it was very strange oh I
don't think you're sweaty you don't
really I I kind of I don't know what
this think of
M I don't know she has a tail like me
though I just want to
wow I tried touching I should try
touching her
tail every we try touch you I can see
maybe maybe she react like
[Music]
me I'm a I'm not going to touch your
tail not my tail
[Music]
was the castle this
Castle it looks
familiar yeah what are you doing
[Music]
here you're going to take me
wa the heroes at the sary B wait is that
us is that
me king I like his mustache he
ear oh the brought you yeah I don't
remember
much travel between
[Music]
worlds I don't like the Calamity
part the thing the
Shadows the white
room
[Music]
sh the K looks kind of fuffy I'll
protect
you you someone maybe I'm here I'm here
to be your
here
okay I'll do my best
I'm not used to all these people but
seen this already great the St okay the
S
[Music]
ba oh yeah let's kill some
his Royal Highness
[Music]
was she doesn't mind if I TCH your tail
are you actually a
Dem you said why you guys when I touch
your
to I don't know feel weird to
me
just I don't
know oh I hurt myself
I don't
know I know her she was trying to beat
me
up I'll protect
[Music]
you Al she's my
friend I have
a no no could you PR for me thank you
I appreciate it hey she's talking to me
[Music]
away I you to the king you
I'm not bullying her I'm just I just
want to hear
the why can't I
[Music]
run
little you are one youus I am r
[Music]
you are I'm ready to protect the
kingdom I'm
[Music]
ready please save my family the K like
I'm just a I'm just a n
hero a hero
that I'm
just I'm not a I'm
[Music]
just I need to protect
something I know how they
[Music]
oh
my
[Music]
W's no no no oh my gosh I'm a
danger the laser laser Danger
[Music]
am I in the FR in the back go go she
going to jump
jump I got to
e eat away from me can I eat again stay
away from me I can't e
again just I'm him
wor there we
go
okay she a
[Music]
trk hey stop that
a square
[Music]
shads ball I can Jo the battle
okay hold your weapon and left click
Revelation okay reation
Revelation
ration
[Music]
Revelation oh what's this
ash revelation
[Music]
Ste has been
red what's going
on ba I did it I'm not inur the mighty
armed one must be the leader the
stinking
fascinating this is not not good
wow I see why they call you ear well
being a right pickle without your
help weay minimal diamonds thanks to
your fathering is thank
you I was Hast to inform His Majesty of
our Victory will you accompany
[Music]
me what are you thinking
wow iard the
news Billy called upon you suddenly
youas my attitude what interests me most
however is the strange power you
manifested during the battle with which
you able to defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from
Annihilation according to the her the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation but once they used it to
Route the stost it seems that the power
vanished Without a
[Music]
Trace that's blood
bril so what are we supposed to do the
next time the St attack revelation we
must cover the secrets of this
phenomenon if we have prail against
many questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of lesto still
stands today thanks to
you I want some more will you lend us
your strength to save the vessal from
ruin on behalf of all the best I thank
you you're welcome
bless to have your Aid kind house allow
me to introduce the four Great guilds
which are responsible for Eno the
Kingdom's peace and
prosperity the for the Curious where
knowledge and creativity are valuable
the Scarlet one a you
R Celesta the home with Glory secret
ambition and vision where closest allies
become fiercest survivals the Amber coin
wow
the sanctum of
healing where the spirit of empathy and
devotion thriv the aing
C and the beacon of the righteous and
loyal where great threats are faced at
even way to CL the DAT SW oh it's
cute these guilds will become your home
during a time a guild
oh what's
Guild beyond the
lies the room of Truth there the whe of
[Music]
thep is it going to be
okay time to roll the dice be seeing
some let save this world
together okay r two wait go forth with B
oh let's save the world
yeah okay okay St on the platform of the
[Music]
an theing of the heart the
peaceful I miss the raising Cur of the
heart seek the peaceful Sur for
[Music]
by
bye that's what I am the
cloak the
cloak inventory
inventory ah I button doesn't work e
button do I put it
here B did I do it
B baa I have something extra special now
I'm with unwavering will seek to defend
the soul of G I'm unwavering will to
defend the soul of G I
[Music]
will
somebody from
before you have like me
blue your's a pink I like mine better I
like
mine yeah Elizabeth I heard you talking
Elizabeth yes I'm you you have an enemy
enemy I don't know my name wait what she
punched me an enemy what's your
name I guess I I got to pick a name hold
on let me ask the voices in my head
what's a good name know your name what's
a good name guys
got are you also part of the Jade sword
Jade sword that's
me and you
are I see I see I don't I
John Watson John you don't look like a
John John Watson John wat my
name wait are all of you
[Music]
oh oh it's not a knife it's called a
scythe a
scythe uh farmer no I think Reaper so
yeah a farmer Farmer of souls maybe swe
Reaper kind swe hey I'm not sweaty cut
it out boy always have really long
fingernails a little swe yeah you're
right you
going
yeah what's
up
look how you do
that it won use again I guess our magic
is only temporary
that was a big sound
wow I think that
was Jonathan Jonathan she's of this
Watson it's a bubble blower something
who are you going to hurt with that a
bubble blower uh I can smack people in
the
head I will defend myself nice that was
a test
he oh what just happened oh my God
I see your name is no my name is my kipy
but you can call me Callie that's the
bone people in in my chat say the Kaya
people yeah that's what they say stay
back though stay back
okay the Jade SW
member and can overcome any challenge
that's true
[Music]
oh this is the
headquarters this is we is
here I'm glad I have you guys on my team
we so
powerful wow are also powerful Jonathan
you Cheng your
friend I don't want to fight
we'll be working with v to repel the
stain and save the
world you ought a familiar familiar eyes
yourself at this Kingdom and learn how
to accept them for four quests okay I
suppose we're all in the same Guild we
all here in
green the
ancors bestowed upon me the Jade
sword
together at the
CH is this yes that's kind of weird why
would they put you
in what am I supposed to do here maybe
they ran out
green I mean red quite Su me I
think I guess if it was green it might
be like a Christmas I don't know if I
want to do
it you look
nice where is this Quest
boy ARA together
[Music]
together yeah do we have like a a place
to rest maybe I think I'd like to go
there
wow I talked to V he said we had to
find Quest
board board maybe it's out here oh
maybe this looks like a main area of
some
[Music]
kind it's a must be around here I wonder
if there's a map somewhere if I could
pull up a
map map I'm going towards the quest
Master where did everybody
go we're to look for the quest board but
I have the map here we could go this way
oh you do all
right
Jonathan else's names speak to your
Guild's
elabe oh
[Music]
Elizabeth the map has shall protect you
you will never leave a GU behind that's
a big sword I will not leave you alone
should we go TOS the quest Master on the
map you only but a few steps away I
don't want to be I want to be by your
okay there's a little bust in here got
it w I can be a shield if you want me to
I wasn't
asking it's I think wait where's
kie oh oh do we find the quest board I
don't know there's a quest Master down
here
no I be a to I I don't have a yet so I
might come to
[Music]
bye all right we're almost there oh
there's so
[Music]
many how do you like to the I don't
know more people I
just what that's
they
[Music]
at my honestly I don't think I was
supposed to find you how you use it of
course never felt special in my entire
life
Master here you must be one of the
heroes and yeah
okay yeah I want to protect the
kingdom that's me a
[Music]
demon I feel Jonathan spoken
to
request main Dy is a the stains but we
can also help the citizens too
right away rapers areed to help
where we going to
go speak to the Guild
Master do you
[Music]
the this here looks like a perfect
job a
complete
side how do
I where is the side
[Music]
we materals needed smiy I'm The
Apprentice there's a bunch of different
quests I've accepted a side quest I the
[Music]
quest you have the same
questy this looks like the perfect job
best of
luck we go to the
[Music]
get think we're on the same Quest okay
it's together then
[Music]
the party I shall invite you to do we
all have a horse within
us everyone is invited to my
[Music]
because it would be a lot less chaotic
if if you press T and then type accept
yeah there's groups there's
groups we start a voice chat group it
says you're in my party yeah we can a
voice group that's
a there she is okay okay okay okay okay
stand
still I shall free you will
yous instead of typing accept you click
on
my how do you click on it oh press T and
then hover over xcept press
[Music]
it as long as we did it right
I we can take
our I want a MAG
be no voice in the
inventory how about making a
group a voice CH group oh voice chat
group get
I we all have hes oh my
gosh I want a white horse oh my goodness
w wow wow w
w what if I don't want a
horse how do we get off
the that's a great question shift shift
how does one
we go this
way I think we're going to use our horse
to get there
faster idea let us
r Wait for
everyone I like
my she Chang color
now a color changing Steam
I don't know if it's okay to ride over
the C
best do do I not need to accept a Quest
from the board or is it that we are I
wonder because we all accepted the quest
but does that mean maybe you should go
ahead and accept the quest just in case
yeah if you do the the right CLI on the
board it should come up if not you
haven't finished talking to the quest
masteral
I'm in a
party
at says we're running low on ra
materials
okay okay ah Quest
accepted let's go to the Smithy then
right where
is's the one with the map it's not
me yeah the map doesn't so
much the one with the map well we shall
Venture forth and see
John
[Music]
wat John Watson John Watson maybe John
Watson's already at the Smithy oh maybe
they vot
[Music]
ahead find a
map
here sorry you guys disappeared you went
so fast
put is this a
Smithy hello little guy I may look scary
but I'm chill oh wow you saw the
quest 10 oak logs okay
okay Oaks sure oh we got 100 coins just
for talking
to that's kind of easyest cash I am
yeah I'm sorry s do not worry about the
horse that just appeared in your
face what's
this my whoa what does that do you
cannot use the enchantment table right
now want to talk to me but I want to use
it I'll wait outside this place is
getting busy
hello Jonathan let's GL up the trees
Jonathan are going to be good friends
then all right shall we go to the flo I
think the gate is that way right have to
go to
the it
ends what go to another location
yes oh yes oh oh
yes there things watch out watch out oh
my
gosh is this correct oh
gosh I like the way they they
cry I killing
get rid of the
St the
stains yeah get get some
exp
right I gu need o
right come back you I think
[Music]
hey T
my good
yeah maybe I should focus on the
logs
oh wow you're doing a good
job uh Fair Maiden maybe uh using a
sword for a tree might not work uh yes
I'm a newbie here I'm still figuring it
out sword is
good well you're very very brave to use
a sword on a tree these trees seem to
grow back very fast Fair they
do Tre where are the
logs I don't know where the logs are are
get
logs oh
[Music]
go take that oh go
did I hit him with
the thank
you thank you kind sir ma'am I should
probably not use
the I will take some one
[Music]
do you think the a little bit
desate you know
what I'll save
[Music]
you is it
yeah I've got eight I've got 10 already
do I have all the what I need this so
many
speeds how I get the logs I only have
five logs how do I know how many logs I
have
why oh my goodness I have I need one
more it's not I made a mistake is not
we' thank you he's not dead I'm just
going to make him dead run away run away
I still need
them there's too many St
[Music]
oh my gosh I need
you why are you crying like
that
B I got the right here we
go
in I need one
more Oak clocks Oak clocks I can't tell
the truth apart
destroy got I
got got
the all right I have well I I have 10 I
have
let's go finish this
Quest
yes
wonderful it's over here this
wait at the
map how to say
[Music]
who
swords
yeah you're not wa you brought the
ls I can't talk to him
H complete the side quest and then speak
to the quest master I'm sorry about the
why won't you let me talk to him
to you brought the logs your master you
bring the raw materials to him you can
make all
tools you can craft logs into planks and
planks into sticks from your inv logs in
hand a sticks seem
useful like
a
pickaxe a wooden
shovel you need certain things like 20
coins three Oak planks and two
sticks do I
do
um maybe I can make the sticks myself
now
sticks we can craft them from inventory
Oak planks I can make somebody else just
I thought we were supposed to make
sticks all
right what are we supposed to did it
work you bring over 10 oak logs there's
a bunch of trees not far outside the
town that you can
chop all right I figured out how you
make a
stick well I have a crafting table if we
would really oh that might work too but
you can also do it in your inventory
yeah make planks first and then sticks
planks then sticks oh I made a pickaxe I
made a and a shovel two four planks I
made four planks two planks makes a
stick wow so they wanted us to make
the you got to make it in your inventory
and then give him the materials do he
want do he want the planks oh butt and
stick and stick you can make sticks in
your inventory by using two planks yeah
just stack them on top of each other
like one on top one on the
bottom I don't think I can fight again
until I have something to eat though
definitely eat
something sticks they're very excited
about making sticks oh wait well
they puppies I got a stick
how many sticks is he asking for a m of
Jade sword after all so I'm what does he
want my inventory is very full now oh
you got to get the pickax you talk to
this guy
want oh I gave you the
pickax pickaxe I need it you just gave
it to me like that oh I purchased it am
I doing this
correctly be
what do I
want thex did I buy I bought
one oh no want to okay I also bought
[Music]
one think
scam you got scam I'm
[Music]
confused do you have a pickaxe in your
inventory I have a pickax but when I
talk to this this fellow here he does
not speak to me oh I
um talk to the quest
Master Okay says leave
town yes the humans buy things with
[Music]
money I a fact our
Quest
well maybe I have to turn the quest then
do we go back
then oh yeah to get the coins huh have
we done the the side quest and speak to
the quest
master I need to get
[Music]
another I think I have to go get more
o I'll be back okay picka
it
completed does anybody have any more oak
logs especially if you need
coins everybody have their pickaxe the
was completed I see and then I'm I'm so
[Music]
confused drop them C you have to
trade yeah make sure you tra with the I
sent trade request okay trade I thought
we have to buy from him we have to trade
too yeah both you your coin you have
enough
them every time
buy You are conducting it must I might
have to the violence
against why you must do it
okay I have low confidence and check the
but maybe we need to do another Quest
I'm not
sure thank
you we did your
quest did I do it right job off you go
okay I think we also need to collect
Cobblestone now I I don't know if I
finished
it oh no I think I think it's okay
[Music]
oh there
was I think I didn't finish
it I don't
think to
purchase collect 10 o speak to the just
create a wooden pickaxe
at I I see
[Music]
I don't know what's
wrong Elizabeth did you finish the
quest I have traded oh
hello I'm not too certain I I'm supposed
to get cobblestone
now
Master this
is we have to go all the way back then
M follow me
m the quest
Master Quest
Master okay okay okay okay he gives me a
new quest ah this is the quest
Master okay I think
so I think so
okay I think so I don't
know did I do it
there's no other
one huh why is why is he saying I didn't
do
it planks pickax pickax wait huhuh
pickax trade box this is not
right
[Music]
what a trade box they disappeared yeah
wait where's the 10 Oak LS I have a
trade box I have the
pickaxe I had one but then it didn't
work what is
it I don't know if I trade worked out I
I haven't finished the quest yet okay we
got to get cobblestone to finish the
quest follow follow I I don't I talk to
the follow me oh okay
The
Voice he's asking if I could bring 10
Oak wogs and when I check my inventory I
do not have them come here all right
wait wait so what do we need I have a
trade
[Music]
box all right uh talk to my m i
more I already got a wooden pickaxe wood
suit your best here going use St and a
bit of coin to show my I'm a rich open
the trade box right I've been trying to
do that a we can craft
stuff I no longer I don't have enough
coins oh oh oh oh my goodness I have to
do it like that
[Music]
huh I rich I am no longer Rich all right
I have 21 coin course do they want
see
I open the trade Bo I did it I think oh
oh
gosh I'm
sorry why am I
[Music]
sorry can't open the train is my mic
hi
hello do you know how to open the trade
box
who are
you I open it I think they're
busy oh a new face is here hello can you
guys hear
me thank God I talked to the quest
Master talk to the
blacksmith I thought it was talk to the
quest
Master guys the quest isn't done yet the
Smith if you have a pickax I think it's
fine we'll just go get
cobblestone I have I have the oak
logs
what oh so with the oak logs then you
make Oak
planks I have Oak
planks buy from him I I bought the oak
picka the wooden
pick Master you should be able to make
you stone tools give it a try
yeah to
him Cobblestone and
St the blacksmith's
Apprentice okay now I can talk to him I
see
[Music]
now
okay now it's completed master craft the
wooden
pickaxe okay so I don't want to talk to
him
then
okay how do I make the wooden
[Music]
pickaxe you must use your Oak
planks I bought I bought a wooden pickax
thece again if you bought one then you
have to mine the
Cobblestone talk to thece he hasn't told
me this
yet I see
figured it
out nice thank you bon okay why was I
supposed to talk to the blacksmith
then is more
important yeah let's see your pickaxe
let me see that
thing
not are we going to go
somewhere can hardly tell the difference
unless the horse's name is pickax we're
not leaving until we see your
pickaxe until you show us your pickax
young all right we're ready
[Music]
let's
boy hey easy enough is this you got to
Beware of the enemies though because I
haven't had a meal in a long time okay
I'll protect you seems like it isn't
working oh that stuff can't be broken I
here away with me
okay it
doesn't go go are you
okay just climb up here that can we get
get get
get
okay
[Music]
I'll need
bedtime that was my last bre cry
Jonathan it is cry think of it that way
it is trying to attack
[Music]
us I got all the
cobone maybe I should get extra just in
caseb
Rob I should be careful a little bit
[Music]
huh
okay oh nice all right let's go turn in
our Quest right okay I don't want to
hurt
myself
okay maybe maybe a song that you heard a
long time ago oh all the enemies are
really ganging up on us I'm going to
go it's too dangerous though it's way
too
dangerous we got theone though
[Music]
didn't horse oh I got the pretty horse
she seems to really like
I don't have enough sticks oh do you
have yeah do you have money and
sticks how much money do I need
50 okay do you have sticks okay
complet I think we completed the quest
okay I want maybe we can go back to the
quest board now
[Music]
I'm going to go outside and
make wait
watch oh my go
[Music]
three what what
we you seem to want to have a fight with
everyone you come across
okay do I look like
this look a little silly thus far we
have known each other you have always
seemed
cool did you guys turn in your
quest not Quest we have to go to the
quest board still okay you talk to The
Apprentice right yeah we did cool then I
guess let's go I'm sorry
oh my voice is stuck oh what's he doing
yes
yes pretty good about about how fast
we've been
going so you've gone and finished the
quest
[Music]
okay F I need some food yeah some food I
could go for a b
[Music]
shop here's a bit of a coin to get you
started oh cool 500 coins we're
rich I can retire now on
this there's more quests on the board do
we want to take another
Quest is there another
quester
weach the shopkeeper okay yeah that's
true maybe we should do that first oh
okay wait where is
she
go red
[Music]
one
Elizabeth you trying to
get oh yes I I yes it's over
here that's great I'm so happy for you
three honestly
your
is know sili
buter for
what find out yeah we speedrun all of
this I bet maybe we could go to a
dungeon
you yeah I want to fight in a dungeon
with you guys and see how good you are
yeah
you pick up another
[Music]
Quest it
it I was going to pick it up after
visiting the shop
yeah why don't we pick up the quest
right now since Elizabeth has it and
then we can go visit the shopkeeper
something I'm a little confused because
it just gave me the option of getting
another the quest unless oh the quest
Master why do you have a raw pork
chop because I killed a pig I'm so proud
of you go talk to the quest leader
[Music]
now are we
waiting
hello hello hello there
fuzzy that's
smaron we go find the
shopkeeper this map is not
helpful oh please don't do that
c not K the
K leave my friends alone
off theing
[Music]
oh away from
my excuse me
excuse talking to my number
theer that's too many
[Music]
people oh gosh this isn't the time for
that instant
[Music]
health I feel like I should buy that but
I'm not going to
why is it
so is kind of
scary are not
very positive people right now are
they what happens over here like
I can use their facilities here you know
the
Sten yeah dang we should have slain some
meat it's good know that we can hop over
and use
that disg yes Amber is disgusting
nothing in
there kind
[Music]
of I like
the everybody's
very very s
looks like there's just a barid selling
potions yeah that's it
right do open some steak what's this
what's this here is this also a shop
looks like we can't enter from the back
door maybe that's illegal can we enter
in the horse oh my God
horse I
want a little sh
what you want to buy make
sense I did it should I go in
here should I go
in I can't go in h why is there a door
then
huh where did everybody go
oh children are to the gardens are they
okay to work like that where did
everybody
[Music]
GOP oh this is the
shopkeeper of a okay just talk and I'll
show you what's in
[Music]
stock why not visit we have money
okay the children tending to
them as yeah things will be hard on my
body and
heart to him
okay visit the Guild Hall of the
four I
want the
ARA when you're tired from avening or
simply looking for a little diversion
okay wa instant Health there is
telling me about all the different
places to go
visit children all the children are Char
of the
gardens
okays I bought speak to thees children
in the gardens got it I'm going to go
hunt and get us all some
food yeah yeah yeah let's go hunting
together shall we I saw a bunch of
themer is right here wonder if we have a
chest that we can store I
found tried to steal oh oh that's
probably not a good idea don't I'm not
[Music]
sure where did joh
go probably continuing the
[Music]
quest we want to go to
child I mean do you think there'll be
food
there maybe there will be food there Wow
Let's go to the Gard small my I have a
small horse
oh I think it's a normal size Horse
let's go to the
gardens wish I had a map to know where
they are Watson was the
maper
map looking at
it I have a map but I don't know how to
read it
I have to pull it out let me oh thank
you for saving this town welcome to my
humble little
shop what can we get what can we get all
right all right just
[Music]
give why are they making them work in
the
Gard what theck wait why do we have to
talk to a kid I just want the goods oh
so for the child so far
I I don't like
this I see it on the map
[Music]
now I need to go this
way
[Music]
follow here's the C found the
best child oh there you are they have
any
here what what the heck
is I
think goly you're one of the heroes boy
this must be my lucky
Dad to come them whenever you like use
them for what oh the
child keep an eye on scway birds and
stuff let me know you're one of the her
my lucky
day you're free to come
herewhere
building you Heroes can build whatever
you like can to build a
right know's a place called The Pit the
M but I can play really fun game there
you hear I'm been that you in maybe you
can check it on tell me when it's play
hope to see you
again P the P I got a bunch of
fun is so far
away just give you a bunch of
bread okay did did anybody else just get
a bunch of bread
[Music]
wow that's a lot of breading to you did
the child get anyone else bread no I
didn't get any bread I
would where's my bread
huho threatening violent
Stu why did you hit this you hit this
child and got bread I think they did no
I didn't do anything like the kid gave
me the bread their own free will that's
a lot of
bre going to eat all look look
[Music]
look give you head what are you
doing
best is that
[Music]
easy what are you doing are you
destroying the bushes I thought we were
making a Sal yeah it Mak so
s really
okay that's a
bush I got some berries
[Laughter]
scavengers yeah Violet on the bushes
Maybe
myouou harou
[Music]
they gave us the bread so that we can
get H
[Music]
theou bushes are
violent yeah we all got to be on our
guard I'm going to die from the
bushes are you guys being called Away by
something that sounds kind of
familiar I
do you want to try and go to the pit
let's go to the pit
yeah the child the child can't go there
okay
on I don't know where we're going I
think theit is the the Amber coin area
it shows on the map it says pit doorman
does it that's a funny name
follow
me are you
following I'm
following a wrong
way this way wrong way this
way is Callie
following I think you
are well this is the
pit like a wow Amber
que here we
[Music]
are
wow is it
for luy lady lucky lady I've got the
game for
you I
new one of new face yeah a new
face I this guy be able to make
for I
think nothing Shady nothing Shady get
be can
buy can't understand what he saying but
it's okay Point yourself at your mate
and right click on
it yeah
some stain they also taught us how to
work as a
team exit for
me we can eventually together swap items
and
coins see you thought it was useful
didn't I you'll thank me for it when
you're
adventuring be a lot easier if
you master wishes to speak to
us again come down here to the pit and
play around
the
master out your Penn don't worry about
it is this are they asking us to do
something
Shady maybe we're going to do like
underground fight
town I don't know gu Master wishes to
speak with you please meet him at let's
run over to the DAT like Master that's
where we're from
right let's head over over early maybe
what the Jade sword guil master I don't
know if that's him
verus that
yeah I went the wrong
way it's over this way oh and then I
can't well I can go around this maybe oh
maybe not that's the water Elizabeth you
said you by forever
[Music]
where's
more going back to
the I don't know where I'm going are you
sure you do uh
okay did I get lost I don't know are we
going back to the same
place here no not here I found
it here here there we go no this is
I did it I'm lost I'm
lost we all met what is before the last
be out Outsider
Kingdom the Calamity and the stains it
has born have turned most of the world
into a wasteland you must be shaken to
suddenly find yourselves in another
world but I pray you at us in our fight
see you anymore our first priority is
finding a way for you to regain your
powers of Revelation yeah the mysterious
powers to that end I have just received
word from one of our Scouts regarding a
possible
[Music]
lead while investigating the C near the
PLS our comrad stand Upon A mysterious
ancient
R man I'm blushing oh gosh I they
observed from a ruin of light AK to that
of Revelation which
used skels from ailda already stationed
at the ruins further investigation okay
I asked that you might join them there
and let them your a go
[Music]
for speak to the J
Master exit the Town Gate head to the pl
speak
to I just received from one
of investigating theity down
wait I found ruin I found
[Music]
is right here SC from already station
investigation I asked that you might
join
join forth with Valor no problem cool I
head of the PLS and speak to H of the
Jade
sword
next sh find another yes yes I am sh
yes it seems like Callie don't
want that probably more Coco and I need
to head off here oh you guys are going
away on a different Journey huh a little
bit of a different Journey but we'll be
back soon okay we'll see you again well
let's adventure together when you guys
come back
yeah it was fun getting to know you both
today let's do our best is J
sword sword stronges
[Music]