[Music]
hello everybody
hi can you hear me can you hear me can
you hear me
hello
kiko masuka
you can you're reacting like you can
hear me hello oh hey oh hey not funny
seeing you here huh funny seeing me here
huh happy birthday girl thank you
that's right today is my birthday my
nine thousand bajillionth birthday wow
you guys thank you
happy birthday goomba thank you happy
birthday
can't hear you
are you lying to me okay no how would
you be lying to me because
well thank
[Music]
i wish we could change the color imagine
if we could change that to a sea of blue
instead of a sea of green it would be a
lot oh well more aesthetically pleasing
uh for me but i guess maybe not for
everybody i'm sure fauna really likes it
when it's green instead of blue but i
don't know final fantasy
[Music]
dude
um
i'm nervous again but what is new uh you
thought that was over but it's not i'm
still incredibly nervous sitting here in
my fish tube actually i was thinking
about it um me and this fish tube that
i'm right here and you know what if it's
actually like just a very large
intestine of a much larger fish
that could potentially that could
potentially be what the situation is
what if we all are just in the large
intestine of a much larger fish
on the earth like a meatball never mind
we don't have to talk about this anyway
thank you guys so much thank you
thank you thank you i've been watching
all of your uh birthday fan arts coming
in you guys thank you uh so much i
really appreciate
uh what everybody's been sending in i
saw the bus the good bus has been the
goomba bus did you guys ride in the
goomba bus
did you get to sit inside the gargura
bus
fill it with
gas
anyway it's really good to see what you
guys are saying because there's just so
much
which i appreciate but um
anyway i'm keeping you though okay you
can hear me we busting we are buzzing
we're officially do you think
we could well never mind that's good
nevermind we don't have to go that route
um
what there's a guru bus there's a girl
bus and i saw videos there's a bunch of
videos you guys some animations as well
um i want to say thank you for making me
feel uh so special on my very special
day
very very special day
what
is the mic okay
the mic is it peeking
wow
hello what is wrong with the mic
can you
mike is acting funny oh great um well as
you guys probably know
well
it sits down i'm a little out of my
element at the moment so i would
appreciate
mike is peeking
i see
i see what you mean why is he doing that
i don't know why he's doing it
ah i'll try not to
overwhelm the microphone i will speak
soft er
okay so um
i hope you guys like the streams
yesterday
they were a lot of fun um
yeah that was a lot of fun actually
it's still kind of sinking in what
happened oh so
oh i'm ah
robot girl what do you mean robot girl
did you like them
yeah the karaoke was a lot of fun i
don't know how much i should say about
it though of course i'm like absolutely
uh filled to the boy with stuff that i
want to talk about wow oh
i'm a i'm united
uh
by
yeah she made me she made me a little
cake and she decorated it with white
chocolate and she made little like sea
creatures and she stuck it to the cake
um and the cake had had coffee in it so
after i ate it i got really energized
because there was like espresso in it
and um it really helped i don't know
helped me to stay awake so i could see
everything that you guys were sending me
on twitter with the hashtag the birthday
hashtag
um what else do we do oh she made me
dinner
yeah she made me she made me dinner she
made me
uh
this is steak and rice and and
broccoli fancy broccoli fancy broccoli
but i eat really slow oh i was kind of
self-conscious about that but um
it's okay she eats slow too she's not
gonna tell you that but she's pretty
slow too all right
all right and watson eats her rice with
soy sauce did you know that i prefer my
rice plain
uh just hot steam rice plain nothing on
it um but watson likes to get her rice
with soy sauce
this little thing did you know that
um
a slow eating competition well i was
anxious um but also i do eat slowly it's
not a bad thing is it do you guys eat
fast or slow
wait what am i doing nevermind i'm
talking to myself soy sauce is pretty
good it is good but the problem when you
put soy sauce on rice is that it makes
it unsticky so then you can't eat it
very easily so you have to do like a
spoon and or a straw or something
whatever you choose
sweet or salty soy sauce i don't know
it's just soy sauce
maybe it's just soy sauce if you guys
eat basil don't you get like i don't
know
indigestion or something
anyway though i'll talk a bit more about
the hanging out with watson later um but
first i
as being my birthday in gura birthday
tradition i have a gift for you
guys a gift for all of you
um
you might guess what it is but uh anyway
um so for all of you uh
prepared a little something with the
help of a very very very very very uh
awesome
uh
artist that i i really i look up to a
lot
um is it more streams yes
um but yes but no but yes but not right
now
um so i have for you
[Music]
oh dear
new emotes
and say the cool thing about this is uh
all of my do you see the shrimp emotes
we have every emotes now
we have now forever what is it
immortalized
ebby's
in the emote list
let's take a look these are by mariette
mariette we have what do we have here
a girl with a pen like that looks like a
gun that's actually i specifically asked
i said can you make girl look like uh
can you make me look like i'm holding a
gun but instead of a gun it's a it's a
pen light uh and then we have a new and
then we have celebration and then we
have comfy guru and then we have guru is
dead and then we have guru is crying
happy and then we have girl girl is
smiling at you very smug and then we
have squish the chico girl and then we
all go scared and then we have guru chad
and now we have a girl going
and then we have my face because you
guys are always looking at me funny and
then we have girl ha ha and then we have
a girl of eyeball and then we have ebby
ebitda
you guys are holding pen lights you guys
are looking at me like i probably just
said something really awful and i don't
realize it um and then you crying and
then your little face is like that when
you say something stupid and don't
realize it and i call you out see
yeah okay you should be able to use them
now okay use them now
there they are nice
excellent
look at all these gourd cheds kakagura
chats
wow what excellent jaw lines you guys
have
wow
nice jawbones guys
ebby looks like patrick like patrick
starr
i'd be cute
i'd be telling you you guys really like
i guess that's not good chat anymore i
guess it's not good chad when you're
here
good attend
good chad
oh they're so cute this is the same
artist that drew mume as well as bonus
emotes and i really really like uh both
of their emotes i use them a lot uh in
the discord especially i'm always using
uh fauna zoom uh fauna not like days and
clover and i'm amazed the loading face i
always use that one so i'm really
excited to be able to get marriott to
help me out with these new emails thank
you mariette if you're watching
thank you
thank you thank you
okay
um
so
this
this year i wanted to do something a
little bit different
uh than what where
i guess what i'm used to doing for
birthdays or i mean i only have one
birthday but i wanted to change it up a
little bit this this year you can't find
abby every time don't go
maybe there's a uh issue with every
every time every child is coming i was
wondering why i couldn't see every
anywhere
i'm sure abby is coming i'm sure manager
is helping right now to make sure ebby's
working no worries i'd be coming
maybe also refresh your page i might be
up but anyway i want to talk about
something that's gonna happen um i
wanted to do some stuff a little bit
differently this year
but i still hope that you guys uh will
like it
um
it took a lot of creative minds and and
patience and and and uh
a lot of helping hands to make this this
uh this year's birthday uh turn into
something
i think is really great and i'm really
excited for and i bro but i'm saying so
much um
so
so so how old am i now oh god how many
times have i answered this question
so many so many times please know that
that's right there's merchandise
merchandise releases today are you
excited i'm really excited
i
i showed one of the other myth members
the merchandise and
she really liked it so i hope you guys
really like it as well
um
okay
anyway
let's go
uh i didn't think of how to segue this
at all whatsoever can you tell them i'm
nervous
where's the shrimp emote i don't know it
should be coming anytime though
uh i need to hold i need to gather my
thoughts i'm really shaking right now um
the personality test that i took said
that i do really well under pressure and
i think i do okay under pressure but
maybe not
productively well i just keep my cool
sort of i think i keep my cool mic is
funky it'll fix in a second it's just
suffering right now but anyway
i wanna sing some songs for you
i wanna i wanna sing some music that's
that i know how to do that i'll do that
for you guys because that'll help
calm me down and stuff
oh it looks so good
i look it
evie
[Music]
hello everyone
cute
i look so good
okay
so yeah i wanna i wanna sing for you
today because that's what i
uh i like to do um
it is an activity like we that we both
like sharing in right here guys
uh so
but we're gonna switch it up
and
um i hope you help help we have a good
time today okay
get ready to shake those pen lights
um
[Music]
close your eyes everybody
close them but don't close them okay
close them now close
so much blue it makes my heart so happy
i love the color blue did you know that
okay
anyway look at the big aquarium wow this
is fishy fishy and look at the floor
it's water
water
splishy splash
and look at me
that's right i'm here too look at me i'm
here
you're here
we're here
to
party
[Music]
but first
i just want to say a big thank you to
you guys
to everybody thank you thank you for
supporting shark and believing in shark
just
sharky
little sharky
all of those for little sharky that's so
crazy thank you guys so much
ah
we also recently hit four baboon
subscribers which is
insanity um also i did some math um
right yeah i know you're doing math look
out but roughly there are 15 shrimp to
one pound so that technically means that
with four million shrimp
something
something is there's a big there's a big
shrimp lurking on the horizon is what
i'm trying to say and he's made up of
millions four million little tiny nano
shrimpies that's all of you you are
building the giga shrimp so we must be
we must be wary and look out for this
very large specimen um you can do the
exact math though uh
because i actually don't know how big
this giggle shrimp is um
uh i think i'm gonna stop myself here
though um but anyways uh
okay
we all know that i cannot do math
but i propose a counter offer
huh
you do the math
i'll do the same
i sing for you
i was okay
um
wow i better start before i get too
awkward okay um
[Music]
oh
for me
[Music]
keep me
you
oh yes
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
will forever be one of my favorite
musical artists
seriously i can always find a way to
recommend people to listen to his music
i don't know what to stream
oh that sucks hey you've heard this
banger before send a link send the link
link link link
i mean i've already told you guys about
how much i enjoy thoughts
does music so
so you guys already know
actually lately my summer playlist has
consisted of
my star various albums uh and then
jeremy's soul as well
i have like two modes right now
it's either
nostalgia for a 1980 summer or or
somewhere in the skyrim tavern looking
to pickpocket
do you guys smell that
do you smell that it smells like
no wait
nom nom i can taste it too
it tastes like herbs and spices
huh
[Music]
like
um
[Music]
is
hallelujah
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh guys
something feels
spooky
guys
[Music]
oh my god
foreign
[Music]
my face
from
[Music]
me
good to see you
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
it
me
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
goodbye
foreign
[Music]
a
foreign
[Music]
me
fish brain
[Music]
to you
oh love with you
[Music]
i will give you all my love
in love with you
[Music]
oh
love with you
[Music]
little trees
you're oh she's waiting in the closet
tonight no way to stop she's dead set on
giving you a fry trick or treat but now
we're all out of candy feeling just a
little sick this jeans that ought to
come in handy
i got a fairy just possessed so let's
spare them
a little bit section of space drop it
low babies hiding behind your screen so
they use spooky halloween without some
mythical
[Music]
i'll fix that
oh
[Music]
not your wife i am a pumpkin
[Applause]
[Music]
that is what we're about
ah
i love singing with the other members of
me
hope you guys liked it too
i really really appreciate everybody's
hard work to make today happen
it's a really nice feeling knowing that
i can rely on my friends
and other super creative people to make
such fun experiences happen for all of
you
i'm so very grateful so
thank you thank you everybody and also
to each of you thank you for your
patience
and your incredible support
another year of shark
i'm so lucky to be surrounded by such
dedicated folks like you
thank you everybody
thank you
now
more fun stuff
birthday stuff
merchandise baby merchandise
give me the good shark give me the goods
i know i know i know i'm so excited
about this year's merch
i seriously love it so much i've been
looking at pictures of it every day
leading up to this exact moment hoping
all of you will be just as excited as i
am
drum roll
[Music]
oh
on sale
pretty soon i don't know exactly when
whatever anyways cute
cute cute
first let's start with adorable art by
bonza
yay
featuring
ebitda
and
hydrangea my favorite summer flower
because it's all blue and there's water
and i'm so cute with my little sailor
outfit and they're so cute i'm so cute i
mentioned how cute i'm so
cute i love this art
so much
and the good thing is is that it's
available as a postcard limited complete
sets will include a hand signed
signature
by me
it's grippy perfect for high octane
activities
like
like gundam building
and
bonus points because it's cute
it's cute i wonder if you can do other
things on it like
i don't know
gaming maybe i don't know just don't get
it dirty well
you can get dirty if you want i mean
it's all right it's cute
okay
next up
i don't think you guys are ready for
this
okay
i know
[Music]
little round yellow toes and scales and
an embroidered ebby on the tushy
designed by none other than sammy
no
dino guru is real dino you can own a
dino gura
dino guba can now
peacefully live
in your home
just for you
and you can pull the hood down and
reveal my twin tails
i'm squishy it's punchable
it's puntable
and i might have cried when i first saw
the plushie designs because my uncle is
such a god at creating cute things
designing anything and everything that's
cute so my uncle is
number one
i hope you will give dino gura a good
home
also while i'm here can uh somebody make
the luigi centrifuge meme video but it's
like dino goober instead that would be
funny
oh maybe i'll do it i can do it
instead
[Music]
it'll be me but i'll be doing
something else
we're not done yet
then we have
to
i am
absolutely dead serious when i say that
kitchenware is my weakness uh also
designed by my uncle the gooba
at the very bottom of the bowl ensuring
that no crumbs are left behind
do you see how cute this bowl
is look at it
[Music]
i love kitchen i love kitchenware i love
kitchenware kitchenware daisuki
in fact i want more i need a myth like a
myth dinnerware set any bowls any plates
any cups we have cups well now i need
the rest of it we need bowls
more bowls i say give me more bowls
please
i won't even use them i will just i just
want to look at them
just let me look at them
oh my god
well there's there's more there's more
guys
to go alongside your very own gargura
bowl
yeah
trident fork
trident chopsticks i repeat trident fork
trident chopsticks it's blue well
turquoise blue
turquoisey blue
i've i've talked to you guys about how
much i wanted to make
a trident fork
okay i wanted it to be glowing this one
doesn't glow but still
look at it
trident cutlery said holy moly mother
lode
trident fork and chopsticks set
designed by yours truly that's right i
decided because we talked about it
remember you guys
uh yeah not quite as powerful as my own
trident but definitely strong enough to
lift your favorite meal into your mouth
lift your favorite meal out of the gooba
bowl and into your mouth
hey
okay
and lastly
a voice pack
featuring some notification sounds that
you can use in whichever device you wish
to girlfy your pc your phone your ipads
your your idevices can i say ipad on
stream i just said ipad any device that
you would like my voice coming out of
that accepts audio
thing
ah now
okay i will say that there are more
things in the oven currently
but they need a bit more time
just a bit
uh and i hope i hope you look forward to
what i'm cooking up
thank you guys for coming to my birthday
party this year
i hope you had a nice time
i hope you like the goods i hope you
like the songs thank you miss for
singing with me and for
uh hanging out with me on my birthday
um i'm very lucky to be surrounded by
such a talented group of group of ladies
and i appreciate and uh uh cherish
every moment that we've been able to
spend together on this this hollow life
journey thank you guys same to you guys
as well watching this journey let's see
where we go next right
now
it is time for me to go
but i'll see you again real soon okay
okey dokey everybody
bye bye everybody
bye bye bye bye
bye
bye bye bye
bye bye
you