oh
[Music]
no it was completely by accident i was
trying i was struggling for them
i was struggling to unmute it
no problem
i generally always feel so bad about
when i do collabs about doing my
kikiriki because it's like it's a
morning car right so it should be filled
with energy but
like i can't just be here like
right please do please do no worries
honestly i need a little like morning
cock-a-doodle-doo you know
to wake me up because right now i'm
feeling it and i have no caffeine in the
house whoo
morning sunshine good morning ladies
oh my god good morning ladies how are
you
[Music]
well it's like it shouldn't it shouldn't
be like that in the world
it shouldn't it was good for a minute
and then it was good for a minute hold
on i'll just leave it like that it's a
stylistic choice yeah
the ghosts are messing with us
right now that's symbolism
declining mental states all right i'm
gonna change it to 720p instead of 180.
oh that's better okay cool oh yeah
it's struggling to put it
yeah
you're looking very good
720p yeah
you go oh there she go oh huh then she
go oh
um is that okay are you cool with that
i think i i think i am what color did
you use green and it didn't mess with
your feathers so
really
green is it can you tell me like it's
just
i gotta go back to the loading screen
two seconds
it looks fine on my stream but i want it
to look good on yours so um
it's the default body
i'm not even gonna
i'm gonna stay on the screen but hide
our bodies maybe let's see
the body
the body hide the body
my brain is just really slow right now
so okay i feel that green
i'm surprised you say that works
yeah it's just the default oh
just the default i mean
even my do even my my feathers will cook
you yeah on my side as well one second
okay first friends what's happening um
they're trying to they're trying to do
some stuff and some stuff crow maki yeah
uh well
what you know what you know what that's
okay that looks okay that looks good i
think yeah
i'm gonna stream it with the girls
okay
my sweet sweet discord john thank you
for watching you guys alone what would
we do without you that's all right you
don't need to leave us alone just bring
that sentiment right into the game with
you
i have to say though my internet is also
not really the bestest you know european
internet is [\h__\h] so ah
how does it look like girls
oh i haven't seen it looks good i think
really for now
this chord likes to lie to us um
uh uh oh
oh
someday we're all going to be able to
get to the same room i'm telling you
this isn't that bad really
it's okay
everything's fine
is this worse and when cali streamed it
um we're not even moving over yeah you
you guys are not moving on my side now
by the way
kelly are they moving on your side yeah
hello what what yeah
well maybe because i'm streaming
no you have to have the you have to have
their window open
at all times see here this is the stuff
that we can't actually check before the
stream for it's stuff that happens
literally during this stream
there's something stuck in my eye
hold on
loaded it was working fine
and then we started streaming
don't move for me when i stream to
them um now it's just black to me
also callie stopped moving for me too
uh oh
nelly okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
well we found there are ghosts
where is
[Music]
sorry are we okay now guys
no well we're gonna have to work we're
fine okay
the final week
i think it was badly when cali streamed
it because i
apparently like it's [\h__\h] and i also
don't get i don't need to move anymore
okay leave it to me
try kelly one more time leave it to me i
got this boy
yes
one second
here we go live
frame rate is 30.
now go
we've got done we're just gonna
roll with this
because i want to go get some ghosts
i don't like cash
no
it's time for spooky it's almost
halloween anyway thanks for coming to
our stream and now we end it just
kidding
just kidding we're gonna play the game
now oh no can you do me one favor
um yes
can you end your stream once and open it
again
yes
before you
okay okay
okay is everyone ready to see the 144p
yo it's okay it just symbolizes the
ghosts you know when ghosts around
technology doesn't work
yeah that's true
yes
break
technology it does be like that
they don't want us to hunt them yeah
obviously
okay thank you thank you from the bottom
of my cocoa
anytime anything you need this is a nice
year
yeah i have an ear right in my face
you haven't eaten you know whose it is
though who's here
oh very highly orange
hi oh baby
looking good i'm inside of your head now
inside of your mouth oh here wanna see
it again
check out these moves i can do
what you got
now i think the scariest out of all of
us today is bae
like the the one that who's the most
scared
i don't like ghosts i don't
deal with ghosts okay they're ghosts
they're in another dimension
i like to live
uh the the rat life in this dimension
okay it's scary
can you tell me how you're dealing with
scary games that this finger you told me
before the stream
oh obs oh
tell him
i don't look at the game screen when i
play scary games i play the game by
looking at the small obs screen that's
kind of smart though
when it gets real scary in resident evil
in the basement sometimes i've been
known to look at obs
i don't know what job we should do we
only have two jobs i'm really surprised
that i'm not the the biggest chicken in
the room and it's bad
stuff that i can't handle
oh
yeah
look at this
yeah we're all not very good at it but
we're going to try our best here are our
options guys yeah that's great it feels
like you're going to buy something
yo
i have 62.00
[Music]
i'll go first hello my name is serious
fauna i am the hollow council's keeper
of nature
and i am extremely good at all horror
games i have never been scared in my
life
and i'm going to find all the ghosts
thank you very much wow confidence
very inspiring please thank you thank
you for anything
i love it i can't i can't get no
are you okay
okay
um what's up everybody it's buzz hey
guys representing
chaos room council what's up hop doing
good um
we we stolen i'm gonna stall for as long
as i can okay
we're gonna catch no ghost today um what
huh you don't need to stall
i'm scared well why did you invite why
did you invite us to play this game then
bae because i know you guys liked the
game wait you invited me
from cali's side no bae invited me to
play uh phasma
she said who would want to play and i
said kiara i'm like okay that's the team
then
i know it's because you like the game in
florida likes
who do you mean with you with the first
you who did you mean callie
yeah
i've played it a couple times
i think it's fun i've played it a couple
times in the past
it's it's spooky
excuses
good hallows hallows hallows weeny game
i would say what's up you're saying
right now you sacrifice yourself so we
can use you today as a sacrifice for the
ghost like a testing object okay cool
whenever we need to you know see if the
ghost is going to attack we're just
going to leave you in the room stay in
the truck
that's okay with you right
[Music]
[Laughter]
you need to
need to haze the haze the
that's how i'm gonna be this week when i
play [\h__\h] outlast oh that's right
that's a fun game yeah that's
a step up from phantom phobia you'll
have a blast so i'm so not looking
forward to it it's the worst thing
that's happening to me this whole year
yes
it's pretty rough
i too screamed a couple times playing
that game
yeah who's next
tiara you want to take it away
of course um hello my name is
takanashikiana from whole life english
and i have set the game's voice
recognition to german on my side so i
will be talking to the ghost and yelling
at the ghost in german today thank you
very much give him a little lesson
a little german lesson yeah
[Music]
yeah
all right
i love that oh man um
last and also least my name is maura
callipe i'm the crew
for it's okay you know it's all right
you can just let it happen i'm the first
apprentice of the grim reaper himself
which means
i'm also
uh when it comes to dealing with ghosts
really bad because usually it's my job
to make humans into ghosts uh when it
comes to dealing with the ghosts um
it's not good and i'm ready to face i'm
ready to live up to my family name and
face full life consequences i'm excited
let's go my specialty in this situation
when it comes to being part of the the
scooby-doo crew
um
is
taking a bunch of items into the house
that i don't know how to use and have no
reason for using and then leaving them
there so uh let's see how that helps us
out in the game nah don't don't leave
everything that we're all broke as hell
in the game you gotta put it back into
the trackline there's manchester city
you can even have enough money to buy
flashlights for everyone
we have one flashlight i can i can buy a
little bit i don't have we already have
one though um how many you have money
one costs thirty dollars pretty
expensive let me buy something i have 74
bucks so okay i have 62. we can hit the
dollar store
i'll get us a flashlight
okay
i got some stuff here you go
okay we got we got all flashlights now
we got four
we got a thermometer okay what else
could we need do you have a ghost
writing book
yes it's in there yeah great okay then
we don't need to buy that spirit box a
uv light video camera one of the six
photo camera camera one of the free
emf reader
i'm one dollar short for a thermometer
guys but we really probably should get
we already have one we have one
excellent okay great
i think we're good we need another video
camera or something
a christmas
a glow
why do we need a glow stick is there a
party here a ghost writing book um it
doesn't look like we have a ghost
writing book it's a zero
is anyone
oh wait we can buy why did i buy four
week flashlights i could buy one strong
flash flashlight yeah i know right
now please
oh wait i have to oh i have some stuff
here oh i didn't realize what the hell
oh maybe because wait what this is all
my stuff
yeah
oh my god wait oh
what does that happen oh wait no no i
have nothing uh i'm going to add salt
two times that's the idea
who times this
okay
i'm gonna add everything
oh salt is always good oh yeah add
everything you've got i'm contributing
yes
salty
i don't understand this how this game
works sometimes yeah
yes because now
all right well this is fine equipment
list is looking good so let's just go
with it
all right ladies here are the jobs that
we have
we've got edgefield street house allow
me to narrate
recommended team two a two-story
six-bedroom house with a basement we
have recently received information about
a possible haunting at this location get
there as soon as you can and gather
evidence for the ghost removal team
we'll have more intel when you arrive
location is small recommended items
thermometer and this difficulty is
amateur
yeah let's start with amateur center
google
let's do it easy
[Music]
i'm ready
let's do our best
you'll be fine babe don't worry about it
right have you noticed bane
[Music]
oh by the way guys when we're talking to
the ghosts and you're listening to our
stream like on our side um
all right
um
and we start the game uh
one okay when we were trying to talk to
the ghost you will hear us speak double
because we have to input our voice into
the game we're not actually using push
to talk stained duct tape
here's the truck screams
why am i alone i'm on my way oh there
you go
wait wait wait wait wait please
oh my god
also this is not loading ebird
because it's waiting for fauna i bet
ah
it says loading game ninety percent
that's how it was for me for a while and
it was a long time until it finally why
is bay's sandy oh just kidding
everyone's sanity is kind of fluctuating
he has been angry with me i kicked it
out of my
my closet that i stream from and
[Music]
margaret anderson this ghost seems to
respond to everyone you should be able
to use its name to anger it and get some
paranormal activity
oh my goodness this game is making my
game full screen when i don't give it
permission
because you're supposed to they want it
to play
[Music]
you're going down is that bleach can we
bleach to go see capture a photo of your
ghost
pickup once again emf reader salt
walk through salt all right ladies so
let's maybe split this up and someone
should use the camera someone you should
use the emf reader someone should use
the salt
i vote on camera uh video camera and
salt all right all right wait can i take
a question how do you use emf reader i
don't know what the controls are someone
tell me
oh good question
e for picking up items
okay and then you can scroll in between
those items i think like free items is
maximum
okay where's the momentum um i actually
can't pick up anything dang it did i
change my buttons you're right chad
let's
drink him go drink some salt milk
i want the emf reader milk
oh i have the emf reader dang it
[Music]
attached to the girls
all right pick up is d for some reason i
have it as z
drop is x
flashlight is c oh this is for me this
is my personal settings
oh
uh are we going someone
[Music]
it's really dark
mama take a lot lookie
cool all right i got the emf right now
and a cross just in case oh thank you i
appreciate it we're good though
again
wait what was that
margaret margaret
[Music]
margaret anderson
oh good we just got to figure out what
room she's in oh that is very creepy
i need to think
let's turn the light on from the
beginning maybe yeah nice idea i don't
have a flashlight
wait there wasn't a flashlight for you
there should be one yeah there was only
three flashlights i feel no no
right here
margaret anderson give us a sign oh my
goodness
are you okay
my double boys spook you yes
margaret anderson give us a sign
no could you just stay in your house
please no she needs to come out i agree
okay margaret there's a dirty dirty ass
woman here living here
oh
don't say that about her clean up your
apartment come on it's kind of nasty
oh she must be upstairs then
you grab the emf reader i don't like
that oh that's
got stairs
all right going upstairs
let's turn on a light
a picture of the child i'm panting
where is everybody
a beautiful
oh wait whoa
oh my god downstairs oh it's downstairs
it's downstairs
are you banging
hold on you like right here it's 14
degrees right here
oh let me see okay maybe she's here
do you see like um like cold
like fumes and stuff
that's not cold enough oh okay yeah it
might not be cold enough
okay okay okay sorry
gotta check every room though babe
because very clearly
sorry the plant looked like the hand oh
my god
how about kitchen
margaret thompson give us a sign
give us the sign
20 degrees not here
for the laundry room
give us a sign
where's this door this is that backyard
i can't open it i don't know okay um oh
i found a bathroom
cat is being very needy today so i might
have to go afk
oh okay
this door is locked
have you guys been upstairs yet yeah we
went up there but we didn't go in every
room is the thing hey come with me let's
go check out every room i have the emf
reader so we should work together
i heard a sound
oh i heard i heard a phone uh vibrating
where me too
i didn't hear anything
[Music]
how do i put the song down
no oh children's room
okay
oh no give us a sign
that's scary
[Music]
we all just like really
really bad horror game players might be
give us a sign
hello hello
what was it margaret thompson
great placement
[Music]
it's here
it's a big house
this bathroom
oh
margaret thompson no this is 20 degrees
what was that
what was it
nice
i'm just gonna put salt everywhere you
always gotta put salt everywhere
yeah
very important here's the room we
haven't been in it was someone breathing
like
yeah right i heard you still before
that was okay
creepy oh was that you
oh
maybe in here
a is the real ghost
and
six people we have
where
where they're often in the basement
where was that i wanted
i wish i had a light on my shoulder
instead of
this teeny tiny light
it's so small wait where did it go to
six degrees the light went out
and am i out of salt
guys the light
the ghost was a little bit active it
seems yes yes i i see it oh i see i'm
not getting any emf activity so i love
it
there must not be a ghost that responds
to emf
well you gotta you guys
name out more more often
[Music]
that's the reason why the ghost hasn't
showed up where are you from
[Music]
oh boy
there's nothing going on right now in
the activity
there's no activity really
yeah there is check out that activity
that's a big spot
no hurry
what is this thing i have in my hand by
the way
emf4 ladies
how do i place this i'm going in i gotta
you know make myself stronger for
outlast yeah good idea
should we put a camera
oh my god
there we go
across
that's protected
[Music]
i was just kidding
i want to put this down here i want to
see if i can get five why turn it guys
help me chat
i'm like there's like a party down here
what
margaret anderson
it was a recording at the door
it's recording right
yeah the ghost is that the entryway guys
perhaps
waiting for us
margaret anderson
[Music]
oh
anderson
it's definitely
[Music]
someone's playing with something a ghost
oh man
oh no
oh man that's a spooky ghost playing
with the lights let's gotta gotta check
off playing with the lights in the
journal
um
margaret anderson [\h__\h] you
okay it's definitely in this
episode
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
margaret anderson
i set up a camera a video camera and uh
um in the entrance room bloody mary
bloody mary the dark it won't you won't
see it i swear bloody mary bloody mary
bloody mary bloody mary bloody mary
bloody mary bloody mary bloody mary oh
there is activity i'm running away yeah
something's happening we just gotta quit
being little cowards and gotta get
deeper into the house i bet it's not
just the entrance
are you sure did you see the ghost
no but it went down to three degrees oh
okay well then maybe it's a room close
by
yeah
well it was useful here what is that
you can't really see anything margaret
margaret anderson [\h__\h]
[Music]
you scared the [\h__\h] out of me my dude
come on is that you
it's it's the ghost
[Music]
you got me
i'm outside i meant outside the house
[Music]
is that is that good
i don't know about that baby we saw
prince in the garage oh is that is that
so rinse in the garage
i'm so scared no we're fine babe don't
worry about it it's you're right this
ghost
[Music]
yeah you can't open it for some reason i
don't want to go to the bed that must be
the ghost
no wait the ghost is hunting probably oh
the door is closed oh boy the ghost is
totally hunting lights off
i'll be watching
i'm dead
it was me
goodbye i heard her laughing
is someone dead
i'm dead
really died i've died
congratulations
i didn't see anything is the activity
over am i safe
um activity wait
did two people die
i heard the door
i can't open it
stop it i can't open the door
you're scaring me which door are you
trying to get gallery yeah trying to get
out
okay there you go oh thanks
thank you open the door bona's dead wait
wait wait tell me i'm dead
wait for me okay
[Music]
oh my god our sanity is all very low
except for base which means we gotta
send bae in again
yeah yeah
he's the bestest i was uh really not
doing good in there what did you guys
see on the camera did you catch anything
no because the camera wasn't positioned
correctly
i positioned it perfectly are you
telling your senpai didn't position the
camera correctly i wonder where santa
was when she died
where where did you put the camera wait
what where on the on the on the little
table on the
entrance on the little table on the
entrance on the little table
huh
yes on the little on the little table on
the entrance what
yeah right at the door on the right side
there's weird stuff on the car
wait do you have the um the other we
need the other flashlight you know the
purple flashlight yeah yes i have to
call the car you have it okay where do
you need it
the door closed again oh oh no
that's bad
um the door is locked um
i took the headphones down i'm not
listening
goodbye i hear someone choking
[Music]
all right okay i'm back i'm i mean i'm
dead but i'm back
well you can pick up my items they're
all at the door i got a i got a photo
camera why were only you killed
because i am okay to kill yeah
also uh here uh who is that woman
character
yeah is it that bae oh no is that fauna
we're going i don't know
you guys are ghosts you got a tournament
ghost we can see each other
i gotta go put some stuff on it hey it's
you and me now
do you want to know where the camera is
the video camera it's uh yeah hold on
let's give this stuff away
stay where you are look to the right
that's where it is the video camera
oh yeah
the green one
yeah
give me this why don't you carry a
picture with you uh fauna is that you
are you doxing it's someone
[Music]
oh yeah i knew it i knew the ghost is
definitely around this area but ghost
is this a body open again
i guess the main all right bae it's up
to you now
um
your journal we have like any
fingerprints we definitely found
fingerprints
freezing did you guys find freezing
temperatures
no all right so maybe no freezing
i found fingerprints gotcha okay finger
prints
all right billy according to chat which
is not me you gotta see if there's ghost
writing okay
if you go into the van
you can do it actually i put the book
upstairs
[Music]
please get up
what is happening here guys i don't i
literally don't know what's happening
oh i couldn't tell who was a human and
who was um all right well
let's try a different job guys
it was pretty bad how about the
tanglewood street house lost all our
stuff recommended team size one how
about that guys a small three bedroom
single floor house the basement we've
recently received information about a
possible haunting at this location head
there gather as much evidence as you can
to a ghost removal team blah blah blah
blah blah blah all right let's go get
some ghosts guys salt
yeah we should add some stuff
man
oh
i can afford things now i want a strong
flashlight money yeah insurance we're
dying oh yeah i don't have insurance oh
that's weird
you always regret it later on that you
didn't get insurance
head-mounted camera
should also be good
i'm gonna add a tripod
well required level eight and we can put
the video camera on nice idea
what was that green dotty thing that we
plant that i placed in the hallway and
candles yeah what was that motion sensor
right don't tell me
really
tell us anything
no
how how do you
should we bring candles again yeah i
want to see if i can light up some rooms
next time
there's someone
otherwise i'll buy some
i bought two don't worry
we have a lighter already
salt never have you can never have too
much salt but i think we have plenty
income uh do we need a thermometer
always good to have just to check
yeah let me buy one unless someone has
one
i'll go buy
l.a right
tanglewood street house
now we're fully equipped again and we're
probably going to lose it all again no
we can we can definitely do this i have
believe we will buy
okay chad we need your help at least i
need your help
we can do it we can do it
the green one it was the dots and it
blinks at the ghost cross through it i
saw that happening actually i saw the
green dots like dim a little bit
and like yeah and change before i died
you can see the ghost in it through a
video camera ah
dot's projector is the green thing okay
i see so it should always be like
combined with a video camera the
thoughts projector oh okay well uh bae i
know you're feeling not ready but you
should push ready in the game
all right i'm gonna oh that's me i'm
supposed to press start there we go
didn't you survive those have been known
to target those who stay in the light
too long
okay we got to move into the darkness
taking her time again that's okay
no worries we got all these times
all right here's what we got
there she is
only respond when people are alone
that's fun
james moore
james moore is that the name of some
famous person it sounds like a famous
person wait only one torch wait why
would we only have one two oh you you
already took one oh get a ghost to blow
out a candle we only have one not lucky
guys no we have two i got one
oh you got one there's one on the floor
you have someone on yours
i got the strong flashlight
oh i probably have uh
oh yeah all right
where's the strong flashlight what does
it say here james moore this ghost also
seems to only respond to people who are
alone you know you heard that bae
you gotta be alone
where's the head cat where's the
head-mounted camera
i think bae is like mentally branded
did i not put all my items in the game
bait did you lose your voice
all right hey
hey bang
you okay hey you heard me
okay
bang you good
you're so quiet like a mouse
anyone know where a lighter is
yeah i could have sworn we had a lighter
last time now i feel like one in there
no it's not this is really weird
i saw it in the no wait no i didn't see
it in the list actually never mind it
was their last stop stuff yeah but i
bought it
so we can't do [\h__\h] with the candles
don't wow just just leave the candles in
there then so that we don't lose them
okay
going in
i have the ghost riding book with me
nice and a torch and that's all i got
all right i got fingerprints
okay
there you go
ecko
[Music]
we have a thermometer still or an ems uh
there should be
like we've definitely brought one
i brought one i have an emf i don't have
it in my hand okay
let's go james moore oh a ball a bone
give us a sign where's the bomb where's
[Music]
i just have a regular old camera
i would like it to be in the kitchen
that would be nice
okay let's go in here
monsieurs
can i set this bad boy down
james
oh someone's taking a photo
i took a photo of the bone
thank you
you didn't even walk in oh i can turn on
james moy do you want to
exchange letters with me ooh
give us a
sign i always wanted someone to exchange
letters with a little pen pal
yes pen pal that sounds kind of cute
actually
wait i found the ocean
oh my god
oh i just thought there was someone here
in my monster's shoes i found the board
where is it no
uh i have it in my hand
ooh is it upstairs i heard something i'm
coming up with it right now yeah i'm
cutting the basement
how do we use this are the doors locked
no i've heard something indoors oh i
heard something
i don't want to hear anything
this is cool is this like a rare item i
heard something i heard something
i want to leave right now
well they gave me the sign i wanted
the luigi board look right here
but i guess we can only use it inside
something did you have
a sign yeah the lights flickered in the
kitchen
oh
there's
there's some running water
i'm gonna use that [\h__\h]
i'm gonna
[Music]
well there's dirty water in the sink is
that one oh yeah
temperature just went down a little bit
give us a sign
he's he's given us the sign
oh god's steak
he's like
water baby
is that a three
it's it's it's not good no emf ready
to ask a question okay drop it do we
have the
emf thing
how do i activate it it's always fun
yeah i have to go
i'm not getting any signs
hold up let me take a picture of the
thing
what is
[Music]
i'm not getting anything emf was hey my
ghost is stabilizing
okay good
we can't even clear amateur stuff wait
where's my old job board i think it's
safe to say no emf
readings someone stole my old job board
did someone take my aren't y'all bored
did the girls take my withdrawals
how do you get the oh i got the bone
it's gone
you picked up the bones
apparently is this you my
dude maybe it's the basement
[Music]
looks like you're a pizza delivery
person only like reply to the old snail
board like in the correct room guys or
anyway
give us the sign probably only in the
classroom
all right guys
here we go okay
james moore
[\h__\h] you
i don't think james would like
bloody mary bloody mary bloody mary
bloody mary
can you come to the bathroom with me
james moore how old are you
[Music]
oh my god hold on i can fix this
james what should i ask kim
are you okay
i'm i'm using the oja board the question
yeah the game can hear me i tested it
wait i want to set up a camera in the
toilet
me i do
oh wait the door closed you guys are in
trouble
yeah we are
i got me though
he got me
as i ran i ran right into the ghost
oh wait it really went from here in my
you asked him a really personal question
i guess i shouldn't move right there's i
shouldn't there's there is safe now um
safe now all right i'll be lookout for
you
guys where did you die someone come back
hey come back
oh
you're a stoner i want to set up i want
to set up the camera
you can pick up the camera where i died
by the way the tripod the tripod is in
the truck you guys
oh it's in the bottom of the show yeah
are getting a reading yeah mf2 in the
bathroom emf ii roll based do
hold on a second uh i'm pressing okay
i'm gonna do something terrible i'm
gonna be brave should i move i won't
come in here it only responds when it's
alone
james might have that give us a second
zero
whoosh
what i heard it said something
i heard i heard
[Music]
right in the
sanity pills are necessary all the stuff
though at the door
you should probably grab it go to the
van and then we just leave and make a
guess
how do i open the door
wait i'll try to open it for you
it's hunting again oh boy
be careful
right i'm the only one left alive i'm
just going to pick up some items and put
it in the truck yeah it's time to go
oh my god
we got um
spirit box oh yeah really the spirit box
works
yeah
am i supposed to be able to see the
other ghosts
i don't think emf level five
though what about fingerprints ghost orb
do we get freezing temperatures
what's happening hey
what is the low temperature you saw bay
[Laughter]
you guys good is everyone dead
babe that is
crouching oh it is
anyone's got the flashback oh yeah scary
this is the demon crouching
oh it is why does it have a flashlight
why does that a flashlight wait oh and
this me
is someone is there any ghost in the
truck right now can we can he tell me
look like i'll go in there i'll go into
the truck oh oh i thought she missed my
ghost is go into the truck all right the
activity is low it's not it's basically
non-existent right now
oh no that's the dead body oh
every single time you go that doesn't
seem right yeah then we really should
get a right guess here and not keep on
losing our money
all right guys
what do we know about him no emf level
five i was everywhere up in that [\h__\h]
with the emf
reader and i didn't get level five so
none of that
but there was a spirit box i put the
book somewhere does anyone know where i
put the book
ghost writing if we get ghost writing
let me just try to find
if the book again
if the book isn't written in then it's
only two it can only be
one of two
phantom and yokai and the stella you put
it in the basement oh dear let's see if
i can make it how about i'll be your
lady
with zero sanity kelly is this you i
can't tell who's who
i'm now entering the house we'll hunt
fast oh god oh god
all right no worries we got this what is
this wait
which one are you guys going for i want
to choose something before i go in so
that i at least have
something here
who is that someone's fat
oh no i'm in the basement
is it hunting
oh did someone die here
you died
but i'm gonna go with um
wait what
what did i do let me read what did
support the guys to do
spirit spirits are very common ghosts
are for powerful passives only attacking
when they need to defend their place of
death to the utmost degree killing
anyone with a love is very contemporary
stop but very sweet okay my spirit
sounds like it could be it's
i can check the book guys
i can check the book
be a spirit though
[Music]
you said it's in the basement drop your
sanity because you can take your photos
and make it temporary just remember me
i commonly said i was from origin i mean
i did speak with the older boy a lot but
he never answered me so it's not a
phantom i think did you put the book
where is the book
uh and oh right i guess the ghost can go
look too huh yeah we're looking it's a
basement in the basement i put the book
like pretty close to the like it's like
on the on the other side of the room
on the bottom on the ground on the
ground i can't see anything on the
ground
yeah
we might not be able to see it
you guys can't see many times
[Music]
try crouching ghosts can see the writing
nice try though okay
uh
right i want to see what the left is
called one of the most dangerous ghosts
oh there's nothing in the boat
right now
yeah but apparently ghosts can't see it
anyway even if like you go so dead dead
players can't see oh that's annoying
i'm just gonna go with
a spirit because this is the most common
and we're playing an amateur game i
don't know biologically crazy
here for me what there was freezing
temperature really was there well was it
just using is below zero oh no there was
no freezing temperature okay um most
candidates
i don't think it was the spirit
oh no emf okay
if there's no emf level five it's not a
spirit
oh we got spirit box though
i'm gonna say no ghost writing just
because
so
poltergeist phantom phantom or yokai
okay well i think maybe a yo guy
i'll choose phantom just to be
contrarian okay okay okay
we have to pick common ghosts that are
attracted to human voices they can
usually be found haunting family home
strengths talking here you'll get a
little angry at increasing your chances
oh i talked a lot to that dude yeah yeah
yeah maybe it's your fault
yeah let's try it
let's try that give it a shot it does
say emf level five it was one of the
evidences but i crossed it off for the
evidence
yeah me too but it comes up doesn't it
well
let's try i don't think so i think it's
just spirit box
it looks like like this
because i didn't see it
should i do it not gonna lie
are you okay
um i like how
this ghost is called hantu
because it like hunting
your guests in the book i did
can i know it uh press j okay
and then what do i do then you click on
uh you could go to evidence go to the
evidence tab
i did okay
okay good then you're fine let's leave
all right
look at our super professional van and
we all just suck i love it
i love it
i'm really unlucky whenever i played
before the ghosts were never so violent
it was a mirror
so we messed up some evidence but it's
fine i got i got we got a little
evidence and photos at least we got some
more money
[Music]
see i don't know there's something kind
of i have a good job
all right we're really horrible at this
one
let's do one more game if that's okay
with you guys do you have
it going to get a ghost writing book
because you have nothing
yeah you can watch our activities
oh i got my items i'm going to add a
perma-meter and a tripod that's all i
got
i'm buying a straw spider
a light a lighter okay now we have a
lighter
on the camera handle photo camera
would love one more candle if possible
guys if anyone stopped by
i will buy
i will buy all right cool i bought
candles
good stuff now let's see what jobs we
have how about we do the farmhouse
because asylum in prison is going to be
no way
um the farmers isn't that pretty pink uh
size recommended is two is a two-story
three-bedroom farmhouse we can do either
that or the prison recommended size
three an asylum recommended size four so
barry
can you like refresh that to give us
something smaller
no unfortunately it doesn't it doesn't
work
i think we'll be fine
farmhouse then yeah let's do it it's got
an attic nice
i'm ready
wait we only have one out of four
flashlights you and one strong one
yeah i bought a strong one i buy one you
buy one bae okay
i cannot afford what
i cannot afford exactly one and then i'm
out of money oh my god
all right someone just stay with
someone who has a flashlight you can
stick with me or babe you were gonna say
that now we should have
now we should have four yeah we have
four to four and one strong one okay
actually then wait wait wait wait wait
then let me can i
uh how do i get rid of one damn it
because we don't need five flashlights
good question
oh well let's just leave one in the
truck go go go
go right you gotta ready yourself up no
okay sorry noise
let's go
we can do this guys i know we can
let's just believe in believe in each
other and we just gotta test out
everything okay
and be extremely careful and hide we
gotta hide i don't believe in us yes
you got to believe
george robinson
seems to respond to everyone you should
be able to use its name to angry against
someone okay we don't have to be alone
for this ghost okay
smudge stick so i didn't bring any
smudge sticks at all
strong flashlight is this is too much
we have smudge sticks right
[Music]
and candle and lighter actually i'll
start off taking candles and then i'll
leave the ghost writing book here for
now if somebody else wants to use ghost
writing book i'm going to light up some
candles in the house oh oh yeah i i'm
bringing the ghost writing book
cool and the video camera uh can anyone
bring the tripod
anyone got some free hands
[Music]
otherwise i'll leave the book behind you
come
i put the book right that makes no sense
then i'll put the book down you take the
tripod and i think the camera end of it
you can okay
[Music]
yeah this map is definitely scarier
which is the strong flashlight is it the
black one or the gray one
black one what's his name again george
something
what was it georgia robinson george
robinson
george robinson
gotcha
i think it's the one that you put on
your shoulder there we go all right
we're good
no i put the weak one away
okay
jordan my dude is winded after two steps
i'm gonna set up this line
[Music]
13 degrees
where are the lights
how do i set it down
here
[Music]
if you find something sauce tell me i
want to take a photo of it you go
there's the candle one candle
go get another one oh god
i'm just gonna follow you
i'll check the activity
okay are you safe it's still relatively
easy i was i was shocked by bae yeah
nothing's really going on right now
who is who
gasps
[Music]
and that means something no i don't like
being in the dark without being able to
see and i don't like ghosts
another candle
i'll put one upstairs just in case
nothing suspicious yet
yeah i have no emf yet
wait we're not playing a manga here i'm
not looking for anything suspicious i
left the tripod hold on
why is the tripod there did i leave that
there
apparently you did still replaced it oh
breakers in a really easy to find spot
hello uh
where's this door
pick it up how can i pick up my house
man
all right bedroom nice hat
oh do i have to be holding it the whole
time oh i see
i understand
uh
[Music]
george morrison give us a sign
where'd you guys go
i'm in the bedroom upstairs looks like
it's not here
george morrison give us a sign
[Music]
it's okay don't worry i'm scaring ghost
noises
but i don't know
um i saw her aria flick
maybe my dude was giving us a sign
how nice of him to help us
progress in the game attic i'm gonna go
to the attic
dad is very brave of you yeah i probably
should have put a candle up here
give us a sign nothing
where would i see a fingerprints
usually
the ghost is like on the door the window
or something you're weird howling
yeah i hear that too what the hell oh
that's you
that was me babe
how like ghosts
give us a stop always
yeah i'm in the attic you're just scared
give us the signs
okay we'll turn the light off everybody
who means
we're all lights
let's see what there's much
[Music]
the purple flashlight
okay okay
give us a sign
[Music]
you found the wrong goal yeah you're
good at finding the rooms which room
which floor
you're right here right here okay which
floor
the second floor
okay there's a bone on the floor
oh i want to take a photo where is the
boom
wait the second floor is boom
second floor bathroom there's a boat
okay
where's bathroom
here
nice got it thank you
okay tripod wait wait wait wait mate put
the tripod down where you think it is
the ghost
[Music]
you gotta grab that bad boy get that
money
i can't i got four hands man all right
i'm in the kitchen ah
i uh
is it really up here cause i'm not
getting anything yeah how do you think
so bae
[Music]
george morrison give us a sign
i'm gonna go grab something george
morrison
can someone put the camera on top of the
tripod here maybe in the hallway yes
it comes out maybe we have no ghost
writing book so let me grab this
oh wait i could take it never mind i got
the boom okay
uh wait wait wait wait where did you put
the tripod it's right by the stairs
stairs
on the second floor
uh on the second floor stairs down to
the first floor
okay
oh god it's so dark
i don't see [\h__\h] yeah i thought i turned
on the lights but here it is
there we go
uh turn the light on oh this candle is
out is it is it filming do you see it
i don't let me
give us a sign
chad says they went to emf 3 but
my candle's out i did not see it or hear
it
where
um
someone is me right oh it's me
okay
give us a sign
what do we do with this cow we need a
lighter when we gonna
switch
um all of the candles i lit up are blown
out um oh
what does that mean should we take a
picture of that is that something
because he did something maybe i mean i
probably should just be witnessing
all right there's no activity at the
moment
we haven't found the right room
thermometer okay i swear it was the
bathroom do you want the thermometer
here yes oh let's maybe go back upstairs
then
okay i'm coming
candles do go out on their own
eventually
maybe we should put a candle upstairs
did you put one upstairs too uh-huh i
brought one with me upstairs
all right give us this the lighter
oh yeah i do
yeah
here where
okay
right next to the book
yeah there we go
we did it she screamed sparks
give us a sign
[\h__\h] uh
i don't know if jordan yeah we gotta
talk more to the ghost i don't think
it's reacting to me at all i think the
game doesn't pick up my voice but
okay well i'm gonna go downstairs and
check on your sanity and just look at
the camera because is this is this
normal
give us a sign
hold up
let me have a look all right well
that's fine
bathroom
put the video camera down in the ghost
room yeah apparently that's a little bit
of
except that stuff here
wait was it the other bathroom is this
the same bathroom no i think it's a
different bathroom one under the
this one
i thought you said doors closed and i
got
extra i didn't
i got scared give us a sign
james morrison
george george oh george morrison
is that an orb there's an orb
george morrison
[Music]
we're experts at this guys
wait george morrison's thinking his knee
the name is george robinson everybody
yes sorry george robinson i'm sorry give
us a sign dude
george robinson george robinson
we did that give us a sign
take a little break you're shy
[Music]
going on there it goes you had nice
sanity
yeah no i want to try to say move the
camera into like the bathroom maybe
george anderson give us a sign
wait forna found it what
give us
i'm the cold temperatures oh okay
and they stand for me
flickering lights oh no
look at my lights
i think i'm dead oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
freak freezing
indeed it is flickering
ring flickering it is uh hunting is that
what it is
it's me i'm dead
i'm dead again
[Music]
wait okay so we got do we get freezing
temperatures that's not true
um well i still can't manage to get any
ghost writing so i think it's okay to
rule that out
no
temperatures
no freezing temperatures we're just cold
but not freezing what was the emf emf
just three
oh come on
useless or not no five
i mean five we've just started down to
three it's either a phantom banshee or a
yokai
like how do we do we have spirit box
yeah ghost what do we actually have
ghost orb and something else
um i don't know if there's a ghost orb i
couldn't tell
didn't someone say we have a ghost orb
oh
i can't turn on the light
why
oh it's walking around upstairs
it's in the attic
creepy
yucky
[Music]
downstairs how do i turn off the
flashlight
oh i just threw it right
that's bad i can't find my flashlight
anymore okay that's not good
creepy man holding a hatchet
please i just want to get
yes
i don't know how to turn off the
flashlight lol
let me open the door
i can't come here
come
look at the light okay
hey hey guys
all right so let's regroup and figure
out what we know
we know that there's
ghost orbs apparently yeah
what
oh man let's see okay
there's definitely no ghost writing
because i was everywhere up in that
[\h__\h] saying that dude's name he didn't
he and comey didn't do nothing
so no ghost writing freezing temperature
oh god damn it i go in and it closes
are you kidding me
yara
no no you can try to run or hide
in a closet
oh we see you in the window i see you in
the window
he's gonna kill me oh he's coming he's
coming for you
are you taking pictures babe from the
outside are you taking pictures of kiara
getting a kitchen
ask me for god's sake
hey my man
no open it try opening it now
oh my god oh my god
i can't believe it wow that was pretty
dope okay okay yeah that was awesome
i don't know if they count as anything
but they're funky photos they have the
ghosts
guys
apparently
everything that i don't see
all right for me it's apparently a fancy
if we really saw ghost orbs
interesting
but there's a banshee
did it stop after you took the photos
because
apparently don't wait don't phantom
disappear after you take a photo or
something wait a little bit yeah just
taking a photo of the phantom and
literally rarely disappeared yeah it was
about to hunt me now
and i took photos into the hair and it
disappeared yeah
oh that was
wait it was a phantom
i'm not sure if it actually disappeared
because i saw it in the kitchen
oh i don't know
it like didn't go into the room where
you were in it went into the kitchen
but it was at the door right
um
no it was it went down the stairs and
then went into the kitchen
uh
yeah no it has to be a phantom because
there weren't any ghost storms
there were no little swords there were
no ghosts
i thought you saw a ghost warp i think
someone said
[Music]
we have is fingerprints and i don't know
i'm going to go throw it on some salt i
put that means you can cross out you can
cross out stuff in the journal if you
click it more times yeah i did i did i
did i did it's not so we have phantom
how you
i just wanted to put down some salt i
was feeling salty
yeah come and get me behind this salt
idiot ha ha
where are you
he said one day
i'll leave you
a phantom
come here
yeah
it's my little salt garden you guys like
it oh my oh
wow
the triangular shape actually protects
you
the secrets of all these worlds of all
this world is the secrets
of the world are there written here in
this triangle
can we go guys
yeah okay
i'm scared
come here
[Music]
gutting the doors making for sure
i'll leave here you got the door
okay where's the door where's the door
where's the door where's the door
here
yeah there's not a lot of activity guys
i think it's fine i think the ghost is
kind of sick of us
you guys all guessed phantom
wait one last thing let me check the
door
there we go
outside i don't want to go inside
it's activity is going up a bit oh
okay bye-bye
okay
on on the door or and lights which is
all
well
once again that was a
very uh eventful at least we didn't we
mostly didn't die 75 percent of the
party is still here somehow
not bad
three four three right now
that means we won't lose items at least
at least the people who
what is that
the people who didn't diet
okay
so are we really going for phantom
i guess i don't know what else we should
go for
yeah
just gotta hold me apparently
maybe we should split
i'll pick anshi okay wait why would it
be banshee
i don't know because because the game
always is right and we always wrong
didn't chase me up the attic even though
there were other people downstairs oh
because the fancy targets one person
specifically
oh
interesting but wouldn't it have saturn
is something about being alone because
here it says everyone usually will not
take me because i will talk to you on
this oh
i see
well i'm gonna close the door now
everyone make your decisions
all right i'll just see what happens i'm
i'm joining the black parade today we'll
see what happens okay
[Music]
all right
you suck weird farmhouse
that dude was really yanking our chain
for a while
[Music]
it was a yokai what the [\h__\h]
we have alright
i don't get it
i'll get it we just got to get good
we just got to get good at fasmo
it really
started it became really difficult after
that stupid update
yeah it did i mean last time you guys
played it you also couldn't get a single
win right exactly exactly and we had
some some decent ghost hunters i would
say this is just a game for like really
elite game lords i think which is fine
that's great yeah games like that should
exist um it just means that we may be
happy to carry your update
coming out tomorrow yeah our timing was
just a bit off but yeah well maybe that
was for the best what else happened yeah
i think it was for the best
oh come on never playing this again
oh no
way
i love spending time with you guys
though yeah
come play
i personally wouldn't mind not playing
it anymore either
it's fun i feel like it's really fun
because you guys are here
yeah
me too i i enjoyed having uh you guys
around and spending time with you guys
because i yeah i haven't had much time
or like possibilities to interact with
the council members specifically
hmm
unfortunately
i've been trying i was gonna ask you how
to do it because i'm not kidding it
feels like it's coming out of my uh
coming out of my chest i'm not i'm not
[Music]
oh my gosh that's really intense i
didn't know it was that it was like that
you should have a good rest
yeah boy you suggest sushi game
there's so many other games that you can
play with four people we couldn't play
at my real party baby
it was still fun
but i wanna make sure you're okay
i'm okay
you guys have fun now you can stay
you've done it yeah of course do it
again
yeah i feel like i'm getting braver at
horror games there are no monsters under
your bed okay should should mommy fauna
check under your bed tonight
[Laughter]
yeah tell them you tell them
i still had a good time though i'm
extremely hungry but i still had a
really good time with you guys i
actually have to i'm watching horror
movies quote-unquote horror movies oh
yeah right hey this is inaudible popcorn
what's your favorite popcorn callie
movie theater butter
butter salty butter extra buttery
oh
yes i've had a time where i only wanted
to eat caramel popcorn
but now i'm back to like i don't mind
eating any kind like salty or butter or
uh caramel popcorn i don't mind yeah and
you can think of that real quick huh
it no i i love when it's like the more
caramel is on it the better
on it yeah more caramel the better yeah
agreed
yeah fana what's your favorite popcorn
um i like classic buttery as well
oh it's a good choice
got some good taste how about you bae
what about you
what's your favorite one bails what's
the question
what's your favorite popcorn
um
i like cheese
you like cheese popcorn
i mean it makes sense you're a wrap
i've i've only seen cheese popcorn
before in japan like i was in a store
where there's like uh 50 different types
of popcorn and they're they all sound
weird as [\h__\h] oh yeah like um like
seaweed flavor and stuff like that even
crazier than that that's that's so super
normal for japan scenes
yeah but it was really weird stuff
really interesting cool
that's tasty at least at least they got
different types red red bean flavors oh
yeah that's right and like spicy super
hot
strawberry flavor they have banana
flavor they definitely have banana
flavored popcorn that's not yummy
actually pizza
like pizza go fish
sorry nerdy out over popcorn a little
bit
i'm glad you're also a popcorn fan kiara
i wouldn't mind whenever i go back to uh
japan
you know what we should do we should
find that store and then get like 20
different types of that popcorn and do a
taste test yeah blindfolded you guys
can't look at it it's a good idea
yeah i mean would be nice to look at it
but i guess popcorn all looks the same
most of the time yeah you got to guess
the flavor that's the fun of it all
ah
yeah fun on mayo being quiet sorry sorry
about it i had to go
yelling again no he had to
check on him
yeah can you give me a cat fact of your
cat
yes he's 21 years old so old first i
mean more like an insider give me an
insider cat fact oh my old man
old man what's an insider cat fact
like uh like something weird about him
that he does
um he sees into the spirit realm
that's cool and look and into mirrors
that's adorable
whenever i pet my cat uh my cats on like
the part right above their tail they
lick themselves
[Music]
always without fail it's very cute
fauna do your cats follow you wherever
you go like as soon as you get up from a
chair do they like run after you
not really but hold on i have to go grab
him just stand the cat stuff
you know what my one of my cats uh
smoothie you know what what cute things
she does um
you know when i'm talking on my stream
like i talk pretty like
like constantly right so when i when i'm
done streaming i immediately stop
talking and smoothie
every time i swear every time i'm done
streaming she immediately comes into my
room because she knows i'm done
streaming because i stopped talking she
walks into my room she says meow and
then she falls down on the floor and she
rolls around and says hello like mommy
you're done with streaming don't play
with me
it's so cute
yeah
she recognizes when i'm done streaming
it's so ah
he's probably figured it out by now
yeah yeah definitely
when mommy is loud she goes to different
room to sleep and when when mommy is
quiet she comes back and says hello
nice
babe do you like cats do you have a good
relationship with cats
yeah why rats
do you ever get chased by cats
yeah that's a good answer
well have you has a cat ever tried to
eat you
no
yeah okay
i think bae is brain dead
yeah i think so
oh well that was fun ladies thank you
for inviting me i'm calm i was calming
something not scary
yeah it's halloween wait we're gonna
play scary games exactly that's the
thing it's just this game because i
can't deal with paranormal any other
kind of horror game
it's not in the dark i can i can
somewhat
pretty much everything
in the park
this horror game is not dark
there by daylight
it has some not dark levels i guess it
says daylight so it's bright i mean yeah
there's like a winter level that's like
pretty bright outside i don't think it's
i don't think it's the type of scary
game that
that you would freak you out bae so i
think it should be fine
i'm excited to play deadline day like
yeah it'll be fun
don't like first person perspective that
makes it too real oh i see um
unless you're the killer but then why
would you be afraid if you were the
killer so yeah you'll be fine you'll be
fine don't you worry about it bae we're
gonna have a great time all right
okay
with that being said guys i guess we
better sign off huh okay
all right
that was fun
[Music]
yeah thank you again
uh maybe we'll see it might just and it
depends on how you guys approach it
because people think i have a grand
master plan but it really is kind of up
to you guys which way but the stuff that
you come up with is like up until now it
was always very scary and spooky so it's
like it's always halloween and you're
teaching everything
i'm glad you at least think that because
right now i feel like everything is very
clownish and very funny and good well
yeah but that's also scary a lot it's
scary
yeah
yeah well i hope that you enjoy the next
installment you guys
looking forward to it yes combat
going to be fun
um anyone else got announcements that
they want to shout out while we have a
chance
schedule is out look at it
um
[Music]
sorry i'm still trying to find the
feelings in my arms um i hope you guys
will be there
um of course i'll be there
it's a very cool thing
i can't wait
wait did you set did you like spoiler
what you're what you were you know
putting out there
no i just said special release
something anything special like not but
not that's it that's all you said yeah
yeah so i know i know more than the
audience yata me too
you guys do yeah yeah um
i'm like gorilla stream tonight cool oh
maybe i don't know what you gonna play
minecraft
oh
boys
very good for gorilla
that's the girl game
yeah um
donkey
[Music]
oh i don't really have anything
i'm taking a little break because
i streamed a lot this week
okay
amazing yeah
we love you
thanks everyone scheduled to be out soon
[Music]
excuse me just a moment wait chat
bye guys
you