Kik ho ho ho this is Kiwa and on day two
I'm here to show you something about
Christmas
markets I think there's Christmas
markets uh oh all over the world but I
feel like Europe does the the best so in
case you are not in Europe let me show
you the beauties of our Christmas
markets and in case you are in Europe
let me show you my favorite items to get
at the Christmas Market so you can copy
and paste how Wawa does it yeah it's a
recipe to success at a Christmas Market
but first of all I want to say um
Christmas markets they're kind of
expensive or they've become really
expensive um I think on the country side
they're a bit less expensive but in the
cities they're definitely
expensive everything's overpriced but
it's really about the atmosphere cuz
Christmas markets usually get really
crowded here and and especially in the
evening everybody goes there to hang out
after work or on the weekends and more
and more you get into the Christmas mood
without these things I feel like you
wouldn't get into the Christmas mood so
anyway I went out to take some videos
for you guys uh so here's a little tour
stle and this is by the way this is not
the Christmas Market I went to this is a
random picture uh to give you an image
of kind of what it looks like uh yeah
but here we are so you can buy like some
ornaments that's lot there's lots and
lots of ornaments to buy but I never
bought one cuz I think buying one single
one is overpriced this is gingerbread
lots of gingerbread high quality here's
some more decorations and Christmas WS
reefs puppets and toys remember we made
those Christmas reefs together last year
we made one I want to make another one
yeah lots of stuff to buy but uh oh yeah
even more more Christmas ornaments some
of them are kind of silly
too and here sorry it's flickering CU of
some weird thing um but there's my
beloved kaash manman which is like sweet
fluffy shredded pancakes served with
applesauce or stewed sugar plums here's
a list of the punches and mold wines Etc
uh wait let me pause here once it's too
fast go back um it's like 6 to eight
bucks uh but you pay like five bucks
extra five yeah for the cup and usually
they're like pretty cute cups uh you
could even collect them you can take
them home but if you bring them back you
get the F five bucks back of course yeah
no worries and it's also like hot
chocolate and coffee and tea Etc but
most people they just go for the the
mold wines and all that there's like a
couple of variations too yeah yeah but
usually for kids like me who don't want
to drink alcoholic ones there's usually
just one option
sadly I wish I could try out all of
those fancy sounding original options
they have one that's like apple strudel
punch which sounds really interesting to
me but it has like some alcohol the
blong alcohol in it I don't know
what that is
next blah blah BL then we had uh potato
snacks can you see and some cheese
they're you see the cheese it's like
melting wow they put that on top of the
CH the potato stuff it's yeah yummy
here's like some traditional chocolate
stuff I forgot what it's
called I never ate it before and these
are Big asran Donuts crap fin with Jam
chocolate or vanilla inside usually
normally they're with Jam but here's
some other choices they're really big
some more
potatoes I think they probably serve
serve it with like sour cream maybe I
don't know and this is ques spla we
cooked those before in my cooking stream
I love them so much they're uh small
dumplings maybe with lots of cheese but
like spicy kind of strong cheese M oh so
good they're so
good uh oh yeah here's some nuts I
couldn't like I took a video but it's
like flickering so bad oh my God I tried
to fix it uh but I couldn't really fix
it well so for for these you just get a
picture but this is one of my favorite
things to get at the Christmas Market
because uh my n this is not I I I prefer
the the almonds the most just normal
almonds really roasted almonds but uh
they have all kinds of variations like
vanilla butter they also have cashew
nuts and other nuts but yeah uh these
are chocolate fruit skewers I love them
so much too but I usually just go for
the strawberry ones more hash browns but
also fresh chest nuts I never had them
before actually what do they taste like
I don't know maybe I should try them
more nuts
M wow
wo
sugy okay what's next oh yeah a picture
oh let me let me
move a picture of my serving of uh the
kaash man the shredded pancakes
basically I love that stuff so much is a
dessert but I ate it for breakfast
basically on that
day with the plum sauce and it maybe
looks a little small but it filled me
quite nicely I was pretty full oh that
was that was a successful breakfast and
I ate I drank the the punch up there the
children punch it was Apple flavor M
really good and M finished so
good more please back to the nuts see
how bad it's flickering ah um I wanted
to take some home so the lady told me if
I wait a few seconds I can get fresh
ones wa I was like oh my God I never had
like really fresh ones before and yeah
those were um roasted sugared almonds
with
cinnamon she was like warning me girl be
careful they're like really hot really
really
hot and then when I tried them they were
indeed crazy hot she gave me uh a small
portion I asked for a small one you can
have a small or a big
one she was weighing it properly and
then there you go I got the fresh
package of nuts M they were so hot looks
like a small portion but I still have
some left over now even 2 days later and
honestly eating all at once kind of gets
boring so good to eat later when they're
cold too as a little snack I think it
was 100 G but yeah hope you enjoyed a
look into our Christmas markets there's
so many different ones and usually they
are at like a really nice location like
a castle or a palace
or some other special building sometimes
they even have ice skating options like
right there um and yeah on the
countryside I think they're like cheaper
and uh I I think I've been to one where
it was like in a really magical romantic
Forest location really quite nice but
yeah if you go
there be ready to uh freeze your ass off
oh my God this
embarrassing be ready to freeze your ass
off it's going to be really cold and
bring lots of money in in Austin and
Christmas markets it's still kind of
basic that you have to pay with cash uh
still which is annoying but so bring
cash and bring gloves and hats and
everything go in your warmest cloves and
have
fun ho ho ho