[Music]
he whaty
good morning
everyone I'm not in the car right now
because I wanted to be here before I
want to chat with you a little bit
before I join the call hello hello hello
everyone yes I am aware this day 15 I
read I'm reading the chat right now
apparently someone was AFK all night
it's fine we roll with the
punches we will be rolling with the
punches um
I don't know are they planning on doing
something about it should I be in the
call does Noone know if I should be in
the call I want on to chat before but if
they're planning on taking measures
around this or unless they're planning
on just they're B are they balling are
we
balling it's okay okay if we are just
balling what the hell is in here someone
in here I was not playing yesterday I
was doing my what the [\h__\h]
this
normal that's a
pig
what is it just sitting there is
chilling what's happened to the
game what's wrong with this house is
this house haunted what's going
on why
what what's going on
here hello buddy oops missed that um
hello
G this is solo time real quick um why y
would you guys I am feeling a little
weird today as in my body has it it
almost feels like the chills but it's
not really the chills and I don't feel
anything regarding like my throat
or but it's my body oh
my there's a pig
loose what the
hell I can
jump you you can
jump hold on let me let me kite this cut
this pig real quick oh my goodness
I missed this pig is
crazy why does it have so much why does
it have so much HP how does the pig have
so much
HP I'm losing everything I'm losing it
all
die please please
die please I don't want to die to
Pig does the HP scale with days I think
there's a difficulty scaling okay it
died um yeah so sorry if I get a little
low energy I'm conserving my energy just
in case I am getting sick I don't think
I am but we can't deny that I am feeling
weird it's like you know the feeling
where your body is really sensitive and
then you you like you touch something or
you're just like sitting there and
you're like why why am I so like like
the cells inside my body are fighting
off whatever is happening it feels like
that what is going
on
die why are you running all of a
sudden
so seeing as we only have
what 4 days left on this
server I have not played this game like
I played this game when it was in Alpha
years ago I think the last time I
actually played this game like minus
when I played with CC was 2018 and then
I played after 2018 for the first time
when I was playing with CCE so I don't
actually know the meta strats of this
game but I want to reach a point where
I'm decked
out I want to try hard but I don't have
the knowledge to try
hard that was a long time ago this game
has been in Alpha a long time really
long time now it's out what is wrong
with this house genuinely what's going
on
here am I beating at come
in I am very
hungry time to bust up the wiki mine
life Pro tip with everything is I I
Google game
name min
max
Reddit so I don't think my skills are
too busted minus the one that I got on
accident actually got fortitude
fortitude's not bad but I didn't want
fortitude yet um I think I want to go
for parkour maybe level two parkour and
then we already have a lot in minor 69er
and motherload we might have to go
strain and then we have to get some in
agility and maybe one in um selfhealing
maybe just like one point in selfhealing
but we need to farm that exp hell is
this you see we have to
cook tools are these not books there's
so many books on here you're telling me
we can't read these books why
did someone was someone actually cooking
in here what is the Environmental
storytelling trying to tell me right
now why is it day 15 right now um little
oopsies there's little oopsies oopsies
[\h__\h] Wy boingle
Boingo it's okay we ball f it we
ball so
many things in here and how do you use
do I need a better uh
crossbow do I need a crossbow to use the
iron ammo how come I don't use my iron
ammo is there a
reason no hold R oh okay I will do that
when I actually need to use it I was
just
curious okay so I think today's goals is
I'm going to speedrun a bunch of
Trader quests and hopefully can get
to tier two of Trader Quest and get the
bike if possible I would like to get a
bike I will join a voice call and if
someone wants to join
me they are welcome to come
along okay I'm going to join the call
now everyone just to see what everyone
is doing
hello yeah she does
g what are you guys planning on doing
there's
a my God the going to us be careful are
we just balling me yeah we're balling
right now okay yes we're doing class
increasing our skills and loots we're
going to build a little house together
oh my gosh oh people coming in
you are a farmer you if you have some
time today can you try to plant our
super
corn yeah yeah I would love to plant
some super crops super
corn okay um if you uh the the super
corn seeds are in the new house next to
the fireplace in the food and Medicine
Chest um there is free uh ears super
corn don't take those just take the
Super corn seeds there's five of them
and if we need more with more grown ears
of super corn I can produce more seeds
because I have some recipes but for now
it's five seeds here you the question is
will the be at the new place nothing
cool in here um anywhere is fine I think
I got I got some magazines
though
magazin oh blade crafting I need that
nice life God I I have heard that the
second wave has already been finished
did it
yes we're
so we survived the second
wave are we still going to be using this
house for another wave or are we doing a
different house now well we might us
house because it's it's well reinforced
right yeah it's very well reinforced
okay so the new house what's good still
all right make the most of it oh my
gosh those lions or Tigers what are
those big cats mountain lions big cat
bigat I a big cat means big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad idea mhm yeah I'm dangerous it
better be are you guys question right
now are you doing a new
[Music]
location um B has like a treasure chest
and we want to go there yeah I have a
treasure map that I'm MH looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys
later right next to
you okay treasure is can you kill me oh
ah big cats I see the big cats guys I
found a like radioactive gigantic green
boar it did respa it gives a lot of meat
if you want to oh if you hunt it you
want to kill it heck yeah okay we are
going on expedition to the Northeast cuz
that's where the treasure is located
Northeast okay I am
around going this way we're following
bio bibu knows where it is it's it's
kind of a far track into the snow so
okay well we should be fine we're not be
careful
yeah hello my sweet wiv oh hi giggy
hello Gigi you have to listen to my cat
story really quickly okay okay so
smoothie one of my cats when she loses
her patience with me and really wants
food and then wants show me she wants
food she will purposefully wherever I
can see and hear it look for plastic
because she knows she can't eat it it's
not allowed to and then she will like
nibble on it and lick it and make these
noises these plastic noises forever yeah
and I push her away and she goes back to
it she does it again and again and she
will not stop until I even leave the
room and then she follows me and she
finds a new thing to nibble and eat or
until I give her food relatable very
relatable
really oh my
God I relate to the
cat relate to the
cat eats plastic when he wants my
attention a oh no I didn't know that was
a common
thing they definitely know when they're
not supposed to yeah that's so bad so so
bad
mhm but it also makes me think
maybe then she knows also since she
knows you not supposed to and she's just
like kind of like annoying me with that
she knows at least that she's not
supposed to swallow it and then you know
at least she she knows where where the
the line is uhhuh good it's not like she
actually wants the plastic she just
wants your attention
yeah cute so
wise I would eat plastic for your
attention
too no no you already got it you already
got it oh now we understand the meaning
should
put the feathers no
no you you all have my attention we're
going to do quests it seems the
Clementine okay yes I'm Clementine is is
cute a cute name yeah right the
Clementine is there any food I am so
starving I am also starving I feel like
we might need to figure out a food I
have 60 meat if you can cook the 60 meat
you have the 60 meat yeah I have 60 meat
okay I'm on my way to the house okay
meat went no oh no I found it what yeah
where behind it I killed two pigs and I
took it off their bodies oh W okay okay
nice we need that yeah we do all right
send that to the to the slow cooker
okay and do you need seed crafting
farming
magazine um I think yeah I already I
feel like I ate one okay I will put it
in the chest I think we should make a
Farm by our house because we're
struggling with food
yeah well I did tell Shi to take the
Super corn and and and play uh plant it
sometime today uh but if she doesn't get
to it I don't know I so making seeds and
farming are two separate skills right oh
are they it it seems to me like it yeah
I'll put the meat in here and I have an
egg
oops
okay oh I am oh I am on zero oh I am
striving to death right now I'm going to
make a bunch of bacon and eggs how fast
does that finish um Takes a Minute 20
each okay I'm coming over because it's
dead death for Life situation right
now I can make some grilled
corn okay anything I didn't know it was
why does it go down so fast and
apocalypse are just so
hungry I know they don't know that we
have to parkour for
food uh how long usually until you
starve for real for real I don't know
why are we all starving how did this
happen so hung
maybe because the we logged we all
logged out right at the apocalypse and
we were just so so exhausted from the
apocalypse you're cooking at our home
right yes okay good good good good I'm
home e a ducky
M oh welcome home you eating the food
that I was supposed to eat now welcoming
you home ah one corn is that
Grill
y
salvation a little
bit okay we'll fill our tummies and then
we'll go questing
okay gy yesterday without you we were
quite efficient too but I think with you
we are we are even more efficient we
missed you three times offici I missed
you too my beautiful wives I feel like
I've been in a coma for for two
weeks yeah I think you have
been fauna got so distracted so often gy
but she's also so Mo motivated she runs
off into random houses all the time and
punches things cuz she's the Fister
strong now my fisting has gotten much
better I've I I've gone for a week and a
half and you're the strongest
Fister it's true it's
[Music]
true she definit really is I did some
research into armor by the way like I
watched this whole video on every armor
set and so I think I found out which
armor set will be best for you fauna oh
which one is that it's like there's I
think there's two heavy armor sets and
one of them the one that's like that
looks the most hardcore that's the one
you need ooh the tank armor yeah see you
like tanking I
do I found this a Assassin outfit do
either of you want this a whole is it
just the top assassin out I do you want
AA um I mean I uh I think you can have
it too okay what does it do it gives
sneak Effectiveness plus 5% medium armor
rating uh something something stamina it
lowers stamina a little bit and it
lowers Mobility a little bit but
Starly why do I have a backpack over
here did I die did you die I don't
remember dying why is there a backpack
icon do not know why I did not die
yesterday on the
way no I didn't why why am
I there a mysterious backpack
harvesting
harvesting how do these how do these
magazines keep on appearing in these
chests so
magically we're so good at finding them
they just appear oh it looks like
everything respawned so we should have
like a bunch more nice loot nice yeah I
see loot in these
cars
uh at Salvage five repair five
not cook faster eat one right in front
of your
[Music]
facei oh this is rough maybe maybe when
we do quests we'll
get
farmer hi everyone Welcome to our home
our abod it's very comfy we've got bacon
and eggs cooking if you're hungry than
God oh you guys ever searched a
toilet oh res must
respawn oh they respawn I see cars are
um unsearched
again all right uh this is the new base
for protecting right so we should put
spikes here I think we're still going to
protect the old one keep the old one as
the base for the next raid until it's
completely run over
okay uh the farm is still at the old
base as well okay um it has not grown
despite it being a
weak oh he actually I'm in while you're
here maybe maybe you could grow the
super corn next to this house I don't
know yeah I need to
get I need to get Rotting Flesh nitrate
powder and clay soil so running flash is
also in there and I think we have all of
those yeah maybe okay I'll I'll work on
it then awesome thank you so much thank
no
[Music]
problem oh you got a spear stuff I'll
take
that take what you want it's fine
anything but I think we really got to go
questing soon to get like to find food
and stuff oh it's almost night time so
we can wait for the night have just
accepted the quest while I was out there
there is a quest is it GG's it might be
mine yes is my name tier one clear I
feel like we could we could do that we
should okay you guys invite me to the
party so I may the
XP I'll work on the farm in the meantime
okay wait thank
you oh you are in a party I think I oh I
sent I think I'm the party leader you oh
oh thank
you this so confusing oh okay I see all
right I'll set up the farm here since
like I'm already herey okay nice thank
you no PR hopefully this grows within
the next week apparently it needs
water have you been watering
it uh I have not been watering it I
don't have a watering
can oh that's also something you need oh
no yeah I thought I was hoping the rain
would be enough you know Mother Nature
at its finest I think so to how can the
rain why why doesn't the rain water our
plants cuz it's Arizona the rain is
alive
Twilight if only this was the Pacific
Northwest if only there was
vampires who could protect us I
know I feelg I was looking for I was
talking about this with Nissa yesterday
um about Twilight in Arizona do you
think that Bella's first time seeing
grass is when she went when she moved to
Fort do they not have any grass in
Arizona they don't I don't believe it
there's there's some grass if they do I
don't believe it
maybe fake
grass I just remember she took a little
Cactus with her that's not grass
random it's
pled for one you have some Stone Arizona
plant I have stone please share I will
come and give the stone after I hit the
street timber
timber all right here's hoping that the
girl the corn
grows super SED pray for the super corn
I put it in the
chest put it to the side of the
house I heard that super corn is not a
food but rather a fuel no no no no most
of the high-end food is made with super
corn oh is it like super corn
meal uh no like several Foods also just
grilled super corn is fine too I guess
but yeah I don't know they they listed
me a couple of things in chat before you
can
make
maybe your cooking might not be good
enough yet but yeah it it will be good
enough at some point no no your
cooking's great though I appreciate your
cooking bacon are
delicious thank yeah better than
Char thank you I've been working
hard Chad what else do I need all right
you guys want to prioritize super corn
right what about like you Uka and hops
whatever that is Yuka I heard is good
too I forgot for what but Yuka okay I'll
take like two yucas then
[Music]
mhm all right seven days to grow let's
go seven days to grow
coin yeah yeah once I can make armor I'm
going to make you an a farmer outfit
there's a uh farmer buff oh yeaw Yeehaw
I like how the farm plots kind of
it's
hovering well it
works pipe pipe pipe P pipe pip pepper
pickles oh we got one more
slot pipe I bet we can do the quest even
though it's night time of course a
little dangerous I think we're strong no
we will do it yeah we're enough okay
good luck you guys I'm going stay here
and farm SP right in front of me I
wasn't ready for
it oh yeah get him you you're so good at
F it's like the shown in anime Arc where
I time skipped I'm like got so much
stronger how much did I
miss I've been
reading reading up the ways of the Fist
I'm going where you girls are let's go
to the quest oh okay I don't think I'm
anywhere near the quest I just went to
this house okay yeah it's really turn
around
[Music]
okay anywhere is there more food that's
done
cooked there might be I would like a
little bite to
eat just a
little I'm also still hungry and thirsty
but can you do egg in this
economy I'm fisting these raw eggs do we
have any
water M you can
we yeah right as long as you're with us
we can just bring from the the sea
that's wonderful thank God for can you
actually Che from the
river yeah with her hat if you put it on
oh oh can you make more hats like that
then no I found a special part that lets
me do it I see I see see FAA because of
that hat is actual the real reason why
I'm sticking with you what what
wife just K all it was only for the Hat
yeah sorry it's all about you know
materialism and then using people for
you know my
advantage it's not true it's not true
it's not true F I can't believe this
after
everything what a
zombie potatoes seed let's go oh
nice Dam all right the farm shall
expand okay should we yeah go to the
quest Point yeah yeah Miss maybe we'll
find food on the way yes
hopefully zombies zombies
yippee
exp
yummy I'm made it to level 10 I need a
better ball oh nice oh you're so
powerful okay okay I'm going to Club it
in the head
die wait I think you're lower level than
me now aren't you don't worry I can
still protect you
die all right I'm going help I'll hop to
a different VC since I'll be focusing on
this stuff I'll see you guys in the B
okay y all right gigy lead the way um I
believe it is this way 1 km West oh okay
gy have you seen bibo's bicycle yet no I
want it yeah I was thinking of you and
she got it like you would that bicycle
the way you're zooming once we do our
Quest we're going to have the coolest
bikes too we'll be a biker
family o oh yeah we can have matching
outfits matching jackets The
Clement y yeah embroidered
bedazzled on the back like those
families at Disney World wearing
matching shirts a we Disney Family
oh oh oh zombie
careful never mind you don't need to be
careful they're so strong I'll put him
on fire
is thank you I get strong to impress you
guys that's my whole reason for getting
strong consider me
impressed I want your attention so bad I
about to eat
[Music]
microplastics
out show me what you have in your mouth
what is in your
mouth role playing as a throw throwing
cat throwing
[Laughter]
up I've noticed actually my cat doesn't
only do that with plastics she also like
when I'm still in bed and I'm just not
coming out of bed to give her food and
there's no no plastics around then she
will like sniff on the mattress and find
all these little like fur balls that
have accumulated and accidentally get
them stuck on her nose nose and then she
like accidentally eats it and she can't
get out of her mou and then she forces
me to pull like pull the hair out and
then I'm like this is so annoying okay
I'll make you food I don't think it's an
accident yeah definitely on purpose she
only does that when she's
hungry they're too smart
yeah is this a fetch Quest or a clear a
a clear Quest okay okay get the punch
stuff yay
exp let's see if it's like a repeated
Quest once again or if it's something
new prob yeah it looks to me it looks
new it's not on an area of my map I've
been
to at least for me
true and also remember that neighborhood
that we found yesterday
FAA we should go loot yeah we should we
should look in the
mailboxes
especially cuz that was a lot of nice
looking houses there
mhm steal their books I heard there are
bookstores oh that guy's scary that guy
got red eyes and he's
fast deer just now you literally one
shot I thought he was going to be scary
you're a
scary maybe maybe the enemies got weaker
because of another one another one on
the server oh she kept dying over and
over and then they're like it's time to
be weak
maybe oh level up I'm level nine oo
nice I'm getting addicted to this game I
just want to level
up where is parkour parkour there I
heard parkour was good got to get one
point in
parkour parkour what is that Ender um
the the foot
icon so I one one like life hack Quality
of Life Hack That parkour gives you is
that you can jump higher and then you
can for example you could put down two
building blocks on top of each other and
now you can jump that high so you jump
up there and the zombies can't jump up
there but they will go towards you and
you just stand up there they can't reach
you but you can reach them with a spare
or so and yeah you just kill them like
that help the snake snake a
snake than I'm sorry to my sledgehammer
the way you just run up and punch it and
it dies like snake meat no it's just
normal snake I didn't get meat yeah but
it's just normal steak H all the
same ow the nope
rope never seen a nope rope before in
this
game nope nope nope nope nope we are
almost there 80 M away let's
go let's see
oh oh this looks familiar but I guess
they all just look everything kind of
looks familiar in this game oh my God go
from the same
company there's
Golem
goem give me your ring give me your
ring he thought you had
it okay start the quest is this you okay
yeah I've got the ring that's why I'm so
strong
my
bres
my in
German have you watched the German
version of course that's like the first
time I watched it it was always in
German like growing up mhm mhm that's
cool yeah nowadays I would watch
everything in English but when I was
younger the First Choice was still um
German ger oh god oh two of
my
stamina there's more upstairs of course
there
is you're so
good my St I need to eat this I know
soup I found no no no no
help oh my God they're coming in from
outside too no I'm closing the door uh
oh I'm bleeding I'm going to die no no
no yeah I have also all kinds
of broken arm I was trying to use my
bandaid and I died oh God oh God oh God
oh God it's so over no no I'll stay
alive we can't fail this we can't fail
this I'm still alive not for long
oh my God the last hits sa me 8
HP I'm out of stamina they R so
fast oh
God got got did it get harder because
it's day 16 it might have yeah but it's
still just one
skull
yeah maybe we just ran in too fast
no I have food by the way if anybody
needs
food I guess
yeah oh like one piece
is okay a
start there's some bankon and eggs oh
yum thank you but did you actually die F
I died yeah I found a c
magazine all right
yeah although it's not there's still
zombies in here right cuz it's not
cleared yeah I think upstairs still
probably in the
closet I'm too I'm I can't go up
there
where may we downstairs too I still have
downstairs area which one was the one to
heal naturally again this
one ouch ouch a bird
bird out of all things now the birds are
coming and joining to kill us yes please
are you downstairs or upstairs or
outside I'm upstairs I went downstairs
but there's nothing down
here Tech
junkie Tech junkie a farmer outfit Farm
outfit yeah oh we got to give that to
Shian awesome too much J junk in my
inventory so much junk in your trunk
really really empty bookcase empty I
found the zombies they're downstairs and
chilling are you ready to fight
them yeah as ready as I can be right now
I will come down there okay if only I
had
ammo wait I still have ammo I can stay
behind oh they're right in this okay you
ready yeah where
oh my
gosh came from
outside there's one on me I'm blind I'm
coming you blind it's just so dark in
here I thought that was a debuff too
he's fast I know so fast I have 18
HP oh you're so strong you're so
powerful I have some Band-Aids here take
a take a Band-Aid thank you do I have
another one yes here go oh let's go
wrapping myself
up oh I have shotgun shells Oh
yay we are also we finished oh we've
cleared it okay but let's take a look if
we missed
anything there's an ammo pile here
random
Shotgun If you see 7.62 let me know okay
[Music]
not that much cool stuff was there a a
mailbox do you need armor
crafting yes yes okay I it's crazy I
already have so much in armor crafting
where are you I will drop it
outside you I have
24 oh my God you're almost at 25 here
you go 25 now hell yeah let's
go yippe okay then back to Trader Chan
yep yay and if we see shiy sometime we
got to give her the farmer out oh yeah
we should drop it off I have too much
stuff I should drop stuff
off okay me too me
too I'm picking up everything off the
ground on the
way okay
oh I'm infected oh yeah got to find some
honey oh there's St oh do you guys have
an axe cuz I didn't bring an axe I have
honey in my inventory all right I have
an axe like not a spare but I have one
where are you need something oh I'm with
okay there you are you look like a
zombie can you do something about that I
can't I can't I need new
outfit and we all need I wish I had the
one piece hat outfit H nobody put on the
Assassin's outfit I put it on I put it
in the chest in our house and I was
thinking giggy will put it on oh once we
get back I'll put it on can wear it I
found that just for you you know for all
the sneaking I do mhm should we go in
here but I will say the Assassin hats
together with the nerd hats are the top
tier hats in the game there's the nerd
hat yeah the nerd hat gives you P buff
actually I want a nerd hat but but the
thing is like the nerd hat is best to to
use during the raids cuz that's when you
get all the XP oh yeah and the Assassin
hat is good because I think it's got
something with
looting and that's better for like
everyday life in the
game I'm going inside this creepy
building this Three Star Building yeah
there is a zombie yes we must I don't
know if we'll survive that we will
survive I Will Survive we will like a
clown
car look how strong FAA
is oh thank you our dear
wife such a Demir wife punching
everything are theere patient kind wife
MH
oh you're breaking everything up here oh
oh the floor is not very
[Music]
strong here be careful or you'll get
stuck with just your
leg are you up there yeah nothing's up
here just
[Music]
trash some snacks how to go down a there
we go we the animations man they have no
climbing animation at all they're
running oh we going in think there's a
dead person in here oh there is a
dead two of them
even there's two dead
people why is it why am I weak does that
mean my armor is almost broken yeah I
think
so I hope I can make some armor soon
need a workbench this other one just
fell down on the ground after breaking
those things on the
Shelf he's dead no he's
not missed both of my point blank shot
fine books
please they got to have some good stuff
here come on yeah this is a three star
area oh
it's a little foggy in
here in here out here everywhere foggy
in my M that
sound there's three of them
there can't reload faster than that oh
it's so aw oh
no I tried my best so good want to just
take two dogs fting your legs they have
meat on them oh they only have Rotting
Flesh wo they're zombie dogs zombie
dog that's why I'm a cat person you know
yeah exp dep let's go I know I have a
Deb too actually I might have recovered
mine already I'm not
sure it does say beware of dog right
here chat what is that debu the 1 hour
39 what is
that it looks weird I've never seen it
before it was so foggy how are you
supposed to read that
far peti need Vitamin oh we have
vitamins at
home I have one vitamin on me
too I'll put it next to your bat I one
vitamin I need I think we go inside from
the window over here oh
there's somebody in
here you putting them out of their
misery
yeah let me in you want sledg Hammer
crafting skill yes okay I will drop it
when you join here it's right by the
window oh dear oh there's the doctor oh
the doctor is out
um almost there else in
here some glue does anyone want a blade
crafting
skill I think bi Boo likes
those okay what
just
oh popping pills popping bottles I had
vitamins too
okay oh my God I have a book for you do
you see this you should take
that I drop it let me see
it thank you wait where are you girls we
went inside just to go through the
window you 20% extra damage to knocked
down and stunned
opponents I'm getting so
strong which
window can you show me
yes I just ate a potato a that one
found
whoa is this a hospital mhm hospital at
the golf place I guess it's the ranger
station hey armor
magazine oh there's one in here too uhoh
oh die zombie
it takes me
like the whole time until you kill him
until I
reload I thought he was
dead there's
[Music]
a
armored oh let's go more more more more
almost 30 armored books here
too what going on that's the fourth in
this room cuz I found too H is there a
button that'll let us through oh you got
the
keys yes yay 29 baby here
29 oh okay okay
okay almost shot
for I'm always up in the
action what do we got a dog
again my arrow not
dog anybody in here for sure definitely
in the
toilet
many let's go okay I want to I want to
uh wear that what you find I think that
is the Assassin Ro good the good one of
the loot bonus
ooh
let that is one of the top here head now
we're now we're finding so many armor
things what the what is
that this person is dressed differently
than others
yeah I'm always hes cuz I I don't want
to accidentally shoot you guys I don't
want to waste bullet
either how much xp from
him no why did I drink it that was
accident I'm fatigued kit about to
pumpkins in
here oh wait don't eat them oh I just
ate all the
pumpkins pumpin don't eat pumpkins this
eat
this soldja D we're past eating raw
ingredients so hungry
bacon
egg anything else in here um no dead end
guess I can leave then
y now to head back home oh we can open
this door oh what it was oh touch the
key rack I've just gone in a gigantic
Circle oh you can go up
there
yeah a there zombies up here nah they
can't
climb oh they can they can climb stairs
at least they have no idea what they're
doing there's a parkour situation up
here I have just skilled into
parkour it's just like
civilization can you explain to me what
that is cuz I don't know um it's a world
where parkour is the main
currency yeah um like a Minecraft world
it's a Minecraft world and then they
only Exchange in parkour and then you
start off as a parkour Noob and uh when
you're a parkour Noob you either go for
the chicken you go for the
beef kill kill
beef or chicken yeah chicken gives you
two hearts of health and then beef gives
you three hearts of health and if you go
for the chicken every day you can never
rank up to be a parkour Pro so you
either live in complacency of being a
parkour Noob for your entire
life or you try and become a parkour
Pro you're so strong die die okay rning
low on stamina though ouch ouch ouch I
missed the point to blank
arrow wa we did it we did it oh sorry oh
God ow not mean the clip got be more
careful my
club there's probably good stuff in here
though it looks like
it passing gas sealed shipping
crate I actually need that pockets are
so full I know me too mine too but I
don't want to skill
into the pack me trade there's some good
armor that um like gives you more
inventory and
stuff lot of medical
stuff there's a magazine for medicine
what Med um yeah two people I think
does anybody scale into bow crafting I
will do it okay wait then I'll leave it
in this uh chest here
this oh there's a reinforced chest
should we break it open it only takes a
bunch of hits yes I guess yes yes no one
knows lock picking
huh oh no I'm sorry it's okay justy just
trying to find a good spot
this a good
spot ow we're almost
there I'll let you I'll let you do the
thing I don't want to die not by your
hands you would feel too
guilty
[Music]
oh there's some 9 mm ammo and bullet
casing on the table I'm going to drink
beer this will
help will it help are you drinking again
GG I can't help it 8 a.m. is the best
time to
drink we need to have a
discussion this no I I just ever since
we I lost my job because of the
apocalypse really hitting me
hard same same we're alling the same
boat girl
yeah I found this lifestyle to be really
fulfilling you know yeah grow our own
food it brings us back to Our Roots you
know yeah I'm just so sad I can't
provide for my wives anymore I don't
what do you mean you do
provide I'm not providing the lifestyle
you deserve Gucci P bags every
[Music]
weekend I don't get a
anymore sometimes a simple life is
better means more than all that stuff
okay as long as we have bacon and eggs
to eat that's all we really need you're
right I found a new perspective on life
I'm no longer
drunk I see the light that was fast just
a quick 20 minute 20
minute drunken session just was just
feeling the buzz a little bit
I'm still out of stamina though I know
me too I'm fatigued too I need
vitamins
what so much is wrong I have vitamins I
have one vitamin you vitamin can I have
it yes I'm trying to right now would you
do you think you would be able to build
a building
block
perhaps I want to go on the roof okay
and I'm trying it with aair here but we
have what's inside vehicle Adventures
does anyone oh vehicle
crafting I'm going to scrap and there's
ammo for you let's go and some B here
you can look
inside
yes vehicle crafting let's go nice ammo
I can help again oh I don't have any
wood I have some wood oh it's a bomb
here take this
okay uh I I shall take because I want
the
block
building building
building uh here take this armor
crafting armor thank magine another one
another
one okay I'm putting down the wood again
because I can't carry this much but
thank you okay I will take my wood back
my 1,000 Woods
oh actually I guess I need one more
block Uh Wood lady can you build one
more block and put it up there
okay here and
[Music]
vitamin thank you vitamins are very
important they are thank
you okay there was nothing up
here good good we just had to
know
yes all right then we shall not get to
distracted and go back home I guess yeah
got to drop off all our items yeah and
then do another Quest yes and another
one I failed this one uhoh almost fell
broken
leg how did I not break my leg careful
careful ladies maybe it was your parkour
yeah save you it could be it could be I
knew there was a parkour God out
there she protects us parkour goddess so
thank you so
thirsty oh we could go to a lake and
drink there's not really it's behind us
should we
behind should we go how thirsty are you
thirsty it's okay I'll make ity okay
but what about a nice picnic by the lake
you know we can make it to the one right
next to the trader that'll be
beautiful
okay I love picnics but my stamina is
quite low because I am dehydrated easy
oh take it
slow you can drink my Molotov
cocktail no no more alcohol I thought we
discussed it that's why you're thirsty
you're dehydrated my alcoholism from the
the 9:00 a.m. beer I can't help it life
is so rough but my wives are here to
make sure I don't fall back to bad
behaviors that's
right even though I just offered the
molotov cocktail the devil and the angel
on my
shoulder I just tested you and I'm
impressed by the results of you
resisting
thank you does that mean that's my man I
can have uppies
later
up you're into uppies I didn't know can
I have uppies
later Shady Slaughter I love
uppies I've been here before let's in
here there's another zombie I'm I'll
punch him two
stamina you're so good at doing that
amaz I just leveled up my punches this
zombie was just a van life YouTuber and
this is what you do to him van life you
all his subscribers will now be
wondering why is he not making any more
van life videos they can subscribe to my
channel instead
life but are you going to bring out the
same content I doubt
it I just had this feeling I heard sh
What the helles
voice is in my head she's been soaking
up our XP this whole time yeah it's
share the mushroom Mining Company our
favorite led to many broken legs
[Music]
here hisorical I saw a clip a perfectly
cut clip from your PO FAA when I was
falling down oh
no that was nice yes and giggy you
missed the most dramatic fight ever
yesterday with the boar we had the boar
I saw
you I haven't fought it I looked at it
yes you want to go back I know no for
maybe not for
[Music]
now so much me from it we died a million
times but we kept on coming back we're
stronger now and the stronger yeah we
did Super corn super corn I doubt it's
stronger it wouldn't learn from its
mistakes yeah doesn't have the
capabilities of
learning I don't want to see grace
anymore no no no no yeah is the Bo's
name Grace it's kind of a name who Nam
it I think so or whatever Bob from Bob's
bores Bob your Bor she's
massive you have a huge successful
successful but also failed I guess that
they didn't want it to be that big and
aggressive with the tiny boards I felt
so bad
for we kept accidentally punching them
when they were
just they were so exhausted I'm
sad you're so
[Laughter]
thirsty here where are the says y also
thirsty you're pretty thirsty on Twitter
as well I can't help it when you show us
your your your I I can't say but my but
yes where am I supposed to look when you
show us your butts I must dropped my
hat it's okay you can you can look at my
buttock all you want your hood is
getting washed away into the river it's
following her why can't I a string what
is happening you have an empty hand go
is there strings attached to
you
yes strings
attached so
thirsty you spam spaming the you bald
under that hat yes I feel like I've
never seen your face in all the time we
been
together a mustache too shaved not Bal I
like it oh Kiara your your mask is so so
cool too oh really I think I have
drinking enough do you need some Kiara
um the blue one is the the first right
your hat okay I'm fine I'm fine it seems
okay I don't know how but I
am all right
continue oh you can finally move
normally again gy yeah I am regening
normally
oh what that's your St no I'm not
looking at the stamina bar I'm looking
at the other blue
bar that one right there
m this game does have a lot of bar bacon
and
eggs you know who else has lots of bars
fa she does spitting them
yeah I haven't heard her spitting them
you didn't see her
[Laughter]
my I guess she spits
occasionally when I'm feeling passionate
about something when she does then she
really she really spits those
bars no joking with her that's right all
right
serious hello tra
magazine
[Music]
gotcha well look here boys we got
ourselves real selling magazin wants to
be
paid oh level up level up level up
oh my inventory is so full goodbye
sewing kit you think you're pretty smart
now don't you wait sewing I'll take that
oh it's on the ground
now I'm too much of a loot Goblin I'll
just crawl home if I need
to there's a buried supplies 400 m east
better take this oh he's selling
workstation crafting skills
books three of them do you have
[Music]
money not enough I can only buy one
right
now but I'll sell some
stuff hey girls when you look into his
um in his shop does he sell Forge ahead
by any chance for
you let me I will Che
probably he's not letting me shop can
only one person shop at a time I don't
know no I thought that was debunked oh
well he's not opening his shop to me I
think you just have to stand like in the
right way so evil for
that oh I might need that actually oh
well I don't know what to sell oh wait
maybe this gets me some good stuff
too oh
okay all
right I'm running home to get rid of
[Music]
everything he can you bring some money
okay like maybe 500 so I can buy his
workstation magazine stock I will bring
it oh he does have Forge ah head he has
two do you have the money my God two for
you and Two For Me Maybe we have the
same like maybe it has the same
inventory oh so if I buy it out he won't
have any more for you too okay
B how many do I still need I think let's
see
um I still
need
uh
six I think right where am I
going oh 10 in order to make one right
yeah okay six I need six more so these
two and maybe he'll restock while we're
playing the next Quest is really close
to our house yeah it is
awesome I want to make some
snacks oh but bird off bird supplies
chest uh quests are often bugged it
seems yesterday we just failed one when
we started it really yeah this one will
be better we see h not too far so it
will be
okay all
right I should also go home and drop
something off but I want to buy the
magazines well geky are you coming back
to the trader I can come back with the
money okay can you just buy the two
magazines and then give them to me um it
looks like there's
only oh there's 2,000 I have 400
go oh my gosh we're rich so
rich of course we
are We Are Born to Be
Rich we're supposed to be rich we look
rich the richness is calling for
us it's our destiny to be rich very
aspirational thinking I like
it put water in
here come on
[Music]
stamina come
on if you play this game for seven
ingame
nights uh oh no never
mind is there no there's no maximum
right this is like endless yeah I think
so
oo you can keep going until you get
tired tired of playing this
game oh I wonder where shy
is well she left our
party oh she wants no more XP huhuh
yeah I'm going to put her outfit in here
yeah we should tell her there's a
farming outfit she can Farm way more
that
now wow farmer outfit looking good I'm
going to I'm just going to go tell her
in voice chat yes I'll be right back
okay be
delighted gigy you use 9 mm ammo I use
shotgun
shells oh okay I I just added I don't
know if that is is that
different I I think they're called
shotgun ammo oh that's an outfit forgot
to take
this is that's an outfit oh oh oh you're
right we found that
huh okay I told her was she
happy yes she was delighted oh we love
to make people happy yes okay I'm going
to buy the oh the items yes
okay I'm running
off you go you go do
that
oh is there
glue there should be I just put some in
there oh I just want to like add on to
it is it a the bottom chest oh yeah well
is there like a theme between no but I
was I was just thinking there should be
[Music]
maybe well that will be difficult to
achieve at this
point yeah we got so many bones can we
make something with the bones I don't
know actually can make a bone knife oh
yeah many bone knives mhm oh let me
guess potato money this you have pissed
me off okay
purchasing which one Southern
farno what you want mix glue and the
what was it the the workstation magazine
I feel like someone might have purchased
it hey there should be two Callie just
bought it Forge ah head wrong chat
bought
it just I need this urgently Le sniper
right from under my no yeah I walk past
her then I only need four more then we
can have a workbench
finally I feel like it's taking forever
to get a workbench like it's crazy like
a workbench is like the most basic thing
in like rust and Minecraft and
all but here it's like a whole mission
it is it's like my life mission MH crazy
is she going to come over to us I
wonder she is at the traitor oh I'll
come to
[Music]
you Traer where are
you I never know when we leave our house
is left or
right up left right it's up left oops up
yeah yeah it's it's up from our house
when you exit our home it's up oh yeah
it's where you coming from right now
right yeah yeah yeah okay how do you
name a box again I think it has a button
and then you can click on
it uh oh e hold e I'm going to try
digging the
thing wait wait wait for us us I will
wait
oh no it's just over here it's oh okay
uh right here is where it's
at Wait f can you come over quickly I
see what's
around oh we're really low on
food wait is this the farm okay hold on
don't don't get distracted don't get
distracted
just quickly going to dig this and then
I'll go over to
[Music]
CI get this tree almost almost there
yeah this area this biomi is
scary okay wait I'm not here I'm here oh
dig dig I'm
digging do I have yes I
have show me where your goods
are is it usually like at the very
Center
of just randomly down oh I found it w
that was fast
yay can you get out of there wait is
this a thing where we all have to find
our own it seems like we all have to
find okay yeah it was like that with the
ow oh no they Z me I'll try I'll try
killing them oh there's a big one oh
there's the big one oh there one that's
SP
[Music]
is that the cop God yes he's
spinning
ouch what's
happening oh I'm dying don't don't don't
behind you behind you behind
you he just
exploded is this because we're uh
digging right now
yeah it's part of the quest kind of
crazy let us dig in peace
please I think you might have the same
one Kiara if you search down there is
there the supply in there
yeah yay it looks like butter
okay what the hell another one why so
many all of a sudden no
no yes are we running or fighting I'm
running run
goodbye run I want to turn in the
quest
yes I feel like digging quests would
probably be like not such a big reward
could it
be hello
hello Callie told me that you you're
very far on Forge Forge thingy K in the
old house if you go to the second floor
there's two magazines in the box if you
want them is it the ones that CI just
bought or SE separate ones from the ones
that cie has or no those are they were
mine I told you yesterday I think that
you could have them but I don't think
you heard
me so there's four in total say's four
in total maybe or maybe that's the ones
Callie is talking about I'm not sure but
there at least two in the old house okay
I'll see I'll see if and we'll see if
the trainer still has two yeah he G did
you check oh it's the Traer doesn't have
anymore
goodbye byebye because cie bought them
from under my nose yeah right yeah so I
don't know nice that she was or like
looking for it though okay now I'll
check in the uh main house or I'll check
later I guess cuz we can just go do a
quest now oh so there is two extra four
in
total I don't want to just just get
bacon and eggs from him but I'm so
hungry no resist take something more
special okay how difficult is it to make
ammo has anyone learned how to make ammo
yet uh no I don't think so I can get you
I don't know should I get this shotgun
shell but we don't know how to make
ammo requires a work
bench all right reward
and withit the Malone residence no no no
not the Malone
please we I know we can't be there
better not okay I've taken the Malone
residence as well did you yeah I take a
different one can we get multiple quests
try taking one and see okay I'm going to
take
Sean's he's giving me 109 mm ammo but
that's not the one I oh I have some ammo
for
[Music]
you I'll just take the 9 mm ammo and
hopefully someone will make use of it I
guess okay just double cheing if he
really has no more but I I want to buy
these
maybe all right later thank you let's go
I'm so hungry drop stuff off and then
go
okay I oh I have some food for
you I have food what kind of food soup
stock and can of chili ooh I'll eat that
actually maybe they have food in the
main house I got to go there anyway
we're going to take some of their
food oh the the main house is kind of
like where the like on the way no the
fetch Quest is on the way to the main
house Won't Anyone think about the
Clement we're hungry
too we are oh we got the super corn
growing yeah it will it will one day it
will serve us well and everybody will
want it we should try to get a du
collector too
maybe yeah I guess so I think it's not
that expensive we just need what is it
duct tape pipes and plastic oh easy we
have that's yeah maybe we should make
one wait someone's saying I can already
make a forge now a forge yeah but not a
workstation right what can I do with a
forge maybe I should make a forge yeah
maybe you can make some stuff with the
forge I don't
know it seems I can make it with the
right
ingredients maybe with that you ah I
smelt stuff with it okay and with the
ingredients that I smelt I guess I can
make the arm armor too perhaps I put the
food in the food
chest thank
you wait I'm coming to her house too I
would also love some
foodit hungry by
default
um hold on how do you make the
do
collector duct tape iron
pipe we only have one duct tape
nah we have more sure we have more it's
just not organized yeah I have two duct
tape but I also need for the forge oh
yeah for the forge I need free duct tape
and free Iron pipes ET okay we can make
the the forge
yeah then I need there one more duct
tape here's duct tape and this wait you
can make duct tape somehow oh wait I can
make duct tape so
talented what else I keep on forgetting
uh one woodlock how do we get a whole
woodlock because I've only
seen that we can Harvest like wood um um
like boards oh I can make one oh okay
yeah it's 10 wood for wood log oh
ah do you need to try
now yeah let's just make it now do you
have any more cloth kiaha CL here's my
wood L if you if you see something in my
chest you can take it okay I don't see
any I'm just missing
okay if there's nothing in there then I
don't think I
has that's okay I will find it is it for
the water
thing yes
H oh we have stuff up
here a
forge Forge ahead
wait can I actually cut up our couch to
get cloth well maybe I shouldn't cut up
our couch sounds will we some else we
can go to their house and take their
couch oh this thing is
huge should I put it inside or
outside could put it upstairs if there's
not room downstairs get rid this I'll
get rid of the kitchen table
yeah this is a good space for
it
woo
here
[Music]
wow where is
that the Harrison have to have a couch
right yeah I can rip
apart this house next door must is this
the Pig house oh it's Bob's house Bob's
house is kind of
scary oh this house is so nice though I
don't want to destroy their stuff wa
let's just destroy Bob's house I'll make
sure it's safe over
here taking out his truck section turn
on the oh it's a leather couch they're
too fancy they have a leather couch
couch uh
uh do we have something use I've got
ceiling zombies
here expected of such a bougie home I
know you can afford ceiling zombies
too oh where it go
what is
around pile of
books fishing
book wait where are
you I'm in um the Harrison's house oh
okay just
reading yeah I'm looking for
cloth how do you take apart their couch
do you need a tool for it I don't know I
just smacked it with my uh my axe but it
didn't give me cloth only leather may
maybe this one's made of
cloth okay I'm at Bob's house looking
for a
couch care why was so desperate for
cloth now we need duct tape to make a do
collector
yeah it is true it is true B I am going
to kill your pigs for
food sorry Bob sorry curtains are also
good holy cow I just one shot it oh I'm
so
hungry ah don't worry I just killed a
pig if I can oh no oh
no what is this room for oh my gosh
there's just a folding chair in the
closet it's the timeout
Corner let's see I'm
[Music]
starving oh I better get home I'm
starving I'm back home F your presence
is missed is there any food in I already
searched in here I think there's in our
home there's one can of chili okay and
one sham
sandwich just get this pig you'll have
so much
food is true he died in a cage and I
can't kill it why are raw eggs in the
output of the cooking
pot shouldn't it be cooked
eggs you can put them back in the food
chest oh I just put them in there for
storing
oh can we not just boiled eggs I
apparently they're
bad they take water I guess it's better
to just make bacon and eggs a a Ain bags
Ain bags aing and
[Music]
Bon bacon bacon you put clay in the
Forge smelter then you can forge it put
clay in the Forge
smelter I got you clay clay clay clay
clay clay clay I saw it
somewhere clay there clay in the Forge
smell
in the ah oh is that why nothing's
happening oh wait do we not have
microplastics I have some do
you no no macr plastic
[Music]
sorry so is this number the
1945 and so on is that um like the iron
being smelted and like possible to use
I see so if I fill all these oh I can
only put two at a time in right so I
can't have like brass lead Sandstone all
at the same
time but I could make some forged iron
for now right that would be
good I have 60 meat
again
whoa we're safe you are
providing once I let go of the alcohol
that was limiting
I can finally provide for my
wives I dismantled our
car it don't need a hope we weren't
going to use
that okay uh I want to Quest I want to
go
questing we can go to the area do do you
want me to come back so you can make
food first though yeah I really want
food I think if we have food and then um
if I can get just a little more plastic
I can make the water collector okay and
then the quest I'm going to is um the
their house is on the way to it so we
can also get your Workshop books once we
do it yeah yes it's more like the quest
is on the
way I feel like
they fends on how you see it I
[Laughter]
guess okay then I don't know I feels
like I feel like I'm not doing anything
on my way
back can you get plastic plastic from
just a random house I don't know
anything see what I can do you can
dismantle cars or tires all right
um we might have barely enough let me
see check my chest again
chest we need nine more Plastics wait is
there some
upstairs trash has plastic
okay we need we need two more
Plastics ah that would have been good oh
I see I just went to their house on
accident I was not following the correct
Arrow like who are these people
are they raiding yeah they're going in
the house together I thought it was a
bunch of really intelligent
zombies oh I'm so
hungry were we not Princess pumpkin is
there I thought we were above eating run
no I didn't eat it we're growing
pumpkins
I found one duct
tape that's
good I'm scared it's getting kind of
scary yeah yeah why what is this
atmosphere oh I just want
some is this
plastic
h no my thing broke my a
broke weird sounds in the
forest I have enough okay I can make the
do
collector I think oh really I think so
God what's this place
again sker place
egg I'm so scared to go into thingsone
we wait this would be such a good uh
base because it has a water source right
in front of the house like its own
little Pond oh that would I know we
probably should have been nearer to
water source but we're also pretty close
to the Traer though yeah right I'll oh
the lake is right behind the
trader
yeah why is this so scary out
here I'm back with the
meat yay I'll put it in the food chest
here is 60 meat and six eggs go thank
you I will be right back real
quick okay
I'm scared
mommy are you come home come home no I
must provide too okay you must
provide we've got a lot of bacon and
eggs
now you okay no I don't have the
confidence right
alone I'm scared I'm going back
I can come with you now in a minute it's
just like there's some kind of Boral
audio going on in there you suddenly
hear the zombies in your both of your
ears it's like ASMR but the worst type
of ASMR don't like
it it
is I have way more confidence with you
girls
around I'm running it's so like time for
me to get a workstation cuz my armor
needs to be replaced ASAP yeah we do
have repair kits if you want to fix it I
don't think it's even worth it I just
need two more magazines if you think
about it two it's nothing we can just
luckily get those
maybe maybe maybe if we get
lucky two
of this chest and
then another two round randomly oh I see
the water collector
wonderful we are so good at this
mhm what did I come over here for ah
food it's
cooking food and the sense of
safety okay are we no longer hungry
welcome back it's cooking okay there's
one one is ready
here while we're cooking do you want to
hear one more cat incident I had yes
always okay so I feel like this happens
to any cat at some point but chunky
wonky she was like sniffing stuff and
touching stuff and she touched something
that had a sticky surface some kind of
sticker and she got it stuck on her uh
tail and the moment she had it stuck
there she freaked out and like
Zoom through the through all the
hallways and back and forth she was
like and I was like running after her
like stop stop let me just like rip it
off when she would just freak out and
not
stop it's so funny they freak out when
they have something stuck to their fur
immediately so silly they're so silly
they are
silly they lose their
minds microplastic eating
Rascals it's so cute
though I'm cleaning up the place I all
this this trash on the floor yeah I
don't need all this stuff this is in the
way but gy did you see the forge here
look at the for my God in our kitchen
like a pizza
oven yeah it is we could make some good
pizzas in pizza what if I put this in
there would you put pineapple on your
pizza yeah always I love pineapple pizza
I do like pineapple pizza this is our
pineapple pizza resident yeah we're all
in
Green Let's
Go does this make sense guys what I'm
doing here Stone as well what happens
with
stone oh but ah I still have all the
iron in here ah it took it
all the meat got used so
fast I don't understand why it costs so
much meat for two bacon strips and one
egg it shrinks a lot in the pain
know especially cuz they don't
differentiate the stakes we get from the
Big Boar versus the vulture for example
or even the snake didn't the snake give
us the same meat yeah
[Music]
crazy a whole first a
kit I'll take one vitamin just in case
sometimes it's handy to have one at
hand
handy an armor book here
too in there oh there we have a book
chest I didn't realize yeah I wanted to
make a book shell but I didn't know how
time to get
reading think
I see CRA why
not robotic didn't I have something in
robotic
maybe harvesting
[Music]
tool free
Salvage
11 armor
33 so high I real good
armor that's like the I bet that's the
highest skill anybody has
in are so efficient yeah I just asserted
dominance I said give me all you got
andai tax you cannot say no to me I am
the most Senai out of all of you except
for Cali cuz she's she is 2 hours older
than
me she was pushing real hard to get out
of that
stomach yeah it was like we were a twin
bird okay I'm pretty much ready to go
okay okay those two hours make the
difference I have three bacon and eggs
for people who are hungry
okay I think I'll survive for now but
it's I am good right now all right so
one of you has a quest right or I have a
quest all right two got two
quests then we shall watch oh somebody
fell a tree me I'm Timber
deforestation hey hey hey no
deforestation are you punching a
boulder getting rid of everything in
this
Forest I feel like con the constant
videos that I consumed today on YouTube
will change my algorithm completely for
a while because I watched a 2hour video
of like jungle survival alone with no
tools and then another one I watched
today was um some guy uh building uh
like his own office under his stairs
and
video the one where where like he made
the chair he couldn't get the corner
right yeah yeah yeah but then he was so
happy about the brass yeah yeah why did
you watch that I don't know it looked
intriguing
wased amazing that was so interesting he
used chat GPT to do math for him and it
did it wrong can't trust chat GPT with
everything I really liked it because
like a lot of these like videos where
like people build stuff they're like
only successful but he had so many
failures I learned a lot of stuff too
just it did kind of make me want to like
make something right me too I felt so
confident watch
woodworking yeah it's like oh even if
you mess up you could just slap some
bronze on top of it and but then again
then again that guy he has his whole
like workstation room and everything he
has a lot of experience with that so I
don't think we could do it that easily
huh no we could we should have a
woodworking Club yeah whittle a horse
for each
other what you know like the we carving
and we make little statues for each
other
oh statues of each
other what if they turn out really
un
[Music]
resid they're doing the quest yeah we
can't do it at the same time we can't
they're doing it we
what's
up they'll probably be done soon right
you guys almost
done it seems like they're pretty done
they're all swarming out
yeah or are
they got to wait unfortunately maybe
they just started go the other
one yeah it's a little bit far but it's
it's there's a deer over there we have
to kill it it's so active though a deer
yeah we kill it we can have meat can I
punch it it's going into the Frozen land
it
runs oh
go can punch him I think I feel like the
Frozen lands are still dangerous because
of the mountain
lions
Mountain it's the National Forest the
deer just go into the water and
drown dad is
like a zombie I've never seen before oh
yeah I see the deer I'm where's the
father CeCe has a forged ahead
magazine she said what in chat I think
so
whoa enough so that's free I haven't
used yet why haven't you used them a to
the
Yol a to the
Yol oh wait do you want to go pick up
the other magazines yeah we can oh wait
are they done oh are they done now no
they said they can't oh no
okay I can't hit this deer it's so good
y
yay y yay did they already clear it out
too I
guess are you still fighting the deer
yeah I'll get it I'll hit it
soon soon I I'm missing I missed 10
arrows on it no it's running
away run dear
run oh miso soup they left so much a
potato oh isn't the like cuz when you
start the quest the enemies inside and
uh respawn does the loot respawn too I
have a feeling it does yeah so if I loot
it now we can get double loot no there's
a zombie get away from my deer stop
that's M it's my deer KY come on the
zombie is eating my de I killed the deer
the zombie is trying to kill my deer
that's my deer for my
wives get off that deer you need help no
no it's okay don't don't worry I got it
I got it there's a wolf over there you
better be careful I know I looked at it
in the eyes wolf with red
scary oh God I hear something really
really terrifying next to me it's a
zombie leave it here alone you better
get out of there I need to
steer it's eating my there's a wolf
walking towards you with glowing red
eyes isn't that the one I want to
make I think I found the the helmet that
belongs to the heavy armor that I want
to make for you fauna oh it's very
terrifying looking it's not very
Charming good good but the crazy thing
is this it's literally in an in a house
that has no skulls no
zombies why why is I have a for head in
here what another one yeah I found it
randomly oh my gosh what then after I
pick up the CC ones we literally have a
workstation anyway here's the Rader hel
helmet fun your prettiness will still be
underneath there somewhere Quest not
available until 4:33
what what time is it
3:45 oh they need to restock the insides
they need to put more zombies
inside guess we can just Lo everything
around here they're all paid
actors it's not real zombies are
real I look scary you look very
scary I will miss your green hair it
made you so easy to recognize yeah
should we go get your books then yeah
let's do it we wait let's do
it um where is it where's that
way do you think if I hit the wolf it
will kill
me you want me to help you find it what
does it
drop meat all right it has red eyes
though doesn't that mean it's like
really dangerous nah I missed three of
my arrows on it
he looks really
dangerous I hit it I hit it I hit it
that was so
sad what about now is it sad now now
it's about to kill you it is sad oh my
God it's really
large oh I'm so
thirsty I'm
sorry I'll find water there
maybe oh it died oh that was
did you resurrect it did you just use
necromancy it broke my arm
I'm it's still L he running after you to
leave my arm
bro don't worry he's out on me
now my leg oh no how am I going to punch
with a broken arm oh I just realized is
that that
part's HP on the top left dead you're so
dead what did we
die oh my
god oh
no why why does it have so much HP I
don't
know ow oh my I have some help
you're speed up you girls got to be more
careful oh no kind of tanky ring up the
he's really
tanky I told you the cold lands are
dangerous I want to kill him I want him
dead I want to know what's on his body
you know what you can still kill him one
day when you're stronger you just have
to today today is that day I hope he's
still there the he's still there he's
eating your dead
body oh he's still mad he's still mad
but I'm
Healed uhoh no he broke my arm
instantly he's so strong I can't feel
this don't worry don't worry I'm alive
now I'm going to shoot my arrows at leg
and my
arm you'll die a second time fall look
at your
HP
did he too strong okay okay okay I'll
kind of I'll kind of I'll distract him
we have to find him together if we're
going to
find oh no staying out of this I'm just
going to go get my books and get
smarter what meanwhile if only I had
shotgun
ammo that' be nice huh you scared of me
I'm running out of
ammo oh
no is he still there yeah don't worry
I'm kiing him over these two
broken no it's
not let's get some water
food my de
though I'm sure he'll give you so much
xp you won't have any debt
anymore he broke my
[Music]
leg is it worth it is it worth it where
Su cost fallacy kill
him I'm having a feast here it's like
Thanksgiving meanwhile you girls don't
worry he's resetting our house he hurts
he really
hurts oh I feel so good here broke my
leg he's dead he's
dead maybe some more bacon eggs so easy
what did he drw um
steroids um do you want te I have
shotgun ammo and
7.62 ammo oh I'll take that and
Mining I will take the art of mining do
it here do you want whatever
here chest I'll take the
steroids my poor leg let's go is your
leg broken
too what a
shame at least we have broken legs
together two broken legs between the two
of us
yeah wa Is This Real
Time 1 hour 24 minutes please no we need
a
split yeah kiaha you can come back and
we can start the quest oh to you girls
okay yeah
[Music]
yeah okay and then when after the quest
maybe I'll uh or oh later is fine too
sometime during the night when we are
not doing any Quest I'll make the
workbench or when we got when we're like
reloading stuff or so whatever when we
have time and then I can make armor
what do I need for making a workbench
anyway
workbench I will need mechanical Parts
duct tape nails woods and forged iron
perfect I think all that oh is our our
doctor left wait did she
leave your doctor our doctor our
doctor she's still in a VC but mhm is
she offline
M why do you need something from her I
need a splint
doctor well I'm also a doctor in
training I could get a few more books
call
911 Moy
mhy could probably infiltrate her
VC I'm worried she logged off for the
day I don't know I don't want to bother
her if she's not streaming she alone in
there yeah maybe she just needs a moment
this job is
stressful it's true smoke break on the
job wait maybe I can make a
splint if I have W duct tape I think you
can do everything fauna that you set
your mind to people say Cece's done for
the day we have broken legs I think I
can
make with wood and duct tape
I have two duct tape do you have wood
can I have duct tape 1,000 wood here for
you that's a lot of I have another
thousand in my inventory don't
worry oh do you have any chopping those
trees I have five cloth fragments I'll
make you a splint I'm glad we could at
least have broken legs together do I
have there you go thank you for this
Flint try that try that out
doctor I'm Healed I have a 40 minute
ailment now I'm healing
recover wa let me give you your wood
back that was worth it I would say yeah
we got so much xp
steroids a
book
yeah um soup
soup tea so
much barel extender mod
schematic I don't know what that is you
want that no idea I'll carry it for now
that sounds like something for a
shotgun increases damage range and aimed
accuracy for my shotgun
I'm typing
the no no no
barely
barely what's in
here or who's going to disassemble their
car they don't need anymore who's
driving I'm almost there 100
m what does Callie mean I should make
the ammo or is she saying she's going to
make the
ammo um how do I interpret that I think
she's going to make ammo oh sick I don't
know that's how I would interpret I'll
get real busy with the armor making
probably yeah all right I'm here where
are you right here oh there
okay let's begin wait wait wait okay
okay we are in did I get it yeah we got
it the SUV change is blue
now that's
happened oh I'm trying to get up here to
search this pile of garbage I wish they
would give us different quests we're
always going to the same
places yeah maybe we need more better oh
there's a guy up
here I can take him though why did I why
did I why did I do that don't worry wait
wait wait wait wait distance oh there's
some more guys I can take them even with
a broken
leg our healing
leg Yeah I need to distance myself from
these toxic
interactions no no no no I said distance
distance dist
distance dead dead
okay soon to be dead nice shot in the
neck gigy yeah he's dead now he's will
be dead soon he can got the jumping
sounds like there's some stuff going on
down there
I'm just looting the
attic I'm get no it's calm it's
calm I'm just babying my
leg I'm going into the basement Who's
down
here
anybody beautiful
me too oh I see him
now meow meow there's two of them
somebody there is the kitty kitty there
no there's just like pictures of cats
really who's cat who's developer finally
cat pictures I thought they were only
dog pictures and bird pictures but
finally some
CH oh I found a stash
I forgot we were doing a
[Laughter]
quest you just get so into your blood
lust I know I'm just here to punch
things oh no I like how it explodes once
you're done looking at them
explodes the pictures are photos of the
death's pets oh we have the confirmation
I knew it I knew it
thank you those are
cute
n where the rest of them W my curier S
oh someone else's I think it's really
badly H like hidden in a way that I
would normally never find it no I found
it by accident is this someone
else's I forgot we to find supplies up
here up here you forgot you were on a
quest too I thought it was a clear Quest
oh there's the K I got it meow meow oh
they're cute two of them two of them oh
I have a medical journal for you soon to
be
doctor thank
you looks dangerous hey have you been to
the attic yet yes I don't think there's
anything left up there you can go if you
want maybe there's a courier Satchel
though oh true there might be
I you forgot an important thing for oh
you didn't open the shipping crate
there's a shipping crate I'll take
it oh there was just ammo that I can use
oh this is a different attic than the
one I was in this is not my attic it's
not my I wouldn't ever miss something
important like that
get hammered cat food thank you or
they're cats yeah for us
now tuna I'm going to have
to where is my career
Satchel is it
downstairs I'm also very
cucumber does somebody want to take some
of my stuff
I am also very cucumber I am also try to
consolidate
though uh how heavy I wonder our
magazines one
space Oh Oh It's about spaces not the
weight yeah oh wa the f I read my
cooking
magazine oh I would love
to it's about as heavy as 1,000 pieces
of wood here in this cooking magazine
you will learn how to make
Austrian schnit pumpkin pie
no or kaisman how about kaisman pumpkin
pie I learned pumpkin pie in
Kaiser
kais
yes what is this shotgun Messiah volume
free oh shotgun I don't use
shotgun gigy use shotgun I use shotgun
point then I I think this magazine might
be good for you
oo and then haven't I already given you
a bow magazine before then take this one
too build onto it yes more bows wow
sharing is caring because we care so
much about each other in the Clementine
family so beautiful that's
right and there's a wait I still haven't
found found
my it should be may be behind you I
don't know it's like does it show up on
your map oh uh yeah I just tried to
follow it now but could it be
outside may
maybe no wait it's that way it's moving
maybe a zombie is carrying it is it
upstairs or
downstairs well it must be right above
me I guess if it's moving around yeah
right above or below me
cuz I checked the attic but I didn't
check the fauna attic oh yeah there's
another Attic in the garage oh but yeah
it wasn't in the garage yet let me check
out the garage the garage
attic so many why does this house need
two
attics I know save some for the rest of
us yeah my house doesn't even have one
attic that's good though atcts are kind
of scary feels like Monsters up there or
rats oh your Satchel up here kiaha oh I
found another one that doesn't belong to
me so I found two that don't belong to
me the one that you found is is it on a
shelf why is it over there no oh okay
wait then it must be the one you your
living room the ledge upstairs or come
to the garage and go up the
ladder the garage and up up the
ladder I broke their sofa and got cloth
you need that
mhm just break all their
stuff that's a living
room through here through here damn
zombies you live like
that across you
see they're hidden so
mean what if I break my
leg you'll be just like us yeah H we can
make you a splint like I saw that one
over there but this one you kidding me
we can
match
yeah okay we're done ladies okay
okay we can go back to the trader how
far is your quest
fa don't know how
far I don't
ladders come on now we're not amateurs
anymore the
a broken leg we have to walk back our
poor
legs I know oh oh still oh
no we're 21 more minutes yeah that's not
so bad I have 28 I don't know if I
jumped maybe I did is is all of that all
those broken legs are from your little
Adventure out there in the
snow no we were in the snow we were we
were at the the street oh yeah we were
in the street yeah not in the snow well
since you girls are walking so slow I'll
check out this house I'm going straight
for this
car murky water I'm assuming you
probably got a decent amount of XP too
kiaha for our our adventure I'm not sure
I wasn't paying attention did I get any
XP CH it was 1,000 for killing that
wol really I hope I got some I feel like
even if you're in a party when you're
not participating in the battle or
you're not even close then I don't think
oh you think yeah
oh playing scary music again it's
daytime what is there to be why is it
playing scary music I know only got
beautiful birds the sky broken legs
mhm you look like a zombie Bei just
walking I'm shambling cucumber when you
see a zombie in a distance and it starts
hitting a
tree
money all right I got I I killed one
zombie in that house and I got 300 coins
from
that that Zombie's Rich that was the
only person in there
wow now I'm walking slow
too I mean how bad is
sprinting it just makes it go back up
what happens I'm going to hover over
splinted
lay oh your max health is lowered by
13.5 so we keep sprinting we are missing
13 Health well I'm still at 100
yeah it's not too
bad
zombie all that money is not going to
help you after your a zombie what are
you going to
buy do you notice how we spawned in like
completely naked with no belongings
isn't that weird that is weird what were
we doing before the
apocalypse don't ask questions you don't
want the answer to I think this is
protagonist syndrome
protagonists always kind of start like
that don't they mysterious but you know
scientists are still doing studies about
it and just not figuring it out yet but
they're getting there we're slowly
Gathering more
information I have caught up to you oh
no gra we're next to more minutes this
is so cute you two seem like like twoo
old married like 90-year-old people who
are taking a really slow hike a really
slow hi should we visit
Grace no no cuum would be sweet wouldn't
it where
cucumbers carry
anything salvation there I I do wonder
if the boards respawned oh I killed a
few so they might not have respawned oh
but the big one probably did yeah the
big one is down
there I have not
I did not try touching it I just
left that is quite the
cliff we're just making our way one step
at a time why is there a cliff when I
have a broken
leg you're rude inconsiderate maybe
somebody did a digging Quest right here
and they just couldn't find
it looks like it they up a home Mountain
yeah I can't believe it's like 30
minutes of real Lifetime and then I know
you don't heal it's two hours of real
lifetime will you now maybe rethink your
choices and regret your actions I'm
happy we killed that me too it was so
worth it it made me feel really
accomplished like I CH something yeah I
would do again if I saw one I'm shooting
me too I'm punching next time maybe I'll
help you so that you don't have to
suffer so
much oh wait wait you have some shot
some some sh some 7.62 or whatever for
me right maybe when you catch up with me
you can give it to me I have
26 awesome I also got 66 9 mm but you
don't use those oh no
does anyone M I think so yeah I saw some
girles but I never get shotgun ammo
drops never now where the shotguns
at
CRA I know I wanted to make you a nice
shotgun when you came back but I I I
couldn't I want have a gift for you wel
you back
Angel we finally have my a workshop 17
days
in well can we minus seven from that 10
days in
crafting trador F have you also been
reading Knuckles crafting books or
there's Knuckles crafting yeah I guess I
should you should I have to too oh thank
you oh let's go armor and I got handgun
crafting this for
you now you did the job I I'll drop you
the Furious
Fist three random these are exactly what
I
mean thank
you oh I can get new
weapons
coin listen up jackass talk to this guy
standing there for I'm going home you
have work to
do okay see you at home open these three
random crafting
books what you man now he's giving me
like good stuff like too much good
stuff here's two armor
crafting bye thank
you I'll also buy one just for
fun he's selling medical
journals oh
do I have
money I have $100 only we have 2,000 at
home
wow
nice um um bad news the fetch Quest is
in our house so hopefully those zombies
don't break
our oh no but we can maybe cancel that
Quest a different one so
easy
anyway why would that happen that's no
that's crazy it might not be maybe it's
no I lied it's the house next to our
house I guess it can only happen at
houses that have skulls to begin with
right and ours didn't yeah yeah yeah we
just have a random house okay you
shocked me gigy you shocked me you
scared
me all right I'm also on my way back I
took a quest by the way just in case we
need one later after
yours okay I have mine too it's a little
far though okay it's always good to have
it's by that big lake to the West oh
also oh wait the fetch Quest maybe after
the kind so close and I'll make a
workstation after the fetch Quest okay
yeah you're still so slow I'm over
cucumber and I have a broken leg and
nothing is going
right wait what's wrong what's wrong I
don't know this just something let talk
about it scary about this cruel world
why is your mid crisis I just don't
understand why when we loot a house and
we think we're doing so good that
everyone respawns and then the door gets
magically fixed right in front of
how you know what would help you and
fulfill you probably alcohol no
alcohol no no no in our house build your
own office Under the Stairs will that
help me yeah Dad will surely fulfill you
I feel like God is Playing Tricks on us
though do I need brass for
that we can we have brass we can use
brass we can cover up the
mistakes going to be fine geky okay okay
I guess I'll build my own office Under
the
Stairs yeah when when you're like sick
of our yapping you can hide I would
never be sick of your yapping a I'm sick
of what God has done to
us no we could have had a beautiful
wonderful life without zombies and
starving why did he put us here this is
true but it is a challenge and we we
have to go through it we'll get stronger
out of it we'll be stronger we can truly
connect in this world where we don't
have to worry about co-workers and
bosses and um and
offices except for the one stairs except
the one that we Robb and we don't have
to worry about the
HOA
yeah that's true I haven't paid our
water bill in like 17 days so wait we're
here now let's let's make the work
station okay do you want to help me
gather things together cuz I forget I
can only remember one thing at a time
what do you need how about four duct
tape do we have that I can make that
okay and 100 Nails we have it that's a
lot of nails 91 Nails oh I have maybe
some in my chest
too I'm almost home I have five nails so
we have 96 snails wait how many f h can
you make snails I have one
nail okay we have 97 out of a 100 Nails
we're so
close well give me give me the ones you
got for now yeah maybe try tracking the
recipe then it will show up on your
screen
oh amazing you can make nails and Forge
all right I have wait why does the DU
collector make dirty
water it wants you to boil it yourself
why is the do
dirty well yeah I think should be clean
don't ask questions God is testing us
the assid do oh no so Cru where are the
nails they're in the bottom
chest
chest I'm just dropping stuff sorry I'm
putting them all in the wrong chest oh
do you know about the deposit button
yeah but it keeps taking my 5 billion
Stone stop stop taking my five billion
Stone I do need my 5 billion
ston what else uh this
and I need a few more of
those weird these ones okay
four duct
tape four Nails
more oh we're so close to a workstation
oh my God I'm so
excited it's very expensive I have an
engine for our
car
yeah and a headlight for car yeah I've
been uh like collecting some car things
and throwing them in there cuz I also
have the vehicle crafting skill
relatively high so we can be the first
ones with a car on This Server ooh yeah
like a minivan for our family
yes would be so cute how much duct tape
do we need
four okay I will craft
it I'm sorry I'm very excited with
working towards us for a while
yeah oh look up some people might be
able to make nails oh I already got
Nails I can make them in the Forge okay
good I already made them like the forge
can make all kinds of stuff can it make
forged iron yes I've been forging a lot
of iron you have some oh yeah how much
do you need um I
need 12 easy
take in front of
Forge thank you I'm going to get brass
knuckles so strong
about what about the duct tape oh duct
tape there you
[Music]
go this is the moment work table
workbench
oh bunch of girls already logged out huh
oh didn't they it's only CI and La up
there
oh I need
food do we have some food for shooting
food we have
some come and get
some it's so
slow okay which one's the Sorting button
get this
one Mo items to
fill
hey
hey we need to be a little bit more
organized it's hard to find
do sorry I'm just working so hard
getting us all the wood that we could
possibly need to start our life
together yeah why are you I saw even
your title says wood why are you so
focused on wood would I just love
hitting
trees then I you a lumberjack
armor oh I am a
beaver no cute Timber I have 3,000 wood
if you need any wood that's that's a lot
for sure I'll get some more don't
worry where did my workstation
go is it in your inventory
no
no where did he
go
where where it
go it was down
here oh
wait did you find it
I was looking in the Forge for the
workstation crafting thing but it was
just in the normal crafting thing in the
normal crafting window oh I'm so
confused I'm so
confused it's like as if you're looking
for your building block in your cooking
pot I would find a block in there in my
cooking pot just got to dig deep
[Music]
glue let me put some
glue it's it's already been almost 3
hours we're supposed to end it at 4
hours I wish it was
longer even though it's so
late I
[Music]
know I'm making my iron
Knuckles wait if you're Gathering so
much wood yeah uh wait wait sorry do you
need it for something specific no I okay
good I just like having it good it's
it's useful for the forge cuz I need a
lot of burning material okay I have
3,700 right now no no no no no right now
it's fine there still plenty in there
but good good to have wood at hand
anytime
oh
oh oh I can make a
glue baked potato is that
good IRL baked potatoes is amazing
that's true I would like a baked potato
IRL I wish I could like type when I'm
looking into a crate I wish I could type
in like the name of what I'm looking for
you can't right oh no I just drank the
murky water that's
fine what did I need
again I always forget chat how do I
know pipe
thanks it's always the
pipe did y'all find your supplies what
does she mean what supplies does she
mean I don't know
I guess she's talking to us right oh in
the quest that we did
maybe you mean our
Quest repair there we
go yeah we did do you want to kick us
off the
server yeah you trying to kick us off
right now
one more hour
please
yay yay thank you why can't I make a a
baked
potato do I not have the skills to make
a baked
potato it's ridiculous oh I don't have
fuel can you put some of your
wood my sweet
1,000 you oh thank you so
much don't worry stand back kitten I
have so much
wood you're the
best okay I have to go to an idle
meeting I'll be right back okay
g hi I'm going to get more wood your
thumbnail is so cute by the way I know
the person who drew me as a beaver is so
cute it's so
cute oh to be a little Beaver oh I got
the workbench yay this is the Glorious
moment workbench achieved best moment of
my
life oh ah you're a
[Music]
sweep no what's happening I placed it
wrongly now it will stay here uh oh
cool hey get your hands off of that so
curious what's in
there yeah I can make armor can
I all right oh I'll need a one two armor
crafting kits for every every single
thing I want to make that's crazy I
think I had a couple already acquired
one there must be more
elsewhere like what else would people be
using those
for uh
what
what does some does the old house have
any spare armor crafting
kits I make those
never
mind never mind you got it
AR just got to remember the basics
sometimes um okay armor part sewing kit
duct
tape all right we'll be needing a lot
more duct tape and swing kits
[Music]
nice my leg is going to be healed in six
minutes finally it's been so long glue
and Claw
glue GL
glue
claw I feel like
s oh one second maybe whenever somebody
wants hello specific hi whenever
somebody wants a specific armor they
shall provide me with two armor crafting
kits for each piece they want and then I
can hello what's going on Gamers hello
hello yeah hello hello hello
I there's a workbench here yeah it has
been completed but uh oh good you should
let me craft things because I have the
highest skill ah yeah you're the one
that can do it but every piece of armor
needs two armor crafting kits and then
10 claw frag fragments I have a couple
of these things but barely enough right
now I see especially like armor crafting
kits and I can make armor crafting kits
but then I would need uh like more duct
tape for example I need a lot more duct
tape oh I see so if you guys have either
duct tape or I think I had some duct
tape in my um I am also in need of duct
tape though to make a baseball bat or
just
the put in the Discord server so we know
what to give you and we'll just put in
your box if you could label it okay you
were doing vehicle too right I have four
vehicle magazines ooh nice
ni I see that um there are some
legendary Parts in here you actually
need those to craft the strongest
version of whatever weapon you have so
the strongest version of the club level
six you need one legendary part and then
the basic Club just so you guys know
what that's for I'm going to make a
baseball bat so I don't necessarily need
a legendary Club but I'm just letting
you know that's what the parts are for
okay yeah oh shotgun weekly let's go
where are you in the house there ah yeah
take magazines if you need B do you want
to go together to base again to drop our
crap or do you want yeah I'm going I
want to go to I want to go back to the
quest Quest or not the quest Quest the
new house I want to go to the new house
I have oh I'm muted no you're here I
hear you hi you're here yeah I have uh
something for you I think one oh you do
oh I give it to you now that you're here
I leave oh I am not I am not at the
house yet you can put it in a chest
though and then I'll grab it if you if
you go it does says that you right there
next to oh no wait no no sorry that's
morning never mind yeah I'm pretty far
but you can put in a chest or something
okay okay what is
it h no it's nothing it's just like a
Knife Guy the magazine
and she's going to shake even harder
people where are you right now I have a
we're at like the the desert or
something we're coming to the the the
new house though we're coming hey K I
got stuff for you too Kiara hold
up you in the house oh yes oh good gosh
why is it so hard to control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it's it's um it gradually
reduces its durability as you use it so
you're going to have to thing I wanted
to give you I think I don't know o thank
you oh no awesome help you I know you
you like I've never Tak care of a bike
before oh wait how do you do that I'll
press what was that yeah I hear scream
there screaming screaming ladies are
coming watch out oh small raid much F
maybe yeah it looks like a small is
coming
a already
blind yeah there are a lot of them we I
I will help
you I'm punching them let go let's do
it hi beibs
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride together yeah in the
forest
Canada yeah this
ones freaking
reloading oh yeah I do it's a peaceful
peaceful existence in Canada and uh she
just killed someone so
peaceful yeah the most peaceful o
loot yeah I wonder if these guys drop a
ton of loot I got one
they're not really dropping much at all
except exp which is good come on drop
something you
fools H behind here yeah hit him yeah I
got him Bo with the BN stick are they
outside I'll park my bike next to yours
there we go oh
okay
hello h Hello that lady looks like give
it to you this
all right this club is extremely strong
now okay I lost
mine I think I need to go now everyone
so thank you so
[Music]
muching
byebye this
I'm okay you made everything respawn so
it's awesome yeah it was
good really it was
done
yeah byebye everyone
seee you got a bicycle too yeah I got a
bike and we met the new Trader there's a
new Trader oh yeah yeah yeah she's nicer
too as she kisses you what no she saids
that she could kiss you if you if you um
what is it if you get a bike and tier 2
quest uh you can talk to the guy and
he'll give you a special dialogue to say
like special Quest and then he'll give
you a quest to visit the new trador ooh
yeah yeah and she's got more stuff I
made a bunch of bandages you're blocking
the uh the
entrance yes okay I'm at the start
Point okay we go I fail
oh it took too long I guess I'm just
looking do we not have any leather at
home a lever maybe I have to make it
craft
one you're so smart but
no I have stuff for you okay here's
vehicle oh leather we do have leather
right um
here's thank
you I have 100 leather there you go nice
yes please I'll give it to you in just a
moment I'm I have to run to the old
house really quick to get duct tape I'll
bring my duct tape too do you have a
storage uh in here Kiara yes mine's over
here uh in the living room of ceiling
okay I'll just TR find it as long as
it's named over here here okay okay all
right I'll name it for you it's okay I
got it oh thank you no problem wow the
archive are doing archive in things
archiving o by the way we did um plant
the super corn yeah yeah it's planted it
should be growing or done growing
hopefully I think I might have messed it
up cuz I punched it and I only got a
couple
seeds to punch it though you get it or
not but you should punch it
right I can you can punch it
farmer yeah I mean you don't turn
guaranteed it's like 50% depending on
your level
probably so punch away as long as it
says it's not
growing for now should we all get into
the same party do you think okay yeah
there's about less than six of us I
think maybe about oh you're leader right
now so I think you can do that oh okay
yeah I a lantern
do we have a crafting table down yet or
no yes yes it's in the kitchen in the
kitchen
okay but yeah if you want to make armor
then you should probably leave it to me
I think I can make weapons with it too
is it scary outside it's a little gloomy
it's night time it seems scary ah she's
running oh yes our spiky house spiky
house it's very powerful
very hard to get into for
zombies and
R
ra no Shi is already wearing the farmer
outfit as far as the farmer are you yeah
yeah I'm wearing it good it's scary in
here when it's dark I a random door in
here I'm coming I have candles here I'll
put in the mood lighting I can
H I can make ammo wait are you girls
doing the F right now I I can make Quest
how I put it I'm coming
over the clear the area Quest do I supp
Quest
oh well I'll just go where you are okay
I can make I can make all types of ammo
now really how did you do that uh I I
have the skill for it I guess oh
oh ammo for
[Music]
everybody zes look at
them owie guess you can only put on
surfaces but you didn't start the quest
yet did you no just them in here okay
okay almost
there so easy when I have corn such a
strong Fister on my side that's right
oops pumpkins there's some good stuff in
these
cabinets I can make pumpkin
bread pumpkin bread looks so good in the
game that I went out and bought
ingredients to make pumpkin bread in
real life and
I'm this is the made me so hungry it did
I had to have it in real life can we
come over and have some that sounds so
good yay send a photo of your pumpkin
bre you guys doing a
t he's fast oh you're doing a class I
can join you yeah yeah I see um most of
them there too by the way uh my don't
you have to add everyone to the same
party I'm trying to I sent the request
just SP and join theirs whichever
works in the quest right now so you have
to wait yeah okay okay I'll just uh join
that then yeah let's merge and Quest
together since I think there's five of
us one two oh crap I I failed a quest oh
it's cuz we dropped the party I guess
yeah uhoh oh that's fine that's fine
that happen find our supplies yeah I
found also one I forgot my bike not mine
there's a biker gang in here
I forgot my bike I'm already running
they're all
upstairs W hungry so anyway I started
laughting get him oh can you guys add me
to the party me too please oh I
mid you mean are we wait until after cuz
you the same location as I am okay
you're sker Place yeah yeah yeah oh what
the you a s Zombie
we red
one pretty lady go around the corner
there's a courier Satchel here one of
yours might be
mine invite I think mine is upstairs I
forgot we were on a quest again I Wasing
and punching I think there must be an
attic cuz I think mine's
[Music]
down all right I'll wait for you beibs
okay I'll
coming yeah you still got to get the the
invite
anyway in here look at you and your bike
I had a walk here just like I thought I
thought you had a bike is that a actual
zom oh I I left it oh it's just there I
left the by accident what oh okay I
think theyve already
started something went spat in there oh
yeah oh uh
sry should be
great ohy water nice a kitty there's a
cat picture in here a different one the
same as before a different
one A orange cat's
[Music]
Behavior new stone spear oh okay found
mine oh my God what a cute cat I know is
there an attic I'm so upset we can't
take the cat pictures and decorate our
there was yeah I was going to steal some
lovecraftian
thing I'm not sure if yours is up here
too but in the Attic that where we were
with the dead person person there's a
um I meant is that your no downstairs oh
a basement not sure
oh but I'll check upstairs again maybe
yeah it's like on a really high shelf
you might have missed it oh weren't we
merging since there like no I think they
already started so we have to do waiting
for them to finish their Quest oh okay
okay there's like a respawn time when we
were trying to do your quest it made us
wait like 2 hours in game two hours in
game yeah that's should we do something
else then besides this
one um you see it I don't
I don't have one oh I see yours okay
yeah I see yours I seeand new I have to
break it
what where are you I we can just do this
one I have to break the kitchen to get
my oh but you found it yeah found it
yeah we can we can do this one for you
after they finish and then we can merge
yeah okay how about we do yours yours is
like right there and near
Mory oh true we are pretty close yeah
I'm putting some for you ladies H do you
have the Hat on uh for drinking yes
please let me drink some here you go we
can also join you guys on your quest now
we just finished ours I
didn't I invite you guys have you turned
in the quest to the trader yet not yet
no okay you'll need to do that or else
it'll make your quest
disappear how about they invite us so
that way they still have the
quest oh I want I still still think that
might affect it I'm
worried
yeah okay we can
wait okay I'm at the Harrison residence
if you want to do your
thing that's my bik I have a bike home
it's my bike it's my pink bik what a
cute bike thank
you ah empty hand
forgot don't look okay now you can look
I'm watching I'm
watching I'm watching I'm
watching pretty good pretty good pretty
good driving skills yes watch watch me
drift I'm drifting I'm drifting look I'm
drifting drift I'm watching She's dri
I'm drifting around the course I'm
drifting oh my go she's crazy I'm so
crazy look at that W she's driving on
the
inside she's um uh tracing
Ray tracing Ray tracing take so long
she's not disgracing
us I'm intimidating should I just wait I
think you just wait Swag yeah right cuz
it goes up okay I have my hat no no no
wrong
way the green
one I know you can't wait know you do
have I do have my hair out I should be
yeah I know I was just I don't know I
thought you were behind G or
so all right let's give back the quest
should we yeah and then we can combine
okay well we'll wait to start any Quest
until we combine so that way we can all
do our Quest together
yeahi I'll head now I'm use my baseb bat
ah by the way Kelly did you like wait
was it l tra closed right I'm going to
go ahead and end it here so I'll see you
guys next time yeah
byebye see you next
time byebye where did you say you
brought it to Kelly it's in the chests
in the new house the ones that aren't
labeled I put leather and duct tape it's
only six duct tape though fine but a
bunch Lea thank you you're
welcome do we have any food I'm starving
yes where are you um in the
forest I I'm coming to
you I'm invting you you want
level Jo a what a level five yeah yes
who uses who uses 44 guns me or I will
be them here take I I have a funny
magazine that if you like go to the shop
with your gun you will get cheaper
prices oh that's so funny yeah that's
funny like you're threatening them
Sil I have magazines for Kiara and
fauna yo magazine songs are
[Music]
rising Fist and rifle I love
reading reading is good for you reading
and fisting
yeah mostly fisting but also reading
about
fisting sounds wrong
it's a deep deep science so much I don't
think it sounds wrong you should embrace
it I too love reading about fisting not
only the act of fisting but reading
about it watching it I love watching you
f like an
art oh my Lord and then the chest inside
the unlabeled ones should have leather
and duct tape duct tape oh nice lots of
here's your fisting magazine thank you
waiter waiter more fisting
[Music]
please I'm getting so
smart okay I'm going to go make my nerd
hat my baseball bat looks so strong oh
my gosh I can't wait to kill things with
this melee for the win
and
then I have two skill points huh I don't
remember what the other stuff was that I
wanted got to look it up again
later ah the preach outfit was a like
the best uh
preacher yeah the preacher the preacher
you have the Hat of that I think yeah
the preacher outfit is the best the
what's not heavy not medium what's that
light armor light armor the best light
armor
set
[Music]
so Raider I want maybe like I don't want
to just make stuff on my own people and
force it onto them they should tell me
what they
out there we got to deal with her quiet
down where is she now
now ra that'll be no more screaming out
of
you there's a bird chasing you watch out
a
bird there's a bird out here is it the
bird that's screaming I think it's the
bird that's screaming
so
loud the dang Birds put it away from now
I keep telling them to do so oh there he
is oh okay just start
shooting Bird's
dead it won't bother us
anymore how do I take
back there's my bike
[Music]
okay what you making me yeah I made oh I
made a nerd hat which I wear I I feel
like I might want to make nerd hats for
everybody because if wear the nerd hat
during the raid you will get so much exp
a t
of we could all use that
tomorrow
yeah ah there's uh shotgun shells and
stuff in the output oh yeah I was making
those ah I accidentally took the 7.6 to2
did you make those for me
yes you nice you too nice you're
welcome you're welcome how far am I from
making level three
chat and how funny do I look
now so you look like a
nerd look at me want to nerd you can see
my orange
hair
nerd
wedgie I give you a swirly Kiara yeah oh
why can't chat not
oh chat if you want to see how it looks
like because chat is covering myself
just look at me I don't I look like a
nerd my life Tov looks like a nerd right
come on it's just like
you wait I'll show you
CH what a inconvenient place to be for
you here
wonder what I look like from the side do
I have like a ponytail or still like
tell let me see hold uh Pony uh let's
see yeah you got a ponytail ponytail
long ponytail kind of bushy looking
frazzled like you don't take care of
your
hair you know some days you're busy
studying I can't
take she's reading up on those
books and like the side of your hair is
like growing out of like the side of
your glasses and like above it it's like
a big bald spot it's kind of weird
bald spot no yeah there is kind of a
bald spot I don't believe it you're
messing with me bald bald no
bald bald there's nothing wrong with
being bald yeah true there's nothing
wrong with nothing there's nothing wrong
with being bald I just don't want to be
oh Trader is opening up so let's go give
the quest shall we go
yeah B
one day we'll all be bald okay never my
head will be full of hair forever do you
need wood I have
6,000
6,000 that's the max stat stack it's,
for my wood can you make another stack
yeah I'm making another stack I think I
canidate my wood now what is it if you
need wood just tell
Gigi I have so much wood don't even
worry
man that's a lot of wood I heard if
you're wood if you have wood for more
than 6 hours you should see a doctor
good thing you're training doctor doctor
can you see my wood
please you guys are freaking
mes my God sweet Jas is Joseph and Mary
nurse nurse I have so much wood can you
come out my wood I don't know how see
the nurse I'm quitting I'm getting my
medical license revoked I'm turning it
back when you get fired from Mal
practice so you don't have to look at my
wood um change of topic does the trador
have like better quests yes yes other
Trader has tier 2 Quest as well so the
quest you guys got going on right now
that you want us to join is that a tier
two yes no finally oh I have I have I
have two tier two Quest okay let's do it
then bio would you like a tempered blade
schematic a tempered blade yes okay I'll
sell you Goods but if you cross me
you'll meet all the Traders will give
you the max Quest you're eligible for oh
okay I'll get tier two here too once I'm
there okay can't say all tra show okay
okay okay good luck kid
um what's happening Quest started oh
here do you want armor craf right here
oh you guys aren't on my party yet oh
yeah one sec one sec
um see let me
see uh fun yes do you have um 200 coins
yes I actually how do you know exactly
how many coins I
have wait did you drop those magazines
for me too oh that was from someone else
oh oh I'm getting all these donations
from these
magazines all right I'm just buying the
last magazine he
has well thank you sir I'm 42 level 42
armor now nice let's go can I make make
the next tier I
wonder all right I'll uh leave
the group and then I'll uh be open to
being invited okay how to leave okay me
me too all right I am single and ready
to mingle leave to
mingle let's mingle I'll mingle with you
I'm ready to be invited as well me too
yeah I invited you wait
Quest failed is it the shared Quest you
just accepted yeah yeah it'll come back
when you when the person rejoins the
party don't worry all right all
right okay doing me a
concern oh I have
joined to Quest let's go invite please
I'm staring okay I'll send it again
thank you you might need to go accept it
in your there we go there you go oh I
have two work station magazines I'll
bring them to you kiaha nice oh oh we're
meeting up anyway aren't we
yeah towards the quest I'll just go
towards the quest and then which Quest
are we going towards I don't know
there's one being shown to follow me
okay I think it's the same I am
[Music]
following yeah we got to climb a
mountain we can do it
we just got a Skyrim horse it you know
easy yeah I'm pretty goat
like oh go you're my goat Gigi that's
for sure oh really my goat okay all
right that doesn't mean you have to you
really don't have to make those noises
if you don't want pretty good at
that not bad not
bad if it makes you happy it makes me
happy nuzzles into your hand and licks
your finger looking for some P I don't
really know if that's necessary I'm just
emulating goat behavior is that not what
goats do she's wild yeah if you went to
a petting zoo I think that's go do
something scary um flashes you my demon
goat
eyes I I have passed out onto my back as
goats do out of fear I begin eating your
liver oh wow they're talking asteris
asteris asteris peeing with words oh
it's the bore Barn
Fields oh
no we got this you want find on no it's
it's on the other side of the board a
different thank god let's run it
ladies all right let's go big
party
hello we can take him oh oh boy oh there
snakes snakes too snakes there's so many
yucky danger
noodle
nice
guys how
come these guys will be easy small
potatoes what's wrong with oh never mind
I got like the angle on it
this so fast oh ceiling zombies worry
not guys I am skinning this warar while
you are
fighting yeah get his goodies
oh there's a lot of them falling from
the sky
wrecked they jump so
high I want to fight too but there's no
zombies in my way
yeah go find them so danger they're
luring they're lurking about they're
falling from the sky oh hey there's even
another ladder to
climb Co can we get much
higher oh I didn't die I didn't break my
leg I was so
scared uhoh I couldn't be crippled again
for two
hours Golem
[Music]
Urban combat give me the shotgun
shells cooling mesh mod there's some
goodies over here guys if you guys want
this stuff and some ammo for both Kiara
and Vio let's go yeah I I failed going
to where you were so I'm giving up on
that cigar what cigars boost your
strength increase your barter ability
and make you look like a sexual
tyrannosaurus
what that's what it says for
what okay I I want to be a sexual
tyranosaurus I learned it tyranosaurus
what even is that I don't
know
Ty that is definitely what I
want you sure yeah I R the I mean I
respect it but huh
I want to be that that
person I'm
okay I'm
fine I also found a ton of gas cans full
of gas for when we get
cars so I'll hold on to them for
now at least I said it for you
guys I muted myself uhoh why me
not everybody has to hear such things
what things things no I'm
curious plays of words I see I think
that's just what the game was getting at
[Music]
so well uh are we done with this Quest
we're done how is this two it was too
easy I agree it was very easy I want to
find the big boar
again want to fight him again maybe that
wolf again we'll lose our Quest we
should we do the quest yeah turn in the
quest first quests are are
better do you want to do you want to do
my quest that's like right nearby sure M
yes I see it yeah I see it wait oh maybe
I don't know wait where I'll just go
where I'll just follow
you what's this one also a clear Quest I
believe
so clears are easiest cuz you don't have
to look around around forever for things
just kill all the zombies we have to
turn in our current Quest first right no
it multiple you can turn in multiple at
the same time just don't die this is on
my way die it's over hopefully I don't
break my leg again I think if you've
cleared the quest and you die you can
still turn it in oh really yeah as long
as you've cleared it I think that be
nice I don't know I might be lying I
hope so I think you can as long as you
clear it yeah as long as you clear it
yes no I wasn't lying I was not lying oh
are you joining us yeah I'm headed over
okay I'll
[Music]
wait this is a nice residence I hope the
Bor steal
it are those bors your source of meat
this whole time yeah that's where you
were getting the bacon from I get those
radioactive boards I have 16 meat right
now I need another board oh wait that's
pretty good though that's a good handful
of
meat okay we let me see let me make sure
I think we're
complete okay we are complete let's
go let's run
it oh just run
shooting you just blasted them
oh I have a magazine for you I'm going
to stand right here while I'm dropping
it magazine for
you thank
you beautiful flow you look good I'm
sorry that was not my intention good
looking
ladies we go up I wonder he hey hey hey
oh I we already in
[Music]
there a sham
sandwich don't eat it it's a sham Sam I
love
sham my tummy is
fine oh there's an upstairs oh
hi well let's
go oh she was working out wow
respect when she turned into a zombie
yeah uhoh so all that tells us no
working out working out I found a nerd
you found a nerd me sorry ipping
you a little too close to please be nice
to my friend ow the club the club it
hurts this baseball bat is so
overpowered kind of laggy I can make
iron tools now
oh we did
it Hunter's Journal Barrel extender I
want these gloves I'm taking them for
me pill sealed shipping crate no oh
here's some
shotgun stuff you found shotgun
shells yeah there's GG do you also use
shotgun yeah but I I'm using my bow
mostly right now so if you have a good
shotgun you can take
it okay
thank you there's um what did I find
here oh I have some bullets for
Kiara thank you some what what does
anyone use knife
magazines I do I use
knife have thank you and here's the
sledgehammer if someone wants to use the
sledgehammer cooking magazine oh I do I
do the hammer I found
hamers wield revolvers right B yes I
will be using revolvers later okay I'll
leave these for you thank you they
increase your revolver chaotic I'll put
it in our home later okay good job team
yeah that's it a it's so fast when we're
a big group it
is we all get the not fighting for my
life I like it this I like steamrolling
enemies a pool a nice house is this good
to drink sip sip let's see really
nice oh no it is it is not sip it is not
[Music]
clean see you're drinking chlorine water
do you need my hat what it's too late
for me I lost I'm going to get I'm going
to get be diarrhea do you need do you
need tea I have tea oh there's no
zombies here I'm
hungry oh wait I have a food oh
no thank you I love how you just come in
from
inside this guy looks like he's an
Outlast
yeah look like he's going to
explode okay that was fun think yeah um
let's return should we back to Traer
yeah
okay go turn in some
quests good job team good job good job
team no
casualties I feel like we could take the
board we could probably I mean we we
finished the quest now so you want to
take the boore let's take the
board all right we've definitely leveled
up a lot since then than ra
and we have stronger weapons partially
and more
people we go in all at
once yeah I guess we could be
strategical about
it or we can all just hit each other
until something happens we can all hit
each other get exp from each other wait
um somehow we're close to our home I'm
just going to drop off some things
really quickly cuz I'm cucumber me too
cucumber I have so much stuff in my
inventory oh you're here already same
fault yes cooking magazine in magazine
chest thank
[Music]
you should I just learn all these is
anybody hey chefs you guys making
anything delicious for us yes you know
how to make the
hoboob you really want that hobo Ste huh
how to make hobo you one day we'll we'll
get we'll get experience got a delicious
pumpkin pie see that's what I'm talking
about fauna makes the best pumpkin pie
in this land most
delicious oh I'm going to get you
cooking
weekly thank
you oh I can I can get a bicycle
now oh yes join the bike G yay so now we
can go meet the
girl I want a
bike me too oh I got to go to the quest
give it back do you have to give back
the other quests at the like right uh
Quest person or can we give back both at
the same person I
wonder I'm want to go back to give Quest
I will
get if you girls are going to the board
let me know okay I'm tra right now okay
step by step there why is there a hole
outside who who dug this yeah that's
kind of not very nice for them to do
that my bitee keeps getting locked in
there yeah oh I swear this is not a
natural hole I think someone did this oh
sorry yeah know someone did that on Purp
purpose to be
mean I have a feeling you know who did
that me it's not giving me a bike want
to give you a bike how oh he giving me a
bike never
mind oo I leveled up
[Music]
too my
bike watch out for the hole
outside Fists
very peace I have armor magazines for
you behind you Ki sorry sorry a sorry I
was muted I was like talking to my
chat what's what's going on problem I
feel like my server is lagging or is it
oh maybe I have armored for you oh thank
you my beep is just endlessly running
for me oh I'm in the I'm in the Traer
yeah but you're like running on the
spot I don't know
why did you buy those for me
fa um I got them as a
reward okay I don't have wait actually I
do have money now he gave a lot for that
one does anybody use like uh bows even
nowadays in our uh I think you do I
think and Cecilia also do I believe and
I'm also going to drop some magazines by
oh but is this magaz Chad is this a
magazine that you only learned once and
then that's it because this doesn't seem
like
a yeah yeah okay then I wonder if she
had this before if it's a one time thing
I don't know I'll take it for now oh
wait oh another one
whoa burning sh use the
bike uh you have to you can't place it
in here you have to leave the the
trailer area and then you can just place
it down and then press e to ride it and
then hold e to pick it back up again oh
oh I'm in the
hole immedately went out for the
hole oh dear someone is doing this to us
on purpose I want them arrested whoever
dug that hole freedom of a
bike a bike the world is my PR x x to
ding ding X to
ding I didn't see the bicycle I got a
bicycle
too special jobs he gives special jobs
now yeah that's the trader that's the
trader Quest that's the new
Trader I urge you all to accept accept
it let me go we can go meet her if You'
like
yes okay I can show you where she is yes
please after everybody accepts the
special job we can go she would have a
different stock for magazines I
suppose yeah she has a different Stu
than the guy such Scholars
here big readers ouch going to tra my
bicycle is red no no it's green ah oh
oh never mind but once we find this new
Trader maybe we want to get a new house
closer to the new trador yeah
maybe you can see me now you can see my
hat oh it's so
cute all right uh are we all going to
the trader gen yeah yeah uh I thought
that'd be cool which
direction that Way Southeast right yep
only about a kilometer
away with my propeller hat and the
bicycle I feel like I can take off
anytime nerd I'm a
helicopter this is the only helicopter
we're going to be able to get in this
game truly no we'll be we'll be able to
get a helicopter I by the end of
this take off in the sky yeah yeah and
then shoot them from the helicopter
where's a supply drop oh I hear it I
hear it I hear it it's only 400 me
away I'm going for it okay let us know
what's in is wait it's in the scary
Forest I'm still going for it oh the
trader the trader is in the scary Forest
anyway oh
yeah yep the supply crates are kind of
underwhelming though I'm not going to
lie there's not a lot of great stuff in
there maybe they get better Al so
depending on how far we are with the
raids I hope so after each stage maybe
better drop I hope fingers
crossed who are these Supply crates from
anyway um yeah Trader Jen she's doing it
for us cuz she wants to kiss us so bad
there's a big oh she did want to kiss me
earlier I'm on my way to watch
you don't oh there's a big hole I'll
give you back did you get it there is a
big
hole Yeah I don't know where it's going
to drop you think it'll drop in the hole
no it it it disappear from the map did
you collect it no no it's coming down H
it is it going in the hole coming
straight in the hole it's coming in the
hole oh
yeah what's in there open it first
shotgun shells that's all I wanted
there's a baked potato there's magazines
too if you want to take the
magazines I'll take the
coffee what kind of magazines let's
let's open these and see what magazines
it has um it has handgun and armor
crafting assault rifle and workstation o
workstation for you oh yes I need both
armor and okay I'll bring those to you
thank you is the trader lady like on a
weird path up a mountain
yes oh yeah you got to take a swirly a a
swirly path yeah I'm on it right now
it's not hard though it's fun I'm on my
way dudy
witch Judy wi familiar
dudy um I'm going to her house by
accident is this a dead end what does
Judy want from you I don't know it's
kind of ominous oh why is her last name
witch do you think that mean something I
I trust that that's why it's
ominous ity does this swirly Road go
down again weirdly like yeah it doesn't
go straight it's a bit up in the
mountains this is
confusing yeah that's why we need a
helicopter am I going back helicopter
helicopter where's a
snake ohy you guys should have seen we
went to go find Bo's treasure and then
it was we went into a snow place and
everything was super
overleveled and we died a million times
I mean they probably saw the messages of
B died Howe died died again it was
intense it was crazy oh oh I'm tracking
the wrong
Quest oh how do you can you change which
Quest you're Quest girl you're tracking
you can uh set a wayo with right
click so
fast what is this
path yeah it circles through the
mountains a bit but then afterward I
just went down very steep I just kind of
mountain goated it all the way down they
could totally place a a roller coaster
here this is perfect place it is very
swirly oh I think
I did I make
it voting our way up
here yeah we could do that or we could
take the biking path there is
one I my legs are not strong enough to
bike up here my Cals you can do it pedal
pedal I'm trying working harder I am a
mountain biker my hard I'm F we need to
put down some signs I keep on taking the
wrong
turns but now I think I got
it yeah it's just a little confusing
yeah I went the total wrong way but I'm
on my way now got this we should have
gone together I know yeah I could have
showed you guys the way sorry about that
I got distracted by the air drop the air
drop what six shotgun shells woo
I'm almost there on my bike wait how do
you get off a
bike e and if I leave my bike somewhere
does it ever despawn or something uh so
hold e and drag to the hand symbol to
pick it up into your inventory
[Music]
okay
wow oh lovely you made it here hi hi you
made it just in time this is her oh it's
a church oh so you took the bike path
and you're already there you're so
fast I'm on the
mountain get lost times just jump
down it's the 0 Dee
incline wose her upper body
okay that's what I said you just you
just like have a front view over chair
[Music]
yes your health is my
priority now I'm motivated to get there
fast I got to see this she's flirting
with me she was like glad to see your
face
oh what I want her to FL with
me I the we have like 15 more minutes
before today shift
and I'm so sad it's fun isn't it it's so
[Music]
fun maybe it would be good to accept
some quests she has so that I don't have
to come here all the time I guess no
never mind we get two tier two quests at
the other guy too so yeah yeah he only
gives me one Quest at a
time okay I think I'll bicycle my way
home so that I can maybe in the last
minutes figure out where to put my skill
points and if I can make one more armor
piece
sure sounds good then I'm going to head
off for tonight thanks for playing guys
thank
you thank
you same time tomor I guess yeah same
time I think okay okay and then we have
the raid too so we'll have to get ready
for that yeah the ra the raid's going to
happen like pretty early right cuz it's
already day ever what day is it 18 yeah
it's on the 21st just get ready for that
three hours I think yeah we can play a
little after though so it's
fine I want to let's do it for sure okay
see you later have fun thank you so much
bye bye byee by take care of yourself oh
she's already
gone I may have taken the wrong way
again I'm in the mountains
are you biking through the mountain I'm
biking through the mountain are you
biking directly up the mountain wait
kiaha is here no not directly up if you
see you see me
uh if
you go that way here around here right
side oh my God you should you should get
there wait where did you go gosh I think
I'm going up the mountain she down
there
G no
I don't know how to get out I can get
down here I can climb
this is it necessary to go through the
mountain no seems very diff she has a
really nice
place
yeah she does how do you repair your
bike uh you Dam she's a little damaged
wait did you did you destroy it no I
just fell down the mountain she oh yeah
you just need to repair aair
that was
[Music]
fasts when was night 14 uh we missed it
chat we missed
it it happened while we were all gone
but that's
okay back soon and I'll have people
probably keep on coming into our streams
like and they missed the beginning where
we explained what happened and they'll
be like what did I miss like did I sleep
through it what
happened I must have did you guys take a
Quest from her I took one no I didn't I
should have you can um I'll just I'll
take
one oh do you want me to help you with
your
leg oh my leg is okay right now my bike
is not very okay she'll be fine though
dang don't worry I'll go up the mountain
again time
to well I don't think you need to go up
the mountain to bike her and I us to
just you did say
it what is this view of her I don't even
see her face you don't see her face you
just you just stare right into the good
it's a very welcome bug it's I don't
think I don't think it's a bug I think
it's
[Laughter]
intended it intended view granda's learn
an
Elixir
okay m Chad do you know what video I was
watching actually let me I have it in my
history the quest I got so close I don't
know if I want to do it
though how long I I can do it if you
minutes I can do it too where are
you
Northeast it's the tier 2 clear d right
yeah yeah yeah where you do you going to
do a
quest let me
go it's the one TI two GT okay I'm going
to try to get there ASAP is it up the
mountain or no no it's not out the
mountain
okay don't break your legs that
way zombies we don't have to like end
exactly at the 4H hour mark right cuz I
just want to spend some time looking at
my skill points no just don't AFK for 7
hours yeah I will
not I'm just picking up stuff on the way
there's a lot of zombies on the way I
need command this one and Know M
yeah oh mie oats brother may I have some
oats zoom zoom
zoom this place is scary I know who
lives
here dead people so scary that dead
people live
here oh we have two quests do we we have
a lot there's like three around each
other whose C is this one oh it's two of
mine okay we can do all three of these
actually oh okay if we're fast I'm
almost there okay
BS I am really
thirsty is there a lake nearby water
here take my coffee thank you ooh H and
all that on your
bike
H could be dying right
now 250 M almost
there please
wait no problem um Wawa is on her
way soon I'm there oh the signs are
telling me to go
slow IGN it's an apocalypse who's going
to enforce them this looks like Fallout
New Vegas it does look like New
Vegas I can't believe we and me we're
all playing near Vegas yeah H funny
danger noodles okay I am so here oh yeah
I have I have stuff for
you me too I have a lots of stuff what
all for me yeah it's Christmas dye
orange dye watch out there's a zombie W
you can dye your bike or whatever else
you want I will die my
clothes yo so many magazines you guys
are amazing
it just good that the whole server knows
what magazines I need you want this
knife
thing I would like a knife thing thank
you scary scary you're
welcome
yes oh I have armor magazines
too does anyone like hammers or
explosives Sledgehammer thingies I do I
do okay there you go yes yes yes
yes
lovely I love how you girls keep on
getting magazines that I
need okay what's up hello
baddies eating a can of pears just
starts blasting everywhere
I can buy something all right let's help
out a little
bit I will help by opening
things oh we just started
blasting I will regret this but I will
go
upstairs I'm behind
you oh there's another upstairs
too in
here
ow oh she just got yellow eyes mhm
orange
eyes yeah it's getting spicier here in
this
area things are getting a little bit
more difficult
dangerous
[Music]
danger that's good I was kind of getting
sick of all the same places yeah too
easy sorry guys am I giving you guys
motion sickness is
upstairs there's a
box oh a forge
ahead let's
go more more more magazines here you
go yumy yummy boooks I
amako I like to eat
boooks oh there's
hello ah he's so F he's on fire waa
Sauron is this
you or is this one of his babies
yay we still haven't finished what's
left no there's more somewhere oh
there's
[Music]
more on the roof yeah all the way up oh
he
just careful
fall get up
here is still not did he not die from
the fall he was
chilling
damn okay good job level 1
wo Commando outfit excuse me who outfit
Commando outfit oh that's I think a
pretty good one
Yeah medium armor oh no but you my
little pretty lady will get a heavy
armor set oh I use uh
medium I don't know or not but there's
many different medium
ones do you have any cool armor right
nowo I just have
the scavenger outfit right now you can
try this
one
better my armor is critically broken
right now uhoh
uhoh it's getting a little bit
yubby well wait do you have a good good
outfit not yet one day I'll hit
these okay I'll just wear it for now and
then once I got the one I really want
I'll put this back into the armor chest
and somebody else can have
it okay
thank you thank you oh I have ammo for
you does anybody use assault
rifle uh no I use machine gun okay kih
waa ammo for you over here where are you
where are
you where are
you behind you I'm jumping up and
down we got to do like hot hot cold cold
oh thank you oh what is that armor part
ah armor part that's that's what I need
to all right second
quest's go let's this one harder right
this is fetch so you got to find an item
be so much easier but everybody's got
their own item
again oh god oh it's St behind us oh
they're twins oh
I feel like we're bullying them uhoh
there's a cop in
here
heting wow juicy how does it have so
much
range yeah the B goes
crazy is this a developer himself yeah
who is this guy
painting oh blue I'm not sure if this is
one of the developers
though
[Music]
hello oh I think they're in the closet
yeah okay okay
okay oh wa
I'm
reloading I think I accidentally stabbed
you I di I think you did accidentally
stab her yeah you you killed me it's
okay my God die as a consequence anyway
no no no no no don't die
don't I failed the quest then no oh I
think I did
too but the other one's still there you
guys you guys are still okay so keep
going I'm feeling hot are you okay cloes
apparently you feel
hot the bre open find a shelter where am
I
going Arizona
baby is this does this all look like
this because of forest fires I think so
unless the zombie apocalypse I die
everyone's
dying what did I what did I die to the
SP it's a spike it's a spike Why didn't
it make
noise I didn't hear it good
spikes but that was I found survivor's
guilt now don't feel guilty get that
reward get that bread also there's two
up
[Music]
here okay
get
upstair maybe that would have been my
Courier
Satchel whoa gy I thought you were a
zombie but like a really pretty one
watch out for the spikes I'll protect
you I'm a Zombie coming back to
life Quest
Limit Oh yeah you daily these uh Quest
have a daily limit
oh so I guess we can go back to give
back the
quest right I think is it are we are we
done in here yeah there's some loot here
yeah I have a medical
journal oh I have some ammo for you you
Kiara and oh I got a brawling for
fun thank you oh we forgot
this so scary here here you go there you
go thank you oh my goodness
sick oh I can drink beer now no don't do
it but it helps me punch better did you
go go into the uh attic and found crates
yeah okay okay okay
good oh now you can you can be like
drunken fist you know hung fu people
drunken
fist the medical
journal some steroids too thank you oh
wow wow my armor level is at 5050 four
now that's half of the
maximum wait I accidentally got a
medical Journey Journal I dropped it
again I think I can make first aid
bandages now
y our second doctor yeah doctor are you
licensed now studying I am I didn't give
up on my dreams even after
all I can you please check something
what was
it
um yeah let's go back I quickly want to
you know take care of everything make
some shoes and stuff do we have to talk
to the same
Trainor that we got the quest from or is
it wa since the three of us failed uh
the quest let's do this one right here
that's mine so it failed the last one
that we did too traffic so we can
complete this one maybe okay I'm so far
I just I was this is just a clear oh you
were fast huh yeah I just closed my eyes
and started
biking she's in a hurry I'm on my way
back there's a quest here baby yeah I
have a clear Quest
here
what I don't see it I don't either but
I'll you don't see the you don't see the
bouncy exclamation point right here yeah
normally we would
see so wait maybe we can't do it
together for some reason hopefully we
can maybe maybe we can't cuz I can't
even press f on it we reached the daily
Quest limit is that why I don't think so
cuz we failed we failed ours so I don't
have a it should say if you have a limit
what do you have at the bottom left do
you have a exclamation mark a red
one no uh
[Music]
is that the one that says you're done
with questing FAA do you have it I have
it yeah we're done with questing for
today oh I don't have it yeah you're not
done oh we help you start no I can't
start it I think it's B so we can go
maybe you can start it because we're in
a group maybe alone you can do it maybe
well I don't even see it for myself okay
so it's okay let's go
home and end our days slowly
yes I'll probably can we turn in the
quest first go to the Traer yeah I
follow you girls I don't know where to
go I feel like I actually have to learn
the maps
now like before I just run around but
now there's like roads and terrains wait
do we go we go up this road go we go
down
we go up we go up you're right you're
right C on him what are you
saying and then I started
[Music]
biking yeah I think learning the roads
is good because now biking cuz it
Doesn't you can't just cut through
really easily with a bike
yeah this place is nice yeah Nice
Landscaping
she just closed it
Sheed oh my gosh my bik in
there bike she stole your she stole my
[Music]
bike what about this one did she Chuck
it outside this pink one did she throw
this oh yes oh did she did she Chuck it
outside you might have thrown your bike
out I see a pink one oh my gosh it do
not work
oh I guess that was nice of her to
[Laughter]
do yeah just just cuz she's closed
doesn't mean she's
heartless we'll figure it out later chat
all right well I guess this is where I
will stop for
today okay okay yeah me
too bye bye I will stay in game just to
quickly skill points and stuff but I
won't stay too long and I will not stay
AFK I will not don't AFK I want to level
up too I have a point wa where's home
where is Home goodbye that way byebye
byebye all right I am done for today I
will not be streaming my POV tomorrow I
will be doing a normal GG stream time at
normal G start time but I will probably
end so I can play this
game I hope you enjoyed I had lots of
fun today see you all tomorrow goodbye
everyone
bye-bye take care I'll drop everyone off
at
kiaha kiaha will deal with you bye-bye
[Music]