oh
wash before you touch me I don't know
what's coming for them
there's only one stop and then don't
stop coming I don't want to play this
anymore I'm done for it to say I'm done
I'm done I'm done how do you turn what a
weird cheat how to
you turn this off
[Music]
that was a joke what does it do it's
like super powerful oh my God
[Laughter]
I want to test that
how about this
[Laughter]
but everyone has the same car
this really fixed my mood okay okay come
on come on that's enough of course it's
a whole Army of cars
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh there's a couple sure join all forces
come over here and make me move big guy
who move does he attack I am going to
attack you
[Laughter]
[Music]
Alfred I love you I love it
[Applause]
I love what he says he says funny things
Furious the monkey boys the monkey
they're friends
wash before you touch me
yes
he doesn't like dirty hands oh they're
coming with the Rams and those ramps
versus my animals who will win I think
it's an obvious win for me
you guys so aggressive okay
what damage you do on the castle
okay come on come on come on faster you
gotta go faster Alfred you gotta go
faster
[Music]
big guy
yes this is a true history this is how
it all happened you don't believe it you
must believe okay
I'm looking for them it's the future
it's the [\h__\h] future how friends
our friends Alfred
your hands are cold okay
what's up I am going to attack you why
don't you come over here
okay okay
I'm gonna help
[Music]
help out my alpaca friends
oh Fred yeah I love you so
our friend is
[Music]
friends come
we must abandon funds to the French
[Applause]
[Music]
memory last Englishman must be taken
down where are they where are they where
are they hiding how was this not already
enough
how are they still thinking that this is
a battle worth fighting oh
this is red
[Music]
Castle's really nearby
okay last Castle they have the last one
standing
[Music]
all right who do you think you are
making me move well
I can't do it I can't do it it has to be
done properly but just imagine we did it
yeah yeah definitely lived with my boots
there