[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
K I already forgot K
forgot I forgot because that's what frog
does
hello
[Music]
anything is
fine both are fine both sound
good she
frot
FR what color am I to you
[Music]
guys hint it's not
yellow yeah green ding d d ding ding
ding green like TOS eyes exactly I am I
am pretty lime green
too no the only reason I tweeted that is
because I watched a clip uh I'm a a clip
Watcher I watched a clip of M and B's
watch
along and Bs was like uh no woman I
don't know who brought it up
first outside of the clip but B was like
her eyes are green people say her eyes
are yellow some people say that
apparently and then BS was like yeah I
think eyes are yellow and Mum was like
no they are green and then they had a
little bit of a
[Laughter]
fight so as a as a common green person
and common color
fist
I wanted to support and back up
M get
[Music]
get chartreuse oh people also say lime
green I would accept that it is still
green lime
green frung death let's go another death
uh please expect me to yell out death
whenever something bad happens
de dear dear de
you I'm I'm curious you don't have
any H life fans in your team right I
mean you might become one today today
might be the day hey devs I made some I
made some frog uh song
merchandise as you can
see over there on on that side on the
left side
feel free to um get your own games
merchandized just not happening
tce I mean you never know they could be
everywhere frog frog frog frog song
deaths could be could be whole live
fans we just don't know it yet it she
might be coming out of nowhere just like
yesterday h
and if not as I said we'll just we'll
just get him into the boat F on [\h__\h]
about collab
merch that that that's totally what this
is or I my whole existence is a
collaboration with frog
song yeah so guys if you didn't get the
merchandise yet wo there it is in the
description is the link Lulu thank you
for the red
ch um I
have I have
two news one bad news one good
news which one do you want to hear
first the bad news or the good news you
choose bad news first okay I did not fix
the
sound but yesterday it was not that b
orome and the day before neither
so so uh just a shout out to the devs
there may be some weird sound but I I
tell people now that it's not
representative of the game you couldn't
even tell okay good then the good news
you think that's not bad then the good
news is even
better the lady from the store is not
she didn't quit I asked
kiddo I asked because I went I went to
the store and I bought something um they
were like what what where were you these
past weeks H and I'm like oh yeah well I
was I was out of the
country so you guys have noticed I was
gone and then as I was given an opening
I asked did she
quit did she quit or what she can't just
quit without telling me beforehand and
then they were like um no she broke
broke her
toe oh no I have to go and nurse her oh
no now okay so she'll be coming
back
yay broke her freaking
toe I don't even have toes do I do I I
don't
know y I'm happy that's good news wait
that's it is good news that's is not
gone we were really sad that she might
be gone so good news yay all right
today
is I mean I don't want to break this
like fourth wall but today is kind of
the last um the last uh frog week
game uh yes just saying
and it's uh I think a little bit on the
longer side I mean yesterday was
surprisingly long
too oh but yeah um this one I think I I
looked up the time and I think it said
like 5 hours five and a half hours or
so so yeah let's make this one
last woohoo I
agree can you stay longer
well I I'll be around for the memb
stream and I'll be around for the Easter
stream Easter stream Easter stream is
looking good by the way I was sent uh a
preview of the map and everything and
the games that have been
implemented yo it really feels like it
could be like a switch game or so I
don't know or like a game on Steam or so
like oh my God we are ambitious with
these games yo let's
go and yeah they're they're saying
they're very confident with um getting
stuff done today
they're um finishing stuff up and
tomorrow they're testing stuff yeah but
they have like when when I say tomorrow
it's like they have um they're both in
Europe so they have like you know the
whole day cuz stream starts at midnight
uh but I just reminded myself I need to
remind the others to make more eggs so
who hasn't made an egg um
oh by the way sh is joining I didn't um
say her name yesterday because I didn't
know uh you
know I didn't know that she was going to
join because I did not see her react in
the initial post because I think she
added it pretty late so I didn't see I
didn't check back to see that I checked
back a few times but I think she she
just waited until she was relatively
certain and I confirmed with her
yesterday evening and she said yeah
she'll be part of it and she immediately
sent me an egg nice so I think I'm
missing an egg
from um egg from
Mor egg from
[Music]
reu right uh I have MAA egg I have only
egg I have F that egg I have Shi
egg yeah oh I need to remind myself too
to make an
egg what what was that last one what
eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs uh and yeah uh
beep beu right B make an egg and just in
case even though she sent me a preview
[Music]
Quon I think I still need your
eggs don't worry it can be simple and
sced but I've already gotten some kind
of crazy ambitious eggs egg designs eggs
EG eggs egg
eggs
um please
within um ASAP we need to model and put
it into the game in the
next
yeah
what was I saying oh yeah some really
ambitious crazy egg you'll see you'll
see some people put a little bit too
much work into their
eggs actually everybody who submitted so
far has gorgeous beautiful Flawless eggs
eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs okay eggs eggs eggs let's go Frog
song yeah close did I have to
save
well
die okay I hope you hear the sound when
it comes frog team games frog oh they
only make frog games or
what good game Studio this game uses
Auto sa features noise do not shut down
the game boa look at the boa no it's
frog shut off your dirty mind
guys this screen only appear on your
first launch all of these settings can
be changed later at any
time what's this weird bar at the bottom
ah oh screen check H do we want screen
check reduced effects adjust colors I
like this
font this whole operation your
idea might as well keep it
yeah
oh oh it's pretty what do you say that's
pretty loud huh
oh what what
no I thought I said
go you can change the
font let's go but I like this one very
much oops instant is okay text
effect
H golden signs will appear in near
puzzles that you can read to receive a
hint oh Auto heal oh sh oh sh the
assistance
FR comic stand no no no scandalous okay
how do I how do I say
okay
oh wait how do I commit to
this oh no I don't want to change
that
when b or start
game
[Music]
oh hey that sounds fine
right that sounds fun cute oh music
already
cute froggy wake up and by the way I
coined a new word because I wanted to
say about a game I wanted to say not
that it's goed I wanted to make up my
new word it's
frogged uh for real overly great games
everybody digs that's frog games they're
frogged they're absolutely
frogged let's St this is an action RPG
apparently so
oh a font I cannot read
Frankie could it be that the bgm is kind
of quiet on your side guys a cute looks
a bit like a Ninja
Turtle with those eye
thingies cute he looks that was like a
cat Okay turned it up a bit please tell
me this is
okay oh he's so cute the way he
walks
a very freaking cute oh my
God I love it yeah the art style is so
cute
[Music]
oh
look oh my God oh my God I have a little
backpack oh my God I'm so cute can I eat
can I eat no maybe in the
future I'm going it a little bit louder
for your convenience and just yeah lower
my headphones a little
bit okay what is this
cute I like this art style oh what are
you doing you're vibing with the leaf
you having a good time with the
leaf oh yeah right I forgot I
didn't oh that doesn't change anything
so
weird small small frog in a big big
world do we go this
way he's so cute you got your
anniversary mer y Ann merch you mean the
ticking I also saw people already
getting the Valentine's merch I guess
that one was like stocked
already and people also already getting
the like those like
um the the the the one with the tray and
the rubber keychain and the badge and
all
that what was that called again the
emblems yeah the emblem the Fire Emblem
merch I guess that one also was like uh
on
stock oh why was you going but I'm going
to go this way this is an arpg game we
have to check out every
corner but maybe in the beginning
doesn't seem like there's much hidden at
all
so that looks like a nice a nice uh
chopping block chopping
tray oh why why why did I do do that
maybe I can just leave it
down open pot yeah let's go
money guys if I miss an important
message from the devs let me know I'm
keeping my eye on the chat but
uh what does it say not The Travelers
remember to bring a map with you so that
you do not get lost signed M do we have
a map oh we do oh
oh look at him go wrong button though
it's this one oh it's orange why must
you be
orange they said you would know what
that means what Su I know I know what Su
means
what okay oh nice map it fills up green
the more we
[Music]
walk oh no it fills up green the parts
uh that we were already in
mhm the cuts of the map
broadc yeah have an eye on
broadc broadc what's this how do we get
rid of this attack oh oh I got a knife
guys knife knife chicken emoji oh now I
can cut the oh
sorry I can shoot him like a ball oh
[\h__\h] but I can't kill them oh I just we
got grass out of it
nice
oh I can cut all the grass now
oo bam swish
swoosh powerful frog with a
dagger damn I want to know his story why
why does he have a backpack why does he
have a dagger what's what's what's
happening and what mission is he what
have people done to
him stabby
frog oh frog frog statue
so I get
stuck there's something big
there oh leap leap
frog yes is this move mhm can I leap
over like water too like probably not in
this case but oh we need to fill all the
statues with like gems like these so
smart Val was so
smart oh oh no I got it I received it
choruses will
grew what Ling stones are are hidden
throughout the world collect them to
increase your health ah so just now I
got an extra heart so to
say sorry it's really addicting
to look at uh all the grass and cut
it
oh okay what's inside here
oh nothing I'm so
cute frogs are so
cute frogs are just the cutest thing
aren't they oh the grass regrew really
fast yo speed I'm really faster when I
leap oh this little Buck I saw him
together with our frog in the promot
picture so it must be our best friend
forever oh hey there little guy you're
not going to attack me right you look
pretty small I should be able to just
sneak past you why why not attack why
not eat H are you following me do you
want something at
all you went into my bag hey wait get
out of my bag my food's in there too
late I guess you can come with me if you
want but if you're going to eat my food
maybe you can help me out a little the
beetle bud can be brought out at any
time if you need some extra help finding
Secrets or fighting monsters ah wow so a
a little bit more
assistance how the beetle butt helps can
be adjusted in the options menu a second
player can also take control of the
belet but by pres pressing the interact
button on their controller y but
probably only couch Co
[Music]
uple but
little
cue it's nice to have him around he
looks like a
dog with a
long
snoot battle body acquired chapter one
New
Beginnings
yes by the way there's like I don't know
if you can hear the water sounds for
example yeah those are probably really
quiet to you well like there's there's
just ambient sounds
now
slightly okay good turn Crank It Up Guys
crank it
up oh wait oh
[Music]
yeah already got a party member yeah oh
he's excited what what oh that he wants
to go for the
crack
oh music suddenly I was just saying
there only ambient
sounds and again we got the Bongo what's
he
doing
huh huh now that's a bug is it I mean
yeah it's a bug
but the way he
like runs away from me when I'm there
wait he's showing me a secret ah okay oh
must be a bug but I can't do anything
here at least not for
[Music]
now ah ah
ah oh sand the
ocean
why but we can't swim what are you
eating Ras no Rasberry BL Blitz oh it's
like a from a drink to top right all
look at what I found in the sand over
there what do you think it is why am I
following the Rhythm there oh my God
it's such a
Bob I don't know how that
[Music]
happen
it's too loud now okay
good I
[Music]
agree no
no
sorry sorry Debs that's um little bit of
a torture meme we have at kfp me adding
Chata to every game bgm I can
find yeah anyway I'm not sure it looks
really pretty
though uh I think it's a magical shield
made by made by an ancient powerful race
of frogs from another planet oh yeah you
believe what you want to believe oh I'm
just kidding I have no clue what it is I
really like its colors yeah oh did you
want it no you can keep it okay cool I
was hoping you would say that I really
wanted to keep it look at his face hello
my name's chorus what's yours I'm Asel
nice to meet you ESO I'm headed to borea
am I walking the right way depends what
way you're walking now you're walking
towards me that is the wrong way indeed
um you got to go west your West are L
waste never mind I think I've got it see
around yeah do do you really think a
frog would
understand okay what's with the secret
[Music]
though can I even open the secret now H
Maybe not maybe not maybe
not need upgrade oh oh oh what
W I'm rich already 45 coins is not bad I
[Music]
think Get
Wrecked oh we got some useful
signs East the glooming Grove West Boral
further east the swamp of
[Music]
Gloom okay West is that
way just had to check in my bra
[Music]
can't why can't we not eat these bugs
I'm
hungry need something to fill my tummy
please
kid oh oh that's all we're already
here
oh
oh hello frogs wow it's a frog City frog
City if 10 million fireflies you would
not believe your
what
yeah you would not believe your eyes
oh where's this little
corner you would not believe your eyes
if 10 million
fireflies L up thegu I fell
asleep m
[Music]
hey you're new in town right do you want
a slice of pie yeah then you should have
bed
one my goodness I'm kidding goodness can
you imagine oh goodness that would be so
rude please ignore him ah please ignore
him he thinks he's hilarious I've heard
someone new is moving to town so my
husband here B eyes a is a female frog
so my husband here baked one of his
world famous Huckleberry pies
Huckleberry is that a certain type of
pie that really exists world famous
really wait a huckleberry is
real a huckleberry in
[Music]
German tell me where are the German
people instant voice mod I'm the voice
mod they're
real what are
they
hidle
be oh it's just hidle be I love hi
highle
[Laughter]
[Music]
be nice
Huckleberry isn't there like
somebody who calls themselves
Huckleberry Finn or something like that
what was
[Music]
that
Huckleberry Huckleberry yeah who's
Huckleberry Finn who is
that that's a book
character why do I remember him I never
read a book in my
[Music]
life Mark Twain story
wow this is why I don't read books
because I have the knowledge already in
my brain without even reading the
book maybe you saw the
anime
no I don't think
[Music]
so well anyway we world famous in boreal
at least here we wanted you to have a
slice really but you don't even know me
welcome to Boreal but now I do get my
pie yo
yummy yummy yummy yummy I got pie in my
tummy fair to travel is five coins
currently there are no fairy routes open
though
oh like everybody is like offering me
such like all you want a pie I should
have made yourself one oh you want a
ride oh well we don't have rides right
now what do you want what look at these
rles what's with his leg he's doing the
thing that the bead that I saw yesterday
is
doing hello are you
ELD oh hello everyone I'd like to
introduce you you devs you're welcome to
hire me to do a full voice over of all
characters
I'd like to introduce you to the new
defense Guild recruit oh oh oh really
what what uh nothing huh if you've got
something to say I want to hear
it uh well it's just when we heard there
was someone new coming to train with us
we expected so that's why I have the
knife and all that and why I came here
cuz I already had like a a new job lined
up oh a bit more muscle
don't say things like that
Bal why not it's true pipsqueak here is
smaller than a SK oh [\h__\h] I skipped
something no no I'll have you know I've
seen some pretty Fierce Warriors the
size of pip squeak
[Music]
here yeah like um
me I guess I don't know I don't really
go out and do fights and War but I could
I
could one almost killed me in the war
the
war which one the Frog War next game
frog
War
I'm he's missing a oh he's missing it oh
I guess so yeah he's missing the little
toesy
thingies we're friends now now why don't
you introduce yourself oh oh oh oh
um I'm I'm course I'm nonbinary and my
pronouns are day Dem I've wanted to join
the defense Guild for a long time so I
moved Bala to to Bala to train hopefully
I can learn lots
here isn't that a holy holy holy name
what's someone like you doing here oh
I've just told
you
[Music]
out fine I'll give them a shot I've seen
weird stuff happen oh [\h__\h] why I keep on
skipping things finger bad finger bad
finger bad bad bad bad
finger chorus I've already started
today's lesson but tomorrow we can
be people of the village
B please welcome this Imperial Majesty
Lord
of the Toro Empire get
out they're like his horses you got to
be kidding me die who did he just say
die good afternoon people of B Ally hail
from the Toral
Empire it looks evil we are powerful in
the vast realm with territory SP
spending halfway across the land of
Salia I am his Imperial magest the
mighty Lord ruler of his powerful this
powerful
domain oh I'm familiar with your Empire
what brings you all the way to
gloral we came to bring very serious
news I have reason to believe there is a
major disaster on the horizon that
threatens your village I need to
[Music]
fix go
what are you talking
about I'm still looking into the nature
of the
disaster but it has potential to wipe
out your entire Village but worry not my
friends for I have an offer for
you the toal Empire is very strong and
we are more than capable of protecting
Bala if your qut little village joins
our Empire my soldiers shall do what
they can to protect
[Music]
you are you serious hit the road
creep are you the Elder of this Village
no but then you are the one I wish to
discuss this
with Excuse me I I am Elder buo of
Bala excellent we can begin discussing
arrangements for
no there is nothing for us to discuss
you may leave now buo with all due
respect you need to understand where way
you DED out as a
Tapo that's their way of saying did you
did did where you dropped as a child as
a
toddler we said we don't want you here
hey get out of here but out let me
handle
this SW you dried out as a
t
nice she's right though we do not need
protection from an
Empire oh oh that was a she oh I made
the voice
[Music]
so m you're making a mistake Elder Bala
is home to the best defense skill
members dis side of
Salia we can handle
ourselves then the blood of your
villagers will be on your
hands goodbye
Elder where you cracked as an egg is
that our chicken way of saying
it creep hm
uh are you sure that was the best idea
he mentioned a disaster if something bad
happens wouldn't we want more help there
is no disaster
pipsqueak didn't you hear how vague he
was about all
that yeah
but it's it's okay
chorus I get the feeling Leos is trying
to trick smaller communities into
joining his Empire I suppose I'll have
to warn the other Elders during our next
meeting okay I'm going to cut today's
lesson short everyone of course a little
bit north from the village is a training
ground we've got set up why don't you
head up there and practice for a bit and
then join in on our lesson tomorrow when
you're done you can get set up in your
new house that we built for you wao it
should be easy to spot it's smaller
smaller well I am the smallest frog here
seemingly am I like a child small small
frog in terms of age I wonder like a
teenager or child if you have any
questions or get lost just stop by my
house I'll be happy to help here I will
pin my house and the training grounds on
your map thank you I'll go check it
out small But Mighty yeah do not
underestimate I have a knife goou oh
goou
you're really going through with this
pip squeak and I'm going to prove I can
be a good
warrior
sure good luck at the training
grounds um yeah I don't need your
luck you stupid
duck oh was he here before hello
hello are my name's chorus I'm new in
town uh I was wondering when we get an A
priest in town I'm not a priest you
should go find Elder buo he'll help ah
sorry I skipped you and went straight to
buo more or less that must be my house
cute but wait let me look around oh who
are
you hey kid don't make my mistakes don't
smoke I'm not a kid I'm 23 oh okay there
there go is my question answered not
that I'd smoke anyways smart kid still
23 yeah but I look like a
kid he's got a cape he must be a
superhero hello hi my name's Cory I
didn't moved here oh oh hello I'm ra
wait are you the new war Warrior bu told
me about yeah no what what are you
reading uh I'll just Boke about the
history of Bala is it interesting uh not
speci especially I'm required to read it
for my job though what kind of job do
you need to read a history book for
um I'm both a successor he's going to
leave me in charge of the village once
he
retires wow that's a really big
responsibility
yeah oh I can ask questions are you
scared you seem scared me sort of it's a
lot of pressure I can't help but feel
like I'm not making any progress on my
studies it's like I'm going in
circles but this is what I want to do
with my life I guess it's complicated
I'm sure you'll do a great job I guess I
better leave you to it good luck see you
around course oh she seems to like me
though she's she's nice good that the
future leader is someone who I can
confirm seems to be
[Music]
nice they all have quite nice Ro robust
looking houses and I can't believe I got
free housing
damn berries are those are those are
huckleberries because I thought a German
the word you you said to me that's in my
mind those are more blue or are those e
what are
[Music]
those those are apples but isn't stuff
here
[Music]
size realistically I don't know
could also be Cranberries or something
like that oh okay I mean I would love to
make this place a little bit more
cozy but at least I have a
seemingly comfortable looking bed yeah a
look at me I look like a
dog when it Sparkles yeah it's
[Music]
new nothing happens oh okay you have to
look at this again everybody look at the
Frog not me look at look at this
frog and the way he gets
up y
stretch it's like a
cat oh my God and the tap tap tap sounds
are so cute
too well so wait uh they wanted me to go
to some training rounds right and also
they wanted me to check out the house of
the leader which is I guess one of those
Marked
[Music]
Ones oh maybe that's the upper one is
maybe the training
[Music]
grounds ah no Elder bu's house
okay tap tap tap tap oh oh oh
interesting path
oh
oh thanks for the membership for 15
months
we okay wow quite a house
wow it's like a Teletubby house hello
wow I like the the red cozy mood
lighting oh hello chorus did you have a
question o m
I
mean maybe about raana oh Rana you met
her she's a very smart little toad
toad she will be a great Elder one day
she dabed herself though she
struggles I know she's doing her best
but I also know she's so afraid of
making a mistake that she holds herself
back she could accomplish such great
things if she gave herself more Credit
Credit
Credit maybe you could try talking to
her you seem quite confident yourself I
already talk to
[Music]
her is is basal always
so basal has always been very set in her
ways I promise you she has a kind heart
she does not have the most open mind
[Music]
it takes a lot for her to change her
opinion I apologize for her Brash
behavior I'm sure together we can get
her to see you can do just as good a job
as
her okay well I won't ask you
everything doesn't seem too
lifechanging but good to know where he
is and in what kind of place he lives
wait
what I
here now we go to draining training
grounds it does not spark
[Music]
Joy wait
what where are the training
grounds not here are they it's the store
wow they also have mood lighting
oh a new customer
welcome what do you have a huckle bear
they are apparently the huckle
Bears I thought they were supposed to be
blue
Shar
cute polet still
pod polet what's a
polet hopefully not
frog a pretty
affordable what do you want to talk
about about yourself me oh my name is
Clea I live here in this little shop
making food with my wife she moved here
from Clear Bay a few years ago when we
first met I wasn't a bit of a rat I
didn't really have any Ambitions
everything felt like a chore but at some
point she took me to this cultural
Festival in clear Bay I didn't want to
go at first but she convinced me and it
was wonderful the art music food and all
sorts reminded me of how much fun life
can be not long after that I finally
gathered the energy to set up shop
M nice person nice
frog okay where are didn't they say the
Battlegrounds were with or close
to oops I got rid of my
bug or
H North okay maybe
here they just don't have it uh marked I
thought they marked it on my
map not Battlegrounds training training
is this a training ground
ouch
Y come here come here come here come
here what is this copper City uhhuh
looks like
M's
signature all right to damage well that
came out of
nowhere it came a little bit out of
nowhere Have I Told You Lately you're
the best
hey what the [\h__\h] was that did you find
something I was looking at the map ah wa
shees wait my bug is too strong oh my
[Music]
God is there more
oh blue pale blue
frog oh interesting you look so fancy
with that color hello oh oh oh hello
there are you from bana yeah I just move
there what is that thing and this is my
Star Glass it allows me to see stars in
the night sky much closer oh wow that's
really cool it really is my name is Baro
I'm a Star Seeker I'm currently mapping
the night sky and tracking the movement
of the Stars what do the stars look like
up close well mostly the same but
there's more than Stars up there like
aliens H yeah the strange clouds of
color streaks of light actually come
back in a few days come at night there
see there's something really fascinating
up there that I'd like to show you all
right I'll see you
around with this oh I can rest in the
sun that's not
[Music]
I can heal but like won't I dry
up isn't that
dangerous that's
a r rhino rhino
bug woo nice
teamwork beak
bug is this still considered the
training rounds like all of
this I wonder cuz it leads very
[Music]
far Wonder should I even go this far but
I have nothing else to do right they
only said oh go to the training ground
ah oh n you should play this
game get down here get down
here flying enemy kind of
op
wait come come here no I missed
him
yeah let's
go those bugs are the most OP because I
cannot kill them
[Music]
hey oh hey another one of those oh wo wo
oh he soloed
him no come here uh
happy birthday Val
me he yo what the
[Music]
hell come
here no no I hate
him I need like an arrow or
something
hey I don't know how far I should go
this looks like a face by the
way I guess we'll go a little bit
[Music]
further that guy is the final boss oh if
I can leap and attack M let's
see oh no I don't I no I can't I can't
do it at the same
[Music]
time
I know they get lower when they attack
me but like it's
also still with that
knowledge difficult
oh I I can't match this enemy can I also
he ignores me ow and I don't think I'm
doing
damage yeah maybe I should go
back yeah my fly
water ah ah wait that was looking at my
fly
[Music]
one let me
try I'm
scared I'm
scared what are you doing attack me what
the
hell he's just chilling
now he's following
[Music]
me yeah low Health danger ow ow
owow can you believe I [\h__\h]
died oh did I lose
anything is this like cuz I if I didn't
rest here once
would I not have respawned here I wonder
if it's like a
checkpoint yeah cash is the same R I'm
so
stupid yeah I think I need I need the
little bug to help
me it's not difficult though I'm just
you
know oh wait there's a path here too huh
ow why why do I run into
[Music]
him yeah okay training
rounds thanks for doing the job for me I
add the copper City should I go to the
Copper City I mean it lets me and it's
so
[Music]
close I feel like it just kind of Bounce
to wander into
[Music]
it hey getting all the work done without
me I was totally going to join you oh
they also have these big ones though
oh he doesn't even try to attack the the
big
boy then maybe they're
Invincible
get I don't know if I should go
[Music]
here deps are probably putting their
heads in their hands and like why does
she go
there why is this player taking this
[Music]
route he's mean I'll go back I'll see
I'll see if I can do
[Music]
something why V
why
H they told me to come at night but it's
not like I can sleep for to make it
night
right I'm going to sleep anyway cuz I'm
assuming it heals
me why frog Trooper
why yeah RPGs oh
oh rest nice that's it but it's not
night time now is
it is it no
froggy wa away I talk to Dean's
[Music]
frogs I talk to him I kind of talk to
them can't talk to them anymore talk to
you I talked to them
before Oh what do I
do maybe I need to ask the Elder all the
questions to move
on maybe I have to go further really you
think
[Music]
so maybe I have to I guess so cuz like
there's nothing else to do right and
they did say go to the training grounds
H wait that's the wrong
place
okay but not to Copper City I
assume or HM who knows
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah but like
uh up to where is the training grounds
cuz we met with a a different frog on
the
way so does that mean that is still a
training
[Music]
ground I'll see how far I can go then
no evil
bug these evil bugs
Kido
sleep
[Music]
thanks no we hate bugs in this
neighborhood hey what the
[\h__\h]
oh what's that big money wait I got to
go back and heal but then he he respawns
I
think they do two damage I think two
damage per hit
oopsie that's kind of crazy
kiddo don't don't don't don't
don't oh he got confused cuz I think he
bed his head on the on the
poles
I'm a
[Music]
crazy not you not wasting my time with
you uh right
[Music]
side yeah it's cute that you rest in the
sun to heal
yeah but like for real I'm confused
don't doesn't the Frog dry
[Music]
up since when do frogs like
sunbathing in the middle of the sun
without without a pond underneath
you oh okay that there's seemingly
something like the end of the training
ground or maybe
not a
bridge a
huh no
okay wet soil and Sun seems a good
combo amphibian cold
water what difference does that make
explain explain
yourself I don't think you fre should
train what Oh you mean all of this is
the path leading to the training ground
h
[Music]
interesting
Theory [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you no damage let's
[Music]
go original game engine was made for
cats honestly this do all of this could
work with a cat yet
so far it could work with a
cat the way it sleeps the way it likes
sleeping in the
Sun the
violence come
here he says
[Music]
ow oh thank you for the
membership M are you guys excited for
the Easter stream tomorrow I'm I'm
nervous about
it I also um I don't know if I'll
actually oh God if I if I'll use actual
VR last year I think I used desktop mode
I think I might use desktop mode
again cuz it's just a a little bit less
stressful as the
host even though
it would be
cuter with proper movement but um H
there's a lot of desktop mode
participants I think although maybe it's
kind of like half half not quite a
little bit less than half and oh yeah I
was going to say I I was going to be uh
only the host because of uneven
participants but now that she already
joined we are indeed ah go away from me
we are indeed
even with my
participation so I'll take part in the
games after all in the games that I have
created I'm
like I'm I'm like a Hunger Games
producer cuz they make the game in the
Hunger I'm
like which is not necessarily a good
thing
I'll be like welcome to the Hunger Games
if you lose you die there can only be
one
Survivor oh look at him what he's got
some cute Stones wait let me heal
first P A different kind of PETA P
different very different kind of
pea Peter what is the horse doing
here what no what is the course doing
[Music]
here
Peter Peter
P
hello hi there are these you rocks uh
yes I'm a gist this is some of my
collection from AR Salia this first rock
to the left is from the globing roof
have you been there I guess it can be a
bit dangerous there be careful if you
have uh ever have to go there next is a
rock from the swamp of Gloom I wasn't
there for very long it's pretty
dangerous even for me this last one's
actually just a chunk of hardened Poland
OH from M mows but it looks like a rock
that place isn't dangerous unless you've
got allergies I guess I'm planning on
traveling around Salia some more to find
more cool rocks nice it's always good to
uh appreciate a cool rock oh wait feel
like am am would like this
[Music]
mentality totally totally you missed out
on the pond
there my
friend where are we what this is crazy
wait that's where the training grounds
are you see the red
thing damn they sent without warning
they sent me on a huge
Journey
what
[Music]
ow I thought it would just be in know
next door so so to
[Music]
say first
dungeon I don't know I feel like I'm
being thrown into cold water
here Al I wish there was like a level
system or so because uh I
feel I feel like too weak for these m
partially
ow I took two damage again
no
[Music]
okay maybe you'll get a better knife
soon yeah although I like this
knife also wait is there a menu
oh one
damage
n o a that's what poets are ah they made
a pie out of that
ew oh join the defense skill start
training I've waited long enough it's
time to move to Boreal and finally start
my life in the defense that's so cute
the drawing is so
cute not a
hold oh it's very grassy
here we might get some surprised by a
sudden
Pokmon better cut all the
[Music]
grass really is very
grassy anybody got a lone mower lone
lone mower is that how you say it La
lawn
mower yes loan my mo mo mo my
[Music]
loans
I watched okay do you want to do you
want to hear about the funny video I
watched yesterday I watched a funny
video
reaction of a
compilation uh okay Cody Co yeah reacted
to a compilation of dudes who give you
like life advice mostly in terms of
money on Tik Tok but I that's that's the
only only way I get like my my fair
share of Tik Tok um but basically the
advice is like very like dumb like these
dudes think they've got it all figured
out but they really don't and then
basically for
[Music]
example what was it there's a there's a
guy who's
like
uh like take out loans just take out
more loans and then get new credit card
and do this get another credit card take
out more loans and then you know file
bankruptcy and it's just a life hack
like oh my God I can't believe people
aren't doing this more just keep on
taking loans and you know never with the
intention of ever paying it
back yeah that's the way to do it oh my
God I can't believe that not everybody's
doing although uh I feel like I I'm
missing a critical point here that makes
it even more ridiculous uh that I
forgot it's like a financial Guru
yeah want a life hack
oh no but whatever he was saying was
kind of illegal and then
um like fraud basically and then there's
a followup cuz he was like he was like
pretty young too and he F like he got it
all figured out and then
he he a follow up Tik Tok where he's
like oh I can't believe you guys fought
I was serious ha haha duh like of course
I wasn't serious I was just
kidding he was obviously not kidding but
he's trying to back peddle so hard and
then there was like another guy who's
like doing something like a TED talk
like a seminar or so I guess and he's
like yo if you don't if you don't if you
if you if you only
only uh earn
400k per year what the [\h__\h] are you
doing like oh my God you have to earn at
least 4 million per
year otherwise otherwise you're
basically just poor and what are you
doing with your
life he was like oh my God what what are
these expectations and another guy was
like yo basically people have it totally
wrong if you want to become rich you
don't say save up money because that's
poor thinking don't save up money spend
it all because then you're like oh now I
don't have money I have to make more
money so the way I get rich is if I have
money I just buy a new car and that will
make me want to more make more money so
and then I get another car and another
whatever don't save money you have to
spend it
all okay
what were you thinking guys don't save
your money oh dear
oh it seems we have reached the training
grounds and then there was also another
guy who was like oh you you have to
gamble you got to go gamble because
eventually eventually you'll you'll hit
the money and then yeah uh Gamble and
also I think they were saying just
gamble with uh loans or so I don't know
they're all [\h__\h]
insane their advice is so bad and and
the
most most the one that pissed me off the
most is like there's this guy he looks
like I don't know he's 4050 or so he
thinks he's
so
so respectful or whatever he does these
like Tik toks I guess where he gives
Financial advice too so he sits in a
restaurant and he's just like showing
off his lifestyle what he eats in a day
and at the end when he's supposed to pay
the waiter gives him the bill right and
then the waiter still stands there and
he's like so the guy is like what do you
want as a tip and apparently it's a trap
okay he the the waiter is just making
like really uh reasonable statements
like oh whatever you think like I so to
say deserve for for the service I gave
you is
fine and then and then the waiter leaves
and then the guy to the camera basically
is like oh that was a big mistake this
is why you don't have success in life
because you don't ask for the things you
really want you could have asked for $1
million tip and I would have given that
to you but now now you're losing out
because I'm only giving you a $100 tip
you know how much you just lost and then
he fumbles like five times over the he's
like yeah 9
99999 what N 9 900 uh what nine he
fumble so so many times I don't know why
they didn't cut it
out and then yeah he finally gets and
he's like yeah yeah
99,900 yeah yeah yeah
yeah
oh my God basically saying oh yeah you
just you should you should totally as a
waiter if somebody ask you this question
but that's like so unrealistic why would
you ask for $1 million in the first
place how could you know that somebody
would be willing to do that like that's
so unrealistic and it's kind of like
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you asking
for 1 million I would be like worried
about you if that's a serious answer I
mean usually if anything you would say
that jokingly yeah just give me 1
million but if you're serious about
about it
like what the [\h__\h] are these life
expectations and how can you say that
like like and then the argument was that
if you ask for so much you will go into
situations where it's like oh wow you're
too greedy now you're too greedy you
need to be humble and thankful and like
you know more realistic otherwise that
also is not good but oh all these all
these guys are
idiots
anyway ah red Beast just cooperate with
us why don't we just eat it eat it my C
dibs on the ls your leus will eat us if
we drop the ball again ah I know what's
see thinking though there's Warriors in
borana I doubt the slicers going to wipe
them out he doesn't want to wipe them
out he wants to scared him what good to
him is a destroyed
Village hello hello yellow
wa W greetings little frog identify
yourself and state your
purpose um I'm I'm course you just saw
me a while
[Music]
ago I'm here to train I was told to come
here wait are you from
bana W oh wow wer wasn't that like metal
chains that wasn't supposed to happen
was it we should run definitely is it
going to attack me now
no yeah yeah do do everything little bug
okay ah I'm helping I'm
helping maybe I shouldn't be
helping he like the biggest damage
dealer I'm just a
distraction oh [\h__\h]
okay he he's still fighting he's still
figh let's go oh he's got some anger
issues he's already dead he's already
dead on the dead on the ground found
he's already dead stop
it chill out
no Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam
Bam what are you thinking this lier is
huge you could have gotten yourself
killed I literally just went to the
training grounds and it attacked me okay
your lucky buo sent me to show you the
ropes who knows what would have got
happened if I hadn't gotten me in time I
just about had it I could have uhuh I
just about had it I I could have had
them or like my buck could have
handled whatever this is too dangerous
for someone as small as you have serious
let's get you back to boa what's the
slier that big even doing here I thought
they didn't live this far north it was
that can he
stop he's still
going oh my
god um he's got some anger issues I
think
[Laughter]
what what is he so angry
about he's already
dead oh oh he's angry that he missed out
on a 100 bucks tip in the
restaurant it was that lios guy a couple
of his soldiers were trying to drag it
over to B I'm pretty sure he was
planning to attack the village of course
that freak would try to pull a stun like
this come on pipsqueak we better get go
tell all the bofo but his Miss and now
you're happy that I you know was here
and found out about all this n are you
not cuz otherwise you wouldn't have gone
there I wouldn't have gone there we
wouldn't have seen that and they would
have attacked us with that
[Music]
so and you're sure it was
Leos yeah it was those two soldiers he
had like those those those horses horse
frogs wait isn't that a
thing oh B have your team take shifts
for night watch for the next few days I
suppose it's a good timing that we got a
new
[Music]
Warrior couldn't focus on the
conversation
oh Alo I know what the Empire is like
the PIP sque doesn't stand a chance
didn't you you see how big that Li sky
was you can't possibly think B out if it
weren't for chorus those soldiers would
have gotten that lier to Boreal people
could have been
hurt whether you like it or not chorus
helped protect the village chorus is
going to train with you and they will
become a part of the defense Guild and
of
discussion understood good night
Elder yeah respect
me I'm maybe
small but my power is triple my
size I'm prank I'm FR and
fr H I'm going to head home now
too I'm sorry course Bal isn't the most
levelheaded individual she has a lot to
learn you your bug also needs to chill
the hell out just just so you know yeah
I'm sorry kind of went out of control
there got some anger issues we'll talk
about it before I go to
sleep I have an angry pocket I'm not
afraid to use them yeah that's my
biggest weapon my bug just does my whole
work for
me wait it's night time I should
go did I get
healed oh no I didn't
M but if I sleep now maybe I'll miss out
on the night
time I mean I that's probably going to
be why is he here
again wait can I could I even
go I mean there'll probably be okay yeah
okay there'll be other opportunities I
can't go
now you have to go byebye
goodbye thank you for
coming oh we're already in Chapter 2 how
many chapters are
there I say already but it's been one a
uh almost half hour
so good morning oh there I think he
wasn't here there before hey heard about
the lier I'm brave of you to fight a
beast like that foolish too you got guts
but you won't last long eh almost haded
I would have been fine even if B hadn't
shown up
sure
okay what's next H hey has training
started uh I forgot all the voices I
came up with for these
people trainings later in the day oh do
you know where Elder buo is he wanted me
to go talk to him this
morning I don't know probably at his
house or something okay before you go
you might be on boer's good side but I'm
the guild leader here oh buer can train
you all he wants thank you oh my god 42
months that's so
long it's my choice whether or not
you're part of the defense skill you may
have survived that fight but I still had
to bail you out also you bug did most of
the work so don't get you hopes up we
might add your bug to the guilt but not
you realistic outcome guess we'll just
have to see
[Music]
then I think she'll probably just add
the bug not
[Music]
me oh oh what is that wait that's is
that is that is that is that the the
angry frog the sand no actually rain
frog you may think it's a sand frog but
we called it a rain frog is that is that
is that he looks like that type of
frog oh my God screaming
frog rain
frog
um you may be screaming in those videos
but he looks like he's just
grumpy
and her final words before her passing
were the final Dawn approaches the
coldest wind shall gra the land the
S the snake yes is there something you
are not telling me of course not you
know how hard I worked with you to end
the war he's pretty small too he's so
cute oh my God look at him look how cute
he
is I would never risk s so ience with
the dry lands then I feel we may need to
prepare our voice for something serious
I'm sorry but the snck is not real just
like crime is not real huh huh it's
real it was just a story invented during
the war to scare you I knew the Frog who
dreamed the story up have I not told you
this
already the the war was ages ago do you
not find it strange to such a young
Frank would know this old T
tail I can't argue with that but that's
just a myth a whole
myth someone must have brought the story
back goodbye
ELO
so he's friend shaped excuse me priest
priest another dude who thinks I'm a
priest my sounds my foot sounds are so
cute
[Music]
oh hello a good morning
chorus what's that what's the SN SN
Snick do you need a Snickers I think you
need need a
Snickers the snake th's dropping no no n
of purpp man don't
misunderstand this it's all right of
course I'm just teasing the Snick is
just an old ghost story we made up in
the war to scare the enemies it's hardly
anything to be concerned about although
I am curious as to why the story has
returned I will have to ask the other
Elders if they have heard similar
stories aside from that chorus I'm glad
you stopped by how come I wanted to ask
what you think of Bala so far I know it
has all been one day but but first
impressions are very important oh it's
fine oh [\h__\h] oopsy no no no I don't mean
it the other worry is it's
just it's nice Bor is really sweet
Village and I really am happy to be
here I I guess I'm disappointed look at
him all the stuff B out said I moved
here to get away from this from that
sort of thing like the
negativity feels easier being here
though it feels like back home everyone
has has a picture of me in their heads
but it isn't who I am but here people
think I'm a priest which is also not who
I am and also the other ones who don't
think I'm a priest they just don't like
me which is also really not nice so
there's not much better from where I
came from
man yeah okay nobody has expectations of
me besides being a priest I don't have
to feel that pressure here no actually I
think you have to feel even more
pressure because they're not not
expecting anything from
you they they don't
those those frogs don't like you but
there are some nice frogs the the the
store frog the pie frog there were some
nice
ones I think I
understand but I don't
agree I'm sure that together we can get
the other Warriors to be more
[Music]
considerate oh there was one more thing
I wanted to talk to you
about I hope this does not come off is
rude but I'd recommend taking your blade
to rimo he's the blacksmith in boreal
trust me when I say that he's the finest
blacksmith you will ever meet he will be
able to determine if your blade is up to
defense skill
standard thank
you I talk to her house is the closest
one to the path away from Boral here I
will put a pin on your map so you do not
forget okay
bye-bye yeah let's upgrade our weapons
good idea cuz one damage is
[Music]
nothing so far so
frog
[Music]
k for the pink Super
Chat blacksmith wait where is the
blacksmith did he put that on the map a
yeah I think so
[Music]
oh
wow he looks cool he also looks like a
cat cat is this a
cat is this a
cat is this a muscle
car is this a
[Music]
butterfly
ah my
[Music]
hand
stay is that a dog frog is this a muscle
[Music]
car holy frog
NY hey ol frog there was supposed to be
a new Warrior tell you do you know where
do you I'm
me sorry about that why don't what what
why why you think I'm holy frog when in
that case I need you to do me a favor uh
the name is raino I'm the blacksmith
around here I have an order of Steel
waiting for me at the forge in the
copper City and I need someone to pick
it up copper
City everyone's so pretentious
therey it's not that bad I was born and
raised there oh sorry if you if you were
raised somewhere like the City why would
you move to somewhere like
borea everyone was super pretentious
there look if you can pick that steel up
for me it would help a lot why can't you
get it I'll just be honest I don't
really like
walking that's how about
hopping that's it if you get it from me
I'll touch up your blade for a discount
H could you do it for free I was about
to say I'd prefer it to be for
free what kind of deal is dead I mean
you're making me walk to Copper City
just because you don't feel like doing
it yourself there's probably monsters on
the way there too and AD doubt it's the
safest trip I feel like touching up my
blade for free is a pretty good trade
for that what if I refuse then I don't
go then yeah then you better get walking
or
hopping nice nice we're good at haggling
all right let's go I like you already
meet me in my shop uh and I'll take a
look at what you're working with wait
after I or
now
now I get the touchup
already oh oh I do but first it sounded
like I have to go there
first my soul is this a S Steel there's
not something you see every day I kind
of went all out when I got a commission
but it only does one freaking
damage I was hoping if I got the best BL
I could it would make up for my
skills listen pal you can give the worst
painter in the world an amazing brush
and their work will still be a load of
mud likewise the world's best P could
make something gorgeous using a single
blade of grass grass or
glass so believe me when they say it's
not the blade that makes the worri but
I'll be the first to admit that saloner
seal is pretty impressive the material
of this blade is high quality but it's
Laing craftsmanship here let me sharpen
it up give me just a moment there's so
much reading in this game my fr's
starting to hurt with all these
voices but I like making
voices fro candy time fr County time
[Music]
K thank you I've been able to sharpen it
a bit further but given how difficult
Salam still is to work with I need
payment for my effort oh wow okay after
that if you want further improvements
I'll need an England of Salamon steel we
can talk again if
you okay no from take a left yeah I know
where it
is tell the big guy I said hi okay thank
you so now we should do more than one
damage I
suppose two
damage let's go power I Feel
[Music]
It by the way we have so much money
right now maybe before the trip I go get
some more food on the
way just in case we're
[Music]
dying welcome back she remembers me she
remembers me heals one heals
two I'll buy and I'll
[Music]
buy yeah maybe one
more okay
bye-bye she's
nice ah story lady always
nice just like
IRL here we go let's go
[Music]
guys and left left right left
right so give the knife to
[Music]
beetle
I still don't want to fight these ones
though oh I got a
hit they go back up so
fast the time window
is
me oh there we
[Music]
go yeah you do that one I I
ah [\h__\h] it no I'm not I'm not dealing
with them until I have a better
[Music]
solution flying enemy not nice not nice
SK
[Music]
all did I go the right way is this way
I'm supposed to
go
wait
did I was that copper city until now and
what I'm
[Music]
confused look at him with his little
straw
damn hi ESO what's that you
holding I'm not sure I can't even tell
what it's made out of some sort of soft
flexible material that is polluting the
Earth that I will choke on if I eat it h
looks delicious wait do you think this
thing is a magic staff I don't think
magic is real magic is
[Music]
real magic I can say is
real okay but if it was this would
definitely be a magic staff right yes hm
I guess so whenever it's made out of
doesn't really look natural exactly
magic materials just between you and me
my guess is that this magic stuff is
extremely
powerful with this and my shield I'm
going to be
unstoppable that's the guy with the with
the bottle
cap yes rest and push
[Music]
button
open
it's very pretty here very bright too oh
purple wait where's my bug I got rid of
it
accidentally oh strong bug did the bug
also get upgraded or what I feel like
it's also stronger
[Music]
now oh
dear oh now I only only took one damage
[Music]
interesting be I cannot kill the
Bees No I did but you're not supposed to
hurt the bees look at him look at him
twirl like a
girl oh my God you TW like a
[Music]
girl these bees are our
friends yeah I feel pretty
bad I wonder how that bee is doing that
I saw yesterday it's probably dead by
now man oh is that eggs what egg egg
egg oh it didn't even try to fight back
they're not even fighting back what am I
doing why am I so ruthless and
evil why am I like
[Music]
this spare them I should I don't even
get exp
so so yeah maybe I'll spare them
[Music]
now I guess in that way it's similar to
Zelda where it's a an
RPG in my
eyes but you don't get exp exp wait so
is this really I just saw in a
description it was
saying it was saying RPG but is it don't
you yeah it's not sorry one game
description and I found it said action
RPG so I was like
okay isn't that the general
um necessity to call ah [\h__\h] you
ouch to call
something an RPG to have a level
system AC RPG is just the most generic
term pretty big pretty loose oh
[Music]
okay yeah get him get
him I'm just a
distraction oh God I have so low HP
again
[Music]
a game where you assume the core of
a the role of a character yeah I guess
[Music]
so more of an action adventure game
mhm I guess
[Music]
so honestly even if I want to fight the
enemy the bug is just so fast and push
PES it away from me easy solution would
be getting rid of the bug but I don't
want
to it's
[Music]
chill I can dodge fruity enemy when it
attacks and not take damage it
seems okay we we have committed to not
hurting the Beast you guys shall do the
same
IRL
[Music]
ow maybe I'll
uh have a a little
Huckleberry Buck only
challenge
be exactly there I knew it I knew I had
a feeling I was like ah maybe I should
wait until the next
map oh I feel like there's a boss
here oh what's with
him what are you hello is this even a
frog I think so hello there what do you
think of the sculpture I'm working on
looks neat what exactly is it oh not
sure just like making these sort of
shapes I use clay from the bottom of
this pool then I let it dry out in the
sun really fun oh man so
creative I'm going to go get back to
working on this one the loops aren't
quite right there yet wow artistic
frog does he look like a frog to
you I wonder what kind of frog it's
supposed to
[Music]
be I'm sure they're all like supposed to
be a certain
[Music]
type
what frog am I am I just a garden frog
uh normal the basic
[Music]
one I'm barely doing
anything I'm just enjoying hopping
through the
game yeah Pond Frog Pond Frog maybe or
tree
frog could be tree
frog
although the markings around the eyes
are are those like very typical of
something look at this
oh it hit sorry I didn't mean to scare
you oh don't worry about it I'm scared
of most
things scar frog
oh nice checkpoint one of the others
called it ah they did they called me
tree
frog
oh my
[Music]
identity
H oh there's a secret there but again I
don't know how
to I don't know what to do with that is
that for later in the
[Music]
game yeah do I get B
PS we need a name for the bug ow okay
this time you hurt me
first cuz I ran into
[Music]
it what do we call the bug
guys help me find a
name wasn't it beetlebot we'll give it a
new new name cuz beetlebot is too long
and I find the word bug to be difficult
to say anyway in the first
place oh hey they're more aggressive now
they're what the
[\h__\h] now they're attacking me I'm almost
[Music]
dead baby emergency
snack
JY
yumy is there no healing spot
here Yum Yum Yum yumy healing
[Music]
no I don't want to eat my Pie
already but
[Music]
okay
Sheldon I like that name
[Music]
Hercules buggy
Malone wow wait frog looks like me in
blue he's
small there's a lot lots of
bugs cute de de I found many bugs
de this is a treasure Grove of bugs de
de got to do something here fix
[Music]
it hello who are
you he's so cute he's so blue I'm green
you're
blue nice are you narissa I saw narissa
is frog fan art today like I put frog
suit on her and then she was a blue
frog she looked really good as a
[Music]
frog blue
woman oh oh hi there are you here to
pick up a pet
oh can
I oh I have a sanctuary here for lost
pets sometimes people come back for them
but not always oh oh oh I'm glad to be
here for what this is a like a
shelter
what who would who would do
this that's very kind of you thank you
it's not always easy taking care of so
many pets but it's always worth it oh my
God I I'll take one if they're as
helpful as my my bug that I don't have a
name for
yet not a h
do that's a cute
little a cute little
[Music]
find what
name what what if we call
it
kitty it's my
kitty kitty
cat call it something that it's not I
like that
[Music]
yeah come kitty
kitty good
[Music]
kitty H guys my phone died again like
that time uh when narissa was
[Music]
here I let it go a little bit too low on
on battery again and then it died and
now I can't charge it again and I did
back then buy a charge uh a a wireless
charger
remember because that was seemingly the
only way we could charge it back up but
the the charg charger the wireless
charger is not really working either it
works on my other phone but it doesn't
work on this one
so yeah I might have to take it to the
store again but tomorrow is a
Sunday so I'll story are not
open so that's a little bit of a problem
my phone is
dead so I don't know if my mommy is
watching this but just so you know if
you're writing to me on Whatsapp
anything I I can't see it right now I
mean I could switch SIM cards but I'm
too Bor uh too
lazy tomorrow's oh yeah okay wait does
that mean Monday is Monday a a holiday
in Austria Easter Monday or
so oh
Secrets
oh yeah oh [\h__\h] so Monday is not open
either a damn it oh New Life new
heart yay oh let's
go
nice always check behind the w Falls
yeah
y oh I like the
floor make Co Falls I guess this kind of
like hints you like if you look at this
you see that maybe there's a path behind
them waterfall could try leaving it on
the charger for a few days just to see
yeah well I did leave it it's it's on it
right now even though it wasn't charging
I put it on top of it
anyway we'll
see M eyes sparkle a brilliant blue
color such a beautiful Hue that
anara an AA color the Seas after them
I'm pretty sure meu that's horribly at
the end of the
story oh no we'll leave that part
[Music]
out something has a loose no no no it's
not a loose cable as I said the other
phone will charge is just this
phone that has this issue generally like
we looked it up back then and we found
out out that the Samsung
s22 and also the new ones
s23 even though they made a new one they
didn't fix the issue they have like some
some of them have a battery
issue where it just won't charge anymore
after it's out of battery
once
yeah
K also oh yo
that's the dudes ohas what are you doing
[Music]
here am I supposed to know you he he
they all forgot me again stay stay back
in I'll not let you inter fear with Lord
slip plant
[Music]
again
again um
dummy my Lord this Li's mission was not
as successful as planed but it wasn't
their fault
this little tree F snuck up a tree [\h__\h]
there you go snuck up on us and free the
sler I beg your forgiveness my Lord it
won't happen
again no matter B's time is coming to an
anend lier or not what's going to happen
to
Bala wretched Brett you really think
your village is important my plans are
far bigger than you
realize Boral is puny and
weak wait is he is he
is he his frog type cuz he's so big is
he that that Australian toad that we
talked about what was his what was the
[Music]
name yeah Kane Kan toad is he a Kan toad
could he
be cuz he's so big thank
[Music]
you
thank you for the membership thank you
than
it B real Bey and weaked means nothing
to
me I have my sight set on something far
larger you're lucky I'm in a good mood
as I just finished discussing
arrangements for the copper City to join
my Empire oh
oh a good night sleep well sleep well
mate
he she let you live for now run back to
your little village and continue your
holy studies while you can uh I'm not a
scholar I'm in to defend what is this
some kind of like running joke and
like maybe a previous game they made why
do they all think he's a priest or
scholar is it because he's small and
that's what small frogs do or
[Music]
what cuz I'm
small or tree frogs maybe are
usually
maybe
fre this is for the NG Plus uhhuh
H that they had religious names so maybe
the p is from a religious
Homeland they think they can't be part
of the ah but isn't there more than just
a priest and a defense Guild I'm sure
there's like more things that you could
[Music]
be cute run along now little warrior go
back and War to your pitiful Village
whatever you're up to isn't going to
work but that's not what I came for I
need a
metal
so I'm not going to go back
now
ooh
hello you won't talk to me okay H how
who goes there uh of course I'm just I'm
just messing with you it's my first day
it's a guard I've always wanted to say
that how to goes there stop right there
classic guard stuff well good luck with
the thanks thanks
[Music]
indeed here we
are cute quite the big city
wow oh he's got bombs
[Music]
oh BS see an ugly crumbling oh bang
surrounded by monsters bang just want to
see a really cool explosion come bombs
yeah um do be safe with them though you
could really hurt yourself if you them
wrong you can buy Six bombs for 20 or 12
for
45 oh that's a good deal
right yo thank you how do I use them
Place bomb down okay
nice look at him who's he he's got
wings oh wait what what go back to
beginning I'm a tree frog I lived in
tens fall my whole life I know all about
Anora of course I'm sure do you have a
moment to talk about her anyways yeah oh
really I've never gotten this far before
like Lord and Savior or something like
that I I don't have anything prepared
come back
tomorrow okay
in honor of malder De Brave founder of
our prosperous City may your legacy live
ages to
come I'm guessing I can't enter any of
these houses besides the one that are
marked oh ah grappies I think I was
supposed to greet you what can I get for
you and raino says Hi H
still getting others to do his chores
for him is he h he was always one of my
favorite customers when you get back
tell him to get his butt down here tell
him I miss
[Music]
him
sneeze
no yeah no actually wait don't tell him
I said that maybe don't say that it's
specifically me who Mr same or anything
maybe just uh maybe uh forget I said
anything
wow
W they're they're a bit expensive though
I get some flap
[Music]
checks well I had a steak sandwich in
the
[Music]
airplane it was
okay
[Music]
bye-bye and they're so expensive what
the
hell big CA is
expensive oh look at that cute little
poison frog is it a dart frog do you
think hello hi are you from comper City
I'm just passing through me have you had
any food here yet I've heard that honey
dew here is delicious there's so many
kinds of snacks in Salia it's so
exciting shaving around trying all sorts
of food a [\h__\h] I keep on pressing the
button too
much cute
[Music]
frog goodness do you think that
Monster's real I don't know but ra saved
I'm sorry right I guess so I don't much
like that Lord
Li look at this one that looks like like
the the lowbudget poison dart
frog hello would you be interested in
purchasing a cute cudly plushy oh can I
put that in my house oh made for me
these plushies would be a lovely way to
decorate you home there we go the first
plushy I have for sale is a cute little
po plushy I can sell oh it's
cheap I'll buy
it thank you I'll make him rich
C to
frog you'll also unlock new items at the
end of each chapter so make sure to
check your chest at home oh okay sounds
good look this frog has
flower oh it's covering one of its eyes
or I like your hat it's really
pretty thank you sadly it seems I'm a
bit stuck stuck what do you mean the
moment I move I just know this flower
will take BL in the Wind
oh and so I'm stuck
here the cost of being
cute oh do you want the piece of
cheesecake yes I have an extra piece
that I'm not going to
eat thank you oh my god what an angel
Marry Me Marry
[Music]
Me what is this whoo Library
oh this one wasn't even
marked there's a book on this shelf
titled culture and practices of the
ancient civilization
ofalia
[Music]
no the Twisted Queen oh interesting
titles musings on the
polet
[Music]
no no not
now sorry my
[Music]
eye something in my eye oh hey you also
got a cute bug is that your pet frogs
have bug pets what the
hell that is so cute I hope you never
lose your control and eat
it good afternoon ma'am or sir or uh I'm
not a girl or a boy oh that's cool I
didn't know you could do that
but what's the not girl boy version of
m' and
sir I don't know actually that's okay
I'll make one up have a good rest of
your day
smm no I like it
smm
smm waa what the [\h__\h] oh
Lord he's
melting this is my darling Cobalt is so
beautiful she's uh she wasn't cheap
either I got her important from some Far
Away Island her shell is naturally shiny
already but I make sure to polish her
shell every day to give it the gorgeous
glimmer
[Music]
shees
yo he can crush
me okay let's go in
here
[Music]
spooky welcome with to the shop of a for
this if you're looking for the findest
honey you know s you've come to the
right place whether you want spiced
sweet or bitter I only sell the best a
bottle of air for this honey will leave
you refreshed Beyond a bottle of Honey
Dew will heal you fly and then some all
extra hearts
if you like a bottle it will cost you
85 I mean yeah we can take one for
now well you didn't ask me if I wanted
the sweet sour or
savory I didn't got to
[Music]
choose H okay so wait where am I going
to get that metal I thought I was going
to get it
[Music]
here oh yeah he said something about a
monster and something along the lines of
the snippet is coming the
snippet not the Snicket not very good
grandma if you ask me still SC scary
though I don't know about you but I'd
rather not get
snipped was it here or was it
[Music]
like I feel like what's
here Rocky wa oh what the hell oh maybe
he has the metal yeah oh yeah I found it
it I'm here to pick up an
order rainbow that's
right oh thank
you be careful out there yeah you be
careful with your little little toy
hands in the lava strange Whispers going
around ever since that bullfrog emper
guy showed up talking about
[Music]
some what the S it
yeah I think it now was the name
rib well thank you again for the steal
tell R I hope he's doing all right
Ribbit I like his place nice
Ambiance anyone's talking about some
sort of monster I'm not buying it though
some 50 fot monster that's going to come
stomping through and kill everyone I
mean yeah there's moners everywhere but
nothing can be that
big
baby wait you're bigger than
me oh what are you up to okay I'm
reviewing the plans for new art gallery
it's going to take a while to build but
I think I'll look very nice once it's
done it's my first big project with the
construction team I'm so excited they oh
he's also a tree frog they little little
tree frogs into the constuction team of
course sure we can't hit a hammer as
hard or carry as much Stone but we can
do things big toes
can't I wish the defense skill would
realize that Throwing
Shade oh are you playing a
game hello there would you like to play
an old Cup game I'm sure you know the
rules I swap the cups around you f the
cup if you pick yeah we
know let's start easy
[Music]
is it the top left I I blinked in the
very beginning and I don't know if it
already moved in that very
beginning I wish say this one but oh
[\h__\h] y thank you
guys with your help surely we can do
hard too right
guys this one's Fast Watch closely oh
God watch Watch Blink now and then never
blink again
go oh
[Music]
God uh I think it's top
left I
thing you lost it
yeah yay hey I got it as well
nice yeah let's gamble some more oh [\h__\h]
I got the easy one I didn't want
[Music]
to I
bottom no what guys help me my eyes
let's do a hard one okay
[Music]
start
[\h__\h]
um I'm counting on you guys for that
[Music]
one
help left again right left top right top
left ah top left was correct one more
guys I I need you to work for me
here okay let's
[Music]
go
sh I lost it I
[Music]
think my eyes are too
tired same
again again is it always left h
this the thir
time okay and my tummy
[Music]
hurt sneak it Snick it
sneak come here whoa I thought something
was burning wait we can go back now
right we got what we
needed can I blink now
yes please
blink please
do oh tummy
hurt tummy hurt tummy hurt
oh what is
[Music]
this
do I have to walk all the way
back Telly hard tell me
hard with a snack out M probably
not
[Music]
ah I
think you know I've been eating a lot of
strawberries
[Music]
recently and at least they're better
than usual but I still think maybe maybe
maybe I I've eaten some not so good ones
although I mean it didn't taste moldy or
anything maybe it's that or it's the
fact that I'm eating those pancakes with
a [\h__\h] ton of Nutella
[Music]
again ah y i
I'm enjoying
the yeah the
crap uh kuu breakfast
again my sweet
[Music]
tooth
why must you hurt me so
much ow why am I letting myself be hurt
so
much a crap ton of Nella
exactly oh why why why why do I do
this I need a healing spot was there one
here
no
not the bees but those bees were more
aggressive than the other ones those
actually attacked
[Music]
me so they're probably more like
wasps wasp
[Music]
wasps
uh was there a secret here yeah let's go
go away go away
kitty kitty is Invincible
okay
oh oh no how much is the cheesecake oh
cinnamon
cheesecake
yummy ow no no why do I let them hit me
so much
now
yeah I don't even know where does this
bring
[Music]
meina today my birthday happy
[Applause]
birthday happy birthday to
[Music]
you why it loading so long
hello hello
hello
hello loading suspiciously
long
hello oh
[Music]
hello I broke
it that doesn't look
right get Dev Dev it's
time see I already said really early on
this is too long I I I knew
it de what do I do do I um close the
game
[Music]
H
de I think I need
to oh wait oh I pressed plus I don't
know if it's a coincidence but the
moment I pressed plus it came back I'm
trying to respond it's
okay I fixed it once again fixing my own
bugs oh
[\h__\h] yeah I'm so embarrassing I already
died twice while the death is
watching and I let the fck do everything
for me ah yeah maybe I paused M yeah
not a
h could be could
be I can see that being a
[Music]
thing just try pressing every button if
this happens to you
guys oh God damn
it and this game I mean it's not that
easy okay
the combat is not not that easy I'll
say I'll have you know it's not that
[Music]
easy oh yeah I think I know why cuz I
was going to check if I got my food
still oh yeah I got my food
back I did I thought when I died maybe I
got my food
uh back or maybe not and I wanted to
check that
was there a secret here too no
[Music]
right
but
the the secret that I opened up is I
think still opened up on the map so I
got my food back and I got
healed but the secret is still there
[Music]
nice nature will come up with a better
fool excuse
me I know these bees are not attacking
me but I need to kill something with my
own hands to feel better about
my gaming skill that is not existing
today did you ever play Hol night no I
didn't I didn't but I feel like that
could be a viable option one day
oh
[\h__\h] by the way when I was looking for
frog
song uh Graphics to make the
[Music]
thumbnail I was trying to find like an
HD high resolution graphic of the game
of like the main art without the logo
and I couldn't find anything um but then
I found a
website with a fitting graphic that I
ended up using for the thumbnail
where the logo was a bit higher and the
art was pretty big so I used that but
anyway that
site it was a a website for a frog
convention
seemingly and what the hell I want to go
there but apparently I think it was I
still have it
open froom
2023 yeah yeah yeah it isn't oh it's it
was online anyway they had they had the
game featured on the website there's
like a a gaming section and I saw
several games frog related games that I
have not heard of yet before even though
I've done a lot of research about frog
games and I found oh I I found most of
the good
ones uh so I don't know if for next frog
week I can really fill a whole week with
some good frog
games but those games they all look
really
nice so I think
now I mean next frog week is really
really long long to
go but in case there will be another one
I think I have a a good a
good reference for more frog games to
choose
from frog leag 202
maybe
or what is this oh is this a oh is this
a
riddle do I have to
press yeah yeah this kind of game oh no
oh
no do they all have to be pushed or all
have to be un pushed I
[Music]
wonder what do you think actually I'm
I'm not
sure
uh now I have only
one it started with everything um like
the button being out everywhere except
for this one and this
one maybe there's a
[Music]
clue
um almost B for the king okay so
probably they all have to be
pushed interesting
hint ah I'm so bad with these kind
of
rles
ah I'll just brute
[Music]
for
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
only
[Music]
two only
one damn
it m
no no
no
oh
[Music]
no
no what w the middle one activates all
four surrounding
it
wait
no and
no we'll be here for a while
uh only one
left surely there's like a tactic uh for
when you have only one left how to go
from there this is like
[Music]
chess
I don't know I'm just pressing things
[Music]
randomly
ah again again again just
[Music]
one
do um wait I have an idea
yeah
uh
[Music]
um
no
[Music]
um
huh I know exactly what I'm doing
of
course damn
[Music]
it of
course it has to be like this one one
left I can get to the one left pretty
often pretty
easily
but
wellow how
about
[Music]
how
about
[Music]
no
help oh man oh ah ah
[Music]
won I mean that's not really a deaf kind
of thing that's that's a thing you guys
could help me out with too
can get
help am I writing a program to solve
this or k solving it you're writing a
program to solve this that's a bit
[Music]
Overkill ah look for a button that
pushes free frog it will be your last
what it will be my last what what what
does what does it sound like a
[Music]
fret fast like one press will end it oh
yeah yeah go up so you can aim to leave
free in the corner make all button GL
what
[Music]
what what help me why ises my kitty not
help me in this
[Music]
situation oh interesting we have
everything up except for one now but I
had that before and I didn't
know where to go from there
um I am right that was a hint
option I wonder if it wait I got it I
got it I got
it right what happened ah oh you get to
hide from it I got it I got
it go let's go get
off another heart very very
necessary for how much damage I take is
that the ah okay that's uh dead end all
right all right nice nice
[Music]
secret maybe we can go to the secret um
that we found in the very beginning the
first
one thank you for the clap clap just
open the beer for I had more time well
you can drink it while
wao nice while you're watching
[Music]
still oh
Mommy ah
[Music]
Mommy good job good job
Kitty such a good
[Music]
kitty yeah more HP that's what I
got maybe you get that in all of the the
secrets I don't
[Music]
know oh hey I have four DMS what the
hell
oh okay I got I got two more eggs let me
send them to seaf
foam
uh rer
egg and beu beu egg looks
nice
[Music]
eggs eggs
eggs preparation is going
well I need to make an egg too
[Music]
still I guess maybe I'll make a frog
egg I think I should make a frog
egg
[Music]
yes also I need to find some bgm to
implement in the in the
map did I tell you this time we're going
to have the I told you right the
scavenger hun Hunt is going to be in the
in a studio where the
camera uh setting stuff F will will be
working so HMA HMA is going to assist
even though Amma is not there HMA will
be helping out cuz HMA already has a lot
of experience with controlling the
cameras smaller area yeah but it's like
more competitive in a way than last
time after all it's the Hunger Games so
it has to be
[Music]
competitive thank you
Hammer
indeed but I feel so bad because it's
going to be 700 a.m.
jst and hma's probably going to be uh D
to like troubleshoot a little bit and
like check out the all the camera angles
and all that
so got to wake up early for me it's
midnight start so I'll just be awake you
know already anyway for my
[Music]
streams
yeah
uh tummy
horn tummy
horn
I feel like I'm hitting but I know I'm
not I'm just
like I I'm Kitty is just too
fast K need's pushing away my enemies I
would totally One V one
them totally see these bees are not
aggressive I
think yeah kid does one oh memberships
thank you wait oops
see thank you so
much y the way back is so
[Music]
long I thought maybe we need some NPCs
that for some reason teleport us back
but no no we have to walk all the
way ah we're here
[Music]
again I think I'll go Idol meeting for a
moment will you guys take care of
froggy for
me
okay
byebye
e
so the my let me go grab some water
too
oh
[Music]
I
I dropped um a caramic bowl on my
toe
oh oh but it didn't shatter at least but
maybe something shattered in my toe
did you hear the
bowl oh it still
hurts you
did
wait isn't it funny Would it be funny if
I break my toe like that lady from the
store uh that would be so funny maybe
because I love her so much I I wanted to
I don't know be like her oh it really
hurts still oh my God wait normally if I
stop my toe it doesn't hurt so
long ow
[Music]
can you feel a
pain I see it um it's
not it's not really it's not bleeding
but I see let me lift my my leg okay I
see something
happen
what is
this it looks weird some kind of is this
bone is this piece of bone coming out of
my toe no just kidding just
kidding um damn it
hurts would it would it be so funny if I
finally broke something I always say I
always want to break something maybe I
finally broke
something oh oh do it again for the
content it's really difficult to tell it
toe's broken without some kind of X-ray
or CT scan don't don't don't a lot of
people go without knowing that their toe
is broken but it actually really hurts
wow H ow
ow oh get some ice H I don't know if I
have like ice like that um oh I think
maybe I have ice cubes that I could put
in a
bag uh
oh I'll I'll try to make
something
okay okay I'm making some ice
cubes toll still hurts but it's um I I
think it's getting a little bit better
let me put that let me put those ah
cold cold let me put those
meatballs oh my
toes
ah ah it's so
cold
ah not
directly what if I I should put on a
sock at least maybe I'm not wearing
socks right
now
[Music]
what
trying times
[Music]
yeah sock is on ice is on
this way it's not too
bad okay remind me of my meatballs so
that I don't keep them out for too
long but how fast how how long do ice
cubes need to become ice
cubes ow ow it's so
cold how long do ice cubes need
legitimate question people are saying
that apparently there is a fast travel
boat where was that by the
water was there one by the because there
were some Waters right
ow depends on how cold your freezer is M
I missed it no
[Music]
sorry
ah few minutes to hours
damn clean socks of course they're clean
socks I I have so many socks ow ow
ow how I want I can I how do I know I
broke my toe can I know is there a
chance I broke my
toe I'd be so
happy I'd be so
happy man maybe it's not probably just a
small fracture or
[Music]
so it's always a chance try wiggling it
oh but now I can't see cuz I wear a
sock wait what happens if I wiggle
it
[Music]
wait what color is it now well that part
is
[Music]
um
oh it looks different than the toe on
the other
[Music]
side the same toe on the other side
looks a bit
different I think I don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
know
[Music]
oh
uh yeah I mean bending I I can kind of
bend it but it
[Music]
[Laughter]
hurts no I want to break it
no oh it
hurts oh my toe oh my oh
my oh
[Music]
my I want to break my
toe okay the death is probably what
what's wrong with this woman with this
frog is because I never broke anything
in my life and I kind of um want
to I I aspire to break a bone someday
and this was I mean this is the best
bone that could ever break like cuz like
I mean it won't hinder me too much
and it probably hurts less than other
bones that you could break and you know
know it's like the best
one
uh when when you dance well f is over
so for now
[Music]
oh I got the
meal tell she helps you're doing
good
man that
[Music]
hurts I broke a toe once and it was just
annoying oh that's fine that that sounds
good that sounds pretty
[Music]
decent don't don't call it just a
sweller
oh oh man oh it actually
[Music]
hurts why why it hurt so much
I hurt so
[Music]
much I'm not I'm not touching it I'm
just I just leaned back cuz it
hurts you want a broken bone h no I'm
just I'm just hope hoping that if this
hurts so much it better be a broken
one did you take any pain no I don't
want
to ow ow
ow ow
[Music]
ow it's funny cuz the the bowl the bowl
had um eggshells in it so when the bowl
fell down the eggshells scattered all
over and first I thought that my bowl
broke but then I realized oh it's just
the eggshells thank God that were
already
broken my
toe
Mye my
toe I'm so sorry
de trying to reposition the ice in a way
that it's
better I don't know should I go to a
hospital what if it's just like swe ing
or like you know nothing big and then I
feel stupid for going
there
um why is it a weekend why is it got to
be on a weekend and then on a on a
holiday though like the normal doctors
won't be all
open and the hospitals might be
crowded oh I don't I barely feel the
cold ah
ah well it's going to be
[Music]
Easter my my
meatballs they're not cold
[Music]
no I'm not touching it I'm just
repositioning the
[Music]
meat if it goes dark purple get it
looked
at okay here come the
Clippers I guess I'm having
meatballs I don't know if I can play
like this it really
hurts [\h__\h]
[Music]
no why did this have to happen
what [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] I need to finish this game in one
stream how far how far am I into the
game it feels like I've have barely
Advanced
[Music]
oh
SE can you tell me how far I am oh
probably not very
[Music]
far
2% that's not the dep I won't trust you
I don't trust you I turn into a
dog
[Music]
I'm still in the no you're also not the
de I don't trust you Frog King is a
friend of the dev oh absolutely don't
finish this game if you're hurting too
much
step
no tell me how far I
am wait so what what is like 2% 3% real
no
way how can that be
[Music]
possible there's six
chapters yeah [\h__\h]
no but like what what what then I I'm
just being pain on my
own without fun
game
let me let me see how let me see let me
try for a little
[Music]
bit not if you go to the
doctor I feel so stupid if I go to the
hospital because of a
[Music]
toll also
H my phone not working is a little bit
of an issue
I I'd like to contact my brother and ask
him if he wants to go with
me I mean it's the end the week
anyway a
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] mommy are you watching my stream if
yes maybe say something to me on Discord
can if you're watching can you ask my
brother if he wants to go to the
hospital with
me
oh
mommy
mommy mom
Mommy what's my mommy's Discord name
again he really I there
Mommy wait I have my brother on Discord
[Music]
too uh what's my brother's Discord
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow I think I have him
on this C don't
[Music]
I I don't
remember is any of this my brother
no I can't tell BR
toy
[Music]
let me look at my my toe again how it's
developing I
mean it's not getting much
[Music]
bigger
I wonder if that part cuz it's the very
tip can that even break it's the very
tip of it I mean I think it's a like a
knuckle feel like it has like one toe
has like maybe two Knuckles where it
bends
right I think it hurts the most and it
fell on the the top uh
[Music]
knuckle wait for an hour or two and
decide then what to do uh you mean okay
wait if it still hurts in 2 hours or so
it's going to get later and later but
maybe maybe the hospital will be emptier
and
emptier oh
man oh
man Tak will be on a break because of a
broken toe and it happened on stream
it's a work accident they have to pay
right no no because I'm not under
insurance from the company or so
[Music]
what can the hospital even do for me if
I besides giving me
painkillers if it's not a broken bone
what can they even
do what would they do guys tell me is it
even
worth to
transpl a a a
splint a
splint
SU
oh oh oh give it some support like
mental support talk to my toe and be
like you're going to
be
ow
ow yeah that's not a normal toe Bonk
that's really painful man I feel so bad
I want to play this
game
uh
I think I can't play like this it hurts
too
much I already have ice on
[Music]
it always next frog no no no I I would I
would play it next week
again extend frog leek for one day like
but not like probably somewhere in the
middle of the
[Music]
week damn
it wait wait let me think can I I do it
no no no no no it's it's like a
pulsating pain when
I yeah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
why this is why you need a gamer bottle
just don't leave don't leave the table
the gaming table don't leave this the
chair cuz that was the issue in the
[Laughter]
end
M if the pain doesn't go away in an hour
then it's something more serious
okay is the bowl
good I hope it didn't hurt the poor
thing oh
man no man
[Music]
oh let me
think let me let me
[Music]
try I have I have a little bit more IU
profine IU profane at
home but then I don't know if it hurts
so unless it's probably not going to be
that strong
but I think
it's I
think I think it's it's chilling a
little bit
[Music]
okay yesterday I cried and we have a
really emotional moment today I break my
toe exciting frog
week what will happen
tomorrow h Hello deare chorus did you
have a question yeah actually I've got
an update on the
Snick situation
it definitely still hurts but I think I
can try a little bit let me see if I can
do it if I can move
on I went to The Copper City and the
people were talking about it lias was
there too someone said that everyone
started talking about the stinet after
he showed up do you think that's the
disaster he was talking about yesterday
oh for 's sake I really should have
known that it was Lord lius first
attempt sler attempted slier attack and
now oh they Snick
[Music]
it my Dynamic wink
ow
ow stupid
[Music]
meatballs they're not
like they're still frozen but they're
not they're not too
they they like they don't stay in
[Music]
place he must be trying to cause Panic
it is the exact same reason we invented
the story during the war to freten the
enemy with a madeup beast only we could
stop the toal Empire seems to be a
bigger threat than they first
appeared I prend that ice are going to
be what the doctors will suggest in the
one if it gets worse get a splint for a
few days sounds like a spring to can we
just say for fun that it's
broken can we just say you like
[Music]
that yeah
sure
yeah
smashed he smashed my
toe
shattered
[Music]
doesn't count hey it
counts no it doesn't
sadly That's How we'll tell the story
yeah yeah
yeah a cast signing stream but then what
who I'll just be signing in you guys
can't sign my cast unless it's a digital
cast for my toe it will be really tiny
can you even all sign so so
small I barely feel the Ice
Man H come and see me tomorrow morning
chorus I will come up with a plan
tonight on how we can stop this rumor
from spreading okay I'll see you
[Music]
tomorrow I lost my toe he's
gone no more toe no more toe for the WWA
I had one toe and I lost
it it was
towed cuz I parked it wrong tow
away no my toe oh no my
toe feed people in
tramples
oh my toe perms
revoked
[Music]
ah n oh oh I can put it like like on the
floor on the Shelf on on the table and
on the Shelf I'll put it here for
now
nice oh these things as well
[Music]
oo
nice
flower
a little bit difficult with the
joystick to put it where I want it oh a
rock a grass
rug what's
this there you
go
plant oh what else the
bowl no I wanted more the
M it makes a squeaky
sound this looks like a blueberry no no
no no no no no no not a blueberry what I
thought you meant with the
Huckleberry
okay how
to ah
finish
nice I can't believe K's toe exploded
after saving an orphanage from an
explosion oh CH chapter three children
said she's so strong and powerful and
her toe is very broken they came back
and finished stream she's so cool that's
me that's a true story can
confirm halfway there okay I'm going to
do it I feel like it's getting
better okay
wait I
accidentally I was like what the [\h__\h]
just happened
I accidentally put a bomb
there didn't we just talk about
explosions minus one
bomb I was like what the hell my bed
just
exploded my toe
exploded oh it's raining great weather
for a
frog best
weather
[Music]
m my toe was like a father to
you
[Music]
oh what's the path always like this
here I'm going to buy some more
[Music]
food he thank you for welcoming me back
I'm going to
buy I don't know about these prices yo
but I'm going to buy a couple of
these she's
Ving I think it's getting
better I think it's getting a little bit
better
guys good that I didn't give
up never give
[Music]
up look
paddles let's go
we don't have to S it off
now oh too late I already did that
that's why it feels better was I not
supposed to do
that help
it oh is he dead looks like he's not
here maybe he's
outside did he
die is this like one of those sad
moments oh there he is okay he's not
dead no ah good morning chorus just
enjoying the the rain what do you mean
I'm
dead I can't believe your toe saved the
ball I think it may
[Music]
have he cut off his
to oh why
[Music]
such a wonderful weather we're having I
was just taking in the air for a moment
sometimes it's important to Simply
exist
true that structure in the distance what
do you supposed to do is hm um I'm not
sure maybe um Paris I don't
know I'm just saying that from the PO of
a frog you
know obviously it's not
Paris never thought about
it it appears to be massive perhaps it
was built by the ones who walked before
us I wonder what Secrets it
holds oh no
whoa I was hoping that would happen
there must be a storm on its way every
time it storms the lightning strikes
that large Tower I've always wondered
why a structure would be built to be
struck by
lightning anyways how are you doing this
morning I'm all right you said you had a
plan for the lia
situation yeah if people learn of Snick
through Rel us rumors they will be
undoubtedly panicked but if someone were
to warn them before liers arrived they
might know better I've already sent
Warriors to Redwood and clear Bay to
warn their Elders Bal is ready to head
out as well but she's standing by until
I get your answer my answer well you see
I believe the elders would be more
receptive to someone they already know
if you spoke to your old Elder it's more
likely that we he would believe
you you want me to go back to tens fall
I know you had a hard time there if
you're not comfortable going B outwell
you can head to the to Moss Fen instead
no I'll do it despite everything I'll
still do what I can to protect tall if
you're sure then basal will go to Mosen
you will head to tful I'm sure you know
the way just explain the situation to
Elder acis hopefully we can end this
Invasion before it truly begins um okay
t
fall return home yeah and I'll be a hero
eventually eventually then they'll treat
me like the hero I am aspiring to
[Music]
be wait
so we're taking a
boat I'll AO a a boat a boat the boat a
aboard aboard the boat par to travel
five car to travel uh yeah where wait
wait wait wait ah no wait took the M
there's only copper
City no no no no no you need to show me
the options before I have to pay money
dude
hey and I button mashed again but there
was no other choice anyway and they
already took my money but now we know
about the boat I don't have wait look at
my money look at my money you like that
don't
you I don't really have anything to do
here right
so I'll go
back at least it's
cheap
[Music]
yeah
okay well where was I supposed to go
[Music]
to upgrade blade upgrade
blade what again huh
nothing didn't we already do that I can
do it
again but didn't I need a more salamanda
steel uh 100
okay but he doesn't need to steal yet I
guess from next time
onwards we'll upgraded
though
yeah uh yeah now we need to steal for
anym
can can
[Music]
canit and so I did
that H it didn't get checked though
[Music]
why H why I upgraded it right and now
it's free damage free damage what a
deal how do I go how do I go to t
[Music]
fall do I need to sleep
maybe guess it needs more but I don't I
don't have any more I
thought of the
material ah I guess I can go on the way
on the way back yeah true that's where I
came
from yeah cute frog
walking Southeast gling gr oh nothing of
that says tense
fall but I guess we still go that way
[Music]
where was there this okay I was about to
ask where was the little thing wa
explosion do I get another heart in here
I
do yo amazing we got so many
now
y
nice he loves the standing explosions he
loves the chaos he Embraces
[Music]
it is this really the right
way can I really go to where I need to
go Ice Cube Check yeah
probably let me check I kind of doubt
it but let's
[Music]
see they are still very very
liquid but I'm
okay I'm
okay yeah I can
walk I'm
fine I'm so sad I'm fine I wish I wasn't
fine I wish I wasn't
[Music]
fine
guys why don't you want me to follow my
dreams I don't get
[Music]
it I thought you guys were supportive of
me and my life
[Music]
goals
[Laughter]
what a strange fixation you have getting
injured maybe I just want someone to
care for me look at him try his
best
a surprised he even sees that as an
enemy oh there's another one here I
didn't remember that one oh it's a
potion let me
check mysteriously fizzy sip this Vivid
teal liquid Sparkles with strange
stinging bubbles it has sticky a sickly
sweet flavor similar to tropical
fruit pineapple
sounds
delicious okay I I might I really I
really hope I'm going the right way now
there seems to be a poth
there and there is the bridge
Again by the way with the Witcher is
there any people who watch The Witcher
I'm at the part
now
where where am
I she she had um the the
girl had the girl of the the spine the
Twisted spine she had and love she made
love with the
guy and uh yeah
yenifer
and uh I met this girl that I only know
from PE I I knew her name from people
cosplaying her a lot
Tris but I was surprised I thought she
had red hair I guess she has red hair in
the game cuz I feel like I I remember
people cosplaying her with red
hair Trish marry
gold
mhm yeah I really like it so far and
they they called Thunder in the bottle I
had to think about the thunder in the
bottle when I saw the thunder hitting
the tower there play your tune and your
heart will grow there are five symbols
above the
message not like I can sing yet I guess
the game has to teach
me they changed a lot from the books
show producers hate the books so they
change everything oh so in the books she
had ah wait okay here I can already make
music teach me the Frog
song
okay minus Japanese
o yeah down down
mouth and and the other o and two
dots uh minus o mouth uh other way ooh
and two
dots o
o
minus
here the
ooh I I think this one
first then the down mouth
and the other way or maybe it was the
other way
around and the dot right or two
dots ah was it
wrong
minus this one
first maybe the mouth this one and two
dots I think it l two dos ah there we go
yeah it was just a matter of the
Ooze
ah you have to head out okay well I hope
there will be not any cases where I have
to call for the death again if you're
leaving everything better be going
smoothly without your
presence another heart let's
go
someone play Sparks with
this someone compose it go go go
go or do you or any wa
song this is kind of sus looking
[Music]
no stream Bell
Sparks
[Music]
okay can I read this
no okay and I think I took the the good
path first cuz that was a dead end it's
the RPG brain in my
brain death friend death friend fills in
okie dokie you also seem to be a frog
lover do you guys just surround
yourselves with with frog
lovers I know have any frog lovers in my
friend Circle
man I'm in the wrong
Community seems like it frogs are cute y
hella cute both me and you have pet
frogs tell me about
it I'm I I I really want either frogs or
you know an aquarium with some fishies
but I feel like
I don't know where I would put it at
least for for an aquarium I feel like
for a frog if you just have one frog
then doesn't need to have such a big big
big big terrarium so maybe I can find
some good space but you have threee
white tree frogs two Pacman ah the tiny
ones and a milk frog what's a milk
frog got to look it
up milk frog
oh wow
[Music]
cute
wow oh my God so
cute oh Amazon
[Music]
milk it is sometimes referred to as the
blue milk fruck due to a sticky
milk-like substance that they produce
when feeling
threatened what are you going to do
producing that substance huh how is that
going to help you just it's like peeing
[Music]
yourself
yeah I'm really interesting what are you
what are you H H it's esel again oh hey
uh I'm going to be completely honest
with you I have no clue what this is um
I'm not quite sure Eva is it like one of
these things you you pull With the Wind
to like
go I don't
know is it the like a a
kite is it a pro is it although that
would be really small if you think about
how small these frogs
[Music]
are I mean it looks like it's supposed
to be some sort of creature it's furry
and it's got fake eyes but I have no
clue what's up with the string wait the
string might be the key to it all what
do you mean it's B
ah yeah that makes sense of the size too
H what bait for what aren't there
stories that saying this Forest used to
be filled with magic monsters maybe some
form some of them are still around and
looking at this bait whenever it has it
is it's it has got to be real weird and
real creepy and with this bait I'm going
to cat it oh good luck with that I think
the bait is meant for something
else but I wish you luck in your
endeavors he's so cute we always find
him in random places with random
items he probably is a hoarder his home
is filled with like random plastic and
cork screw whatever
objects oh look at all the pets the
cuties
oh [\h__\h] no by accident I pressed that
button again no my
bombs my
[Music]
bombs I I press it cuz I want to exit
out of um like an instinct I want to
exit out of the the sleeping
menu oh my
toe look at him look at him oh I can
talk to
him he's up there what's up
frog secret frog
hello I am a being from Beyond I can see
you in the tree there no you can't I'm a
ghost keep my words forces of power and
Malice have begun to emerge
H I implore you child of the vo stay
vigilant let's you encounter danger far
stronger than yourself and remember to
stay hydrated cowboy on the
[Music]
water are you just out here messing with
people who walk by
no leave now let me be frog
Ghost frog
ghost cute the way he's hanging onto the
tree so
[Music]
cute I like the music on this map maybe
also because um I Heard the other music
for way too long
now but I like this
one it it fits the forest I
think very Adventure
vibes
frog of the tree tell us your wisdom the
wisdom is danger stranger
danger
oh wait wasn't I just here no I don't
remember being here what do you mean oh
no I'm going a am I
I honestly I would not have noticed that
I was going in circles if
maybe this wasn't the best
[Music]
idea or is it was the frog saying that
oh oh oh we looks similar even though he
looks more like brownish up there the
picture looks so
green oh sorry I didn't mean to sneak up
on you ah CH I'm actually really glad
you're here NE since you're in the
defense Guild is there any chance you
could help me
out well it's almost the 10th
anniversary of when but without Jo the
defense skill I wanted to get her some
something nice as a gift but I got lost
no there's a lot of moners here oh yeah
I could help take you back to Boreal
safely no I have to go the other way I
still want to get something nice for B
out I just feel safe if I wasn't alone
oh sure um I'm on my way to t fall to
talk to my old Elder maybe we could find
a gift there okay are you going to fight
with me
too he's so
big be careful to not stomp on me
please party got
bigger yeah let's see if he fights with
[Music]
me no he is not
intending to fight it
seems all
right if you don't want to help then why
are you in the defense wait I know I
think this frog is not in the defense
skill never mind that's why they were
like oh yeah you're in the defense Guild
can you help
me I chose the right path first I hope
that's the right
decision
I feel like there's a lot of
[Music]
empty little areas where there's no no
enemies either oh yeah I did the right
decision I did make it oh he wants worms
want worm mman knows you want worm
Mudman has
worms keep worm yes if worm is what you
truly desire mman will give you we'll
take worm worm
yeah yeah
wors oh that's that was R oh I didn't
recognize her oh [\h__\h] oopsie oopsie
she's she's interested in Bal out of all
frogs
Wow have worm now take can eat frog uh
can eat
worm
no what what's do with worm more
worm more worm
yes oh wait take money no not take
money now now two worm more
worm more more more room more more room
more
[Applause]
what are they
for 1
worm
more if you rearrange the letters of
worm you can say more no but
yes wait what yeah oh [\h__\h] what warm
burden what do you mean warm burden for
life wait wa wa wa wait he's saying
something else worms are all gone start
off new adventure for Mudman yes perhaps
travel perhaps fight monster perhaps
even Mudman go EV wait I did take all
his worms his worm basket is
empty anything is possible world is
oyster mman is little Pearl
inside people do say the world is your
oyster but I never heard someone end it
by saying the obvious thing that you're
the Pearl inside because what else would
you be there's nothing else in the
Oyster right I never heard that second
part though but I think that's what
you're supposed to do otherwise you
don't get this dialogue you have to get
all the worms this was the only right
thing to do maybe we'll meet him
somewhere else
now cuz the world is his
oyster we freed him from his
worms and now maybe they're forever in
my
inventory the worm worm burden
nice
[Music]
nice I did a good
thing
[Music]
Yes
W wait where's my other
[Music]
there did I just get hurt from that
thing I thought I was already away from
it
I I missed something worm related
earlier oh no
no no is it far
away
[Music]
warm big
Bool free I'll take all please excuse me
what
why why want first area okay I'll
[Music]
okay I try to find worm
later yummy gummy
worms I want some gummy
worms these life worms are just not the
same I want them I want the gummy worms
with the
sugar all the sour stuff on it m best
best worm best
worm you should try feeding your frogs
gummy worms they love
it just kidding don't you probably know
better look at this boy he's got a tail
is is that the is that the Axel oh hello
there I see you still have your tail ah
okay no he's just like still kind of in
your tadpole
form a couple days now I remember when
my legs grew and it's so
exciting is it the water safe everything
outside of the water is so big who knows
what's out there oh I guess when I was
little I was so excited I never thought
about things like that well I can tell
you after being on land for years it's
not that bad oh [\h__\h] no no the butt
maging
no I want to know what what the frog
said
froglet in between form
cute sure there's a lot of uh things
that can go wrong but there's a lot of
amazing things that you can't experience
if you stay in the water M I guess
you're all right do you need help
getting out so cute we can also rip out
your tail make it faster it's like it's
like is I think this is the exact same
situation with human toddlers or
children who are losing their milk teeth
and there's still one there and it's
like you want to get rid of it but like
you're too scared as the child to like
you know wiggle wiggle it out and then
sometimes they the parents are so help
you and they bam rip it out yeah yeah
sometimes you have to force
Evolution I can help you little froglet
let me rip out your
[Music]
tail I still have nightmares about it I
don't think I don't think I ever tried
any crazy method to get uh a tooth out
like
that I was pretty good at wiggling it
out to a point that it was just
fun
yeah baby teeth you know what I mean you
know what I mean I no I'll get out when
I'm ready okay take your
time cute manyi
frog you know Mr or Mrs de
friend developer friend I um I did a
frog tier list that you might find
amusing it's the last 30 minutes of the
the reveal stream you should watch
it I wonder what you think about my frog
opinions my frog
opinions hey what's what's it like being
uh in the defense Guild oh uh um I don't
think I'm actually a part of it yet yeah
not officially I think oh I see well I'm
sure you'll get there soon
enough doesn't
matter I don't need that status I know
I'm a hero on my
own she says
menacingly highly recommended frog
content very very good
education and I'm an educational Channel
after
all what's up these
slugs I guess they only come out when
it's
rainy they're so disgusting in real life
though pretty cute in the game pretty
disgusting
IRL frog bird of course of course frog
bird is on the top of the
list so so uh what do you think of B out
uh she's
rude all she's really done is put me
down since I got here I don't think
she'll ever accept me as part of the
defense Guild kid all oh I don't think
she tries to be mean she's just Rough
Around the Edges she's really protective
of people maybe she's just worried
you'll get hurt there's better ways of
showing
it yeah
I don't
know welcoming me like that with that
attitude is just
me got to work on
yourself oh hello what a fancy hat
you're wearing are you like from frog
detective the other
day did I see you
there hello there's an ER of Adventure
about you I'm guessing you are an
Explorer I used to be an Explorer myself
a treasure hunter to be exact I but
those days are long behind me my name is
melis what is yours I'm
course have you ever heard of the Lily
ston chorus or heard beautiful little
drums crafted by the Ancients of
Salia when I carry one with me I feel
more determined
I'm sure it is merely a placeo a place
boow but if nothing else they're nice to
look at there's plenty of Lily Stones
hiding around our land in fact I believe
I know where some are right now if you
like I could mark their locations on
your map for you a treasure hunter
instincts never wrong would you like me
to mark you the the locations of Lily
stones on your map on your map
eh that that that maybe not that again
makes it a lot easier huh and we we've
been finding them pretty easily already
anyway I on the
map maybe no ah an Explorer thr and thr
looking for secret treasure on your own
is a bit of a treasure
itself excuse my a accent it's like an
accident my accent is an
accident
yeah uh I know we have to go over there
to the
east but there's also something there I
think we shouldn't go there there's too
much of a
path
[Music]
there's too
much okay I go back to
normal yo I did that all those hits were
from me let me read this actually the
Lost B
oh it's not the goal okay but then this
is actually uh probably another dead end
okay the Lost moth
[Music]
Tavern w
oh
nice
hello you got some good some good uh
juice or something look at them look at
those fros they're so small what are
those those those look like they could
be the the small
[Music]
ones ah pumpkin
toadlets interesting you're giving me
all the all the details about what frogs
they are pumpkin
toad oh my God those are tiny even when
they're not a toadlet holy [\h__\h] no wait
those are no they are always
toadlets cuz I I Googled pumpkin toad
but they just come out as
[Music]
toadlets oh my God
they're so tiny and they are so orange
guys oh my God they're like a small as a
nail they're always called toilets cuz
so little oh my God you're so smart you
know everything about
froggles yes let's go thank you for
sharing your wisdom they're very bad at
jumping because of how small they are I
know a lot of things that are good at
jumping because they're
small
that's
surprising wow this one's kind of big oh
because it's not
real
[Music]
small they look a little bit like okay
this this looks like a chicken
though let me show
you this looks like an a chicken without
its feathers doesn't it like the legs
look at those
legs
looks like it's ready to be put in the
oven this is what this is they look
pretty
accurate but look at the texture of the
[Music]
skin it's literally no unfried raw
chicken
[Music]
skin
amazing
I'm learning so
much making myself a bit
smaller needs barbecue
sauce cute welcome to Welcome to the L
muffin it's the last mouth T I thought
it was a
Tav no no no she's right it's a tab
welcome to the last mouth tabn oh what
do you got I see what I want to talk
about M about you my name's Lina I cook
most of the food it's nice to meet them
I'm as bartender let me know if you need
anything I'm B hi don't think it
personally if she doesn't talk to you
too much she's just
quiet she's Al she's also the smart one
there's no way we could run this place
without
her
[Music]
thanks just cleaning the table
constantly so
cute if you want raw chicken frog and
the most raw chicken is the albino
African clawed frog oh my God what
species of the
sculptor you know
everything albino African claw frog I
think I heard of the African claw frog I
did my research maybe albino African
Cloud
frog what the [\h__\h] yeah that looks like
that you're right that's what that
was that looks exactly like this thing
what the [\h__\h] is
[Laughter]
this oh
no oh
no look at
this this is this is the picture that
looks the most like the
chicken oh my
God oh my
[Music]
God I
mean it almost
looks like a
axel look at
[Music]
this what the hell is
this
crazy he so funny FR are so
[Music]
funny
nice what do you got w
w yo I like the stuff you got cozy soup
tea this is like the perfect menu with
some nice cake as a dessert M five four
and six I'll get one of each man the
food the food in this
[Music]
game I'm hungry now
yeah I I know that issue that feeling
also they should put like a healing
spot here in a restaurant like
this
cuz otherwise I have to eat the food
that I just bought but I want to be
healed for free what's the state of the
Meatballs I put the meatballs back into
the freezer don't
worry we
good okay now we go up this way let's go
follow me follow me how was the toe the
toe yeah why don't you ask for the
meatballs before you ask about my toe
you care more about the meatballs than
about my
toe man what the hell what are those
priorities disappointed in you the
bowl no
um my toe it feels fuzzy and
warm yeah it's okay it's it's it's uh
healing my my will and my will power
basically made it
um I I I wield it to uh being
okay all inflammation response
oh interesting superpowers what is this
place I can't interact with it that's
just a interesting
statue
H that must mean the swelling is done
why does it sound like I I just finished
baking a cake or
something oh pine
cone caution spruce trees ahead watch
for falling pine cones
ah that is the danger of a small animal
like us I can
imagine let the to
cook frog leg ready to
eat excuse
me no one here will be eating my frog
legs oh y y I was looking at
the oh man this that's a lot of pine
clones holy
[\h__\h]
skill issue looking at the
map well I don't live in France I live
in Austria
okay we don't eat frogs
here and I would assume that even in
France it's not that
common just one of those things where
you hear about one thing they eat that's
funny and then you you think you you try
to spread the idea that they eat it all
the
[Music]
time let's give them the benefit of the
doubt okay what frog is
this let's do a frog check every time we
see a new frog we need a frog
check cuz this this one looks
interesting death friend FR
t a Pac-Man subses this is a Pac-Man
shouldn't they be smaller also
like I I was just um wondering cuz like
his his he has like tfts or something
like that that look funny to me is that
a Pac-Man thing Pac-Man frog Pac-Man
frogs are huge I thought they were
small was I thinking of the wrong frogs
packman
frog oh wait they look so
funny they're not that small I guess
[Music]
wow oh they're like perfectly
shaped I think out of all frogs this has
one of the most perfect shapes
yeah they have nice colors too I think
that's why they're so popular as pets
cuz they have nice colors and they're
nice nice
shape this guy is called serum horned
tote
oh
surum
orange ah there we go oh my God it looks
like a
crab it looks like a
crab especially from the
front look oh wait can I put this
in ah it doesn't
show oh because it's saved as a [\h__\h]
AV AV if file what the
[\h__\h] but that's the best
picture the front guys please Google
Pac-Man frog s sing them horned or
something like that
the one where he looks to the front like
maybe I can change can I change
[Music]
the
uh where did I save
it oh I don't know where it
went there it
is
oh a
[\h__\h] the things I do for a
[Music]
frog does this
work
ah no I
worked look at him first of all what a
chunk oh my God
second of all does not does he not look
like a crap to you the color
and and those those tfts and he looks
like you know those
little that's those little Pokey
thingies on his
body
yeah you thought it was a crab right
wow damn what a frog
totally what a frog man Amazing Frog so
okay
sorry frogs are interesting ah ah well
met traveler prepare to be amazed for I
am a wizard witness my Powers behold the
sun's power harnessed the arrange
themselves controlled by the hands of
frog that's a JY of fireflies and the
watering can uh well these components
merely assist me in attuning to Powers
it seems as though these simple Magics
are not impressing one such as yourself
perhaps you would be more interested in
deeper stranger powers powers that allow
you to alter the world around you as
though it were soft clay oh can you do
that I'm still figuring it
out
what I I don't understand but I agree I
agree but I also don't understand as we
like to say here at at
[Music]
kfp well
then is is that one uh poisonous from
now on dear death friend when you give
me a frog name can you also add whoever
and oh I went back we or not it's
poisonous or
not that was a Fairy Circle there oh
really oh you mean this ah indeed I
always want the additional info if it's
poisonous or
not
please for future reference Al and I I
knew this when we did the frog T list I
just forgot to say it and you guys were
like oh did you know and I knew I just
didn't mention it
um I think it was the the poisonous dart
frogs if you keep them as a
pet uh you and you feed
them some basically something they like
not different stuff than from what they
eat in normal nature then they're not
they don't have to be poisonous so it's
basically just depends on what they
eat you guys were telling me that but I
already
knew I I I learned that in my
research which is really interesting cuz
I would have assumed ass they were
always poisonous but no it depends on
their diet
H very interesting all the Slugs around
my money get out of
[Music]
here yeah it's really
cool
wow froggy Effects by Froggy Wawa and de
de frog frog friend dog what what frog
frog friend frog friend
de
frog de friend frog frog de
friend wait did I just go in a
circle I
did now hold this is like a shortcut I
suppose snakes that grew up captive
their poison varies by diet
oh
[Music]
uh okay this
way W more pine
cones yeah but this is a new area right
yeah come here
yeah and now I'm actually doing more
wait isn't my thing missing my
pet there it
is was it missing this whole
time
ow I get to fight a little bit more
these
days or these hours might I
say
you guys know tomorrow
tomorrow tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow it will be April the 1st
right a new month finally this weird
time is over this weird time of me
traveling I was gone for like three
weeks of the month holy
[\h__\h] now that we're back and I don't
have any travel plans for April um
I intend to revive holot
talk and revive Girls
Talk those will be coming back y let's
go let's
go and we'll playing we'll be playing
Yakuza of course a
lot
yeah want to play a couple of those fotm
games too like the climbing game and I
want want to play the new Holo life fan
game that everybody's playing
now ghost
yeah I got to set some dates though can
we stop for a moment are you okay yeah
I'm just oh all of this is overwhelming
we're almost uh to tful there shouldn't
be many monsters from here on no not
that the whole Elder training thing
every day I try harder and harder I feel
like I'm going to explode one day
everyone in bore is going to depend on
me I'm just too scared and also I really
want to get this gift right for
pel she's just really cool NE I want to
get something that that'll make her
happy I want to make her
happy I wish I could help you with the
Elder training but I don't know anything
about being an elder but I could try to
help you figure out what you get for
bers what sort of things does she like
she likes refurbishing old paints her
favorite color is red and she really
likes painting too what bid paints what
kind of things does she paint mostly
snails oh sometimes PL or other little
creatures but mostly snails it's really
cute cool I meant cool oh cool I meant
cool
Mia uh there's someone at tens fall who
does Pottery maybe you could get baz out
something to paint oh maybe a little
dish she could mix her colors on it oh
and we could even even get it shaped
like a snail shell oh cute I can
imagine how do you feel I'm okay I'm
going to be okay thank you corus let's
keep going sweet wow we such a great
emotional
support and who's going to emotionally
support me
though it's okay I got Kitty my kitty
cat but yeah that's what April is
looking
like
some things some programs coming back
and
generally just
normal normal
streams and oh yeah I want to get the go
collab going
hopefully that would be
neat ow going
die yeah
[Music]
go uh what happened last time in yaka I
think we're good I
mean yeah if somebody wants to prepare
that we can we can look into it what
happened last
time don't tell me there's a light spot
here close by where I could have healed
yo I did I already lose like 2 Hp
again the Beast they
sting a thank you
faker happy to hear
that you feel like
that I like to work out when I watch
streams so a lot of my stream watching
is when I'm working out toally today I
finally called the live stream let's go
are you working out now then
never Skip Leg
Day am I right or am I right but also
don't skip the other days don't skip but
day don't skip Friday
Friday Friday should have should be on
Friday right what the [\h__\h] is this a
turtle hello Turtle are you alive you
look kind of
dead
worked out before stream oh damn you
guys sheesh I
[Music]
respect
spring
peeper poisonous or
not spring
peeper
spring
peeper cute sounds like he can jump
quite well oh my God they're like
perfect
size cute
[Music]
oh they're
cute
small
[Music]
baby this is sleep ASMR I could listen
to him all
[Music]
night they
goep
going
on oh chunkers the the frog has summoned
chunky wony hi hi baby do you want to
eat
frog the real
kitty she's so she's so
baby I want
[Music]
to I turned it up so that you guys can
hear the me me ah oh he woke up oh no
why did we wake him up
oh
oh hello there youed one ask your name
of course you don't need to do the whole
oh blessed
course BR hey you don't need to do the
whole fancy greeting thing what you are
a holy frog are you not no actually I'm
a
warrior oh I see well course the warrior
are you aware of the ancient holy
practice of dream reading m I think my
Elder mentioned it once didn't the
Ancients of Salia study dreams I think I
passed by a dream reading temple on my
way to
Boreal yes it is a custom dating back
hundreds of years must believe the
technique to be forgotten or should I
say frog gotten however course the
warrior some still exist today who are
trained in the art of dream reading
these individuals are a rare few and one
would find it quite challenging to
locate such an
individual but
l or
I the I Yi problem man today Co the
warrior you have found yourself in quite
the lucky scenario l
oh you're you're a dream my friend I am
a dream reader yeah oh I'm a servant of
Fate itself hearing its voice from my
holy
H as a matter of fact Co the war if you
describe to me what you d last night I
shall translate what Fate has in store
for you for a reasonable Fe of course
dream reading will cost you 100 holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no or
yes is it worth it worth it oh worth
it it better
be excellent now we shall begin now
please describe last night's dream to me
uh
wait I actually remember
something I remember a black yeah yeah
yeah a black pan for attacking
me something like that I was I was
remembering it to to tell
you but when it was like charging at me
to attacking me it uh like the the
moment it was right in front of my face
it's it was like oh oh never mind and it
it ran
away that's the only part of the dream
that's the one part I
remember it started with oh okay H
depending on my choices I wonder if I
get like a different outcome of like
effect maybe I get like a like a buff or
something I don't know I have many
dreams which one should I describe a
knock on the door beautiful music bright
light on loud
sound a loud sound AKA my cat
meowing
much in my ear and
[Music]
then I fell for the floor monsters
are he I don't know what to
choose is this
important this sounds like a nightmare
this too
this could be something
else she's the alarm you didn't
need let's say let's
say I know I had something important to
do
maybe and
then a giant bird appeared and
finally I had to I had to react to the
bird I'm sorry I think I died or
[Music]
something I turned back into a
tadpole and then I woke
up that's totally what happened ah yes I
see of course the warrior can hear F
speaking as he described his dream to me
this is what Fate has to say about you
you're capable of great things
wow scam de
friend de friend you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
you
you you little [\h__\h] you didn't know I
had a gun did you I trusted you and you
used my dress for
what you scared me oh you probably in it
with this
frog probably sharing the money aren't
you you little [\h__\h]
y never show your face again but yes
please show your face again and uh tell
me more but
frogs oh my God I can't believe this I
really fought I could trust
you no way you little frog
[\h__\h] oh my God he's a
scammer that's why he can afford such a
crazy
home whoa whoa of course you love scam
frog because you're sharing the income
the
money I would love that
too
damn well at least I streamed it so
everybody who plays the game because
they saw it in my stream they will
not fall through the same
Destiny cuz they know no they better not
get
scammed I think we have
[Music]
arrived yeah I recorded the proof I I'll
report to the
police I'll have Frog song the game
taken down
forever can't have something like this
in the switch game
store
M what's
this I LIF oh up to the
[Music]
tree hold on
okay the
fbb hello is this the fbb yeah I've just
experienced a serious crime oh he's got
the same markings as
[Music]
me of course right yeah that's right are
you're the one who's trying to be a
warrior right yeah strange times we live
in what that supposed to mean oh wait
they're all tree fs and we live in a big
tree like Village isn't that nice no
interesting wow for that shitty
comment I will ring the bell until your
ears are
ringing how's your ears huh
HH Pacific tree frogs
oh they run on PST time
huh oh look at him oh look at him small
small boy hello ARA oh is it's a girl oh
hello course what brings you back to T
uh R this is ARA she's the one who does
the pottery
ah a course is a chorus Pacific triple
there's a chorus
[Music]
Pacific I have to look
now Horus
Pacific Tree
Frog wow this is like the perfect
example of a
frog yeah I won't show you a picture
because it's pretty
normal he's he's a perfect frog if I've
ever seen
one also very
small
oh I've kissed the Frog
before just so you know I've kissed the
Frog and I liked it I want to
[Music]
you would probably kiss
too don't judge
me if it's teen that's just why why does
that make it fine I I could kiss a frog
as an adult
[Music]
too nothing wrong with that as long as
it's not a poison dart frog or or a can
toad
or but I feel like we don't even have
poisonous frogs in Austria I don't know
do we I feel like we don't we don't have
poisonous anything that the Frog consent
it did not hop out of my hand I was
holding it for quite a
while it could have hopped
away it seemed very very happy in my
[Music]
hands it was so weird it was so cute not
weird I said weird because I read the
comments please stop being weird excuse
me why what's wrong with loving
nature I was just for a picture
anyway I'm like what if I kiss a frog
for a
[Music]
picture anyway R this is Ira she's the
one who does the pottery hello I was
wondering if you were able to make a
dish for me I'm sure what
kind while you while you get this
figured out I'll go ahead and find Elder
ACC and talk with him aie
doggy look at him they all look so
cute wait looks like only GID is on the
[Music]
tree ah hello C I've been practicing my
sing character listen
sure
[Music]
more yeah that was different wasn't
it is
it yeah I think there different
Melodies
cute PR
cute good afternoon young carus I see
you have returned to our sacred Village
of ten fall hi fder gr what have you
been up to myself I was merely observing
the fields before us something of not I
have witnessed there appears to be much
activity around that giant ancient
structure oh oh he's also looking at
that the one with a strange Twisted
Tower it was struck by lightning earlier
this morning an ominous Omen I would say
the structure it is in close proximity
to the great city of Torah though it is
great and name only a wretched place it
is something onious is brewing from the
depth of depravity in that old structure
me thinks me
thinks English
words best to stay away from those
bullfrog folks I'd say oh okay wwise my
little varent friend you must use more
words when you speak or no one else will
know how smart you are okay interesting
I'll try I'll try to use more words is
there something in
[Music]
here oh oh my old house I should
probably clear out the rest of this junk
sometime what are these dolls mfy I
can't believe I forgot here here I used
to not be able to sleep without this
thing I guess I better take her home so
I don't forget forget again
Mory morphe that's all I think I can do
here we can put her into our new house
[Music]
morphe
okay next ooh this looks
important
ooh
wow oh the blood child
what the blood child was the first child
of Anora and it started started killing
everything around it and then an turned
it into a monster's punishment actually
maybe it turned into a monster first and
then started killing stuff it got
banished or locked up or something too I
think I don't really remember a lot of
the old stories have weird dark
meaningless stuff nobody likes talking
about Everyone likes talking about the
poetic happy
stuff okay well not
hold the blood child what a
name this book is open to a p as yes and
the grassler coiled about spattering the
grass with acidic fuff the grassler LED
out a horrendous streak and lunged at
dask at last dask spoke I sh deliver D2
die warm fatter dask drew his plate and
swung all was quiet in the forest for a
moment The Red Shed Beast would Prey
Upon villagers no longer task's work was
done the next page has an illustration
of a frog with a blindfold hiding from a
monster that looks like a cross between
a rat and a snake with way too many
legs rat and snake is that a real
ah what could that
[Music]
be no I also found about a cedia next W
one original song
centipede Cent centy
centipede Cent Cy centi
[Music]
peed oh Caris back so soon I take it
you'll did not last long in the defense
Guild Shane but Fate has a place for all
of us I
suppose
I actually
I good afternoon Elder of t fall I am
here to deliver a message on behalf of
the defense Guild of Boral huh is that
so Lord leus Rua of the torel Empire has
been traveling to different Villages
attempting to convince them to join his
Empire he has also been spreading rumors
of a monster known as the
Snicket we believe the purpose of these
rumors is to spread fear making the
Elders of the villagers uh easier to
convince CH there is no need to act so
formal with me I'm your Elder remember I
have known you since you were a tadpole
come now don't be a stranger tell me
more about this
Beast no R say it's a giant monster
capable of terrible destruction but
that's not the
point s you always were a f of monster
stories we do not need the tal Empire to
protect us this creature sounds like a
hoax that's what I'm trying to tell you
the name Snickers or something like that
it does not ring a bell but even if we
assumed it was real we would simply need
to send a warrior with the sun blade to
face
it do I get it the sun blade that sounds
epic one job from the Sun blade and it
would surely perish it's like a master
sword wait the sunblade is real I
thought it was just a story of course
it's real how else do you think Anora
would have R the world of all magical
beasts course do not let these monster
stories get to you the life of a defense
skild member promises much excitement
but it is a dangerous path it's no place
for a frog like you I know you're
smarter than
this oh I don't know what else I
expected from this look just watch out
for Lia Empire okay that's all I came
here to say uh when you are done playing
soldier you're always welcome to come
back
home I'll never be
done this my destiny it's what I want to
be this is not my home and you're not my
Elder excuse me
princess I left this place because
people like you refuse to accept me
nobody in this Village wants to see the
real me I haven't been welcome here for
a long time you are being
ridiculous all I have ever done for you
is nurture you and help you br I want
what is best for you no you don't you
just want what makes you comfortable
I've already done what I came here for
I'm going back home to Boreal
goodbye
I told her I told
[Music]
them I asserted dominance
perfect
now they
probably hopefully think of me as bigger
of a frog than I am um hey cars did you
find the Elder yeah I'm ready to get out
of here did you get the dish yeah I
think B's going to really like it I hope
she will just got to find the right time
to give it to her now let's
go quick I want to get out of
here but I also want to see what's on
this side did I check that out oh
shop oh of course I wasn't expecting you
to see you back in t fall so soon
couldn't stay away from my baking huh
actually I'm here on defense Guild
business but maybe some frog buns
wouldn't be bad frog buns remember that
one mud Moon Feast a few years ago when
I made the biggest B of frog buns ever
and then you ate so many you were sore
for a week I was only sore for a day
okay good okay frog buns heal two each
okay h a bag of four frog buns for 80 M
yeah that sounds good I
think don't eat them all at
[Music]
once oh
cute
oh a fluffy roll baked with fresh herbs
M yum can't wait to dig
in need some garlic
though welcome back oh a course right oh
s I'm still getting used to your new
name it's okay I get it it's going to
take some time no really I'm sorry I
keep forgetting forgetting I should know
better I'm
sorry remember the
name you are really
old someone there y have to speak up a
bit my eyes and ears aren't what they
once were hello Grand Cadence it's
chorus of course you are always my
favorite pupil I was but I was always
distracted and I was always doodling in
my
notes but your toodles were always so
cute look at you now we've gone enough
to the to join the defense skill like
you always
dreamed everyone else you thinks that's
weird have I ever told you about why our
village is named tful no I don't think
so or maybe you didn't I for
forgot the old story say that long ago
there used to be Two
Moons the Eastern Moon and the Western
Moon the Eastern Moon was raised by a
child of a Nora named pal the Western
moon was raised by a child of a nor
named ten one day ten grew tired of
controlling her Moon she came down to
our world she saw M's beautiful plants
and decided she wanted to make some
herself instead of the green plants M
made the 10 made plants of all sorts of
colors cre
flowers where does the fall part intense
fall come from then
well Anor didn't like the
10 did that so she killed her
brutal my point is that if 10 did not
stray from the path we would not have
flowers and we certainly do not miss the
other Moon our village has plenty of
people to raise the moon you chorus you
are creating
flowers deep story deep
lore they they mention a lot like kind
of brutal lore too
though every frog comes with a knife I
don't know about that but
uh I will not go anywhere without my
knife or my
gun all right time to go and we can take
the boat this
time let's go on a boat shall we
oh and everyone died great
story you sure you're
European
yeah cuz it's not a real gun I wouldn't
use a real
gun okay let's
go and
[Music]
B frog on the big white ocean that is
probably just a little
lake or
a
pond stay safe out
there
right really it means a lot that you
help me out oh was no problem really I'm
just glad I could help someone this is
the whole reason why I'm here but sorry
I should go report back to Elder
bufo
[Music]
bye-bye also let me put something in to
my
[Music]
house already looking way better than in
the
beginning right oh oh I can see it
better now it's supposed to be a like a
muff right
[Music]
a I can put it on top of my bed
nice
he
okay
cute
okay let's
[Music]
go you think my gun is
real it's better that way
you should think that way for your own
safety hello gorus are you back from
tens fall how do you go think it went
okay I mean I think tens fall is going
to be fine well that is good no the
Warriors have told me they were
successful in Redwood and clear Bay as
well B Sal is likely still on her way
back mossan is a bit of a track
especially in this weather she will
likely be back tomorrow morning okay I
have something I wanted to ask why do
you believe in me I mean I don't get
don't get me wrong I I appreciate it but
nobody else does I'm not as stronger
skill as basal or anyone else really are
you just being nice oh
course has anyone told you about what
happened to my
leg no well I
dropped I dropped a a bowl on my toe and
it had to be cut off the whole thing now
not just the toe the whole leg it was
terrible ow
[Music]
ow if if you asked anyone why it was
missing they would surely tell you that
I lost it in the war that is why I have
told everyone what I have told everyone
for
years such a sad story but that is not
true I was born without it
oh I joined the defense Guild as a young
frog just as the war was emerging I
wanted to protect the people of Salia so
badly I was certain they would turn me
away because of my leg but I was allowed
join not all frogs are built the same I
was totally built
different when I came home from the war
I wanted to seem strong I told everyone
that I lost my leg in a brutal fight
truth be told I was rarely involved in
combat this is the only lie I've ever
told the villagers but I've kept it up
for so long damn I feared that if they
found out I had been lying all this time
they would never trust me again wow and
you're telling me must really trust
me but I must admit seeing how you've
never let your sze stop you it's made me
rethink something perhaps perhaps I will
tell the others
oh well
with your age it's
um you know maybe good to tell
people you don't you know have much
longer to live perhaps and it's good to
open up before you go and you feel more
free when it's time
Mia I'm going to stop if you tell them
the truth I suppose you right thank you
chorus I'm feeling quite tired now we
have done the best we can about this Li
a situation I think you it's time for
this old frog to get some rest I'll
speak with you
tomorrow this whole time I feel like
there's a flag red flag if he goes to
sleep now I I have this feeling that
tomorrow she'll be dead he or she I
don't
know this whole time before
also when when when the Frog wasn't
inside the house I was like oh must be
dead what's this red flag it's going to
happen I'm sure it be like this dramatic
sad emotional moment and that's that's
when ra will take over obviously and
she'll be like okay I don't feel quite
ready yet but now I'm being forced into
the situation so I'm going to step up
and do my best and that will also be
really inspiring you know oh wow I I I
wrote the
script I'm calling the
story I mean it's it's all laid
perfectly in place I mean just the fact
that they have a frog like that dad that
is um nervous about stepping into the
footsteps is it just makes
sense chapter four there's two more I
mean I guess three more cuz we're just
starting chapter
four okay so we're halfway through
yab yab I mean we did waste some time
with my
toe maybe there's some shorter chapters
good stopping but no I don't I I am
supposed to finish
this it's it's only been 4 and a half
hours three days until
retirement and
although you are right [\h__\h] it's already
10 p.m.
almost I thought we could manage to do
this
faster death friend do you know if I you
know considering I I may have taken
longer until now because of my
toe uh what do you think how much longer
it would take me from now
there's also epilogue
oh
oh what what time is ena's outfit
reveal I don't think I saw it in the
calendar I mean there's no no overlap
and G but
damn what
what do you mean it's a 20 minutes but
then probably add 40 minutes of
uh looking at
pictures of uh potential uh you know
designs so an
hour
no what you guys are probably curious
about that so you would probably go
there or want to go there
spoilers wait is is De death friend gone
I don't see
[Music]
reply ah you here what do you think how
how much
longer but yeah I I it would seem rude
of me to overlap with Ina so
even though there's no overlap
[Music]
NG 7 hours in total so three more so
we're really halfway through
huh maybe I can even finish it as a
member stream because I feel like we
maybe have members perms I got to check
though oh quite a few more hours damn it
damn
it I wasted too much
time
yeah I'll see what I can do if it's um
if I have perms for members then I might
finish it in the memb Stream cuz you
know always feel like oh it's always
nice to have a little game for members
as well um and that way we can end frog
week publicly at
least the way it was planned oh I'm not
a member
no maybe maybe if you come to lawa
streams more often they always gift
memberships quite quite often so you
might get one but I I do kind of want
the Frog lore I do want the Frog lore
I'll see I'll see what I can do but I I
already planned out next week and I just
kept one day uh open still for a member
stream oh are we going to try
again yesterday we already gifted
memberships do you guys still have it in
[Laughter]
[Music]
you seems
difficult I'll try I'll try I I don't
want to keep the deaths away and the
Frog I'll see what I can do I'll see see
what I can do unless you you catch him
catch him catch
him it always misses the one you're
aiming for doesn't
it yeah be sure to turn uh receiving
gifts on but I heard that it's like on
by default
now not
sure I'll try to catch him too let's see
who's got the best
aim ah ah you had to turn it
on did I hit
you oh I'm still in time in time for
what we're we're we we realized we
probably should end it here M
unfortunately um I thought I could read
super chats for quite long but if we're
going to well I mean we can read super
chats for a while even though a little
bit into ena's stream if she's just
checking pictures as I
assume from uh what's the word not not
assumptions what's the Lord
again can make super chat reading stream
next week just uh I want to catch up a
little bit
though
predictions
yeah what the weather is so
bad wait looks like the storm is getting
worse seems really quiet today where is
everyone scare me what is this flag red
flag red flag red flag let's go into my
house
was there bgm in my house no that's too
bad thought I could use the game
bgm for
for
bgm did we catch him yet doesn't look
like we caught him
yet you guys are
crazy froggy fellow with 10 gifted thank
you oh my
God
we are so bad at
sniping yeah it's it's sad that you
can't aim like they didn't add a
function to choose who you're gifting it
to you guys can try a little little bit
longer uh while I open up my super
chats stop hopping
around hi hopp you w going to be my
property my frog I'm going to catch you
with a poke
ball I really wonder if it's true of
like uh
more not active but like more like
viewers who are more often on the
channel have higher chances of catching
a membership then it's probably lesser
chances for you what frog fact uh frog
fact tell me frog fact
about I don't know how can I know what
frog fact I want to know if I don't know
a frog
fact
frog I heard I told in my frog
uh tier list I told the people about
this one Frog who um doesn't and when
when they make make baby they don't
become a tadpole no they immediately
turn
into toadlet or froglet one of those
things yeah froglets and everybody was
like whoa I forgot which frog that was
but are there more are there
several lots of frogs skip the tadpole
face there we go a lot of micro highight
frogs do
oo see interesting wow wow wow wow
they're skipping a
whole life stage it's
amazing I don't know what else give me
give me random frog
fact
random I'm looking at frog pictures I
should be opening my super
chats damn
it oh what speedrun ah yeah yeah yeah
yeah they do be fast they do be dooming
I'll give you some bgm
guys there you oh no
wrong
uh
[Music]
yeah oh I
should uh where is
it o save and
quit yes
did we get him yet still not oh there's
oh a two logist you're two list and you
hope to work with
frogs oh two
larest that sounds fun you can do you do
you work wait Z lares not
necessarily wait there's two bgms
though y
wait wait
okay that doesn't necessarily mean that
you work in a in a zoo already right if
you work in a
zoo can you say hi to Red Pandas for me
I love red
panda I want to
touch the study okay
okay ah ah maybe one day you can work in
a zoo anybody here who works in a
zoo I don't like going to frogs H to to
zoos what my brain sorry
multitasking I don't like going to zoos
really usually because of the you know
the F first of all all Zoes are pretty
much the
same and the Captivity makes me
sad
yeah and usually you can't interact with
interact with most of them so it's like
what's the point I'm just looking at
them it's still fun but I don't
know I there's no need for me to go to a
zoo that often having seen one Zoo
pretty much yeah satisfies my urge for
seeing a zoo for 10
[Music]
years weab itating animals that sounds
fine that sounds
good yeah
aquarium as well although aquariums are
pretty
fascinating with like I don't know
jellyfish and stuff but still it's also
pretty much always the same fish I'd
rather go to a nice Island and then go
snorkeling or diving so since I want to
get a diver's license
this
year that's my goal and then I'll see
the fishies with my own eyes and see see
all kinds of stuff like turtles and Rays
as I I've already seen some of them and
that's that's that's freaking
fascinating that's way cooler than going
to an aquarium seeing them without a
wall a glass wall between us it's so
much
[Music]
nicer I want to see it
myself yeah diving is expensive though
yeah W the diver I will not give up on
the
dream diving in caves
[Music]
yeah scary scary okay we're going to
read the super chats where we left
off
um I think I remember
roughly 30 six I already got it I
already got it I have it marked in Hyer
it's nice in Hyer you can mark something
and then when you open the page again
the Mark is still
there shout out to Mark who's always
there so sorry guys I couldn't finish
the game that's kind of unfortunate I
also didn't realize that uh yeah in know
out for the reveal was happening right
after this thank you feel free to catch
any stream
anytime even if it's not frog related if
you're feeling vtuber next week I will
look different it leaves on a
cliffhanger oh no so everyone has to buy
the game themselves to see what
happens oh you mean my stream leaves it
at a
cliffhanger that makes everybody need to
buy it well yeah yeah yeah you guys are
welcome to buy the game it's on the
switch
[Music]
she had an anniversary stream
mhm are we done have you guys given up
gifting
members good try
guys good try you made a lot of other
people happy we once again apparently
got
213 holy [\h__\h]
guys you guys are getting my new members
uh
statistics up by a
lot yeah throw those eggs getting ready
for Easter we need L lots of Easter
eggs to hide them in the
map spread those Easter
eggs let's
go
[Music]
eggs eggs
eggs okay sorry I ate a little
[Music]
chocolate there's some frog eggs in my
pond oh you have frog eggs and you have
a pond for so the frogs that you have
you don't keep them in like a glass
thing you keep them in a pond really I
feel like those frogs that you have you
have to keep them in a glass thing right
in a
container
right cuz they're special frogs I do but
I have wild frogs too oh let's go my mom
also um she has frogs in a little Pond
too I mean it's more like a puddle than
a pond I'm going to
say and it's very very overgrown and all
that she was very proud having a frog
there and I was really excited about her
having a frog there but I didn't see it
very well it's it's it's just always
hiding how do I get a frog out of hiding
do you have
a an advice for that my frogs frog
expert frog
expert
use a
cricket go out at night they're
nocturnal but then I can't see
them will they be around the the pond
doll or will they be in the
grass depends on the Frog I
suppose bring a flashlight
okay I remember last time when I was at
my mom's place at night there was like a
a straight cat cat like there's a lot of
straight cats around where my mom lives
cuz she's on the countryside in the
middle of nowhere I always say that it's
true and I would tell her to get a cat
and she's like no I can't but also like
there's so many stray cats that I'm
feeding already anyway there's so many
Neighborhood Cats and stray cats and
mostly Neighborhood Cats that just roam
around
freely and then I saw just in front of
her house door there's just this one cat
cat Jing constantly in front of a door
and so I was like I was staring at it
forever and my mom's like go to sleep go
to sleep and I'm like no but there's a
cat in front of your door can I let it
in she's like no don't you can't let it
in I'm like but please it's it's waiting
it's standing in front of the door with
hopes and
dreams need to put cat
inside
I was so curious it was like almost like
one of those Quest Giver cats too cuz it
was standing at the the one lit up
[Music]
space it knows it knows where to stand
so that it stands
out what if it's cold I don't I don't
think it was really
cold yeah I don't think so cuz that was
like summer late summer
I right I was going to read Super Chat
okay we'll read a little bit maybe you
guys can have Ena open on the side and
like let me know when when it starts to
get
serious
okay let me
[Music]
know I'll do
maximum maybe 30 minutes we'll see we'll
see okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay we're probably 45 minutes
yeah we know how it goes we know how it
goes uh Nico no thanks for the pinky
your performances for the first stage
were so good I loved the new song Kimera
and you do it with Chloe was also very
hot oo your dancing was at 100% power
and I loved it thank you for being my
Kami Oshi and my only Oshi much love
thank
you
no sorry I don't know why I gave you a
kiss it it was only a pinky and if
anything I'm I'm doing something else
now oopsie sorry I I just feel very very
lovey lovey
[Music]
doy thank you yeah I do think that was
100% this time and the tracking was
really good I appreciate good
tracking Improvement
of the
studio nail it this year thank
you stop stop stop oh yeah we're going
to watch it tomorrow in the members only
stream we're going to rewatch the stage
one day one stage one where I
performed oh my God finally yeah kept
you guys waiting
sorry I would have done it earlier but
when I had time they didn't have the VA
up yet so oh yeah anyway thank you so
much Nik no maybe you can take some time
to watch it together with me
again take Monkey D J SW D for the red
chat D sorry
[Music]
D the V just took forever for real it
took like a week I think
super hype and fun weekend even in the
online gang we got spicy performances
and cute performances too all the w we
could want yeah I heard I heard that the
camera angles were overall pretty good I
mean it could still be
improved um but you know stuff like that
it's live so
um un subsidize that to wait do I have
to give you one two
them
random
Collision I well that was pretty good
they were pretty good okay yeah I didn't
hear many complaints or any complaints
so they did edit the camera and the
Vault too oh
really
really yeah I I know about the
backup
D yeah
made an a big oopsie with my backup
vocals but yeah now they are there good
thing is people didn't know what it was
supposed to sound like so they didn't
know that there was a lot
missing
yeah oh actually Nikon no himself
subsidized or whatever it because the
there's a second pinky down there I see
it okay chase wber you know what you're
getting are you ready open your eyes or
something
[Music]
else
mem mem you are being blessed by a frog
accept the
[Music]
mem yeah all the WWA take all the WWA I
hope you got enough of Wawa during the
concert cuz there's no more WWA now only
froggy
waa Jacob 47 D oh for the pinky Adorable
song with coo and was pleasantly
surprised to see their return oh is this
already the second day of the home
summer unit yeah you and coob are really
good doing both vocal and movements and
the crowd seemed hyped overall congrats
on a a very good fifth rest you did
fantastic thank you yeah this time time
for the special stage I was in two songs
because yeah lucky me was also in the so
to say theme
song that made a
comeback yeah I was surprised to see a
lot of people surprised that the song
was performed it was also honeyworks it
was it may have been like way earlier
released than the rest of the whole
project but still you
know I think it's good cuz it's at least
one of the bigger group songs and
besides that it was mostly like solos
and Duets so it needed a couple of group
songs I would say like bigger
ones for hype hype
hype yeah and yeah the song of kuu as
expected you know it did the thing it
did the thing that it needed to do with
all the all the chant and everything
everybody chanted so well I mean it's
it's good because it's like pretty easy
chants
too that are easy to follow along and I
think the people who did go to the
honeyworks concert also um knew what
they were getting themselves into and
studied all the songs beforehand by
listening to the album beforehand I
think I think that must be true
mhm I saw a lot of um Japanese Bros too
tweet how they're looking forward to it
h because of the chant seeming very fun
to
do yeah I listen so much to you and K
song to make sure to get the timings
right it's mostly just repeating what we
say and
[Music]
like
are you
ready
one yeah such a fun song yeah I'm happy
I was um in a unit with
cooo that was fun Aon thank you for the
[Music]
red oh in
go
[Music]
embarrassing Nik no thank you for the
second pinky a second pinky for the
second day of Fest ah your honey workor
stage stage performance of Co was so
cute the whole summmer song was so good
I really loved your range in giving us
both mature and cute wa this F love you
w yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it was very
cleanly cleanly separated into cute and
St cushy
sexy cool mature
waha honey works I mean I don't I don't
know how would have fit a sexy Wawa into
the honeyworks performance is kind of
impossible so no I I was glad I could
show both
sides I'm glad you sound less sick today
oh yeah I'm I'm fine I'm
fine I feel very good I still like spit
out a little bit of of legum here and
there when I wake up or so but it's
pretty much
gone
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah and it's even when I spit it out
it's like mostly it feels like very
diluted
diluted the toe the toe the toe hurts to
the touch but without touching it's
fine
sadly well well
well I came so
close to great
[Music]
you guys really get
triggered all
right why I you like
this why I just
me my broken stuff it sucks I don't want
that for you a yeah I mean of course it
sucks but like what I'm saying is that
this toe situation and the skiing
situation both were great opportunities
like if I'm going to get hurt might as
well you know I know you won't like
agree with me and you won't listen to me
so I'm like whatever let's not even get
into
it let's not get into
it you you do understand the logic
okay
yeah I have four DMS again what's up
what's
up
oh oh
[\h__\h] oh okay okay oh
[Music]
go an update about the progress
of the coding for the games for VR
tomorrow looking good looking
good oh and I got updated about my logo
for my jacket even though it's just a
digital
release
Kima
[Music]
H what do you call
that n I'll reply
[Music]
later
okay tap tap tap tap where was I oh yeah
ultim MK thank you for two pinkies I
thought I was prepared getting ready to
do a somewhat decent and fitting cheer
for Chima but it didn't even matter
because after 5 Seconds my jaw
dropped then my T lights dropped and
then I dropped to the floor to bow down
before the queen oh [\h__\h] but also let's
talk about hero for a day H oh no I have
nothing richy or sophis to say oh no K
is staring at
[Music]
me no but seriously it's such a lovely
song and you and K were so cute on stage
Su thank
[Music]
you I'm glad I'm glad thank you so much
are your knees
okay maybe your knees hurt the way my my
toes has my toe has been hurting
yeah
well you seem very very
enthusiastic a good
kfp thank you for all the love and the
support Ultimo the ultimate support the
Ultimate Chicken the ultimate
kfp thank you much much love and a
little LM perhaps would you like a
little
mum
that's
[Music]
Nissa no she didn't want my tissues
so
no and it's in his name so got to give
him
[Music]
that
she blew it with
tissue
unbelievable no it's okay I still love
[Music]
her yeah space wonderful thanks for the
pinky woo that was great you and KU were
amazing W Ito was so good was cheering
so hard at home maybe too much even a
glant toy say archive love that song
especially because of
you what thank you so much for your
great performance oh my God that
literally look like like a like a
password or something a
randomly randomly generated password I
love you so much proud of you thank you
I'm flattered I'll take all the
compliments even though froggy W myself
did not
perform thank you I'm I'm so flattered
and so
honored praise me more praise me more I
deserve
it thank you so much for your sweet
words ion v d all thank
you thank
you Cruz
Rand thank you for being here the last
couple years and know you've done doing
those you're one in a krillion and we're
blessed to have you here's a chair for
the future to the Future years however
they may come thank
you good good attempt on the
German but
um if you say if you want to you know
put an article in front of USA I would
say it would
be in this case like normally it's D USA
But you said as D USA when you say as
like from then the D you know it gets
like consumated or whatever and it turns
into a d i
there yeah you know there's daddy
does yeah I I house is like coming from
somewhere so then the the Articles
change again there's like so many rules
man I was there was that oh
yeah there's I guess there's two
choices no you can say
both no you can say both don't you
Germans correct my
German no both 100%
both learn German
mode don't quote my mother don't take my
mother's words into your
mouth
[Music]
uh what do I
say D I think I say
d yeah or do
I no I don't know I think I
said
die Nutella
die yeah those are some interesting um
like questions in in there's a couple of
these words
where uh you would think that you have
to use I think maybe it's only for non
German words that we brought into the
German language where some people fight
over
it's de or dust and for me it seems very
obvious what sounds better naturally but
then other people say it differently and
I'm like ew disgusting how how dare you
use this article on this word it's is a
German thing it's it's
really
yeah I feel like there's several great
examples I just can't think of them
right
now when next time I hear something like
that I'll try to remember it and let you
know you have that in Spanish too in
French too what really oh that's
[Music]
interesting in Danish too oh
wow okay
um
Sky Studio thanks for r Super Chat oh oh
my God there's actually like two
sentences in this long sentences in the
Super Chat Studio Rob and in English t a
I wanted to sneak this in before signing
off the light that Shone on my dark life
these last few days was wonderful oh my
God he's
talking convey my love and gratitude to
Yago and all the Holo members for me
please and thank you wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what is the love for me
wait what this convey the love and
gratitude to Yago and all the Hol
members I
mean that sounds
very
spread huh Studio Rob what's this
about what's this about it it includes
me yeah but is that really what you
[Music]
mean it's too
General it's too
General no thank you it's nice to see
you write more than T in your Super Chat
you're like quite the phenomenon for
me thank you so
much thank you for the support I I'll
try I'll
try to convey the
love thank you though surely most of
that you want it you want to convey it
to me right I'll take it I'll take
it instead of
kieni
Domin
aim for the pinky you did absolutely
amazing on the F it was really great
even just watching the stream and really
enjoyed it hope you will get now some
proper rest and we get soon can't wait
for future events L wow thank you I I
rested like for maybe one
day and then I had
to go back and do stuff like go back I
mean go out and do
stuff yeah I I didn't want to I didn't
want to cancel like everything no I
cancel no I I didn't cancel like
something I I streamed was still sick as
you guys
remember but besides the the few streams
that I did I I didn't really do much and
then on the last like two days or three
days I did some stuff but I was like
mostly feeling better it's just my nose
still running a
lot had to blow my nose the whole time
which is really
really comfortable in Japan cuz like you
get those judgmental looks you're not
really supposed to blow your nose in
public I guess but I still had to do it
sometimes because I was just that like
it's so disgusting to me to like sniff
it back up like that like no ew ew e e e
I already have so much flum in my throat
that I'm trying to get out I'm not going
to add more onto it it's
gross and you know little sniffles are
still like if I'm next to you and I hear
you doing little sniffles that's okay
but sometimes people ew when they suck
the snot back up in their nose it
disgusts me so much it's one of my
biggest pet
peeves one people one people some people
they you feel personally attacked
improve yourself I don't want to hear
those noises some people you know they
go like oh my God I hear this on the
street in Austria every so
often they go like through their throat
like no it's like I think through the
nose but it almost sounds as like
through their throat they they made this
like really
loud like pig sound pretty much like a
deep really deep snort and then they
spit on the
pavement it's
so disgusting
oh oh my
God [\h__\h] nasty as
[\h__\h] so at least at least I take a
tissue and blow into the tissue and not
spit on the floor like suck it up and
then spit on the floor like e e e e e e
e yeah so gross so gross so gross so
gross so
gross
[Music]
sorry I can't control my sinus blow your
nose that's basically vandalism
yeah what if there's no tissue we had
this discussion
before this very same discussion we had
it before what if there's no tissue
around well I don't [\h__\h] know if you
if you have this car commonly obviously
if you do this I feel like you have it
commonly if you're the type of person
that snorts so deeply that spits on the
pavement then I'm pretty sure these type
of people that I'm talking about they do
it
commonly so then you could prepare
yourself and bring
tissues last time I was also very sick
smoke is doing a lot yeah I suppose
that's what like M what happens to your
to your
[Music]
body when you smoke a lot
Maybe
[Music]
for
I try to use nasal spray to make sure
I'm not that bad enough stuffed up
oh are you a smoker is that what you're
saying
handkerchiefs I prefer to use normal
like tissues rather than
[Music]
handkerchiefs
I haven't gotten a cold and the W it's
just allergies I get me yeah JMA also
has really bad allergies oh I remember I
got this massage in Japan right early on
uh and it was a really good
massage but the lady who was massaging
me she was so nice had some nice
conversations but she had really bad
allergies I guess she also like
apologized for it but like this whole
time I swear every every honestly every
second really or every breath she was
taking
she sniffed it back up and it sounded
really like like there was a lot a lot
running out of her nose and this all
time was thinking oh oh she can just
blow her nose I absolutely don't mind oh
man it's like endlessly running and
running while she's massaging me so all
I'm hearing is like the
endless
sounds and I like hyperfocus on it like
oh man this lady really has a runny
[Music]
nose oh she apologize for it I feel bad
like if if it's your allergies then you
know that's rough that's really
[Music]
rough that's really
rough but her massage was still good and
then uh while I was getting my massage
someone else entered another Foreigner
so I was a foreigner the massage lady
was a foreign I think she told me she
was from China and then the Never lady
enters lies down a customer also gets a
massage I kind of hear their
conversation too they also have the same
conversation as like oh where are you
from oh you're fora too oh I'm also fora
so both the massage therapists that are
massaging and both the customers like
four people are here and they're all
foreigners it was kind of funny cuz we
also all were um fluent in Japanese but
I I think I was more fluent than the
lady who was massaging me and the other
customer also seemingly was more fluent
than the lady that was massaging her but
still they were still good at at
Japanese and we were like having some
nice
conversations between foreigners from
Foreigner to
Foreigner but I have that quite often
when I go to massage in
Japan there's a lot of like it depends
on the type of massage really there's a
lot of non-japanese
people who give massages and I talk to
them and I'm l at the time I have at
least a better accent and usually also a
better vocabulary than them and then my
Japanese is very good even though it's
gotten a bit
Rusty
yeah quite Rusty but when I get into
talking when I live in Japan or stay in
Japan for a little bit it always comes
back to me and then I get like more
smooth
again yeah it always comes back to
[Music]
me if you want a freshen up on Japan
japaneses collab of any of the Holo
babies no why why would it why would it
be with the Hol
babies
no h where was i m
m- yeah GD thanks for the pinky great
performance K I only caught the stage
one live but seeing the comments for the
others was making me very hyped to see
the B it's worth going there and loving
to see some cave
peeps wait so you were at the venue
right for stage one right oh my
God I'm so happy so many of you guys
went there really it makes me so so
so okay can't believe it you went so far
so many of you went so
far big U on the travel for everybody
who went there thank you and also for
the everybody who watched it from home
thank you so much for watching yeah I
guess I should
go is she still checking her
submissions yeah it's probably going to
do it for 15 more minutes I
imagine but I I'm I'm about I'm I'm
going to like pH out now don't
worry well well thank you TD thank you
let's watch it again tomorrow and like
relive those memories shall we maybe
I'll find you in the
audience thank you so much for your
support as always you're the
[Music]
best Tassimo thanks for the pinky it was
an amazing experience seeing you all on
stage singing and dancing was super fun
also great work from staff to make this
whole thing possible next year I
definitely want to come in person you
were on fire can and your hips as well
oh you should you really got to come in
person yeah it's it's like a special
experience I think especially when you
travel and and you meet other kfp there
that also travel like I think everybody
just had this like crazy once in the
lifetime experience going to places that
I recommended before as well
and meeting up there with other
kfp I think it's just yeah
amazing so plan ahead if you can I'm
glad they made um it easier for
foreigners to get a ticket and and get a
trip possible to Japan and all that
things have become more easy and
generally I also have to say from like
behind the scenes POV I think they like
staff and everybody the company with
this concert they made a lot of
improvements for um us talents as well
that makes everything feel better so
really things are just like improving a
lot in my
opinion so I've been feeling very very
blessed #
blessed
T okay one more t uh tyen thank you for
the red super chat thank it all it's
honestly hard to describe how happy I am
to keep supporting you and how amazing I
found your performances this
weekend every year that passes I'm more
thankful to have found you and more
Blown Away by everything you do here's
to another year of serving
stuff thank you I'm also so happy you
found me I've been very very emotional
about people supporting me
these days so thank you very much for
being part of kfb for such a long time
especially D I hope I can make you guys
feel very very
proud with these kind of opportunities
also um I'm going to be contacting you
after the stream to help me write uh an
um a a sue sue letter to Frog song for
scamming me in game and also having um
someone help the friend the death friend
help scam me
so on that uh thing uh yeah so keep your
eyes open I'll be contacting you I'll
slide into your DMs with my slimy slimy
body yeah okay guys and in Frogger we
say
what we say oh yeah I RI
dirty I see you tomorrow I put up the
reservations hopefully before I sleep
and I need to think about what to eat
[Music]
goodbye thank you so much for
watching I'm going to rest my toe
now
[Music]