[Music]
oh
sorry sorry for taking so long one more
one more
moment
[Music]
okay one second
one
[Music]
no
no try yeah I just isn't this kind of
cute me only showing this part of my
head only head yes sorry I'm not wearing
I'm only wearing my underwear is it okay
if I only show this part of myself
today I'm a bit NY I'm a bit
[Music]
NY I'm a bit
NY no that's not okay what the
hell okay guys sorry for being so late
because uh I I was like okay I until 1
minute before the stream I was still
cuddling with my
cat and then during the loading screen I
was making tea quickly and uh and
setting up everything cuz this was also
still everything uh like like for shadow
ver set
[Laughter]
up
yeah speedrun cat cudle yeah how can I
ever resist
okay today we are playing Animal
Crossing for the first time in a long
time the last time I played it it was on
members only um which was also lots of
fun cuz I was working on my Island but
ever since then I have not played it
so again been a long
[Music]
time I only have play games when there's
like I stream what is
this I stream oh yeah don't don't trust
the DAT that's uh
yeah don't don't worry about it don't
worry about it okay no
news documentary
show boxing history of boxing you know
what you know what's what much more
interesting than
that YouTube
[Music]
channel no no no thank you though thank
you I have no interest in boxing at
least not like watching other people box
I would like to box myself with some
oh my God what's with my hair what it is
it because I haven't
a cute
oh oh my God it's been such a long time
oh
such I don't oh I don't know what
I'm
doing okay well today is a special
Animal Crossing episode because I will
be checking out everyone else's Islands
I was uh asking you guys to send me in
some of your islands and I'm quite
surprised that how many people sent me
um screenshots and wanted me to
visit yeah thank you guys everyone uh
for um uh signing up up I don't know if
we can I mean I'll do as many as I
contacted hopefully and then first
anniversary C oh my
God is that is that a matcha cake oh
how did I turn them I really
haven't played it in a long time and why
am I playing it for the OBS screen I do
not know anyway that's a beautiful cake
damn it looks yummy what she saw first
anniversary of uh the game
when was
that oh okay I ran with with B okay okay
okay so my Island still isn't very
special so that's why I think we should
go check out everyone else's
Islands well wait let me change my
outfit though oh wait I do have
uh I should have some other cute outfits
let
me yes how do I use it again
[Music]
no
no I forgot how to use
it I I just a oh God damn it wait wait
wait wait wait wait
wait why am I still playing for the obs
screen I think that's confusing me as
well but ah it's just a God damn it okay
well that one's
cute and that one should be cute too I
think oh yeah let's go with that one yes
yes I'm going with that one okay so um
everyone who I contacted I think
literally everyone actually wrote back
to me and already sent me the their Doo
Cotes thank you guys so much for like
being professional uh cuz I told them to
be there while I'm streaming and have
the doo codes ready and they have
perfectly prepared and they are on on uh
standby thank you
sasuka and they I don't really have a
specific order so I'll just visit uh
whatever and for they are since they all
watching let me say um I don't have time
to type messages in the chat so you guys
can type whatever you want if you want
to tell me something but I will answer
in the Stream so there might be a little
bit of awkward delay for you guys if you
are I mean I'm talking to the people who
show me their Island but for like a
general um guideline we just just start
uh once I arrive just start showing me
your Island like I will follow you and
you show me everything that you think uh
should be seen and everything that's
important and then you lead me back
please don't make it take longer than 10
minutes if possible and yeah does it
sound good does it sound good then I
will start with the first ER Island I
think which one should I go
first
um okay I don't know I'm just just going
to go let's go with the the the earliest
DM that I
received and I will hide the
screen on OBS first so that you guys
don't see the doo code
[Music]
okay and then
wait
first victim there have been like some
genu genuinely um beautiful islands and
some that are uh a bit um special
because
they have some yeah funny things to see
but mostly they're all just uh really
really pretty I went for mostly islands
that look like a lot of work went into
them m so I don't I don't know what I
don't remember which one this one is
that we're going to first I want to
visit someone yes yes uh online play yes
yes yes yes yes yes I know you
[Music]
don't what software upd is C please
restart the software perform software up
you if you restart the software
well can I do this later it says later
too but I guess I I probably have to do
it
now God damn it okay wait this should be
fast a software upd is required update
dat yeah okay okay let's go why you tell
me on the freaking
uh airport tell me oh yeah this there is
not enough free space to download the
data you will need 200 MB of free space
in the console system memory or on the
micro SD card please archive some
software to make space okay okay okay
okay
wait Pokemon Shield yes
archive uh is that enough I think that
was
enough byebye Pokémon Shield bye-bye but
archiving is fine right I can retrieve
it whenever
I really have no space on my switch like
there's ways to add space right but I
don't have uh looked into them
yet okay one one minute
remaining to download the
data wait wait it's downloading
downloading downloading a Micro SD card
you could buy a bigger micro SD yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I know I know I know I know I know but
up until now I was I just I'm just
whatever I just archived the the games
it was fine up until now I never felt
like that was in such an issue because
mostly there's a lot of games that I
don't play anymore anyway yeah H I made
tea is it drinkable
already oh wait I think we're
done I think I have to get into animal
cring Again
download the safe data will now be
updated to the new release version yeah
I guess I yeah I haven't updated since a
long time so there was a lot of stuff
missing I think the game will start
okay guys today is Thurday it's Thurday
thur day getting down on Thursday you
know I'm so excited because I want
Friday to come and then I want I want
the the next week to
come really excited I just want this
week week to be over by tomorrow oh my
God I got like um tomorrow like my my
move is on Saturday but
spontaneously um
tomorrow I am sorry just restarting the
game tomorrow I am like picking up my
bed that I ordered my new bed it
actually arrived
early earlier than I expected I thought
I I thought I had to like wait a bit
longer until it actually arrives in the
in the new um for not in the new
apartment I have to pick it up at the
place but so one day before I got the
message that it arrived I I went on
Amazon and bought the most
expensive air bed that I could find like
a really comfy automatically
uh filling itself up really good air bad
because I was like whatever um my bed is
probably still going to take a while to
come but then turns out one day later I
got the email that my a bed has arrived
in the warehouse and is ready to pick
up God damn
it but it's good because that airb I can
just use whenever for like
guests oh yeah right so whenever
whenever my my family comes over but I
did also want to get like a proper guest
bed as well and put it in my
office in my office room uh I want to
visit
[Music]
someone uh online
play okay now here we
go
Roger H Doo
C
first off okay let me warn you lots of
muffins you are first I'm coming to you
right now I hope your Doo code is still
active if not sent me a new one
immediately but I'm coming to
you uh search me a do
Cod okay
okay uh rega the do code for me yes so
it is uh is are you in the chat I wonder
maybe you don't have the same name but
okay
mhm n
w confirm that should be correct the
roasting will begin I don't know they
all look super good I don't think I can
roast those islands that much they they
all look good looks like we got a flight
for
windfall okay we're
ready let's fly
oo this is much uh more organized than
the last time when we visited islands
and when people came to see me because
that took ages and you know I didn't
know which place was save and all that
but this time this time I organized it
on Twitter beforehand so thank you
everyone for signing up if you are not
chosen today or if we don't have time
and um I'm sure we're going to do
another stream like this in the future
for some more h day Vibes visiting some
islands and yeah let me try to drink my
tea I'm drinking my my Christmas Market
tea again hot tea
oh
wo wo
wo
hi
oh my God okay for people who don't play
Animal
Crossing this it it takes like millions
of hours of work it's so annoying to
like it takes so much time like even
just making one path it takes you like
15 seconds so it's that that that
already looked like so
much
that one looked amazing from
above looks amazing at first glance yeah
welcome to the video hi k your name is k
cute I love your hat it's so cute give
me your clothes I love your clothes
they're so cute okay anyway I I will
follow you is that for
me what is that thank you it even like
comes in my colors is is that is that uh
like Tom is that by accident what is
that open oh no no no no not wrong
wait
can you decide what colors the the
presents come in Deco duck sh shba thank
you for Sha Sha I love your hat so much
oh my God I love her wait look at her
flag look at her flag look at her flag
it's C oh my God what a sweetheart I
love you Kate wait wait wait wait you
know what those those those those those
sweets do you see that those are called
Crain I don't know what they're called
in animal crafting but officially like
in in my country they're called C and
then and they F like with jam and I ate
like two yesterday actually for
breakfast oh my God why why is that an
animal cing that's so
cool that's so cool I love her
flag so excited I love it when people
like include oh oh my God oh my God oh
my God look at that is so cool so I 11
of people include like like kfp stuffff
I love those those Carpets on the ground
they are they look obviously like um
like custom content that like you can
like download I guess like uh I don't
know how to how that really is called in
Animal Crossing um my brain is in Sims 4
still but that's so cute with that with
that wait is it really though maybe it's
not is that an actual like item or is
that like a DLC thingy cuz there's a
pillow
there in the same
pattern H I really like this place with
the with this um how do you call that
how what what would you call that and
look at the duck is that the duck that I
have
too oh God I love this place I just want
to chill here I'm spending too much time
here but this is beautiful also because
of the waterfall in the background must
the K I love that and the banner yeah
the banner is beautiful I also I also
like this the pot here okay sorry I'm
really excited about your Island it's
beautiful there's those little Stones
here oh my God okay hello hello coming
I'm coming
oh well that looks really pretty nice
decoration with the butterflies wow I
didn't know they they come that big when
you like put them outside wow look at
those mushrooms they look beautiful even
though I hate mushrooms W that big
flower
wow
wow it's like when I go to Idol concerts
in front of the concert hall they would
have millions of those flower stands
like congratulating them for having a
concert and all that yeah like really
big ones too really fancy ones oh here
we have like some uh Asian style
Japanese oh Z Garden I guess with lots
of bum boo
oh me and Cy had one of of those uh in
our in our private room we had like a
private bath outside in the snow and it
LO it looked like that around about the
same size too
wow that's so pretty ah you know what
that is guys that's H from tan it's a
Japanese like holiday I'm not sure if
you could call it holiday but um on the
7th of July 77 I think it is you put um
like wishes on a pie piece of paper on a
long piece of paper H and and and put it
on on like a bamboo tree yeah it's t
look it up it's really a sweet sweet uh
little H look at
never and frog which I think is supposed
to be like a plate and uh and like some
food cuz that looks like uh Chopsticks
but it's a good idea to put that on here
and the ground here that's also like
downloaded the uh self-made stuff I
think so that's a lot of work too to
place all of that the one of the most
annoying things about Animal Crossing
that I thought is really annoying is
like putting down um like ground
patterns that are not already in the
game it takes so long okay sorry sorry
and lots of Sakura like um cherry
blossoms elements too
damn
beautiful wow oh sorry
W here's the for the guests the camping
spot okay okay more Ducks so many ducks
I love that that's so
adorable oh another one another place
for picnic that's so
sweet I love playing around in leaves
and you see there was those butterflies
everywhere the butterflies and the Ducks
are like a reoccurring
thing which I think is very nice detail
W it's so girly here too oh God are you
okay is he hurt did you hurt him one
second let me take a sip from my tea
I've been talking so much I'm so
[Music]
excited oh wait why do I see here it's
like a cardboard game TT RPG something
like that also reminds me of uh Magic
and and and uh men the game that we
played with C on looks like combination
of all those games
oh what is that that's cute can you open
it oh no you can't but it's cute sorry
I'm coming I'm
coming this is so
cute more Ducks more Ducks oh and is
that is that the the the thing the fly
head statue I don't see it well with the
camera like that that's that's really
hard to see I can't see the top oh oh
you can lay down here that's so chill
one of the few ah Statue of Liberty one
of the few actually like usable objects
oh there now you can see it
oh oh my God can I move into your Island
Kate oh that's again so pretty look at
all those details Kate if you can type
in the chat like how much time it took
please move it can you tell me how much
time how long you've been working on
this island and I one of those baths and
I love that coconut juice thingy I don't
really like coconuts but that looks so
fancy
525 hours logged in oh god oh wow ah
wait doesa went Axel oh okay I but maybe
Raina lives here because of
that
cute
oh how much is that in days 525 hours
it's a croc crck or is that called
different in English in in German it's
called a cl
cl
wow I love that
place oh that's so pretty I didn't know
you could put those objects on the stone
as
well 20
days CL we we have I
what do you call those in English then
the Zelda breath of the wild
thingies that's what you call them in
English well that's so close why are you
guys acting as if I said something
really weird oh there's more of those
cin oh wait optical illusion I thought
that was actually like like going up
like
elevated and some pillows can I sit on
oh you can sit on them a wait you kitty
k oh golden roses wait wait wait wait
wait wait hello I don't see you
me yeah yeah my name's K hi
Miss A I didn't really see much of you
but you look cute from like the little
part of you that I saw yeah she seems
kind of popular cute she looks like a
Siamese cat come
onina
oh well can I ride on those animal
crafting please make more objects abely
usable that would be awesome oh we jump
from here p p i can jump I'm a bunny
today no problem Oh that cake looks
yummy wait is that is that sign what's
that sign is that PE
or and some Easter eggs nice oh the cake
that I just got oh yeah we went back to
here back here we were here before oh
that is actually pink oh the pee pie oh
should I write something on your
worldall quickly
wow she had a lot of visitors before you
can make up to two post during one trip
oh God wait
oh uh uh okay I have I have uh I'm using
I have it docked right now I'm using my
switch controller so I can't really do
much I'm just going to sign with letters
K that is uh yeah really
lame and that's all can
do y
yeah really um on personal signature
that was it I think was it or do you
want me I want to show your uh house the
inside of your
house wait that's that's cute too I
didn't see that one
before wow for the flowers ew Beetle ew
disgusting
oh oh hello he look cute
honk wait what's hey there's a c flag
here oh my God that's so
cute oh that's your house huh oh around
all the waterfalls
Dam and it's pink so cute and the Heart
do you see those hearts uh on the ground
wow so much detail
love
tea who I like I like how it's so
dark very
elegant dark wood with blue and green
wow wow it's very
mature very mature very pretty oh here
comes the Gir stuff wow that bed
and that couch oh those are like the the
wait is that cinnamon rail or what was
it called this one I think it's cinnamon
rail This Is The Stuff uh from that IAL
that I told you guys that s SEL is doing
a collab with h live so um that's like
you will see stuff like that combined
with the with some H Live members I
don't know if you guys missed out on
that announcement but this is for
example one yes please give me
W you have another one of those couches
oh my God please yes I I have uh some
space in my inventory I'll take it
gladly thank you thank
you yeah that was cinon I I like cinon r
s is one of the super cute sandal
characters oh she's looking for her
couch right now I think I'll go to the
right room then and check it out while
she's looking for the couch I hope it's
okay what is this room oh
who
whoa
wow 10 out of 10 for
that again very elegant combining the
dark brown wood with uh flowers and
green wow that's beautiful I want to
jump into that
bath
nice one that's so cozy I want that room
me
too how does it compared to your new
apartment my new apartment's bathroom
has a very different
style a bit more modern than that but I
like that style very much
too oh my God that
kitchen not God spare C but oh you got a
different one oh my God look at that
beautiful
kitchen w
a that again looks like the whole house
I like how you know a lot of people have
like all their rooms in a different
theme but I feel like there's an ongoing
theme in her house except for her
bedroom maybe but like again you see the
walls in like like some dark brown
bluish tone and the dark wood again and
like the same color elements and style
seem to repeat itself so I think that's
really beautiful so
good so good can can I go up and down
too is it okay Kate is it okay to go up
and
down your house is so beauti oh look at
all those villagers oh is that her
villagers oh oh you have that popular
one the one with the glasses that one
that is for some reason super
popular she got like some chicken
too okay I'll go I'll go
up I'll go yeah Raymond Raymond was his
name he's super popular I did have oh
you let him go W again though
look I didn't get him oh you just want
him I guess wao what the
hell again the wood and like like the
elegant oh man it looks very very fancy
here I like the music playing here too
and the windows are really
beautiful some kind of painting up there
that I can't see fully what is
blob
cool it looks very comfy though like and
Rich yeah she looks very rich like
honestly she gives me like British Vibes
of Scottish Vibes like the whole the way
she like designs her apartment oh my God
a second bedroom this one looks more
calm and very Asian Japanese style are
you hear the
shami you hear that sham
wait wait
fo it's quiet
now there it is is that is that
Shamy I think that's
Shamy oo and those kimon no on the wall
and oh
beautiful I like the wall shelves and
the
katana sticky
k
I think I saw everything now I already
checked out those rooms
Kate damn nice really beautiful
house would live in there 10 out of 10
the whole island beautiful and that's
for
me oh oh I have the wa for her to come
out I think oh there you go what did I
get this the duck then the cinnamon Ro
tray the k k canop be snack and the Kiki
l oh Kiki and laa yeah I know them thank
you
oh yeah thank
you berina oh yeah that's a German name
in Australia we call it K and in German
uh they call them bellina I think yeah
yeah yeah B you can't please show me the
exit yummy thank you wow what a sweet
girl I love her I love
her she looks so cute
too marry
Mei josi very girly you had amazing
taste I give your Island
H I give you all the 10 out of 10 Bye by
thank you wait how do I do
wait it's okay auto correct uh wait oh
yeah
uh uh joint thank you do you want to
take a screenshot quick uh from your
side if you want I I'll be posing I'll
be posing for
you uh wait
uh
cheese
everyone did she do it I wonder I wonder
if it's okay maybe she doesn't want a
photo okay
[Music]
[Applause]
byebye yay thank you Kate thank you that
was a lovely first Village uh island did
it take us I feel like it took us wait
how is it
already
6:40 6 P 6:40 p.m. how how is that
possible how is that possible didn't how
how did that but the island visit itself
didn't take me longer than 20 minutes
right oh my
[Music]
God okay let's go next Island
okay I guess every Alum takes about 20
minutes if you do it properly uh
then next up let's go
to Felicia I'm coming to you I'm coming
to
you are you ready for the S I have your
coat just going to quickly fly back home
once and then come to
[Music]
you which them too wait who's that m
Mouse
huh I don't I don't have a mouse like
that living in my on my island is that
just some
NPC did I invite that Mouse to move
in I don't remember inviting him I was
looking for a mouse to move in in my
members only stream I think but I don't
remember actually inviting someone did I
Casper
Casper wait why did I just get
money anyway let me uh drop off some
items uh here on the
ground uh Dr actually I want to see how
the sofa looks
like
wait
Mor W oh my God that looks so cute it
fits my current
outfit Kate you're the best thank you I
wasn't around when those items were
around I don't think you can really get
them anymore now right can you still I
wonder I don't think you can I think
those are all like limited time
only so I was very lucky to receive that
thank
you H yeah cat cat is one of my
villagers yep yep yep okay next Island
we got to hurry up a little bit
wow I want to
fly help me fly you cute little B you
got a nice
be uh I want to visit someone
please I want to go online online online
please okay connect me do it do it just
do it
oh
wait do it I'm okay I'm going to drink
my tea before it gets
cold
okay how do you want to travel don't
don't call
please sorry I got a cat hair in my
mouth
let me hide the screen and there we go
this letter
and this
number and this letter and this and this
one okay I'm on my way I'm on my
way let's go next island is from
Felicia another cute
girl the island's name is n oh what a
cute
[Music]
name that's the sound that I make when
I'm flying over to the
island gosh it's so hot here right now
why am I I'm already naked obviously why
am why am I still feeling so
hot now got
S I should change into something more
light okay let's see let's see what will
what will the first look be like from
[Music]
above drop the hats
maybe I'll feel a little bit yeah a
little bit cooler than
H well I talked too much
too oh wait actually probably because I
drank that tea I feel hot right now
makes
sense are you guys ready for another
Island be nice everyone but I only
really chose beautiful islands I think
mostly there's just one or two like
somewhat funny Islands maybe somewhat
funny and I can some way because it has
like whole life
references but besides that it's really
just beautiful islands m
w oh it's um it's uh it's it's it's for
Autumn here I think because the ground
is uh
yellow
wow look at this whole life outfits did
you see those oh oh God a lot of items
are those for are those for
me are those for me me damn so many
presents guys you don't have to give me
presents it takes a lot time too so even
if you give him presents one or one or
two or three is fine but okay okay okay
okay the
offerings for your leader takaz
kiar it's mandatory no it's not it's not
mandatory let me out of the plane oh
hello you look cute you got a matress oh
and Shaka Shaka maras oh Shaka
Shaka can I am I allowed to take them oh
my God she got the Salo
items oh my
God okay I have to take those All of Me
Oh my
God oh my God are those all s new items
I don't I don't even know if I have
enough space for all of them oh my God a
bridge Cloud oh my
God s items everywhere pom ping R pom
pom buing bed pom ping R oh my God P ter
p p is the the one that oh hello that's
me wait do I even have that much space
Oh God uh I have to CH Choose Wisely oh
God uh
H oh my God I don't even have that much
space probably let me take the
chair pum puding is the one with like
the the pudding themed one cat tower I
don't think I have one I need one
definitely what is that you have a kitty
dress pom pom ping
puding yes pom pom ping pom pom
ping oh my god oh she has a wait did I
already pick up a Kiki L of B gu I
didn't but I I guess I don't really need
that ah there's too much stuff I got a
bit more space let me let me check what
you have snon roll sofa did I get that
one just now no it didn't right I got I
got Kik and L sofa right pum up in
TV Grand Q&A Birdwing model what does
that look like I one the Kiki and lot
dress you know what I want that and that
hello Kitty hat okay why
not and Simon roll table signage what is
that signage table tray kiing out pin
someon real hat cute I want
it socks animal nose Dynamic painting
kicking out a wall Posta K okay wait I
still have three
[Music]
more
H I choose I Choose You and I choose no
no no not that one whatever okay
hopefully that Mom's embroidery is cute
okay let's get started please lead me
around ficia please show me your
beautiful Island new come listen to
Island tune okay wa that's a shop though
ah you only hear it in
there let me in let me
in oh thank you for the Super
Chat
oh ooh wait I want that makeup table for
my new apartment damn it oh wait what's
that
oh is that the island to oh talk to them
okay what do we have here I'm impressed
that you traveled all the way to a fa
Island what can I do for you
today I don't know
[Music]
did the work oh I'm not sure I didn't
really
no I don't think I heard a j heart
Challenger what the music in the
[Music]
background I talk of
it ah
[Music]
oh nice one everyone stream heart
Challenger stream heart Challenger
stream heart
Challenger Felicia that is absolutely
amazing you are you are great I love all
of these people Animal Crossing players
are just the best people on
earth oh you can have a concert here w
Wait where did she go where did you go I
here
stream stream
challer guys why are you not streaming H
Challenger on the side right
[Music]
now we're almost at 1 million views
please guys stream it stream it there's
a music playlist on Myan
Channel you are a genius
Felicia thank you for the
advertisement this was not planned by
the way this was not planned she did
that on her own
ooh pretty pretty
pretty wow wow wow W oh you can get the
coins what those are the Mario
items
o o
[Music]
oo
cool
boom it's like an amusement park damn I
like all those little like small spotty
paths and this entrance is cute with a
rainbow pastel colored wood
M
pretty ooh wo oh wait is this like does
this place only look like this because
it's Autumn because it looks really good
in Autumn maybe she hasn't set so it's
always Autumn look at all those S items
cute they they like fit together so well
they have lots of
Harmony oh c cinnamon Road villager oh
right I think I heard about that that
there was like one
special uh
villager
I don't think
I oh
CH where's your house you're just
visiting yeah BT dubs
what I'm the only fully trained and
licensed trans set and all of new I hope
we can be
friends that's cute a adorable
callina here there's a cinnamon R
villager awesome wow you're really lucky
that you have her all right moving on
please oh so it goes up here and then
more more House Hotel there's a hotel
here who whose house is
that let's go in I
guess wait the map looks so pretty I
just saw it for a moment but it looks so
organized so well
organized I it must must be her house
right but she built it like a hotel oh
that does look like a hotel
lobby oh they have she has like
the the uh reception here with lots of
gold
bars the music is dope here too did she
go
left did she go left I think she went
the
left c i a w why is every on
what wait is that are you guys just
spamming or reacting to
something
what
what I think it's just
Spam what what's going on do I have a
mod
here wait wait you have you have oh my
God go you have cockroaches
here step on the yeah yeah I know okay
don't don't don't worry I'm stepping on
him this this is so pink
wow wait I don't have a slow mode on
wait one second sorry sorry Felicia I
need to do something really
quick sorry I don't have any
mods
uh chat slow
mode uh there we
go
okay what up up
ah chat stop
lagging and I'm going to ban some people
[Music]
ban I don't even know what that
means ban this dude and ban
him okay okay and did I ban you
already okay okay ban
you now now now we should be fine I
don't see anymore tell me guys if there
is
more
okay very pink room very
girly wait what does this mean these
rooms are all uh bedrooms because it's a
hotel damn this music is so
chill what's
here oh yeah another bathroom oh why are
there
cockroaches
I don't want to stay in this hotel if
there's cockroaches
here hey this room comes with lots of
food right away like if you arrive in
the hotel and you're like super hungry
right away this is the room for
you more cockroaches I like this room
this sty
style I wonder what would you call this
style you
clores oh very
pretty Victorian European yeah I guess
something like
that then I guess another hotel room oh
I went down
sorry I went downstairs do we have the
usual room there or never like uh guest
room
wa wow I guess that's like the hotel
restaurant/bar
what what what all the I got rid of all
your
cockroaches wow that looks so cute I
love the color
combination it's so such an interesting
theme like the like he actually looks
like he's going to serve me some
milkshake from outer space so
good wow the floor is
moving and the rock is like the herb oh
my God that's such a cute detail let me
get off of that chair let me get off
damn I love the light blue SL like
turquoise theme that she's got going on
here obviously in a hotel you need a
restaurant SL bar as well so
okay what's up
here maybe the the suite the
Presidential
Suite C what the hell was
[Music]
that W that's so
cute
W it's like a like a like a Cafe Garden
uh okay I don't know how to describe
that what do you call like um the garden
houses that's really
pretty I want to I want to do some um
like eat some cookies and drink some tea
here come on
p a greenh house yeah that's what I me
garden house green house not so
difficult all right please show me the
rest of your I
[Music]
M also this again looks like she took
like thousands of hours to build this
island look at all those bikes you can
rent oh it's like camping
Style
hey pretty oh that's
chill home point, 300 hours dear
Lord
wow I love those
beds
so wow so
creative pretty I like the Halloween
objects she has in there as well like
the pumpkins and stuff cuz it fits the
Autumn
style wo that's cute too W also isn't
she like super popular that
Viller
sorry oh baseball fan living
here oh like oh my God it's like so much
love put in here with all those can I
kill that bug no with all the diff
different themes I guess she has like I
don't know what's the theme Here music
and and and and not
sure
damn what's the Christmas tree doing
there she even got trash cans for the
villagers oh the heart L is pretty oh
and the path around it so pretty
too woo lot of Flowers and Butterflies
they're so hute here they kind
Cho what how is that one so big how can
you get them so big you don't
rest in peace do go that must oh wait
that's a that's a photo of him
a I must be really really sad to lose
your pet I'm
sorry but that's so sweet that you made
that
doggo he will come back to you in
another life I'm sure
doggos are some of the best animals
living on Earth Earth so I'm sure they
get revived as as Doo again they love
being dogos that villager is so cute he
look kind of looks like
you or she she really really cute cute
kitty cat I like her
clothes wait I have her too what do you
say because I have you too do you do
react to that
aie I know you aie I have you on my
Island
oh my God that is so cool what a fishing
spot and the crab it actually
moves
W I wish you could turn the camera
around to the
side huge crab it's it's
breathing y
w there's a treasure chest
who look at all those crabs and stuff
and jelly fish in the background oo and
I like how the chairs are like
shells oh have ice cream oh my God
that's so
cute where did she go I lost her last
stop my basement your
basement your basement I thought already
was at your
basement is it the usual
room let's take a look at your usual
room
y I'm scared guys she's taking me oh
that's her actual
house ah it's safe room she says it's
safe guys is do you do you think it's
okay to go
in look at all those
recipes
damn I'm scared stranger danger
oh she she doesn't even want to to show
us her house she just wants me to see
her her
basement
[Music]
oh Zelda and and oh there Ru and
Danga and
Fain it's her U room oh my God
FGL
cosplayer yeah I saw she's a cosplayer
actually on her Twitter account I saw oh
are those older oh she has a sewing
machine oh that makes
sense it's like her probably her real
room that's definitely her real
[Laughter]
room all right damn that was really
cool thank you I wonder if all those
costumes she actually really like did
for real like outside of the game or
just randomly put out some uh outfits
there but I can imagine her actually
hanging up each outfit that she did
awesome oh yeah yeah yeah I saw that too
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah hello outfits
cute I I I still don't have I still
didn't download the
my own outfit uh I want that one I want
it that looks so well made the good one
looks great
too that looks so
comfy W wait it's still continues oh my
god wow all those cakes it's a bakery
it's a cafe so cute I like how she put
up that wall there it's a really nice
way to like have a an outside Cafe but
like make it seem like really like it's
its own
thing I want I want that cake that cake
that cake
yeah what is
it you mean that part I she forgot that
part almost I guess you want to take a
phot down with me wait I'm going to
pose a custom
hat ah oh those cakes are hat
now I get oh my God that is so
[Music]
smart yay all right then thank
you thank you for inviting me oh was
beautiful 10 out of
10 wow very colorful very happy very
energetic girly Lively Island
beautiful
[Music]
I love you too thank
you wait did you hear it
again oh my God that's such a cute
detail thank you so much for doing
that damn
you didn't write her a note yeah but my
notes are shitty
anyway I mean she has she has the stream
as a as a memory that I
visited I can't do proper signs right
now
anyway stream High Challenger stream
High
Challenger let me drink some
[Music]
water this island made everyone look bad
no like l Lally every island that
I um picked out looks
amazing absolutely
amazing oh wait look I actually have the
same villager that you know the one that
we saw I think in the first V uh first
island the
cat the cute kitty cat that's why she
looks so familiar to
me okay so so let's let's leave uh the
items that I uh received I got a lot of
items from her damn she had way more
still thank you I think it's a fox e no
I mean the white blue
cat oops
oops okay so making a mess here again
because I need to drop off all of those
items
drop on
drop
drop and
drop Drop it like it's hot Drop it like
it's hot Drop it like it's
hot Drop it Like A T drop it like a t
drop it like a
h no
space Drop It Like A Drop It Like A Drop
It Like
[Music]
A got so many s
items
a I really think they were time limited
so we're really lucky to receive so many
presents so going
You Drop it like it's hot Drop it like
it's
hot Drop it Like It's Hot Cat tow I want
to place it actually let me see cute
it's pink too
adorable
drop drop let me drop those too oh uh
drop
drop and
drop drop I wish you could select more
than one freaking item that would be
amazing
drop
drop okay yeah I'm going to leave the
rest in my inventory let's go to the
next
Island which one should I go to
[Music]
next let me
see let's
see okay H this one this one looked
really good on the screenshots link I'm
coming to you next okay hope you are
ready for me to come
link
yes I I don't remember the looks I just
remember it looked amazing there were so
many islands so many
people I want to fly fly
high where did you want to go I want to
visit someone the f f not victim I don't
know why you guys keep on saying victim
online
play r
okay let me
hide let me hide the screen for
moment you want to how do you want to tr
we and the do code okay so it is this
and then
this and this and this
and this let's
go can you find
it Adia is the name of the
island let's fly can I just real quick
while we're flying let me let me let me
let me get get get into something more
light real quick I'm feeling really hot
one
second
[Music]
just
okay you didn't see it right you didn't
see when I was
changing people in the chat said uh
there's a fight oh welcome thank you
Fire Emblem uh
reference also has aie everyone has
[Music]
aie okay from above it didn't look like
super super super special but there was
like a like a nice welcome Visage very
kind how quick very quickly prepare
thank you so much let's see what is
special about this
island I think yeah I think I remember
some reference to Fire Emblem in uh the
screen screenshot something there that I
saw which made me choose this island
hello thank you for having me please
show me your
Island oh that was a cute
tune oh it comes from that uh this thing
here I think yeah
cute
welcome okay so we have a little little
um Park I
guess cute with some shops and some ice
cream oh right that's not ice cream
that's
a cotton
candy look at the map though his his
island is really well uh
organized all it's okay some simple
islands are also nice to see oh look at
the is that is that like a is that
the uh sign for like ID guards uh house
thingy oh yeah okay
okay I forgot what that looks like it
has been a while since I played Fire
Emblem free
oh Blossom viewing Lantern ooh I'll take
that oh c take the L and a golden Rose
thank
you I like that little spot for free
items okay okay it's not it's not as
much decorated and clct as all the other
Islands but it still has its
charm
oh refer oh that's kind of a spoiler
isn't
[Music]
it pain mea mea is
suffering wasn't there an announcement
that something new is
coming oo very nice natural
here lot of
Dreams yeah new movie you guys saw that
a new movie is coming
out oh Graves very sad who died here
yeah I asked um did I ask that oh yeah I
think I asked on Twitter I replied and
asked if those are the gra Graves from
um the students said ad guard
killed since it's kind of like a fire
emblem
reference the whole island is the whole
island the spoiler I wouldn't say so I
want to have some tea with me okay okay
mate let's drink some tea sup sup I'm
actually already done with my tea
so
okay actually wait my wait wait wait one
second my black outfit was actually wait
can I not change right
now
oh oh where is
it ah ah wait that's the one I'm wearing
underneath I
guess I see now we have like partner
look going
on Partner look partner look I feel like
his his what he's wearing is like the
male version of my
dress
I like that house that's cute there we
go that's what I wanted to
[Music]
see and for the people who' have been
following my channel you know that I
play Fire Emblem free houses on my
channel uh we started like at the very
beginning of my um career and uh we we
played the eard black Eagles
route Ard art very nice that was the the
reason why I chose this
island a little Japanese garden I feel
like every every
island uh kind of has like some kind of
Japanese garden Z Garden oh oh yeah that
reminds me of coron
senpai oh very pretty I need to make a
garden like that as
well yeah Japanese Gardens are really
pretty oh he's cute is he
koala cute but koalas are dangerous
koalas suck actually they're really cute
they look cute but they suck as we have
learned also their Scream is very
disturbing oo Rainbow Road oh more H
guard you really like H guard don't you
and
mik
M let's let's get in here let's see if
there's even more F emblem
references should we make an M koala
video oh very Halloween
is the music
too
ooh I like
this I didn't get the Halloween set so
this is the first time I actually see
that I wasn't playing back then so I
missed out on it
unfortunately M cool yes please Tel
actually like someone clipped it already
you got a freaking hamster oh my God
it's so cute oh b and a God
yes I actually ended up marrying inard
myself with BFF so I ship it too
although I I also shipped Petra with VI
but that didn't happen unfortunately
pain look at the Hamer it's running
running it never Tire oh right there re
tired I thought I thought it would stop
it would never stop and run endlessly K
now I want a hamster too all those flags
oh that's also El guard
[Laughter]
makes me want to play Fire Emblem
again okay we're checking out that room
let's go what's in
here
oh that's also a very pretty bathroom
that well is really uh popular I think
I've seen it in every island until
now I don't
know
o again the Japanese onen type of B
Japanese toilet that opens automatically
that is Japanese like mat where you can
chill on I love
that that is so nice but I wonder like
in what where where do you where do
Japanese people usually have that I
never actually saw it in Japan like
[Music]
oh or I ah okay Japanese Bros says it's
not really a common thing in Japan Japan
either they don't don't say see it
either
[Music]
normally oh pretty I like the the red
color theme here with the dark wood very
pretty oh I like that
desk
oh all right all right ladies first
ha
jaanese Bros I didn't know there's so
many Japanese Bros here today even
though it's already late at night for
them did he did he go
up ah he didn't come yet okay I guess
I'm just going up
[Music]
myself oh my God it's another one of
those like uh U rooms oh
oh damn all those outfits again I I
recognize the uh hat Miku one and the
Muka Maga ones but the
others I don't really wa
SS I don't Rec recognize those wait was
that Sons I don't know a KDA
ooh
nice all right nice and let's
downstairs mag mag I remember watching
that a long time ago I really liked it a
lot
too okay let's see what's downstairs I
hope I'm allowed to go
downstairs oh you got a skeleton in your
[Music]
basement oh that's a chill
room I feel like that's like the a
really ideal uh basement where you can
have like some some gaming yeah game
rooms Game Room Game Machines like old
school ones and Billard and and uh table
soccer dead
beats are the skeletons for the dead
beats oh we have a dead beat
here that looks like a Japanese uh
vending
machine okay all right tone forever yes
I
agree
takon I think was that it for this
[Music]
island I feel like we've
seen all of it
perhaps you should get rid of the
tarantula it's really
scary you have anything else to show are
we done I like the colors of that
flowers
Orange lots of orange ooh the pumpkin
thingy W what she's very colorful very
colorful
villager rainbow
villager okay I think that's
it thank you for showing me your Island
D yeah thank you
bye-bye maybe maybe uh not as cluttered
as the other Islands but still beautiful
and seems like
and a nice place to live in and spend
your time at so thank
[Music]
you you think he wants a a photo okay
wait wait wait wait I don't have time
I'm trying to squeeze in all the islands
but okay I'm coming I'm coming for a
photo if you want one wait okay even
with the partner
outfit okay let me pose let's still also
yoga
POS
wow is you take
it okay thank
you maybe you can put it on your
wall thank you for showing me your
Island nice tour nice
tour maybe needs more decoration
especially I would recommend like for
the Villagers
houses uh to give them a little bit more
personality you know add some more stuff
for them as well in front of the uh
front
yards H and I think then it would look
much much much more
special all right next up clear sky
thank you
byebye I still feel so hot I think we
have the heating on too
F maybe I should open a
window
Okay
Okay window has been
opened so
hot wow wow look at all my villagers
having a party there say hi I have a
phoenix villager did you guys know I
have a freaking Phoenix
villager fresh air yeah feels nice ooo
all right next Island uh I want to go to
that one we have a I got a very
interesting Island uh to show you which
is very much the island of a whole life
fan
uh especially of one specific member not
me uh but
still I saw some something of me
included as
well CJ
I'm coming to you CJ is that how I
pronounce your
name I'm coming to
you that Island looks very very very
special former uh Japanese H life me uh
member a big
fan oh very obviously oh
shut up shut up Lo Go Play let me
do it
again let me do it again uh I want to
[Music]
fly yeah yeah yeah yeah I want to visit
someone and I play there we
go the four four person we are visiting
now
okay
you will see in a moment you will
see what is so special about that
Island this
and
this and
this okay I'm really excited about those
kind of islands because they're really
really
funny with all the all the whole life
references I want to see more like that
okay the name of the island is
rink let's
fly let's go I need more water I'm
running out of
water I ran out of water no more
water d d
I think this
person is uh uh what generally seems to
like um whole life fifth gen and whole
life English the
most but what there's one member that
this person likes over everyone
else
[Music]
come on come on come on show us don't be
scared don't be
shy okay okay you can't see it yet oh oh
oh
oh there we
go
hi everything's so blue too themed in
blue colors and and we got a taco DTI oh
she's wearing the Lami outfit as
well big fan of Lami and
Ena so big boobies and flat I see I see
you like all kinds of sizes
it's it's nice to say that you don't
like the girls because of their
sizes hey CJ do I pronounce your name
correctly I like the bunny you have here
wait let me change my
outfit I want I want to change my
outfit
hold well let's go
for let's go for maybe that
one I like that one that's cute okay
let's go she got the beer too very
fitting that's how you pronounce oh God
I kind of missed it was it CJ is it
okay leave a note on the bulletin board
okay
go look all this outfits FG Hallen Siege
oh okay okay a sorry I already ran ran
here but like that's the first thing
that jumped into my
face where are K's boobs though K's
boobs need to be added to that outfit
over there it needs more boob
detail very cultured yeah again Kiana's
outfit I wonder if that's the same as
the other one that we saw okay continue
please I should I Rite it now
oops wait I put it
away okay I can only Rite K
though oh K hello YouTube hope you like
my friend's
Island thank
you okay okay I I'll ride
[Music]
quickly
ah okay
y wow with so much
love okay I'm following
[Music]
you you're
welcome W I love all those like light
blue color oh is that for
me present present
present
present oh what's that shamra soda oo
and the bunny W yeah thank you
oo everything's light blue I love it
light blue is such a pretty
color cool very chill outside
bar SE I don't have much time oh it's
lamy's bar oh makes sense only we have
Ramen here oh
yummy
Ramen rameno s oh that looks very yummy
me actually that's EBY in
there oh all those references oh my God
wait stand morning
mus you you like morning musim you're so
cultured
SI oh my God why are you so
cultured morning Muslim is a group from
Hell project uh an idol agency a real
Idol
agency that I am a huge fan of not
necessarily M musim but like I like
other Idol groups in hello project more
but morning musim is like really OG
they've been around for
ages so yeah that's really
cultured oh we got a huge workstation oh
it's like a like art study outside art
study beautiful I like that idea
I want to do that too
[Music]
yay oh little camping spot with a nice
hot fire and a camping station and oh
that's cool I didn't know you could
build up
[Music]
here I thought that was
impossible oh
pretty nice decoration on the beach as
well
[Music]
W
cute lots of trees lots of money trees
too
wow
oh and here we have the Villagers houses
I like that they add like these these uh
paintings of their faces so you know uh
who lives
where M very kind comy a big fire oh you
can have dinner here oh Grill station as
well and some
[Music]
soup oh I like that it's evening time
here right now because it keeps it give
gives all those lamps and all that more
atmosphere I love those light blue
lamps wow wow the piano is so
pretty
ooh oh that's so nice you can like look
at the stars here
oh very
nice okay okay
okay
pretty
M let's do some stargazing
guys oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh that's that's where AI lives I got
aie as
well oh we got a gaming station games
games
oh perfect every island needs a gaming
station what else do we
have so much Mario stuff yeah the doo
cute no I wow oh that looks
really wow I don't know what it is but
there's something about this
house and I guess the wall around
it makes it seem uh really
fancy and
Rich holy wow wow there's a whole party
going on here
cration down come on wow
okay very sparkly lots of confetti on
the
ground nice bathroom a little bit
different from the other ones I like the
I like the the tree
wall the sound from the bathtubs is so
soothing what's with those stones is
that like
a what is the purpose of does that like
warm up the
room I don't understand because there's
like stones around it but inside there's
wood it's a
sauna massage Stones sauna
Stones does that make it a
sauna E I didn't know that that's how it
works
sa
Stones pull water over them steam ah
okay okay so the the the the the the
fire whims up the stones and you pull
water over them okay makes sense carara
I cooked that the other day M very yummy
I like carara okay the kitchen is uh
cute but could use some more
work some more like like
them a bit more of a theme
M what do we have
here finish fans getting a agitated why
because of the
sauna do I even have finish
fans ooh comfy I like that you're
sleeping on the floor or or I guess up
here as well and oh we have ena's ena's
outfit on the wall
and lumy senpai's outfit as well oh wait
the Hat it's a taco Dy
[Music]
hat okay okay okay it looks very much
like a realistic room rather than like a
animal crossing super perfect them room
looks like how your room could actually
look
like okay we're going down
nice Taco Dy hat yeah I want it I love
hats you guys know
that oh is that the Chica Chica
outfit oh cute I like this is this the
office
o you have a hamster too cute I yeah c
yeah that was the name I actually didn't
watch the anime I just know the
character cuz it got like really popular
wait we have money there as
well Love is
War wait is the whole the whole room
recreated like after kaga
summer it did kind of give me like those
kind of office Vibes a little bit oh yes
it is oh okay it reminded me a bit of it
oh there's some you kind of need to
clean up here there's a lot of trash
under the
ground oh is this also a reference to
something or just just something mixed
together like I have to roast you a
little bit because this room has like
too many like different not elements
that don't fit each other that well okay
that's that's that's I have to say
that it looks a bit too much mixed
together needs more of a theme yeah
it has it has
potential so but in general that was a
nice house especially from the outside
it looks really good too very well
presented from the outside with some
workbenches and stuff nice and like I
like those I like those
walls oh outside TV station oh again
okay I get it you like Nan and L Senai
don't scam
M working progress for ena's
birthday what do you mean for's birthday
you want to look show her a screenshot
or you're working on that I see I see oh
what's going on here is that a streaming
station or what what like a work
[Music]
office I hope Ena sees this yeah Ena
needs to watch this Ena needs to see
this
island computer shop oh oh like it looks
like an internet cafe like an outside
internet
cafe where did you go there you
are o
mat again a lot of bamboo I I like
bamboo it looks really really elegant oh
and more light light
blue ly Senai image color uh I don't
know what this is but yeah big party
going on here and more on outside
on big
fishy ah is not some idle group a a a a
cool a
course that's some idle group isn't it
but I I I'm wondering with some a
forever H project
stand yeah from love life oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah I prefer idle
Master oh I like this area with the
bikes well made they're parking their
bikes here okay w w w w w w w w w Wait
can I check your able sister store what
what do they have in there right now can
I check
[Music]
okay Moy Moy knock knock did you see
that station outside next to the able
sister store with the like like the the
we
we weaving thingy oh okay n not
necessarily anything super special that
I want to
get okay
[Music]
byebye I don't know the name of that
thing in English what is
that this thing here that look
cool I got to give you that you put that
at the perfect spot and this Beach area
is so nice
too
ooh I like how you have like a general
color Fame going on for the whole
island sorry that was by accident oh I
got some nice Stones here is what is
this Memorial the they leave you are
those villagers that left
you kind of
sad who is that a moth I love mobs
they're so fluffy and cute look at this
beautiful what are all these villager
memorials did they
die and
[Music]
morei where is that where is the takasi
Kiara tribute where is it where is it
where is Tak
KF anything okay but it's it's okay it's
okay I mean there there's something here
there's something
here all right I think that's it
right next
time we will see about that okay if you
want to take a photo I'll will pose for
you for a
moment uh there we
go Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle Sparkle
Sparkle okay bye-bye
I hope oh I hope you took it in
time thank you for showing me your
Island it was very very
um like uh uish lots of fandoms in here
not only H Al but partially also like
other Idol stuff which I thought was
really
interesting
M victim number number five who do we
visit wait how the freak has it already
been 2
hours the time passes by so
fast oh my
[Music]
God okay okay I don't I really don't
know if I can visit all these islands
that I wanted to visit uh yeah B which
one should I go
to wait this one didn't answer
okay this one didn't send me a
code this one also didn't send me a
code
[Music]
uh oh that I want to see
that H Christina lanita I'm coming to
your Island but can you make it like a
little bit quick like a
[Music]
quicky maybe you could like give me like
a quick tour with not too many stops you
know there's something I want to see on
your Island I want to show my
people I have your dodo cat so I'll be
coming I'm on the way just wait for
me ooh Sunset beautiful did I get any
presents oh yes I did
oh
let me what oh yeah what other actually
wait wait wait wait I want to open them
I got some presents what is
it pirate dress
ooh mermaid fishy dress
oo prom sash
oh snowflake
cute cute but I'm I'll drop them here
for
now but they sound really
cute thank you for the
gift okay moving on to the next
Island Christina are you ready are you
ready did you clean up your Island
so I hope you cleaned
up uh I want to
fly
I want to visit someone
please online
play
R oh neck
crack do not touch do not don't touch it
don't touch it it makes me want to touch
it though if you tell me to not touch it
how can I not touch it okay entering Doo
come
BRB and uh wait okay so it's
uh
this and this nice crack thank you
guys
three and
this okay while we're flying I'm going
to go uh grab a water grabbing water
RTA jump onny f
let's fly let's go okay grabbing water I
think this is fine I don't need to press
anything right
okay
okay I'm back am I still flying
well what a long
flight I'm back I'm
back and my favorite soft drink uh IC
tea is that a soft
drink oo
[Music]
cute cute cute cute welcome to Japan
P
oh cute oh you got some cute little and
you look cute
too oh I'm hi oh oops you
didn't
oops sorry about
it I was reacting and you guys couldn't
even see it damn
it it looked
cute looked clean very
clean oo oh my God my ch Cena I know you
have that like like raccoon thing going
on right wait what the
why is that here that's very
insulting okay I'm going
home okay bye
[Music]
B
yeah okay okay but but you're going to
make up for it right you're going to
make up for it
Christina Christina what what love you
love me uhhuh
uhhuh I hope you do I see some presents
there I'm just going to go ahead and
take
them a
ring pron
present why an apple why did why are you
giving me an Apple I don't care about
apples thank you
present
open throw back
rocket and a blue
feather how can I wear it oh yeah I'm
transformed right now but okay okay okay
thank
you now please show me your
Island a quickie please please
Christina Christina I love I love the
raccoon like mask that you have on your
eyes it's really cute it's really cute
and your hat is cute too
cute I like the outfit really really
cute okay I'm following you you got the
light stick yeah cheering for me stream
High Challenger stream High Challenger
I like the floor here
W fun oh those there simple wooden
benches I like
those big teddy bears
w a lot of stuff going on
here Kuma concert oh they are
performing they don't have enough
expression and emotions though I got to
say they look kind of dead is that poop
oh my God you placed poop next to the
toilet oh no you didn't oh
finally your final form thank you that's
what I wanted to see yep thank you CH oh
yeah yeah okay let me
okay F those F those Bears let me sing
Let Me
perform yay
[Music]
okay thank
you I love that that's so cute that's so
C cute
Christina a
cute what a
simp a cute simp so I
forgive give me those clothes by the way
send them to me ship them to me okay
playground for
children mm
[Music]
MH you're changing
again oh oh hey I have the fitting
outfit for that wonderful wonderful I
like the fed you have on your hat on on
your head oh
wow
wow wow you did well in that
part I like how you use those those
Japanese uh uh paper uh door
thingies so
[Music]
good
Shute okay Christina faster faster speed
speed speed speed speed your beat music
[Music]
please running we got to go
fast where are we going you got to go
first before
me I'm following you oh oh pretty is it
Autumn here right now as
well oh why is everything so yellow is
that is that summer it should be
Autumn looks like it's Autumn
here oh wow what is this place H can you
like marry
here I'm frog okay okay Christina okay I
know you you're a s you're not a frog
you're a
s I'm
frog
cute she got all those outfits
ready oh this is like a fashion
show as well she that only shows me her
Island oh wait do I have some fitting
outfit
wait
[Music]
I I I guess I can Pride with that cuz we
got the same Blazer now wait I don't I
can't dance I want to dance
too I got I
got well I mean that's what I can
do clapping with one
hand ew I like the The Ice elements
there as well cuz part when you party it
gets a little bit
hot so you got to cool it down boo what
boo are you
crying cuz it's
um did Daka die D my six next to
zero what does that
mean what do that mean so we got we got
a death Sensei
here
huh
cha you're amazing like a really
hype uh hyped
up kfb
employee everyone take her as an example
okay this is this is what I want you
guys to show me your love and I want you
guys to wear your uniforms all the time
okay okay this this place needs some
more work chrisy now this place sucks
okay and Le more detail there's nothing
going on
here really bad really
bad wa who is that why is that on my
face
Christina I have
a complaint what what why is that flag
not my face is that your face why is it
on my
face okay it's okay I forgive
Christina cuz you did so well of the
other elements like you know wearing
your uniform and all that it's you okay
okay
okay W what the hell get rid of that
beo now now quick I want to see your
your place too you want me to write
something huh
[Music]
okay
okay it's not going to oh
oh
Christina you little
sweetheart
I love
you
what what so cute I'm going to
cry
a sweet now show me your room quick
Speed Run Speed Run speed
run d d d that's not your room that's
not your room that's just a stupid uh
dinosaur or Godzilla actually I guess hi
Taco
Yaki
o pretty cat you got there m is she
single let me
[Music]
in m m is that your house
Christina Godzilla will remember that
wait is Godzilla not just some dinosaur
w w there's some Japanese drama going on
here well I like I wow I love what you
did with the living
room cuz like I feel like most people
with the entrance or the living room oh
oh God there's lots of coins on the
ground too uh usually people have like
something in the middle something really
big in the middle and like yeah I don't
know it doesn't give you living room
Vibes that much but this really has some
living room Vibes cuz you parted it in
those sections really
well good job
Christina I like how you were like still
hiding behind that door
cute okay okay
bedroom
ah yes that's what I was waiting
for do it for her
it's
me that is your altar now tell me please
tell me that you have that here all the
time and not just for this
stream do it for
me this is beautiful this is what I
wanted to see that that's what I was
waiting for yes and I like what I'm
seeing we're not a CO no of course we're
not wait there's a puzle here too do you
have a usual this the usual room no it
looks way too
nice thank you what a
s the the what a cute simp though like
in in in the best way I could ever mean
it what a
s 10 out of
10 what's down here us your
room
oh W what is this place w h guy fight
the
money is she like studying some stuff
here cuz it's like very scientific the
room which
room what
room W I love this
place it's very um I don't know
mysterious magical you got your uh is
that a pen
tablet I guess I guess not it's like a
tra tracing station thingy
oo W kind of scary too but very
mysterious I like
[Music]
it it's not the usual room it's D
room and up up we
go witchcraft witchcraft
raccoon don't say that to her oh
m is that your
bedroom nice got some like Asian
elements here as well kind of mixed you
need you need
a cuz it got those like European Vibes
but
also Asian Vibes it's like you can't
decide what you want in your in
life oh wait Stein
skate and uh uh Santa Moon and I guess
that one is probably pie
oh what a nerd
OT Christina is Big
OT nice I like the Stein skate ref for
ends Christina you you're in the way
though move you're too
big
move let's take fast I love hook Papa
art Hooka Hooka is
amazing
you are an
utak nice I like your house quite a lot
and I like that flooring ooh is that all
the super chats that uh you're keeping
away from me the salary that you were
supposed to pay me but you just decided
to hide it away well I see it now you
should have you should have hide it hid
it more PR
properly it's all out
now I saw okay thank
you than
Christina oh I love you Island and you
you're so sweet thank you I love your
uniform too and all your other outfits
too and you you were so enthusiastic I
like
that thank
you
all right it's time to go home I to get
rid of that that's absolutely like I
can't I can't even look at that that's
ridiculous
ridiculous I'll take a BCT okay I I love
tenu who the freak is
that are you talking about
me okay okay I okay picture time
Christina stand beside
me and take a picture I'm not the one
taking the picture you guys are taking
the
pictures confetti you
done okay bye-bye I hope you I hope you
I hope you got the
picture great Island very very much the
island of a
s I like seeing that thank you so much
I do you want to write a in but it was
too long for you to write or you didn't
know how to write it because you just
usually just copy and paste
it I would have given you 10 out of 10
but you didn't write lvas in so I gave
you minus one
point we
say no Al do not AUST beas in that was
imply that we see each other in August
again
no by the way August in German is
written the same way we just say AUST
not August we say
AUST all right all right all right all
right you guys I I want to do um one
more Island I'm sorry I could I can't do
every
island maybe two maybe twoo much ah did
I visit that one oh that one looked
really cool I need to go okay we're
going to we're going to
do ah there's so many islands I
want to
[Music]
see all right we got to do this again
sometime okay let's do this one for now
we might do uh two
more let's do
uh Livy Livy F I'm coming to you is your
Doo code still
working I'm coming to
you do I have some do I need to clean up
my
inventory not necessarily
but let me
throw that out of my inventory and that
and that why does she give me a ring is
that like is she trying to marry me
I'm
taken I belong to the one and only
death okay we're going to the next
Island
Lan I want to
fly I really need to go to an idle
meeting so maybe this time when we're
flying I'm going to do a idle meeting
RTA
let's see how fast I can be VI online
play okay okay okay
uh Kate yeah well Kate was freaking cute
but but I I said that but I didn't mean
it that I'm I'm married to
C we have a child
together
search dehydration RTA yeah before I I
needed to hydrate RTA and now I'm doing
dehydration
RTA okay
yes by the way guys tomorrow I was
planning on playing
Yakuza but um I have to go pick up the
bed and probably also build it so it's
it it it might get a little bit late me
so because of that uh Yakuza is not
happening tomorrow but I'm going to if
everything goes well uh I'm going to um
play Yakuza twice next
week and then tomorrow I'm not sure what
we'll be doing yet we'll either play
Mario Kart
or I don't know something
short because I I just don't want to
overlap with Ena
somehow recently I've been like like I
feel like I've been doing really well uh
by not overlapping with anyone I've been
just purposefully streaming before
Ena anyway R see you in a
second
[Music]
come
I'm back I'm back I'm back oh it's
raining W did you guys see uh how great
the island looks already from like above
hi
William oh see that looked so dope on
screenshots like it looks like freaking
or
something this Tory should be short yeah
on your on the on the map it looks like
it's not done maybe but like the the
bottom right side is like oh IAB oh
that's really cool that you chose iabuk
as your
[Music]
inspiration let's see if it will look
like iabo thank you for the presents red
feather thanix feather oh oh an umbrella
frog
umbrella thank
you yeah I didn't bring my
you C frog umbrella that's so doble frog
umbrella is the best umbrella okay let's
let's enjoy this
WOW
W So Co this is this is the first island
where I don't want to like run for
everything I want to like like take my
time walking through
this look at all the detail K Books oh
my God
o oh my oh my God apologies for the
frame what do you mean frame drops oh no
problem I don't see any frame drops
hello are you in the way now go away
your villager in the way move I can't
move wait I'm waiting for him to go go
away please J okay now we
go wow apoll yeah that was his name yeah
yeah Mr AP poo I want to see what's on
that side I wish you could move the
camera and Animal Crossing godam look at
all those
refrigerators
an oh and the telephone thingies oh my
God it does definitely look like a
Japanese
um City View
yeah oh is that a shrine wait wait
that's that's fascinating this house I
know it's a villager house but for a
moment it reminded me of like a house in
a
shrine oh my
God unfinished restaurant
oh this is so
amazing how much time did it take you
there's millions of vending
machines what 70 did you see
7-Eleven oh my god I didn't even realize
wait that is
so like cool like this is aquariums but
if you look from here it does look like
the entrance of a convenience
[Music]
store I don't plan on being done wait
you think you'll never be done for like
a year or
two oh my God yeah I guess like normal
people don't get like everything like as
a present like me so it takes more
time
oh if I can help you I I I I would love
to help
you
kfp family M oh my God mazia oh my God
oh this is this is Maia it's a in Japan
that is a very uh popular like like
Japanese food fast food restaurant it
has like rice Bows Oh my God again the
aquarians that's so nice competition
yeah oh my God not the CF he has any
exactly this is freaking dope I'm not
sure if I'm allowed to show this on
stream but I don't care I'm showing
it more vending machines oh oh my God
this
looks this doesn't even look like Animal
Crossing
anymore holy this looks like some
RPG
game oh my
God
person five looks like yaku yeah kind
of oh my God P
oh or should I listen should I talk to
them
okay I wonder what it is oh oh wait oh
that was it I guess wait I guess if I
talk to them I can hear it again
oh I love that band cute
okay wait is
that m is that is it what I think it is
Family
Mart that's Family Mart
[Music]
right wait where's this song um like
what am I thinking of
what am I thinking
of some family Mt
remix song I don't
know this is so amazing this Market
isn't done yeah it looks like not done
but it's already looks
amazing how do you do
this how do you do all
this okay so what I see coffee Valley I
know that that's a restaurant too like a
cafe house we got the cup
again oh my
God this like shows you what you can do
in Animal Crossing oh look at that
screen but you can do in Animal
Crossing that is like so original on
Creative that other people usually don't
do that was amazing William that is like
coolest thing I've ever seen in Animal
[Music]
Crossing you want to take a photo I can
pose for
you strike a
pose uh yeah there you go
yay do you want your your umbrella back
I can give it back to
you place is so dope I hope you got the
picture I I can I can I can give the
umbrella back if you want do you want it
back do you want it
back oh I'll leave
it I'll put it
away and
drop thank you vam that was a million
out of a million that was absolutely
amazing
oh you can keep oh now it's too late I
think I have one at home anyway I
think wow please keep on working on it
if you ever finish it let me know I want
to see it again
[Music]
m 8 3 5 hours and how do you know did he
say
that holy
holy
Mo holy
macaroni that was oh my
God
absolutely
fascinating all right mariku I'm coming
to you now sorry to keep you
waiting I'm coming to you
I'm coming
to beats My Breath of the wild
time the honestly Animal Crossing
players are so dedicated they spend so
much freaking time on their Islands I I
wish I could be that dedicated to animal
crafting but I just lose like interest
and I don't have the
[Music]
time wait I got did I get oh
yeah
moreos what is that for cookie card
cool cute find some cookies are so
yummy what is
that okay mortar
sign wow yeah he had that on his Island
a lot
open menu chalkboard
ooh
cute and that red f i want to implement
that in some outfit of
[Music]
mine no New Year's noodles
drop and 12 grape dish whatever that is
thank you wo lot of presents
again next
Island
next
oh yes that's a yes
somehow with a lot of imagination yeah
yeah I can see
that
yep a crack a little
crack I need a
[Music]
massage all right let's visit
man I think if I remember oh I
that
no and and now he wants me to talk to
him from the beginning all over again
like please uh please do something about
this cover screen no not worried I I I I
know what I'm doing I know I should
cover this screen I've been doing that
the whole
time
[Music]
I oh
wait oh no okay
okay I'm so excited for tomorrow
[Music]
okay oh my oh
[Laughter]
my never mind let me hide the screen for
a
moment how did the recording go I went
fine I just recorded it on my own in in
audacity
audacity and
I also recorded Harmony for the whole
song even though it's a collaboration
but I just recorded it for for for like
everyone's Parts like me and I'm doing a
uh a song cover of
uh is the name of the island oh and song
cover with another whole life English
member
uh and I still don't know when we can
upload it because I'm still waiting for
her to uh record her
vocals but mixing should be quick and I
I am already uh done with my
vocals so hopefully I can release this
one but I just really wonder what would
be the best timing to release it because
next week there's a lot of stuff going
on a lot of stuff I just I just feel
like I shouldn't like
forcefully squeeze it in but at the same
time
time I want to release it soon because
I've been like waiting for it to be
ready to release a long
time and because of of like the the
video taking quite some time
w we got another super special
Island W did you see those train
tracks
oh oh there she's
sitting a cute the duckies on the ground
[Music]
a very fancy
looking very
pretty yeah because it's night time it
also makes it look very
pretty oh
sh I am excited to see your Island but
what the hell are you wearing your mask
creeps me
out combine that mask with those
pajamas I I am
scared P oh I guess so but the
mask didn't you did you have a mask with
no studs perhaps
oh what is this
music what where does that come from
where do that come
from what is
that is like only
here oh I like I like the the the this
like
pinkish walls with the bricks and on the
ground you see those bunnies and the the
carrots ah from the radio here
ah I like the white and pinkish bricks
really a lot I love that
Kawai
pink
oh really pretty is that your house bir
villager okay we don't really have time
to visit each villager
but thank you thank you I wouldn't mind
seeing your house at the end wow it's so
pretty oh I love that coat oh my
God and the Big Bear over
there
cute with the pink lights over there
that's
perfect yours isn't decorated you put so
much work in the outside but you don't
decorate your own house
okay no problem no
problem wow cute cute I love those
little like children's chairs that you
use them outside oh that's the Museum
oh I see I see cute I like the
[Music]
toast very
girly I follow
you lady ladies first bunnies first but
I'm also a bunny we're both
bunnies reject Burness become
bunny W that's so cute what the hell is
that is that also from
Sano it doesn't really look like Sano to
me is it it's so
cute or it is oh well that waterfall is
really welld designed designed with the
river flowing through it like in a
diagonal
way wow pretty see so this girl she like
decorated around the houses of the
villagers very well a ton of
flowers here oh my God are you just
breeding flowers here oh my God oh my
God too yep yep too many
flowers I guess it's just like a
breeding station for flowers
oh ah oh you can't to that on beach
actually oh so it is supposed to be a
decoration I guess okay I mean no real
like pattern going on here but still
nice oh really small Ally alley
Alleyway wow that's
cute what I like what she did there with
like the the walls in the background
like an optical illusion making it look
like houses but it's really just like
really thin walls and there the paper
tree cute the playground is really
adorable too with the little tent and
the drawings on the
ground a I love those train tracks too
what is a duck do oh my God can someone
get the duck away from there what if it
what if the train comes
the duck is stopping the train from
coming lots of pink
here du for oh no no no no no no
no W that's so
cute wow I love the details here oh
hello bunny she really likes bunnies
perhaps W again the trainer Rax I love
that ongoing theme very nice very nice
and again all those walls making it look
like a
city
oh oh oh
cute
cute and picnic up here really
nice it looks very
[Music]
comfy stargazing area yeah I'm sure that
looks nice
here oo comfy pillows some foof Nintendo
switch I love the the the the ground
patterns here it fits well with the
bridge as
well because all those patterns on the
ground are custom patterns it must have
been so much work to place all of them
oh my
[Music]
God outside
shower
[Music]
oh oh what is this place
unfinished kind of looks unfinished not
okay okay
okay wonder what will be
here see she did she probably already
spent hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of hours but still isn't finished you
can spend so much time on your island in
Animal Crossing it's
crazy oh oh that's
pretty it's kind of
romantic
romantic m
cute so Pink So
Girly oh is that a ukul or a guitar
anyway another house of a villager and
more bunnies she really likes
bunnies he Liv's my wife oh but she's
not home right now is
she Lolly who's Lolly is it a bunny
perhaps oh pinball station and a vending
machine oh it's a cat oh I'm surprised
okay bunny and a cat
Okay
cute what is is that what is that on the
ground is that what is that fish or
[Music]
trash oh oh wait the
way oh Secrets the way you like
decorated around looks uh what's it
called looks laddin oh oh because is
German oh wait why is
it wait is my game set to German right
now and I didn't
notice oh
wait I didn't want to enter wait is my
game set to German why is it called nuk
ladin but I didn't realize do you speak
German right now no she speaks
English she's so cute it's like a orange
fed uh
cat oh because you are German
[Music]
oh oh no no
hello oh because my game is set to
English but I mean I am was obviously
from a German speaking country as well
so I thought it was because of me a so
it shows you the language that the
player uh has said huh I like that
clothing that's looks very
comfy wait why is there a
camera facing at the
shower and the lighning source as
well I need an explanation what what's
going on
here hey you want to recreate The Sims 4
scene of Takami huh I know I know I know
I know I know I know you cute bunny
fluffy oh it's very pretty here with the
mushroom lights and all those flowers I
feel like I'm in Minecraft right
now
wow it looks like there's not much
decoration here but it looks so romantic
and pretty a stone circle oh yeah I
don't think you need many objects here
the nature already does everything
and the way you build those those
waterfalls like it looks very natural it
doesn't have like a like a stiff feeling
to it
oo Kitt
it
oo oh
[Music]
okay let's go up here I guess not
finished though looks like not
finished okay I'll not go there then
okay okay
wow oh okay you want to go okay I guess
wow she still has not finished
areas
what why is there eyes on the ground
that reminds me of a jibbly the you know
those fuzzy things with
eyes W what's going on here suddenly so
dark here oo and the train tracks again
but also much darker
ah suit Spirit that's what they're
called oh and like I guess this is uh on
purpose a lot of uh Wheats you know I I
do like the look of weeds in the game so
I I think that's nice to implement some
of
those ooh wait what what I didn't see
all of that
part it's so
pretty uh that's not finished I guess
[Music]
but
this is so cool I like how there's
suddenly a a change in the theme I can't
move because of the Villager I think is
there a villager standing there
yep
okay uh you want to go left
okay
[Music]
very moody here ooh and
mysterious is that blood yeah that
actually yeah wait what the hell little
more c yeah yeah yeah no I I see blood
on the streets all the time in the city
yeah yeah yeah I get what you
mean no actually what's going on here
wait now now now her outfit also makes a
bit more sense like that pink cuteness
with that weird
mask I'm scared
now yeah I'm
scared she has like like it's like she
has two personalities like something
really dark inside inside of that
cuteness on the outside but inside it's
like dark dark and scary oh my God it's
like a horror movie what the Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah Yeah very City like I I I hang
out my Blood Stained cloes outside as
[Music]
well yeah no
normal yeah it it it it it it dries
better when you hang your blood stain
cloes
outside I like that I like the moon
there though very what the is all
the blood and the prison
[Music]
wall no
no it's like two different islands put
into
one and suddenly the the villagers are
also like darker
here it's like like they know where they
belong
to oh my God she's going to kill you
tangel yeah I have a feeling like that
too right now like
a it's okay guys I'm a phoenix I can
take it I mean it's so scary
though run run to the
plane just
[Music]
run y I like that little path here oh
she's trying to make up an excuse or
something no no okay I thought she was
typing for one oh why is there so many
holes there does she want me to fall
into
one war crime
area all right not looks looks not not
not not so finished here
okay
okay m m mommy please pick me up I'm I'm
scared
mommy I think we're done y
um are we are we done
money you you your Island was a present
okay your is was great
um oh oh no what what does she give
me what is not much but thank you so
much
giant tiny
a baby
CH thank you do you want to take a Qui
picture we're both bunnies I feel like
we we could be best friends but but
that's what I thought at first but now
your Island scares me so I'm not sure
about the best friends thing
anymore well look at the map though it's
so
detailed
all right then thank
you I can't
pass
byebye
[Music]
feel
and I want to go
home I want to go home please do bring
me home quickly quick quickly
please typical Warcraft criminals
no #
coexist
yeah yeah I wonder who's her favorite
her life member is it you guys may keep
on making piod out references but I I
I'm not sure about
that it it must be
me
obviously thank
[Music]
you okay okay
uh uh did I go to this
one
H wait there only way been three hours
now oh my
God I feel
[Music]
like you could also oh wait I got a few
new codes
oh this one looks so dope too a I got to
check that one out but maybe maybe next
one is the last one but let me Choose
Wisely either this
[Music]
one what did that one look
like also very
pretty but not doesn't look finished
even though it's very
[Music]
pretty oh that one is nice
too M okay but I think I know where I'm
going sorry to the people that I
contacted but can't visit but I want to
make the next one the last
one
and so
F I'm coming to
[Music]
you please don't worry we'll probably do
this again because there were a lot of
interesting
um Island and I want to see more I want
to see
more some people are like insanely
creative
so I want to see what you guys do with
your
Islands hus
be last one last Island
Fong f f with
ph I want to fly
the sixth Island that we are
[Music]
visiting and
on
drum roll last Island season
two I just wanted I I wanted to visit as
many as possible but it surprisingly
takes a lot of time going through these
islands so let me write the
code
[Music]
uh and this number and this and this and
then that one
okay I love you K thank you I love you
too next
Island next
Island I feel like this island was
also kind of inspired
uh by Japan I
think or like to uh
Tokyo
especially so let's freaking go let's
see what the last Island looks like
so Mis
Island next Island clap clap clap clap
[Music]
need to drink more
water drum roll
please
W
oh oh I saw p m
oh more M by oh that's
me okay that was a great choice yep yep
that was a great choice
[Music]
okay what a what what a great taste this
person
has oh beautiful island I like like the
dark the dark uh
pavement p you call it pavement right
the ground the dark dark dark uh
concrete
[Music]
M and looks really good at
nighttime here's my
salary me you know what's up you know
what you know what's up thank you thank
you wow okay first
look see very Japanese style I like it I
like
it yeah that has Japanese writing on it
oh that looks very Japan is
wo and the
[Music]
music oh I want to look slowly for this
one as well who what the hell is
that that's so dope it's a y outside uh
food food
St ooh you know I mean it looks really
cool but I feel like you could make it
even um more
narrow and then it would give it a bit
more of a Tokyo Vibe because this should
probably be a bit more narrow to make it
even more Tokyo is look at all those M
seni on wait there's me on the ground as
well
[Music]
kers kfp wait this oh my God my eyes
were looking at something else but look
at
kfp did you just make that for the
stream now did you prepare that just for
now oh those are hats this is so smart
this is so freaking
smart oh my God that's amazing
[Music]
base
chicken amazing I love it wow I love the
dedication and the effort I follow you
please
continue beautiful the ramen looks so
yummy
oh
Diamond the music is
perfect M now we go outside of uh
Tokyo
oh that is so cool with the custom
ground ground pattern floor pattern
oh I guess
so
oh ooh concert area I love those lights
of the piano at the bar again o this
gives me Hawai Vibes a Senai flyers on
the ground Manan M my
flyers what of all these
flyers that's so cute oh thank you for
the membership welcome thank you soon
please enjoy your membership is that
your
house
oh I want to enter there we go
[Music]
H it is a room tour time let's see what
it looks
inside oh my God it's a freaking ramen
restaurant so good I love it when people
transform their own houses into like
restaurants or as we see saw before like
a hotel and all that so rather than
using it as your home you use it as like
like some kind of like store or
whatever that's so
cool should I check out the other rooms
too can I come behind do you want me to
show okay okay
okay nice Ramen balls
yeah oh okay no he has his own room that
looks like a typical like like
student uh apartment Japanese
tiny ass apartment with kind of like an
office as well cuz the walls look like
office walls yeah I guess I guess it's
like a just a back
office
ah the table kind of gave me like gave
me like um apartment Vibes as
well but I guess it yeah it's like a
back office SL break room
M what do we have here wait did you see
the M Senpai towel on the rack in the
entr friends you got to check check it
out when we go
back oh what the
hell who it's a
cinema oh my
God that's also something I've never
seen
before like in in in Animal
Crossing with pizza and
tacles maybe and popcorn oh my God
[Music]
yeah here look at the mik Senai face on
the
rack
oh oh my God what do we have here then
oh my
god oh okay okay okay yeah well of
course a place like this needs a back
but oh it's like a public bathroom very
well made can I go past it oh yeah
oh very smart design and here with all
the
sinks
[Music]
oh
damn yep yep yep yep yep that's that's
that's a very creative way to build your
own
house okay we go downstairs I I'm
guessing it's a game gaming room perhaps
like a game
center that's what I could
imagine oh oh my God it's a public
bathroom
cental a bath house japanes bath oh my
God you know people usually make the
bathrooms the and one of the um smaller
rooms on the ground floor but using the
one of the big rooms like
[Music]
this okay okay okay going upstairs oh my
God the fog effect on the floor yeah
don't move the don't move the camera
okay okay I guess it's optical illusion
time
oh yeah I saw that on his screenshot
that is so perfect okay I'm not going to
move the camera even though I'm very uh
tempted to
who wait
how wait is that how do
that that's Prett
pretty move down what do you mean like
like oh yeah like that oh my
[Music]
god
wow and the music
too oh my God that is so
beautiful I want to cry
this makes me cry look like a
[Music]
anime why is this Animal Crossing room
making me
cry it's the music it's the music and
the the
firewoods oh it's so romantic and sweet
and
emotional I'm going to
cry why are you about to cry I hate it
it's beautiful way too beautiful I don't
like it it's too
[Music]
[Applause]
beautiful it's
beautiful I want that I want that house
can I buy it I want it give it to me
please CA yeah I
agree
so
good oh my God what is this now another
restaurant
oh okay I need some Ramen all wait wa I
don't want the beer I want the
ramen oh and in the back he's cooking
like
pasta or more Ramen I guess and the flow
is Al romantic it's like a really
elegant type of Japanese restaurant not
like
the the fast food type of Japanese
restaurant but like an elegant expensive
type oh my god oh
[Music]
coin public like laundry
uh place that you can use and everybody
has freaking
p
[Music]
p oh that's cute too
I wish I had this much like get get up
this much creativity in Animal Crossing
I'm generally a creative type of
person but I don't have the P I guess
okay yeah it's not really a problem of
creativity it's just a pro problem of
patience and
time a wait I have that dress I have
that dress actually I have it uh in my
in my stick as well cute
really cute up here with all the dresses
outside very elegant
dresses very calm here
too
wow how did you put on top of the
vending machine how did you put those
magazines up there I didn't know you
could do
that where did he go
there oh even more like little stores
oh what
that's like a cafe Starbucks like
outside
Starbucks and then another Ramen
Place Sushi oh wait no not Ramen Sushi
it's a sushi restaurant oh with the fish
in the background oh not my thing cuz I
I I don't really like ra fish or like
crab and all that kind of
stuff
SSH oh my God what is this
another s oh my God and then here we
[Laughter]
have have to promote them yeah thank you
for promoting kfb as well here and there
oh look they're on the side on these on
these banners as well on the screens
[Music]
here
oh oh my God he built a freaking
shingin
SK oh that's so
smart oh my
God the
dude what what who are
you oh my
God
who the hell are
you oh my
God this place is insane this island is
insane you have no
space after you after you kill area here
as well everything's so impressive I
don't I I I lost my words like his house
though his house oh
my there's something special about this
River I don't know
why yo
oh oh my God oh my God I am in love I
want to move in here as
well oh my God I love
this it's so cute oh we go straight
okay it feels so big like there're so
much to see we're still not
done oh my God this is
amazing a another cute Beach Place area
for picnic with some comfy chairs and a
a hanging mat some pillows on the ground
some fruit
juice ooh some cute beach lamps lots of
coconuts very cute oh I love
that I love
that oh have you noticed he sat uh his I
don't know if it's because he has a
different date but I think it's not
really the season for cherry blossoms
anymore but it's a raining cherry
blossoms here maybe he has that all the
time W look at all these Beach LS I love
those I want those
too wait that stone Ah that's one of
those um horoscope of thingy uh star
sign uh items
thingies wow that area is cute
too oh music
change
oh co cool cool cool cool cool very cool
stuff
she definitely put a lot of thought and
a lot of time into this
island Misa if you want you can tell me
how many hours you put into this I would
actually be really
interested how many hours you put into
this
island it must be like like at least
1,000
hours please tell me or he walk slowly
through here on purpose
oh
745 to say he's done and then I guess a
bit
more
wo oh I love this path oh my
God that's so
cute
[Music]
oh you know I'm smiling the whole time
cuz I'm so fascinated about what you
guys did with your Islands
my face is a bit tired from all that
smiling it looks like a whole new room a
liary I don't know
bookstore
oh that is so cute I love this idea it's
so calm here the BDM changes are another
like really sweet detail a lot of people
I think um no matter how detailed their
island is a lot of people forget about
that they could do that as
well he works with that a lot
though oh
mountain mountain area ooh camping area
nice
nice well barbecue oh that looks so
comfy you know that that reminds me of
all those videos of like people making
really yummy food with like camping Tils
but it's like so simple but it looks
like so much more delicious and you're
like why am I cooking all these
delicious meals when I could just throw
something together with camping tools
and looks so much so much more yummy for
some reason how do they do
that guys do you guys know what I'm
talking
about oh
oh okay I was just wondering why you
have a ship there I was wondering how
you did that but that's that's that's
that's the dude who sells uh uh the
paintings right wow you decorated
everything for him as well here with the
paintings
aw who gave him a little little area of
his own and I like the ground of the the
animal prce uh because obviously the
people who live here are our animals
some more M Senpai Elite
M now I would like to advertise my holot
talk episode with M Senpai if you guys
haven't seen
it holot talk watch it that's really
cool with the painting uh
tools oh and sitting by the waterfall to
paint sounds really
nice how are we still not done oh my God
there's a wedding area over
there oh my
God this
island is
insane and we have a wedding area oh my
God for you and
Callie I got to bring cie here to marry
her thank
you would you like to take cie as your
beloved wife for eternity
Tak
yes I would and you Kelly would you like
to take hiana as your beloved wife for
eternity yes I guess
whatever yay you now may kiss your
bride I Now Pronounce You oh wait that
comes before the kiss I pronounce you
wife and
wife Tak forever thank you thank you
than you than you wait I want to do
[Music]
wait yay where did he go
there I just want to hang out in this
island
forever you still have something to show
me oh my
god
oh so what
h w it's a
shrine
oh my God that's so cute that's so
pretty small yeah
ging this island is so unique yeah the
ambience yeah it's
insane like I still can't believe that
he he a room in his house made me feel
emotional it's Animal
Crossing
wow this is so pretty
too B it's
beautiful oh and he I think he like
parted it for like you know men and
women here like Japanese BS usually are
part
it
oh there we go
a I so cute what is that what is that
object what is
that
beautiful very thoughtful design yep I
see a lot of thought went through that
how do you even plan something like that
like I want my Island to look nice too
but I don't even know where to start
like begin planning how do you
[Music]
start you can't just like start this out
of nowhere you you must have some kind
of idea of what you want it to look like
and and where you want what to be and
BL
[Music]
does she stream on Twitch no I do
not I stream on YouTube please
subscribe oh my God wait have we not
been through here either how how big is
this island
they I'm still not done looking at your
Island how
how sh what the
hell that's it oh my
[Music]
god let's let's you want to do you want
to I mean I know you look like Piko much
more but do you want to screenshot with
me as well like maybe at kfp I think it
was here
[Music]
[Laughter]
I want to take a screenshot too
honestly okay well I I I want I want
screenshot wait wait uh
up I forgot how to take
screenshots here a there we go can I Mis
can I take one alone too is that
okay is a photo
op there we go thank you
uh
uh that's perfect there you go wait no
no no no no why is the why is the menu
there I want to hide the
menu how do you hide the
menu why does it come
back is there a way to hide the
menu is that
L I should ah okay with the normal
camera uh wait but then then the stuff
is in front of me I guess you can't do
anything about that in in photo
mode oh that's very
[Music]
difficult it's a photo session
sat okay so wait but uh
okay do this and then h
nice okay bottom right you can hide
bottom right what do you mean ah it's
okay it's okay I I took a a nice photo
y I love how he's running around here
it's like so
[Music]
perfect what kind of RNG is
this amazing wow wow wow just wow I have
to say that that was perfect as the last
Island because this might have been my
favorite there were many amazing Islands
some of the the one that looked like
iabuk it was just not finished I feel
like that has more potential like even
that small part of the island was insane
but uh I guess in in in one year he
might be finished to show me even
more W Misa your Island amazing 10 out
of 10 best island I I've seen today oh
my
[Music]
God it felt like even though all islands
are the same size it felt much much
bigger than all the other islands for
some reason like he put so much stuff in
there but it didn't feel like cluttered
either I mean maybe in some spots but
that's
okay cuz sometimes having it look
cluttered is also a
look that was that was that was
inspiring
fascinating um clap clap Applause for
everyone who showed me their Island
today thank
you thank you for showing me your
islands and and and taking your time uh
sorry for the ones who didn't get in
today um there will be another chance
don't worry I'll do another stream like
this in the
future thank you beautiful islands
beautiful wow now if you guys don't
mind um I think
I
think let me see let me see let me see
let me
see okay I think we can do Super Chat
reading
quickly one second let me
prepare I don't I only have to read the
super chats from today's stream I think
so we should be
fine m
let me prepare it really quick that was
[Music]
amazing
wow everyone puts in like so much love
into their
islands and now I look at my Island and
it just looks like but I don't have
the time and the the motivation to put
in much more work so that's that
and all right there we
go thank you everyone
[Music]
H H everyone who needs to go to sleep
thank you for watching and see you soon
but now if you want to stay for a little
bit of a Super Chat reading you're
welcome to stay and I will now
look up the super
chats okay scrolling
down thank you for the stream no thank
you Shadows super oh oh I didn't read
Shadow super chats okay okay yeah that's
right yeah oh okay
Shadows stream that was yesterday H it
feels like two days ago for some
reason okay let me get out the
thumbnail Shadow
verse there we not that one that one
there we
go mythical Showdown and as we all know
I won five out of six matches
is that went very well I I I was very
confident to begin with but some of you
guys were like I don't know for some
reason you guys still doubted
me H some of you guys were like don't
get too cocky and all that and I I get I
get that I guess I shouldn't get too
cocky but I was I was very confident and
now we know that there was more than
enough
reason to be
cocky wait how do you save an animal
crossing got
it and I need to get out of the game ah
ready to wrap things up for now yeah
save and end okay there we
[Music]
go one thing I I kind of regret is that
we both didn't prepare like more proper
decks like I mean in the end she used my
deck but still like we should have
prepared more like different kind of
decks um because it it was very much
one-sided but I didn't expect us to need
that cuz I thought we would be fine I
thought it would be like more of a you
know proper
battle uh so I thought having one dag
each is fine also we we we we we it's
this a sponsored stream it was time
limited and and the deck preparation
stream was also 2 hours and you know I
just didn't didn't think that that would
be something that we would be necessary
now looking back I feel like we we could
have definitely had some more decks but
e
yeah yeah but I definitely had fun and I
I practiced and I tried to understand my
cards and even though you might not
think that way but I I really um always
like tried doing the right thing I
didn't just play C cards
randomly I was trying to think things
through and uh read my cards and
understand them and mostly I understood
them like I knew what my cards were
doing I KN I knew the basic game
mechanics and all that so it was
definitely a big improvement from like
the first Shadow V stream when you got
to keep in mind that we only had like
three three Shadow streams up until
now and we're still very much beginners
so I think Whoever has like like issues
with how we both played the game needs
to shut up
because also you got to consider that we
don't have that much free time we have
other things to prepare and I'm not
going to like for a sponsor stream or
any kind of stream I'm not going to
spend 10 hours outside of the streaming
time to practice for a stream to be
absolutely perfect and have no flaws I'm
not going to do that
because why why why I don't have the
time uh but I think I did well and I did
prepare I did uh practice like uh the
day of the stream I I I I wanted I know
I said I wanted to practice 6 hours but
I didn't have that much time so I
practiced like 2 hours 2 hours before
the stream and yeah yeah took took some
time to understand the game thank you
guys I think I did well
too I just don't understand there's
still some people who complained but um
I I personally feel like I did well and
I don't even I don't care
about any kind of criticism about that
stream I think we did uh perfectly fine
and it was
fun it was fun and I'm looking forward
to the
tournament yeah for that one we will
have actual coaches and I I don't know
if they're going to coach us before the
stream or during the stream or like
before the tournament or during the
tournament I honestly don't know how
it's going to work and what going to
happen but I'm just going to let it
happen
yeah I I wonder if for the tournament I
need to prepare maybe more decks or or
like if it's normal that in tournaments
you only use one deck I don't know what
is normal so I will have to ask them if
they want me to prepare more decks well
then I guess I will do that but I'm not
sure like what what to go
for but because like in order to really
really really know exactly what I'm
doing and which deck does what and all
that I would have to invest hours and
hours and hours and weeks into this game
I just don't have the time for that even
though it's a wonderful game and I'm
really enjoying it but I just don't have
the
time so I hope it's fine if I just play
with Haven craft and maybe one more
craft but that's about
it let me drink some more
water especially now that I'm moving
yeah and tomorrow
tomorrow tomorrow um uh we're picking up
my bed uh and and probably already on to
build it and then on Saturday we're
doing the big move but we now got like
six people and another friend start uh
uh said um that he would help so we have
a lot of people helping so it should go
smoothly
and uh yeah I don't have that much
Furniture in the beginning so Furniture
building shouldn't take too long got a
track van oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we
ordered uh I booked I booked a like a
van thingy for
Saturday and for tomorrow for the bed
the person who have to pick it up has a
big big big car for that one day
only yeah
and then I'm going to from s Saturday to
Sunday I'm going to even though I've
been I I will be done moving and have my
bed and all that I'll probably still
sleep uh in this apartment that I'm in
right now uh
because I I won't have internet over
there yet and I don't want to spend like
a whole day only with my phone and just
my empty fonts so from Saturday to
Sunday I'll still sleep over here and
keep my cats here as well and then from
Sunday to Monday I'll sleep in my
apartment in my new apartment and bring
my cats over as well on Sunday
[Music]
evening
good luck to your noodle armsel don't
worry I mostly don't have furniture most
of it is like just like cardboard boxes
yesterday room roommate John even helped
me build uh uh fill up some some
cardboard boxes very sweet very sweet
she helped me um without I didn't even
ask her she just started filling up my
cardboard
boxes she's so sweet
yeah and
uh we got we got um
people uh we got girls and boys helping
out with the move so the furniture the
the heavy Furniture like I don't know I
mean there's not much but my my chair I
guess and my uh cat tree and
my uh bookshelf those kind of things
things they can definitely help out with
and then you know those smaller boxes
I'm going to do my best to help as much
as
possible oh yeah my gamer table yeah
yeah I didn't unpack it yet it's it's
still in in the cardboard box so it
should be easy to
move but I'm I'm a bit nervous but it
should go well it's a very busy weekend
but it will go
well and on
Monday the reason why I'm sleeping on in
my new apartment from Sunday to Monday
is because on Monday in the early
morning someone from the internet
company should come by and then set up
my internet and the time window is very
big but it starts very early he he'll
probably not be there that early but I
have to be there that early just in case
he comes early so Monday morning I'll be
waiting for that dude and then I plan I
plan to stream Monday late evening my
time I plan to stream
Yakuza Monday late
evening so keep that in mind guys but I
will I will make a schedule for next
week we don't have one for this week but
I'll make one for next
week H the internet speed for my new
apartment will
be at least as good as the one I have
now you know cuz I recently two days ago
got a bit little little bit of a faster
internet and now I finally move in 60
FPS again I don't know if you have
noticed so it should be about
this please be there from 10: to 10 yeah
it was something like please be there
from 7 to 11: but I might not even make
it before 11s or whatever just be there
all the
time definitely looks smoother well I'm
I'm really glad to hear that smooth is
buto thank you thank
you move is
[Music]
grav hot butter
gravy is internet expensive in Australia
yeah it is like for what you get it's
way too
expensive you get like nothing it's
ridiculous but it's not only in
Australia it's in Europe just everywhere
in Europe it's so ridiculously expensive
for like zero speed
ridiculous makes me mad like a yeah it
is a ripoff but
like looking at it from a perspective
from other countries it looks like a
ripoff but here it's just normal so
before going to Japan I didn't even
realize that in in my country internet
is so bad and and expensive I needed
another country to compare
it uh in order to make that judgment but
now that I know how it is in other
countries I'm just like what the
how how have how do we not have
better choices and better
internet it's freaking
Europe oh
well 40 year- gets you one G gbps and up
and down that that that's good right
because I get what 15 m m
bits for okay my roommate pays like uh
for this new contract she pays like 30
uh Euro which is like uh $30 something
like that 30
45 for 15 M uh
upload which
is I mean here it's
normal but
15 for $30 per
month
M want
yeah that's trash why is that worse than
Ohio I don't know Europe has shitty
internet for the highest prices anyway
we should read super chats why did we
get go to this topic cuz I was talking
about my move yeah yep yep yep yep yep
okay so now that you guys know what's on
on my side I will not read the super
chats because tangents
yep ah Mr Cas
Z hope your week ain't to packed just
want to say thanks for giving us this
much content even though your week is a
bit chaotic thank you it is kind of
packed yeah but I'm trying to keep a
calm mind and take everything one by one
step by
step and Chris D cast stream heart
Challenger D hey boss can you tell
people to stream hard challenge or else
I'll beat them up also please lie and
talk about my strength s they fear me
thank
you guys heart Challenger is so close to
1 million views so please use the music
playlist to listen to my songs or make
your own
playlist I would really appre appreciate
it it's it's been really like Bamboozled
because of the Shadow bamboozle you know
that happened
previously so people don't get it in
their recommendations and
so it's been going really really
slow the past months it's been quite
frustrating
but
but but
[Music]
soon
I try my best
to like advertise it as much as possible
to you
guys and I know my kfb my loyal kfb
people who are always here and I know
you probably watch heart
challenger but yeah it's only like a
handful of people it feels
like I've been trying my best to spread
it but I I don't have all the power it's
only me like I'm the only one
advertising it
I'm the only one it's not like I get
like a advertising budget or anything
like
that or any any support from you know
cover it's just me doing my best
here I'll share it right now thank you
print
fers
have faith thank you I don't have faith
I gave up on
it I gave up and it's kind of
sad it will get there eventually but
then I'm like okay wow yeah eventually
everything is going to reach a certain
number of views but
like it's it's just it's just uh a bit
like like killing my motivation
I don't think it matters that it is a
seasonal song like it's not really that
seasonal as yeah it had Valentine's Day
as a theme but it's the theme is more
like about love and happy and all that
kind of stuff so I feel like you can
listen to that song at any time anyway
anyway anyway it will get there thank
you guys for all the support everyone
who keeps on like supporting me like
that also today and crafing as well for
the people who are like stream heart
Challenger that's so cute thank you so
much I really appreciate
that you guys are so
sweet thank
you looking for the top Danon Sky Dano
gbr
Danon chocolate dipped buffalo wing Dano
play t rock on guy
D yeah cuz the other day I mentioned
that I play played Turok when I was
younger and I have quite funed memories
of it from that back then but I I I
don't really think I would pick it up as
a stream
game Jeff the phoenixian oh D what does
he have to say holy
one we have heard your Mighty voice your
commands however the young ones still do
not believe as they have not experience
you glow what the how did they not
experience it I literally just like
build up a huge training Center in
Phoenix uh
phoenixon but do not worry oh Divine
bird we will make sure to reeducate them
so that they may know of the full might
of the Phoenix yeah just show them like
all the trainings what the hell show
them all the shops that we got going on
you can't miss it it's right in front of
your
eyes thank you Jeff I'm glad you are
such a loyal and respectful Phoenix
tonian I'm I'm I'm proud to have
you
Tai FL pudding
Mo Fenix s thank you for red Super
Chat we are all cheering for you no
matter what the outcome is it's a good
outcome because it's another ton stream
that's right thank
you yes yes I'm always happy to spend
time with CI whatever it is no matter if
it's a card game or if it's
K or if it's Minecraft doesn't matter
does not matter it's always time always
always fun to be with
her 79 T magic t
g KP sh R thank you for the
pinky good luck T remember your training
and the Heart of the cards know that
thank
you I generally think I I I had I I knew
what I was doing
generally I mean still yeah that might
have been some little mistakes but
everyone makes mistakes especially if
you're a
beginner thank you
Aon hey
Kito
but that's that's that's so far from my
name that I don't know if you know who
you are writing to I know I'm just
another a subscriber I will be gone for
3 years and I hope that both of you are
still here when I come back ah because
that was the collab I guess you wanted
to write Takami and not
kitoi Audrey
ckk 79
Patrick CH s 7332
d let me get one of
my throat
thingies they taste like gummy
bears what's popping goo
goofballs yeah who's
Kito dad already said K is your property
it's official I was about to ask when
but I guess you mean she did say
something like similar I
guess yeah what did she say she owns me
yeah in reality she owns me that's what
she said yeah
interesting
[Music]
I'm
her D Chris Harvey D Daisy Daisy thank
you for the red super chat let's fing go
yeah thank you for your support
Daisy I hope you were rooting for me
where are
you thank you in any case than for your
generous
[Music]
support hope you enjoyed the stream for
the most
part what do you mean for the most
part oh that's so cute you're getting a
rot wild puppy oh my
God will you do the honor of bestowing a
name onto her I mean it only
seems fitting since she'll probably be
guarding kfp against future creeper
attacks I promise to raise her to be
loyal to you and kfp that's so cute
thank you K dead beat thank you for the
r Super Chat I'm reading it now for some
reason
but a rot while a
puppy oh I I I might need to see like a
[Music]
picture maybe you can send me a a
picture on Twitter
and then I can maybe throw some ideas at
you I mean I know what what R rers look
like but like depending on the
color they might want to give a
different name and depending on the face
and all that definitely can't okay I'm
waiting for it that's so cute that
you're getting a
puppy see I was I I I mentioned before
that I kind of want like
another cat
but the other day my roommate told me
that a friend of her um got like um like
like lives at a like on the countryside
and got like kittens
okay and asked me if I would want one of
those kittens I would I couldn't get
them right away because they were just
born but like in a few weeks and um I
was thinking about it because I guess
that's perfect I kind of wanted to uh
adopt from a shelter but I guess from
the uh Bal hole what's that in English
again what's Bow and H again in
English a farm I guess we the farm they
also like need people to take their
kits but and at least they're like
kittens because I I wanted to get
kittens but in the shelter I when the
last time I checked I didn't have any
kittens M now one kittens because I feel
like then I at least least have some
chance to make my current cats accept
the new cat because if it's like an
older single cat then I feel like the
the chances of them accepting them is a
bit
lower even though I do want to help like
an older cat as well but but but but but
I think as a kitten it will be much
easier to like get them used to each
other and accept each
other so I got that offer and I was
thinking about it but I I I even though
I kind of want more and more cats my
current two cats are
so attached to
me that I feel like if I would get a new
cat they would be really really
jealous and kind of sad and I don't want
them to be
jealous I feel like definitely chunkers
would be jealous and sad I feel like
chunkers sometimes even now is kind of
jealous at smoothie as
[Music]
well so I'm not sure what to
do
[Music]
junkers junkers is spoiled yeah I mean
they're both super spoiled both of
them and like I've been giving them so
so so so much attention and even if I
for one second don't give them
attention they are really craving it
so if I give all that attention to a
kitten because a kitten needs a lot of
attention cuz the kitten keeps you busy
if I would give alled attention to a
kitten I feel like my cats would be very
jealous and that might not be very good
for their
relationship Eva and and my heart my
heart would
break so I don't know what to do maybe
it's too early I don't know I I'm I'm
I'm thinking about it but I also
personally feel like not even about my
cats but about myself I also feel like
it might be a bit too early to get a
third cat right now I I I'm not sure if
I'm mentally prepared ready for
that yeah could be territorial too yeah
who knows who knows they might they
might really not like
it yes it is a full-time job
yes no even after settling into my
apartment I don't know I'm not ready in
the next few months I
think my cats never cared about
newcomers
oh you got very very Toler tolerant
cats if you aren't ready then don't
force it yeah I agree with that I mean I
mean I would probably still be fine but
I just don't feel mentally
ready oh my God Cat
hello
hello what is
[Music]
it
movie you want attention huh huh I know
you do you heard the meow she's now on
my lap but she won't stay for
long my
baby cute she wants pets yes yes yes
yes if only she would just stay on my
lap I could I could give her endless
pets forever and
ever but oh no oh no so anyway continue
reading where did I stop a looking for
the top D Bean tiger D unknown d
a S7
b2ar hero fire D Love 67 thank you for
the
pinky apparently there's a chicken wing
shortage in the USA going on right now
for real so we're really valuable now
you'd never sell us to make a quick book
right book
no I would never you guys belong to
[Music]
me yeah you guys belong to me I'm not
telling you guys for real is that really
a thing though there's a chicken wing
shortage
really
never heard of it we love our wings so
much apparently apparently yes oh my God
prices are going up for chicken
wings all right interesting well then we
got to get everyone to go to
kfp
oh not we because we have vegan vegan
chicken
wings yeah it's it's a it's about the
same
thing it's it tastes like chicken wings
but it's not actual
chicken congrats on your Victory thank
you
than AAL memory
than I take back the good luck you
didn't need it at all
yeah although I was I was very nervous
uh and and and and I I feel like there
was some moments where um I was getting
really low in HP and I I needed to focus
but in the end Sanctuary Haven just
continuously heals you up again and
again there's really no need to worry
Trev g d Daisy D death crying baby D
Nick finson D zeronic 64 D Daisy D tyan
thank you for a red Super
Chat and so death was conquered by the
never-ending renewal of Life the light
of the Phoenix Shone through the
darkness of the underworld and led her
followers to New Life and Glory life has
found the way until the frer calls
congratulations on the on the win Viva
Lana thank
you very very well deserved I would say
CI won against me in many other
games in especially in the Clubhouse
games collab so I think I deserve to win
for once as well so don't take that away
from me that's my win and I'll keep it
it's my win
thank you
tyen evening up the score yeah
basically but it seems like
cie didn't like uh like losing or or or
not being like you know perfectly
professional player on that day because
she decided to play more Shadow verse
even outside of a sponsor stream well
cool does is that like her like
competitive side I
wonder cuz she is planning a shadow ver
stream for next week even though up
until now all Shadow ver streams were
were sponsored but she wants to practice
more and yeah she wants a rematch well
that's probably not happening un unless
we both get really far in the
tournament she got pretty salty see what
do you mean wait did you talk about it
in the
Stream speaking of I saw the clip of G
talking about my Sims 4 stream I was so
happy I didn't know that she was
watching I guess she watched the archive
or so
but the way she talked about my stream
saying is like the funniest content
she's
seen like in know in a long
time the funniest stream
that made me so
happy that was very
sweet I want to do more Sims 4 streams
especially because everyone liked the
last one so much but I don't want to do
it weekly I don't want to like overdo it
so I have to control myself and wait a
little
bit
[Music]
I couldn't brep just during the car the
creation yeah lot of you guys were
saying it was so funny you were laughing
so much you couldn't
breathe one per month I want to do a bit
more maybe maybe maybe I don't know we
will see how life goes in the next few
weeks next time is the yeah where is
still something we haven't done yeah
that's a good idea we need to do a
wedding stream a wedding special where
we
um yeah finally do the wedding ceremony
I feel like there might be
some scandalous things happening again
during the
wedding but after that I'm not sure what
to do I mean there's a lot of like
expansion packs that let you do funny
things like the one where we went to go
skiing and onand and all that
I wonder what else we could
do when colls I die
laughing yeah but all those things are
like partially like I just Sims doing s
Sims things it's just like quite a
normal thing for Sims to
[Music]
do create a whole town oh kind of
difficult yeah we need claraa to grow up
yeah
yeah IO 79
d uh K Shadow Mr KAS Denny SC S7
b42 and the big havencraft star allows T
to cheat death how can this be
congratulations on the Glorious Victory
T thank
you looking for the top D nothing but a
fan D thank you GD
d t RS D Kitty to D and saf kitten d
That's all the super chats for The
shadowe
Showdown and now we go on
to today's super
chats oh sorry I I I might like sound a
little bit less energy right now than
usual I feel a little bit a little bit
tired and my voice hurts my my throat
hurts a little bit
I've been having that a lot recently
interestingly thank you guys thank you
thank
you a by the way I don't have time for
whole talk next week it's not happening
next week
either next week is way too busy way too
much stuff going on so the the week
afterwards
it's probably going to be 15th or 16th
April uh yep yep yep yep yep I need more
time to prepare and I don't have time to
prepare next
week so just wait a little bit longer
and then we'll be back to normal to our
usual
schedule yep April
I mean May okay
may do you have a guest in mind I do I
do I
do okay looking for the
top Chris than sending Good Vibes for
your move don't worry for a second we
forget about you over a few days off you
could take a year off and I know at wait
in line for 300 a.m.
redut thank you thank you so
much I'll try to upload some some short
video on the weekend
hopefully at least something
something de love 67
dun Idol fan Cas big dun I I actually
answered to to your super chat during
the pre
chat and in a very detailed way so I
hope that was
okay
mute mute Anthony Anthony M
lunchbox Lord EV GD mute
soon
[Music]
apparently in Japan at unic CLA there a
collaboration with Animal Crossing going
on that's so cool I wish I could get
something I got a lot of like merch when
um Animal Crossing had a collaboration
with Japanese convenience
store uh they had like some gacha you
could like get some
tickets and then like lottery
tickets and then if you're lucky you get
some really cool stuff that's Animal
Crossing related and I got a few
things nothing too special I was way
luckier with other other Convenience St
gotas you're moving in 20 FPS yeah I I I
think I've noticed that too it went down
probably because it's prime time right
now
H
yeah it has sometimes where it's good
and where it's
bad
I jinxed it oops oopsy
oops Yeah last time we also had it like
uh lose lose frames around like 11:00
p.m. oh well oh well so you're the
Jersy
[Music]
for
60 FPS 20 FPS 2 FPS I saay for anything
thank
you thank you for two pinkies which
makes one red Super Chat
than pry CL get spended sorry but I
couldn't send a super chat yesterday oh
no problem no problem any anytime is
fine Taki Phoenix Part Time Warrior
comedian Tanto hot wings ggs Mama
transformed a card game into an epic
battle and 106 no no it's one six
five you got something wrong there oh
yeah you you corrected it later
on with a your cuteness a lot of it
concentration and willpower there wasn't
much the Grim Reaper first Apprentice
could do despite the stress uh with the
move you've managed in just one day or
night to learn the deck and be able to
play it perfectly you're amazing we love
you
T thank
you thank you thank you for like
noticing that thank you I appreciate
that
[Music]
shadow
for yeah yep
[Music]
so in German over back to
English thank you so much for your sweet
words thank you thank you for all your
support and your
generosity
thank
Daisy
pudding g s penguin thank you for the
red super
chat sorry t i was sleeping in last
Super Chat reading stream and I have a
dream I dreamed that you'll give me a
special High Honey the voice that make
me not hungry at morning I miss that
voice so much can you say
or with that voice make my breakfast
delicious you know what I'll gladly do
that if you would have asked for another
hi honey I'm going to I I was going to
ignore
you but
[Music]
okay I wish I could do a hard pose for
you I've been to some maid cafes in
Japan a long time ago I was really into
maides when I was
younger nowadays I don't care about M
cafes that much anymore because it's
just expensive and I don't know I don't
fall for their charms
anymore
you've grown too powerful for them
yeah dad must be it thank you penguin I
hope your breakfast will be super extra
yummy what are you eating for breakfast
I recommend French toast or waffles or
or pancakes very sweet breakfast but I
sometimes I like non-sweet breakfast as
well
water
I ran out of water again damn it let's
see if I can make it until the
end not I think that is a red super chat
I don't quite recognize the currency but
I think it is a red one thank you n nce
finally get to watch tanra live after a
long week's work loved your collab of
that yesterday Havey have you seen the
kisaki takamori animated video by haki
yes I've seen it I think I retweeted it
I think that Affiliated just love their
video thanks for always bringing a smile
to our faces
we thank you
too thank you for your support yeah I
love I love those kind of like fan-made
music videos that people make with us
even if it's like not a song from us but
like a some kind of anime song or so
H I really like those you should always
have water on hand yeah I need more
water I've been drinking so much water
and still and the the the the the cough
drop also is gone
already and it didn't really help much
and I'm getting a headache again why do
I always get a headache recently when I
read super chats that started recently
this week and only starts when I do the
Super Chat r
why screen headache but I've been
streaming like hours and hours and hours
and always been
fine not enough air that cannot be I
thought so yesterday but I I've had the
window open for a while
now
and I've been drinking a lot too but let
me let me grab some low water
okay beer
[Music]
be
that's a really good smug
face e
good
face okay okay okay we don't have that
much more to read so we'll be
fine I don't know what it is I want to
be like
100% like healthy and energetic and all
that but I don't know what it is
recently this week it's not even that
I'm like super super super busy like
constantly running from one thing to
another that's definitely not the case
but I don't know
maybe I mean today I definitely didn't
eat well I I ate
like waffles you know those chocolate
waffles with fruit that I've been eating
I've ate I've ate them today and besides
that I haven't eaten anything else so
and yesterday
my what I ate yesterday probably also
wasn't very super
healthy and
energizing
yeah and today's
dinner I don't really have anything
proper here right now so I should maybe
order
food maybe it's just not your week yeah
maybe maybe maybe I'll feel better once
I
move not enough vitamins I don't know
maybe let me cook for you oh I wish you
could don't skip your meals no no I'm
not skipping I usually always just eat
eat like breakfast and
dinner and maybe in between sometimes I
eat a
snack but today I also kind of got up
pretty late and then I ate breakfast and
then I recorded something and prepared
the stream and then here I am it's just
I wasn't even awake for that long before
the stream CU I was I was awake until f
a little bit a little bit after 500
a.m. uh cuz I was watching ing the
handmaid
tail the first three episodes of the new
season came out
guys yep and I've watched them all in
one
go it was uh devastating as
always very typical for the handmaid's
tail absolutely devastate is there
anyone else who watched it the the new
season only three episodes are out for
now you guys should watch it it it's
this is the fourth season if you you
haven't seen it and you're looking for
something to
watch I recommend it but it it you
up
mentally I've only read the book it's
awesome oh
yeah not seen the show yet you should
watch
it the handm mates ta give you a
headache yeah I didn't sleep that much
so maybe that's also one thing I mean
still more than
more than like it should be enough like
maybe 6 seven hours normally that should
be enough but
still I am just that type of person who
needs eight hours of
sleep at least better than before I I
used to need like 10 hours of sleep and
now I'm down to 8 hours the older I get
I guess the less sleep I
need
M that's a
thing blood
circulation oh Oh you mean I need to
move does this include the Naps no not
really I didn't take a nap
today
oh
now
tired thank you for red
super pel have fun visiting Islands I
don't have Animal Crossing so I feel
like I'm missing out
oh I mean I don't think you were missing
out just looking at those masterpieces
of islands I think was
already like nice to enough if you don't
have to play the game yourself you can
enjoy it through my streams m not only
Animal Crossing but all kinds of games
that I play I guess you don't have to
play them yourself you can just watch me
play it
h i love Teno thank you do some jumping
jacks I'm too lazy for
that bring
fit shut
up Felix thank you for your support and
every
time you've been so generous thank you
Felix I really really appreciate that
thanin for being such a big big big
supporter kfp and I appreciate you very
much all good love to
you T Daisy thank you for red Super Chat
another one from
Daisy I was I was going to make some
make the same dirty joke about being a
fat pink rooster now that I did in cie
stream but that would be improper in
public oh I just did a well six months
member woo don't worry I don't really
know what you're talking
about I don't really know what he's
talking
about
sty what are you what are you talking
[Music]
I don't quite
understand but it's okay it's probably
better for me to not
understand a hatched chicken doesn't
look pink though you guys are
[Music]
white
I want f is it too late to order f i
wonder let me finish the super chats we
should get it done before before 11 p.m.
my time there should still be some
things
open so yeah Daisy uh I'm confused but
thank you as always for your
support thank you from the bottom of my
heart love love love thank you Alberto
D Daisy D crispy D Emily D Fred e
Daisy
uh
wait uh your name I will try to read it
in
Chinese
I can't stop yawning Shen D sh thank you
and happy happy birthday to
you yay wait how do I say happy birthday
in Chinese
wait happy
birthday
sh
sh happy
birthday I hope you have a lovely fun
birthday please enjoy yourself and eat
lots of cake than thank you for your
support looking for the
top tap
Shane
46 Scarlet
singer Daisy pudding
Dominic magic Dominic
Domin thank you for supporting heart
Challenger than Dominic I appreciate
that so
much perfect example of a kfp employee
always streaming heart Challenger in the
background and
B Le
Jo
iron thank you you're treasure K thank
you sweet
iron
wow X
potato creeper Reaper iron T tapai
looking for the top t l collab win good
question we didn't have a you know that
New Year's stream official whole life
collab up where she was in and I was in
and some other girls were in that was
fun I want to I do want to do something
with Lamy Senai again maybe oneon-one or
maybe a three person
[Music]
collab D iron h d check Monkey D
all life Phantom has a ton of creativity
now would someone be willing to sell
some of the creativity to me no but
you're right they really
Doan SK
page Dylan di Dylan Johnson D and thank
you for the pinky I can't always catch
your streams because of my other job but
I appreciate you so much but thank you
I'm happy to hear that I hope you can
come to my stream whenever you have have
time I would be
happy this
look what are you doing
again than soon Tak destroyed next 60
and the shadow collab dat oh it was true
bullying Duma used the same type of deck
unit oh I feel like I saw that on my
Twitter timeline something like
that maybe
H
hum that sounds
fun I hope both of you downloaded the
game with my download
link
[Music]
next
chrisa oh I'm going to skip the flush
super chats scary fox jat than soon you
turned 20 yesterday oh happy late
birthday
L be
action oh yeah yeah I want to visit that
that ikuro Island again sometime to see
how he improves
it
for
[Music]
thank you Japan bro
for being in my
stream Jonathan Antonio
Sky Neil
[Music]
Neil I glad you've been enjoying my cat
pictur so far oh
yeah that they were really cute thank
you and
refreshing the
course there we go z p1234 m d Mr viewer
thank you for red Super Chat oh in
British
Pounds my British fans are
existing I'm glad to see that I don't
see many like pounds donations in
general so it makes me think like I
don't have many viewers in
England I wonder
why where am I where are my British
people do they just not like
vtubers hey we exist but not many of
you I'm a br view I'm just
broke okay I guess that's that's maybe
one thing maybe British people are just
broke
maybe they just don't show up in super
chats but they are
here maybe they're just
broke brexit was
[Music]
hard well Mr viewer let's let's read
your
message by the way kissy for
you since you're bottom left no offense
great
linguist what maybe you and could sing
Opposites Attract from Saints R 4 I've
never heard that
song never heard of it
before but I don't know we we do want to
do like a
takiab again probably whenever we will
be together at the same place again that
would be nice
yeah thank you thank you for supporting
takam
Mr The Grove coaster DLC is out yeah
have you guys seen it you guys play
Grove coaster I'll have a stream on it
sometime soon actually next week yeah
next week is my grp coaster
stream I want to check it out I'm not
good with rithm games since I don't have
any experience of
it but looking at how good I played it
it seemed simple
enough but again we talked about that
before she just makes it look simple but
I think that game is genuinely not as
hard as other r
games I'm not sure if it's available in
PC version okay well we we I don't know
we will have to figure out that there
there must be a way I mean
they they are uh sponsoring the stream
so there must be a way for me to play it
just relax playing it yeah I don't care
even if I up it's about listening
to the music and feeling the music okay
and vibing to the beat yeah yeah
yeah moose St thank you for red Super
Chat hello Teno just wanted to tell you
that you are so cute and I like your
stream so much love you Teno thank you
sh I'm happy to hear that I love you too
m
thank you for your support
moose thank you for your generous
donation and your lovely support thank
you very much keep on
supporting
CIS promotion to advertising team
permitt permitted to spread the good
word of streaming hard Challenger bu of
course I
mean why haven't you been doing it all
along here there you go why do you need
permission but okay there we go there
you go
[Music]
if you like GM games please check out G
Coaster kada song is in it and CI
song and I think some other H life songs
as well no I think wasn't there like
some H life songs in there as well
besides our new
ones I've had your heck playlist on Loop
for like a week thank you I love
you m is in it oh we're going to play
that one too there's our DLC Packs oh I
want them I need I need them to give
those to
me shiny SMY story oh I saw I saw good
out playing with
those and Dom kfb dead thank you for red
Super
Chat oh yeah I read that one already
thank you again F than that's the guy
that uh was the owner of the last Island
that we checked out M thank you for
taking time to come to my Island and
thank you for all the hard work you do
of course s you can live on my Island as
for rent Fame and the kfp way I'll give
you the rent
money you understand very well how the
system
works I appreciate that thank you I
respect you for the work you put into
that Island
damn n thank you for red Super Chat
N just here to tell you that you are
amazing hardw work potential not
everything you do will be an instant hit
but we do love heart Challenger also you
did amazing in Shadow verse you read
about the cards and knowing is half the
battle so go you you cute sexy
Phoenix thank
you thank you that so sweet I want to
give you hug thank
you thank
you I appreciate that was very kind I
mean I wish I wish everyone would
everything would be an instant hit but
yeah it it is it is how it is I'm going
to continue working hard so that um
everyone will enjoy my music more and
more
people and that people will recognize me
as a musician as well not only as the
bottom left chicken from H live
English who had shitty microphone and
lots of technical issues and cried a lot
in the beginning of her career I want
people to see me the way I really
am and part of that includes me wanting
to see that me wanting them to see me as
a musician as well so sing more I've
been doing my best
okay I'm organizing another song cover
collab right now as I am speaking as we
are speaking
[Music]
there only like I I can't put out a new
song every goddamn week since I I need I
I can't produce everything on my own I
need I need others to work with
me and there's also things like budget
you
know budget is also a
thing
so I follow you because I heard a clip
of you singing oh really thank
you
wow
Andrew you know what's
up thank you radio
Sound you're very inspiring to be honest
thank you darlly I freaking love you
boys thank you v v
[Music]
I came for the cute girl stay for the
wholesome lovable Phoenix thank
you thank you very much sorry sorry I've
been a bit like negative today maybe
it's not what I want to be but it's it's
reality
thank you motion thank you the satisy
thank you
bradle your Han rendition will always be
my
favorite singing Hani was a blast
yeah I wonder if I could get permission
to put out like a proper uh song cover
because that wasn't an unarchived stream
so not not everyone got to see
it I would love that to be like a proper
S cover
only later I found out that you're not
only a wonderful singer but a wonderful
person too plus I love the bottom left
part too thank
you be be going to listen to Heart
Challenger again that's the way to
go thank you very much your deod colover
was amazing thank you
than I always made time for your angelic
voice no matter how busy was I'll
freaking do it again thank
you than than sh you guys are so
sweet sing it again someday on arft K
well I mean there was a reason why it
was on unarchived K there's a reason for
it yeah but maybe you know maybe I can
get permission it's definitely easier
for the Japanese songs there's just like
a a certain list that I go
through um of sing songs and and k um
instrumentals that we have permission
for um but sometimes like sometimes even
things that are not on the
list Can Be Sung as well if you find the
right instrumental and get the rights to
it and all that but that is very
complicated so I would usually only go
through the list uh but the list has a
lot of songs that I have no interest in
anyway so there's not much choice I wish
I could do more archived Cala streams
but
[Music]
yeah okay so see I I I I I don't know
about that light I was thinking about
that because other people said that too
because my B cover the title was written
in Japanese but I mean I mean people
would be able to find it anyway if they
type it in romanji because I had it in
the tags and I had it in the description
and I don't think that people just
didn't click it because it had some
Japanese is
Ki like hi in the title I don't think
that makes people not click it but I
definitely had like the ragi version of
the title in the description on on
download but anyway I changed it now the
title is now in razi as
well
yeah they can search it easily of course
they can it's in my it was in my tags
and in the description so if you look up
Andi it would come up
anyway anyway it doesn't matter okay it
doesn't matter we uh I did everything I
can I I added some more tags and I
replied to comments to help with the
algorithm and all
that so that's yeah I can't I can't do
much more than what I did
now
yeah it's okay I mean in the end
for it's okay because it was in the end
it's a it's a birthday present for hook
Papa and like it's not meant to be like
super Banger that brings me millions of
views it was just supposed to be a
present and supposed to like show him
how much I appreciate
him
still even then it is just criminal
how how few people have watched it you
know generally I don't mind that much
but it's just still weird to
me
yeah oh
well if hook likes it that's what
matters exactly and he was very happy
with it so I'm happy
[Music]
too
uh okay I'm sick of this
discussion let's stop it motion D thank
you for the
pinking sorry to seem like I only super
chat about at here but I'm curious now
that the mysterious Trilogy got a deluxe
version before the rise of stream she
said s Sophie was your favorite is that
still true asking mostly because I'm
going to start Sophie after my
finals I'm not
sure maybe I don't even remember that
well anymore rise ahead taunted my
memory but I guess yeah maybe it was my
favorite could be perhaps
maybe well enjoy it I'm surprised you
didn't play it
yet enjoy it Sophie is uh the character
is an AA Sophie are really
cute like I mean they are in every
freaking a game there are so cute in
every AIA game
do you draw I sometimes do I used to do
much
more the book girl being
hot yeah PL it's hot how have
you not played oh my God motion motion
what is wrong with you how have you not
played a Sophie yet that's the game with
pla I just realized again cuz you
reminded me oh my God
what go play it now go
go I've been playing all the other ones
but you've missing out on one of the
most important
ones you call yourself an actually
fan
wow pla is so sexy I love her character
design
sorry sorry motion knows way more about
AIA games than I
do
P1 18 D Hi D how are you fine thank you
how are
you r d Alec D the African dog Dan
little late because I was in German
class before I didn't really have a
reason to learn the language when and I
was failing in class after watching you
I was motivated and I now have a passing
crate no nice
congratulations keep it up V Arctic
Sentry do you have a top 10 anime
opening
songs well not from the top of my head
but there would probably be a lot of
like FRP side
songs
and back monar songs in
it uh other than that uh ah
um the the dragon ma
opening and S no
method because that was also from
aana fana
[Music]
F besides that I can't really remember
now but there's probably many more other
good
ones uh
I I like the work
working openings a lot too they are very
energetic and
kanagi oh the kanagi
[Music]
opening crazy Shing
girl
unbelievable
[Music]
oh SK oh my God is of course sh
Gap
yes through
the I'm surprised like people like a lot
of comments
in a lot of the comments say like oh my
God I didn't know that her papa is uh
the same Papa the same artist for Stein
skate and black Ro shooter and I'm like
huh you've been watching me for this
long time and you still like didn't
realize that I mean yeah the style looks
a little bit different but I've been
it's it's written in my my Twitter
profile and I mention him a lot it's in
my debut and all that in my free deut
like it's not like it's not not like you
have to watch my debut from half a year
ago it's in a very in my recent debuts
as well all that
information
looks a little bit like Yuki from St get
zero that was your first
impression like I personally look
looking at hook Papa's previous works I
definitely see that he like used a
different kind of art style on me but
you you definitely see his like usual
style a bit more in the illustrations
that he did for hoton and for my debut
um
celebration there you can kind of see it
but just looking at me like that I guess
I wouldn't notice
[Music]
either you're so bright and colorful
it's a shock heing hooka are you okay
yeah but there's one Hint by the way
that makes it make makes you like
realize ah yeah yeah yeah yeah there's a
pattern there's one thing that I noticed
myself recently as well I didn't notice
up until now and I asked hooka Papa
about
it
there's one thing about my
design that I thought
maybe is a reference to Black Black Rock
Shooter my
hat white stars on black
fabric Black Rock Shooter is
also usually white stars on
black so I asked him if that's like on
purpose I asked him just like two days
ago cuz I just now
noticed and he said no it's not on
purpose but uh he he just uh he I he was
like oh I guess I I guess I have this
habit of like always drawing like white
stars on black something like yeah black
background it's like his thing like a
pattern that he keeps on
drawing literally it's it is a
pattern just some kind of pattern that
he really likes so he uses it a lot
subconsciously yeah yeah so somehow yeah
so I thought it was a reference but it's
not but it it is like yeah his trademark
yeah I guess
so
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah I mean it would have been
funny if I would have been happy if he
would have said yeah it is on purpose it
is a reference to Black o shooter that
would have been hype but it's
it's just uh by
coincidence I thought the skulls in your
eyes are a reference there are no skulls
in my
eyes
did you order F yet no I didn't oh
my God I'm done with Super Chat almost
wait wait wait wait uh
X looking for the top thank for two red
super chats but in honor of someone else
choose in honor of hokan and his
wholesome message from last stream best
of luck with the move and feel better
thank you kissy kissy for hook on I
guess and yeah the move thank you I will
need the luck I think it will go well
thankfully my friends are helping I'm
very very thankful that they take their
time to help me I appreciate that a lot
and I hope I will feel better soon maybe
it is the food yeah I'll need I I will
need to eat some more proper
food thank you for your support this
Laria I am glad you are here did you see
the islands or did you just come at the
very end
H if you missed the islands you should
check them out they were
awesome Dominic k
d
wait ah I forgot again how to read
that
wait what uh what was it again a
translate
Shen you're
welcome this
again sneaky
kiss oh yeah that one that one was by
the way in honor of green Wilder
Immortal lyrics oh yeah so good so
good also I saw the clips you guys made
thank you guys for clipping the
um the never going to eat you
up
thank
you thank you for the
effort I hope people will see
it shake my head nine why why why did I
wait was it
[Music]
wrong and wait where was I
here that's my favorite song of
yours oh two
harassment what some some people love
your dump truck some love your milk
trucks some even love your FES I am in
love with the way you say words that end
with
r Wait I don't know what you talking
about how give me an
example
weather
uh
War I say them normally don't
I whatever what
whatever
uh whatever whatever but I say
normally y'all need the Lord
I can kind of see
it where where
where
huh you pronounce the words of a heart
ER R and it's Ador heart
are your accent is scute I don't have an
accent shut
[Music]
up P BR 121 new follow thank
youis bu you say thank you
missis Daisy car Morales thank you for
the pinky hey D I wanted to thank you
for always speaking some Japanese into
your stream it helps me practice the
language and makes me super happy when I
understand what you're saying love your
work GL to thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you for your support I'm
glad you're enjoying
it today I saw a lot of Japanese viewers
in the chat so I felt like speaking a
little bit more
I hope it didn't bother anyone there we
go again I said something with an r at
the end but
butter that's a really difficult word Bo
bother bother B bother th is really um a
bit difficult to pronounce for
me B
bother B
bother Bob bobber bob bob bob the b
b oh shut up about
smoothie I say smoothie is just
fine it's th smoothie is written th H
okay not V it's not
V It's s m o o t h i
e GD thank you for the red super chat M
hi K how are you and the cuties here s
for your song production fun thank you
we've been doing very well chunkers has
been actually both of them have been uh
losing the fur a lot they they fur a
lot and
um okay now that you guys said that
thing about the r i really noticed it
myself that it's hard for me to
pronounce anything anything at all in
English language
Dage uh I've been saying yeah they've
been losing so much fur that like if you
if you take your uh like big Thum and
your the the the long the long finger
down you take those and you you pull out
hair a little little bit softly just
softly you get like a a lot of soft like
under undercoat hair fur from the cats
like you pull and you get like already a
big big chunk of
hair
from them so yeah that that's the
current state of shedding that they are
in right now it's really bad yeah it's
shedding season I touched them once and
I have ton of hair on my
[Music]
hand
is there a lot of hair in the uh well no
not not generally unless I I I I I pet
them and then I you know whirling
[Music]
around okay uh let's finish this
oh yeah here's some for your s
production fun thank you
GD love you thank you for all the
support mate I'm surprised you're
actually here did you just wake up thank
you for coming to this unhuman
times even in fake Australia for coming
even to during these times thank
you than soon
Dominic thank you you want me to up Ty
and D miss that clean D hey Mommy you're
so sexy and beautiful I must worship
after Jesus of
course and thank him for such a
wonderful mama and wife I tirelessly
work for and AD door love you so much
God bless
you okay M Mario eight than soon r d
than thank you for the
pinky I would be stok with this hack for
the working openings in the K sometime
yeah yeah yeah it's one of my favorite
anime and the songs match your fun
energy also here's some food funds for
you boss please take thank you okay okay
oh my God it's 11:00 p.m. okay okay we
did it we did it I think uh but wait
there one one more came in from
GD
yeah another pinky you deserve a kiss
now for the Roomba since the cutest are
shedding thank you never people really
want me to buy a Roomba
what is all this Roomba funding by now I
can probably buy five roombas actually I
don't know how much roombas cost
but oh saona the professional
lesbian thank you for the pinky Hi D
you're really glad I managed to cat to
the end of the stream after work your
energy is contagious my cat is trying to
Bonk you for the screen watch out that's
so cute hey Cat hey wow
wow
wow wow
let me speak to your
cat
[Music]
saction atypical I didn't watch atypical
yet I know it's really
[Music]
popular the great is
dke
you're confusing my cat
nice oh my cat CH hello I I summoned my
own
cat oh she answered me hello oh both of
them
came
oh
[Music]
good oh
baby
a black Frank
D GG
d
I need to cud my
cat no not that face okay fix fix that
face
okay okay okay I'll go C my cats now
thank you everyone for your
support and your
patience
hi tomorrow stream
planned at maybe 8:00 p.m. or something
like that I don't know uh I will have to
see how long the the whole bed thing
takes I'll see you guys tomorrow
hopefully because on the weekend I'm not
streaming so you better come tomorrow
okay please I'm counting on
you okay um like if I would do like a
short St stream like Mario Kart sliver
among us anything like that what what
would you want to
[Music]
see can be also something I didn't
mention just
now a d thank
you Mario Kart a lot of Mario Kart a lot
of a still but more more more Mario Cart
you guys know I suck right
H Mario
Kart Among Us is also
popular Mona no I'm not in the
mood I don't know it didn't it
didn't it didn't I don't feel it I don't
feel
itus
[Music]
oh okay I'll see I'll see tomorrow out
I'll decide
spontaneously EG egg the egg the egg
game a good idea too good idea cuz I
want some change as well I don't always
want to play the same short stream
games okay I'll think about it I'll
decide
spontaneously yeah we need to revisit
the egg
game all right
a
[Music]
you I'll see you guys tomorrow oh yeah
Fall Guys yeah but fall guys I would
love to play fall guys but it triggers
me so hard when people like always annoy
me and I like than
soon you
remember okay I'll leave now byebye guys
thank you for watching watching today I
love you thank you thank you for
participating and yeah staying here and
talking to me as always and supporting
me and please watch hard Challenger on
YouTube and also on your streaming
devices like Spotify or whatever H thank
you and in German we
say not aost V in and not Al
get it right it's Al
V good
night
[Music]
bye-bye a