food we're coming through
Canada
don't be an idiot what do you mean don't
mean I was born like this
so German you guys
we need a [\h__\h] counter
whoa sick
I think the white one oh oh sorry oh
sorry oh sorry oh sorry oh sorry oh
that's good
I hope I don't have to pay for the
repairs wait for me go away go
that sick turns
out
can I do it again
okay baby she's watching anime I was on
the phone boy don't be listening
sorry Mommy you're good hold me
which is why I am very honored to
announce to you bonus bonus
wow why would you shoot so soon
headshot I don't know who's my friend or
headshot whoa
what what you must let me in no who's
living here Jimmy
Jimmy oh it's so mean come here out of
the window jump into my arms and I'll
rescue you princess
this is so dangerous I
over pictures of my friends oh my God
unbelievable
what a sick bastard great
great at least
[Laughter]
oh I see what you're doing
all right now calm down get yourself a
room bye
car ah
look at my back seat
pushed against your skull
chat you told me a little bit too
[\h__\h] late all right merry Christmas
[Music]
okay World changed
tooth fairy coming tonight but yeah
not gonna leave a single tooth nah gonna
need your grandma's teeth next
yes he's just like me we both still use
wired headphones but at that time he
probably didn't have much choice
[Music]
stop oh wait
you
are you doing
there there it is that's my fault I only
saw a truck boats
what I just arrived [\h__\h] oh my heart
oh it's on the track I thought it was
normally a boat should be on the water
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
someone in my home is it a tennis
instructor
yeah yeah yeah yeah I know exactly the
cars already gave it away you don't have
to look at those
Amanda
not in my house
150 bucks an hour to [\h__\h] my wife in my
own bed Michael go away oh I'm sorry bro
she said you hadn't arranged dude
[Music]
bastard gonna [\h__\h] kill him hey [\h__\h]
it I'm in let's roll let's get this
[\h__\h] yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
yes we will kill him
shuts the door like that's like a
[\h__\h] teenager all right let's go to
my house take my money
okay we're doing it this way
let's see what happens
oh that's not real estate
[Music]
oh hello oh
you know who I am no no you don't know
who I am no idea who am I no idea I
think Martin madrazo I guess Mr madrazo
is a legitimate businessman got a
question oh yes I can answer everything
did you pull an architecture significant
murderous Wonder homes
looks like I'm gonna have to postpone my
retirement
it's Rob somewhere back
look I only know one way to make money
I'm gonna have to give an old friend a
call
you gonna let me in or what give me a
minute
ah before then Duty takes down dog
okay hello what what a [\h__\h] mess
I was wondering when you'd show up damn
boy you live like this praise be so
you're back in the game
I guess how's it going Dogo you found
something now
oh you're gonna get demoted if you don't
find me the dude no no I'm not gonna
play ball with you suddenly did you find
him oh he finally stop stop
[Music]
filthy [\h__\h]
I mean we don't we really don't want to
see that but can you stop oh no
[Music]
choppy go to chop pull him off oh man oh
my God this is for real I could easily
do that without the dog
let's get a dog [\h__\h] you and your stupid
dog why don't I just use my guns
I'll be faster yeah okay finally