do
[Music]
hmm
music
hi guys hi hi hey
sorry i'm ready for the delay but we
made it we did not leave inna behind we
could not go back thank you
yeah yeah
never never never look at us beautiful
cute girls together on a disney date
today except on gooda's screen
apparently mummy is
not so cute
nana steve what happened that's me did
you not shave your beard
listen it's been a long week for me
to like
mention all this
disney stuff it sounds like we shouldn't
be saying it's very uh no no
we may talk about it i'm i'm sure it's
fine um everybody else
has headphones for the best experience
well well today we are visiting the
magic kingdom with the following members
from halloween
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
before the stream outed herself as a big
nerd so she will be our tour guide today
i am the park tour guide because i know
much too much about the disney world
park that i should but i do what do you
know this is my you know wire thing
i know that this is pretty accurate i
can tell you that the monorails are to
the left the boat transportation is
straight ahead behind us and then to the
the other left is the bus transportation
park properties and hotels and then over
here is where you get your tickets and
your your hats and then they actually
check your id
and stuff like that and then this is
like this is concessions here you can
get a bunch of stuff that might be a
little expensive and then inside you get
strollers which is what i'll do
i see okay so you don't know where the
bathroom is would you like to tell us
which disney
world land this is modeled after which
place which country this is this is
disney world from florida usa orlando
baby oh florida i've never been to where
the crocodiles are
right yeah yeah
who here has been to disneyland and
which one and how often moment you start
i went once when i was smaller small i
don't remember much i just remember the
one with the boat like the steamboat and
it scared me oh steamboats
yeah the animatronics scared me or that
you know the guy fishing there's a guy
fishing it's terrifying terrifying
fishing guys understandable
what about inya
sorry my uh stream is having a little
troubles but um
oh you haven't been to disney world but
i've been to disneyland
disney disneyland and
manchester united
california california oh yeah oh
i went several times in japan to disney
sea and disneyland although i preferred
disneysea
and i went to the one in paris two times
but i never went to the one in america
so this will be like the first time i
see the og the orange is this the og
right
no this is not the og but it is the
superior park um this is the mirror one
okay how is it superior
it's bigger it's more updated but most
importantly it's bigger oh
oh nice okay i'm excited it's good
essential then
oh wait um
genma the bgm that is playing on my
stream i knew you would be worried this
is from audio stock this is i know it
sounds like this
but it
is mine
okay nice okay
so shall we
get going
let's go
lead us yes yes do you have a problem
oh [\h__\h]
yeah stream's a little little scuffed
right now um
this is bedrock edition so bedrock might
be a bit
ah
bedrock kfp is it fine on my side and
you know your curse is
and then the monorail will take you to
the
ticket ticket station i think it's
called the transportation and the ticket
center for those of you that uh
don't stay in the parks
and then and then i can actually tell
you the monorail the monorail track i
know it goes okay if you go on it goes
to the contemporary resort next to the
bay lake tower which is the disney
vacation club members only hotel
and then it goes
wait
i might be missing one but then i
believe it goes to the grand floridian
resort and spa uh with the wedding
pavilion as well there's some people
giving them another
and then it goes to the disney
polynesian resort which is like hawaii
and stuff like that i think i might be
missing one and then he goes to the
transportation and ticket center with
continuing service to
disney's holly oh god hollywood studios
i think
sorry epcot it's been a while oh
okay well goodnight it's like you you
used to have like a part-time job as a
tour guide in disney world is that so
actually the monorail the disney world
monorail system has uh has the police
you know please stay seated and stuff
like that i used to have the spanish
monologue memorized but i no longer have
the spanish monologue memorized but
i can't
[Laughter]
you're so informative
do i have to pay for you being here with
us
no it's okay i'm sorry
no no no no please continue this is good
because like uh it will be it will be an
informative stream like yeah uh-huh
isn't there they used to sell the they
used to sell the the spanish monologue
on t-shirts as well so i'm not that
crazy it was like a fan favorite to hear
i don't know why but it was and they
sold it
yeah they had the text
yeah yeah like uh
right
yeah but it's just for the
transportation thing also buzzing is the
best ac
okay oh there's food here we get to eat
the food in the park as well i remember
reading this uh we can eat the dole whip
and kara was like what's it what does it
do
okay sorry for the race i think i might
just not stream today uh i'm really
really sorry yeah i can't fix that yeah
i'm sorry no you're so cursed today i'm
sorry i mean i can try one last thing
but um
i'm so sorry no problem
guna will entertain us with everything
she knows
so a dollar whip which apparently you
can get in the game a dole whip is uh
it's like an ice cream swirl it has
vanilla ice cream and then orange like
sorbet sherbert or you can get like
pineapple or something like that i don't
know it's one of those like cult classic
disney snacks but quite honestly i can't
stand the taste of it i'm more of a
churro person or perhaps
or perhaps a mickey a mickey ice cream
bar because it's the perfect temperature
and it's like cold enough to bite into
and it doesn't really melt maybe it's
chemicals i don't know i like to believe
it's the taste of magic in my mouth
what's the while at the walt disney
world
what's the cow lip thing that you
mentioned before oh what something like
maybe you mentioned some
dull whip don't call it double lip
adult i don't even know what's that ice
cream one it's the orangey swirl it's
like cream soup yeah you can get a
pineapple too yeah okay okay
now you remember how much it cost
probably like eight bucks six to eight
rice cream i think so yeah well it is
disney it is disneyland they also have
an egg roll cart
it grows like cheeseburger egg rolls
yeah okay
my stream we can go
sorry about that okay and oh by the way
we can get autographs in this book look
this is fascinating meet your favorite
disney characters around the park i
wonder if we'll actually find some and
then we have the map here that we can
always look at but we don't need a map
because we have glitter
yeah
i'm the map i'm
[Music]
feel free you're welcome everywhere
take a seat and enjoy the show good
where did we go actually where do you
always go first
uh i usually start i go to tomorrowland
and i work my way around that way
because i like riding the people mover
because it's like it's essentially just
it's actually really cool hold on
the people mover
the people mover usually there's a
really long line but it's really easy
on an escalator up and you sit in this
like it's just like an automated it goes
on like a track all the time and it goes
actually through other rides in the
tomorrowland section like there's a
stitch ride and then there's the space
mountain which is one of the three
classic mountain rides and you actually
go like underneath people while they're
riding the ride and it just spins you
around a little bit it's pretty chill
it's really nice you can't eat on it
though but i really wish you could
okay
okay girl script or something
no i just know too much about this i i
feel like i really uh did the right
choice like actually um i i was the one
who thought of uh doing this collab and
i was like okay who did i invite and
first i thought of inna because we had a
little bit of a milky mouse arc in
minecraft before and then i was like
yeah who else likes disney and i just
assumed gooda is the type to like disney
so i invited good for me yeah i also
assumed you maybe like disney so i guess
it was correct
and then at some point yes yes
surprise hey i expected everyone to like
disney if the gouda has so much
information about yeah theme park yeah
i'm so surprised
why there's a top left
icon
is it showing it for you guys too
and enter the world of yesterday
tomorrow and fancy let's get it
let me
wait why do people get strollers do we
have a baby
i've never seen some people they
travelers
oh they have a wheelchair is this who i
think it is
but it's like be
[Music]
i
okay
i think should i turn off sound blocks
no just in case i will turn everything
[Music]
wait where is ghoula where's our tour
guide come on
we need you to be kind
[Music]
we're dying
i'm hungry i've been running around
[Music]
the characters
yo actually i never see in japanese
in japanese
i've never even seen one of these
characters before only in
paris
maybe they don't wait you have you guys
have sound effects turned off yeah i
think i have everything turned off now
where is you go in the slider okay
thumbs down
again
yeah
um only
knowledge that i could flex that cuda
probably doesn't have um is that
apparently okay so this this part may be
good on those apparently every park
disney park over the world has like
their own like character that they use
as a mascot and for paris it's tinker
bell did you know that gordon
what
what parents
paris disneyland their their mascot is
tinkerbell
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know apparently every party has
one
is it mickey mouse gun
uh
are you an imagineer
is
you buy spaghetti here actually that's
really
mediocre spaghetti dinner
the guy has forget these
[Music]
oh sorry guys my game is germany
everyone takes some good food
oh
[Music]
in american disney world actually run
around with pickles in their hand
yeah you can buy pickles then yeah
they're next to the college people you
don't eat them that's the parade yeah
next to like the iced beverages the
powerade and the designees the pickles
pickles in a bag
[Laughter]
i mean i like pickles but i wouldn't
just eat them as a snack like that in
disneyland what the hell
okay must be an american
oh wow
there's like a band that plays
there's a band that plays and comes
around here trash can it looks nice this
is a fire station
even though i don't know if it really is
a fire station can i go merchandise i
don't think you can go in but this is a
merchant oh no it's going here
merchandise merge go get the merch
[Music]
i wear it yes you can i can wear it oh
so cute
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god oh my god
steve looks better
plushie can
[Music]
so cute girl
what the [\h__\h]
wait how do you put on the backpack
[Music]
there's a bag oh that's so cute
oh mommy that's why it looks so cute on
you
oh
okay
how do we take
how does one take screenshots in bedrock
is this
what was it i don't know
wasn't it
[Music]
please take a cute
shot of us please thank you
[Music]
fall into any traps like that closes my
game
yeah bedrock i don't know how about that
yeah okay follow up
candy that's a candy this is a candy
this is the main street confectioner oh
rumor has it that they actually pump
smells into the park and i believe this
is the culprit really smells delicious
in the other shop
backpacks if someone still wants one
oh
this one and this one where i am there's
still backpacks like two backpacks and
sweaters and stuff
let me see
well
oh oh
oh
oh there's another person there's a
sweater
oh
minnie mouse
minnie mouse backpack
i'm gonna eat
oh
[Music]
balloon
the balloons look crazy they look so
stiff
they look like uh they look like
lollipops yeah like huge lollipops oh
i want to lick it
this is fun i love this this is almost
almost as if we are actually in disney
world almost so close
oh wait there's somebody else over here
do you have more stuff
in vr because then it would be even more
immersive
you can really bedrock minecraft and vr
i'm not sure if yeah
i'm not sure if it's bedrock but
there's more stuff here ah this is the
same stuff that we have
[Music]
blue
of
[Music]
those are so
cute and then we have
ina who is mickey mouse cat looks like
she's german secretly
[Music]
he is
hello
ah this is exciting
okay okay what do we do next we have we
are dressed up we are absolutely styling
we're ready being in fashion i like the
color coordination for good as well with
the blue oh yeah
[Laughter]
what is everybody's favorite uh disney
character
oh good question
good question yeah um there's a
starbucks in here somewhere i'm not sure
i even have one who are these people go
out
there
yeah they're just dancing yeah
[Music]
probably singing about how cute we
what do you think that means
it means
we're going to replace them
oh we're going to consume their flesh i
shall be orange i am orange this is
where you get a chili dog
[Music]
where's it
okay you can never find cedar ever you
have to put on a leash in disneyland
[Music]
and this is the ice cream palette
okay either this is the chili dog and
this is the ice cream and this is the
ice cream and this is good chili dogs
i found there come get your leash
oh no
you can get i've actually never eaten
there but there's noodles over there but
you are out of control that's the
crystal palace that is disney character
dining spot buffet i've never eaten
there but i've always wanted to i think
it's really hard to get seating
wow
why it's lit up right now are there
gonna be fireworks can we activate them
i
wonder it's pretty challenging wow it's
huge
[Music]
huge man really wowie this is actually
accurate because i recently updated the
park to have this additional walkway and
stuff here
[Music]
there might be characters in there is it
like not possible
[Music]
moving forward
oh my god my eyes hurt my brain hurts oh
no
i'm in the twilight zone
how do i stop oh
oh god oh god
i can't push you
yeah there's no friendly fire
we're getting close to the egg roll cart
i can smell it
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
even if i haven't even gotten to the
right yet
all right i'm on a rock
one time i was standing here and i saw a
bullfrog swallow an entire french fries
entire fridge for like an american
french pie like the pulsar like you know
that one bit ooh eventually you know
that one big french fry you get yeah it
swallowed that one what happened
if i leave the
world i think we get kicked out
we don't want that to win
i think you should though you're stuck
there can't you yeah we'll try yeah save
and end and then let's see
maybe hide your screen just in case
hiding you're good to go now okay hold
on guys we're gonna yep disconnected oh
[\h__\h]
okay wait i'll go in
again uh
hold on guys we're reset in the world
there's a teleport
i'll go the bathroom
where the bathroom
in the room the real bathroom
oh yeah wait never mind i'll be right
back okay okay
maybe you give me a bathroom
okay oh i'm in the water okay try to
join the world again
okay because my apartment is fixed
or i'll also send you an invite
okay
we got our cosmetics no
yeah i still have them you know i still
have okay
nothing is lost it's all good nice
sorry for the trouble
that's okay
okay
[Music]
is a ride is it crystal palace buffet
with character is food
it's food
with character who are these characters
does that mean there's any characters in
here
apparently you can click on the map to
teleport so if you get stuck again you
can maybe
ah you can tell along click on the map
yeah there's more food here guys
[Music]
take some food
is the first day this might be the first
aid or where they put the babies i don't
really know
you know like the babies that they don't
want to deal with
the babies
also you run by double pressing w i just
learned
i'm just using ctrl
okay hello
yellow is back
okay
[Music]
tomorrowland we go on space mountain oh
okay
nothing
[Music]
i think we should go to tomorrowland
first
okay yeah
this way where is
[Music]
everybody hold hands
okay
[Music]
when i bounce the ears bounce do you see
that on your side
yes i do i think i do what they do
also these are the bathrooms in the park
i don't know if that's important but i'm
just going to say the noodle terrace
there's also a fireworks show here but a
little bit expensive to get it you
see this is where they sell the food if
i get annoying tell me to shut up the
weekend no no no you're the perfect
perfect tour guide
food
chili cheese dog there's so much food
places in there yeah
makes me really hungry
[Music]
you're so pretty
they also used to have a garbage can
that talked to you
what
yeah i would like move around that's so
high moves
oh
i found characters oh does tomorrowland
have an attraction
oh my god
[Music]
that wazowski
is it mike mussowski or my close-ups
[Music]
is this not licensed
oh my gosh
what
the silence
what put his hand on his hip i'm so
scared wait even the dummy it says mike
w in here but then his name is
glidzowski or right there
what but his signature has a w for
wazowski
yes
who are you little green man
oh he's so cute oh he's doing your front
dancing
[Music]
oh you should take off here take off
your fake costume you fraud
wait what's your name
ah
beans bean
is it actually silly let me see yourself
oh
it's like four girls bullying the fluffy
boy
[Music]
mike actually mike doesn't have well
he'd just be skinned right he has no
skin he doesn't have scales or hair or
anything well we just poke poke his eye
poke i poke you no
skin
like a lizard
[Music]
okay is that an attraction that looks
fancy
this is the thing on the space thing
that flings you around there's actually
a ride to the right
we've got one
oh
[Music]
he's really short yeah he's tiny not
stitched that stitch is uh kind of it's
just a belly why is stitched so big and
it was like you said this belly
it does have a belly
[Music]
buzz
it's so tiny yeah is he small he's a boy
oh i guess he's supposed to be a toy i
guess he doesn't like harry's little
shorty shorts
face
i can't wait for the new movie coming
out it looks so good oh yeah oh yeah
yeah yeah
right here
what's next
can we ride the ride we want to ride
yeah
[Music]
in paris and i was really good at it the
waiting room looks like it too
oh
[Music]
is this one but you're in the way yeah i
hear someone gotta wait what are we
showing here
i'll
[Music]
now we have to wait
yeah this is the waiting line oh don't
wait
a pickle
[Music]
oh my goodness you are so far ahead of
me yes
um
actually secret places to shoot i wonder
if they still work in the game
i mean yeah
yeah i used to i used to look them up
before i rode the rides
i don't think so i
get on to my level you can't be a
holobub look at his nose looks like a
boy
i don't know
i think it's ending
[Music]
where it's like even when you move it
looks like it's looking good
nice this is lifeless lifeless
one color pixel eyes yeah yeah
this is fun
you know waiting right now or what's
happening now we're waiting
[Music]
good at doing waiting times you must
have some extra techniques or something
yeah
i pull out my phone okay
phone time i see
oh yeah
that's like really the worst time is the
waiting time for me i hate it
i like looking at restaurant menus while
i wait and also other wait times i point
and laughter
the longer wait time
it's the end yeah we're in space without
the real space
shoot the space there's stuff what's
going on that's
[Music]
how many rides do you ride in the one
day
good question uh oh it's still
continuing
time don't know how many times you can
get on
if it's a ride if it's like if i go with
my family and it's like
i like to do the single rider line lanes
for like better rides like test track
the one that goes really fast
because then you get to go through
really really really quickly and i'll
just stick you with a random group of
people getting a really far one
i guess that is one strap to get more
rides
yeah
yeah i mean you always sit next to
strangers
over a couple minutes
i think it's ending for real oh yeah oh
it's ending
that is on the right yeah the points are
um
114k on my side and 55k on mumei so i
have like double
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
oh my god it's accurate is it
how do you oh sort of
it's like
but the last part they didn't have in
paris the alien shooty part
oh my god it's kind of accurate
how do you shoot
right click right button i mean let's
click left click right click for me
right click right left for me
maybe that's one of your points where
it's a low movement
was it supposed to be left but for me
was right click
maybe both
wait none of that is worth it
yeah that's because in the beginning
there is nothing to shoot yet you think
it starts but there's nothing to shoot
yet but there is already got 62 000
points
[Music]
i can't shoot anything
this is accurate
not really no
i felt like it was kind of to the
i don't know yeah
[Music]
i'm going on the rocket
okay
there's a flying thingy that you can go
go on top and now you can shoot this but
i guess it doesn't want to look astral
orbiter
yes yes yes can you take the oh it
doesn't move your head
i told
[Music]
i think i don't know
who's this
oh my gosh
maybe this is two people only as well
oh wow
let's write this yeah
[Music]
oh no i'm gonna get so much in soda
guy comes how did they do this in
minecraft this is crazy yeah oh we got
this one
so well little right
now
oh wait can we go up yeah can we control
oops
i know right this is crazy minecraft
here we're in purple we're so lonely
i'm so lost
right
first person
nice doesn't actually do anything i'm
gonna get real points oh what are you
supposed to do i'm not sure just hang on
chilling oh i think i did go higher
wait what did you do i just um that's it
i i pressed
oh what are you shooting let's wait for
the other girls i guess
yeah let's go down come on
bye-bye
you almost have a million
are they
call me girl
oh i can't quite get a million that's so
sad
you almost had a million
[Music]
eno oh okay so it's good
[Laughter]
yeah
i realized
that the targets like far away at the
top they give you a [\h__\h] ton of points i
realized that they saved like 50 000.
yeah yeah
i was trying to play once again i
thought you're supposed to spam it
oh here they are
where are you guys hello
hello this is the carousel progress that
has a lot of history behind it we just
went on the
space orbiter do you guys want to go too
yeah yeah yeah is it all right
here can i take an elevator i don't
think i can go on it i'll close my eyes
i'll close my eyes you feel sick because
of it
yeah
elevator and lift
oh here we are
let's see how many how many can we do
get in get in here everybody get another
robot girls
[Music]
wow
all together
look if you look up and down to control
your rocket oh
it's just looking
looking
oh boy
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
is
it's amazing what's possible in
minecraft but i mean yeah obviously a
lot of work is behind this honestly
really impressed yeah
i mean this disney half the world that
we're talking about
din
suny wow
wow the sky is so beautiful yeah this
does
is there fireworks
we will see it should be eventually
there must be and uh but there won't be
a parade will there oh i don't think
probably no curry i don't know but
fireworks is manageable
[Music]
i made it
okay how do you eat this again
[Music]
okay
what's next gura what's next
[Music]
oh and you want to use bathroom i do get
a bathroom
[Music]
i want to turn on sound effects really
bad please
dark
[Music]
before even in real life because that
was too much of a chicken but this is
pretty cool already in the waiting room
oh cool look space mountain is just kind
of old yes but i think that adds to the
thrill of it because you're like is this
oh
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
that is so cool we're going up
oh there's even like roller coaster like
sound effects they're upside down don't
hear any should i turn them on
uh there's no music but i wouldn't i
don't know there's no music the creator
mode turned off the music the
copyrighted music
they're just rollercoasters nouns oh no
it's dark it's completely dark i'm
scared
[Applause]
i don't know anymore
[Music]
exactly we're just traveling real fast
wait how did i end up in the back oh
yeah
now
whoa
i wonder how they did all this it's so
cool
is she barfing
i think i think she's barfing
are you on the right kara
no
i think she's what goes out or i was on
the ride before everybody else and then
everybody jumped in and i got kicked out
which is so ironic because a few days
ago on my stream i was like i knew this
was gonna happen so i was like i'm gonna
definitely be in there first because i
know it's gonna hap happening and i
won't be the one getting kicked out but
here we go
are you done already
yeah we're done
i i tried going on the other one but i
don't know i i do i go into it but it
won't let me
move maybe now that you're done maybe i
can try the other one the omega one
i want to see you too when is it a
roller coaster huh
yeah we went through space
you just you just went into it by right
cooking now
i think so you just need to brave i just
wait for the timer okay ah okay okay
okay okay
[Music]
just you actually so it might be worth
it oh my god
oh my god
well i never i never had
the guts to go on this one for real
so this is like a test run maybe one day
in real life i can ride it
let's go together
[Music]
yeah merchandise for me
it's the same merchandise
as you already have where's the
exclusive merchandises
[Music]
it's part of the experience
you can like suffer like people
yay
well we're going up chad i'm so scared
i'm so scared tell me when they're
taking the picture by the way i don't
know where they take the pictures
this is this right here
this is the race way white space uh
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] i can't imagine how
intense it must be
oh my return to you why so fast even in
minecraft wait oh my god oh my god
you ride the people mover
really don't ride it without me
[Music]
oh it's just a walkway oh
never mind it's just a big walkway
is it
exactly
they have those things like they have an
airport like uh they can have those
little cars
like with people
they have that
[Music]
please please
uh parties please get to
[Music]
this is incredible
what's incredible
no she's not actually doing it
right now what what are we looking at
right oh there you are
[Music]
where are we ah
i can't see your heads isn't it
wow there's a lot to do in here
well that will be a clip
[Music]
well wait you see i watched i watched
the peculiar stream of this disney
adventure and i thought i was prepared
but i was not our treat
trees even look the same
that's so cool
they look like blocks
they're fitting
minecraft
[Applause]
[Music]
what
though imagine if we can do this in the
actual like minecraft
please make it possible
[Music]
for me
i'm catching it i'm catching intercourse
maybe i'll
have a resource pack full horse to make
it into a car maybe that could
maybe
[Music]
up
oh
i love that that is that is not quite
accurate though because it's get it's
way more controlled in real life like
you can't
i didn't
hey
[Music]
laughing
coffee
tea burger
coffee cafe
i need some coffee
your only visitors are here tenth to us
now
[Music]
now that everybody's eaten
yes this way i am [\h__\h] going on a
sunny ride is not a good idea
it's the best idea what do you mean
i'm sure there might be some projectiles
children
one time
one time uh i got my body stuck in this
case
the gate here
oh no
yeah
i hear it of course the cast oh i was
trying to slip in between and
accidentally got my body stuck peacocks
pink one oh can we all get it
oh we gotta get in oh oh nice wow
oh
[Music]
oh god this is actually kind of like it
i can feel i can feel my lunch
chat are you enjoying this view
you can feel my lunch
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's amazing it actually kind of makes
me sick
no
let me out oh it's over
okay it's over oh thank goodness
are you are you girls good is everyone
fine how's your stomach doing is
[Music]
yeah
it's like the real thing
oh
i feel like the real thing it would make
me less sick then yeah i think it's on
the minecraft like
the leg
honestly i did not expect so many
different attractions to actually
actually be playable
like interactive
so cool what can we who is you
who are you he's an animatronic
he's actually much scarier in person but
what does he do
he's like he's like uh like hello ladies
and gentlemen what eat your chee burger
[Music]
well where do you guys want to go now
that's
[Music]
this is actually accurate
it's accurate it's historically accurate
this is actually like a very spooky
adventure now oh oh oh can you ride this
one
it's a roller coaster i'll show you
we must ride it yeah there's music i
don't hear music
how do you not hear music wait hold on
turn everything off everything
everything everything everything i don't
know what i was thinking of sorry guys
[Music]
environment maybe that's different that
is
[Music]
i want to get yammed
i don't think you guys want to write
dumbo
[Music]
i thought he was a dog he's a girl isn't
he a don a garch wait where are you guys
gosh girl spoofy please first it looks
scary
right here
where is
oh
[Music]
every impression i do just sounds like
mickey
[Music]
wait we can ride the roller coaster
oh wait
wait for me
right
[Music]
okay
i don't want to write dumbo i want to
write the yeah let's go
um
to childish for you or what
yeah
i'm gonna go check the wait time
[Music]
went the wrong this is not okay
oh no
nice poo look so smug
i'll go
we'll go we'll go watch the go watch
them on the ride
[Music]
oh it doesn't
me move
mom get the couch
moving thank you
[Music]
we don't even disney do you die will i
die if i don't eat what
i don't know
i was wondering probably won't run away
yeah
mama i'm going so fast
[Applause]
[Music]
children that totally are tall enough to
ride the ride because we are totally
tall and totally don't get told i'm this
tall
we're all the same height here
i think guna might be too small for
the ride oh okay no
i am talking about this i need to bring
out the measuring tape hmm i think it's
136 centimeters or is
[Music]
thank you
if you need some apples you can come to
my german class
and maybe
is this someone else
oh it's autograph winnie thank you
[Music]
oh yeah what's this place
oh yeah i like how in this this world we
can jump over fences can we implement
that please don't do that in real life
yeah but i want to do it in java
minecraft please oh java
i want to do this right has a lot of
stuff you can touch
11 doors mine
[Music]
oh
cute
[Music]
got in are not streaming
yeah oh no
well now we wait
okay
[Music]
we are fine i think this
is
so cool i oh thank god it's shining
shine brightly
diamond
diamond past
one of them is sleeping with me
[Music]
wow
that's crazy oh it's so cute
this is the awkward time where we're
waiting in line um
very realistic hey wait wait i've got
some food
that's good eat some food
and i have a cold ass cheeseburger from
like an hour ago
[Music]
are we going into the forest now
stinky stinky keys
need some cleaning
[Music]
all right
what do you mean
[Music]
several rides go on at the same time
that would have been smite says kiaran
oh she's playing what was that one's
name dopey
you think i can entertain my child for
hours while waiting in line this is
[Music]
give you a
not so good feeling let's go
let's go
[Music]
and get out of here
what is this the bathroom is it really
this one
i didn't think it was a roller coaster
it is a roller coaster
how cute this is really pretty
it's like a huh like a medium oh
medium roller coaster oh the speed lines
the anime speed lines
always show your shoes i wish the camera
move along though this is kind of better
man is it what's better
is that a reindeer
shiny
[Music]
ha ho
hi ho diamond pack
[Music]
grumpy dopey doofus and duck
you know all their names yeah so this is
the new cave update huh
[Music]
that's dark
oh okay oh
the clock is killed
somebody said shoot at them no no no
this is not a shooting game
don't kill the dwarves man
you're supposed to sing with them
[Music]
now we're going into a foreign
we cannot we cannot
[Music]
i'm gonna be honest at roller coasters
i'm the type to first scream very loudly
for five seconds then be so panicked
that i stopped screaming lose my voice
look down close my eyes and become a
baby
i'm not able to look at what's happening
around me
oh so you're talking oh that's what
happened to me one time man
are we done it's so slow again who's she
dancing with who's this the dwarfs oh
cute titties it's like her harem man
that's a double-headed dwarf
they're writing like like like you know
oh my god why does he have a man
what does he have a head around his
waist as well oh what
[Music]
a
witch the wicked witch
what what chat what
what
[Music]
what is that what that was fun
cute
i like this one it wasn't as scary as
space mountain
it's on my level yeah i can handle this
where are the other girls
oh i took mommy to the bathroom
right here
[Music]
we are guests put our services
careful
[Music]
it came out of her butt
what comes out of her butt
[Music]
how did we not see this before
did we touch her before i don't think it
might have been just looking from the
front
you should always place this one
it comes out of your butt huh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
did you guys know bears can make juice
what
huh um what kind of juice
[Music]
where i'm going where are we going we'll
make it
[Music]
oh
everybody ignores the other cast members
when there is oh my delaney
[Music]
oh i want to call you sven but i don't
think that's right there's
[Music]
oh
charming regal carousel oh is it the the
the mango around here american round
yeah
[Music]
what happened with your knowledge
where is
[Music]
knowledge and that's where it ends
oh
thank you
pinocchio village this is where you get
a really big cinnamon bun
[Music]
the food so far that was the same in
every store but
there's a lot of choice
yum yum yum
it here maybe it's it might actually be
in another brown building
what the [\h__\h] is that what's great
yeah good question
some fake gray stuff food
it's yummy maybe it's in there that you
get the
i think it's there
wait
you're like a food guide for disney
world
a food guide perhaps probably
maybe even like oh yeah that's just fan
made that probably exists
are we so sweet instagram that's about
disneyland
hello
oh
[Music]
is
run run
[Music]
she's so pretty
gorgeous
oh my gosh wow
she hasn't she'll give
it's time for a pickle wait i could look
if you fall in the water it makes you
get out
you're not allowed to die here can't
have any drowning in this
[Music]
i don't know i guess no
we can find another ride
oh yeah there's been so many
[Music]
liberty square
nap time
[Music]
how's it ever been daytime i feel like
it's been night time the whole time it's
been daytime okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
because i've always only been like one
day
[Music]
man those idle autographs they even like
each other i don't remember i feel like
they're like first i do what the hell is
going on here though what what is donald
duck doing in that light uh
in the ceiling
is he stuck can we help him ah
these people have one of the options
what are your actions this is peter he's
being mangled what is the propeller i
need a pen
i dances
she just waves we should have done it
with ariel damn it
[Music]
comes out of your butt
okay
oh he flies
that flex oh my god
[Music]
there's an attraction here peter pan's
flights i did this a little more let's
do it
okay i'm in for sure no one is taking
this away from
[Music]
okay can we follow you
wait it blocks you from going in in
different attractions
[Music]
oh they talk to us
halfway
[Music]
is it london big bang chicago
but there's some sort of water rocking
away
you can't convince me on that one
no no no no trust me that's a small
world oh
it moves well that's really weird you
try it okay
that is mars
and not the moon
let's go no
we can cross over here
marshmallows wait
[Music]
[Applause]
which one is this one is it
oh mermaid oh hello
i guess that turned it off but maybe
they're singing
it off though
maybe it's called copyrighted mysterious
[Music]
don't jump lady don't jump
no
oh taking over
[Music]
where's the alligator
she's shaking please let her live no
oh there's
oh he's standing up on his
mouth i guess
yeah
that's cute girls you can you can do it
now if you wanna we're done here
um we're on a different ride i don't
know which one it is it's like right
across from here names
[Music]
um
go up it's incredibly slow
all right are we in the wrong side
oh it's even the lady that's your way
back hello my nails are there right now
up the stairs
up the stairs up the stairs i feel like
this ride wouldn't be very cool though
without the sound effects yeah yeah it's
just silent all right it looks nice
though we're gonna have to ride it and
it had the music it'd be i went is there
is there any more roller coasters left
that we didn't do
i think so let me see the map
[Music]
mansion
there's
a caribbean ride yes
they're still kind of like
damn
is there a
splash mountain
no it doesn't seem to be here
wait this ride is actually so long
no
you're looking really long
yeah wow you guys know where they're way
over there
[Music]
i'm sorry
yeah
do you wanna do the honeymoon yeah
you're scared i am escaping it's gonna
be outlast 2.0
outlast oh
[Music]
it's in case the the line gets any
longer
i guess oh
is this the way in oh
[Music]
strange and frightening sounds
that is the time when ghosts are present
practicing their terror
[Music]
oh this is where the room gets taller
all right welcome foolish mortals
monkey monkey i am your host your ghost
host
next to you
[Music]
find myself all the way in make room for
everybody there's no turning back
[Music]
where you see paintings of some of our
guests
as they appeared in their corruptable
mortars
[Music]
metamorphosis
or is it your imagination no it's really
happening
where are we now
no windows
which offers you this chilling challenge
to finally find a way out really was
that was that a thing i i think they
just opened the door for me eventually
there's always my room
[Applause]
[Music]
your brother my brothers
your brothers are my brothers
[Music]
oh yeah i was eating on the rice
inside watch your children okay i'll be
watching is it me or is everything on
fire
it does look like it's on fire
only ghost stories oh no they're dancing
around good i know something oh okay
that makes more sense i thought they
were just
i thought they were uh
whose shadow is that 99 happy hunts what
shadow is that
cool
this is really creepy without the music
it's just nothing sound
and i have jazzy music on so it's not
quite the right atmosphere
they all seem to have trouble getting
through monkey
monkey
wallace
oh they're koalas
over australia
oh
oh no they're bears no oh this
[Music]
every room has wall-to-wall creeps
oh creepers everywhere don't explode
please and hot and cold running
[Music]
i don't like sitting on the edge of the
ride i feel like somebody's gonna grab
me
[Music]
turn this around
oh he's trying to get out of his
her clothes are really nice though i
like it
[Music]
right
i got stuck here once for like half an
hour
here
oh that you couldn't go there
did the ride
up they wouldn't sit down or something
yeah
they're screaming
wherever they're at oh
my god it's a floaty bubble wow
they made you look very minecrafty small
is relative yeah
it's not a small world afterwards
at all
[Music]
awaken the spirits
let there be music from regions beyond
oh my god whoever made this the disney
nerd there it is the hidden mickey plate
what the heck
disney made it probably
damn that's cool that's a weird detail
though wow
you see on the table do you see the
plates on the table yeah
one set of plates is in the shape of
mickey mouse's hand
you're right
[Music]
oh my god worse
do us part i rock
isn't it
bye fighters
oh houston i can read that
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't know where the haunted house is
[Music]
another archive of kiwawa to disappear
hmm
[Music]
there she is
oh you guys are done you know how i
mentioned that looks like i think it's
just in the disney parks actually ashes
were scattered in the haunted mansion
[Music]
we seen your
[Laughter]
[Music]
roller coaster let's see the map all
right
we
[Music]
the
boat sounds pretty loud
yeah let's do that one oh yeah
wait we can teleport right
oh i think so wait which time you click
on it number five
oh
i can't even see it
can i like zoom in
if you zoom in there's like a little way
mark and i can click teleport
how do you do that
there's a lot
wait where where is where is where is
the pirate thingy
uh
but okay i got a lot in the autograph
wait for me oh i guess
i guess we have to walk no you can
teleport yeah you can teleport you have
to click on the way
yeah pretty close
oh god this is
it's like imagine you're on a disney
dark ride and then everybody
disappears and you're just
on the dark ride
like even at night hello
aladdin
hello
[Music]
is
wait i have special music for this oh
gosh interact with prizes
i mean i mean
how many people can do this actually is
this a four person oh there's four okay
[Music]
oh
it hasn't been that long since the last
time i was on this one
just uh i think oh when
[Music]
the gang's all here
ahoy
[Music]
this is my music playing don't worry
about it
[Music]
there's like small world again slightly
i'm gonna get ptsd
[Music]
wow
it's a crab are they real spelling
javier
skeleton yes you oh [\h__\h] the crabs are
deadly is that a model
yeah
so accurate that's so crazy who knows
when that evil curse will strike the
group
wow
[Music]
dead man
baby jones no
[Laughter]
i don't know if we're even moving
[Music]
oh
this is the good thing about you guys
not streaming you can enjoy it to its
fullest
yeah for you
[Music]
jump into the wall and save yourself
is
johnny depp for this oh he'd be better
he should be he should be in the right
spot
yeah like i think very much at the end
i remember him being at the very a scary
[Music]
wow that's really updated they look
better than the minecraft chimpkins
and they look better than the minecraft
goats
and the tacos
why does she look so modern
i'll buy them
[Music]
no no it is a bottle no i don't know
what this is i think it's a key it's a
key wow they even have the oh
[Music]
broomsticks
everything's on fire what's going on oh
no
oh no they started the fire today
sparks
[Music]
meow is the hat guy in this gate oh look
at those cats
oh you'll be a fight you want me
well what they have green eyes
cause they're
alien and they look kind of freaky
the chicken is life for me wait let's
reply their
[Music]
is
i used to like to look up in his pant
leg because you could see the electronic
parts oh don't don't do it
don't do him like that
he's the one showing his ankles the dog
has the key
[Music]
there he is
is
[Music]
front row now but it's kind of late for
that
thank you though
don't worry about it
that was cute
[Music]
wait i'm inside somebody
oh wow cool
damn impressive stuff really impressive
oh at the good store of course
the goodies
well
[Music]
is she buying merchandise no no no i'm
here there's a jungle cruise
there's big thunder that's uh that's a
real room i want a fast one
[Music]
number seven
numbers oh no okay
going seven
wait wait wait wait wait wait
let's turn this up ah park music he's
hurry not really anywhere
no right there so he just walked there
yeah i think we can walk it's like to
the right
oh it's there oh wait wait run away from
the copyrighted music
okay
oh no i think it's this way
[Music]
oh my god they have the freaking
freaking french fries
[Music]
give me some nachos oh my gosh is she
okay we got jessie down
why is good excited
what'd you find yes tacos
apples
tacos you know what else ah
it's cowboy
we got the
wait you saw that go to oh there you are
i'm right here okay okay i guess she
walked instead of teleporting
yeah i got one of them recorders i think
i see someone quarter shoot them up
things
there's a snake in my boot
oh
[Music]
what's happening in country bear
jamboree
ah
it's like a musical show
with animals
okay okay i see
oh
oh wait that's actually
because they're changing splash mountain
from splash mountain into something
that's themed after tiana and tiana's
movie so it's actually
she's like a spoiler wait i got 22 out
of 20 sorry how much do you guys have
same amount
yeah we're pretty close to getting all
of them
oh yeah
it's time for the big
middle room
[Music]
how do we get up here though
climb this way
let's become
mountain climbers oh that was bad is
this the exit shortcut
other oh it's just like
where's the oh there she is
we want to do it
we want to do it can we down the wrong
side
oh
[Music]
that's so cool
flashing lights and colors
again that we went there before
wait wait wait wait how are you guys
still have to get there let's get there
uh
uh you go you go out the front
go out and then uh don't go yet go
around
no i won't you have to go up the front
come to the front uh maybe here no
is it this way this seems like it it
looks
[Music]
there she is on your mind
okay
i think this is two oh
four players
okay good
[Music]
yeah this is
a really popular
[Music]
okay i think it hurts
oh
[Music]
going up again
no no more i can't take no more i can't
take this anymore
so much like
everybody let go of the lap belt put
your hands up i'm already putting them
up
[Music]
i actually have a hand up post so that
way
wow
oh
[Music]
oh my god
okay
[Music]
right now
i am too old i require
a big
hot dog big burger
big big chili dog i have some chili con
carne without chili in my fridge girl
wait how do you make like corny without
chili
you don't need chili for chili con
kindness
[Music]
that's like having a hamburger without
the burgers
wow they got cheeseburger without the
cheese
exactly that one is just
burger
but then still it's a corny
hardness in chili
[Music]
there is meat though right yeah there's
otherwise
and then there's corn and then there's
bell peppers so everything that's just
not spicy
uh-huh
hello we're done yeah yeah
that's fine holy [\h__\h] there's so much to
do
oh it's like the real thing i feel like
we'll be here for hours and hours yeah
we should we could sleep in one of the
disney hotels i wish they could have
here
go kind of soon because i have to take
my animal out yeah okay yeah don't
forget one more ride i mean we can maybe
do one more ride yeah
is there anything
what would be a good last attraction we
didn't go inside the castle by the way
the big castle and we know
can we actually fireworks somehow let's
do that let's do that let's do that it's
a good way to end it maybe if we go to
the to the castle maybe there's
something to activate it
maybe yeah let's call it
you know what happens
is that alice who is that wait what is
that alice
wait who is this
[Music]
who the hell is that
cast member no
is it all right
wait we'll find out um some random oh
god no don't go to time
or don't go oh oh
my gosh
[Music]
tom sawyers yawn
i don't think i ever went to that island
just need to go to the center and
activate fireworks okay would be nice if
it was nighttime though does someone
know how to make it nighttime in
creative mode chat i don't know how to
do it
do you girls know
i'm so hungry
i'm
[Music]
[Laughter]
poor
guy i need you might have enjoyed that
i need poop
oh there's oh this looks promising
yes
[Music]
this time what did i not have
like someone's lips okay now i know what
you were saying
now i get it
yeah i think i know how to set it if it
works okay
let's go see fireworks oh thanks it's
not enabled in this world it says so i
don't think i can do it
when it's not enabled
uh setting the time
custom time oh oh oh oh okay to make it
dark
no it's okay you might just have to wait
a little bit yeah
if we're lucky oh this feels like all
the presidents
the best ride to take a nap
oh the shade
and this is the sleepy hollow where you
get really yummy fried bread mm-hmm
like a custom umbrella yeah what's
pretty
we should build this you know we should
build a casual hollow
castle
to start firework oh my god wait till
nighttime
[Music]
oh
participated
[Music]
go
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
happy new year
[Music]
sorry i don't have my sound on so i need
to make sound effects by myself
ow pow pow power
oh beautiful is this also 100 accuracy
or what about this
i don't know
[Music]
wow
that was the big end was it
nope there's still more oh my gosh
there's more
people
in the disney opening
with the
[Music]
oh the trunk has all the things
whoa that's why everybody goes like wow
[Music]
there's someone taking videos with his
nintendo ds
[Music]
that's legit what happened to me last
time um disneyland someone was taking
videos of his nintendo ds yeah
oh wait you can do that apparently i
mean it was one of the newer generations
i think
[Music]
you can take pictures or videos of this
oh my gosh it's never ending
it keeps going
well this has been really fun though i
want to say that yeah thanks for
watching
you think you're a better guy than you
i just kind of ran around making monkeys
no no no no no you're very informative
perfect
oh my god the saxophone
[Music]
get rid of the balloons they're kind of
they become really big okay
balloons girls yeah okay oh perfect
beautiful
are you attacking them send me one later
now
okay hold on give me one second maybe
yeah maybe it just doesn't oh that's
good that's good oh yeah yeah f5 girl
no
oh it just keeps going
come on
no it's just the for now the music
oh wow
i mean i imagine if you're actually at
disney world you'd want it to be this
long oh yeah
wow
oh planets
yeah i think i think that's i think i
got some good good shots thank you
f2 and bedrock okay maybe they're just
not telling me i took one but i did take
one and it's saving it somewhere yeah
okay okay
this is it come on
i think it's gonna keep going
endless fireworks
[Music]
that was definitely yeah did you know
that it's like different uh chemicals
used to create the different colors of
the fireworks oh and they smell like
sulfur which smells like stinky
oh wow
[Music]
the back of my head
i tried but i have some like ui stuff in
it that's okay that's a lot of good ones
last thing i want to check is if we can
go inside the castle here
i think i'm walking
quick look inside hello hello
i want to keep these stitch ears they're
so cute
yeah
yeah honestly i would be surprised if
you have never actually bought those in
real life in disney world before
let's be honest
cinderella
[Music]
yeah
okay that's squishy's in the castle that
was uh worth going through
yeah that was worth it ella
25 out of 20. wait you were here before
we were like
pocahontas
and uh
okay okay cutie pie thanks for having us
cinderella and all the other people here
thank you girls for
going on a disney date together it was a
lot of fun really impressive i did not
expect uh this to be so full of content
right yeah why yeah
did everyone have some favorite
attractions
[Music]
i did actually enjoy the small world one
even though it was very long and it was
really cute like it was really well made
yeah yeah
i really like these thunders
what oh space mountain was good
because yeah
with the stars like floating around yeah
that was really
i also like the cars
i like this
a lot as well it's one of my faves in
real life so
[Music]
okay
well everybody if you're interested you
can check this out yourself of the
actual original music this is not
sponsored but i think it would be fun to
check it out with the actual
og music without muting everything you
got to get bedrock
oh my god
it's waiting for my butt what the hell
is tiny casper bae bae is that you
[Music]
this is yellow babe i got the name of
that one oh good i disappeared
all right then i think we can end it
here
you can get
[Music]
it's a breakfast area i can actually you
can actual
polar bear oh
you can actually eat here yeah
nice it's probably always super crowded
i still have a staircase
it's not very impressive in here though
it's just like you know
with the breakfast place windows
wow oh it is cool
it looks like you need like reservations
even like yeah we're actually coming
here in order to get a seat like in real
life i mean if this is really a thing
probably six months in advance yeah
only for the for the biggest disney fans
the most crazy ones
um yes okay shall we
okay take our leaf
yeah yes
thank you for watching everybody
thank you everybody
hope you enjoyed it let's hope that
someday in real life we can all go to
some places disneyland together girls
wouldn't that be nice
i want to go to disney c in japan with
you oh that'd be fun oh yeah disney let
me be
i want to be a real guy in disney world
so i actually get to run you guys around
please please be our guide
yeah
[Music]
it will not be suspicious at all if uh
at disney sea you suddenly see 11
foreigners in a group um
[Laughter]
[Music]
one with a shark tail
who could that shark girl possibly be
and and that shrek girl the purple shrek
and that bird will the feathers on her
top oh
who's that girl of the frame
i'll just be wearing like a
inconspicuous mask over my head or we
dress up as no no actually that's not
allowed even at least in japanese
disneyland you can't dress up as the
princesses at least for there's one day
where you may but all the other days
you're not allowed to um halloween you
can
[Music]
bye
oops
[Music]
uh i'll see you guys in depth loop
tomorrow
def loop that loop
and then i'll be reading super chats at
that time
[Music]
you