[Music]
for
okay
[Music]
he
hello hello
hello hello welcome to our debut collab
stream oh my and another
timeline new timeline yeah this this is
that one other
time all right should we do
self it's the
first should we should we introduce
ourselves okay hey I'll start hello
everybody I'm Amelia Watson the
astronaut the first lady Free Falling In
Space into virtual space and I'm here
today with my gen mates should we start
with who's this purple one nice to meet
you astronaut oh thank you thank you
nice to meet
you oh who who Go's next you
purple hello I'm the I'm the purple one
you know nise the uh the neat gamer of
the group yeah just like to stay indoors
and play video games all day fun
stuff sounds cozy yeah okay okay you go
next Who's you you you
okay lady oh man I I wonder how I should
greet people I I don't have a greeting
yet do you girls have a good greeting
that an exercise instructor would do
Let's Get Physical kick kick kick no
something no I don't know anything about
kicks well sometimes in my exercise well
let's get physical sounds good
yeah let's get physical physical yeah
I'm whole Liv's one and only first uh
exercise instructor I just came
literally from the 70s or 80s I'm not
sure about that I'm a little bit confus
my worst enemy what I exercise i f the
70s where your enemy the exercise part
the e
word it's okay I'll I'll help you all
out from now on I'll make you girls
exercise all right oh no how do you like
exercise
no not the e word too bad I'm going to
throw you like a football no um
ready shall I yeah your turn uh the blue
one I am Debbie by the Sea your favorite
blue dolphin
dolphin Dophin now what sharp teeth you
have yeah you do dolphin
sound sounds accurate honestly what do
you think what kind of teeth do you
think a dolphin has like straight human
teeth yeah they do have kind of Shar
teeth I love
Dolphins how about you large booby lady
me oh I yes I am the large booby Lady of
this particular generation hey uh my
name is U Malaya porori and I'm the I'm
the first rock and roll bunny girl of
Hol but not the first bunny girl hi nice
to meet
you I have a guitar are those real no I
see the headband oh did you just ask me
if something was real yeah I wasn't St
but when you just ask which one yeah the
ears oh the
ears no no I'm a cosplayer okay oh in
the
house we're such a cute group wow what
do we call
ourselves oh um could be
magic
magic magic m a g
my Bas plays magic notes they kill
people when they touch you oh wait does
a dolphin have magic powers too again
like supersonic ooh supersonic
echolocation o that's cool the ability
to
be annoying and Sarah FAA is raing us is
is that our Senai don't oh Faun Senai
thank
you nice to meet you nice to meet you
indeed oh my goodness I
noticed I'm nervous now nous I hope we
become friends I notic us wow I'm so
honored she's so supportive wow I know
she's so nice
ooh ooh is that what she usually says
yeah she says yeah you know already wow
I didn't do any research on my I watch
your streams all the time I used to
watch it before before
they yeah she's a real gamer you know I
got I got to keep Gamers and check you
know be my rivals yeah
gamer all right what a
group what a silly what a silly group
what a weird group cool is The Jig up
yeah I think the CHS
UPS oh no they're on to us
dang it I still have to be Debbie no you
don't have to be it's okay you don't
have to we're good back to be yay all
right everybody Welcome to our myth
collab
[Music]
hello hello welcome is back in Action
hello
yeah so what are we going to do in this
collab do you guys know I'm going to put
you on the
spot what are we doing in this collab
you're first you're so funny in this
collab we shall H well first of all
since this is a very nostalgic
background we we could be nostalgic
about
things M okay good put someone else on
the spot okay uh what else are we doing
in this
collab uh
uh
dolphin um spending time together well
that's a good one yeah true and talking
yeah with each
other yeah okay we're already doing that
that's good okaying the obious little
bit that's one off the checklist yeah
all right uh what are we doing today you
know we're going to dig a hole for 3
hours
please save me not so fast clapping Mory
I got it
first it's only because Amit chose you
to be
first can you be more specific about
with the future we're going to do
something arbitrary we're going to do
something that we did together a long
time ago we're going to visit an old
place where old memories were
made go into our old home the old Holan
server and we're going to dig another
freaking hole but for what though a hole
going where for
fun our dreams in the future Beyond I
know we're going to space who could say
okay I just realized one thing yeah why
am OBS is also Frozen our faces are
frozen oh oh I refreshed it oh no has it
been like this all day uh no but I'm wor
I'm worried it's a PC problem cuz I was
messing around with some stuff in my PC
earlier but
oh oh there
goes kind of what happened you and me
now back out of
existence how is it how can I only see
you I'm trying to see everyone else okay
yeah I also saw everyone
else and
N okay I rejoined
hello okay oh and Cur here we go we're
back hey at least let's be honest here
it's easier to fix than it was with four
years yeah some improvements mhm they
did make it easier to
fix
so yes so we diing a hole or what oh
right now we have to oh oh we don't have
to right now no the the whole digging
thing is just it's just a silly joke we
don't really need to do that but we are
going to go back to the old server yeah
we are going to play some
Minecraft yeah but should we chat for a
little bit and then go into
it sure sounds
good yeah reminiscing in the last four
years yeah yeah in the last four years
what have you what have you investigated
have you been investigating well we did
kind of wrap up our investigation when
we did our 3D uh collab debut
stream that we had I do remember
wrapping up the investigation there so
you know opening up back opening up the
old files is it's kind of not really too
efficient you know the cases were closed
you guys were cleared of being innocent
and also cute and also unique and like
amazing and talented and wonderful
so um the case was
closed but I would love to still look
back and you know reminisce on on these
last four years and all cool stuff that
we've been able to do
together nice no need to reopen my case
File detective I have done nothing wrong
I think of all charges I'm going to put
a note there hey what just because I
resisted or something like that
resisting arrest yeah been watching a
lot of a little a lot of funny I think I
wanted in several
countries it's all those cables you you
chewed on
the the fiber it's F in her diet okay I
know but you know the
Internet true that's why my internet's
messed up oh okay I'm telling yeah I
might need to reopen your F Internet
please how could you not during this
collab this special collab together
mhm I think we already we already
answered the question that's like uh
what was your favorite memory so do you
guys have any other ideas of what kind
of uh reminiscent we could
do let's see yeah favorite memory is
such a easy one I feel right what was
the let's
see no that's going to bring down what
no it's not what was the scuffi stream
we ever did oh the scuff stream
mosted
stream I'm trying to remember extreme
anxiety moment wasn't it the first VR
stream we did together the small stream
I feel like that one was really
scuffed it was fun oh oh my gosh oh my
God I can't believe we forgot this
singing shiny Smiley story but thinking
that we were playing the recorded
version and we weren't and we were just
screaming yeah and it was horrific I
miss hey I thought that was kind of no
it wasn't on
purpose that was not supposed to happen
oh what it kind of came out super cute
though yeah I uh first off collab too
remember we were all trying to share
like one Ru suit oh oh my God yeah we
yeah we had we had like two suits
between us and we were switching back
and forth and it was really rushed and
it I mean yeah it was scuffed but it it
kind of worked it was fun yeah it worked
that was a
good that was fun made it work H else
what other scuffed ones trying to think
I think it's easier to point out
noncuffed ones I feel like we had
noncuffed on the only noncuffed one is
probably like
official yeah something we did at the
studio
maybe I mean I think I think even the
ones we had at the studio like if it was
just us like something
happened like right before the stream or
something and we're just like well here
we go again yeah that's
true do we all want to maybe give um uh
just ask for give am a memory of us with
am something we that comes to mind with
I love am is the password
oh when we played Project Tango yeah
yeah you like made a password or
something like that and it was you said
you have to say I love Amit it's the
password yeah
it's cuz I was in the elevator and I had
to let you back in and I wouldn't let
you back in unless you said the
password yeah I remember that was cute I
was I was pissed off at the time but
deep inside I was like oh I really do
love though dang it I'm going to change
all my passwords to that from now
on don't don't try to me no man I know
your email address no don't please I'm
just trying to do what's the right
thing okay that's that's cute I don't I
love Tango I don't think I was not in
that coll Tango yeah just me and two
player game a solo rainforest collab
rfor Forest it's still the password you
know they should have they should have
done a rainforest collab Cafe and call
it the oh true with me hey rainforest
pafe you're missing out oh god wow the
animal screams with you
guys recreate the animal sounds game
yeah yeah my Tom screams and then the
thunderstorm every 20 minutes is
actually just you guys
screaming good of an idea is it the
Thunder or is it my
stomach Rumble all right going down the
line an idea who's next somebody else
take the mic
dolphin
um I don't know I feel like I feel
like we we talked quite a bit about
stuff of the past uh yesterday am and
I choose one from those one from those a
favorite memory oh I want to think of a
new
one what about April fools remember that
stream stop calling you that oh that was
cute April fools April fools one that
was cute I had fun I hope you guys like
that with the the funny spinning wheel
and then remember
so getting upset that you kept getting
the weenie or
something and we had feet for hands
that it was so R brilliant actually even
the I think even the dance class stream
that was Lot true man that was rough
back then with especially since you know
real dance lessons versus like having
the heavy VR stuff on you it's different
yeah although I feel like I had a hard
time remembering the coreio mhm me
too it's different when you do it in
person like if you're not in the same
room it's you're just not quite
realizing we had so fun when we all were
in the same like dance class and we were
all learning together was like a core
memory and the background looked super
cool the way it was glowing like the I
don't know it's so memorable just that
stream the way it looked very athetic V
dance
stream thank you that's one of the few
VR streams that I tried to get going
yeah it was so fun it turned out good H
you guys are sharing stream memories but
I want to bring up just a random core
memory in my mind about Amit when we um
were when we were all in America
together for I think it was like wasn't
it our first get together I think more
or less with all five of
us yeah and and I remember so I feel
like I think I had to to leave uh
earlier than everybody else quite early
in the morning um and so uh me and Amma
were like staying on the same floor I
think the other girls were floor
remember and am was sleeping in the
living room on the couch uh and I was
like in a guest room on the same floor
so when I was leaving uh I just said
goodbye to am um like I I tried to but
it was so early in the morning and am
was sleeping but one funny thing I
noticed is that she had a baseball bat
or
so right next to her uh like on the
bottom uh like on the floor like on next
to the couch right at anytime ready to
protect myth at all cost yeah cuz you
guys all had a room but I was in the
living room and it was like kind of by
the front door so I was like I'm
the first line of defense you
know find that am but you know that's
that's how am survived all these years
you know she's always prepared
to the
defender yeah I'm I'm so wait I guess
the way you said that now it sounded
like it was more about protecting
yourself rather than Miss but usually
we're going to protect all of us yeah
yeah as an example she's always prepared
for you know yeah whatever whatever
would happen was it a baseball bat or
was it something else uh it was a really
long metal candle holder ah a oh I
didn't know about that I I didn't know
this story yeah got to be prepared after
all
MH I appreciate it of course it was hard
to say goodbye to Amma cuz I didn't want
to wake her up and her sleepy face was
so cute yeah I was really tired cuz we
went to bed super late that day and then
we had to wake up super early like I
think I only got 2 hours of sleep cuz it
was really hard for me to fall asleep
too so oh no oh it's okay I survived
yay you survived the myth trip we all
did all
right ah I have so many good memories
it's hard to choose but like one of the
things that I can think of like right
off the bat is like you remember we did
the Christmas like everyone prepared
different gifts
or or the I still think like neither
she's talking about the the self-made
gifts right yeah yeah yeah where we also
did the the song where we wrote a song
or was it a poem what we wrote a poem or
song Oh I think yeah yeah I think it was
oh no it's the other Christmas I get
what you mean yeah first Christmas po
yeah yeah yeah I don't I still feel like
that was like one of the hardest I've
laughed like in my life yay yeah it was
Jingle Bell smells somebody on my Laden
K Laden egg that's what it was like am
always prepares like such cute gifts for
everyone we met off meet like offline
and stuff true
and and like you know one of the things
one of the favorite things I know that
am made was like the the takachi and the
terrari
ofi so cute oh thank you yeah that's my
first time well I think it was like one
of the first few times I tried carving
stone so I I poured concrete into a mold
and then I waited for the concrete to
set and then I just got like a little
Filer and I
just I was filing it down to takachi
shape and I think I breathed in concrete
powder I was going to ask you how much
stone dust did you no I learned to wear
a mask so I think it's fine I didn't
even think about you having like carved
that yourself somehow I just just
assumed that it was existing T yeah
maybe out in the wild or you bought it
somewhere I don't know I made it I know
it was like it was so impressive and
like the terrarium you buil was like so
nice too thank you thank you liked it a
awful gift oh thank you yeah I don't
know what happened to that actually some
staff has it I think it put it out in
the exhibition right fesh yeah but it
had plants so I couldn't like take it
back from Japan cuz I had to buy the
plants in
Japan yeah I remember we went like
shopping for like the plants and stuff
in we went to like a tour aquarium stor
is cool yeah that was a really cool
store
MH right made neat i g i don't think you
you might have been I remember going
with Iris and youa I think there was
just three of us possibly oh maybe I'm
thinking of a different member we I
think C was there
too yeah I'm pretty sure that I was
there that was
fun A yeah oh this is also random but
there's another big memory I have of all
of us going to a certain theme park
together
yeah remember we planed it like
spontaneously Yeah well yeah I mean you
know I like to just you know keep things
General but oh I've talked about it very
specifically before okay yeah we went on
a we went on a ride that Kiara liked a
lot and it involves some Oh you mean
that theme I'm thinking of round one oh
okay different one wa that's not really
a theme party that's why I was confused
why she was the spontaneous one where we
just like we're like you know we should
go and then we were like on the spot
buying like the tickets and stuff it was
right after rehearsal for something yeah
I remember I remember was at the old
studio right yeah it was in the old
studio and then we were in the hallway
and we're just like let's do it let's go
let's do it except I think it was
already last minute so we couldn't get
the fast passes yeah everything was last
minute yeah it was fun like just
rounding let's go and then meeting up
inviting qu was also last minute oh yeah
yeah oh yeah Quon and then and then
Kiara was clapping at the end of that
ride with the yellow the yellow
characters and around and I said to a I
was like a you want to ride it again and
am made a distinct symbol with her hand
that indicated to me that she did not in
fact want to ride it again what whaty I
have to say though those like me meat
bun or whatever Cur was pretty good of
that yellow R yummy yeah it's because
the line was so long like we were
waiting in line for what 2 hours or
something an hour and a half yeah it was
pretty pretty and then the ride itself
is is less than yeah it's it less than 2
minutes obvious I think I remember that
ride being really like motion sickness
like oh yeah you're like in a big car in
a big theater it was so good it was so
good I definitely felt the little motion
sness really you can't do roller
coasters oh I can do roller coasters but
the ones with like moving screens and
stuff the screen is not like really good
high quality like you know gaming yeah
FPS yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that makes
sense understandable me and me and Ena
and gubba went to the Monster Hunter
thing right oh yeah that
was and then in the meantime rainforest
was doing what with
quason were walking around walking
around yeah actually we wanted to go on
the like a ride you were too late yeah
they closed it we couldn't get there
there closed for like 3 minutes it was
very sad it was clutch but sad oh man
monst was so cool we just had like a we
had like a blue
churro wish went on hun too cuz it was
it was really fun seems like you guys
had a good time yeah
dang it you know we can still hang out
offline if if uh we all happen to be in
we will we will I'm going to crash your
guys parties still owes me a visit in
Europe yeah I want to go I still want to
go it's just traveling I didn't I didn't
realize it's a lot it's so much takes so
much time well now you'll have more time
to travel kie wants to go too I'll go at
the same time let's go please oh
everybody reunion in in Austria yeah
I'll
go Christmas markets in Austria
Christmas in Vienna that sounds nice I
always get reals about that Christmas
Vienna yeah yeah the big city can have
authentic Vienna
sausage is that really a
thing yeah they're called Vina Vina
sausage oh like we just get anywhere in
a we have better sausages those are the
most basic sausages a but fine yeah Vina
sa yeah oh cuz we're the winners yeah no
no not how you write it but
close when do Christmas Market
start uh like pretty much I think some
start maybe end of
November and then throughout all of
December and some late ones run a little
bit to like mid or end of January oh
so like yeah throughout the winter
winter time okay I want to go me too got
to do
it Austria welcomes
you we could go skiing we could go
skiing me and Cy I have me and Cy went
to the skiing trip before and I have
very traumatic memories from it but we
should still go I have traumatic
memories about snowboarding oh did you
break
something uh possibly but I'm not sure
but I still feel the effects to this day
cuz it never got checked
out that doesn't B well your jacket kind
of reminds me of like a snowboarders
jacket I could totally imagine
you
getto that be
cool where's your snowboard
outfit you know how to ski or snowboard
I've never done that I've never been on
a Snow
Mountain
either we'll have three of us in the
warm
cozy drinking chocolate right slow okay
but that's actually the best part about
it like I'm telling you after sliding
down the mountain several times and
going back up eating Austrian like we
call it like hidden food like the Hut
the the huts on the mountain they have
special food and it's like aan food but
it tastes even better on the mountain
it's like all kinds of like sweet
dumplings or
with vanilla sauce and app strudle and
that kind of stuff you know good hot
chocolate by the fire oh yes hot
chocolate and and mold wine and stuff
like that mold mold I love mold wine
mold mold mold mold m u l l e d what is
that moldy wine warm wine with spiced
Stu but you never heard of it even
more reason for you to come over cuz
they also that's like main the main
drink at Christmas markets I don't like
wine it's okay they I don't like it
either but they also have um uh what
punch punch hot punch ooh okay hot punch
you're selling me Kiara you're
selling guess I guess even if we don't
know how to ski or snowbo we can go
sledding or
something I know how to do that no but I
know the best ski teacher ever I I met
this like 80-year-old ski teacher around
romly who's kind of retired but he
taught me so well he could teach all of
us well you can teach us too cuz you you
learned right so yeah sure right Callie
I mind can teach them right Callie she's
a pro sck with like SL tube thumbs up
tubes are fun
yeah fun tubes get so fast sometimes
insane avalanches and and
bears yeah they're Bears or like those
people that are skiing or snowboarding
and then they just fall into a giant ice
hole that they didn't see ooh that's
like I think that's probably more like
when you ski off
the pre prepared
tracks yeah those like what are those
called like the black diamond courses
like the high level SK courses yeah well
not even those there should be no holes
there but um I know the last Black
Diamond that I skied down I was skiing
down and I looked to my left and it was
just a cliff
[Music]
the only thing was like a thin rope girl
when did you ski down a black diamond
thing when I was very young okay I had
no choice cuz last time I saw you
properly you were still doing the pizza
thing so I don't think you should go
down the Black Diamond Road I was much
better when I was much younger me too I
had real
lessons it's not like riding a bicycle
not at
all a French fight yeah we'll teach you
am a girl we'll teach you how to SK I'll
try it I'll try
it you never have to do it again skiing
definitely more beginner friendly than
snowboard really but snowboarding looks
so much cooler it does it does but it's
so
hard trust her she has a snowboarder
jacket true she knows what she's
saying enough yeah H so okay I'm
awaiting you girls
what I'm awaiting you oh okay awaiting
oh is it time to dig our long hole no no
I mean an AA but yeah we can go down oh
sorry I thought you were waiting in
Minecraft yeah no I'll come
anytime there's mold wine I'm there Yi
I'll see when a good time is I want to
go too going in the winter set it does
sound nice I'll see I'll see how cold
does it get
M it depends like obviously the
mountains it's way colder but I can also
only tell you in uh Celsius I don't know
fhe I'm okay with Celsius oh
nice well if you're not on the mountain
then maybe so December around 0 to 5 CS
maybe oh my God maybe or more like
December is still kind of warmish maybe
5 degrees to 10 or 5 to 7 and then
January February definitely zero and
then sometimes - 5 -
but barely I guess it's different right
well
yeah that's that's like I was thinking
we're going to go minus 20s here oh no
no in the mountain yeah but in the city
it's not so
bad what about the snow there's a lot of
snowfall January February yeah but why
are we talking about so much about so
let's let's talk about Amy oh true true
Amy
yes oh man I loved your aquarium
yesterday oh thank
you all the different fish about it
earlier otherwise I canceled all my
plans and gone yeah I didn't know you
were touring well we can still do that
now I don't know I don't know because
we're going to play Minecraft so we have
to pick Minecraft or aquarium so the
Minecraft is fine okay yeah I'll check
out the trip down memory lane with
Minecraft yeah what did you decide that
what fish we would be yeah yeah I made
like a list for everyone and I was like
oh this fish would be good this fish
would be good that type of thing why was
I not a
swordfish uh are you calling me fat by
making me a puffa fish no that's funny
po fish are cuter funny I'm just kidding
it was really cute and it it also it
gets big and it gets small like you know
fish I wonder if there the pictures and
videos I saw what was that the big form
or the small form I think that was the
big one yeah I I I think it does defate
at some point but I I don't know I
didn't see it so maybe not I can't
believe you made me into an octopus no
one would ever imagine me to be an
octopus
right it looks so good yeah it just
feels like really fit for some reason
I'm not sure why I just why was C an eel
it's supposed to it supposed to be like
Smooth yeah it's supposed to be like a
play on words like Mory eel oh okay wait
that makes perfect sense I like
that and I'm long I am the longest of
all of meth very long like I'm long and
maybe the eel represents like the
flowiness of your Veil and your hair
longevity yeah oh oh
longevity longevity Elric
personality
wow they all looked so cool don't they
bite everyone was awesome yeah they do
they can bite girl was a shark right yes
[Laughter]
no that was a dolphin right it was a
very yeah it was very dolphin like
should have been a
dolphin big
fish that was so cute yeah why were you
in an enemy no urin sea urchin a sea Ur
urin sea Ur are yummy also delicious
yeah originally I was a shrimp and uh it
got I got made as a shrimp too but then
I decided I wanted to be sea urchin
instead so yeah I don't know not for any
particular reason just cuz I like them I
think they're cute oh imagine the irony
if GAA would have been made of shrimp
now you're the shrimp who's the shrimp
now thank you shrimp that's as big as a
shark noig shrimp Godzilla shrimp do you
think like somewhere in the deep deep
deep ocean there's a gigantic shrimp
there's got to be I feel like there is
we just haven't discovered it yet yeah
and it eats dead bodies that fall to the
bottom of the ocean yeah
yeah cool I want to meet that shrimp me
too since when were you working on that
aquarium um it's been like I think a
month and a half 2 months Maybe
yeah I mean seao was the one that did
the whole map layout uh I think that
really brought it all together cuz I did
do a really terrible uh Ms paint drawing
of how the layout should go and they
just you know they just took it and made
it better so oh well as usual nice yeah
yeah let me see if I have it here you
guys can check I I'll scenes Let me see
uh did you did you show the others yeah
did you show you know your viewers yet
uh not yet oh it's a big surprise first
reveal yeah first reveal behind the
scenes of Amelia Watson's brain here it
is oh oh what it doesn't look scribbles
this is brilliant this is solid so yeah
this is the entrance area and then it
goes into like where there's the
Shipwreck and then the hallway into the
tunnel area with jellyfish and then our
rooms and then the shop but they just
kind of made it loop around wow yeah
that's very easy to comprehend H yeah as
someone like who works on stuff like
request to make stuff like these kind of
sketches help so much like visualize the
project but that so good look at
that amazing that's like really helpful
absolutely like best kind of
commissioner who prepares all the stuff
you know
they have a vision and you know how to
make it and it's like
amazing I hope I gave them like a lot of
stuff to get inspiration from so yeah it
turned out really awesome so they did a
really good
job that's so cool thank you that we can
still do things like that though you
know like like a zoo or something like
that oh that'd be crazy po zoo or
something I don't know I just I love to
think that like things like that can
still happen you know M well I me with
this big aquarium can I ask what's like
now that like all of your big projects
you know have been revealed uhhuh from
the four years basically including the
aquarium what's your favorite project
that you made I think honestly it well
it's really recent but maybe I'm bias
the aquarium I
think better and better yeah
understandable all the 3D modelers uh
have also really improved over the last
four years too the ones that I've been
working with and I don't know maybe I
help them improve a little bit too and
you know to see like their the
culmination of all their hard years of
work is really cool so yeah I really
like it a lot sweet I like it too I've
been seeing like the artists post their
like fishes on Twitter all day and I'm
like yeah there so many
MH so sweet they perfect for everyone
too so fitting yeah well thank you would
you one of my favorite projects in VR
that you did was definitely the
Halloween one where like we were in a
maze and like sharks and frog shark fros
shark
fros yeah that was really cool yeah cuz
I think the not everybody had a model
that we could use or something or I
think it was teams I don't remember but
yeah I I looked for a few hours trying
to find what what is a model that we can
use you know and that's what you came to
well because there w a lot of options
stuff that was ready for VR chat and
then stuff that we could also use on
stream like permissions wise so yeah
that's kind of what we ended up
with see and my favorite like project of
yours I think is like the Christmas the
VR
Christmas yeah that was the ornaments we
all
decorated yeah the whole project was so
tit so sweet
yeah I like how that one turned out too
yeah those custom 3D assets I yeah
remember I I messaged everybody I was
like hey can you design an ornament
we're going to decorate the tree with it
in
3D yeah yeah that was so sweet M yeah I
still hold like the you know the first
uh like the myth area you made oh like
what everyone had different rooms and
stuff I I still really really really
love that one cuz that was like I guess
like my first one of the first times I
did PR and just seeing everything like
there was like just magical to me was so
nice and it has been expanded so much
too at this point and then there's the
different versions like the Halloween
version and then there's the Easter
version there's so many versions now
yeah I I think when the map releases I'm
not sure but usually everything is
connected via the elevator so it might
be possible to see like everything at
once in one go but I'm not sure about
that cool the elevator
yeah the Hub sool The Hub The Hub World
elevator Hub and then you helped me do
like a a small live 3D one time too
concert yeah yeah that turned out
cute oh yeah and like the the I guess
like the TV showroom I don't know what
else to call the studio yeah the studio
cameras all the cameras and props that's
so nice been making good use of
it yeah you guys use it oh yeah K use it
for her Easter project right the yeah
Easter and a different collab with
another YouTuber and you know like all
kinds of things so I I also used uh the
the cameras for the V AVR whole talk
episode Ah that's right that's right I
remember it was cool it was so perfect
for that Mama M so good I'm glad I use
it again I hope people yeah I hope
people will keep using it oh sorry
Bubba's here so
love he's running
[Laughter]
[Music]
around me too the cats that looks so
crazy it looks
3D oh
good meet baa is that a real picture yes
based off my my tutu it's my tutu girl
cat it almost looks like like a like
it's almost not a drawing like it's it's
like a cropped out picture but made 3D
2D does that Mak sense yeah yeah I can
see what you mean that's cool realistic
she's real to me you're real right
you're real right dudo oh she's
real my
baby okay we've yapped like 50 minutes
should we go into Minecraft now yeah we
can continue y there too okay Yap in
Minecraft Let's go see if tutu's in the
way though I'll have to move first Tut
you got to say goodbye
[Music]
no got to say
goodbye
okay welcome
oh answer whoopsie
doodle go let me move myself a little
bit oh I can it's okay I can oh sticky
you got it I'll put my guitar away
way to if it helps you we can align our
uh our Heights so that's not
so okay yeah like you guys sitting down
yeah sure yeah I'm going to sit get
closer take a little sit right here oh
Ena you're getting so
close oh my Lord ladies ladies I'm
getting
nervous well now we're smaller than gooa
Still Standing dog sit just
kidding goba is standing and we're
sitting cuz she's too short to reach the
[Music]
desk all right so wait C everybody's
here okay
mhm we
will check out the old server
[Music]
memory
lane cuz wait yeah is something going to
happen to this I guess we don't know if
the Ser will be around for a while
explod I mean it's not going to
disappear but I think there's stuff uh
stuff changing with like how the servers
are connected and stuff with the new
updates whatnot makes sense not too sure
I have to double check but this is the
only server that I live in really and do
anything in so I wanted to stay yeah I
still have all my stuff here
yeah can they hire us moving
services that' be nice they just give
you a bunch of ender chests and then put
oh I guess only one Ender Chest oh what
are those big thingies called uh shulker
box yeah they could give you a bunch of
shulker box bunch of shulker boxes
that'd be nice for free for free yeah
they
should cool yeah there were a bunch of
free shulker boxes I think oh okay I
wonder I forget who no wait
no fall to her death come back I'm I'm
going back I got
lost uhoh I didn't mean to fall it hold
on I remember where the entrance
is isn't it up the stairs in the little
ring yeah yes yes I remember yeah I
remember the
well okay I remember we were discussing
like how to do the transition between
the servers that first we're told oh
many ideas she's there oh okay let's go
creater let's go yeah
[Music]
yeah hello y hi hello
hi she's back yeah soone
explore I don't have shaders on though
sorry
chat default original experience we love
vanilla
Minecraft oh good my my sinus uh vending
machine still
working oh good times I think with like
shaders and stuff this whole area seems
like really dark so it's kind of scary
the black part spooky
scary
Oh yay I graffiti there more signs oh
yeah you got to press the button oh I
got one
it's gotcha I think yeah it
is I got normal wood all right we
love okay I'm putting my graffiti on the
wall it's very simple but it gets the
message across wait we did the same
thing mine's a little more
frantic great minds think
alike beautiful thank you you're welcome
Big
Ups what's the wise Gooby going to
write um eyes on go yes how I
just that's pretty silly that was so
funny I watched a clip that like
immediately after you guys uh were done
streaming was uploaded and it explained
like what why you wrote that cuz you
didn't remember do you know now I no I
don't think we ever I don't think we
ever came to the conclusion for that one
I can tell you I saw a clip I think I
know why yeah you it was before one of
your Minecraft streams you were just
sitting muted or like I think your
microphone was muted in the VC and
suddenly Amit came in and she said
something what did you say just boo you
remember I don't know I don't remember
that and then yeah and you tell told
your viewers in your stream like you you
were you were so close to saying I
streaming you you were I was streaming
no you were about to stream but the
thing happened before right before your
stream
ah you can watch the CL the clip later
okay I don't have any memory of this
yeah me
NE oh oopsie this seems very silly oh
all right I'm where should we look next
uhoh I we could go uh counterclockwise I
guess okay yeah this is definitely kind
of where like a council
was yeah oh it's the
flower oh the FL it's the flower 2021 oh
my God so long
ago wow feeling old oh kfp first
employee
20120 a
Jimmy you know him by name yeah they're
all named Jimmy sometimes
oh the watch it's still ticking say it's
still
ticking tick Tu Tick T where' the time
go where did the time go from 2020
dang wait so people have been asking
have you answered this question am are
you giving the watch back no no okay no
it's HT sheing down to jump timeline
it's a gift it was a gift
okay but what is this she surely sees it
like that
what is
this
membrane is your
KN
okay yeah yeah
okay who's this
pizza1 I'm your chat will know yeah yeah
I don't remember someone's p
bread big bread big bread love bread
this is a nice place name bones what's
going on museum H the council really
come out in
yeah years for 2021 cuz uh December 2021
we did the VR check collab I'm pretty
sure the Christmas one oh oh yeah God oh
my
goodness can't believe where time go for
real oh this does this go back down oh
no it doesn't this no this is just a p
I've always wondered why this wasn't
like a infinite water source synthetic
whoever it built it didn't
finish W mysterious a lot of
things oh yeah IR is melon farm yes I've
used that a lot really a lot of times I
remember it was really helpful when we
were getting stuff from the JP server
when we first connected ah yeah you
could like trade melons for emerald and
stuff yeah yeah and in Phoenix tin or
whatever the the yes
yeah yeah Iris wanted to just put this
melon farm out here without anything
around it so I was like hey you got to
put something on it you you can't put a
melon F oh you got to make it look nice
you told her yeah to put a big melon
around it what a good idea stand by
telling her kohai what to do
cuz this is the entrance area we can't
just have Machinery out and about it's
dangerous no true true brilliant oh from
sh backed
up oh ooh free emeralds free take care
be why are they separated us they didn't
troll me I think it's from my my the
statue no the Amy statue oh maybe
yeah is it cuz they put a advertisement
where you
yeah my you pass
by okay big old
Melon m thank you all right we we we can
take the train back but first we should
finish up looking at everything right
yeah there's so much what's this oh yeah
the milk and cookies vending machine
milk and cookies's favorite
spot we were all so motivated to like
build this whole area because we were
like opening the portal right yeah yeah
this is like our most developed area the
prettiest
area he's so proud there and then me and
Ena made the onen up there it's so
nice it's full of a couple rooms that
aren't finished but
most it's like that on purpose it's a
minimalistic design to also build this
playground I don't think I
yeah yeah
yeah playr remember this was like a
popular spot for pictures when JP was
doing tours around
here everyone would just like sit here
and take
pictures oh yeah yeah the sandbox boo
boo baba wants to play a Sandbox
together it is a sand game it's co and
rough and it gets
everywhere get
everywhere
on welc to waterfall and everything
potato machine Ena did a lot of the
heavy lifting here though I just turned
out so nice wait why is there so much
snow think there was a snowman
atere that makes sense that makes sense
we got like real futons on the ground oh
yeah why is there fish in meat here oh I
think we were grilling something but oh
yeah great view into the the right here
oh wow
2024 oh how like it's so updated I
wonder if anybody will update it again
at some
point maybe we still have fure we still
have a little more of 2024 left true we
do for the for the time being
yeah it's cool though this room's
awesome yeah but is that the glowy thing
is that with uh red red sand red stone
red stone yeah
probably really cool seems complicated
Redstone is pretty cool yeah I'll leave
that to some yeah we'll leave it to yeah
whoever built it yeah technical experts
oh was it not am no not
sign forget was this is the simp room
for the
PO oh nice I remember this was not
finished for a long time oh yeah it took
us a while yeah yeah this is pretty good
view
too I think this was the view into the
snowy Parts yeah if I remember correctly
memories it's the type of place I like
to
Vacation the
winter wow nice pretty stars
wow tower that you can farm from the
hidden entrance to Bunker rooni
somewhere out there somewhere out there
somewhere out
there lots of memories
mhm no zombie no zomie you're not
allowed in here oh boy they can't get in
here I'm pretty sure yeah away with you
defend our
onand oi oi
oi okay nice on then Scoundrels next
what's next all right we have beds here
if you want to quickly
you there's also the Bedrock baths you
can't this goes down deep yeah this is
the basement own sense right yeah I
remember secret
rooma where the BS the lava room I've
never seen this room I was still working
on this one it's like a waterfall bath
oh sleepy sleepy I'll disconnect really
quick if you want
but spawn oh okay okay this is the the
stone bath with all the different gems
and stuff in the walls it's pretty
neat like a sauna oh the lava bath the
lava Bath's pretty cool uh it's got umet
fter characters here kung
fu kung
fu the SAA which I didn't completely
finish it's like not all Acacia but it's
close enough hey it's I this place is
nice yeah you can meditate in the Soul
Sand
room work pretty hard on barely fit in
here yeah it's where you trap yourself
to like just be alone with your thoughts
you know I see we uncomfortably close to
a stranger
ooh okay wait are we sleeping I think
it's daytime no oh no I was just setting
the SP no I guess we can sleep I can
yeah yeah it's still night there's a
bunch of beds upstairs here I think yeah
up here that's the communal bed
area are we sleeping
actually
yeah okay if there aren't enough beds I
can
disconnect it's an old s yoka there
should be enough beds there should
always be enough bed hopefully I I think
I'm
frozen oh oh no nice sleep over at the
on that was fun I'm
leg
no maybe that'll fix
[Music]
it
hello not moving anymore I know she's
back okay Str Frozen she's back this is
such a good view from here what the hell
oh yeah pretty so colorful the flowers
oh that house over there is so cute
gingerbread
house I about this oh there's a snowman
don't let him out made
this yeah who else was working on I was
working on it a lot of people came and
helped the Snowman he moves yeah
yeah let him melt captured a real
snowman right beside the fire he going
to melt he lives here like that soup
commercial there's a child stuck in
there oh yeah yeah he has air
conditioning and is welled you trying to
kill him no it's by accident I'm going
to put it away I keep on activating it
he's been alone in here for 2 years a no
he's fine he has a painting and a couch
and a
fire yeah that's all you need really I
don't think snowman's need
F there's a cow hello cow oh cow I
answer you get out of here we answered
you I'll I'll I guess the same door we
came in I guess so little cute little
backyard yeah he's he's chilling he's
got his own place I could eat this whole
place I'm getting
hungry to is this a little ter terrarium
I think this is or is this not the
bakery maybe yeah Bakery is further over
to the oh this is like a indoor oh wow
this is like an indoor mall or something
it's huge Mall
I ah over there wow I've never seen that
before yeah who built this wait what do
it say it this she did a lot of building
here oh this is her base huh yeah yeah
yeah I'm pretty sure it's good really
uhhuh oh wow Bakery it seems dangerous
though up here it's like all
open uhoh yeah fall don't
die wow and you can climb the tower from
here I think oh it takes a really long
time to get up to the top doesn't it
yeah yeah yeah it does fast as way down
jump yes see precisely
oh oh I think it has access to the
bakery yeah direct access a treehouse
that's so cute what a good
idea cute I took a lot of bread from
here in the past me
too to take some more
I'm going to take some the bread's still
there Minecraft bread can't hurt you m I
got to eat a lot of after after 2
years I wonder if it's not Tak proper
care of there's not really that much
left there's only pie left I've
ransacked the cookies is pretty
good oh and the shrine ah yes oh yeah
remember this I think I made it with
room May did I
I think I made it with es fortune
telling I got stuck in the door there's
a button look look where oh there's one
here there Fortune I got one it's just
luck oh that's not bad mine is four how
did I not see that you're
doomed you're supposed to put it up here
yeah oh not my bread that's whoopsy
Dole dang it is doomed I feel like that
really I want to get a fortune where do
I get a fortune oh right here you
Shinigami
no oh cast oh I got it have your fortune
is neutral now I just got a better one
oh okay okay wait it's say no I got I
got the cursed one H now you would like
a neutral right the other one's mine oh
come on you stole it from me yeah you
can have your neutral one
how it goes let me see yeah here it's on
oh Sor on
theor now you want it
okay thank you okay I'll put it
back H what's your fortune I got doomed
do you oh my go doomed Doom let's you
have to put it up here it says right
yeah if you got doomed you got to put it
up on thing be G Doom oh mine's neutral
too wait I didn't put the cursed one on
the thing does that mean
that on you only put the bad ones on the
wall so that you know it can be maybe
fixed
okay yay
nice you got to ring the
bell oh was it was
like like what clap twice bow
twice I forget something like
that throw some money in though make
sure to
important I really want you to put the
money I have a jewel here you
go oh I wasn't serious you didn't have
to but thank you I shall gladly accept
any payment as a priestess hey this is
my
Shrine I I'm the Priestess
now you can't just take from other
shrines yeah also I was see and REO I'm
a
priestess but but have you ever actually
worked in a Japanese uh Shrine before
cuz I
have yeah part time as a shrine Maiden
as
a yeah teaching you guys new knowledge
that you didn't even know about me yet I
think I remember make that
sake uh sake no no um well I did help
like in like some wedding ceremonies
where I gave them like special um
comu uh tea and I cleaned the shrine and
I sold fortunes and I sold uh the the
protecting charms and yeah all kinds of
stuff no it's dressed in the typical Mo
outfit
o basically I was sakur
Miko cool but you're
takiki yeah I can be
both where are you going I what's this
part it's a tunnel I built I want to see
if there's anything on the other side
yet oh ohue yet you were anticipating
something to be built yeah there's
nothing here though there's a half buil
structure yeah I don't know who this is
there was a
vision investigation
begins uh let's find out I can't there's
no entryway or anything so hm
want Farm oh I'm a
bee now you're stuck there forever I'm a
bee the ruins of a dream I I have
scaffoldings I could get out oh oh it's
super cute wait what are they doing
though like how do you even Farm them
making honey oh I think it's under the
ground probably some kind of dispenser
TR okay there is a hole over there but
I'm afraid to go down
oh no it it doesn't go down oh
okay maybe they just used this to bre
breeder oh yeah breed okay that makes
sense
[Music]
yeah wait this is a cave I don't know oh
here it
is oh spin no spunkin today right spin
today the whole what we're going to dig
is
what if we we're digging a hole shortest
hole threatening to dig the hole but we
are we digging our own
graes graes today already some Graves on
our server oh yeah that's true there are
where are you guys Adam Saddler my
suspiciously I guess we could we could
Dig's grave jeez I want to to hold the
Minecraft Funeral For Me Oh I love to
hold you Minecraft we would I think we
could yeah okay and then that's where
I'll
disconnect okay we'll make it in the
humorous way no we'll make it funny
we'll make it silly it'll be the
silliest Funeral Ever logs out forever
well I have to log back in because I
wanted to fix something before I logged
off
forever okay thank
you all right should we go to bueron and
then we'll take the train yeah bunker I
buoni really I think the entrance is
somewhere here we can walk the rails
what is this long tunel road what a
thrill M oh it's all it's just the
ladder should we go up I don't trust it
I think that's just to the tree farm no
okay don't worry I'm going to go I'll
tell you guys what's up here down okay
she's going you guys know how to get to
buoni right um not
really sarcasm remember there has been
updates
but I might remember who knows remember
it was some kind of sunflower with
[Music]
like there was like
fake are you enjoying the climb on it no
I feel
claustrophobic down no s I'm almost
there where we could
like I think Crouch down and get in
that's what I was trying to find mind
there's like a hole
here
somewhere oh the
buoni is it there very nice 10 out of 10
thank
you it's somewhere but no it's not that
button oh you found
it
no I saw it cuz I saw a button but it
didn't know do anything I'm still
climbing there's another way I know
there's another way I think I'm going
into outer space
face is that just a joke like making
someone climb for like several minutes
like 10 minutes because they're thinking
oh there must be something up there that
is worth it and then up there there's
nothing minutes like 2 minutes a sign of
the smiley face but it might be 10
minutes in the end oh I found it oh I
remember it was like the the button
below from outside I'm about to jump
yeah yeah yeah okay met Gear Solid
reference yeah it is I was
it oh she after my own
heart Shez a tie up what the heck I can
see the whole Minecraft world is it flat
no it looks curved
actually like a real Circle honest to
goodness Circle that good to know Tower
still goes that high
though oh oh no no okay we got to water
funeral water there I thought there was
water I thought there was water too they
she put like a little thing in the
middle so that you fall and die instead
of land all the way at the bottom it's
okay I'm not that far prank skydiving
might have been more fun just a prank I
I didn't have anything important in my
inventory so don't worry okay I might
need some I guess we did have the ID cut
where we like put away stuff so
yeah uh today is your last day on the
Minecraft server but it reminds me like
back in the day you're like you were
creating all these super cool things on
the server you were you had a million
wats Watson Railways and you know I put
Watson Railways as a sponsor of Hol talk
all these years yeah yeah yeah Watson
Industries yeah yeah yeah that's true I
mean everybody make cool stuff though on
the Minecraft servers not just me really
consider sponsoring Holo
talk what is this room that's a big farm
yeah this is the indoor Farm
Boni I think I'll just take
everything people have this much she's
going to log in no she feels a
disturbance in the force R sack it R
sack it girls big potatoes for everyone
I need to eat no I should have stopped
them oh no I wasn't a part of this
that's what Farms are for to get food
so yeah you know just you know replant
little bit I'll just I'll just replant
it's so nice organized wow I remember
the early days of buoni was just
Stone I don't know if I'm planting the
right plant but hopefully
it she's going to
notice it's
fine we're
sorry I'm
not it'll be a nice thing to leave
behind yeah ravaging the
Fields all right just a prank bro yeah
there's a ton of rooms here that are
yeah this is like the back rooms Buon is
kind of like the back rooms of our
server honestly there's like gates to
the nether portal and and stuff here too
I remember
oops deeper down yeah
yeah I know I'm not going to go all the
way down there there's I know buaron is
huge yeah but I don't think we have to
go for in
detail let's keep her private rooms
private yeah what a legend I'm going
back to the rail I want to take the rail
into the the maina all right oh sorry
Kelly almost got you I love the rail
almost got me hopefully
they some mine carts I don't know there
never are mine carts no I think you
check the wrong they're always gone
people never put them back I like
walking on the rails honestly I like
honestly it's not too bad to walk yeah
as long as there's a path all good
there's a way
yeah walking slowly for the
legs the
statues yeah think for a nice walk I
have I'm listening to very chill jazz
piano music right now o you like
jazz yeah it feels nostalgic if you like
jazz you guys should listen even though
it's not maybe not perfect jazz but you
you guys should listen to the new myth
song The Show Goes On appar Cy tweeted
about our
Shenanigans oh no he knows oh there's
two mine carts two mine carts I found
anyone want to share I can wish we could
share oh everybody wants to Lo I'm
taking a mine cart
yeah be slowly I'm I'm I'm on
the no guys are blocking no I'm going to
go the other way no
wait that's what you get
I remember how surprised I was how there
was like addition to the rails and I'm
just like stop here but then I kep going
you have to get out you have to be
fast I lost many mine carts to that yeah
there's probably 20 mine carts at the
end of the
rail is being chased by a zombie
no I'll beat
him just punch him Waton punch him I'm
beating him
ow ow I'm dying oh sorry call you're
good push him off the edge yeah push him
off the Dark Souls method hold
on there we go nice dead I almost di
don't fall don't
fall okay single file single file I'm
walking weird Okay
ooh
Express what a great location for
advertisement is there a
potato why
not potatoes are
good especially baked potatoes that
could go for a big potato and now I can
mine cart yes wait no
wait get out of here before I get run
over wait wa wait for you guys to the
end dang it shoot my goodness you should
always stay ahead of her guys otherwise
she's going to drive away with the mine
cart she'll rattle us she'll rattle our
bones
she's getting away
oh my
[Music]
frogs frog update yeah
frog I wonder when we're getting the
next Minecraft
update no need for
sleep no need for Sleeps No I just
wanted to reset the spawn point oh
okay yeah these turned out really good
if you want
yes let's sleep okay oh I guess so
there's no pink so I'll take red orange
oh
okay nope denied I'm sorry there was no
purple am is the new orange oh or yellow
and orange are pretty close yeah true
enough all righty cute a rainbow brid
from
Ollie oh my God M oh my gosh the thing
that you and G Built yeah it looks good
the 7 hours
stream oh my god oh that one oh God
I 7 hours of blog placing it was it was
great it was my best that it was maybe
more enjoyable than the tunnel digging
maybe the tunnel
digging oh the original the first shop
the endless chickens that like one of
the first things I ever oh I guess
they're still there
free them from the usual room quick
while she's not
looking oh my are Gates still they can
jump over freed them free them I'm
trying Hey I set him free that's not how
you set them
free how do you set them free like
this no no that's not how you set them
free either they have not reached the
hybrid Phoenix status yet please don't
do that they can
yeah they eventually you know after some
fire trials they become hybrid phoenixes
and then they can die once only
one
interesting
die you bu a lot of stuff here K big
birdie yeah yeah was you know I'm not
building in Minecraft is not my favorite
thing but here and there a little bit
yeah who built the weird white Gumby
thing white G uh the the eel no it's not
eel need some eel and then the tennis
racket can't forget the tennis racket
tennis racket not a tennis
racket at least in the new server you
can't mistake my magnifying glass is a
tennis racket anymore true true is that
a Shader thing though no no oh there's
nothing wrong with it being a tennis
racket you can be proud of it o ena's
house which almost burned down
oh yeah the green corn dog that burned
down and then I just turned it into that
I saw it get stress by before the before
the Sakura update so like that pink is
just oh oh wait I thought it was Sakura
stuff no it was before that update so
it's just pink W I didn't so closely
yeah I was like I want a tree there but
then like I was like what if it turns
into like one of my Emos with the brain
I'm just like big brain constru I
seriously don't know what that is
in the sky is it like a Castle in the
Sky hot hot's Castle in the Sky it's
cool oh and the cake the cake and the
Ender Dragon egg oh Christmas
tree together the Christmas Tre our
first Christmas together I think it's
actually so well done the tree it's
pretty good we all Place different
ornaments
emotional
e yeah I'm going to put a green one
on we built a lot of stuff together wait
what date did we build this does anybody
have like the date the date the date you
know like day day go December
19th oh
actually 2020 actually I don't know I'm
guessing I'm guessing must have been
2020 they're saying December
21st
cute four years almost four years ago
wow it'll be four years ago this holiday
season yeah
M that's crazy they said December 18th I
was really close M I thought it was a
19th time
zones yeah it was a 19th and some time
zone mhm uh this is a hatama grave I
guess yeah one of the graves it's normal
to have a grave one of the gra there's
another there's other Graves over here
yeah from ID members
right my God
all the cats people die of they
[Music]
killed the wolf Farm nice all my wolf
Farm I
remember
Mo oh my gosh so
much yeah cool stuff Yow meow and then I
remember Kiara's uh ice bridge that went
to Phoenix y then me and G had the
abandoned Carnival o someone iron
abandon Carnival yeah yeah it's pretty
funny oh the iron farm good iron
farm really it's still
temporary it does it not work anymore
does it um there's some iron in there I
see guys in there like the Golems yeah
might be broken I'm not sure if the
update or something broke it or not I
remember updates like break some of the
Farms but we didn't come here often to
uhhuh yeah we are Community
chests weones building materials Etc we
were reallying our best best things only
the most luxurious things of course
before we F the nether dragon didn't we
stock up here yeah
yeah
yeah I don't want to go into nether it's
scary yeah
let's pass on the go see my house in
Callie's
house house I love this area so
memorable this whole myth area is so
memorable state is that wor yeah this is
my little bunker my little
cave yeah when you moved out of my place
sorry I was heartbroken you know sorry
about that you're accident To Go My Own
Way pretty unfinished but it was fun I
had a bath we bath myself cozy you know
it's cool painting you got image of Mr
yeah Mr Bones Mr steeds Mr steeds too I
had some good stuff in
here early Minecraft mommy house a
nostalgic mommy house I just have a
bunch of gifts in the middle of the room
yeah you never clean up what do you mean
I took stuff out of here oh look it's a
frog you gave
me thank you I think I did take
one I remember I remember one time you
almost burned your house down cuz there
lava
yeah but I I tamed it you tamed the
fire want to check out my potato farm
yes
potato potato potato looks good check on
it uh hold on I think it's this thingy
are you going to sell your house oh yes
it's working what's the market value of
your house not selling my house selling
it no in this a will die her proper she
wishes M what about it you could make
money no and use it on
wood on on the funeral cost no Minecraft
funeral
[Laughter]
please you're
silly I could buy your her house no okay
well she's going to squat here anyway
so if I see you doing anything to it on
stream I'm going to tell
staff I'm going to I'm going to tatt
tail okay well you have you I I would
think I would have more power over this
place than you at that point
uh-uh St will ban
you no that's true I heard I heard they
would do get in
trouble Phoenix I guess you want to go
to Phoenix well there's somebody can
ride with me a I got the
[Laughter]
boat oh shrimp
unbelievable when is there shrimp there
oh yeah the shrimp there's a cat who
built the
shrimp M me you built well yeah looks
good thank
you that's the giant shm that we were
talking about the abandon Carnival with
the unfinished Ferris wheel that doesn't
move it moves over here right oh yeah
great oh
yeah the villagers lives we were just
not so technically advanced yet couldn't
make it move right I want to see the car
gra
hard take but yes but nothing ah that
was Blended in ooh looks cool
camouflaged yeah there's like a haunted
mansion and there's like a fortune
telling room and then there's a chicken
Stall
oh yeahp Fried Chicken
stall yeah there's shooting range here
yeah there's a fox really finished but
if you shoot it you get gold oh a fox
made a home in there this was supposed
to be the underground fight club/
haunted house but it never came to be
and then here's
you're so proud of your petting zoo so
cute yeah my petting zoo look at the
skeleton don't we have a panda
in was a here where' it go or polar bear
rather this is a oh yeah polar bear
polar bear polar bear looks a little
weird polar bear a cow could be a panda
that be if you ever need a panda put a
cow
there I want to see the whole life sign
I think there's a good place to see it
from here kind of
what how do these Golems oh my God what
is this how did this happen oh yeah
sorry it's kind of like there so manys
in here yeah they responding for the
build that live close
[Music]
by oh my God it's kind of an iron farm
having a party down here oh an iron can
they beat me to death that' be so funny
if you hit one of those jum in there no
no don't do it I all my stuff though got
lot we don't need
two two
funerals there's a lot of them oh my
goodness yeah that's so funny then there
was this was this the fortune telling
room no please Al fortunes to the chest
oh yes Fortune room I wonder if we can
make them fight each other I don't think
[Music]
so feelings too help with this one
actually reply hazy try again you'll be
in a sticky situation soon can I go
again oh no wait are we supposed to ask
a question or something or is it just
you'll meet a super strong and cool
Reaper what o I think every want wait
does that mean I'm going to die run mine
says run run run run oh hey look there's
the dunk tank too the dunk tank was
prettyy cool oh oh yeah dunk tank was
pretty fun it works
dunk yeah the dunk tank might might have
been the best thing yeah for sure yeah I
get in the get in the chair see if we
can shoot
you Fire Away
[Music]
Ladies oh wait I'm going to drown I'm
going to
drown is this why you guys she actually
drownings I'm bullying the detective it
works it works oh I like
only that
works
Co yeah a oh yeah I think this is G
theme like the one of the only working
items here I think
yeah cool that's the abandoned Carnival
all right should we uh take the
minecart PPP to
PPP ooh yes yes P my favorite place
remember on Earth good old time it hard
carried us for
sure one person will have to walk
zombies allowed in
phoenixon don't let the zombie in a
there's a spider too don't let the
spider in oh there's so many spiders
have okay I don't we may need to run we
may need to run don't don't die you have
an elytra on you true I'm oh you got a
cat in your boat hold on I'll kick this
cat out
okay you're good okay we're good let's
hurry this abandoned Carnival's full of
thie get
in I'm in you do here
okay to slow rollers man did you hit it
I think it's okay
hen okay get out move okay
[Music]
wow being on the bridge and looking at
all this is
crazy right this such nice memory so
many years of Minecraft MH and
especially when there was just like five
of us like for us to have built what's
here is for five people that's like a
lot that is a
lot you know I I feel like um you know
now is super nice too but I do also miss
the old times when it was just us five
yeah the old days it was nice and cozy
yeah I think it's interesting to look at
our server compared to the other servers
our server is really uh spread out and
kind of we can be proud of it yeah we
have that's for sure call I'm coming I'm
coming she running all right we'll meet
up at P here I mean uh at the rail at
the rail okay at the rail okay I'm
coming yeah but our server definitely
had its Charisma its own style MH charm
something special all
right that's why I was clinging on to it
and never wanted to go to the Japanese
server even now I don't even have a
house and not oh wait I have a gifted
house from P S I think but oh gifted
house yeah but I never really used it
she could do that just gift you a house
there might be rails on the way no this
way I don't think so oh the tunnel
ah the nice beautiful
tunnel do you guys remember chat do you
remember this
stream all right everybody getting your
mine
carts oh oh thank you is it enough mine
carts yeah
oh I'll go first a CH wait I want to get
it hold
on start
wait wait I want to take a picture too M
Train ch ch ch
can you all look
up look up wait is it f but okay that's
fine the back of her heads are beautiful
too okay let's go how to go
W okay uh uh somehow okay hold W
hold you have to hold it the whole
time catch you by the way is there a
different B
let's just re re you just press W going
the right direction and then you hit the
red thing no the no the guard
no I've lost the last
two I can't see
them regained the
cart K you still
trying yeah I'm still trying to figure
out my inventory is full is the
problem Oh wait here thanks just go go
go we're winning I'm
winning you're definitely winning got to
speed up girl catch up to her if you
hold W you might go faster place it yeah
on the you press shift you might go
faster no that's not I I have the exit
the car not me
D exit is with tab okay how do I enter
it click
can't why can't I enter you my
heart what is it on the rail guys still
stuck I still don't
understand AIO
Kart I feel like we're going to end up
looping you girls you're going to get
off at the right stop right uh this one
ends I think or does it loop I think
this one has a stop stop I think it PPP
right
yeah can you imagine we we dug
this we dug this we
did big old T oh potato o
potato potato dropping potatoes for
your they're going right yeah I don't
think anybody can pick them up cuz we're
too
fast I'm picking them up but I'm leaving
more behind oh okay for the other that's
good that's good oh Big Ups I'll look
out for
them yeah you won't see them for like
another
to you never this is like the perfect
zadan section of Minecraft streams
that's true yeah yeah when we collabs
yeah yeah yeah we didn't get elytra for
a really long time yeah it took a
while yeah I don't know anything about
we made it yeah this one has a real stab
oh no it's going wait wait wait don't
you should get that cuz that's going to
no no no get out want to P it's going to
stop
me it's going to S them back in the
other direction no oh I see potatoes why
there so many potatoes on the
road get the you're on the way you're
almost stop hitting it stop hitting it
stop oh I can see light the other tunnel
key I'm not even there yet you're far
from being there oh maybe not maybe I
saw something
else oh oh hi hi oh it worked okay
okay so who lost their potatoes that was
mine you want them no it's okay they're
raw
yeah but I'm going to eat him
anyways I have faked
potato one oh there move out the way
move out of the way out the way we don't
want to send her back
by after her oh wait there was still
quite a way to
gole it it keeps going it Loops all the
way around we could probably take it
back after uh I have more mine carts I'd
love to take it back yeah you set my
spawn oh good idea
let's
go here's a p oh think I I think I broke
the music thing once somewhat recently
AKA in the past one year or so and I'm
not sure if it was fixed it broke it did
you release
the uh I think they changed the order or
something oh I think fix no do thing
still work I won't know until the this
little guy in there walks on the thingy
do
something do
[Music]
something come on
move oh he's so cute look at him with on
his little
chick hi buddy what you doing buddy I
guess they never grow huh he's like
stuck like
this
forever oh you know what this reminds me
of this PPP reminds me of our um PPP and
one block yeah oh the one that you had
to rebuild four
times that was a challenge that like a
speedrun of this PPP build oh it works
yeah you guys heard that
right sounded Right video game There's a
Zombie all the
explosions I remember all the hours
spent here fishing exp Gathering um now
there's there's a lot of useful Farms
that are over there like
uh the there's another Farm uh what is
it fauna's farm
[Music]
and yeah they really tried and farm too
yeah see in the distance they really
optimized a lot the new folks really
brought a lot of new stuff yeah oh be
I'm my
cake there's not really that much to see
here yeah no I'm in no isn't this your
Fishinger yeah I think I made it
with yeah yeah
yeah all those
Fishers I'm going to catch a
shark you're going to need a bigger
boat oh you did catch a ow you actually
H me let's go to thear you go she's on a
leash how did she Escape those aquarium
she was literally there
yesterday put her back she reminds you
of uh what is it I didn't know you could
actually hook someone yeah that's what I
was doing in one block when you guys
were getting hit by those little guys
that make you float I was catching
people with the fishing rod
C hey there's another cake what was our
deal with cakes here uh I built this a
lot of them I don't know what maybe for
a birthday stream or something I'm not
sure yeah I have some faint memory
even though I
don't get stitches by the way that's
kind of that's kind of ding what the
snitches get stitches oh does it say
that there oh who put that there that
surrounded by thorny voice like
something M would do it does seem like a
m thing it
does yeah chat is saying probably
B oh dear what happened who hurt her
all you guys ready there's not really
much to see here we could just take the
cart all the way back around yeah okay
okay I don't remember where the old rail
the other rail goes so I'm kind of
excited to see this goes all the way
back to the beginning maybe I think
there's a stop at uh buoni somewhere you
take that one good okay we looking for a
specific wyomi back then I don't
remember what the point
[Music]
B byebye me
bye were we looking for some specific
one or get in get in get in oh I had my
own card well
go here you take my card I okay too
late wait what if I stopped here in the
middle just keep holding W oh they
looking for an ey spy on
me where are you GA what were you
looking for any anyway like I mean a
place to build but were you looking for
a specific like biom wait where wait
wait we were building this
tunnel what was the did I propose the
tunnel of course you did this one no not
this one the previous one we were going
to the ocean to
build the coral the Coral Place yeah
yeah no but the first tunnel that we
built it was because you found an area
to put Atlantis I think right yeah it
was the ocean that's where I put
PPP yeah
yeah a we were trying to connect to that
uh-huh Cuz the spawn point and the ocean
was kind of far and we could have just
gone straight if we had the coordinates
but we just made all kinds of Curves and
turn I mean we were all kind of new to
Minecraft
you know I remember like coming in
watching Minecraft streams and she'
always be counting till like 8 1 2 3 4 5
6 78 1 2 3 4 that's number you need for
the rails okay that was the ideal number
true
true yeah it's
efficiency oh there it is this is the
bunker onlyi stop there's a
a what sorry it's okay what the doing
sor
there's a sheep in the cart now what the
heck there's a lot of carts oh no
they're going back got to stop him wa
get out are we supposed to keep going
get out it's still going no we can get
out
here yeah we can get out oh no it's
going is this the other tunel
momentum I'll put all these carts back
at the other uhoh
there oh did they go this is the bueron
St walk is good for you know
and then you keep going and you go back
to the
original train I see the Minecraft movie
trailer oh yeah I saw it what did we
think that works I guess wait is it IRL
I'd like
to forget about it sometimes it is it is
both IRL and animated I guess okay yeah
I don't really oh I didn't watch it I
need to there it goes dang it hey where
where are you guys guys we're at the
bunker only stop oh I thought is that
where we're getting off no I'm going to
keep going I thought going I want to
keep going too push me push me push me
push me push me oh
boy you know save
me oh no
stop it never okay there's a there's a
gap here so it stops now automatically
wait oh no I did I did can't push
anything it just happened all right get
out get out get out it's fine I have
more cards we should just walk oh
oh okay ooh it's snowing that's
pretty a walk sounds nice walk in the
snow just keep on going where you don't
want them to
go there now there's a
stop nice
Sor right okay let's walk yeah I'm going
to take the car I don't care I'm
in byebye you guys want a scared me
there's another
one I'm going to jump in this
one oh no I'm going back again no
something pushed me back oh she going to
she going to pump into
us always be Loop
R get out of the way oh is it of the
Cur bye girl is this the
original incoming I don't know where C
is this is the original hole I'm right
behind you oh there it is right there
now it's that train station yeah call
you're close too I see you
underground and there she
is we're
backy oh that's where that connects
yeah what whoa mind is to know the
tunnel is still a fever dream As It Ever
Was yeah we escape though should we go
back to the JP server or something sure
sure yeah let's go back let's go whoa
now
she's hooked to Phoenix this time I'll
come willingly very
willingly oh sorry hey he don't wait why
are we going back aren't we building
your grave my what
oh no not going to build a Minecraft
grave for
me is it is a little messed up but
there's other
Graves why don't we build something fun
together like a garden or something wake
got to made fun I mean I already have a
statue here you can put like rip on it
or something if you
[Laughter]
want instead of the 2024 we put r
hey but if we build one last thing
whatever it is I feel like we should
build it here not on the Japanese
server uh okay okay well what I mean we
could have a boat but that's what I
think but you girls can change the boat
whatever I do worry about um I do worry
about what's going to happen to This
Server I would like people to be able
think this going to be connected to
anything after the big update so depends
to see what we
build that's
true a lot of things are going to be
lost that's really sad yeah why can't we
keep it I mean we are keeping it we we
still have access to it it's just won't
be like connected to like the total
server and stuff that's
fine I'll leave it up to you guys
happening no they'll keep it connected
why not yeah no they can't get rid of
this I mean what would be the reason
they run out of money to host a server
like no they're not getting rid of it
all the way like I'm sure they'll keep
it it's just won't be connected to like
the total server and stuff is what I'm
thinking it's history it's a
museum yeah I want Generations far in
the future to be able to see this if
they won't
yes okay so we're not building a grave
whatever we
building we'll be good what what what
what could
represent should we try to uh uh attempt
to build the myth logo or so think
that's a little too complicated the bus
stop seems super tough the bus stop a oh
yeah yeah cute I like a bus stop should
get some sand blocks to build the fake
desert or so little I said we can go to
the desert biome cuz I know I think
there's a way to get to a desert biome
in like the shared server that Kyla
built it was like a rail s where hat
like we have sand over where you know
all right we'll find it build it over
there anywhere okay I think we'll have
better materials over there in the other
server what there oh that's what you
mean with there okay no you want to put
it over
there what you you just
all right I'm going this
[Laughter]
way wherever I'm just very um attached
to the Ian server yeah it's full of
beautiful memories but we can always
make new ones new places too oh
oh oh sorry okay back to JP yeah where
can we get sand there's got to be like
some oh Kyla's
uh thingy place
Kyla resources I I get lost here so
easily uh me too where is anything oh
there it is I see it the block the block
yeah the big block with
the pickaxe maybe she has some
sand this s looks crunchier to me I
don't know
why you guys see that I wonder if it's
cuz it's heav crunchy crunchy what kind
of crunch
uh like a really crisp crunch really
crispy crunch crispy wafer crunch
getting hungry you guys know if fauna
finished her
tree she's still working on it I
think what in that always scares
me what is
that all right let's see what we got
kylo monsters in there
armor ky's got everything
[Music]
Quest
boo diamonds all this stuff is on the
second floor she's got a lot of Soul
Sand but that's not quite what we're
looking for yeah
uh there must
be there's a lot of glass but no sand
dirt no wa there's one sand block come
on well
maybe I don't know if she has any sand
here a lot of other blocks
though do you guys have
elytra yeah yeah oh my Ender box I think
girl uh no but
but in I can get one in my nether box
okay here I have I have an Ender Chest
over or she has one in there Ender oh
yeah yeah yeah I'm going to my
house okie dokie what I found some end
rods that I think will look really good
at the bus stop oh cool okay yeah that
could be good for the bus sign yeah the
sign is there end chest here where is
the Ender I have one in my house if you
guys come to the magnifying glass
I don't know where put
[Music]
my oh if you leave Kyla's thing and then
you look to the right if you see a
circle in the
distance
circle
circle I see
moies I see
it God that tree is huge oh with big
scary eyes oh I see a circle
oh looks like a bubble
yeah yeah oh that's that's the new
tennis racket
no you see it with shaders it looks
really
cool oh yeah yeah let's
[Music]
see oh nice it's got a little
yeah it's more like a bubble now
cute
no magnifying
glass it looks like one of those soap
bubble soap blowy thingies we bubble
blower you're just saying that you don't
[Music]
know oh I have one elytra I wonder where
my actual elytra is
isn't that sand oh maybe it is made of
sand but we're not going to break apart
on his house to make a bus you imagine
uh thinking that we just fly in a
direction until we find sand biome I'm
in okay remember where we are right now
might be dangerous but I mean that's
Adventure I will say my elytra isn't
very repaired so I can't fly too far
there's camels in this game there's
camels oh yeah is
when um last update I
think
a yeah I can't find my actual elytra
somewhere that's good if you have a
backup that's
good I just have like one
elyra wait are we also building it there
or are we just getting sand uh I figured
we just build it there okay I have 55
sand I have oh okay we can find a spot
to
build yeah I feel like 50 is pretty big
block we just kind of make it look like
there's a little sand pit yeah everybody
is saying uh you should read a letter
that Aqua Senai wrote for you ah I did
see it on stream oh okay she saw it
already yeah she looked at it on her
stream M there you go oh mov owls creepy
let me see if I have any more
sand I might have more in my house here
I have three blocks of
sand here I'll give you a lot of sand
where you at am I'll give you the blocks
I have I'm I'm by the firework vending
machine there's a firework vending
machine need them it's by the Gat are
these are these one there's different
levels yeah but this one's just one
which is the preferred one for most
people anyway oh okay by the beetle
right is it near the
beetle yeah the Portal's by the beetle I
think
yeah
wo okay I remember how to fly good good
good well I guess if we have enough sand
we don't really need to fly anywhere but
ah oh okay that's also good there you go
just need to find a spot to build when
the Sun is up
thank you okay I'm going to go home and
check if I have more standand I feel
like I did cuz I I needed a lot of glass
so okay I think we'll just need a
shovel what are we going to build a
bench with wood uh yeah I have I have uh
some wood here I'm building stairs for
the
bench awesome wonder if this is enough
[Music]
fireworks sounds kind of
therapeutic vending machine oh you're
listen yeah sorry I was kind of like
endlessly taking them cuz it's free like
what a deal yeah why not free fire let's
go you don't take all of them cuzz I
don't know somebody needs to replenish
them at some point well barely anybody's
been playing besides FAA
so even it's not a high demand right
even Japanese girls yeah okay well if
anybody ever needs to refill it you just
have to dig a hole like you dig one
block and you'll be able to access under
the button
oh cool what where do you dig like this
I can't I can't so it's not a firework
maker no just a
dispenser I don't have a I don't have a
pickaxe so I can't dig it but underneath
here underneath the button you should be
able to access
it okay well uh do you want to like uh
en
enclose it somehow with like glass or
with a fence or how what you want the
vending machine oh the no the bus stop
no doesn't need to be in close you just
can put uh I say flowers but you need
grass I think for flowers so I mean I
have a lot of glass I have lanterns I
thought lanterns could be cool kind I
have 64 sea lanterns if you want to use
it oh I I brought some lanterns I I have
a regular Lantern and I have four sea
lanterns cool I have like almost two
stacks of sea lanterns if you need it oh
okay uh should I bring some glass go the
sand yeah I don't know any need glass I
wasn't planning to encase it or anything
M I can bring a glow item for you I
don't know if you want to put anything
the desert is vast after all okay glow
item I'll put my light for there it'll
be like break for
emergencies needed a shovel right yeah
bring my good sh how you doing my throat
is HTS you throat hurs yeah it is that
time of year tea tea time tea time
I'm so excited that it's getting colder
I've been drinking tea now too
again my lungs have been drying up so
thank God for that yeah that's
good are you guys excited for the hot
season to be over yes I really I did
that in order to you know feel like a
human being an nor
Reaper actually like After experiencing
the summer for the full like full
duration is not too bad also there too
bad not too
bad fall I don't know about you fall and
it was hot and sticky but I don't think
it was like
a as bad as I
expected yeah everybody's got their
favorite
season still like winter yeah winter
let's
go what are we looking for right
we're waiting for en oh okay there was
just a lot of uh zombies here so oh no
ol she really wanted to be part of this
clam sweet Ollie I'm kind of scared to
ELA cuz I would lose a lot if I die
but this is the way maybe this is the
way have you seen this have you guys
answered these questions no you can
press this button and answer a question
or no get a question and then you answer
it and you say true or false then you
hit this button
exciting okay you go first
[Laughter]
Kiara uh this is an easy one question
are you human
no true it works it works how does it
know okay mine is do you wear no
underwear I don't want to answer
this do I wear no under all right does
no underwear are you
Commando wait what was your lie what was
your
answer huh did you say yes you you do
wear no underwear or no you do no I
thought that it meant false as in like I
do not wear oh never mind you guys have
to return your questions here at this
box no it's a lie because it's you
thought it was a statement not a
question yes right okay
okay m is are you an enemy does that
mean you to
answer
no
true so far pretty trustworthy this
thing wait where do we put I'm not
getting any question this up this one up
here this box the one that's up this
Barrel it says
return someone else of questions think
it's a reference to S s's like
are you a te are you an enemy or a
friend okay shall we decide on a place
yeah where should it be somewhere around
the tree or somewhere behind the tree
or guess the tree is kind of where all
the ends are kind of I should it be by
your house oh yeah by your house would
be nice yeah well why I yeah I guess
it'd be nice to have a bus stop pretty
close by that way I can oh the house
price is going
up increasing the value well she's not
sing so Prime
realate I guess it doesn't matter huh oh
so far oh all the shade where you going
can I fly through it there oh nice
there's no glass yeah I made it so you
can fly through it and land in imag
there was glass
ouch but now even more so I think it's a
bubble soap blowy thingy
if it's if there's no glass then yeah
magnifying glasss
stop all right how about here there's
like a little uh area that we can turn
into like deserty SL ground all right
you dig and I'll I'll place the sand
here I'll give you guys sand how far do
I have to dig who here somebody take
some sand somebody take some sand I took
it
we'll just replace this floor area like
this oh Kelly don't she's digging a hole
she's digging a
hole we have enough yeah we'll like
centered it around here in this little
shelf then we replay the music don't let
me dig a hole I'll go
crazy wow
nostalgic it's not a grave okay
something it's not a grave it's just a
bus stop yeah just a bus
[Music]
stop nothing else why are you digging
this whole thing out I don't know aren't
we supposed to put sand there uh have
that
sand
oh why didn't you say that you put it
that way I put some box maybe not
just a bus stop just a bus probably get
of this yeah do you want some sea
lantern o sea lantern good idea here
I'll replace this
one I want to put sand there and then
there and there and
there do we have materials for the bench
yeah I have
some good
well it might be kind of hard cuz it's
not really straight but I guess I'll put
it against the sand
wall wait how do you make a bench again
like
this yeah yeah looks like a bench to Me
Maybe with a fence on the
side okay I have one I brought one
nice nice nice that looks good oh yeah
that looks like the yeah yeah
[Music]
it
taller mind if I play some end
rods yeah I think that'll make it pretty
oh the sign oh nice I can't this is like
a
buop I wish it was a little bigger I was
going to make it here oh you put the
sign up there on that oh okay on the
below it I'm going to put the lantern
over
here oh nice yeah I don't think I can
put it on the End Rod so I'll put it
here that
work make this a little bit
taller why is it raining for
hours it's
raining becauseit is
rain is
rain I mean it's also it's also candy
candy does anybody have one more block
of sand no I do yeah yeah yeah right
here okay yeah right here right this one
yeah and this
one that's good wait wait wait and this
one yeah wait wait and this one okay
this is my last one oh
[Music]
okay I mean I can come back later too
with more sand and fill it in yeah yeah
this this back area looks kind of
we have very limited
resources nice oh yeah I guess it right
here a small
bench can we make it a free seater uh
yeah I have
more there we
go how's that we can squeeze into a free
seater maybe oh all of us yeah oh you
got to wait where the clock buess with
me a clock we can wait with you oh here
I think a clock I wish that there was a
better way to make a clock oh there we
go oh oh it stopped
raining oh it looks like a clock yeah
it's unintentional but it works oh
cute he can I even turn there we go
awesome all right H I wonder what time
it
is I'm in time I'm in time oh photo time
oops
oh maybe we can stand in the back of the
bench yeah I'll stand
here wait let me sit in
the there
go maybe I'll get a little closer hold
on sorry yeah there we go what's this
bus stop called the
station uh the um
way way I like so you got to straighten
out straighten out no when somebody asks
which way does this bus go you say the
the
[Music]
okay
wow I don't I don't have a screenshot of
thing but it's on the stream beautiful
bus
stop yeah thank you a bunch of make sure
to decorate it more when we have more
resources yeah you guys can come back
and add more that be cool yeah yeah I
want to make it nice yeah
okay even
sandier now what it should
be what do you want to do what I'm going
to put my stuff
away but uh I'm probably gonna log off
online or log on offline that way
because I there's something I wanted to
finish so I'll
wait are they you mean are they letting
you like
enter forever or no just means today or
tomorrow yeah it'll be yeah uh something
I want to do today or
tomorrow okay unless I mean they
probably won't know just
kidding you could sneak on we'd help you
by not saying
anything we'll see Secret
I should have enough time to finish
everything I
think okay Many Adventures should we go
back to our detective or our
office our office oh yeah oh yeah I M
sure yeah totally let's totally Walk
This Way in Minecraft which is the
direction of the office ha guys oh go
ahead of me I'll watch you go go
on the
office go inside it and then sit down in
front of oh we got there so fast w wow
so fast that took no time at all
crazy I'm going to
realign stand up please do please
do let me stand
properly somewhere
here yeah yeah oh maybe now I look too
[Music]
tall okay yay back in
prison it's not prison it's an
interrogation
I feel like I got to get my photo taken
with the plaque I'm
holding PL plaque plaque oh with my name
in the
front they at my heart oh yeah well yeah
you're you're not you're not being held
against your will you've not been
arrested so you don't have the the
number okay it's
fine good for my mug shot then it
my it's just I those are the only chairs
I have in my office right now so that's
fine they'll
do they'll do so as that was our last
Minecraft mythcraft collab mythcraft
mythcraft o I don't like saying that
yeah sounds feel good sounds
crummy
yeah I wish there was a better way to
say yeah it might not be though
M mining my mine my my mine mine my mine
my
mine yeah it doesn't really work not I'm
not coming up with anything I'm coming
up short it's
okay so well well well we've been
through a lot yeah but I you know I I I
do hope that I did have a good talk with
um you know staff and stuff so I think
think that you guys will see me again
for some type of project and if you have
me so you know it's not completely the
end of goodbye and we are going to see
each other in person again because I
would like to say hi to you guys
whenever you guys are going to do
something special maybe I could stop by
um not on stream though probably not on
stream thank you well we'll see always
welcome thank you we'll keep in touch
right yes yes it's hard I I think it's a
I'm really
bad at messaging people and stuff but
I'll try my best to I think I'll see a
lot of stuff that will remind me of you
guys and I'll send you little images and
memes and gifts and things that I
find I'm going to spam you it's going to
get annoying yeah yeah I never
mind since this is the well you
know well this is the last my G right so
can I ask you for some words for our
continuing
Journey maybe some well
wishes okay I think you guys I hope you
guys already know how special you each
are and um you know we were all picked
for a reason
and I think it was really really cool to
get to know all of you guys and see how
how kind you guys are and your
personalities is they're so sweet
and each everyone in in myth is so
different but I really like that we can
get together and just relax and laugh
and you know just talk sometimes
not really but you know shoot the
kind of thing yeah but um for your
future endeavors and uh and whatever it
is that you end up doing I know you guys
are going to be successful because you
all work so hard and you're you have
unique talents that pretty much only you
know you who you are can accomplish in
the only way you know how I know
everybody says I'm a way but you guys
each have your own way of doing things
so I look forward to always seeing your
success and I'll always be cheering for
you and like I said it's not going to be
the last you hear of me so well we'll
have other things I'm sure we'll do
together soon I think coming out
soon well detective thank you for
investigating us yeah big up of course
it was the most fun
investigation yeah
mhm we're going to do stuff
together
yeah I don't know is is like it's like
such a it's it's like a it is a big
shift though it's it's Uncharted
Territory for sure I don't know I guess
going through the the Minecraft servers
like brought up so many so many memories
it's crazy and you see the date slapped
on some of that stuff like 2021 2020 and
then you realize like wo we've all been
through so much
together yeah it feels like it was
yesterday though those memories are so
vivid to me it's so weird cuz it feels
like we've been doing this for like I
mean I said this in my tweet too it's
like it feels like we've been doing this
for so long but at the same time it
feels like we saw it just yesterday yeah
it went by fast at the same time feels
like a lifetime M
yeah yeah had no idea would turn out
this way you know like I don't know all
of us doing so many like amazing things
and following our own paths you know
yeah
but I'm glad I'm glad we all got to do
all kinds of stuff together too too you
know yeah yeah and I know it can seem
like the end or any or something like
that but I don't I have hope that uh
we'll be able to continue to do stuff in
the future some way somehow definitely I
want to know what I'm is going to do
next oh what am I going to do next uh
the next investigation the next case
well I think the next case is going to
involve cleaning my room because my off
his space I've been throwing wires
around you know rushing to find some
things that I think I lost but uh yeah
cleaning is going to be the first to
step
nice yeah well wherever your next
investigation takes you I'm going to be
watching I can't let you out of my sight
oh thank you yes you're always looking
over me protecting me making sure you
don't die it's the one thing I can
really do right I'm sure
awesome good luck out there detective
thank you I will be watching you guys
with my no longer my magnifying glass
but maybe like a telescope something
that uh what do pirates use they use
like the telescope yeah yeah it's a
telescope like
binocular yeah
yeah okay yep oh uh
spy glass that's good spy glass yeah say
something other things
what yes uh you
want something no no
nothing I let my cat
[Laughter]
speak the cats are saying
love love
I want to meet
cats see they want to meet me too
they're going to they heard you they
heard you speaking on the other
[Music]
end all right then the investigation
will be wrapped up real
no investigate me
more I will I'm going to watch with my
spy
glass mhm
yeah can't use your magnifying glass
that's too close yeah too too close I
don't want you to see those things you
see the pores on my
face count each strand on your head
please no
I'm going to start finding gray hairs
pretty soon I'm looking for the peach
fuz
no all right
so end no don't end it we're going to do
stuff together St it's not you know it
is I could see why it can be sad but um
you know part of the reason why it's not
being called just aive graduation is
because there will be some projects
where we'll be able to do some things
together in the
future
yeah yeah
yeah there
thereare D
dare dare just kind
weird not doing I'm just trying to give
you like a head pad or something Jesus I
don't know I didn't want to cover G so
oh we cover up
Ena dang it there's no winning there's
no
winning well we're going to miss you I
know you didn't want this to be sad but
we're going to miss you I'm going to
miss you guys
too well we we still we'll still have
our group chats and things you
know yeah yeah I mean we're the lucky
ones right we get to still hit you up
and whatnot but yeah and I'm sure Kara
you know if you ever have any Tech
problems with your you know home 3D or
whatever I'm just a message
away well I wish you the best of luck
thank you and I hope you'll be watching
our streams
always we'll be observing you too and
not the scuffy ones if you ever need us
you offering your help to us but we also
I think want to help off for our help to
you if you ever eat anything we're here
thank you thank
you yeah yeah you guys are the first
ones that go to if I if I need advice
for some stuff which I think I already
have asked you guys for some advice on
some things so thank you you'll always
have a space here got your
back there'll always be a gap for you
thank you wait a what a gap Oh I thought
you said a dab I don't know what a dab I
don't
know dab for let's go everyone dab
for oh thank you thank you for creating
so many cool memories and opportunities
and collabs and projects for us thank
you for always gluing us together not
just myth but all of again thank you for
being the one
normal human
human the one say sound I'm human yeah
yeah yeah
whatever sure she
is now we needed a a a sound sane mind
like you to bring us together thank you
excuse me no no no stop trying I shall I
shall now take over as the you have
tentacles what not my fault tentacles
what are those ears huh they're just a
little longer than the
normal ear
noral you are Shrek ears I don't have sh
you don't even have
ears me yeah well they're somewhere
there I don't see them I don't see them
what do you think my earrings are
holding on to I don't know your hair
your hair no they're there they're just
I have fluffy 80s hair okay
yeah okay I
I thank you guys too I mean I know
obviously it's in a big focus on me but
nothing could be we couldn't have done
what we did um you know to if we weren't
together as myth so we each
filled different spots that we were
missing and together we became like
complete and we we did we all did stuff
that neither of us could do in a sense
so so you know together we worked so
well so thank you thank you guys for uh
letting me experiment so much and going
along with the crazy last minute rushed
ideas even if it turned out a little bit
scuff it always worked out in the in the
end and you guys helped a lot and we're
really patient to thank you thank
you you're
welcome I do it again
anytime again and again anytime
thank you for creating whole life
English with us no you guys too thank
thank you it's been a long road but you
know roads they path they you the paths
they go in different directions and
stuff and yeah it's just it's just the
bus
stop this is really long bus Journey you
know don't say that dang it f
[Music]
f yeah
well
man I I I don't know man I could like
stall forever
but sorry I'm useless now that's
okay all right thank you so much to
no
no thank you to the kfp to takachi the
dead beats and of course teammates
thank you guys I hope we will continue
to support each other as in the other
fan bases and continue to watch all of
the talents of course and I look forward
to you know whenever we get even more
new additions into en and continue to
support them as well so thank you so
much for supporting all of us and myth
yeah thank you thank
you thank you I don't even know how to
close I
mean oat smth for yeah Cara are you
ready will you count us down for an
o no
no you got you got no no come
on come
on no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
that's still that's I'm I'm keep on
thinking this is like the
[Music]
last you never
know you never
know I have to spit out some more
F it's good to to hold on to hope for
things in the future I think something
landed on girl's
shoe oh oh later sorry what were you
saying Callie huh oh uh gosh what was I
saying I think it's important to hold on
to hope for for later I guess yeah I
mean this is kind of a first time it's
happening so you know yeah you never
know I know I told you know um I did
have a meeting and I told them like hey
I'm open for anything you know if you
guys want me to come back for whatever
I'm down for it so um yeah we got a
pester staff and be like
hey sneaking I'm here maybe if you want
sure I'm sure we can we can pester staff
enough to bring back to some things I
mean we've been doing that for Ping
stuff for four years got pretty good at
it right yeah I'm sure I'm sure they can
work something out M I feel hopeful you
know
yeah yeah we got good at that
hard-headed people here Cara you going
to count us down to
otth no no I know it's hard to
do no no no you have to force
me okay what comes after
zero what what comes after two no wait
one what comes after one m
no okay how about we we'll do this I can
start and then uh we'll end with Kiara
I'll go five Ed can go four G can go
three k can go two Kiara will go one say
one you'll never say one and then we all
say one together and then we say
ultimate okay okay all right
five
[Music]
four three
two do I have to say
it
ready it's so nice of you guys to wait
for me
I'm can't do it you can do it you can do
it you can do
it one and a
half 1 and
[Music]
3/4 is that going up wait
shoot no is not my strong suit
that sounded like a one to
me no this was definitely
close
but am will always be your
number one one
to
me thank you yeah thank you guys for
watching thanks guys thank you we'll
catch you later all right goodbye
everybody Amy by everyone thanks thank
you see you detective yes we'll see
you
byebye bye
okay
okay me too me too I want to go too yes
yes come here get in
here yes yes yes go not in front dang
sorry sorry sorry there we
go yes yes
yes it's going to be okay
yeah we'll see you guys later thank you
for everything for the you know last
four years and so as well thank you
everybody all right I have a members uh
on archived karaoke stream coming up
soon so I will schedule that right away
and thank you myth again uh I'm really
glad we got to do this together so thank
you thank you thank
you all right byebye you're welcome it
later Detective
[Music]