foreign
[Music]
you could be like
out that's cute
that's cute I'm gonna steal it
it's almost
oh wait I didn't even tweet out I I was
too fast because we were just talking
um I was out I made this sound uh oh and
then good I was like oh and that was
like she probably doesn't doesn't know
what that sounds like to me oh so I was
trying to explain the words that's like
the sound of a really old messenger it
was either I used to kill or some other
old messenger and she was like what's
Isaac and I'm like oh my God that what a
Zoomer I'm such a boomer she's such a
Superman
I was like he said dialed what is that
a what is like AOL dial is that the same
thing I guess you know what maybe it's
also like a regional thing maybe I stick
you wasn't used that much in other
regions because yeah the thing that you
mentioned AOL I've I think I've heard of
it but I don't really
I think that was not really common in my
in my area yeah
maybe I'm not a boomer well
there was one more uh what was the other
the other message that was popular
during yeah
oh my God you don't understand not
really I think I know Skype more than I
know MSN
and and and what was what was those you
remember those like old video video
chatting services like ooVoo was that
one
oh
I don't know that one but I know others
I guess
I'm waiting for Chad to say yes I
remember that girl you're not crazy I
remember those those like
um those those online chat rooms where
everyone would like log in with their
webcams and then you then like mostly
teenagers and then they would all have
their webcam on and they would be like
five or ten in one room or so yeah what
was that what was that is that something
like that there was another one I called
like tiny chat is that what it was
called tiny chat chat party oh wait the
one I was thinking it was I guess Omegle
was one of those two I think oh my God I
remember I remember
Omegle people still used Omegle for a
while right
for the videos
oh you know
I was just thinking I kind of want to do
like a chat room like YouTuber Edition
where we go and chat relay as a YouTuber
or our video and then
um
[Laughter]
interest right so you you add whole life
as you're interested in you then you're
like obviously this will be cut this
will not be live stream
I was gonna say oh that's a one-way
ticket to yeah Bay world if you do it
live but
true that could be that could be funny
to do yeah and like a like a edited
definitely edited videos cut everything
out that's yeah bye of course yes well
oh that was a nice introduction talk
would you like to go to sleep once yeah
[Music]
maybe I have one I don't have one zombie
oh what's this where are you up
on my way to my home
yes what are we doing today
I mean I have it on my screen and I
think Google has it on her screen too
we're building this little Monument
pixel art Monument of ourselves from the
song cover we did together called
aikotoba
yeah
have you guys listened to it I love you
when did we do that was that like a
month ago two months ago
oh
it feels not so long ago but time passes
so quickly so I guess it was over a
month ago maybe already
my goodness wow wow wow wow wow well if
you haven't listened to it guys everyone
absolutely who everyone who has listened
to it absolutely loved it so you're
missing out on something it's on my
channel by the way so check it out
stream Sparks
I heard James Sparks names
all right so we both have some kind of
like help open on the side uh where
um we can kind of see which blocks we're
supposed to use yes and and most of it
is wool and I already have pretty much
everything honey do you have what you
need no not yet I'm collecting all right
we also need to figure out hi gouda holy
diamond
hmm
[Music]
what was I saying oh yeah we need to
figure out where to build this thing too
oh I need some of this thank God Ina
made these yeah I was actually
I was actually
um for a few hours uh I was I was
camping here kind of a okay to make it
produce more
um so that we have enough of everything
and I was uh most of the time was I was
AFK and I was I was in another room and
I was watching Netflix and then after a
while like I completely forgot about the
fact that I was AFK in here but I after
a few hours I I realized wait a second
wait a second wait a second if I don't
sleep for a long time then the Phantoms
will show up and and oh
you by now because it's been hours and
probably I would be dead by now and if I
was dead then I probably already lost my
items oh my God like it instantly came
to me so I ran over to my to this room
to the office and I looked and I was
actually I was in the middle of being
attacked by Phantoms I was still very
much alive but it was happening how many
you must have had like eight
no it was only free but oh okay I came
on the right moment thank God even
though it already has been hours I
thought I would already be dead by long
[Music]
thank God that was definitely really
nervous for a moment
um
yeah we should replace the uh the shears
afterwards I was because I made a lot of
shares but then I was like where do I
actually put them I wasn't sure because
there's an item popper do I put it in
there ah I think you put it in the
what
what oh
uh there's like a uh
I don't think
I think you maybe put in the dispenser
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think so maybe not
I'm sure Chad knows though
okay I made it a lot and then I wanted
to put in there but I put them back in
my storage so I'll do that later all
right
I'm almost ready do you have a packed
eyes cause I got a ton for you
packed ice no I don't have any wait
actually I'm not sure do I have guys do
I have pack guys or do I have the other
eyes which eyes do I have do you have
any eyes are there any adults bunny oh I
do need eyes oh yeah but I have a lot
because I went on a little trip to some
Icy area to choose to some ice spikes
and uh I got a lot so um yeah I have
black guys come on with some
[Music]
time
a big chicken I'm still I'm still using
my no no not the big chicken that's just
the decoration
to my old house uh I'm still oh
up up
yeah I still have to build finished
building every time I look at the the
half-built shark house I'm like
have you ever been in here yeah a while
ago I don't know Kelly used to sleep in
here too right yeah yeah yeah anyway
I'll come back in here and this one and
this is what a lifetime ago take as much
as you need oh thank you thank you we
probably need oh wait I can it should
say until the one that I sent you to say
how much you need does it
uh in the other one that I said you need
you need one stack plus 20 blocks oh
okay nice
you're not prepared hello this is the
first time I'm building something like
this yeah me too I've seen like
sometimes build it like I remember
watching us
before I build something
yeah they've built so many of these
pixel arts over there in their server
their masters on it yeah
okay where are we building
a good question so you have all your
materials yes I have enough to start
definitely okay
well it should be a big flat area but we
don't really have much of that so
you want to build it up at the oh God ah
yeah I was thinking
um filming it like on top of a mountain
or so and then after it's done getting
rid of the mountain so that it's like
floating would be cool because then you
could always eat it up in the sky
well
um there's a big mountain yeah this one
the one the one over here by
you know this one over here
what you want which one I know all the
mountains oh yeah I forgot food places
wait wait wait wait wait there I'm gonna
take some food that I put in there by
the way you were I watched the clip of
you eating the cookies and it was so
cute because I put them in there for you
guys to eat it obviously you need to
share chest but you kept them being like
can I take one coffee no yeah just take
all the goddamn cookies and eat them all
it makes me happy but you were like I
don't know
I'm so sorry
next time I'm taking without asking you
you were you were just asking yourself
you weren't even asking me because I
wasn't there but you just
of course you're allowed to take the
goddam n key I'm sorry
and then we're so low on HB and hearts
and everything you should have eaten way
more cookies than that please just give
me the cookie
we have
well first of all how do we get up there
I don't know we have any scaffolding
well we're gonna get it we're gonna get
it
um I had some recently to build my my
ice oh
ice
I what do you what I what did I call
that packed Ice Road no I made an ice
road I don't know did you see it the new
thing up in the sky uh above Amelia's
tennis racket yeah I was gonna ask you
what that was but it doesn't even load
from here on my side oh it loaded for me
earlier yeah it is oh yeah yeah yeah
well it's a it's a highway speed highway
to uh Phoenix 10 just to test the whole
thing out I made water elevators as well
I know how to do that now and but I'm
gonna make it to a lot of places I
wanted to make it in
um
in the in the Never as well
it's like an Autobahn there's no there's
no speed limit you just go as fast as
you can
the boats and it's like the fastest way
you could never go anywhere apparently
it's still the fastest way of moving
[Music]
what am I looking for a scaffolding
um I might let me go check I got 51 I
don't think we can go all to the top of
that is there another hill we can build
it on maybe we want to build
uh
[Music]
it should be it should be you know what
it shouldn't be too far away maybe
because we want to start like making
this place look as crazy as the whole
life Japan server yeah so
uh it should still be like somewhere in
the center close to the center okay by
the way I'm looking for scaffolding yeah
remember we can probably borrow some
from Ina I got 51 and you know probably
has a lot okay doesn't she says bamboo
we can use that too it goes real fast
does it though does it though I think so
but I think you also need string which
might be an issue she got 12 in there
but she must have more somewhere else
she has so much stuff in her home
there's so many animals
wow yeah she has foxes too right they
make weird noise
yeah
boxes
[Music]
the fox say
right something like that
what's up what sound does it make I
actually don't remember that what does
it make
it's cutting out
okay I'll do a little one yeah
foxes are really scary isn't it called
like a it's called like a vixen Screech
or something and because they actually
sound like a human like a blood curdling
scream I've never heard one before
the way you described it makes it sound
like they're absolute monsters they
sound like it well maybe they sound like
it
well the two when did you get any
scaffolding no I didn't steal some
bamboo
all right all right all right if you
need string too though
oh damn it all right maybe we have
enough I can just speak and we can
Bounce from side to side that'll be fine
all right all right and and if not then
oh we'll just build it somewhere
decently low oh not that so high oh we
could try to get up up on that mountain
but there's always something up there
I don't think that was really
well no we don't have to we don't have
to tear it down we can just build next
to it because from like from here you
would see our monument that that would
be good enough it's just it's just so
very thin but very wide layer of
cute girls
um I don't think I don't think that the
51 scaffolding will be enough to get up
there yeah
wool or whatever you can get up there
with 51 that'll be easy we'll parkour
the rest of the way yeah damn you have a
good feeling for this I I have a very
there you go okay all right okay
pass the moon okay we went past them all
no
um
yep okay uh saw that coming hardest part
of your entire oh stream is getting up
the scaffolding pew pew pew
Pew I hate scaffolding it was my biggest
enemy
I
might die from this we'll be fine don't
worry about it
foreign
[Music]
nice to build here we need to flatten it
out a little bit yummy
okay do you believe in my parkour skills
no oh oh wow
wow I see how it is distrusting my
parkour skills
uh what do I do here uh it's
[Music]
builds build like here in the middle I
guess
yeah sure
I can do that um but I guess we should
try to like get this on the same level
and flatten it out a little bit yeah
um with some dirt and Stones so I guess
we'll go down again did you bring Jordan
Stones I guess not I did not but I have
a shovel
or oh yeah I guess
we could get it from like here
yes yes
yeah oh
let's make this thing uh
without destroying anything that has
been built here up until now why are
there sheep up here dear Lord they must
be scared that was me I was trying to
dye sheep a different color and then Ina
built Ina built the vending machine up
here
scare them to frighten them I assuming
my dominance you know oh I don't wanna
what I don't I don't even know this is
based on my inventory okay oh this will
do for now
foreign
okay
yeah this was the space the space
program we were doing where we were
trying to launch everybody and it ended
I was not part of that I think you were
you're probably sleeping yeah I was
sleeping stop it times yeah time zones
all right what is this the this is what
we're leveling out
we can level it out here I mean how many
it's only one block wide right so yeah
but we maybe want to have something like
to fall down on because we're gonna fall
down a lot I guess
you might be but I'm not gonna die of
this dream I've decided
[Music]
it's falling down a lot
I guess
um have some
from area to walk around and uh you know
this would be much easier I guess if we
had eritora what is
I know what that is
the super cape oh Emily should bring up
torches I guess this is way too dark up
here I'll bring some torches I got some
I got you I have one no I don't I have
15.
aha well then uh put them around here I
guess
yes by the way I have you
actually like seen because because our
server got updated too have you seen
anything from the update I haven't I
wanted to go on like a like a safari
where I went and seeked out all the the
update things like the yeah
and the billy goats and stuff
yeah the Japanese girls already have
been doing that the whole time on the
past days
I was like I want to go too there it
looks looks like it's a lot of uh cool
new stuff like the only thing I saw from
the update was today when I was like
running around our area and I jumped
into the the water that is around Emma's
house
uh there was a glowing
um
what do you call that animal again a
glowing Taco
octopus yeah yeah and then I was like
that I never saw it glowing before
yeah I saw those on Ina's stream when
she was collecting
a drop of glowing ink sacks now like
what can you do with them chat what can
you do with glowing ink socks can you
make the glowing text because I know you
can make Signs Now with glowing text
maybe that's what you use
baby I don't know I'm sure chat knows
though glowing signs they do say glowing
signs oh huge yeah so you can like see
it in the dark I guess yeah they had
them at the the festival the Summer
Festival like the haunted house was
written in red glowing texts
Ah that's how that works oh I was
wondering if that was I don't know some
fancy effect they had on the server or
whatever yeah
foreign
things have been added besides the
fishies
and the goats there's goats now that's
what I know oh can we have an intruder
daddy kick his ass
I have kicked his ass successfully all
right
and then I guess we can get going also
this was too high we can lower this uh
[Music]
thank you
good at cute
magic
people I want you to say that again
what
is that new too the red moon yeah
okay shut up
so wait a minute the red moon
oh it's really your blood blood moon you
know
aha
what but look much fancier than usual
the red oh I see the red moon wow it's
so warm yeah it's almost like it's the
Sun
I wish I almost could be the sun it
could could be
wow all right you know what I'll take
the 12 more uh thingies that I saw at
Eno's place maybe I'mma have some
scaffolding too is she mine
I think we should both have some
scaffolding on each side
uh 12 remember that chat 12 to give back
to Ina
and let's see
[Music]
did you see uh was it live stream
today yeah
no I didn't watch it but
um
I I thought she would uh arrest me next
time she was doing a stream like that
but nope not yet
no I think she's going for
um
[Music]
people have been reporting me a lot what
else I may have scaffolding
people can you imagine going down my own
people have been reporting me the whole
time to Subaru but I think Okay the
reason why she's not going yeah
because me and somebody have a special
bond
have you been you've been paying your
workers right
about that thing
can't see
ruin the issue because you blink if you
need help blink twice if you need help
are you okay kfp
[Music]
don't even don't know
is I'm in the chat in your chat
I know
do we have some scaffolding now
much too or only borrow some scaffolding
I couldn't find any nice sniffer up
to me in your account
yeah she's a she's supposed to face with
a big long Pinocchio nose ah
well maybe in my house
check but uh I don't see any of these
ones do you have another secret storage
somewhere else Pat her down she's got a
scaffolding somewhere in there
did I miss something
is this why I don't know how many ways
oh do I want to go to PVP no no
I do not want to
I will I have 42 now do you think well
that's enough yeah probably
three four
I need to tell how many across this is
because I now ever find we can just go
as we go right here right right actually
actually our our thingies are about
53 blocks are so tall
it's not gonna be enough but for now for
now for now for now yeah for a little
while okay wait am I on the left or the
right
oh uh
uh on the right side on the right side
oh okay
on the right
okay
[Music]
don't die from the scaffolding
no okay I'll give you I'll give you like
half of the scaffolding
thank you
thank you all right and ah wait wait
wait wait we have to figure out
uh if you start feeling on the right
side bye guys
I don't want our thing is to collide at
some point we really have to
um
you know do math on how
where to start mine and where to start
yours you know what I mean yeah but let
me let me write out the butt wait wait
one two three four five six seven all
right that's the size okay of my feet
you have to think of the fact that your
head is pretty wide
of course only only in the pixel art not
in reality
yeah that's not gonna be enough actually
but I guess I guess that's like from
this from The Edge uh on the right side
it's totally okay to like go over the
edge
wait which way do we want this to face
as well we wanted to face yeah I would
say that that way inside okay okay I
mean it would look it will face both
ways
huh oh yeah this way as well but yeah
[Music]
okay wait that's good okay your feetsies
are here so if I look if I zoom in
let's see how many are between
[Music]
oh dear oh that's kind of hard to count
on this thing but I guess if it's
okay guys I need to chat to help me
right now her foot ends at X 59
and then
just kind of many blocks are in between
us right
but it's like it doesn't really it's
it's a bit it doesn't
Okay and then and then x 44 is when mine
starts
which means 59 minus 34. which means
um 20 25 did I do quick math correctly
I think I did
oh my God
25 that's okay by far not enough space
we need more uh one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven I'll get
some more dirt
yes
zombie stuff get out of here
all right more dirt
get that dirt get that dirt get down and
dirty
I'm waiting for my caffeine to hit me
come on what what is the energy drink of
your choice
Sparkling Ice caffeine blue raspberry is
the best flavor because it keeps me it
gets me makes me feel alive it's the
only thing that makes me feel alive
these days yeah is that like uh is that
a is that is that a brand snail yeah
it's apparently water sparkling water
with caffeine in it
oh
it's delicious and there's not as much
caffeine and there's like a a monster or
anything so it doesn't make it doesn't
make my heart go do funny things and
they don't have that here I think
um
okay I don't need it
all right all right you guys want bgm so
bad let me turn some pizza on
like non-stop lately
uh I want something more upbeat here
there you go guys did you hear that that
should probably be louder
I want them to do like uh can you
imagine doing hinatoli and put
Challenger and Sparks can you imagine
Sparks and Lo-Fi how good that would be
um well I definitely already have uh
heard uh Hino Tony hinatoli
jazz in jazz before and I covered it in
jazz as well like I sang a jazz version
of it and my stream yeah that sounded
really damn good the jazz version
because Jazz is the best flavor of music
there is even though people like to deny
it do you like jazz you like jazz it's
my favorite color I like jealous
okay Chad are you happy now do you hear
that pajama
um
yeah okay A bit loud you sure you're
sure about that
you're doing that beautifully did you
actually counter no
was I supposed to
oh I mean wait a second let me count
oh wait sorry I didn't Loop the video
nice I love this one okay okay good out
count with me
[Music]
Where did German lady
yes six six seven seven
act nine nine ten ten f l
12 12.
10 right then
say uh
Afton
19.
it's fancy fancy
I love Sunfish ions fancy
science
something play on something
wait what fiance Fancy please
good
[Music]
it concept ion okay concentration
free yeah the number four fear fear and
then and
I'll feel and Swansea yeah
okay you built actually more than enough
so
it was a nice repeating of what we've
learned previously
foreign
[Music]
I'm gonna die now I should probably
build a box because I'm gonna die yeah
you should you should die just in order
to make up for this I couldn't help it
you were standing right there you're
counting everything was perfect
um is you treat your teacher huh
and now you treat your teacher
oh wait I don't need this
I need
a show I saw is this how it's gonna be
good out between you and me today maybe
hopefully
how do I get up uh you better be careful
go down the day comes when I'll pay you
back
a little weak weak little shark
yeah I was gonna do that because I was
like she's not doing it
I Was preparing and you started killing
me you started killing
all right all right all right fair fair
all right all right and we actually have
two months here this is gonna not look
so good when it's I don't know what the
answer but okay we can start with more
than we need that'll be fun
more than we need yeah if we start with
too much we can take away as we go
um
yes yes okay
[Music]
all right let's get this party going uh
I said 25 until my foot starts right oh
wait actually
oh yeah that's where my foot starts
that's actually good that I have more
space all right all right all right all
right
um
thanks I
oh are you scared
are you fearful
thanks even now 19 minutes
I won't do anything
uh-huh
what what what one two three four one
two all right let's go uh are you
building oh you're building there
another hotel huh
this is right right this is right
I mean
yeah I mean it would have been nice if
you would have built like here
in the middle of the path
that's all right I can start over
do you need to share uh do you have one
it's way way faster with a share I only
brought one so for now we could have it
oh thank you
God damn it I have to count again
one two three four five
eight seven seven three eight four
five six seven seven nine
[Music]
um
yeah maybe
one one row
wait where am I in the front
uh one row more in front of the one
where you built right now I guess
wait what wait hello
on the same plural is uh
same now I got it I got it I got it yeah
yeah the new one the new one that you
built
is correct okay
yes
[Music]
how how many blocks
this is gonna be a long long stream wait
was I all right building all the way
over here did you want me closer to you
the distance in between us is uh perfect
if that was the end of your inner foot
aha okay
what okay speaking of feet what the hell
was that tweet good at uh the members
made me do it
the memories
there was a reason behind that huh okay
yeah right members
why did they make you do that
because they something about feet feet
tweet
it's an ongoing thing they're always
trying to get me to tweet feet so I'm
trying my hardest to do everything
except tweet the entire word I've
tweeted a picture of my own feet
remember that Trend that was going
around of the vtuber feet I tweeted my
feet
and then I tweeted a picture that we
draw of me wearing a foot hat but I have
yet to tweet feet and I never will if I
can help it unless I lose a bet we've
been betting on stream
okay well it seems like you have a lot
of wholesome relationship with them of
course we do right
thanks seven
one two all right
uh
uh oh I Got Dirt
yeah
my my inventory is too full I don't like
it
wow oh yeah oh ah before the stream when
I was AF King I already told my pre-chat
but uh
I logged in and I was running around and
I noticed that all of my llamas were
afraid they were not on a leash anymore
and I was really confused they were
roaming around there do you know
anything about that probably not right
no
any one of us I feel like they were
freed through maybe I mean that sounds
weird but is it possible that the update
somehow deleted the leashes and they
were afraid
for some reason
I don't know sounds weird maybe Chad
knows I have no idea they don't seem to
have seen anything from other streams
social
free through free in between and then
seven
this is testing your math skills
look the red moon is rising you see it
shut up shut up
uh oh yeah I'm in the dangerous position
here how many is that one two three four
five uh
uh seven I need one dirt underneath
the oh
wow nice
I need more food though maybe I should
go down and make food there's a skeleton
not the skeleton
uh what
if you hit me one more time okay okay
okay you bastard hit me Skelly one more
time
where are you
oh oh well that's that was the Phoenix
fire I didn't even have to touch you it
burned from the Sun
and turn into ashes
wait is this right one two three one two
three one two three
trippy
oh my oh my God
a bit trippy
uh oh wait
huh how's it going gouda good going
surprisingly well so far I just need to
it's hard swapping in between now we can
have one foot done wow that's that's
we're doing good progress but I feel
like it's gonna be difficult the higher
we get the wider the the pixel art gets
I'm getting nervous about the space the
eyes the eyes look really hard I built
this before and why why
there's a lot of blocks and stuff
oh in the face
oh wait I'm doing this wrong uh oh wait
yeah in the face in the face
[Music]
blue
oh
okay
oh rude comment this 2D model is perfect
for good as chest
kind of rolled back hitting chat don't
ban him but um
bring it to the YouTube room the usual
room
yeah
one two three
and then one here
oh I see I finally got the base down I
think wow this will be almost above my
house
wow actually it will be because um my my
feet end here but my dress keeps going
nice the lights go on the world
[Music]
okay and I will finally uh
do my part I guess your show
this goes here and this goes here and
then uh
easy and then
and then this goes here and then this
girl this girl this guy is here
and
um
this goes here and then this goes
does it go here yeah I think it goes
here
oh this is gonna be confusing whatever
what if I mess up you won't mess up you
won't mess up I think
ow how do you know yeah go well this
goes here
oh here it's still easy because it's so
low I can fall down it's all good I can
look at it from a different angle
[Music]
I wish I had wings
Elijah
but we're doing we're doing it we're
doing and and the dragon soon oh yeah I
remember we're trying to figure out when
to do that right
yeah it's gonna be
somewhere around
the next
next next next week
it's next week next month next week but
the next week
yeah and I don't like I've been studying
on how to defeat the Ender Dragon maybe
we can use a Speed Run Strat you're
supposed to use beds and stuff well we
don't we don't don't need a speed one
strategy with five strong soldiers
but imagine
okay I'm imagining
I'll call it a beetle if we built it and
we've like defeated it really fast
yeah but I I don't think we can do that
this stream are probably long
yeah
fast enough with suffer and struggle and
die a million times and I'll be like yep
no problem uh uh Phoenix can got you
with the diamond armor no matter how
many times you die
and
whoa what
does it
oh
I just realized I really can't miss
something wrong no isn't that is it a
big thing no I just I can't mess up with
the ice
ah why because my pickaxe said oh I
don't have soft touch I have silk
touched oh silk touch nice big and I
have a Sig I have many sick touch
pickaxes because that's one of the
things you can get at Phoenix 10. oh
yeah with all your villagers
yes yes indeed nice that is such a smart
move I remember spending a lot of time
in there and then I couldn't find my way
I know I've seen it I watched the whole
thing oh
okay wait hold it
oh already confused uh on it
yep
[Music]
we should probably put up but is there a
chest here no
never mind
will you bring food
please do you need food yes okay
um well you know what I'll put
um
oh wait I think I messed up huh
wait what
did you do I was really confusing right
I haven't messed this up already
uh
same I also messed up that's why I'm
getting scissors now
[Music]
let's go
and the chest would be nice
I missed this was oh no legs too close
how did I miss count until closest two
it's three
three are there supposed to be three
blocks of fire and a two are you showing
them on your stream that that window too
the the clothes the thingy nah this is a
picture of it okay okay
why don't you guys say anything we did
say something
dang it now what no
do you think it matters should I redo it
uh it depends I'm not sure exactly how
how yeah yeah you should redo it
probably yeah okay we're doing it
I'm bringing you a silk touch pickaxe
thank you have I not actually put one
into the present box so that I gave you
once a while ago I I mean I'm not sure
really could have been
I put a lot of stuff in there guys do
you remember chatting remember what I
gave her I gave her some stuff I gave
her some enchantments and some some
diamond stuff like I think ax and
[Music]
okay well I don't know here I'll give
you uh food and uh
pickaxe thank you uh oh I think I picked
up some blocks from you
thank you thank you
go down wait wait wait stop stop
here there you go did you pick that up
yeah
[Music]
and food
learning I picked it I picked it up
again
oh nice uh
now I gave you all of it I I I gave it a
whole stack accidentally all right
you
okay thank you
dang it I thought I had this in the bag
okay
I made a mistake too the mistake that I
made was
uh
being being
um
being here
what and I suddenly felt like the price
of espresso
oh
are you are you okay
I don't know
okay I'm standing with the sexy legs now
[Music]
one two three four five six seven all
right we go again easy
this is supposed to be ice but I'm just
gonna put wool there because what the
hell who cares
chat my
nah they don't even know what I'm
looking at they don't even know that
they're supposed to be eyes so they
can't complain I mean they know now but
now they will forget forever
um
[Music]
not the usual room anything but the
usual
[Music]
one
will do
oh no yeah yeah it's correct correct
oh it's getting pretty dark here again
should we sleep or no we can walk
through the night right yeah
oh yeah
until they attack us
Tuesday until they come for us the
Phantoms oh that's right the fandom is
screeching Phantoms
oh this is easy this is easy this is
easy
okay my leg is done one leg nice but I'm
gonna continue here nice jump okay
ah one two three four one two
three three and down
by the way
besides all you know I I don't know if
you've seen it but I've been doing
um okay recently not so much anymore but
for a while recently I've been cooking a
lot and uh
therefore people have been seeing me as
the cook of of her live English but I
said like no but goodness besides me we
were done talking who in hell out of
English actually Cooks a lot and the
only one I can really think of was you
because of your meatloaf and stuff
yeah the the like the one time I cooked
actual food on stream yeah
you think a lot of stuff that's true I
like baking I haven't done it in a while
but also uh my cooking streams there's a
reflection of how I actually cook and
that's not very often I usually uh
I go for convenience more than
um
yeah so like there's like uh lately I
just make sure I have protein so it's
either like hard-boiled egg or some type
of like chicken usually like a chicken
sausage or two or something and then I'm
like all right that's good I look at the
macros and I'm like yeah
30 grams of protein I should be good for
the next eight hours let's go you just
eat like a chicken and an egg without
anything else yeah cause lately all I
care about is the macros
my chat is currently panicking because
you mentioned chicken
I meant vegan chicken so it's actually
it's called seitan not Satan but Satan
Satan
I don't know why they call it that
it was actually a vegan chicken no it
was real chicken but uh I'll say it's
not oh for the sake of the KFC sorry
guys well thank you Google that is very
considerate I love you
is that higher than this side
man I forgot where I was I started
thinking about food oh one two three
order and then white
wait
is it higher
no it's not
is it oh
oh
they are messed up again I missed the
board but two I think yeah
yeah
I missed something up oh no
yeah it's it's supposed yeah it's
supposed to be too high here three High
here and it's supposed to be too high
here and free high here but now it's
pretty high and foreign
okay no problem
wait what
I think we both need to concentrate more
I guess so not always strong suit but
you know
what to do myself where are you
currently are you building the the skirt
already well like the I guess you have
pants actually I
hold on I need a brain brain power
I am it's not as easy as you think it
would be it's really not
I need a one two three oh no
wait blue blue red blue red blue red
blue teal
I have both legs are done I'm working on
the yeah the skirt part now okay maybe
we'll be able to finish this in like
ew
I think three hours should be enough I
do too actually maximum we're doing all
right yeah oh no no
okay so where did I go wrong
oh
where did I go no so it's okay it's okay
Kiana
oh
[Music]
yeah
oh my God Brian you got it yeah reminds
me of uh like the color by number books
you can get
ah
[Music]
um
let's go sleep don't don't die oh do you
have an extra bed anyway nope we gotta
go down I think oh man
here they come
yeah they hit me already
[Music]
I only have one bat in my home so
you gotta go somewhere else I think
we should bring a bed with us
oh that's a good idea
let's do it
does he even have a bed in here I sure
hope so yes nice
I almost died
oh didn't they didn't didn't Minecraft
add something what was that I heard they
were adding something like
what was that you can sleep
for real even if not everyone sleeps or
is that something that they're going to
add what was that I heard something
about that so you're telling me they're
gonna add a sleep function but they're
not gonna add an auto sort inventory
[Music]
I need it
it's a server this is setting server
option is that already out with this
update or is that something they said
that would add later on
I'm going to add later uh need server
admin
did you bring it back
bang in the bed yes okay
and then back up we go oh the feet look
nice from down here okay now that's
correct now I can do the skirt now this
clip
the what
the script let's get scared
[Laughter]
what is skirt in German
Rock
yeah rock you ride it like you're right
rock and roll
a lot
but the thing is we also in German we
also call rock and roll
[Laughter]
okay
uh-huh
we continue this
your colors are red white and blue
I wanna cheese
a German lesson
Japanese viewers have been begging me to
do another Japanese lesson with you
yeah we can do it
I would like that
[Music]
um
for
[Music]
eign
huh
kusoni Hong Kong
[Music]
um
no no nuts Chicago no no no the
tadashini homegirls
Naruto don't uh uh uh did I teach you
teach you did I teach you magic come Ben
no what is coming I didn't I
it's okay magic combin he's uh it's like
give me a freaking break it's like give
me a break let's see coming
oh
shh magic company
magic Campbell
come Ben and Ben
yeah
can you say it like an annoyed teenager
[Laughter]
yeah I mean I've never heard a Japanese
Tina you're saying like that
this Cali sound like an edgy teenager
then
Japanese
um no she just sounds like a very
nihongo or Jose
now we're home though
[Music]
all right I got sorry that was kind of a
sick band wasn't it sick burn too bad
she's not here to defend herself good
all can you do an Irish accent would you
teach me how to do it thank you tap in
the morning to you ladies I'm what's his
name I am Jacksepticeye and today
was that Irish I think so
oh
okay wait I think I finally got like the
flow out of this one now
I I've Got a Feeling
oh wait no I messed up
okay
wait can't you do the British accent
uh
to tell me you don't like fate that was
so British of me
oh British but here I did it
you sound like you have like a potato
like you're holding a potato between
your teeth
[Music]
close soundings that I ever saw them
before is it is it
in it
be careful thank you
you sound like a bird just now like a
certain bird called attack
I got him
is this right
why is this so difficult for my brain
there's too much blue Guru how are you
messing this up I I don't know how
you're doing it but at a certain point
like for example now I'm doing a skirt
that's just like I like how you wear uh
if you start at one like instead of
starting like somewhere in the middle
randomly you should start at the very
edge of it and then just make the whole
row that's what I'm trying to do okay
okay then we we at least have the the I
guess the strategy down
we definitely have the Strat done it's
just my execution is uh needs some work
but I mean because I'm talking to you no
no no no in that lovely oh I'm gonna die
in that lovely British accent
beautiful right what's up what's a jab I
know they don't like being called that
oi oy chab a chab is that a Chad just in
British I don't know I don't think they
like it very much so oh
huh good I don't huh don't say don't I'm
assuming it's exactly what it that's
exactly what it is
you don't want to be called a child that
people like that no oh
[Music]
not a hold up it's just not very good
word
we both would like to apologize for our
lack of knowledge yeah
[Music]
we already up
uh all right no problem no problem I
cannot I need to hold on I need to
really think about this
me too I reached a point where oh oh no
it's going good
oh
oh I just had the wrong color
one two three four
I saved it nice okay nice go down I stay
nice
foreign
[Music]
it's like
um very closely very close almost almost
not
um
like for example making it just in time
I feel like I told you this before maybe
it's just my my maybe I don't have a
Deja Vu yeah just barely so if you say
it again safe get it safe it's like
it was just barely safe
I know it's lyrics and uh Ethan and I
are borderline they say
yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
so good oh my god
when we go to Japan We Go karaoke it's
my favorite thing to do in Japan hey
good night karaoke I like yeah
[Music]
count one two
this is so hard why is it so difficult
why
and then once she's okay we can do it I
need to get rid of those now
and then one and then and then one and
then
one two three
this is this is how where we will prove
our big brain although wait even though
we might feel super big brain by doing
this I think our audience might not see
it the same way
hahaha
yeah I said okay
okay I got those two first two layers of
uh the skirts down wow
now it goes inside so I start here
nice
hi
red red one blue one blue
one one one what oh I see what
the I cut up my way down I'll just
um I just never go down again that's
that's it
or I'll have good uh Rescue Me
okay
okay continuing
um
[Music]
this is not so difficult no wait wait oh
what
no white
no no no
okay go down are you concentrating yes I
was concentrating I got it now for real
I got it now for real
I wanted to get a little bit more of
that out of that cooking conversation oh
yeah okay do we sleep though
sleep oh because it's dark okay sure wow
I have my bed okay no problem ah
what is
your like please tell me every uh recipe
that you can cook
like every that counts the things that
you like tell me each thing you can cook
like from a recipe or by brain it's just
each oh
hmm
I guess with a recipe works well as well
with the recipe I'm unstoppable I lost
my bed why
damn it okay what happened
I got it I got it again
uh damn it
oh damn it oh
all right so yeah
tell me the all the things you can cook
ah I can cook Savory Foods I've cooked
Korean stews and soups of all kinds like
cup which is soup where you just steam
the pumpkin and blend it together
it's yummy I can make like a roasted
entire uh various uh Meats before I
won't specifically say chicken but it
was a chicken and a turkey
oh whoa and I can bake like cakes before
cakes from scratch and cookies from
scratch I've done a bunch of different
types of cookies and uh yeah I'm pretty
I'm pretty Unstoppable with a recipe
you seem to be yeah it's easy with a
recipe
okay without recipe by heart
I can make an egg
I just push a button
okay I think I can probably make more
things by heart than you but with like I
haven't yet uh
experimented as much as you have I guess
ah when you make recipes like oh yeah I
have um
uh okay I can make for example it's a
German Austria Australian dish uh called
Schnitzer oh schnitzel yes do you know
what schnitzel is
um
sort of maybe
it's kind of it's a it's uh uh it's meat
that is covered covered in like a
breading
uh-huh uh and then fried in oil
it's like a thin layer of meat that your
first Hammer you hammer on it you go
like to make it soft and thin and then
you pouted it yeah
exactly and then you put it into the
breading and then you put it into the
oil then you make some
um some potatoes on the side some um
with special special stuff and then you
eat it with like some
uh prizes so it's a special type of
berry jam
oh it's really yummy so that's that's
like the the most
um popular
Australian food that we have I can cook
that it's really yummy
and I can make I can make pancakes I can
make a French toast I can make a pasta a
Bolognese and I can make pasta carbonara
I can now make Alfie love what's an elf
laughing in English Apple
student what's our fluff Apple uh
I grabbed and yeah I can make all kinds
of gratins now and I might have a
streusel before
though
oh
that's pretty
uh High wait did you make apple strudel
I don't know I just had like cinnamon
and stuff in it oh and that sounds high
level
with the recipe yeah about the recipe
but I think so even with the recipe uh
like you can still mess it up so
good job
thank you is that is that the whole
layer just orange yeah it is okay
all right easy
oh yeah what else can I make um uh I
forgot uh well I can oh
[Music]
where are you
coming back
[Music]
we're good
I'm good don't worry
that happens I I have I have seen it in
the future that this will happen I died
first I'm the stinky I see
foreign
[Music]
fair enough fair enough I got what I had
coming
here oh here it's all difficult okay
it's a long red
it is totally delicious it is you got
something
um on you I think it's a little bit of
Amelia Watson
kind of um I had to say that in English
is
how to say that in English
she's coloring off on youth oh she's
rubbing off on you yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
are you playing Minecraft with your game
capture card
what no hold on I'm trying to count
okay
one two three one two oh my God this is
going so well seven okay one two three
and in Germany
no yeah
wait I think I miscounted
seven wait one two
oh I didn't miss count oh
interesting
my face is full of cat hairs isn't it
delicious
no
boys have a snack nearby
that hair in your mouth
I'm confused no no it's yummy
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait one two
three on fire crying out okay
okay count with gura
where one
four
three k three okay three three one two
three all right yes and then the rest
what is the rest one two three four one
one two three
oh
my God okay I'm ready okay yep
am I higher than you by now I think I
might oh I think
I don't think so
uh where am I
oh here okay
and then for sure well where am I
oh
oh and then blue
I'm just getting really really
complicated
[Music]
I'm on the arms now
yeah I'm actually I'm real too but I
forgot I guess I yeah I didn't do
oh they're oh
I'm way on the same row basically unless
your arms are shorter than
mine no they're under the same height
yeah we're the same height here
[Music]
but because there's space between them I
didn't start them
oh God damn it wait red I guess I'll do
them afterwards okay where the hell am I
oh okay
uh
oh never mind
oh
you're saying
uh what am I supposed to say brown this
time what's wrong this time
sand is the problem building underneath
oh no
oh
God
uh right now it's fine it's fine
[Music]
oh I'm trying to also figure out how I'm
Gonna Fill This Gap and how I'm gonna
get rid of it
for now
I guess this should be fine
uh
so far what the hell
are you building up why are you building
up so much what do you mean
I'm just following the path it's
somebody's doing
holy on it efficiency okay okay
fish
fish snc you know efficiency a
efficiency
fish and sea eat patients fish fish and
sea fish and see what you get
um and see what you get from the fish in
the sea oh my God
she's a pun Master Ena would be proud oh
my God
you have efficiency you will fish and
see what you get from the fish in the
sea oh
and
yeah
I'm not following are you lost me
I I I I
found myself now you lie you might I
might have lost you but I have found
myself my calling
yourself
how many books
one two three
oh one two three five one two three
four five
okay oh this is dangerous fun
one two three four five
do you have ice on yours to build
nice no I don't have any ice this is
dangerous
oh because you're slippery oh no I am
slippery yes that does sound extremely
dangerous yeah
oh dear I I do not envy you on that
design Choice
it was not me the program came up with
it
I'm just gonna build the arm before
jumping back over
okay
oh dangerous
uh so I'm here now
and that's uh one two
three
I guess what and what
and then
[Music]
right oh boy
and then there's orange
and then there is more sand
and that's my fist and I will use that
fist to hit you good at Square in the
mouth yeah dude
your mouth is bigger than mine though
you could probably fish your entire
favorite fish you could probably figure
it out open your mouth right now and go
down let's see who's bigger
yours is like two of mine you can fit
your whole fist in your mouth easy
ah gouda you can put an entire meatball
in there
good
um what
okay
am I wrong okay
you know I've been recently
um being recommended to um out of
context good at Clips yeah
crazy I don't know where they get that
stuff from
unbelievable
I don't know if I mean that one was like
I mean that that was like no that one
that the one that I've watched I feel
like that wasn't really your fault yeah
okay
it happens it happens it happens a lot
with me too because like I say a lot of
things that
um like sound normal at least in my head
and in my language but not really in
English and I don't realize until I say
it remember the time we had that
Christmas clamp yeah and I said like
what touching it's normal to touch your
friends what did I say why
there was no issue with that everyone
was just overreacting I think
um
yeah what did I say good friends good no
I don't know I don't know what was the
expecting it's okay to touch each other
once in a while but I think that was it
yeah
about that I honestly don't know like
and I think everyone's overreacting but
okay
probably
what where am I
oh
I messed up again how did I do that oh
no
red white red white what
did I skip a line
oh no
uh I wish there was is there like a way
you can put a
there's got to be a way for me to like
put lines yeah like put a block so I
know what line I'm on
yeah
put a block in the in the in the thingy
that I sent you
you can like draw in it
um there's like a pen uh I'll turn on
the top left
uh-huh
I guess you can draw like uh you can
even draw certain blocks in there I
think if you choose no I'm not exactly
sure
but yeah with some proper lines it would
be
use the replacement I don't think we
need that
[Music]
um
it's all right I'll wing it a little
torches to mark
huh oh
there's a there's zombies hello
just don't fall down
not planning on it how did I really set
up
where am I
oh did you put a home bed a good idea
should we sleep I can't there's monsters
nearby oh yeah Ryan oh yeah all right I
at least here sit
there were five
let me finish this row I'm gonna do two
of these one two and then I do two of
these one two
what what oh I see and then one
red white white white blue black what
one two
dakoma if you're here in the chat the
person who made
um the thing is I saw her in the chat
just let me know if I made a mistake and
I didn't realize it I have wonderful
help here are you are you looking with
me already anyway yeah she seems to be
looking this week
at the same thing that's good that's
good did I make a mistake I don't think
so not yet wait but uh
okay red one
two
and then we ran
and then what yeah okay okay
okay
I guess I should probably build the
other arm now before I continue with the
hair here yeah yeah yeah good idea
because that's where it connects okay
that's where it connects anyway
wait what oh no
but please don't fall down
wait don't fall down
blue
okay nice
this is gonna be so hard with the sand I
need to think about this one no you
gotta build something under the sand and
over order to hi creeper oh I know that
too
hold it
hold it hold send
okay okay here we have some concrete I
think I was gonna just use Brown for
that
I think
[Music]
I've been a watermelon I say bless you
in German
Eureka
[Music]
it's getting so damn good now tell me
when you can sleep
okay
wait I didn't sneeze yet don't tell him
he's on the chat I'm gonna sleep forever
be right back
all right you can stay like that follow
a minute and I'll sleep
um
it's okay at least you don't have a link
I mean
it's important
thing with you this will
was Albert Einstein German
yeah I think so the name sounds very
German so I'm gonna stay here Albert
Einstein
yeah you know oh we're actually in
German language we use the I I guess it
came from him
um but like we use the word Einstein to
describe a genius but like when we call
someone a genius we say oh you're such
an Einstein and I guess that comes from
you know Albert Einstein being so smart
and that's how we use it in a language
nowadays yeah we used to do someone
smite eh in English you can call
somebody an Einstein
Mike we do that a lot too we probably
use a lot of English words in our own
language yeah like Boston melon I see
where you're going no no
no no
Islam we've been steal it from
watermelon it just sounds similar
because we're friends a family of
languages let me copy your homework
people know
what it is
oh wait I probably shouldn't build like
that I shouldn't build underneath oh
[Music]
um
why no problem no problem
huh
what hmm
like audit
ah my inventory again with this
oh I'm confused
what happened did you lose where you
were
uh
yeah I don't really I don't really know
where is this oh yeah I guess okay
this is probably here
and then there's a
um
am I doing this right
I think I'll wait one
we want to
one two
I messed up I don't know where I am
oh no
LOL that inventory shut up
where's my sore inventory button
I have TNT I can blow this party up
I would cry I'd be so sad
where are we
are you counted
no I'm just I'm not coming I'm just
trying to not mess up
um bird brain hyper focused
you're the one talking bird brace you've
been messing up the whole time that is
true
I don't know where I am either wait I
need to wait what
uh got it
no no
one two three
this is wrong this is wrong
this is wrong
this is wrong wrong wrong
ah
here I'm missing one more yellow on top
of that all right
did I make it to top two
oh
there's supposed to be only one red
block in between the in between the
yellow oh but I made a two right
oh
[Music]
and
huh what
uh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
do you need anything oh wait never mind
I can just take it from here
nope no Stones necessary but if there's
a if there's a red one here and then the
orange one here and an orange one here I
have I feel like that was correct but I
guess I messed up in the middle
oh wait no that is just one block it
just looked at the the distorted from
over there no
no way oh
look over there because that's only one
Vlog and I thought it was two blocks oh
huh
oh
that was correct
I was correct let me see how you doing
how am I doing what why is
that well you can help me if you get
done early I'm not sure if I want you to
help me what
what are you scared of efficiency
I'm not scared of a fish in the sea but
some some minor mistakes they're not
mistakes they're uh artistics the things
we're both kind of brains yes but if we
combine two book brains will it be
maximum brain or will it be improved
brain will it be less of a bird brain is
plus and plus minus normally
that sounds like a lot of power that can
be disastrous
honestly what are we doing
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait so orange orange red and then
on top of the red goes another red
all right right
and then on that we're building just the
same thing again because I actually had
it right and I just got rid of it though
oh no
it's okay just one row
just a little bit of a setback that's
okay no problem no problem
I want I would love to show it on on
stream as well but it would like take up
a lot of the screen in order to make you
guys see it the way I see it so I'm just
not gonna do it also it might eat up
more RAM oh no probably not never mind
I don't think it would eat up that much
that was incorrect
wait did I mess well what are you
currently doing gouda blue I'm almost in
my face on this side oh what yeah both
arms and everything no no I only did one
side so far ah you're building from one
side to the middle now okay you're
building one side upwards ah that I was
about to do that but then I decided now
I'll go down again and then build the
whole row again and I don't know that's
why you're so high ah but I made a
mistake
there's no mistakes just happy accidents
right just artistic Liberties artistic
what is it called when the artist says
I'm gonna change this
but wait no this is still weird though
wait why
did not look at it when I went around
this part I was doing that wrong okay no
that's okay okay that's okay that's okay
that's okay and on top of that goes to
send
[Music]
like that
wait
okay
I'm gonna mod you
oh
I can see you easier no
how am I messing up now now what gura
wait
yeah all right
please make yourself useful for your
queen bird burp Queen uh we want
um
one
two three four
did you know that you're cute
thank you
I did did you know that
you're also cute very cute
yeah
that might be true yes
very cute but also hold on my brain is
struggling mm-hmm
what is this no problem four one two
three four is this four I can't see the
sun the red moon is in the way
[Music]
that that is
that's um is this three or four
I can't tell
I think it's four
so one two three so this is wrong so we
have to move in one yeah all right
okay I got it
I didn't realize this was gonna take
someone's brain power
you thought this was gonna be easy I did
I was like I will tell you something in
Japanese now okay
but I think I told you already in this
case I would say uh pixel art
is like don't don't direct the translate
it's like don't lick me but
but that's just directly translated if
you would translate it uh not directly
but what it actually means is like don't
don't underestimate for example don't
underestimate uh pixel art I will not
underestimate my strength and my power
don't lick the pixel art I'll make the
Pixar when I say
I don't mean don't lick me I mean don't
underestimate me but I guess at the same
time I do mean don't like me because I I
guess I mean both
lick the pixel art
well oh wait I wanted to make the arm oh
okay before I continue that I guess
that makes the arm I don't want to make
the arm because then there's like space
in between all right all right all right
okay so that's
uh
uh all this red is so bright one two
two not three here four
here on the height of this one right
you're getting help
well from the person who made the pixel
art
the person who made the pixel art is a
kfp employee actually
who has made a ton of pixel art of
all of us and also made my intro and
actually also
um was commissioned by Ahmed to make
amit's intro screen uh I don't know if
she's still using it I guess not the one
where where you know that I'm a intro
screen where um it's like this this uh
crane Japanese crane machine with our
plushies inside yeah I know that and
that's the one that's made so docomo is
the same person who made the pixel art
that we're building and the same person
who made Amazon
things things
try opening and mine as well it's made
so many things she's amazing wow
I want pixel art like food Sprites those
are cute maybe we can make some of those
in here too food Foods yeah
big tasty Foods you sure you don't want
to actually make footpix light
you should make one big
oh
you're welcome please
to finishing this one your next mission
is to make one big foot like the back
side of the foot
they can hear you stop it luggage chat
you didn't hear anything that is never
disappearing that idea
no that's gotta be like a like if I lose
a bet if we bet and I lose
you can probably just build with uh one
color and you know what instead of
making it like like this in in like the
sky you can make it on the ground and
then every time someone comes to visit
our server you could be like that's
where Bigfoot visits
it's not the difficulty it's the entire
thing it's the
do we really want a Bigfoot a big huge
foot good that would be
because you could be like that's our big
ancestors like
because whole life you know whole life
sometimes there are big answers these
days they're big and and they they made
a whole life to what it is now you could
say that that's your Footprints and
we're trying to you know walk in their
big feet how do you say that in English
um walking in their footsteps yeah
eggs that are big feet until we fit into
them oh it has so many meanings so much
more meaning good than you thought it
would have it's not so shallow that's
that's what your your fans have been
trying to tell you I finally realized
too but there's so much more behind that
they're not just trying to get you into
a foot fetish or something they're
trying to you know inspire you to
something much much bigger that you have
never even founded
hold on
give me a second
yes keep talking
I think I'm done oh no please keep going
are you recording me or no no no no no
tell me more about the feet
no I I was done I was dumb all right my
joke's not done yet keep going
you don't yeah where do I continue
um
I
want I lost the string of my story
so so okay so you could build you could
build up a big big foot on the ground
and it will just it would not just be a
fetish it will be you know it will be a
legislative eyes have left behind us it
will be a beautiful big foot that you
built out of respect for them in order
to honor them and what they've done up
until now in order for Honor for the big
big whole life that they've built up you
know to to make us you know we become
alive
fetish it's so it's summer your viewers
are way smarter than that they just
they're not just into feet they're into
the history of whole life
I'm talking what you like I'm listening
intensely this
isn't talking I don't know I'm here I'm
here you can hear me I mean what
happened on the other side nothing I'm
just listening to your explanation did
you mute
I need to watch stuff no I was just
listening to you trying to justify
building a giant foot
a giant foot atrocity on this server
[Music]
the ground like you just have to shave
off some mountains and then can you
build it on the big round that's so much
easier because it you won't fall down
and you can build with sand on the
ground because the sand will fall down
on the ground so you don't need to have
anything underneath it because there's
already something underneath it it will
be so easy like I can I can help you out
with that but honestly I think it's your
mission you know as the biggest whole
life English member I think and you know
I also in order to to honor your dearest
football I think you should build a
foot on the ground and then you can be
like that is for Boogie sent by his
footprint and yeah um
when you think about it
I'll think about it we'll think about it
the complete track of where I was here
uh
where the hell one time okay oh my God
[Music]
inspired you know don't judge me no I'm
not I'm judging a little bit but that's
all right nothing
with the food cake okay
that wasn't me
foreign
I hate this so much right now
okay I gotta I gotta extend my my
platform on this side
I'm sweating good the make me made
me sweat
feel
[Music]
foreign
okay
sweaty yeah I sweat a lot too when I
stream and when I get too hot and sweaty
though my brain really struggles to work
oh
yeah
do you not have air conditioning I
thought like in in the country of uh
Atlantic under the ocean that uh
everything every every uh Place comes
with air conditioning my AC is busted
it's you because
um you could probably call someone to
repair it
I could if they showed up oh you didn't
they didn't show up nah
and I was too scared to touch it
oh yeah I understand that like I
wouldn't I probably wouldn't want to
touch it either probably just make it
worse yeah I was like you know what it's
fine I'll just I'll just whine about it
a little bit no I mean in summer how
the fan will work fine
you have a lot of fans you have three
million fans all right uh oh look how
proud you are you're so proud of
yourself for that one
for me to make puns in English language
okay make them in German
uh well then we have to speak in German
and you're not you're not as good as I
thought you were with that
but uh yeah you're right I'm really not
you speak French
you actually
I wasn't expecting that wait a minute
since when since when do you speak
French as well okay I always spoke
French especially when it comes to
phrases like that
how do I not know that wait a minute
oh come on
you know meat bye
foreign
I apologize I thought I knew
thank you actually that phrase was just
one phrase from The Song Moulin Rouge
from
um uh Christina Aguilera pink little Kim
and uh Missy Elliott who else was in
there I've seen them wait the movie
Moulin Rouge
yeah I guess that was the song to it it
goes like
yeah and then there's there's one part
of the song where they chant
this is
all my sisters yeah
and it means would you like to sleep
with me tonight
too
does that mean yes
but I think that's um something else
hold on
have you seen that movie though
no I just uh actually back then I was a
really edgy teenager I was really into
Christina Aguilera and all that so I
really like that song
though
oh maybe did you watch it
I have seen that movie Yes with uh with
uh what's his name and Scottish guy and
that other girl right oh what's his name
is
my members it's what's his name wasn't
he in Star Wars oh dear God this is when
I get made fun of
um
you won you win McGregor you won you won
and uh Nicole something
yeah Obi-Wan I think yeah Obi-Wan Kenobi
yeah
Obi-Wan McGregor and the other girl
Gordon Ramsay no no different different
Scottish guy he's Scottish right
oh
where am I all right okay uh but yeah I
was gonna say I sang that song in my
last anarch cupcado because that was
really fun
yeah I think that that's that that song
is so much fun to sing you should maybe
listen to it once hey I'm surprised you
don't wait have you never heard of that
song even though you watched a movie I
guess it does it not actually come up in
the movie
um it might have it's been a while
though since I've seen it so maybe I
just don't remember it
oh no this is wrong
wait is it wrong it is wrong oh
I'm getting really slow here I should
probably focus more now we had a little
a little fun banter and now we're back
to focusing let's go wait no that's not
it's not the right color
this is the right color
okay that's okay that's okay
I do not trust that why is this wrong
oh that's correct that's correct that's
correct
that's correct oh shoot
am I doing fine
am I doing fine you're so high up in the
sky but since you're only doing one side
I guess I'm catching up quite well
yeah you're doing both sides at once
right kind of yeah I'm finding myself in
the middle again now because I made the
second arm now
[Music]
um where am I and I keep losing track
right now damn it
what is this
all right uh-huh
that means that there's an orange one
here
and now and there's an orange in here
and then that means that this is there
all right
all right we're getting somewhere
[Music]
I'm already above the belly button
basically there's no belly button on
this pixel art but that's where it would
be so
the belly button
why did I call it a button though I mean
it makes sense if you have an Audi belly
but shouldn't you call it like the belly
Bowl since it goes in sometimes
you know what that's some kind of that's
something that you should Google why is
a belly button called belly button
why is it the belly button
S I would say because it was just like
named at the moment when they looked at
someone with like an Audi belly button
and they were like yeah that's a button
even though there's also a lot of other
others
now if I asked you a belly button you
have
what you have an indie or an Audi
I I'm I have an uh ah okay
navel comes from the word the
um
oh that's way cooler yeah show me your
show me your umbilicus
what like umbilical cord but it's the
umbilicus that would be my that would be
my my Roman warrior name
or I guess my Greek warrior name realm
and bore your name Roman warrior good
house screw the Romans yeah my Greek
warrior name is umbilicus
yeah what's up
I told that and I told my audience
I went to I went to uh Greece uh
recently when I was a day holiday yeah
yeah yeah I had to think a little bit
about you because uh of your of your
song
you did no that was that was uh oh uh
ice cream old Greek
what do you call them in English
[Music]
you just got an old Greek both Greek
can I ask you because you wrote the
English parts of that lyrics Right who
wrote The Greek ones did you just put it
for Google translators
not worrying now they're all quotes
are there quotes ancient quotes from
Smart kisses
that's Roman uh smart smartical smart
kiss
Spartacus spider kiss
they're old scholar quotes from smart
people Smart Guys
oh how does that go that's wrong
it's Sportacus that reminds me of that
old television show LazyTown
[Music]
connected with you again I thought if we
were from a different kind of timeline
but you coming out with a lazy town oh
dear I mean I did not like it much but
foreign
[Music]
How does it go again
um
[Music]
but first oh you know that's what
I'm talking about though
I know tell me what you're talking about
the girl with the pink wig and then
there was the blue guy who was really
fast almost like Sonic
[Laughter]
that was his name oh yeah oh I didn't
really realize because I guess I watched
it in German
um what was his German name
[Music]
person that I say after I wake up
silly where's the camera
that was a cute song
oh shoot
oh my God I finally filled this whole
okay oh
okay
[Music]
I'm lazy town oh man
I need to see how this looks
this is right right yeah this is right
right totally everything you do is right
I think I'm gonna start on the other
side actually oh my God
wait isn't that we are number one hey
what
we uh you wanna we are number one
oh look the red moon is coming or
leaving
there's a there's a red moon here and a
blue moon here
hold on Alma said something I'm in the
chat detective in the chat
hey am I still here and you're chat
break it down
that's right
is this correct
is it
oh I think it is
[Music]
correct yay
anyway good I want to know
um because uh speak talking about my
um
my vacation in Greece right you know
what I have once again realized what is
that
it is that I hate sand and all my homies
hate sand and hate is of course in
Europe and irritating and it gets
everywhere yeah you as a as a uh
as the official fish in the sea who
obviously has to deal with a lot of sand
how do you how what's your what's your
stance uh with sand what's the
relationship with sand oh it sucks but I
only have to deal with it when I'm out
of the water that was the first time
when I came to Lynn I realized I'm like
wow this sucks it's hot and it sticks to
everything
okay that makes sense because when
you're in a lot of swimming it's really
not irritating at all that's true it's
actually just soft and nice when you
when you feed our all the sand in the
water yes I thought you were gonna be
like I love sand and all that but no not
necessarily what the hell is going on
here nah screws in yeah the good thing
about sandals when you're under the
waters you can like dig chairs out of it
they make really comfy beds you can like
dig chairs and stuff yeah dig a hole
what dick dick cherries out of the sand
no no dig like a chair hole have you
ever you can do the uh on land as well
but you can do it under the water too
yes it sucks
don't quite know what you're talking
about
but also because this is confusing me
right now what is this is this correct
what is even on that sign okay so uh we
have no no uh
this is straight and then a brown one
here
oh yeah yeah and then
and then this here correct
right
yeah I have someone controlling my
homework checking my homework I love
that yeah
[Music]
so fill this up with orange until this
point nice wait wait wait wait
foreign
[Music]
starts right
okay
that is gonna be another challenge
because it goes outwards again
ah
[Music]
um
kill the circus music because the clowns
are in town
that's us we're the Clones what is this
what is this where am I is this where I
think I am yeah okay on top of this is I
think
it's color right right back
and then
I don't know it's green now green and
green should we sleep because it's the
colors are a bit hard to see
again
okay let's go don't fall down go down
you don't need to die whenever I wanted
to sleep you died until now so how about
you don't die I will do my best but I
cannot make any promises
nice okay
good morning
wow it's a red moon
Ohio red moon Ohio it's so scary why is
the why does the Sun not come up anymore
is it because I'm here oh
it almost makes me so
shy and embarrassed when her and the
boys like to say that I'm their son they
do say that sometimes that's why I have
to wear the sun hat because you're so
bright
i i i i i blind myself with my own light
okay let's go
[Music]
let's do this let's do this how many how
many how many how many up until here
[Music]
let's go let's go
you're sure
looking good
really
I think so
what I have the original creator of this
pixel art happened with my homework and
I guess you've got ammet is she actually
actually
um checking if you're doing everything
correctly though I wonder you're
probably just listening on the side nah
she's she's peanut gallery she keeps
adding like peanut Gallery yeah
oh
peanut gallery
was that mean it means like um
uh oh God how did you describe the
peanut gallery that's like
oh how would you describe that
when you think I made a mistake
oh no where am I shouldn't there be
brown here yeah yeah yeah okay I can
easily fix that that should be brown
just because one block
right
a back seating I don't understand that
you have to uh explain that to me uh let
me see if Chad has a good explanation
um
um people people making funny comments
yeah
from the outside saying silly stuff
Why didn't I didn't want called peanut
gallery that is so cute I think peanuts
is I don't know like like crazy people
what are you doing Peanut Gallery she
says she'll be doing a thorough
inspection later though
that is so good yeah
actually
that is so cute oh that is all of this
just orange until the end
it's orange for a while
one two one two one
this should be correct
the circus audience
oh yeah
uh
well Mama one two
I can't count one two
oh come on come on I believe in you one
two three four one two three four
and then oh no
what did you do oh no it's right it's
right it's red is right it's right as
red is right wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait one right ah one and
then
I think all right taco mom
another rhyme
oh my God got a freaking heart uh cats
and
hearts and what
a heart oh yeah let me tell you what
heart attack in German is hats in fact
Hudson
sounds like my heart is yes it
sounds like
that's what it means too no it's not
you don't write it like the English word
but yeah
thank you duke thank you is that from
Norway that's so cool I want to go to
Norway no way good night I think you
will you will like it there as a as a
fish in the city I think you will like
Norway
Maybe
hmm wait eyes white eyes white eyes
white yeah I need to focus to where the
hell am I again
white one two three industry right okay
so
one more orange
one more orange orange until
oh
no orange until
here
right then
one more layer of
that color yes
what is that is
this Color
Wow Wow
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah
how's it going Gora it's going all right
I think
you look very thin you should I don't
know eat some more shrimps perhaps
um
I have watermelon that's all I have now
though
yeah that's why you're so thin right now
I think
I'm
frog again later
not not sticking Phoenix meat or
whatever
[Laughter]
oh
cyan
oh wait how do you pronounce that
cyan Maybe
but that's just the same that I said
right cyan sign in no your Empress
science
yeah
Super Saiyan Super Saiyan have they made
a meme event it made a mean of that a
meme of that Super Saiyan they must have
is it is it orange now or one orange and
then the other color again
that's not orange is that orange
is that supposed to be orange I guess
that the light is so bright right now
white white white white white white
white white
oh geez why
red where am I where am I
saying am I doing it right
I don't she's doing it right
they may never know
so loud I haven't been never looked at
uh looked at it from below for a long
time now so
I'm really curious I hope they oh I
wonder if you can even see it from below
properly and unless you you make your
random distance really really high I
hope you see it properly
all our hard work
yeah
okay so I think there should be sand
over there
okay okay I know what I'm doing I don't
know what I'm doing one and
and
right and
four and I think one more here
oh
don't be dumb and I'm free sand
ow stupid Earth how did you go did you
go down to look at it I did
oh can you also see how mine looks but I
guess oh no you can't really see it from
there you probably have to go all the
way down look
how does yours look she's coming
together doesn't look correct to
understand any mistakes no it actually
looks correct
right now though
[Music]
yeah all right let's see Kiara's now
oh
looking good
I have both arms nice
hey and I'm working on the hair on the
side as well
and I'm all right now I'm doing I'm like
around the boobies
are you not missing a real potential am
I talking about am I missing around oh
tell me I'm not missing around
I shouldn't be it
did I miss a whole row
by the way that's possible to check
science what do you mean check science
science
what do you mean it's okay okay
fun right I'm fine I'm fine I'm doing
fine
she's all right
I think you had extra science in the
beginning
over there
I'll I'll look at it but I didn't I at
least didn't forget the whole row did I
wouldn't wait wait no no no no
uh sand and then free Orange
one blue two three
and then three cyan
uh-huh uh-huh
white white white
Orange
the peanut gallery refers to the seed's
farthest from the stage where people
would criticize their insignificant
insignificant details of the performers
[Music]
oh that makes sense that makes sense
that's like if you're looking for who
asked you know like if somebody if
you're talking about something and
somebody goes oh and says some kind of
stupid comment you're like hey thanks
peanut gallery nobody asked that kind of
thing
I like that yeah
in in German we would reply to that with
who else
huh Latin maybe add a little bit of a
win after betting Platinum so that okay
people are shocked probably that I said
that
what does that mean
I said a swear word I usually don't like
saying swear words in German
say it again
thank you
you know what I I will go myself
I will do that
how do you say uh uh
uh
I say this
this like this
that specifically but you know what you
could also say
we also like to say um stick they can
Snee when we're really mad we say
yourself into the knee
yeah I don't know why we say that the
fake dick is clean
why
is it funny
I can't talk back
you can take all my words and I can't
say anything but yeah
you you chose to pick on someone that
who cannot talk back to well as well as
like if I can eat it so
yeah
this says this is uh I feel very bad
why
uh because I said you know you know how
I swear a lot in English yeah yes um
but the thing is actually people ask
like when I when I speak German they
expect me to that I expect that I like
wearing the same amount in German as
well but it's actually not true that was
a really real exception right now like I
I'm I guess very very say so when I
speak in German I think
the things that I just told you
it hurt me in my heart to tell you those
things like I I really can't but I I I I
I can't get myself to swear uh in German
on stream normally
um
you know that maybe the words don't have
the same weight to you in English
exactly yeah exactly yeah yeah that's it
that is true my dear godal instead of
lying
yeah thank you
yeah yeah yeah
oh okay
back to focusing back to work we
obviously can't do two things at once uh
um
okay okay I'm going back inside I'm done
with going outside I'm going back inside
nice I like it that means that this goes
here
oh this one
no this one
[Music]
white white blue
six
what
nope nope nope nope
how you doing how you doing
did you ask me yeah yeah that was yeah
I am
doing
beautifully actually yeah
um I'm doing really fine you know what
taking two days off was uh really
refreshing
yeah sometimes sometimes I don't know it
does really good things for your brain
and plus it gives you time to do stuff
like outside of streaming so that when
you come back you're like so much to
talk about because like I was I was
actually talking about that in the
member stream uh yesterday because I was
like Hey guys uh absolutely nothing has
happened between then and now because I
just went to bed and woke up so hey
what's up
yeah I watched a clip of you where you
talked about needing to take days off in
order to come back with stories and that
is very true yeah
yeah did you ever do jet skiing go down
jet ski no I think I almost got to do it
uh but it had a really bad sunburn and
Mama sharks said no and I cried about it
oh
oh yeah
um
how do you like roller coasters because
if you like roller coasters you might
like jet skiing
um I I need to be encouraged to get on a
roller coaster but then afterwards I I
kind of go in a fighter flight mode
where it's like well I'm here now
and then I enjoy it
so if you went with me and you said do
this or else I'd be like haha okay
and I probably
I'm kind of similar to you when it comes
to roller coasters it's not my favorite
thing to do but like I I it's somewhat
easy to get me on it but then I regret
it afterwards and I I basically die
every time I'm on a roller coaster it's
not right not very fun pictures
oh yeah they're another really funny
though
I look at my face and I'm just like in
pain obviously pretty much anything
because you gotta time it you got a
timer you gotta guess where the camera
is gonna be you gotta make funny things
people know though why is everyone
honestly written a ride like these
hundred times and they have like a chess
board and like stuff they pull out I
don't know how how unsafe is that
try it at some point but like oh like
um like last time uh when I was in the
roller coaster with a friend like she
was the roller coaster a few times so
she kind of knew where the camera was
and then she was like Kiana the little
camera is here right now coming up and I
was like okay and but like I didn't see
it I still missed out on it and she was
posing cutely and I just messed up
I was just yet again looking very much
in pain because I never looked good in
these things
it's hard all the wind's blowing in your
face and you're probably mid-scream and
one of your eyes is closed yeah do you
ever do like the loop-de-loop ones ever
been the one that goes upside down
yeah I I I I have had the pleasure to be
in one of those before yeah
uh at least it's like very quick
um most of the time but it makes me
again feel like I'm dying
I think that's a mutual feeling oh do
you know there's those big big ass ships
that go from one side to the other side
and your stomach basically just wants to
throw up when you're on it
yes
you know which ones the huge massive
ships like there are eventually back and
forth like yeah
[Music]
yeah
I don't like those either
I've never been on one of those I've
been on I mean do you know those ones
are like carnivals where they it's like
a big hamster wheel and they spin you
around and around
uh you mean spin you
um
um how to say that oh like like a
centrifuge a human centrifuge oh I think
I've been in one of those before but
there there's there's a like nice ones
too there's bad ones and there's nice
ones I think oh
the red moon
okay red one here and then I think one
more
lights
a duck wait what white green
Stone
white white white white white white
hi we're on the same height did you make
both arms by now uh almost I haven't
done the arm yet but um I'm on the uh
yeah
I feel like a hotel I have to go all the
way up now because my scaffolding is uh
wow
I haven't I have barely used my
scaffolding because I full one did not
fall down yet
[Music]
now so what happened soon probably she
jinxed it
thanks
for me I'm knocking my head there you go
makes the same sound yes
how many four
what yeah I think it's one two little
three four
um blue and
[Music]
Orange
one two three four five six six red nice
one
oh my God I can't believe we're actually
like when I finish this one two one two
yeah three four five six it's not taking
as long as I thought it would either so
I might want to do this more often more
decoration
did they just what just happened what
did that was that a bug or did I heat
those out of my inventory
oh
they are okay Minecraft thank you for
being weird
wait a second
where am I
what
wait I didn't fix them I didn't look and
fix something that I wanted to look at
ah because uh
you said that I did too much uh cyan
oyster or turquoise on the other side
did I
I wonder
what what I think it was okay okay but
wait a second something's not this is
here something is not right
uh
wait a second
this this this huh
wait what
oh
have you tried pressing F5 while you're
standing there you can suddenly look at
it much better
oh dear God that helps a lot
[Music]
hey thanks Chad
Chad yeah
wow okay what is going on here how long
have we been playing this game how many
times I mean I know the existence of it
but I didn't think it would be useful
here I have a tail what
you didn't know you have a tail not on
my model on this thing oh wait you
actually never
I've never seen my butt before in
Minecraft or I have but I haven't
noticed it
okay because I'm sure for photos you
must have used F5 before
yeah
huh
not the more you know
the more you know
oh so where did I mess up here did I
mess up
uh wait where was I
Advent Day Advent
the blue yeah something is wrong here
but only in the upper row not in the
below row right
oh wait
wait
there's ah did I use
what
I totally messed up real world uh oh but
I told I I think I was like one off with
everything right
one one too far am I still ordered
[Music]
let's get rid of it and make it again I
think I'm gonna have to die to get down
for me for me I still have like a little
bit to go with my with my scaffolding
but I am ready to die afterwards I'm so
ready do you see that tiny thing of
water down there yeah we could try to
jump in in some water yeah there's a
little pool of water we can make it easy
there's two blocks of different oh hold
it wait I'm gonna continue here uh
wait that's not right sand
oh wait wait
I'm like here
I mean I lost orientation completely
oh no they know that there's oh no this
all right
and then two
of that
and then orange
right I need
all right I'm trying to jump
and now I think I think I got it now
are you jumping good
no
good job
promo
got it
I thought you were gonna die but okay
I'm just gonna use white wool
no do it
for what for us instead of snow Yeah it
costs for like a snow
yeah I got some snow in mine too but I
don't have snow so I'm just going for a
wool as well I think that's fun pretty
much the same
color
oh all right I made a look whoopsie
oh what did you do this time I yeah ah
you see a mistake from looking From
Below yes in the middle or at the very
top can you still fix it without getting
rid of everything else oh yeah I could
face it like a big noise yeah
yourself
oh how am I supposed to get back up oh
that might be a problem one two three
four five one two three four five
one two three
four five
one
[Music]
two
am I in the right room oh wait
am I am I here dakuma is that where I am
my hero
I think it's time for me to build my
other hand
do it you need two hands good on
well
you could also replace them with some
with with some fin thins yeah fins on
the forehand sounds not that give
yourself some fins
and then you can swim in the air like uh
like the air fish
an air fish
yeah
all right
foreign league in the fish
oh no I don't know where to start oh
oh wait yeah I do oh
oh wait was that
oh no okay
one
two three
[Music]
all right
one
two
what I'm still kind of weird oh
arm your arm is weird ah Johnson the arm
looks a little weird
they are weird what's that over there
what
what the hell did I mess up I messed up
huh
what is that what is that
focused on
I don't know
red
yeah no it's the tip of the hair but I
missed something huh
oh I messed something up
oh
[Music]
I think I think
yeah yeah mama yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
go down
wait the time what's wrong with the tie
it looks
I'm so confused fine is it isn't that
orange here
oh the arm is messed up
know that fine but going back
this one is wrong too
I think
oh God this is so busted
it's okay
yeah my arms messed up they're all right
it's okay though I can fix it
and something I think I fixed mine too
nice
yeah
and then you you
know and then it goes up
here
yep I should be right
nice and easy one two three four one
let's just go straight up from here
okay no I think it's correct chat don't
don't
yeah yeah this red is incorrect as well
yes yes yes yes
I was not that far yet
okay wait one
can we sleep it's dark
yeah we can thank you I think that is a
good idea because I I don't see the
colors anymore evil so dark can't see
I've died three times
I changed myself in the beginning
because I said you know what I've
decided I'm not gonna die wow
guess what well this went very well
very well
um
but it's getting very dangerous like
this this height is very very dangerous
and we are we didn't take uh any
security precautions
nope living on the edge
so basically
I think I see it
is it
this and then this is wrong
they won two
three
four
five
nice back jump okay
ah I told him we was looking at
something else there because
why is the blue there
yeah I think I skipped some parts there
what is the pool there
I must not grow up again okay okay let's
just get rid of all of that we do
I think I just like um
uh-huh yep yep
one wait wait wait wait wait
oh so okay okay that's easy that's easy
that's easy now that that's gone
nope
basically that's that
which means
this goes here
and then
yeah we just fill this up probably
I think I got the haters
just don't fall
this arm is too long what do you mean
[Music]
what did you do
oh no
what wait no it's not it's in line with
yours turquoise should be
here
you sound like Gollum
in what happens here
so
what did I do ah
what did I what did I do
oh now all right
oh halfway through is getting really
complicated here oh dear
um
up until what points should I get rid of
this and make it over
well
is that that is that part incorrect too
we'll see if underneath okay no no that
should be correct then
man
I I I
oh God now what
well that looks about right on that side
and then
[Music]
haha
are you losing your mind as well yeah a
little bit
just because I I started building before
I double checked
[Music]
I think I think
I think I got it
Okay so
uh what what
so here
wait one more
um that and then one and two
um sand and one and two
and
did you fall down again no I just saw
something no no no no no no no no no
everything is
fine bye
thing
it looks around right now yeah yeah
I fixed it nice wait one two three four
one two three okay
[Music]
I messed it up again somehow
if something happens right you you think
you're following it oh correct me and
then you realize at the very end of the
row oh something went wrong
still too long
what
oh my word how did you what did you make
too long my arm is too long
it's still too long I'm messing up again
I got it this time
Oh wrong color
nice
nice one two
three
one two three four five nice this row is
perfect easy one easy
so good at what are you having for
dinner tonight
[Music]
oh you know what that's perfect height
okay that's good we can look at it from
below now
I guess that's still a good height
that's the last time I will go down
dinner panel will go down watermelon
watermelon
[Music]
and an energy drink and maybe a
hard-boiled egg yeah
what the hell that's that's literally
your lunch and your breakfast though
yeah what the heck is going on here I
keep what
what I want to talk excuse me Chad
recently I've been I I found this one
pesto sauce in the supermarket that has
been absolutely magical so I've been
eating that uh for the past two days
yummy today will be the third day that I
will eat that because it's so yummy it's
um walnuts and Bella what's Bella in
English
pesto sauce it's so good
foreign
wild garlic and walnut uh pesto sauce
pesto do you know what pesto is going on
because yeah like my English speaking
viewers always think I'm talking about a
normal pasta sauce but there's a
difference between pasta sauce and pesto
sauce uh how do they know pesto sauce is
like uh like green and yeah it's
garlicky and Herby and yummy
you get the description right but it
doesn't have to come in green that
there's others as well actually but yeah
most of them come in green now
there's red pesto as well right yeah
yeah yeah yeah I think it's any sauce
it's not tomato sauce it's garlicky and
Herby right
yeah I love those so much I'm so into
those that's like my one of my favorite
things to cook because it's so easy and
I I usually add some like cherry
tomatoes to it and uh sometimes I add
some
um some some other things like zucchinis
or sometimes I even add like small a
little small Stripes of bacon or
sometimes I add water it's tiny tiny
baby mozzarella balls to it and all
kinds of stuff yeah yeah
mm-hmm all right what other color and I
need some pink some more pink probably I
don't want to go down anymore after that
so
I think a little bit of
[Music]
um
one two one two
this is
do I have black I have some black I
might need some more black wait
F5 right
[Music]
I'm gonna probably need some more Shams
much more sand
is that enough is that enough sound
to see
for the rest because it's like all of
the face
uh oh it could be enough I also need a
tiny bit of green
and a bit more yellow
oh I'm on right now
what are you doing fixing it maybe
that's slime wait three one two three
blue
no no now what what why am I having so
much trouble with this no I'm having so
much
so many issues with this one arm
this is
oh okay
[Music]
all right whatever if I need to go look
down again I'll come down okay okay
ten more light blue
I have light blue if you need it
actually no I don't need any more light
blue above that because it was only
those uh feathers and above that there
is no more okay no I'm fine thank you
chat but and thank you good but no more
light below for me
oh man look at oh my God you're big
but I'm also looking so that looks so
adorable those dresses look so cute they
are very cute they look even better if I
could do it right
like they're so floral I love that so
much the designs that you not you not
made you not made our music video and
the Arts and the designs and they're so
cute what do I hear a zombie
oh that shocked me
wait like this
one two three four one two three four oh
my am I am I oh my God
I know that you probably know that Amai
means uh sweet right yeah but in this
sense when I say
it means wait I can't really think of
the English word for it but it means for
example that you're doing something
recklessly maybe
like not good enough you're on again
underestimating I guess would also be a
way to or naive in a naive way
um so if you don't put enough torches
down here then you would say
because bakitobushi is trying to do to
hold back the spawning of enemies that's
about kitsubishi ah
and I'm calling that Amaya because we're
doing it not good enough we're doing it
naively thinking that this is enough
it is not enough as we can see
am I
Chicago
drops have you heard that one
no is that a new one I have only really
knowledge of Vocaloid songs from back of
from like seven to ten years ago oh uh I
don't think it's new necessarily but
it's definitely newer than seven to ten
years ago it's super cute though
I think the only
um Vocaloid producers that I have been
keeping up with is my favorites from
back in today which would be for example
and Michi
also produced my new song Sparks streams
yeah those I guess are my two uh
favorites uh Deco Nina and uh and uh
um got it what did I just say
oh what was the other one I just
mentioned not Kira I mean the other one
what's that my mind oh my brain mine is
Michi Michi um
[Music]
yeah
I love the part where they're putting in
some was that Spanish or Italian
are you here to help me
up your things that's all right that's
all right
okay wait the red needs to go under the
red needs to go under the red needs to
go on the red needs to go the red needs
to go under the red needs to go
under the red needs to go under the red
needs to go under and then the red needs
to be underneath the first Blue Block
okay okay fix the time sorry I'm really
struggling with this yes
in-game only all right
you know we're gonna do a fresh respect
reset
[Music]
I am dated how about you you motivated
please no more no I tried so hard to be
free from that curse
see I don't I guess I don't really have
that feeling because I didn't play the
game but I kind of find it funny because
my my people started
um like meming that at me in my chat and
I didn't even know the origin of it not
really though not really no but now I
kind of knowing that for now for now I'm
I'm still very entertained by it so
it's all right Virgil shows up some way
or another every single stream either I
bring it up but Chad brings it up so now
I'm motivated huh
Virgil
which role am I on I don't know at the
bowl where is where in the very middle
there's this one spot of sand right
mm-hmm
which means that the next thing I would
come here is this
no
not too much
yeah
what the hell
I know that's the real um run row above
ah the sand comes after that huh
okay okay
wait wait
you sneezing no no no no I'm figuring
out this stupid this stupid ah okay
we're good
no we're not good we are not good I'm
still I I'm getting there honestly
[Music]
one two three four
I am having fun I'm just
I did need a
wait this is this is just the exact
amount I need I think yep
yeah it is
because it goes like this
that's exactly what I did I did not even
calculate that is this too many
one nice two three four five this is
five and it's supposed to be one two
three four it's supposed to be four I
just I just
you
sound broken you sound a bit broken
[Music]
my toe
bye towel
it's all right
uh-huh
indeed
yeah yes
hi hi
hi hi hi
oh I have the new public it's happened
in the full commandant Republic it can
be house is
yay
mm-hmm
yep
yep yep yep yep okay okay
let's continue on that side
oh my god I think I'm doing I'm gonna
mess it up somehow though I just know it
oh I'm doing the line of my face now it
seems like it
at least
yep
okay that means huh
um
one two three I finally did it I
finished my arm
s
we can now do you cute clapping sound
waiting
I need more light blue oh do I need it
on the other side
oh God damn it okay we're still yeah
we're still at the point where I can go
down
all right
I need what seven more
we're still going down
you wanna build up
a pirate ship
oh wait I'm not I'm laughing in a
comment but yeah pirate ship sounds good
they did that in the Japan server it
looks so good yeah it looks like it took
them a million hours yeah yeah yeah
that's the one I'm talking about that
looks so good yes
you should do it do it
no wait don't let your dreams be dreams
do it
I did it
now I gotta fix the other one
uh oh you messed up the other one too
the other one's really messed up yeah oh
dear
wait
I can look at it from Below
I'm down here right now
maybe I'll leave it it might be better
to leave it because I might have to redo
a lot
uh
it's wrong
yeah but it doesn't look like so bad it
looks okay okay I think you could keep
it because yeah you really did go up
quite far right now yeah
maybe we're about the same Pace pretty
much
um
my arms
it doesn't bother me from down here
unless
OCD might have a problem with that
I'll fix it for you
hey all I can fix my arm please I can
I'll go back to it we'll move on we'll
move on
because they don't know like how how
they don't have a exact uh guide of how
it's supposed to look like except for
that tiny one on our screens yeah it
doesn't make a big difference it'll be
all right
I might die I'm gonna hook it down and
get more colors
mistaken mine I don't think so
those hurts to look at because I'm so
used to looking at mine and yeah
you're so cute they are cute I'm excited
to see them when they're all done
they're so cute it looks so good and it
does show oh you're down here too it
does show up from below properly so I
might not taller than you oh I don't
know anger
I mean I mean just because you built a
little bit more of your
um on on on your head by now don't get
cocky don't but
yeah okay
you want to fix it or not
no
I got kicked out oh
all right
come back
now
I'm still streaming right guys you see
me you hear me right you're on my side I
can hear you on the side and see you oh
[Music]
hello I'm already back
okay let's bring food do we have any
food
do you you don't you had to eat a lot of
food tacos you I keep dying I mean I'm
around with dying I don't need it but uh
if you need it you can take it from the
community chest there's also still
cookies in there if you want to
oh they made them for you I made them
for you but I don't want to eat through
them all because they don't they only
give like one Health and I'd have to
like continuously eat all of them
right now
bring you the food go down
there's building I gotta do
I just fix that eventually all right
[Music]
there's a weird delay between our two
streams who who is uh
who is delayed me or her I'm with leader
my internet faster right no no they say
they say I'm faster than your stream
in my stream you will get all the all
the depths of good are faster than
anyone else
oh let me give you food while you're
down here thank you
you're my child thank you take take half
of my food 48 seconds faster 30 seconds
what are they timing this
do you have the stream setting set to uh
okay it says it here in Japanese for me
so actually I actually don't know what
it's called and
English
like low latency oh yeah yeah I I chose
the one that's at the very bottom which
one do you always choose I always use
that one but sometimes uh
uh uh I when I I feel like you know when
you reuse settings right it'll
automatically set it but I'd start a new
stream for this one and I always go back
to the first one yeah I forgot that
setting ah dang it that's the one thing
I forgot to do because I thought I did a
reuse for this this stream but I didn't
so sorry guys that's why there's delays
that makes sense all right can I win the
sleep we can sleep I need more
scaffolding I need to make more
oh yeah I'm I'm at the point where where
I accepted the fact that if I go any
higher than this then there will be no
uh scaffolding
um
how about the chat people know about DVR
I don't I I don't even really know what
DVR is I just know that I should always
turn it off because YouTube
automatically always turns it on DVR is
like so when you're watching a live
stream people can like go through and
scrub scrub through the beginning
whereas if the DVR is off then they
can't go back until the bond is done
I'm pretty sure
Oh you mean like if I'm streaming hmm
live still if I had DVR on they could go
oh yeah that's cool though like if you
lose uh if you come into the stream too
late and you still you wanna you don't
want to wait until the archive is ready
you wanna oh yeah I don't why don't
people tell us to turn it off I kind of
like that setting hmm
why do people turn it on uh
yeah okay I just I just followed that
too I said I see I say oh
it doesn't really matter though because
people are recording streams anyway
yes
protect you from the oven you say that
well done
I need scaffolding and stream
and I'm not I don't think I have any but
it might be something
probably finally tell you the secret
location of all of her scaffolding
either scuffling apparently yeah
what's she playing
no Mario Mario
wow
all right
I have this feeling that normally she
starts a little bit later
uh what time is it it's from me it's for
me it's midnight
I have no idea time zones I'm gonna go
PPP and get a thingy
why there's a dark wood what
all right I'll be fast yeah one time
where was I where was it
where was I there's some watermelon
water oh oh oh I'm here ah here I am
one two three
something's messed up here
hold it
oh no no
ah I love what I said
that one's supposed to be red DVR adds
delay and that's why people hate it
DVR DVR
getting very technical here I'll say I
really like it
is the lighting bugged I don't know
oh there's also like in the new update
there's also like gems you can find
right like the like there's like a
stalagmites and stalactites and all that
I want to go check out the new stuff but
I have to probably wait until my next
Minecraft stream next week or so yeah
yeah yeah I'm gonna go wanna go check
out everyone like well what is there to
see besides those species everyone's so
hyped out hyped up about those fishes
but what's up
[Music]
that's well I think that's pretty much
it but yeah the the caves the caves
because it was only half the update the
caves is the next update I think right
oh right they didn't add that yeah the
the new material that you get in the
cave what was it called I have no idea
but I know only half of it is updated
I forgot
purple gems
still like my tight
you can Farm lava now what does that
mean
no I mean yeah I mean copper copper is
already available don't know
no I don't think Copper's in the game
yet
oh
what do you need copper for I don't know
what's it for it
so you can build like is that like gonna
be an in-between material between like
Stone and gold there's gonna be like
stones
my spine is either you don't use it for
creating
um armor or weapons you don't use it for
that you use it for other stuff
oh okay yeah but but there's no copper
armor or anything like that
going in for the cheeks what cheeks
not the butt cheeks unfortunately
wow yeah I don't know why there's no
butt in this
challenge until the giant Shred
oh wait baby it's not an idea on your
own or did you oh yeah copyright where
are we or did the chat tell you that
that's all from up here baby
thank you
is that also where did she goes yeah so
in between is all sad
nice
okay
I'm bringing scaffolding I have two
stacks of 60.
oh nice hmm
very nice
with a big butt maybe we can do it
ourselves
don't ruin it that's let's not ruin it
we'll probably just make it worse I feel
like that's something Watson would do
pretty and beautiful
because I was the one that added the
boom booms on her little statue thing
I don't know what you're talking about
you
did I just hear cat meow
[Music]
one of my cats is rolling on the floor
from one side into another side and
she's like meow meow stretching herself
just like hit my belly
cute wow
[Music]
cute that it's smoothie
smoothie
she wants my attention yeah
no you don't have to build this thing
okay so we are here so there is two more
of that
oh
[Music]
more of that
um one of that
up up
you know
watermelon
do you do you spit out the seeds or do
you crunch and and eat them I spit out
the hard seeds but I eat the like the
white seeds I want yeah yeah yeah me too
me too
how many blocks is that
four four sand plugs and then the mouth
Dogma
one two three four
I think it's fine
yeah
and then there would be this one here
yeah yeah
in the attack
yeah that's how it is
wait two no wait Frank did I make did I
mean yeah so I should be free free white
oopsie
coming
I breathed in the mistake you bring the
scaffolding noise could you add some uh
to my tower of scaffolding at the very
bottom just add to it yes my queen
just making this big uh I guess just add
one full stack I guess that should be
probably enough because you got two
stacks right yes my queen
scaffolding
[Music]
sausage
of course I know that
[Music]
going to the Moon
was not necessary I'm not going that
high
it's all right it's better to be
prepared yeah
why the hell am I now you're just this
[Music]
um
steak fries
misheard Anime Lyrics
oh I guess I I heard I watched videos of
mishaired lyrics in general yeah
not necessarily Anime Lyrics though
um
red okay well
now that I have the scaffolding oh this
is no more issue
finally I'm building again yay
you weren't away for that long
I'm getting stuck on the arm and I had
to redo the arm over and over
wait we've been doing this for
three hours now well
um
anywhere at the face now huh
not bad
is it
huh
is it not bad I don't know do you wanna
you wanna sleep again one two three four
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait let
me do a one two three one two
three sleeping while looking at those
beauties
all right
I made a mistake hello
oh yeah I might have maybe
[Music]
this is the vine Exquisite did you see
my
did you see my newest my green screen
clip thingy
um I saw the thumbnail but I didn't see
it yet no it's basically just me
pointing at nothing and being like okay
but this is divine
Exquisite and now people have been
putting it on on top of everything
literally everything like um on top of
Cali's ass for example and they're like
but this is exactly what I intended to
do so that's good
which side is incorrect we're both
incorrect oh Kelly
[Music]
here this Vlog is one more to the left
is it
yeah and then dude this is this bubble
those are red
now I think I get it
all according to kikaku
translator's note better is short
oh
[Music]
no oh no
oh I'll try oh I guess I just dig down
here instead of getting rid of all the
road that's not necessary right
sorry if I add this here to one and two
here and then one here
I'm gonna have to yeah I think I can
work around it right
oh
that gonna tell me 40 minutes ago God
damn it what did I tell you about red
okay
wait where does this
nothing just
[Music]
here we go
no not like that no
[Music]
what is your exhale I just need to get
rid of that part not the whole all of
the rows right okay
[Music]
goddamn blocking
um
how
does this happen Kiara it doesn't make
sense someone is sabotaging us
sabotaging we're the only two on the
server though are you sure about that
you sure about it I don't know the
ancient ones are always watching us
the ancient ones maybe they can help
instead
uh-huh how about spotting us some free
Elite Trends huh yes please
[Music]
oh eyeball time
she brought me a bit more exact and not
eyeballing everything
oh no no I'm building eyeball unless
that was the joke one oh
I'm doing it
wait no so fast please oh
I can't keep up
okay so we get rid of like somewhere
uh-huh there okay
one two three four
five
come on
oh my God it's happening
what is happening yes
sparkly sparkly good at eyes okay
basically this
this
[Music]
um
okay what now
I'm gonna build one eyeball
wait wait wait
that is red
wait what
this one oh
well one two three
one two three one two three one two
three one
foreign
[Music]
oh no I've already messed up you're
joking no I haven't we're good
[Music]
am I doing it right destroy one sand
block
[Music]
huh oh no wait one oh no
wait I'm confused how do I open my
inventory again
oh no
um
oh man I hope I build these eyeballs so
like one's higher than the other that
would be funny
one two one two three one two
so
one two
three one two right
[Music]
I think I made a whoopsie
it's fixed
and you put scaffolding on like the
oh
I think I fixed it
I I tried to aim for the water I missed
that was on purpose I was actually I I
was seeing you fall down from my ankle
so that was nice
it was on purpose though it's all right
that was playing
Compton you're really an Entertainer
more than an idol
Entertainer first Idol second or either
last
goober first Idol last
let's build the other eyeballs
I am do I actually
um like
um like any kind of like real
um non-anime like real Idol groups from
Japan
do you know any
feel like I do
hmm
none are coming to mind right now
um
[Music]
yes I know akb48 oh I mean it's not my
favorite I guess you would know it
uh yes
um
[Music]
pretty popular do you know baby metal
although that yeah I don't know what I
call that give me chocolate
yeah but my my favorites are all from
Hello project do you know hello project
no does love live contest
that's an anime I I don't group inside
of an anime so I was talking about link
idle groups that are not from an anime
oh I see
um I guess you could call them Idols but
like Idols that were like part of a
story inside of an anime
it would recommend you
hello project idle groups yes yeah
especially Venice Global and cute and
smiling and juice juice and morning most
of them those are the best and maybe
what wait morning is that the song right
yes yes nobody Muslim is a group from
Hello project which has been around
since at least like 20 years I think
more by now because uh morning Muslim
keeps on getting new members and members
keep on leaving but it has like this
this this uh system of change changing
members and you know getting new members
all the time foreign
[Music]
groups a big thing in Japan yeah yeah
yeah it was the most popular Idol group
in Japan for a long time
that makes sense that makes sense
because that does sound familiar to me
but he says that song Maybe you know it
it goes like
[Music]
revolutions
is that their most popular song
uh one of their most popular socks yeah
wow I usually know songs by their
validation but not the things
[Music]
yeah
I freaking love it I used to be such a
huge fan
um I went to their concerts when I was
living in Japan yeah I went to a lot of
people project concerts and then I was I
was looking like such an
otaku I was real I was I was wearing the
whole attire and I was I had lots of
glow sticks with me and I was wearing
the t-shirts and onto the t-shirts I
have like their pictures pinned onto the
t-shirts I was wearing their wristband
and I was wearing every thing that you
can imagine and then they had these
these uh these towels they had small
towels which you would wrap around your
neck in order like sometimes they they
always have at least one song in a
concert where you would put take the
towel instead of the glow sticks and
then just
um like turn turn the towel like like a
cowboy you know what I mean oh like a
bandana
around your neck no no no no no you you
hold it with your hand and you go like
I yeah yeah you're swinging around yeah
yeah they always have at least one one
one song in the concert where you swing
your towel and at the end of the song
with the most hype they go like frog
every time everyone throws the tail in
the air and then you try to catch it and
it's really exciting
oh I see oh you have that but then if
you want to go one step further you have
one of their big towels as well and oh
my God their whole body is on it and you
you pin that until your back's like a
cape or onto your front as well as well
that's okay both is okay but there that
goes a little bit too far because then
you can still uh you can't copy their
choreography yeah yeah you need to be
able to move a lot because in hella
project concerts uh otaku is always copy
the choreography and they dance along a
lot like you sometimes you feel like
they that the the audience dance is
better than the idols and know the
choreography better than the idols
sometimes
yeah wow you really are a dedicated fan
my God
I was I was very well known I would also
get very good seats I would like sit in
the very front front for certain methods
that would get through seats and then I
would I would sit down there and then
the the the other Japanese otaku next to
me would look at me and be like oh
yeah
number one fan what about it buddy
exactly
oh that was good those were good times I
messed up something here I think
something's wrong here
I I also messed up somewhere
wait what or did I oh yeah
hold it
didn't I didn't I didn't
of course I did not wait one two
I think one two
one
next is two pinks and then one red okay
eat
I'm just going to those Island concerts
but all my favorites idle groups they
are graduated by now
oh that's very sad oh you know like
um uh
Coco said if I graduated and I was
watching the concert and it kind of like
reminded me of those times when my
favorite Idols graduated and I had to
watch the graduation concerts and that
was just the most painful thing ever uh
it reminded me of those times and it
reminded me like how I was like oh well
all of my favorite Idols are graduated
now good that I don't have to go through
that pain anymore uh surprise
oh yeah
yeah I mean I mean I didn't see Coco
Senpai in the same way as I saw those
favorite Idols from Hello project but it
it was still very painful to watch yeah
although most of it was uh
was very cheerful well that has to be
another color yep yeah I never really I
never understood how people can be like
such massive massive massive fans or
something like not even Idols but like
I guess other things people in general
I don't know it just never well I don't
know
again I'm a huge fan of one specific
thing no not to like not like a to an
extreme point of like buying merchandise
or anything like that hollow life yeah
because I feel like a part of it and
it's like supporting it all
but no like I know like like I remember
like music musicians like bands and
stuff people go crazy for bands and I'd
be like what why I don't understand
I don't know
I I haven't had that for a long time
either anymore and I kind of miss it but
I guess I get what you mean but that's
surprising to me like I I had I was very
very very into those Idol groups so
specific ones and very specific members
of those Idol groups back in the day but
it is a lot of fun to support them and
but it's very sad when they leave
um maybe that's why maybe my brain's
been like protecting myself for like
when that time comes I somebody leaves
or something like bands always uh they
they uh what is it they
they go their separate ways right like
group musicians they usually end up the
brand oh my God the band breaks apart
maybe my brain's been protecting me from
that moment
does that make sense my my brain is
hurting from this
I don't think your brain was thinking
that far oh
no honestly yeah I'm surprised
yeah
why this does not make sense
one two three what
[Music]
all right
this
and then orange
I'm also getting very close to the eye
next row I have an item good
how do you do this again and again and
again
you're like a monster of that you should
be a phoenix not me
sometimes we have reincarnated in this
stream this is so
slowly now then I don't even know who
the Phoenix is anymore
Cali must be real sick of seeing me
today
it's cute though oh my oh it's cute
dying my face my face is getting there
uh I am yeah just yeah you just wanted
to go down in order to see your face
right yes that was part of the plan I
didn't want to spend time going down the
the scaffolding huh
I think I'm messed up somewhere though
no
no no no
I just want to at least get this eye
done
one more
we still have
quite quite some big heads to go well
we've easily done 75 right we only have
like 25 left easy about a thing like
around the head area there's a lot of
um
a lot of bros where there's a lot of the
same color so you can easily mess up
like the num the numbers uh there like
be like ah
okay most of this is all one color and
you go for it and then you realize later
on that was not it
I have a feeling that that might happen
um I need to do this still need to speed
up a little bit
but I have hairs on my nose
cat hair everywhere
okay where was where was we
where is that right that goes on for a
while and then
well we are here now so
um we do I have one and then white
we do
maybe that's what the problem was
in a light
oh hey I'm doing hi
I think I did it
not what you did but I'm proud of you
my name was saying though I think
I'm gonna get some more sand
four
what is it four I think it's four
I hope I have enough and
hmm
one two three blue
notes
one two three
one two three four
oh she's going well
uh on the white one sand one
Orange
oh my God
uh one
you
and then one two and then we go up one
okay nice
oh wait
we go outside again by one
and uh
here
um
[Music]
it's so hard to see one
one two three
I'm on top of my eyeball
right one
oh
um
uh to uh okay it's just the same
okay
oh
[Music]
no just some creative input that uh that
I could do on my
on my figure specifically
huh
no no
no I do what they have told me to do
well
I guess I'm gonna die
okay
why did you do that why was that there's
no way down I had to get down somehow
hey Morgan it was a strategic jump all
right uh-huh I need to go get more sand
I still haven't died a single time
except that one time when you killed me
and that does not count
all right I gotta go insane I'll be back
unless there's some sand in the Box
we'll see
um I don't think also if I almost just
died again
[Music]
let me see
blocks
how's it look crazy look
oh you look so cute
[Music]
oh my gosh the little hair the flippies
at the end they're like
so cute and your boobs look big this is
cute
you can add a layer and make them well
maybe not maybe that won't work yeah
that's literally what that German one uh
uh told me to do but I told him no
um
my work might not though hold on I gotta
get it
[Music]
okay so we have come to this point where
I have to do this I think yeah is that
correct
wow oh it's cute
[Music]
no wait was that supposed to be one
below
oh yeah
this is uneven
um
that is on that one here
one below that's okay
I think I understand
all right
do you need anything while I'm done here
no what do you think
granola I need something I'll just come
down on my own
bye
and we have a
orange and then we have a little bit of
a red
and that's it no we do this and we do
that
kfp how surprised are you that I have
not fallen down yet
you gotta do it at least once there's
still time yeah
for content right I'm hoping that this
happens naturally
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
actually uh but I didn't catch I guess
they played Devil May Cry I'm
unfortunate I missed that one it's a
game it's like a I think it's a charity
stream event or a bunch of speedrunners
play games really quick
oh yeah on that one specific person it's
like an event
yeah they have lots of different people
come on and they play different games I
was watching this person they were
playing like a medieval game that looked
I don't want to say it looks pretty bad
because I'm sure it's like amazing
people mad it looked it didn't look
great
but they sure did it quick yeah it was
like swords and castles and stuff
cool you know that that reminds me uh
there's a Sims 4 Sims free Sims 3
medieval game that was actually quite
fun really
um oh also I'm playing a Sims 4 again
next week I hope you will not be on fire
again
but I think next time I play Sims next
week I think it will be more about uh
Clara growing up you know me my mine and
Cali's child
because that one was born at the very
end of the last Sims 4 stream
and we waited her to grow up Clara
did you
did you adopt a bait how did that work
how
would that work
I think it's possible in Sims 4.
so you're telling me yes
and the place is good at me and me and
Kelly did it in many places we even did
it in your room I'm not asking about
that I'm asking about some Logistics
I think that one specifically was that
made a conceived in your bathroom or was
that after the birthday
wait is that I can't yeah I guess you're
not related to the baby I was gonna say
it's your niece or whatever but I guess
it's not because we're not oh my God
unfortunately
base or something
I guess
that I guess come on welcome someone new
to your family
still makes them feel unwelcomed
laughs
what's the Baby Gotta think huh who had
the baby
uh I think yeah yeah I'm the mama now
he's a dad what kind of question is that
I was just I just I just wondering all
right
um
didn't you watch the last Sims 4 stream
actually I didn't even say something
like that you laughed so much about it
did you only watch a part of it I guess
and well no I think I know about the
maybe I did watch I just don't remember
I know a long time ago and I know you
know I all drowned in the pool did she
drown or was she just in the pool she
was just chilling in the pool I think
and then
dogged out in the pool and she had uh no
hair anymore I think she was bald oh God
oh God
yeah but the moment oh yeah I was I was
uh at work and it was literally everyone
but me there but then you were cooking
and then you started setting a fire and
then and then uh Callie and I mean you
know we're trying to put you out and
that was when I came home
you like so good
hmm
Sims is fun I've never played Sims
before I played sport it's kind of like
sports oh yeah yes boy is also a pretty
cool game um
yeah
I know I never really got into it
because I guess just because it had not
um no I guess you could say it's cute
but um
I remember when sport came out it was
just kind of legendary that they did
something like that
yeah really one-ups Neopets take that
Neil pets
[Music]
is you you oh
my
I want to finish this today even though
we already took so much time I want to
finish this I don't know about you
if you don't wanna if you want to stop
somewhere let me know it's okay but I
think we got so close now we have to
finish it
Adventure
let's do it let's do it
[Music]
motivated
I'm so motivated I've come so far we
can't give up now no way
oh God
it's fun when the chat goes
motivated
[Music]
uh wait one wait
whoa one
and then and then wait one one
have you been keeping track if I've been
making mistakes or am I good
[Music]
sand all this gets tricky here one two
very tricky
I think it's okay I think so too
surprisingly
[Music]
yeah
okay so now we go one more outside which
means we do and this uh
oh God yummy
that's close
scary
on this am I right am I right oh am I
right
[Music]
um
uh this goes here and
jump jump
wait I'll be right back I'll be right
back okay okay okay I'm gonna BRB
I'm waiting for you okay
hello
hello everyone I'm gonna stream are you
listen to me am I am I am I Audible
hello hello
[Music]
if you if you uh didn't this is very
related to what we're building right now
but we're building I cooked about free
monuments what is this well me and gooda
have done an absolutely legendary
um so cover of this marmaloid song
called
wait what am I doing where am I what is
this correct probably probably fine
and
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's on my channel
if you have missed it
it has some really cute dance animations
even yes probably the first time and
maybe the last time that he was no just
kidding
is the first time definitely that you'll
see good at dancing yeah it has a really
cute envy and actually the the
um there's like translations of the
lyrics in there and I think it's really
really uh cute especially in combination
with the MV art
definitely something to look at and
enjoy
that looks good yeah
I just needed to remind you because I
think a lot of the good up here is
haven't seen it unfortunately because
it's not on her Challenge on my channel
because well it's it is that way because
I organized it
because I wanted to do it
yep oh but
I think everyone who has seen it can
recommend it to you guys
yeah
grandma is looking at me
listening very cautiously very excitedly
that's probably not really a word is it
can you say excitedly
oh what is your face oh
there TV eating she be eating
watermelons
probably
still muted
it is a word oh really huh
I kissed her
[Music]
stop doing that I I you know when you
blush it makes me blush it's so cute
[Music]
you know what since you were gone for no
one can I go too I need to wash my face
for God's sake it's so itchy yes
oh my God
what
I do it relay wow awesome
it did some audio thingy oh
yeah okay okay
I pulled the plug for a moment oh God oh
God oh all right see you in a minute all
right
all right kfp I'm in charge now
what's up
I have only in watermelon today so I'm
kind of running on fumes well whatever
watermelon is made of that's what I'm
running on
sugar and water
this is a workout for my brain girl is
in control right now that's right gurus
in control
can I have help with this
where's my brain
I need to like go down and build step by
step that's what I need to do oh wow I'm
already back that was fast oh my God I
just washed my nose your nose
yeah because it was like it's so itchy
because of all the cats here and hair
and the more I touch it because I also
have cat hair on my hands the worse I
make it yeah
I see
all right I saw you chat I saw you
trying to ask for SOS forever for you
asked her to get SLS no no not happening
what
no what what
by the way
[Music]
are you aware and do you have any German
viewers German Germany viewers hello
are you there dude
I don't know sometimes sometimes I get
like a oh wait I think I got a Super
Chat the other day that was in German or
they said something in german yes I see
a yes you probably have way more than
you're aware of probably
can I give them a message from me yeah
uh uh I'm fine I'll ghost in Dusseldorf
is
[Music]
don't call me yeah talk about that yeah
I heard about it tell them if they are
going to Dogo me they might
they might uh be able to do something
like meeting me
suggested me that's exciting yeah and
you know what I suggested because like
I've seen that whole life uh Japan
members have been doing like
um
like kind of like one-on-one meet and
greets with uh their fans and some
special events oh uh like them in one
room with a with a fan and and but but
like on a screen you know on the screen
on the table but but they're like they
have a webcam and they can see the fan
in front of them and all that and do
like live communication so I suggested
to talk on me that we'll do that
yes
oh my God that sounds exciting are you
excited yeah I'm so excited I'm so
that's it's like the first time that
I'll be able to like interact with fans
in that way so I don't like super
excited and I I was I'm gonna like
hopefully get them to take photos like
to get a movie like a selfie oh my God
yeah
super excited for that
[Laughter]
[Music]
doctor
Brazil time to die no I'm right at the
water gouda oh nice
but I have full health I might even if I
hit the ground that should be fine
probably oh
yeah why why am I the one that lives
what
typical Phoenix stuff you know
come back from the dead yeah I want to
show everyone how I go up in flames and
then I turn into ashes and then here I
am and everyone's like whoa
ah
but yeah I have I have Diamond Armor All
Over yeah oh that's why I didn't die yes
although I don't think do you guys think
I would survive a jump from here as well
from here down to there
hey guys thank God subscribers should we
test it out
[Laughter]
yeah anyway where were we
no no okay
you don't believe come on you just gotta
believe
I believe
I believe I can fly are you excited to
start up the ttrpg
[Music]
I think it's one more week yeah yeah now
we have something like this weekend was
my birthday and next week it's Kathleen
uh having something there yeah yeah
so we're doing it the week after that
finally we're getting to but that gives
me a bit more time to do my character so
I'm I'm a bit glad about that yeah
I'm excited I'm so excited for all the
characters to interact and stuff
[Music]
I'll be a bit shy maybe oh your eyes are
done it's so cute
sort of hopefully they look right we
don't know yet
oh yeah
do they look great oh
I feel um I don't know let me look at
the reference No it should be fun it
should be fun should be fun
when was the last time you looked at
them from down below oh a while ago they
look all right
uh did I finish the uh eyelash bro did I
one two three
oh no oh wait then I did something wrong
[Music]
Karina's house gonna have a huge shadow
oh I didn't think about that good it
looked like we're throwing a huge Shadow
over it to be honest from that from here
already
horrifying shadow
oh I guess because the sun is there
right now
I don't think she would mind
one two three
oh my brain power
wait not right right oh no
about it
I'm also losing it
oh I'm at that room
so that means this would be like that
right
um no this is here
now I go like that
oh wait no I don't know where I am oh my
God okay we're gonna fix this anyway I'm
moving on
uh here and then
here
um
until
I'm doing two rows at the time now
because I want to be faster maybe I
don't know this one I mean you know okay
I thought something about my thingy
I want one two uh
[Music]
one two three one two three four I think
I've lost my mind I think my sanity is
yeah the top of the head's jumping
yummy we can do it though
well you know I can do it we can do it
stats motivation let's go
something's wrong yeah
wrong
yeah I'm doing wrong I missed uh
something yeah
honey
honey no no no no no
mistake
mistake wait this is also wrong we're
hot
now we're fine we're fine we're fine
no we're not fine this is not fun
when you when when they say you're fine
but you're not really fine with you when
you find not fun
foreign
I love that
I love that Meme that's one of my
favorite memes yes how far did I have to
delete that
[Music]
basically
wait did you sound like you're going
crazy
you're losing your mind literally
iPad is an energy drink and three pieces
of watermelon and a whole lot of math
one two three four oh excuse me hold on
what math
okay the numbers
counting whatever
I would hope still okay no problem
[Music]
let's go
is there a red one supposed to go here
[Music]
hello
do you prefer hot weather or cold
weather
oh wow you're asking me questions now
huh yeah I had a little bit of brain
activity because I saw I had pineapple
here too oh fruit salad yummy yummy
I would prefer cold weather good choice
no no I am a phoenix I prefer hot water
it would make sense though if you prefer
cold weather because it's like you're so
used to hot all the time that like cold
is different I warm myself up anyway all
right so
mm-hmm yeah I mean um
one thing that I definitely don't like
though is humid weather
that one's really not good for my body
you know what it sucks
[Music]
it really does can you eat warm
pineapple
warm pineapple and you ask me if you can
eat it I guess you can't eat it but I
don't think it's really good am I gonna
get sick
no
okay
pineapple very good I eat pineapple very
often
love pineapple also pineapple is good
for your voice pineapple juice very good
Toki no sodas and bye told me that
yeah cause it
makes you salivate so it keeps dry mouth
okay it's like a green apple no the
reason for it but okay yeah green apples
and pineapple juice is recommended for
vocals if you have a bit of a dry mouth
or a
a dryness because it makes you salivate
you don't have a pineapple like
it's sourness you can do with green
apples as well there's something in
green apples that's supposed to be good
too yeah really
[Music]
I think I just realized a mistake here
though yeah
[Music]
one two three one two three oh we're
going in now woohoo
a lot more oh well whatever huh
on pizza
what are you talking about
pineapple pizza yeah I actually have one
I think that's what I'm eating tonight
because I have uh Frozen pineapple pizza
in my freezer yummy
what does that make the pesto pasta
pesto pesto noodles not sure
I want pesto it's been a while since I
impressed though my mom loves making
those by herself
um
and like she had this walnut tree
and when the walnuts were in season she
had like millions millions of walnuts
she was going crazy and she was making
so many things with llamas like
everything everything was walnuts
everything because you knew a lot with
walnuts roasted walnuts are yummy
that's my favorite thing to eat in
Christmas markets here
almonds roasted almonds yeah what's the
almonds and I guess chocolate covered
strawberries but yeah
[Music]
on it
um
so glowy whoa
oh my God
wait why does it always have to get rid
of so many
okay I don't know what I'm doing I don't
either
there's some creative freedom here right
now
um
one two
wait ah I made the I think I made the
bangs too low now but I guess it's okay
what do you think
[Music]
it's dark can we go to bed I can't see
yes nice wait sorry but that looks so
dope well look at me looking cool
wow
uh I was just looking at my beauty
[Music]
gazing upon my beauty
but I want to see what these look like
now let me see update update
oh
oh I need to get rid of that cute
did you go now are you looking at any
From Below yeah looks super cute
look like I made the mistake
uh wow I died a lot ah I couldn't see
the film where I was I couldn't see any
there are no mistakes
[Music]
he died oh no how the hell am I gonna do
this now
it's fine it's fine I'm okay
[Music]
that looks okay it's not it's not 100 oh
wait
I think I can hold it
I don't I don't know anymore what's
right and what's wrong
we started so strong and that was oh
it's okay
it is
[Music]
yeah I can roll with that
one two one two three this is the hard
part there's so much white blocks here
that I just don't know what to do with
um
oh God ah yeah the bangs are a bit too
low it's okay I forgot to cut my bangs
in this one
foreign
[Music]
s
yeah
I want to grow my long enough so I can
tie him into a ponytail like a like a
unicorn horn
y
cutting your bangs my little child every
week
ponytails thingies
one on the front of my head and then two
on the side
you can't do that without growing out
your bangs you can do do a third
ponytail in the back for example you
could even probably do it now with this
with the short Pony of short bangs even
true to be honest no you could but I
don't want to tell you to do it
true that means will that be something
we can expect for uh Whenever there is
ever a new outfit coming outfit coming
out that will be your new hairstyle
either that I can grow it out really
long and then I'll swoop it to one side
so you only see one of my eyes oh yeah
oh yeah
edgy hairstyle very what do they call it
some raccoon tails oh my God
we're cool what's your raccoon what
skunk what
I know what you mean though like a scene
did you ever have a face in your life
where you were listening to like like
emo scene ish music I wanted to be a
scene kid yeah
no did your mom also not let you
know yep
did your mama let you make your hair all
fancy hell no she's like no oh man
I wanna that's so bad
he said
let's like wanting to become a scene kid
but they're they're except those who
actually became the same kid that
everyone who did not became a scene kid
inspired to become a scene kid and were
not able to because of their parents
nanny
what
that is unfortunate
[Music]
there was this I think one one of those
uh groups that I can remember that list
that I was listening to that was really
really edgy was flying leave have you
ever heard of it no fly leaf um
a museum of the viewers know what that
was pretty edgy slightly
yeah
no I've never heard of them oh there's
no oh exciting
I know
um
can you sing kids no I think it what
scene of something else more we are now
the scene of YouTubers we're those
sinkets beat oversync is exactly oh yeah
where am I
oh this is
okay we're fine
they're just getting more and more
confusing how is this possible
orange and then sand and then sand and
sand until orange okay okay
good and then this one
no no
what one two three
all right this is fun I got this now
we're just gonna do it like the same
oh oh we're all finished oh I was doing
two over there okay
okay oh
next bro I gotta go down and get more
wool oh
go get it wait did I miss you get that I
think I messed up
once you get supposed to be two wait one
two three
oh and then one two three four oh I
messed up pretty bad got it one two
three four
shouldn't I be
I see a mistake
I say it too but we're exactly
only
ah the the red thing on the side where
it goes inside should be one above right
I didn't put that would mean that I
wouldn't oh
absolutely
[Music]
oh whatever we're gonna finish this
up up up
[Music]
how you doing
me yeah
I'm good how are you doing who deserves
it
we're doing all right yeah I'll just do
I'll just do one more
row of
of not going inwards
here
oh my God
I think I think that's okay
okay bye bye red
and then
do it here
and then do this and
this um
how about that
it's tearing us apart Kiara come on it's
not that bad
I could easily fix it
hello
I guess I guess in theory the way it is
now on top here it's correct it's just
that down there there's some mistake
[Music]
with lyrics
no I don't want to fix
but if it looks different on that side
need to go one more to the side what do
you mean
what do you mean one two three four five
six seven eight nine
for quite a loud
wait
um no
it is
uh-huh
yeah
[Music]
one two
three done look at that no more
I mean I mean wait stop wait
let me get what how do I audit
oh
and then
[Music]
oh yeah I'm gonna die when I fall down
here yep
the last line of the eyebrow needs to go
one further out ah
one one two three
seven we're not doing the eyebrows yet
two three four five six
seven Living on a Prayer
I'm sick of seeing squares
baby
half a head right now yeah it's a red
Corner goes out twice all hat no brain
currently what do you mean in what
language are you speaking to me Espanol
you're speaking
any more white stuff
[Music]
should I just should I should I go down
um how
well I mean am I oh wait let's just look
at this from a different perspective
here here here we have that the the
realm where the I wish start eyelash
starts is correct
and then the row above the eyelash start
the middle eyelash is uh
[Music]
it's it's the mistake below that
oh God
I think
man I think that all my build sure is
scary
what
that like the like the the white the
worm I don't know what that is the white
thing I know what you mean yeah I am I
think it's is it from like a show
[Music]
what the something pushed me oh no
well it wasn't me
FBI
I don't have time oh God it's lagging
because these aren't
God okay I'll run
and chest stupid chest
yeah it's because it's too close to
spawn what
this looks really cute from over here
uh-huh
oh no then I'm down here I can finally
and look at it not those boobs no no I
can find them okay oh the mistake from
below that looks good I don't see any
mistake
oh thank you hmm
what was it that stupid chest and why
the hell did I fell down
she has thick eyebrows down
damn she take
eyebrows is don't they look cute
those do you mean the ID figure
thingies yeah the thing they're really
cute they're like uh welcome to Whole
Life Indonesia service
wait why are you doing all the way over
there
because my bed was like I slept in it
but I destroyed it so therefore my spawn
was uh yeah
oh no
oh well
okay oh my God that's so cute
[Music]
okay but where did I go wrong no oh I
see what this is this is it's like uh
there's something here too
well
oh never hold down oh I see
order
it's
super cute
uh
ouch
I'm coming
[Music]
oh God it's all the same color
oh
gifts
sorry
sorry what what did you say it cut out I
was I was swearing oh I cannot that's
very good I got censored on your stream
at least oh that's all right let it rip
my items oh they were exactly did I fall
down blue five blue six blue
da
and we're here can I just fill this all
in and I I
below
what
one two three
[Music]
one two three five
two
one too
[Music]
die double
wait where is it where is
I have no idea what's going on
is it following me I don't think so
you're good
uh I'm On One height well that doesn't
sound good Tyler was trying to kill me
while I was trying to fight my armor uh
and okay there we go
give it to me
ow
second take it goddamn leg
s
what's going on
[Music]
okay we're good
with the lag what's with the lag
oh
yeah
I'm really adding some server lag issues
you good
well I guess hopefully that counts as I
picked everything up so I guess I'll
just disconnect once maybe uh-huh
[Music]
oh it's his back
back again
like something didn't I have a full
inventory I don't know well what
happened did you lose all your stuff I'm
not sure
hmm
what what
what's what's for you guys again
Minecraft why why why
am I why are Mama's all over again
crap what the
no don't tell me the leads are gone
again I had two more demolishes and I
because they
they're
Minecraft okay you're really me
over right now Minecraft this is not
they work oh comma
um
now I'm logged in today and suddenly all
the leashes was gone and all my llamas
were all over the place so I took I took
two releases from my storage because I
only had two but thankfully llamas
follow one another so at least two
Amazon to kfp again and the unalignments
were sticking together but now the
leashes are gone again and the llama's
all over and I don't have any more
leashes
you understand the situation have you
tried turning it on and off again
okay well I guess I have no malicious so
I have no more llamas thank you for
nothing Minecraft I'm really salty now
this is this sucks
this is not fair this is not this is not
a stupid spider I hate you
did you know that watermelon is 80 water
[Laughter]
did you know that this sucks like this
is literally takes away leeches from you
without like giving you a reason they
just take it away from you you know I
could be losing some really important
animals to me that that mean a lot to me
you know that mean my life to me and
they just take it away from me it breaks
my freaking height it breaks my heart
Don't Go Breaking My Heart
[Music]
as distressed clucking
but when Clippers clip me and when I
make like laughing noises or whatever
they dance
like happy clucking noises happy chicken
noises
wild got out is yours finished
no
I messed something up and I'm not sure
how to fix it foreign
I gotta get rid of this like thing under
my character eyeball
I am so mad I am really filled with rage
you could have fooled me just kidding
you're just gonna leave they're just
gonna leave
we don't want to live here anymore if
you don't have leashes Minecraft just
you can take it away we don't care
bye-bye
put them in a box hurry
gotta box them in all right I could do
that
no but
okay they look cute down there now my
Minecraft's just gonna take them away
from me again
Minecraft's gonna take defense away from
me I'm telling you
it might take it away
I'm gonna take every away ever no and
I've owned everything that's important
to me everything that's fair to me
for what Minecraft for what Dad Billy
goes to the game and some squishy pink
lizards all of that yeah
yeah is that the price that I have to
pay huh for those goats and those weird
fishes huh Kiara loses all her llamas
for what
funny Pink Lizard but the funny Pink
Lizard
I haven't even seen them yet she went to
me I don't I want to have proof that
they exist I don't have any for now
are they Ina has some I know she spends
a lot of time Gathering I can't believe
it anyway
bro
go back inside go back in there go I
will kill you you stupid llama I loved
you up until now but now everything that
looks like you know it reminds me of
your amazing man
that's not happening
foreign
build a fence you have any friends oh
really we're doing good or really good
does that look like we're doing good
no we are actually doing good we are
Cowboy we are excelling
you better you better wait
oh wait I guess oh wait I can write them
in can I can I I don't know again
about that disgusting sound
[Music]
do you have one leash that I could use
to put them in a place and then I give
you the leash back I don't think I have
any leashes no
um Ina might have one though
[Music]
yeah she has too many she has all the
power
okay flour I hate flowers go back in
there
okay
go back okay you know what could uh I
don't like llamas anymore my least
favorite animal I give up this is what
four and a half hours of building pixel
art in first person looks like
anger
the planet they lost frustration the
seven stages of first-person pixel
building
wait where am I think I think whole life
Japan members are just so used to it
they they really don't feel anything
anymore when they do this kind of stuff
I don't know I don't know how
[Music]
Julia maybe is it like one person per
hour or do they have like multiple
people working on the same thing
but they must go faster like if we had
split this like you do one side and the
other I think often they build stuff
together
because that would make this go we
probably would have been done easy
and a little and like we have two things
to build so I guess not
um
yeah I'm sorry I'm I'm here to fix my
mistakes
namaste
[Music]
how do we do this huh
did I go where did I go wrong
this sounds so sad but I really want to
know where did I go wrong
red outline block on the hair is the
part that is wrong
oh yeah I mean there's a lot of red
outline though
um
is that two and it should be three
no that's free one two three
and then should it be one more outside
one more to the left
at the point where I am standing
one above
one above that line should the red one
be one more to the left okay
uh that means that
I can put
this here and then
seven eight nine ten oh
eleven
oh so one more outside
three three and I built that again from
here when I'm stuck here and jump on top
of it
I feel
oh
I don't want you bye bye
bye
it's so hard to see I wish they had like
more defining
oh like for all the same color blocks
like all these this white blocks I wish
that you could see the outlines on the
the software thingy
you know
oh
did I do it right
I think I did but like there has to be
yeah okay the above part obviously has
to be fixed yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
we've really slowed down our things at
least at least I did I have also seen
pacing yeah I have a lot of
wait you can turn on the grid in the
software how do you do that
why is our grin but Al is a grid
settings maybe oh yes you know it was
that easy
stop it
yeah okay now the people like you had no
grade on you now surprised I've been
making so many mistakes we had no great
on
we were doing this blind that's
impressive we did it blind wow
oh my God all right look at this look at
this girl
oh no
look at us
it's all right but we've already I'm so
fine I already up so
um
well
first of all let me get rid of that
okay
one two three four five six one that
should be correct seven I don't know how
many this is that should be correct
right we're doing fine now right
seven
it has to be like that
yeah okay and now
right now yes
and this
and
this
that is
wrong on the other side too though I
think I made a different mistake on the
other side
okay okay okay okay okay
oh no oh I can make it don't worry
I got it watch this
oh
wow oh never mind I don't have to it's
fine
we got this if I said no never mind that
no never mind
okay what went wrong here everything
um
diagonal one is correct right now
yeah what's up
what's up
[Music]
I thought you died but there's a big
Buddha right next to me so I guess
you're here in your life very much
are you always present
um omnipresent
I am an enigma I am always present
okay have I fixed it
I'm gonna have a pineapple hold on
how many rows do I want to get rid of
[Music]
I mean that's incorrect
oh my God
um
free those free are covered right
one two three one two got it no wait is
it four is that four on the right side
one word
I'm getting getting rid of uh one more
one more
and then you'll be
and then one
and that is that correct
I'm gonna put the TNT down now
wouldn't that be awful if I just blow
everything up at the end I wouldn't do
that well that would be funny but it'd
be bad but yeah I wouldn't do that toy
well it can go really far yeah okay
um
is this okay
is everything below correct no
is it I don't boom
by Chopper
then
yeah yeah yeah
and then
uh
one red right
and then we built a long time ago and
then we do that great right
we're doing it we're doing it we're
doing it wait wait wait wait
wait wait one two three one
oh
oh my God
one two three
one two actually you're online no I
don't think so sorry
[Music]
fix the arm no it's fine it works
no try to tell him we fix the arm and I
said nothing oh oh okay
you're not a perfectionist huh okay
um usually but not in this moment though
there's this game that I want to play
where you like it's like uh it's like
you play as a medieval Knight in
multiplayer online game
no oh
I think it'd be fun
yeah that's it
[Music]
blue the one here
what what what
three
yeah and then one uh one more red on top
of that empty space
oh
foreign
it's the one where you can like turn the
sword on yourself
it looks like yeah it looks like
chivalry too I want to play chivalry
wait how do I get rid of that now
one two three four
oh there we go
okay
okay let's focus on making one bro at a
time we got it
where which road am I in though
the one below the hole okay oh we've
looked great it's so much easier now can
count them yes
whoa okay that's one two three four five
six seven eight oranges
below the hole and I have already three
so that's five more okay
so much easier one two three four five
okay and now we got one black one sand
one orange one sound
foreign
one two one
stand
on Orange
one stand
when orange one orange
okay
now we need some I I know we're both
really focused and all that wow you can
find another small talk topic small
topic
topic topic up topic
well like
um what are some games that are
releasing releasing in this year that
you're looking forward to our last three
in October Baby great free in October I
think so hopefully which free games no
at last three the third Outlast came out
last night cut out Discord cut it out
yeah
is that an FPS game no it's uh it's the
horrible scary game in the uh like the
Asylum you're like a journalist and you
go in to explore what's going on
a game yeah you should play Outlast I
think it'd be fun yeah
have you played one before
a horror game or Outlast or any horror
game how to play one on screen I I I I I
played
you know for Halloween I felt like I had
to play some kind of horror game
um
but I went with a really not scary one
it was really not scary though so I kind
of took the easy way out
um what did you play
just some kind of like game that some
students made
I was free on Steam and we had
permission for so it was not really
scary at all besides that I guess I
never have played the horror game
besides phasmophobia for example which I
guess you could oh yeah
yeah
but yeah
one two three four five six seven eight
one two
foreign
so this is going to be incorrect anyway
which is okay
I want two three four five six seven
eight wheel it goes up oh yeah that
makes sense okay okay yeah I want I'm
looking forward to it I'm saying this
um with no influence or anything I I
might be sponsored but the game I'm
looking forward to the most in this
whole year is Tales of orions and the
airplanes I'm gonna ask you about that
with the Ambassador Queen man
yeah
I I did I did a sponsor stream uh on it
the other day this week on Monday
but I would have done it like I would
play Tesla variety even without being
spons being sponsored I just I just love
the tales of syrians so much it means so
much to me remember my favorite my very
favorite so
yeah I'm excited for it
finally because it's a new Mothership
title and uh like a spaceship
no
it's like a what what is a monster title
title it's like um how do I describe
that chat help me out one two Mothership
seven eight uh it's a flagship did I
mean Flagship oh maybe I guess someone's
flagships yeah my Mothership
things confused I'm sorry
oh
from saying Steam
have you never played a tails off game
before I've never played a tailzone game
before have you ever played a jrpg game
before
I played Scarlet Nexus does that count
oh wait that's the only
let's play The Final Fantasy account oh
that's an admination
but if you say MMO does that mean you
only played uh ff14 yeah oh but I would
still call it a little Jacob you never
played any other FF game no
me neither though because I was wearing
the Tails offside but still I'm
surprised because many people
um playing FF because it just became
pretty mainstream but what about near
automata
no
wait you played nothing no never no why
I guess that's just not your thing yeah
yeah
you don't like
that's that's interesting and you do
play very different games than I do yeah
Hotel
which one am I on
yeah though I played uh well wait what
else you put I played well that's not a
jrpg I'm gonna say fantasy alive Fantasy
Life that's not a that's not a jrpg
or does it does it count does Fantasy
Life count does a jrpg I don't know what
that is it's cute it's like uh it's on
the like 3DS and you go around and you
uh
Devil May Cry camp
and probably not oh wait what the hell
where am I
Fantasy Life Michael
it's just cute though
and his life is a jpgs oh they say it is
they say it is cute
Pokemon
this Pokemon comments yeah I guess it it
does it it's a role-play game I'm
role-playing that's my Pokemon trailer
it's not really the kind of tear Vegeta
I'm thinking of but I guess it is it
falls into the category rough link
technically
oh
so you played Pokemon before right yes
a little Pokemon well that's something
who hasn't right it hasn't played
Pokemon on their game boy or something
did you know Pokemon go is almost five
years old
I oh my god did you play Pokemon go when
it came out because I did one of my most
fun summers in my life I did play that
game Pokemon go yeah that was so much
fun yeah actually made me go outside and
then I appreciate that is it correct
I have to ask I don't want to mess up
anymore Mario and Luigi Bowser's Inside
Story yeah is that a jrpg RPG what does
that stand for Japanese role-play game
right yeah yeah I will play this Mario
and Luigi
you role-played as Mario
yeah I did the Bing Bing Wahoo I did the
Bing the Bing Bing Wahoo that's what he
says
bye real oh
okay
I never I never wait did you ever play a
Zelda came
briefly I played I played breath of the
wild for like 30 seconds
I'm playing Majora's Mask and then it
got too hard yeah yeah
it's like from whatever yeah I only
watched a full gameplay on it I never
played it myself but from what I know
it's kind of hard yeah yeah I couldn't
figure it out it was too much for my
brain
hmm
and it's still correct we're still okay
let's focus on this row again but I
think that's correct one two three four
five six seven eight okay
[Music]
and then eight Orange
and then three and three black
eight orange one of them is done yeah
okay holy cow we're getting somewhere
now
no
I did something wrong there
I started the eyebrow one two okay I see
it I see it fixable
fixable how
[Music]
what
one two three four five six we're gonna
go up six one two three four five six
okay what the
six now current now correct okay
dear Lord
this was fun in the beginning now we're
reaching apart where it's not fun
I finished it tonight
's necklace almost it's five hours now I
mean I don't know I'm not tired but
it's like you're not your body's it's
like you're not tired but also your
brain's exhausted
I I mean I couldn't I can still go
longer but I can too but I'm kind of
like flatlining you know my brain
I always just finished the the like do
maybe five more rows and then finish
your rest privately one two three four
five six seven eight okay
[Music]
oh
what's going on here
when the zero four one two three four
one two one two
[Music]
I guess there's so I can go one more
it's creativity uh uh I I may use my
creativity here right
yep yep right what what
ah
oh wait what
Rhythm gamer what did I do that have to
do with real oh counting that's not
that's kind of Rhythm gaming do you like
Rhythm games
[Music]
I I I I I think
but I'm not really good at them uh and I
they're not really the I mean that it's
it's a kind of game that I would play
um oh
uh like in my free time but I wouldn't
really want to play it on the stream I
did that once a while ago as a sponsor
stream a group coach but
yeah but it made me um
it made me nervous I feel like it was
much more fun playing it off stream than
it was playing it on stream
okay I know you seem to be very used to
it yeah you can handle everything but I
guess you also when you stream Rhythm
games I guess you go into it with a
different feeling than me like I go into
it and especially with a sponsors German
I'm I'm like oh I need to I need to
entertain them even when I'm super super
super focused uh I burn one block to the
side okay even when I'm super super
focused on on the game especially when
it's a ribbon game even then
it comes to sponsor stream and streams
I'm like I need to give it my best I
need to be entertaining I need to I need
to talk I need to constantly talk but
I'm like that in all kinds of streams
um I have this this voice inside me that
tells me I I need to constantly talk so
yeah uh what the hell
[Music]
but anyway that's why that's why it was
kind of hard and
um it was gross coaster maybe but I mean
I had fun it must have been fun playing
your own song in a video game though
right uh yeah but I also felt very dizzy
um
understandable
um but that was only hidden specifically
for some reason I think the the graphics
there where
um it made me very dizzy because the
other the other songs did not make me
dizzy but yeah I really wanted to nail
my own songs so I tried it again and
again and again and again uh-huh
uh yeah I I did I did not feel so well
at the end lots of flashy lights and
like spinny yeah and all that stuff yeah
yeah
oh wow I messed up somewhere gouda oh no
oh no
can you fix it let me see how you've
done so far oh wait one more one more
time
I think I understand how
[Music]
oh it looks good though
you're looking at it from the bottom yes
when you play Rhythm games
no
sometimes if I'm tired when I play I get
really dizzy but like sometimes I just
can't play a certain game for whatever
reason like yeah yeah
like I don't know it just depends on the
game sometimes the brain is just not
having it so yeah I understand what you
mean yeah they can make you dizzy
um
thank you
[Music]
okay
um
really uh
okay so
um
there's one there's okay
Allah
wait which side am I looking at outside
that
is not how I just had it
but it should be correct
oh my guys in action game yeah your bill
action
is it gonna rain oh no it's just dark
never mind
it's beautiful beautiful stars are so
beautiful
isn't it
very beautiful almost as beautiful as
the sparkles in your eyes oh my goodness
yeah you know what was fun that did the
whole dating game that we did on until
then my birthday all the monster didn't
go yeah yeah so much fun that was good
that was good yeah
one two three four five six seven eight
and then a red one okay this should be
easy enough
oh
one two one two three five five six
seven eight
yeah okay yeah oh that's all right I
already did that part but it seems to be
incorrect
I know that's correct no it's like it's
correct it's correct I it's gonna end
yeah
[Music]
so happy
she did it
so I'm on the run where the yellow
starts now and that will be how many
oranges
oh eins
sexy from act 19 elf elf I'm sand
okay
can you make this go sideways oh
thanks
if I press shift I'm screwed all right
that's fine though
don't unpress shift now if I press it
though I'll fall right through the floor
oh this light is easy one two three four
five
six seven
Doom
phone sexy but
too
[Music]
young babies learning how to cook
but cut out the part where I was really
really angry at the game
really uh it's swearing a lot you should
probably yeah cut out that part
um
it's all right it makes them learn
faster
right good does it I don't know
whoa we're playing with fire here whoa
Chad I've been wondering
play with fire you get burned kid
where's Commander
Sans
[Music]
oh my God
it's just one round
I hate okay
um
I'm gonna pick up my stuff and um
yeah
um
how you doing how how far are you of
yours are you almost I am almost done I
probably have another 30 45 minutes of
work to do how about you
40 minutes oh if I wouldn't keep on
making mistakes every round out
um
I don't know
it looks like you still have most of
your hat and your hair and your
accessories too well if you're done you
could I guess help try to help me yes
all right let me try him
we'll finish this we will finish this
even if it kills us
yeah just like no that was just not fair
dude
oh
[Music]
um
I will put I never put torches on it
once we're done at the very top yes yes
but now I don't know it doesn't make
sense to put any on there because I have
to keep on getting rid of them
anyway where's my stuff where did I fall
down all right before
time
I have no idea I have no idea where I
fell down
they fall down somewhere here
I'm more out there no
can we sleep
[Music]
um
my bed is uh
uh I'm trying to sleep
where is the where is bed oh wait there
is one here
okay I'll check my status feed in a
moment
oh my God it's so cute
I mean you still have a lot and that's I
mean percentage-wise I'm not that uh far
off from you
I don't know because you still have wow
thank you
we will see my dear Google
[Music]
did you just explode
I did I am alive I am very much alive my
dear did is that it's just scaffolding
it's just
I'm not mad at all I am not mad I am not
mad
come make myself go disappeared don't
make it disappear
[Music]
how do you get this stuff to go up okay
I got it
where's my stuff where's my stuff
yummy baby
nothing fell down wow everything here
UPS Daisy
oh I think cool
anything everything is here
all right uh you know what this I'm
gonna put my bed here
and you should eat some food
while I'm here
I'll go back up okay okay at the moment
everything should be correct so let's
let's continue where we left off
finally
[Music]
we got this
yes yes yes we do where did I stop which
sign
is it even right now
my my nose is itchy again not it again
oh thank you okay
so are we doing green I think we're
doing no we're doing one more yellow uh
red yellow green red red red
what
red
I'm gonna die friends no don't die don't
die
did you fall down again no no
wait what a weapon ready no I don't care
if anything I could use my ax but in
that moment you know when it's like
really
no space here and the zombie is coming
at you you just don't wanna it's just a
difficult situation to be fighting on
top of this place
yes not an easy situation to handle did
something attack you on top of your
building yet not yet thankfully you're
lucky
I need to come down and get more
yeah
come on where are we going
were you trying to fall into the water
or trying to I'll try to parkour I was
gonna thread the needle and then you
could quit okay don't try this at home
kids don't try to do it like good out
okay
a lot don't be good or die too much
[Music]
seeing Earth's perfect
these are 24 oranges
[Music]
London Fancy
no I think I give my character oh wait
maybe I didn't okay I was gonna say one
of my arms is short like Nemo but I
think I'm all right I think
but I have like a skin goatee that's a
little disturbing to look at I need to
fix that somehow
but made of skin
I have a skin beard a flesh beard I
wonder what that looks like
I need it because I needed clay for it I
don't have any clay so I gotta think of
what to replace yeah
what what do you mean uh in between the
smile and the like the red lines and the
where the the head meets the neck ah
that part what did I use for that I
think I just used I had something else
there oh not a whole doll oh and what
did you what did you put there
there's more sand there's no separating
mine I gotta yeah I gotta fix it oh
that's how I can I can see it now uh you
could have I guess just put more of that
red there
yeah I like to do that can you still fix
it
I think so
hmm
I'm gonna go dumb one just just put red
there then you would just have a little
the chin there I think it should or or
pink I guess that could not the creator
of this says pink would be good probably
hey you don't have to you don't have to
do what she says but it's a it's your
choice an artist's suggestion yes that's
it
yeah so okay let's go for it uh I'm
sorry I thought I feel from sex even
after nine
nice sweat bye
six seven oh
I'm so like ah
um all right
wait wait wait fun
I'm doing my highlights now yeah
I decided for your phone sex
I'm saying hi yeah oh I see
you see it have you had a alloy Stone
a what
a large dog enlightenment
a Lloyd
you're so cute when you speak language
that is not your main language
think
no no no what are you trying to say
again no no bad word no no no do I have
to do the little Slappy thingy on your
on your booty
thanks you can try I don't really I
don't really want anyone is my children
like that to be honest but you leave me
with no choice
please
are you saying yes please no let's say
this building blocks is torture enough
right now okay foreign
I'm not doing any mistakes
it's going faster finally
I'm winging it honestly oh no I need
that please come back to me I'm gonna
use this one this is two this one this
is one
two one was three this is two
it is much easier with the grade on
yes wait what
yes
four
and say hi
this is inside
we were
oh no I was looking at the wrong side
no no no
I was looking at the uh wait maybe I
wasn't wrong wait a minute wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait one two three one one two three oh
I missed one
oh I'm going so fast
let's go
huh
nice
fun
is that the end of that I don't know
where the end is of this
we're going so fast that it shouldn't be
allowed that's how we like it you heard
what I said get out of your head life is
only what you're making you're gonna be
okay yeah yeah go ahead and do it do it
if you want it let's just do it
bags
kind of I'm gonna set the way into that
one
now I lost track of where I am
thank you God for the advertisement
you're like a cheerleader
strange Sparks the space bars are just
that's the only thing you can say now
right now is the only thing my brain can
handle
it's very easy very easy to remember
space box where we brainwashed everyone
sorry
strange bars
[Music]
part of me kind of wanted uh to do a
spontaneous
um
stream gorilla stream yesterday where I
would sing spikes for one hour or two
hours or so oh my God yeah turned out
yeah I didn't really have a
the time and all for that uh maybe I'll
do it next week
at the one week anniversary
oh hi I'll keep on doing that
I don't know if it's the game like
lagging because I fall off the
scaffolding and I try and steer myself
to get back on it but I just never reach
it I can't imagine lagging I can't
confirm that I just I don't know what
happens I just can't reach
I call her next to it but I never hit it
that sounds depressing
we try your best
uh to get what you want but now what you
need that is so true you speak the words
out of my heart I speak the language of
Coldplay
anymore wool
I am so close to being finished sort of
we don't
mom
well that's a long one oh
oh well I said I feel from sex oh I'm
sorry if I'm so easy but I don't know
anything else yeah
[Music]
they're annoying
many many Germans today
[Music]
soon
enjoyment only stream when
yeah
that's deutsches
[Music]
[Applause]
Love Balloons not Nancy's these are not
Nancy's no it's sick
why is my face bigger than yours
where
my face looks bigger than yours what is
this from below yeah oh maybe they are
well then well then you probably made a
mistake
I gave myself a big old square head
this is really it looked correct before
I feel like you would have probably
noticed if you really messed up
maybe oh they are just see some oh no
the bangs what the hell happened with
the bangs no
no see that guy
on the left side of the bangs
what happened I don't want to fix that
are you still down there no oh
does it look stupid no no
how do
wait go to bed uh can you damn it what
uh how do I push them down
you mean very carefully okay now we'll
go wrong
there's nothing that jumping would be
the best option right now
I love it
yeah
[Music]
I promise
you the stream on my side will be up you
can continue streaming without ending
okay please get a hold of you
oh
I heard it
die joe boo
are you good
um huh it was nice of you
um I'll finish this uh
did it explode your face
did you lose progress what happened
[Music]
yes I did those progress um
what happened do I have to go see I
gotta go see
oh
I don't I don't know if I want to see
where's my stuff though
I think I mean I couldn't see anything I
think it'll be fine I'm moving you
couldn't see
anything
you're just trying to
oh it's fine
it's fine it's not fine
okay it's not that bad but you know it's
not funny
I don't know
but you know whatever you want to do I'm
just
um
I feel like people probably already left
[Music]
well just
Reviving
yeah what do you want to do though guys
where did I fall down where did I where
did it fell down at the very bottom
fall down go boom where
uh
is by the pond
by the pond it happened so fast
I'll go down
oh man
there's probably still one up there
oh man my hard work
[Music]
because they know I wouldn't be any
challenge to them they're like oh
no Kiara is more fun to pick on
sounds about right or is Anna oh yeah
did I lose my shoes
were they still damaged
[Music]
oh I have an idea it's okay with the
night time
you have an idea I did it I was uh my
light on this on the screen was flashing
you know what I'll bring an I'm bringing
a bow a bow this time so that I can
in case that happens again I can kill
him from a distance yeah yeah oh I could
even use my first try it
you know what I named my Trident what
I'll type it for you
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
first try
isn't that good were you even looking
for the Trident you weren't even looking
at those accidents
it was an accident and I built an entire
freaking Farm after trying to go after
them and farming them normally then I
went up to it oh now you can't get as
many as you want but you're not even
using it I ever heard
well I have to put on the other enchant
and John Thomas on it
it messes up
me too me too
where did you mess it up this time
um
I'm I I don't know it's hard to tell
where I messed up I have Arrows with me
and the task in the thingy look at it
all audience look at it just look at it
you have them with me
in my bar thingy hello creeper no okay
well I hope that was worth it you stupid
creepers
um oh man where is that what is this
which part is that what am I looking at
oh maybe this is supposed to be
I understand I understand okay I know
where I am
all right we'll fix this up quickly
[Music]
this means so uh
wait actually you know what what oh
shoot um too short
you're too short I can't get to this
part I need to so I just gotta stay here
and build okay that's fine
[Music]
wait where are we
here okay here in here blue and and the
black guys what is going on here
what happened to him did I not finish
this
well oh yeah that was when I noticed a
creepers okay
there's a lot of the
deaths now
Oh Yeah from my side I got what I was
asking for I guess
all right
oh then I gotta move everything again
I want more
um
that was purposeful
really what all right
if you say so I feel oh it's like that
catch
catch the catch the stuff
oh
Jets lost track of this at this point
yeah we've died I've died a lot yeah not
so much WoW sort of towards the end
okay I'm excited
um
[Music]
okay
section 10.
I think everyone who's watching this
stream has learned how to count in
German by now I I also think so yes
one two three
four
we're getting somewhere again here we go
again oh man
I don't know what's wrong what am I
doing
oh
do ya I I do I just once I fall
it's hasta la vista what
oh
that's the lobby stuff baby it is
there's no coming back from it
we need you know what we need we need to
leave trash and when do we need it now
when do we need it about three hours ago
laughs
can't wait to get those but where are
you good Elite tranza wait how are you
gonna win Insurance again and after you
kill the Ender Dragon you can explore
the end of the world and they are just
randomly there here and there oh how
like that no I have no idea but I do
know what it is after the Ender Dragon
yeah it must be something like that I've
been told before but I kind of forgot
they're in N cities you have to find it
are they liking chests
and end chips and chests in the end City
now to hold the okay we're gonna go
treasure hunting who's gonna get the
first one huh which one which member
which em number will be the first one to
find elytra Wings Ina there's seem to be
enough though to have all of the whole
live Japan members carry one around at
all times so
Miko standby lost her wings a lot so
maybe can you like dupe items in the
game maybe somebody can know
foreign
oh like if somebody comes in somebody
like a moderator right or admin whoever
admins can come in and do like forward
slash give elytra or whatever
for sure but I don't think they do
[Music]
I don't know
I'm doing the cute flower details yeah
okay
we can finish this we can do it
I feel
unless I'm making no more mistakes now I
think
that's so annoying I don't know how to
use this
use what
scaffolding I oh my God I I've been like
that for a long time I was struggling
got logged out
I was traveling a lot with scaffolding
but I finally kind of low-key figured it
out
I uh
I don't I well
it's hard
one two three four one two one
okay they didn't register me building
that I guess
hold up didn't I already build all of
that
oh yeah where am I now
they be sabotaging me
um oh yeah I started yeah I think that's
where I am
okay fine we're fine we're fine we're
fine yeah
[Music]
if something is off uh because is that
not for did it turn into five
I see it
everything's good
the lag teleports me somewhere else
suddenly really scary when you're only
standing on one block
oh yeah
to Me game
is that for you okay
as well those trippy teleports with the
serving lag or is it a little yes
as well yes oh there
okay
I thought it was a my internet
connection but I guess it's really just
destroy everything yeah
it is just a server thingy no worries
but I'm glad though that we at least
updated from Realms to a proper servery
I agree
that is good
[Music]
oh what
don't die we're good we're good we're
good we're good we're good I heard you
dying there
oh their summer really doesn't like me
now it's kicked me out again it's
telling us to stop it's time to stop
but I'm so close to the end
I think maybe we'll send this at the
same time
perhaps one two three
not if I get up get kicked out so many
times oh where am I now oh come on
oh come on
I'm gonna learn this by heart if this
keeps on happening I keep on repeating
myself
oh
there goes one two three oh that's a
great one
on it uh two one two
nice
[Music]
oh my God I can see the end
oh
[Music]
my God
that's how you see the end no don't go
don't go towards that end go down the
other end
I didn't register my job
the game really doesn't want us to
finish this right now but we will uh
[Applause]
you okay are you getting a mad like I
would be mad I would be it's okay to be
mad I think my brain's a bit too fried
to be actually mad but um
frustrated yep
losing track of which line I'm on oh
all right
46.
okay okay 46 okay
got it
uh
uh really confusing really confusing
really confusing really confusing really
confusing on the inside right and then
before
um um I think I made this wrong
oh
but
that's okay
it's okay that you don't have to be so
strict about it I think I'm scared my
head's gonna be like the wrong
sometimes you're gonna be wrong you know
[Music]
BFF tonight
um
okay we're almost there we're so close
yes
what does it want to do
okay one two three
double
start what's the word let's do it
I can't um
chat
chat do you have
anything you uh it's it's so it is so
calm right now if you wanted to pick up
some questions Now's the Time
ask a question if you dare
please make it easy though because our
brain or my brain anyway easy questions
only
okay wait one that means this one this
is here and then this goes here
oh and then
and then
one two three three three three three
one two three
yum yum
that's about Iris
[Music]
a conversation with her and the other
day on her while she was going live on
on Twitter
right I messed up
I messed up it's kind of kind of nice
that we were able to be uh together for
an apple because we I think we all
remember the moment when our Twitter
went live for the first time and we were
five together and like we were actually
like I wanted to that was actually
already really late for me
um but everyone was awake and still
there because of the collaboration and
and we had a little bit of a talk after
the collab so it was already pretty
close to the Twitter uh
um
um creation so we were like staying in
the Discord and waiting and then we we
got to the idea to
out of nowhere ask ask Iris to join us
in the voice chat and hang out with us
uh until her uh Twitter gets online so
we called her in
and then yeah we had some talkie talk
[Music]
I think that's good she she was I think
she was probably nervous that is that
it's happening and all that I would be
we don't we don't want her to go through
all of this alone so even though she
will have a one man one month
collaboration ban we will obviously be
for be there for be there for her
whenever she needs us on Discord and all
that and and bonding with her as much as
possible beforehand
um
yeah
yes
that most of Yara we're gonna mix it
oh no
she's very sweet she called us so I'm
glad I told her don't call us um don't
call me
sorry
I'm sorry I have you ever have sex even
yeah though very cute
okay and
thank you
we are five six wait a minute guys
season uh
okay yeah I feel like
um when you're all alone you know I
think I think she has been very hesitant
to actually talk to us actively
so I feel like we're gonna we need to
give her a little push there
um I told her if she needs any help with
uh OBS or microphones or whatever
then she's welcome to ask us anytime go
down you keep on dying in French
how about less dying and more
Staying Alive
hey can we sleep so I can go get my
stuff and I'll die or you I can go yeah
uh my bed is down there but yeah so I
will come down
go go
okay it's scary okay let's go yeah
um
yeah what else can I say I mean we
didn't uh
we didn't get to know or at that well
just yet oh that was our first
conversation like first voice chat
conversation
uh on the day her Twitter was made I'm
shocked that her Twitter is still dead
that's ridiculous
yeah man that would be really frustrated
I mean for one day it's funny for two
days okay but
it's way more than two days by now hmm
yeah Me Knocking On Twitter's door hello
here's Twitter her W is um in how one
one day and some hours or what something
like that
would have been nice to have been able
to do some kind of promotion on her on
her Twitter I guess right she must have
been
uh planning some things I I would
suppose I would I would think so you
know show some screenshots of her design
and all that even though I guess Hair
Design is already
fully out there but um
her design is so good I love her so I
love the design so much like I love red
juice love the red juice since the
Vocaloid days then uh didn't the red
juice draw The Artful
um
that art was done by him oh it's the
first time when I ever
um saw red juice art I think
[Music]
laying in the bed uh with that cute
white T-shirt dress for me yes is that
the number one princess or whatever it's
called
yes princess of the world
yeah the beat map's all right
[Laughter]
I always hear the typical uh reaction
from a rhythm gamer that's the only
place I know it from isia I know world
is mine yeah
one of my favorite songs back in the day
um
uh which part am I on right now
order did I
good night
mess up something
I feel like
I'm taking this baby home
and science
take me home okay
that makes no sense
it's so it's okay is it though
is that free looks like two to me is it
free
the one I'm standing on right now is
that three blocks or two ah okay if I'm
gonna go this don't worry about it
what was that without like giving
away anything at all can you give any
comment about Iris I didn't know we were
allowed to talk about it that's why I
stayed quiet I thought we weren't
supposed to say anything no yeah why
would we not be allowed to talk about
the fact that we talked to her that
that's okay I'm pretty sure otherwise
you can blame me for that
uh I don't why would that be dumb it
well at least we're not giving out any
information about what her voice is like
or whatever I didn't say anything about
a personality or anything I just said uh
you know we talked to her no no okay
dumb no I don't think there's any issue
um
I think it would be expected that we
would have some kind of conversation
yeah
I mean it was really late so
um
we didn't get to really talk to her oh
before that but yeah
our first voice conversation was very
spontaneous though but I wouldn't want
to want her to be alone on a day like
that
no no no way no we're going out alone it
must be
I don't know yeah no uh I don't know I
don't know I'm scared I'll take the
bunking but I don't think there will be
any bonking okay
I would have already gotten a direct
message by now and I have received
nothing
it's easier to ask for forgiveness
no no no no I'm inside life here I think
I've just finished hand too big what oh
dang it no I'm not done the hand's too
big okay I'm almost finished too though
almost almost
is that two I think it's two on the
inside of the outside is it too big
inside
[Music]
one of my arms is bigger than the other
one of it
it just means I have more power in my
left hand
they are the same height though one is
just wait one oh what okay
one two three
yeah though I'm excited I'm excited All
I'm gonna say is that I'm very very
excited to see Iris iris's debut
the opening
well I was like an anime damn I was
shook yes I was shook
I mean I did not know that I mean I knew
about when the announcement was coming
but I didn't know about the countdown
that one caught me off off guard I think
I surprised everybody
yeah
I was still like in the middle of
celebrating and then bam count down
there you go there's never a dull moment
in the whole life
all right something's wrong uh
that line is correct
oh have I done it
am I something up I'm missing this uh
yeah me oh I gotta fix skin goatee
you're right you're right you're right
we're gonna put dirt there like a shadow
like a natural skin shadow
oh
that's it
and two I'm excited to see like design
wise like you know how everybody's
stream is like a bit of their own
personality wise in terms of their
aesthetic I'm really excited to see that
yeah I wonder what she's gonna do with
her Debbie's dream Society
[Music]
which is gonna be giving us showing us
presenting us
it's fine I hope she sings well she's a
big singer so
I would hope so
[Music]
um
is this gonna look really bad or
it's gonna look gorgeous it's gonna look
so good and it's gonna be inserting
dominance over the server I love that
yeah our life is learning dominance I do
I do
very important very important
yep I think I'm done
I need to go see it from the bottom
though
how far are you
oh
one two three four five six rows or so
to go but they they the more they go up
the more narrow they become so yeah yeah
I think I definitely messed up my my
talenting
oh no
oh I did myself but it's not that
noticeable oh yeah it is oh yeah it is
yes it is
anyway
oh no
my head has a lump in my head has like a
divot in it
a dance
did you know did you not concentrate
bunk in my head
yeah I'll go fix it
and oops
and
you know I when I wear my headphones I
have to make sure that the the right ear
cup you know I have like like the right
ear cup
well it's always like more extended than
the left and it kind of made me worry
that my head like my ears were lopsided
but then when I see them in the mirror
they look normal so I don't know why my
headphones the right side has to be more
extended than the left side does that
make sense is my head
I don't think so I'm not sure
wait that's not supposed to be here
three is it
oh no it is
wait I did something I did something
wrong
I didn't I do something wrong mama
it that because because uh on the very
right side
huh
it's time to give myself a unicorn horn
two three
times
it's so I mean I need to get rid of one
of one yellow one but
it's all good okay it just looks like
more from the distance I thought those
were free but there's only two okay okay
but this one goes away
I can check it here one two one two
[Music]
three
yeah
on it wait no I'm I'm not aware I think
I am
all right I think it's all done
I missed something no I'm gonna stand
out I don't get it free did I yeah
something is wrong at the edge after all
I think
time to sit back and watch Kiara I think
I I know I know I think I know oh my God
hello cat so basically I would have to
get rid of one of those and maybe rid of
one of those and then
um
[Music]
wow no order
wait
one question
one
one two
where's a good place to see this from
Nina's house maybe
they even see me from there like where I
am
skeleton he sniped me I was already on
the ground
I don't know if I changed something or
didn't I did it the same way but stop
sniping me it's not fair ow
IE come get your deadbeat he shot me in
the
right in the head I actually fixed it I
think I did ridiculous
he looked like a pin cushion it take
take care of all those enemies down
there
it looks better
better I did it I am done you did you
did nice one it's a little lopsided but
that's all right because I'm lopsided
it's all good
bow what about the bowl
I dropped the bow where's the ball
where's the boat yet where's the bow
good as really fully focused on
entertaining again and now can talk full
of sentences again I can talk
okay
where's the ball oh What boat no don't
die
you'll die
I can't lose this ball
oh I lost it a while ago yeah it was uh
I guess I lost it already
I think
it was the one that Cali made for me
I'm gonna kill this skeleton
no no yeah good job protect yourself
yeah
um
oh yeah I know I run on the bridge to be
useful and bring me some bread up here
you don't have to do
UK
oh my gosh
what's happening down there
come on
are you crying or I don't know
oh where are ya stop dying stop dying
you little Phoenix imitator he's waiting
for me I can't get it wrong
where is he up here
hmm
I need to go down anyway to get some
wool
I got it I got it
oh I got it yeah
I know oh okay I was gonna blow him up
with TNT thank you for saving me no
problem thank you for saving me
if you were done with building and still
I am the one who comes down to help you
out
thank you
no problem I feel very useful
well I am a part-time Warrior after all
come see how cute
this should do something wrong because
it looks fine
that's good did you even fix the arm I
did I fixed the arm nice
oh
was finished I'm almost finished let's
take thank you let me go at the end yeah
all right let me help
okay I mean
yeah done so I'm not sure
um
if you need any help or yeah that's
right come up come up with me what color
is your name uh only only orange and no
wait uh yellow yellow and red yellow and
red is the only color I still need and I
have it but I can I can give you or you
can take it from the wolf you need all
right I'm at the wall so I'll take I'll
put back what I don't need and then take
what we will need oh yeah
I mean if you want to come up just to
die again that's fine with me too
it seems like it's the thing that you do
it just seems to be your thing now
I don't think it's cool that you take
that away from me because that's kind of
my thing
hey hey you acknowledge the lag too you
can't you can't there's no
you're claiming that all of these steps
are because of the lag
let's sleep
what colors wait red and yellow red and
red and yellow yeah oh it feels so nice
to see a color other than a blue
all right
um I'll sleep at Ina's house
okay didn't you take the bed from Ina's
house no that's my bed I brought up ah
okay
[Music]
um
fell she hit the skeleton without
six hours now by the way I mean I
mean I'd need that long
um where in the beginning we were like
ah it'll be like three give or take
right I think if we would have turned on
grids earlier we could have
um been done earlier yeah the
grid definitely makes all the difference
not not all of it but a lot of it it's
so much easier you can go chunk at a
time instead of just guessing everything
yeah I mean I wasn't guessing I was
still trying to put my mouse there each
time and try to count it but yeah okay
so how many yellows is that row dear
Lord uh I swear from sex
uh it's even at
19.99
23 yellows
uh and no what the hell that's not I'm
coming up
what did I say 23. I wasn't listening
you gotta listen
I said I feel from things
[Music]
you know what you can do instead of uh
um from from the picture you can count
on the top the yellows
[Music]
okay
you can count the the top three the top
one the yellow the top three yellow
lines uh in the in the image and then
tell me later on how much they are and
now I lost track a bit okay uh you know
what I mean
uh-huh
yeah
wait what do you mean like lengthwise or
height wise uh now how many
um on the top three top three uh lines
that I have left or the top four
actually okay top one is only red but
below that there's a
three more that are yellow with a weird
outline yeah now count me from those
three yellow lines count mean how many
in each row how many yellows oh yeah
okay
we have been able to
get out point across wait what
all the way across
huh yeah
oh no wait you're on the I I am now
um
um uh from from the top uh from the top
red line
the top red line being number one I am
at one two three four now
so I wanna know how many yellow blocks
you can you can okay you know what
counts the top two yellow lines the top
two yellow rows okay Roger how many
yellows okay okay
um
oh man
oh yeah
it's 28 so you need 28.
28 for the top two
together or each each line seven each
one's ever oh my God okay one two three
Seventeen
Seventeen and the one that comes next oh
you're oh
seven wait let me jump over here
okay okay I'm crouching so you couldn't
even get me down anyway that's okay it's
all good it's all good we're good 17 in
the next one you sure
17 from the second from the top
Seventeen from the second from the top
oh no that's the third line the third
line wait Top Line is red
excellent I I don't know I couldn't
believe that
I think uh I'm just gonna be fine
um
I just
um what is Arrow in my head sorry this
is the second to last yellow line so
yeah the next one is just gonna be three
red ones and then fill it up uh yep okay
okay sorry the arrow lodged in my my
temple is scrambling my brain waves
okay
uh oh you know what you can you can
quickly bring uh wait do you have yellow
with you I got lots of yellow bring it
to me my my little
um made uh uh assistance assistant
I got it I got it no it's okay now we're
good so this is still last line I think
so it should be one
so all right all right
does anyone ever have I hope my head's
not gonna be destroyed am I
and then one more completely red I think
I think it should be correct
why are you laughing I've lost my mind
[Music]
I wasn't expecting this to take six
hours this is crazy this is madness
sorry no don't be sorry that's fine I'm
sorry my I don't know my brain I thought
in the beginning
look at something legendary people will
look at it and be like oh that's so cute
every time they come to our server and
we'll be able to tell a story of uh how
we did aikotova together and I am
officially finished but ah you know what
would be good torches on top and I only
have one
but I guess I have five
oh did you put any on yours though no
if enemies spawn up here as long as
there's nothing to for example if it's a
creeper as long as we don't as if no one
is there to activate the creeper then
nothing's gonna happen right so yeah
it's not really necessary to put
anything there oh ah wait how are they
even able to uh they're able to spawn on
wood but not on carpet huh well I don't
have any carpet ah wait oh yeah that's
true lightning if lightning hits this
it's gonna Burn It To The Ground what
what yeah
lightning well then even the the Torches
won't help right yeah I know it's only
because it's made of wool
it's highly flammable
wait what can we do against that put
iron above put glass above ah one layer
of Glass on top of that would that work
oh
oh my God
okay I can do that I can do that
do we want to quickly do that to finish
it out
it might
how do you make that with copper perhaps
we don't have any copper didn't you guys
tell me with cobbler
is there no way but glass would work too
right a glass will be Wrigley
easy
let's go with glass if that works it
would distract from the
oh wouldn't it I don't know glass sounds
use the glasswork somewhere I don't
think it will stand out much to be
honest
wait I didn't make a lightning rod
but but would it have to be
um only at the very top layer I wonder
because
on the side it like the edges they they
don't know how to explain what I'm
trying to say
last for now when the next patch is in
take out and put a lightning around
can you guys say lightning rod already
exists let me see
made my gamer done no it doesn't okay
well then we don't have no choice but to
go for glass okay just a tap lightning
doesn't hit sideways I mean I didn't
mean sideways but yeah I guess okay just
uh do you have glass
uh no okay I'll give I'll give you I'll
give you I have enough for both of us
just for the very top layer that should
be enough are you still up there uh no I
was looking at it it's so cute
come back up with me coming
two copper ingots make a lightning stick
oh it does exist that just because I
didn't mind copper yet I don't have it
in my recipe book is that it where do
you find Copper is it pretty shallow in
the earth's or it seems to be everywhere
honestly I saw someone else streaming uh
in in the update and it seems to be
everywhere literally right we up high
already
that makes sense all right I'll give you
this uh this here
oh there you go
[Music]
thank you now we go up and finish
ing
all the way no our server already has
the update
it has it
because Ina went to to look for the
thingy
I was just answering someone in the chat
but we have the update we have the
update
Trident Farm is also a copper Farm hell
how does that work
oh no
what oh no uh well I started with like
70 scaffolding but I only have 20 so oh
you can take this online I'm done now oh
I mean for building back up also how
many did I take from Ina
we took we took like two steps
yeah we took that from PPP but was that
like does that belong to people I just
need to give back 12 or so to email for
sure oh I remember that that was correct
oh I
um we can put the leftover Stacks into
the community chest here just I think
that would be fine yeah it makes sense
because then they can take it back to
PPP oh look at that we'll just use it
here yeah
um where is it
was not really 49 oh they fell down
all the way down I think that's it
drowners drop cover oh nice
drowners drop copper yeah the the
water's on
but they do it often is that enough
scaffolding yes
wait how did you do this I didn't I
didn't finish it of course I did what do
you mean
all of the public blocks yeah that's
what I was asking if I need to like put
it on on these edges as well you know
but then I didn't know how to explain it
whatever
should be fine yeah
hey
how wait where do we put this just like
along the top of everything
yeah I need to do it um
[Music]
yeah that was a big one
hahaha
and I'm almost done yeah now she's like
doing the thing on the floor again where
she we see him rolls around like a
pancake
he'll I don't even know if he'll Blaze
I still need to make my pizza
Pizza
I have a bit more what am I doing this
right
are you
I kind of wanna oh we're crying for
[Music]
um
okay where do you where do you find iron
I'm wilting like a flower sorry guys I
have my no food maybe maybe here
hi my my personal Minecraft food bar has
been at a half the entire stream so
sorry okay I got a lot of oh not of
glass
Michelle
okay that has to be enough
it's you
I is here
up
very much okay go
you're still hmm
I had the stock oh well oh I like I like
because I died on the scaffolding
weirdly
oh
good job good job yay
how much
how much do you think you need
43 enough
yes it's more than enough thank you
alrighty
man I lost a diamond pickaxe where did
that go
I don't even know where that went I have
more for you don't worry did you pick up
my stuff though because I died on the
scaffolding
and myself my stuff fell down but I
don't know where it went
oh maybe that was it
oh did you get it
no
oh well the pickaxe was lost but I mean
it should be somewhere but if it's lost
you know you only have to come to
Phoenix Town see you next time
I need you I need your scaffolding I
guess oh wow wow I guess I can take your
scaffolding already because you're
probably not planning to use it on the
way down right I'll just use my feet
yeah
is
or my head whichever I fall on first
you ready
if I die though then
wait a minute I'm gonna try land in the
water
it's not not very uh
it's beautiful and it's snowing but
it kind of disturbs my real
not cook oh well like I said I started
coming
it's uh at the Water by the way
at the little pond that's why you tried
that's exactly what you tried to call
into huh oh they will never take me out
the circus I would feel that so terribly
it's all right though all this stuff
I'll go get my stuff and then
I guess I guess we're done we did it
do we have a problem sure no sir
no
yeah I'm gonna blow up the skeleton
and do I have to put it there too guys
I don't have to put it there do I oh no
where was that
did you hear that
there's a grandpa oh creeper okay
oh man wait where's my I don't know
I have myself touch with me now stream
behind Challenger
it wasn't the one you gave to me right
that I lost
it oh oh well even if it doesn't matter
can't get out of that Phoenix 10 anytime
okay
dude are you saying I have to put it
there too
hasta la vista
[Laughter]
you lived
please don't kill me this will be so sad
if you end up killing me you can't kill
me you can't kill me
is there water there no
you're telling me you have to put it
there too
you guys are kidding me right
I'm safe here
I don't know how that creeper survived
the TNT blast
foreign
how did you live
there's no way you survived that
am I gonna survive that though
where's the cookies okay
what about here do I have to put it here
guys this thing is above so probably not
right I think it's the lag oh cake oh
chicken
no okay
oh you did die
that was totally the lag it is because I
can't actually it was not oh that's why
I can't eat never mind
okay
how
all right
oh we look kind of ominous we look like
Silent Hill with the rain because it's
like foggy
oh that sounds
that sounds like it has a nice
atmosphere to it yeah also I forgot I
was using uh OptiFine so that means I
can zoom oh yeah
okay uh
um
look how cute
very cute
I will come in a minute I just have to
finish up one more thing and I'll
probably die again while doing it
because there's no other way to do it
and we do chat
looks like picture
okay
um
is there more
when I survived that I mean I got oh
wait I should just put on this and now I
survived
all right
okay she survived uh now that jump I
will not survive
um
oh wait that's water that's water oh I
could try to jump in there
well
oh my God what are you doing
I try I'm like somewhere in the middle
of my Monument trying to find a way to
get down
all right all right all right I'll I'll
do it 360 no scope gamer
come on come on
[Music]
it was a lightning rod
no lightning rod use glasses let me use
that once we have copper but for now it
is what it is
did you take away the scaffolding here
oh no no maybe
well I'll make my way down somehow
wait did you remove the scaffolding
behind yours
uh no not yet I meant the on the way
down from the mountains oh wait that
pond was there
this one
or was I looking at Ina's Pond wait oh
oh wait was it Eno's pond
what pond was I looking at
okay
it's much much bigger than that
all right still got my diamond armor
okay it's time to remove the scaffolding
oh I blew up the scaffolding with the
THC oh
well you know what I'll leave whatever
it is I still have 18 I'll get that to
Ina
oh I know
the range teacher we have to sleep
ah you know
um damn it all right uh wanna want to
sleep you're there as well let's sleep
sleep
okay
sleepy oh it's not night
it's now it's just raining
it works oh my God is it like a sleeve
ah okay well no choice I'll go up and
remove the scaffolding I guess
grab five percent battery am I like two
percent
two percent battery
two you're such a scared ah
wow wow
I've slept it's just a little blood
sugar you know
whoa low blood sugar I yeah food no food
today watermelon pineapple and an energy
drink yes
all right then after this immediately
usual
something fall down
okay I got that part of the scaffolding
what else did I come up here for just
for the scaffolding right and to get my
bed perhaps
do you want to leave your bed up here
I'm I'll bring it down for you where did
you where did you take it from
originally it's behind my character I
know I know but where did you take it
from my house
okay I'll bring it for you
yeah
[Music]
all right I got everything I got it all
coming down thank you
[Music]
can I get it I think I got it
there you are you did not move I see am
I gonna get kicked for uh an activity
not anymore
wow okay
I give those two
we lost a lot of scaffolding there
actually here is your bed
thank you let's try to sleep one more
time it's still not night okay
all right let me bring the scaffolding
to Eno's place we still have time until
it's night we need a nice picture
okay
back it up I'm coming yeah I'm fine
if you're not feeling so well then you
really should uh well we'll say
something besides watermelon after this
and
blah blah blah
bling anymore
you know that song
I don't know that thumbnail okay we're
listening to Looney Tunes
[Music]
my child is going crazy when's the red
moon going to rise
in front of me
when the night has come
well
like Kiana
you still um deserve that because in the
beginning you killed me that's very true
I have that coming for six hours let's
not pick up anything from you I don't
think besides the bed
say say the name of your your weapon
with your tongue out
with your tongue with your tongue out do
it again yeah
no you're supposed to say for the town
Outlet
never mind it's supposed to make you say
ass whatever it's fine
you're being Brown it's funny right now
it's almost drunk or something it's
called low blood sugar it's time for
girls
stop
[Music]
take a picture like that that's
disgusting that's most costly it doesn't
look good
oh you know what I want to remove the
ground under my should I do that now
I'll do it eventually but not now
let us sleep let us sleep how long does
it take to let us sleep this bed is
obstructed oh
yeah yeah
sleep
please
what sleep hey
you can only snip at night or doing
thunderstorms
so it's raining but it's not Thunder
back
no you probably can't even at this point
the way you're acting now I don't think
you can even put the right color into
the right
um chest
so I think you can do it another time
[Music]
my brain is perfectly functioning
act like that huh I guess it's the food
though six out yeah six hours without
proper preparation yes
no snacks
no more snack is for these kind of
situations more snackies me too though I
need more like snacks that I can easily
eat during this dream when I gotta get
those shakes that like old people drink
but with the vitamins oh that's what I
usually drink
well that's not cool
what are they doing up there you you
drink shakes that little people drink
yeah it's not like protein and vitamins
and stuff and it's like I think that's
awesome what people who do uh workout
drink well
yes I got it
I I have nothing to say against that is
it night now I think it's nightmare
is it no it looks like it but it has
been looking like it all the time okay
I'm in the nighttime
[Music]
bedtime
for me too it's not nice they say go
down it's apparently not night yet
Chad says that
chances
of the rain
but the Sun is setting though we're
almost there is it oh is that supposed
to be the Sun that foggy light over
there oh oh yeah it's getting darker
girl are you living on life support no
it's so good oh my God okay that's
that's really pretty uh yeah that's
really that is really pretty uh
I don't know print screen
okay I did it okay yeah wait I went a
bit closer that is so pretty there's
this weird Scaffolding in the middle
wait can you stand next to me uh-huh
let's see if we can take the cute
picture yeah
oh I see what you're doing yeah yeah
next to me
good angle
I'll take off my
stuff yeah
there's a red flower in the light oh
there we go
what oh my
oh no can you go down on you on your on
your knees
oh my
uh that is that is if that is not cute
then I don't know what is oh my we did
it
I don't know with what but yeah a high
five job well freaking done
we did and and there are no mistakes I
think we fixed all the mistakes I'm oh
wait I just realized I see one mistake
but I'll fix that whenever I have an Ely
Trail the bags you see my bangs on the
left side
my hat's pretty messed up and so is the
bow on my head but ah
ah you're my right science or left side
I guess yeah something is wrong yes
definitely it's okay you don't really
notice it on the first look I think
[Music]
it was very helpful
wow cute
yeah oh and thank you everybody who hung
up with us this entire time
the maddest of lads thank you
I think you have witnessed a lot of
different
facets of me and gouda yes
a lot of uh phases of anger and
confusion and frustration and
um yeah all kinds of us
and the motivation we had motivational
moments as well inspirational moments we
had funny moments all kinds of moments
that's true I like it we came out with
something in the end it would have been
so sad if we didn't finish right hmm and
I think in the end the only thing we can
say
is watch I caught about three song cover
if you haven't yet
[Music]
you haven't watched it yet what are you
doing it's been Alfred yeah two months
already go listen to it I actually saw
somebody I think it was either a comment
or a chat I don't remember but somebody
was like wow I hope Kiara and Guru are
saying a duet someday I think their
voices oh my god really good I was like
buddy wait wait that was a comment today
in your chat no it was a little while
ago I don't remember if it was a chat or
something but I was like oh buddy you
missed it I already done one
oh girl if you're watching the snow
bunny then go go to Kiana Channel and
check it out but um you know what I I
really like the outfits that
um were designed for us which is a
particular song cover maybe yeah one day
I can only dream of it but maybe one day
they'll be made into life to the outfits
for us I am only dreaming of it though
maybe they can be our very first Idol
outfits everybody can get like a cute
summary the same style yeah yeah oh they
can't we can get Yuna to design all of
them
yes
I would I wouldn't mind uh having that
as our Idol outfit that would be
adorable oh oh well good and you know
what I like to go now
[Music]
um
creating this with me thank you thank
you for creating this with me thank you
you're the one that reached out and got
the the pixel art made thank you
all right then uh thank you guys
tomorrow is humble talk with God the one
and only not so you know
God God do you have that
confession to God
no
I like that awkward silence just now
it's kind of sounds like your answer
should have been yes I was thinking
about that one that one that's the
reason for a clip
with the cup don't think about it don't
think about even thinking about it it
might be a sin
all right everyone think about it but uh
okay
I'm thinking about it we need something
hurry something needs to happen Okay
thank you everybody for watching us
build thank you
aussied
bye
bye good I still if you don't have a
like a good good bye-bye I guess I say
or two and I say bye
goodbye
okay
bye
foreign