[Music]
so
do
[Music]
oh god dammit
i had everything muted [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
hello hello it's
ghostbusters time yeah we are not afraid
of no ghosts
we are not afraid
we played a little bit of this game and
i got so scared i almost cried
and you only got scared because it got
dark
because i was alone with me in the dark
it would have been funny but it was just
me by myself and it was very frightening
she was screaming so much like crying
is mine like dropping my my game my pc
does not like this game all of a sudden
whoa
whoa red frame drop whoa
whoa here oh this is just the internet
possibly uh no it's whenever i whenever
i'm in the game it's just
yeah uh let me let me i'm gonna adjust
some settings real quick okay i'm gonna
leave the lava okay
come back okay no problem
by the way guys i bought a lighter and i
bought some salt oh because there was
none you bought salt
sauce yup i did i did salt i bought salt
yes salt are we cooking who is what does
the salt do
uh i don't know maybe you can use it in
exorcisms i'll bring up their mom that
i'll buy a thermometer
where do we go where do we buy items
uh in the server lobby in the lobby
how are you guys moving around i'm stuck
at this at the screen
or is that is that good uh that's kiara
huh how did you break free from
justin oh ah do we not have a tripod is
that why the camera thing didn't work
probably i mean i just i tried to sit
down the camera but i can uh you can
pass it on to the floor or something oh
the the camera in the truck never showed
any
anything besides outside
did was the green light on on the camera
did you see
cali did you turn the green light on uh
yes i turned it on
i'm gonna buy a tripod because i have
exactly 25 dollars
oh perfect okay that should work really
well then oh wait no i need to be level
two and i'm probably level one
yeah we're all we're all eleven level
one ghosty hunters okay never mind
after this one we'll be level two i
think oh yeah
cannot go shopping hold on i'm joining
back
i'm coming back right now
let's see if this helps yeah
also uh chad says that the salt can be
used to track the ghost via uv
oh they step on it and then they like
leave a trip
yeah or something like that i don't know
we'll figure it out
oh we're so cool this is like this is
like a an anime or like tv show or
something we're like cool
ghost hunters and this is our home cool
now
very scared possibly yes
okay uh by the way we're gonna we're
gonna use the proximity chat right
yes so we're gonna mute us on discord
once we're in the game
okay i'm ready
um i'm ready i can't
wait should i turn should i turn the v
on or off what does that do i don't
understand why my game is
all of a sudden now like
maybe it has to do with the fact you're
also streaming
well why this game what yeah
strange oh well if you're i mean is it
different friend uh different what's
going to call it
do you think off maybe it's v sync is on
i'm going to tweak one voicemail yeah
they said
always should be off ah maybe that's
what it is maybe
[Music]
yeah yeah it drops performance when it
doesn't consistently hit 60 frames
so yeah maybe oh my now everything is
going wrong oh i love this
that's game we got time we got time no
problem i'm just gonna sip some music
don't mind um uh i got
five dollars in the dream take your time
take your time
oh this is bad what happened uh
what did it get worse everything
everything is going
very wrong all of a sudden oh no what do
you mean
welcome to hollow eaton that's my that's
mine there's always gonna be a little
stuff
do i i'm gonna restart my game do i
apologize if you want to play around
without me
please please go ahead we can wait
it's cool sometimes when i tap into the
game window i start i want to try and
learn about some of these ghosts notice
anything like that guys
what is
are you huh oh no okay wait what
you're like ah my game turned into like
a strip a strip on the screen what
happened
oh yeah oh bye-bye oh she's gone
i think girl is the next ghost where is
the next ghost
this is not going to plan this was
working fine about 10 seconds 10 minutes
ago
i think the ghost got to you your pc
no not the oh it's okay not everything's
gonna be perfect i mean look at look at
the character models and how they might
be a good game
i'm not [\h__\h] on the game it's just
let me dance for you
guys let me dance for you callie let me
dance for you callie let me thank you
catch me with you i'm trying to say
[Music]
i don't know about sexy but i mean
there's a dance
[Laughter]
what about my hands her hands are very
weird
oh when you when you wait when you when
you're like that you look like you're
gonna do the naruto run you're gonna
like
[Applause]
that did anybody
like tweak their settings at all or is
this working fine on everybody else's
i didn't change anything like i tweaked
it a little bit but i don't know if it
did anything uh okay
how are you doing that this is weird how
do you fold over like cardboard
okay well i'll try this whenever you
look down with your mouse
you're doing that pose yeah let's do the
naruto run
the only thing is we can't be very fast
oh my god
[Music]
waiting for you oh now we
how's it going now wait i hear um
i hear the voice of amelia watson
[Laughter]
let's try this again yeah okay okey
dokey okay sending us messages to help
solve this problem once again it's going
it's going it's going it's gone it's
gone
so bad wha what what is what exactly
happens
is it like laggy or um yeah every time i
every time i tab into the game and i
start moving around
uh every day it drops it just goes
it goes bad um did you restart the game
stupid question yes i turned it on and
off again
okay let's see um all right so how about
60 frames per second
and one 920 by
i 1080. that's what it's on yeah maybe
double check
okay yeah yeah are you ready to want to
play around without me
i feel so bad like this i don't feel bad
all right you're good um and also make
sure the game and obs are at high
priority how do you close
ah okay okay
cali let's play hide and seek all right
sure whatever
where do you think i am oh wow you hid
pretty quickly because
hold on a sec it's fine we've done this
before um
[Music]
sorry everyone i don't i'm sorry this is
good
with your time you'll never find me
kelly you'll never i'm searching for
[\h__\h]
you underestimate me i will find you
hang on hang on a sec
all right you you hid pretty well i give
you that much um
oh you crashed i wonder huh
getting colder colder hotter hotter
hotter hotter oh eena knows where it
cold cold is hot hot hot
not me you know are you the dude
wait oh wait oh my god emilia is doing
technical support right now in our
discord she's not in the
collab which is in the discord helping
us with technical stuff
amazing amazing
amazing oh kiara there you are where
were you you have to tell me
what wait this looks better on my side
already wait i am
cali no no no wait i'm in the closet
trapped in the closet i close the door
like that
okay i'm coming out of the closet for
you cali
thanks
[Laughter]
yeah it's only when i tab into the game
everything all of a sudden just goes
really bad
um is it because uh
you were hosting the game possibly
[Music]
oh maybe i'm not hosting it
i'm gonna stop her right there we all
know what happens
i try to sing that song on youtube uh
okay
it seems better because i'm tabbed out
okay i'm gonna tap in
it
also it's obvious that's dropping to the
red yeah obs is jumping into the ring
um uh you guys play a player game
without me if um while i figure this out
if you want
i i'm not sure if i can do it without
you
you're the most experienced one when it
comes to ghosts
unless it's not that bad should we just
try one like this let's see
let's just try let's just try let's just
try it okay what was the girl's name
and he says kathy go to hell what
sorry i'm saying a song sorry should we
select a house yes please farmhouse
okay whoa the farmhouse the farmhouse
with the moomoos
oh they're all using in gaming chat or
are we using oh yeah
in-game yes yeah just for an hour okay
okay ready
ready are you ready
okay alrighty
also is everybody that liked is
everybody watching know what
phasmophobia is
have they played it before oh yeah good
out please a pro explanation about the
game
uh pretty much er ghostbusters except
hey it's us
we gotta hunt down the ghosts we gotta
we gotta search for clues before the
ghost
gets us and kills us in front of our
team
um it'll be easier to explain as we go
along i think yeah
okay uh-oh hold on we're gonna go
loud are we getting your voice now
okay
hello everyone oh [\h__\h]
hello hello i'm just kidding i can hear
you now
for help 100
the name is mary davis yeah we're
looking for married
babies mary mary dave mary
david hey kiara lancaster you have the
tripod right
uh no i couldn't buy it
ah okay this ghost only responds to
people who are alone
right okay so we can stick together
no no we gotta we have to yeah spread
the word first
you gotta spread out you should be able
to use its name to
anger it and get some paranormal look
make sure to refer to your journal and
write down anything okay
come here yeah where's the
author
[Music]
smashing
you're only 17.5 degrees
okay that's okay are you okay make sense
that's fahrenheit right i'm probably
fine i'm just just don't worry about it
all right do we want to go ahead and
already grab their stuff oh yeah
[Music]
to capture a photo of the ghost
never mind i'll do it the camera that i
have is that one for
taking videos or for taking photos
the one for taking photos is the one
tally has and
when you have us for videos okay so i
have to put it down in the room where i
think
it is okay
i could use a flashlight you guys all
have flashlights
yes uh we only have limited amount of
flashlights though
one over there is the uv light for
seeing fingerprints and stuff
oh okay since you brought salt kelly
without a flashlight
oh damn she was so scared in the dark
but how did you all get likes but you
have one on your shoulder that's not
fair
yeah well it sure helps me a lot
okay okay let's get started are you good
we're good i'm good
let's go all right open up
say something
[Music]
hi i'm here too i'm adjusting more
settings yeah okay
okay it's okay it's okay take your time
i'm going in first i'm not scared of
ghosts no
no nothing can scare me la la la la la
la last time all right does someone have
to keep
someone please go first i do i did okay
okay
what is that is everybody's life life
hello mary david oh my god
mary davis oh god the in-game mic
telescope
mary davis wow that mary davis huh
uh so right now we gotta we gotta we
gotta
probably scope out where the
what this hello oh oh
i'm dropping frames too now
i see guitar that's a guitar
do we have all the all this stuff we
need
what is this well we don't have smudge
sticks but we do have a camera to take a
picture of her
chat is the fbs dropping
is really bad so we gotta find like
closets to hide in right
okay okay i don't know why this is a big
map
let me turn off this radio wherever it
is again
turn it off turn it off where is the
stupid radio i don't see it where is it
did you hear that footsteps
foot you heard footsteps oh no
no no no no no it's okay from the
bathroom maybe they're
your own footsteps so if we gotta find
dirty water it's probably gonna be in
here
well maybe it might be in the bathroom
wait did anyone check
uh where the breaker is
oh yeah god the in-game audio is
horrible horrible
in before a discord visits us in the
chat again and tells us to use discord
you girls heal me right why did nobody
laugh at my joke
oh sorry i i laughed but i just wasn't
pressing d okay thank you
[Laughter]
hello yeah you're funny because it's
ally thank you
apparently it makes her really angry
with me
[Music]
davis
bloody mary
are you looking at a sexy poster hi no
no dumb legs right nice
nice legs they go all the way up
i like i like your spirit glass
so okay ghost this is a double car
garage
merry christmas babies where are you
mary davis
mary davis hello are we she doesn't
respond when we're alone right
when we're together
[Music]
um i left hey guys i left the um
the notebook in the kitchen so maybe she
will write a message for us
maybe what we can do is we can all be in
separate rooms that are close to each
other and then close the door and then
try and summon the ghost
because the ghost doesn't like people
together right he likes people alone oh
the lights went out
yep the lights are gone
where was it again it's down here right
down there
i'm in the basement i'm in the basement
you're in the basement i'm kissing for
you i'm coming down there
thank you i'm sorry no problem just
it's okay i found it i found it i found
it
okay uh is it back it's
it's red now should it be red i'll click
it
okay it's green it's green it now it
should be fine
uh that the breaker should be on again
is
are the lights working upstairs over
no what okay
what's going on
here you see that you see that
that radio is really
definitely turn back to normal
i don't want to go upstairs now mary
davis
you go facebook you go first give us a
second
i heard something callie's the type to
antagonize the ghosts
[Music]
hello hello mary davis how are you mary
davis where are you
what if we all say mary davis at the
same time
one two three mary davis
right here guys freezing temperatures in
this closet macaroni
should i put the camera right there i
have the spirit box i'm a dummy i'm
sorry
whoa hello okay thank you
uh i'm gonna turn on the spirit box
mary davis
how do i do the camera thing ah mary
davis how do i drop can you give us
a sign how do i drop an item again
okay
i see i see something
we might have to go out to check our
sanity we've been in that for a while
okay let's go back just in case i agree
let's go back okay cool
i'll stay here no don't stay there
you're gonna die it's all right it's all
right
i'm going to the truck is cali behind me
yeah kelly
uh sanity is for for
gouda at 55 for ina
for inat 64. four kelly at 66 for me at
58.
good eyes at 50. so be careful go down
can we bring this uh cool radio and
maybe we can play some tunes
for mary
oh that's uh i don't see much on the
camera
can someone reposition the camera maybe
a little bit better
oh did you place it oh man yeah i can't
see anything
yeah that that's a different one but
[Music]
um
i think someone is already repositioning
it because now i can't
see uh swap the camera anymore
good inna are you alive hello
are you repositioning the camera
most emoji
please walkie-talkie over
all right
oh yes i see your sexy feet
hot time i would be proud of you for
these feet
all right man
i don't see much besides the feet though
yeah we probably need uh we probably
need uh
we need one of those tripods
[Music]
no
yeah you gotta click on the keyboard
yep it's it's place we see a floor
i don't i don't think it gets much
better than that but yeah
but it's now in the best we can do it
it's not i see you yeah it's not in the
direction of the closet but i see a
person i see a person
you're dancing gonna be dancing
i guess so do we have any uh evidence
except
freezing temperatures
i'm supposed to take pictures we saw we
saw ghost
we saw ghost orbs yep i didn't see it
but the chat saw it
close what you saw ghost yeah uh ghost
orbs
go down you need to go into the truck
you only have 35 percent
sanity
where did you see ghost orbs wait chad
why do you see
ghost arbs do i see that it does it
freezing temperatures
yes sir is it
you guys didn't see it
[Music]
uh i cannot i cannot guarantee the ghost
orbs uh
ovec
should i go back
[Music]
uh
i'm in the truck
sanity very dangerous please be careful
[Music]
maybe someone with more sanity wait we
don't want to lose good
let's narrow down let's narrow down some
candidates first and then we can
uh figure it out from there okay okay
that sounds good
no need to die for that yet but it's
fun oh not yet do we have anything
anything besides freezing temperatures
because the ghost orb summoned
some people in the chat said that but i
wouldn't trust it that much
anything besides yeah i wouldn't be able
to tell because i didn't see it myself
i don't think it was there i think they
saw a flashlight
i didn't see any orbs i only saw the
temperatures
um yeah well temperature we can still
roll out some
so
uh
banshee phantom race
rap we didn't have emp emf five though
we only had emf
two
so we can rule out a few more too
actually
right yeah
did we try the spirit blocks
uh i can try it some more i didn't
really do much with it
it's still i think i still have it i
think yeah since the
the ghost only responds to when you're
alone we probably
have to send one person there
i volunteer okay but you're
still only at 24 22 23.
how long does it have an activity
good luck i'm also gonna go into the
house
on the ground yeah
you can come get the camera it's in the
truck ah
sorry i forgot to use top button no no
but i'm going to stay far away from you
so you can talk to the ghost i'm just
going to watch from afar
ah content i'll get you the clip
gotta see what happens in there
i'm your host gal kuran the toughest
predator truck
okay the lights went out we're fine okay
how far do i have to stay away from you
i wonder
i'll be downstairs
all the lights are broken
is in the closet
i'm your host gargoyla goyla harry davis
mary davis you are the next part oh my
god
would you like to
[Music]
is in the closet over
i think we gotta go a little bit further
away oh my flashlight
oh
what happened to kelly
what happened
thank you i'm always in the closet
though
there's no closets there's no closets
oh
i don't want to open any doors
[Laughter]
girl you might have to get out of here
did you see callie's dead buddy did you
see that
she was like she's yeah
it was a pool door oh my god gouda is
that four percent percent sanity four
four
[Music]
and i just didn't open it because it was
a full door
what yes i have a flashlight yes yes yes
i'm coming coming but gouda is like
dangerously low on sanity like dangerous
yeah well if her body is close we can
just
are you still alive oh yeah yeah she is
okay yeah hi i just got a picture how do
i take a picture
oh that's a nice picture
[Music]
isn't that only five pictures maximum um
oh
[Music]
there's a flashlight on the ground i
think he's dead okay
can you hear me uh yes i can
holy [\h__\h] i'm dead we are finally
together
i watched the ghost take your life
really he swooped out of nowhere and was
like
and she said she that could have said
i tried to protect
but finally we're together smile because
death party does
that's what i said no one listened
they did it anyway for fun they're a
left
why is there free people though
is that amick do you also see free
wait amelia oh wait is one of them you
ah i guess ah that's you right
he's dead bodies yeah so i got on the
stairs and you died in the entrance
ah well
cali i've seen this world way too many
times kelly
i know we've met many times in it
as usual normally you're not really dead
i mean you're deaf but you're normally
not dead
yeah right right this is a new
experience for me i must say
it's a bit like it's different it's
different
i wonder where mary davis is yeah i
wonder if we can see her
but wait does that mean she must be here
i saw very dangerous
i know she saw me she was crazy i
watched her kill you
okay but she was probably hunting so
generally generally she's maybe up there
yeah in general probably i don't i don't
know if you can see it do i want to go
up here
i'm going to sleep out of the darkness
nothing is scary with you when you're on
my side nothing is scary
yeah yeah i guess so
yeah i guess so
what would be cool is if the game let us
turn the lights on and off
i know that we can still collect
evidence and do our journals
so that we can also get money oh i
wonder if we can help though
it would be nice to help but i think i
think
let's see what they're talking about
what are you
okay okay stay here stay here
[Music]
ah we can move stuff yes if there is
they say we can't move stuff
in uh sorry i mean if you plug your ears
on the top detector
[Laughter]
i'm a stop detective forever
no one can beat it
i can't hear your feet
kelly where are you kelly kelly my wife
where are you
i'm following up
in
are we ever gonna solve this we still
only have one evidence right
oh cool yeah they've they've talked
about uh letting us go
help someday and future updates that's
kind of cool
by the way i asked the chat i asked the
chat for that question was for the chat
oh yeah didn't talk to callie
i hope they're okay
i heard footsteps when i was upstairs in
the closet
[Music]
yeah did they lay down the journal i
guess they didn't what else did they
have to do i wonder i think they didn't
lay down the journal
they should have laid down the journal
to let the ghost ride
huh it should it's right here where come
on
here it is here it is i laid it down in
the beginning
ah i should probably be uh upstairs
though they should have moved upstairs
in the dark
but maybe if i believe that there's also
ghost orbs then we can rule a bit more
out
[Music]
yeah i have ghost orb and freezing
temperatures but uh
the only options i get are phantom mare
and you day
yeah you need fingerprints though
yes
[Music]
making some ex theories
well i wonder what it is
[Music]
attack in the dark turning the lights on
around the mirror lowest chance to check
spirit box it could be a man what did
you put kiara
hey i didn't put anything yet i'm trying
to find something that fits i think mare
makes sense
and what was the other one phantom wait
what does that say
consider drop your sanity but apparently
my sanity was
still very high so um
probably not phantom
they should then we can't talk to the
other girls but they should try the old
oops i didn't oh [\h__\h] i left oh
goddammit god damn it
one second
[Laughter]
goddammit wait one second one second
[Music]
what was the code again uh miss kiara
eh yeah i tried to leave the the menu
but i accidentally left the room one
second
oh okay
like the whole group or just one person
because like if it was like an average
between everyone then it started
attacking a lot more
after that gurus dropped really low
right so
oh it's the group it's the whole group
oh okay okay that makes sense
ah by the way you you got some uh
the the the journal was in the kitchen
so we should have
eventually moved it upstairs so they
could ride in there and also we should
have been looking for the ogia
void ojab board please work
yeah yeah how do you pronounce that but
we should have been looking for that
because it probably would have helped
people say luigi
so journal next time we move it where it
belongs
ah that sounds hey can i buy a
flashlight
if you have thirty dollars uh i think i
have
i think i have ten bucks and some bus
tokens and some pocket lists so can
anyone lend me like maybe 20 bucks
if someone has extra money then they can
buy them you don't have to you know
i'm five dollars don't worry it's fine
we're all broke
i'll just wander through the darkness we
already have a ghost writing book right
or is that a different thing
that always appears in the trunk i think
then i think i'll buy a tripod now wait
i keep talking about pressing the button
same same i keep forgetting okay i
bought a tripod okay so we can bring a
maximum of two
and then we already have one so okay i
bought the tripod
so we can have the camera up higher and
see more things now
okay all right gotta select a job is it
my turn now
yeah i think so why is cali still left
okay so which one did we do before
just now
that was like a house a farmhouse yeah
that was uh no that was a normal house
it wasn't
there's two houses and then one normal
house
uh street ridgeview roadhouse and
edgefield street
house ah because she died first want to
go to texas
we shouldn't go we shouldn't do
something too big though
we shouldn't do something too big
because we're never gonna finish it
so let's go to texas
said it sounds like a dangerous ghost is
haunting the area this one sounds
dangerous so you'll have to be careful
with this one
yeah no [\h__\h] sherlock yeah you're going
to leave as soon as you can
more info when you arrive inside thank
you amen
thank you i'm watching all the streams
are you for
windowing two-story six-bedroom with a
basement
possible ghost sighting this one sounds
dangerous yeah wow you
could have sold that one gather evidence
and leave recommended items therma
ah and then disney super chats
four-bedroom with the basement the owner
called this morning i just cracked my
neck
i'm in the area bring us a monitor
okay so i wonder team should be small
you guys want to do the one
the one-person one because
maybe we can actually accomplish it okay
we're going to texas yeah wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait uh i have to add the
tripod oh yeah
okay done done there we go
hey also how do you guys use the items
that you buy
uh you have to add them in the equipment
list
yeah yeah okay got it got it okay
howdy folks howdy ghosty
cowboys
oh oh yeah now you added it okay good
okay there is no salt though there is no
salt cali
but but we might need it you have to
ready up by the way we needed this these
are nuts
yeah here we go
here we go here we go
howdy
oh yeah sorry i was talking and you guys
didn't hear me um nice tripod brown
only responds in the mirror alone come
on you should use it's
going to be like that's a paranormal
activity refer to your journal does
anyone have a crucifix
no i think uh
[Music]
raise your lightest boys this is a sad
song
oh my gosh look at this
there is salt wait is there a limited
amount of salt or do you have like in
the salt is this better
it's amelia in here it just depends on
they will be inspiring they will be more
quiet if they're further away so it's
[Music]
on the salt by the way guys oh okay okay
okay
yeah okay
if you need more i just need to roll on
some gotcha and you'll have more
witness a ghost event i think with with
how slow we are doing these things i
think this might be the last game
yeah maybe yeah so yeah
yes our goal is to have everyone alive
yes let's go
hello should i say the iconic
i bring the tripod later on
all right all right because i otherwise
i can't have a flashlight
oh boy you think that'll summon the
ghost
hello let's get some light popping up in
here
hold on i have a lighter
uh what's the name again
what's the name of the ghost again it's
richard brown richard brown richard
brown
what are some what's some richard
nicknames
richie i'm loving
oh my god you clipped to the door scared
me
richard brown richard brown
oh got a children's room i don't like
this
richard brown hello ricardo
hello richard brown rick
maybe he doesn't speak english guys
are they ever in these normal rooms it
seems like
are they ever in there always like
downstairs or upstairs hello
richard brown
uh
he's at the dinner table i think he's
hungry richard brown
guys we have some we have free contempt
oh god so he's yeah he's definitely
there
he's definitely there he flipped the cup
at me freezing temps in the dining room
oh okay i'm scared i use the salt
did someone play with the lights just
now maybe i should use the salt guys
is there alexia mr brown i'll put some
salt in the kitchen
that was me by the way that was me that
was me
my heart just jumped into my forehead
come on give me some light
light yeah yep yep yep yep um the salt
isn't working when i try to use it okay
i'm gonna get the tripod i'm getting the
tripod
nokia why
i'm not seeing i'm just getting the
tripod
but do they have the camera that's the
photo camera right
that's the video camera how do i attach
it
uh how do i attach that
ah
f okay and now i take that okay
perfect oh god
it's not waterproof is it waterproof i
wonder
would be funny if it was broken now
i'm back with the camera and the tripod
in which direction should i put the
camera
towards the dining room dining table
okay
um
i don't know i keep on forgetting the
ground how do i turn it on
ah now it's on let's see what's
what i turned on the camera i turned on
the camera i'm gonna i'm gonna check
[Music]
truck is safe zone
truck is safe done okay no activity
sanity looks good
and the camera
oh okay
let's see maybe we see something spooky
spooky time although the rain is so
noisy
no i'm not a chicken no no no no no
no
no i'm the camera girl
i'm the camera girl someone has to look
at it but i don't see any ghosts or
should i should i be seeing ghost arbs
if they were ghost up should i be seeing
them right now turn off the lights
uh there we go is this
how i see ghost starbs
what i'm i'm in the truck i'm checking
the camera
okay okay i thought i didn't hear it for
a while
don't marry i'm alive and everyone's
sanity is looking good however there has
been some
activity from the ghost a little bit a
little bit
okay
he's wear night vision
what is that what is goes up ghost off
confirmed
i think is that a ghost story is that a
ghost story
i see a ghost orbs confirmed girls
i'm not sure what it is maybe it's
breath maybe it's go for
or chats is like 50 50 divided
i see a lot of it though
there's a lot of breath there
by the way frames are dropping pretty
hard right
especially if i go out of the obs window
to play the game then it gets worse
why are the frames dropping so strong
right now i wonder
yeah maybe maybe it's just because of
the freezing temperatures
no it was like around like in the back
there was uh
i don't know whatever it is but
my frames are fun really maybe it's just
in my in my
maybe it's better for you guys than what
i see
get in there okay i'm going in
maybe i can bring this one what is the
camera even useful for what are the
photos useful for is there some things
that i can see only in the photos
okay sorry what are you doing back there
more money oh
does it matter what i take
i'm back in the house to take some
photos
and i'm still not sure because the chat
was like 50 50 on whether or not it was
ghost orbs or if it was
breath
richard brown
is it richard brown was it richard brown
richard brown where are you richard
brown hello
which is wow he doesn't like that
richard brown how are you
richard brown where are you here
it's cold bread i know i have only five
photos but i don't know what one i
should take
a little candle oh
where where can you see that on the door
in the basement
temperatures and we have um
what upstairs upstairs
okay okay it's either a wraith or a
[\h__\h]
i don't know if you guys can see it but
oh how did you see that you're a smart
girl
wait no cha cha told me
wait tell me again that is it that green
thing that showed up there
yeah i want to take a photo of it
do you have the camera yeah i have the
camera uh oh
a bit more a bit more oh there we go ah
ah it's a bit more to the left
it's moving i saw that
it flew
how do you know that we haven't had any
footsteps so it's either a banshee or a
wraith go to light oh
please tell us are you here
because you're already sure
richard brown please write something
richard brown howdy yeehaw
maybe let's just talk to him and not use
his name okay maybe he doesn't like it
with me
okay please write something
has anyone heard footsteps no
no i don't think so please write
a message
be it likes us to be alone right yeah so
i'm leaving bye-bye
also likes to be alone
he wants to be alone okay he wants to be
alone change the camera angle chicken no
i'm not a chicken i'm a phoenix
woo i gotta check these things this is
important good eyes again uh
going low
oh i don't see anything you guys are in
the way
but should we change the the camera
angle maybe
but i think it's in a good angle wait
does that mean we have no time
we have fingerprints right oh what
ah but we don't ma we maybe don't have
ghost stirrups right we're not sure of
that
oh my god there's a lot of post activity
it's a maximum ghost activity
do you guys hear me holy [\h__\h]
yep they're leaving i think they didn't
hear me they all dead
what do i do now i saw the ghost in the
camera girls hello hello
hello
[Music]
is
oh no oh no
that's no good i saw the ghost on the
live camera by the way it was really
pretty
you guys hear me right what kind of
ghost what did it look like
uh what the ghost looked like it looked
like
i don't i don't really know how the
other ghosts look like so i'm not sure
but the chat was like oh
banshee or something like that
[Music]
to pick up
on the camera you don't have to okay
what the hell what's up who's got the
camera i want to see this
i gotta get a picture of this does
anybody have a camera yeah i'm curious
uh
i only have to i only have the video
camera handling
oh yeah yeah we already know about that
oh yes take a
pic i can't i can't take a pic i only i
can only take a video
and you guys want to guess so i don't
know what do we have what do you think
it is
banshee
right i'm thinking it's
thanksgiving excuse me don't [\h__\h]
scream or am i just
typically a band she would scream i
guess not a ghost banshee but uh
so when eda died did we hear footsteps
because i
i'm pretty sure uh i think i heard
footsteps
i didn't hear anything but we didn't get
am f level five
and the ray fingerprint reason spirit
box
what what spirit box again i can't
remember if i heard footsteps now
um somebody else wanna but about the emf
the banshee would have needed emf 5
as well no and we didn't get that
oh we didn't get we did not get emf5 but
we did get the radio
so is that spirit box
did we say something over the spirit box
actually i'm not sure
maybe that was the other house
it it's the spirit oh spirit box
my chat my chat says a toxicity
uh we did get we did get emf level five
so it must be a banshee
okay benchy yes
yes i am for the bouncy
i do let's go
bring do i have do i have to bring back
the items
you know the tripod do i have to bring
it back
uh i don't know i maybe
when i bring the tripod i can't bring
anything else though
i don't have to i don't have to hey yeah
i wonder uh chad says no
okay they also
all right so we did it we did it i think
it it's pretty sure that it's a bad
thing
is that not a thing i thought banters
are only
wait wait girls wait wait wait wait
aren't banshees only female and this
name is male
is it huh is that random does that
matter in the game i thought banshees
were only
irish banshees can be male maybe
i wonder not
okay maybe not in this game okay so i
think we can say banshee does everyone
have it in the journal
yup i updated it sounds good okay good
already
[Music]
what is a wrap
oh my ears
oh wow great hooray
yeah i'm upset welcome back
if i heard footsteps though but oh i
suppose
i forgot to film my journals
ah oh you know the bone
is it called why am i level one and you
guys are level two
because you you died uh
in the first game so early i guess i
don't know
uh yeah i suppose that makes sense
that's there
do you guys want to play one more quick
one
i can do one more you want to do them
one yes okay
one for one person okay
i wonder if there's anything i have 25
[Music]
i want a head mounted camera
that sounds fun that's all right oh no
you have a vlog squad
i'm 25 let's see
gather evidence do we want to buy
something a lighter
afterwards let's see i want to look for
a small one what can i do with a lighter
how about tanglewood street house size
one person a small three bedroom single
floor house the basement got an email
from a friend
he says there is definitely some kind of
paranormal activity here
head there and gather as much evidence
as you can so ghost removal team can
finish the job
okay let's go what is she reading
ah i'm ready spaghetti
i voted i am also ready
spaghetti i'm also ready carbonara
i want to be level two i want to be
level two
i want to be level two you know where
does this door go i'm gonna go out here
where did he not go you know you know i
was buying my thermometer
ah i'm ready uh
okay let's go last game
last game wait wait wait wait wait guys
guys guys can we
push to talk yeah oh um
we have to like leave the lobby to get
to the settings oh we have to leave
correctly yeah forget that forget that
next time okay donkey
let's go
we're going in all right lads
what do we got patricia clay
and remember to check the whiteboard for
help on your screen where is this
time
[Laughter]
um a photo of dirty water in a sink i
can take a picture of that that seems
easy enough emf reader
dirty water attack that's no better if
it's red does it mean
ems five all together i said one two
three four five ah okay okay okay
excellent
i'll be checking the emf
i got the book too and i'll pick the um
i thought that was money for a second
what is that
uh for the do you have a writer for the
smudge stick
i do i do excellent would you like it
would you like me to give it to whoever
has this much sticks
no i think i think anyone you might need
always forget this i always forget that
i don't know how to use them either but
we'll learn okay maybe one of us can
have the sticks and one of us will light
them i have the lighter so we can do
that then
all right let's move out roast gestures
thank you for the super chat thank you
friends welcome to my crib
welcome to my cr
what was the name again of the dos
patricia
oh see this time there's no bone what
was that bone before then
there was a in the previous household
evidence
yeah oh
that wasn't evidence i thought that was
weird
give us a sign
do i just have to keep on turning this
on and off to see it
give us a sign i have to keep it turned
on
maybe like that patricia clark
give us a sign i'm going to check the
basement for the ouija board
i'm going to follow you where are you
oh when you eat chicken wings you should
clean up your bones man
clean up your bones patricia
guys take a picture i don't have the
camera
yeah that's right the dirty water i
don't have the camera
or the i'm useful i'm useful i can do it
does someone have the camera this looks
like uh
i have a camera where's your stick
though you should take a photo of the
bone you should take a photo of the bone
or maybe the water doesn't show up
itself okay nothing
girl don't say behind me
[Music]
oh we got emf4 emf4 in this
position uh yep um four
where are you here uh uh it's gone now
it's gone
emf 4 but it's gone
i was exactly here here
oh okay let me
but it's gone now why is it gone come
back
kitchen or storage all right patty give
us the next amazon
[Music]
patricia clark where are you patricia
clark
hey i hear it guys somebody got
something in the closet no
huh
let's see i'm gonna leave some salt
that's my radio that's my spirit oh
oh what what what is that
what's that always there what is that
it's not so oh it's my size ah okay okay
i wonder where else i should put it i'm
gonna bring the
i'm gonna bring the camera into tripod
brb
gotta go
why do they walk so slow i wish they
could walk a bit faster
oh everyone's doing pretty fine
oops i got that man i got that man
i got them every time
how do i take the whole thing
i have to have an empty hand okay
i'm bringing the camera
i'm back in the house give us a sign
where should i put the camera where i
found the signal or is it
in the kitchen okay
everybody put fingerprints in your jar i
know
oh wait how do i put it down again
like this
the lights are dead the lights are good
it said kill in the box it's
kill in the box never
okay everybody it says kill so everybody
put the spirit box in your in your
journal please
we'll do got you is that the only
evidence we have
oh we have fingerprints okay true okay
so it can be either a spirit
does it say anything about uh okay i'm
talking about
somebody had lending so i can find out
where the notepad is
um
[Music]
i i got i have activity i think
emf too only though
yes i have uh the boxes on emf ii right
now
i hope i don't die maybe let's switch
emf 4 emf 4 emf 4 emi4
it's active the ghost is active don't
die
oh god
run run wait where am i ah where am i
where's that
it's about to hunt
oh my god
should we reposition dead i don't think
[Applause]
good job good good job
okay
what else can we try what are you guys
saying
i really want to see if we get dirty
water in the sink
maybe there's some there are pretty rare
oh
that's a shaver i want to reposition it
how should i move it again how do i move
the whole thing
[Music]
the phone the phone the phone why did
the phone ring
did someone make it ring it stopped
good question
guys do we have to pick it up do we have
to pick the phone up
patricia clarke is this still patricia
clark
patricia clarke yeah i think so where
are you patricia clark
talk to me freezing temperatures no
no please right patricia clay
something has anybody seen a ghost orb
no but i repositioned the camera to the
basement so maybe
i don't know where should we where
should i put the camera
it didn't see anything when i pointed it
to the kitchen
okay i relit the candles wait did you
stop the camera
yeah i did before but in the kitchen it
didn't really see anything
give us a sign there could be here
definitely give us a sign
do you want to use the i mean we already
have spirit box evidence we don't really
need it
um unless you wanna
oh
hello patty give us a sign
patty give us a sign
patricia throw something
trisha clark are you here
i'm gonna go check the camera
okay okay
uh emf 2 why does it turn on the water
f2 f2 is it brown you made 4 ems for it
i had to turn
oh
i heard something a ghost says stinky
brownie blue in my foot
i heard it too basement
[Music]
oh my god callie callie
callie be safe i'm gonna try summon
missy mazzy
oh because i wanted to see if maybe
something's down here
do you see something
we have to turn off the laptop i'm
turning up the light turning up the
lights okay uh
i'm scared inna do you see something you
know i don't think
okay
okay i'm gonna point it to the kitchen
then put the camera down
um
[Music]
patricia clark i love you patricia clark
i love you patricia
i look like you're from patricia
patricia clark give us a sign
there's a sign patricia
patricia patricia i love you
patricia patricia are you married
patricia are you married
patricia clark do you have children
patricia clarke where do you come from
patricia clarke what's your age
how old are you that's cool
are you looking for a boyfriend
but you said you live in the void
that's your shock like what's your
favorite food
that's what that's like nothing in the
book
nothing what a boring ghost
what'd you say you're kinda lame
he's in the garage i'm taking your car
for a spin but where's the gun
patricia come on
yes patricia is the chicken not me not
messiah
[Music]
who's playing with the lights who's
playing with the lights
okay
breath footsteps everything
let's go let's go let's go
oh cali is screaming
yeah you're in the closet yeah why are
you uh i'm leaving
i'm leaving i'm leaving i'm going to the
truck
is kelly dead
kelly's dead
okay wait they did they did right though
right so we have ghost writing spirit
box
wait it it can it not only be a spirit
because we got spirit box we got
fingerprints and we got
ghost riding don't we have all of that
i think someone said they wrote kill no
no that was the fear
[Music]
yeah but it has to be alone right if
they want to write down something they
gotta be alone
okay
yeah where is the book now isn't it
already
uh it's on the dining table right
the it's on the dining table right now
i can't i feel like it's in the kitchen
so
i'm just trying to see if i can move it
to the kitchen table
okay but we don't have freezing
temperatures
we don't have em level five
the only thing that could be left is
ghost doorbell ghost riding and we
didn't see
ghost or ups i guess oh my oh
what what nani
is that kelly
let me see the camera
what's in the camera do you see i don't
see anything you see the body
i see nobody wait what oh you gotta
sweat
you don't see that what do you mean you
don't see that no
i don't see anybody what do you what
why do you not if what
it's not on your screen
i guess my game is bugging or something
um
yeah yes yes
i feel like since we placed a camera and
saw no ghost orbs it must be ghost
riding
oh my god
[Laughter]
yep i would say it's a spirit because
the they did we didn't see any ghost
orbs at all it must be the writing so it
can only be the spirit
hello i forgot your name that's a good
point patricia patricia
[Music]
i don't like the clock sound hold the
book if you want to move around
oh it's a product why do you think it's
a poltergeist
very good camera angle placement
oh yeah right
[Music]
um
light flickered light flickered you see
activity
okay
are the lights off
yes they are off yes
all right maybe leave the book on the
table for a while
yeah put it down yeah let's try putting
it down
can't we anger it somehow
patricia clarke where are you
patricia clark give us a sign wait don't
don't flash this
don't don't use the flashlight oh okay
patricia clark give us a sign patricia
clarke please write in the book
patricia clarke hello patricia clark
what's your show should we do it
patricia clarke where are you
patricia clarke hello patricia clark
how old are you
are you here patricia i don't have any
more time just
show them up already
laundry room with the book yes
yeah maybe the ghost ghost has moved
perhaps
what the hell am i alone right now
i'm coming back where's the
[Music]
i feel like i picked it up but then i
don't know what happened
do you can you scroll your item and oh
yeah i think i see that man
yeah sorry i saw it
one thing come think
where did you go where did you go wait
you know where did you go you know where
did you go
you know where did you go
through the wall kiara and the ghost
went straight for you
were so close to getting out finally
we're together
again all right man let's look ah
at least you know are still alive but we
can't rule out
we also didn't have ghost orbs though so
with the evidence that we have the only
other thing that we could find is ghost
orbs or ghost writing
i think
because we don't have uh we don't have
words we don't have the freezing and we
don't have the emf level five
right then wait what
okay but culture guys throw things and
slam doors and this ghost didn't do any
of that
ah i think here i have them
appeared in the book yeah but maybe the
book is just placed wrong
already or the camera is placed wrong
could be
that could
we're really bad with finding these
ghosts huh what is that
uh oh oh
that's it patricia clark will you write
in this book please it can't be that
hard just pick up the pencil
yeah slap it around just [\h__\h] ride it
throw it
through
for god's sake just right in there
give us some evidence or move the camera
again again come in
put the book in the garage yeah maybe um
i wish i could chelsea i ever died
it killed her here yeah
that's because it was hunting you know
you can't hear me but it was hunting
that's why it moved around
normally oh my god all right so i blew
the breaker sure
the game really isn't hey patricia
i know you you were all like oh this
game is so much
scarier than the other game you play the
only really scary moment is for
like a second when you hear some noises
but that's like not even that scary
i was thinking fast moving is going to
be such a
scary game that i was like yesterday i
was like
i don't want a bandit's game i want to
maybe i can ask
ahmed to play instead of me last minute
i was about to like cancel
but then i saw and then then i saw uh
hold up started playing the game
yesterday
and it didn't really look that scary uh
yeah rihanna might be different yeah vr
might
make it much more scarier are we playing
on easy ah
is it scarier if we don't play on easy
[Music]
what mario 64 for next halloween what
mario 64 is not scary it's just really
angry
really a little bit be careful anger
yeah yeah do what you want
all right
ghost
[Laughter]
yeah i know it's hilarious all right
well i'm in that thing
what are you stop it
it'll be weird you're weird
it's a it's a greeting in german
speaking language it's a chick on the
left
or do you want to guess the left and
nook is on the right cheek
i'm underworld yet so
uh
i
no we don't know who it will go for it's
just you know you don't know where it'll
pop up so
whoever there's oh there's this like
maybe the road
okay we gotta go check the book okay
let's go
together okay and then if
there's a hunt let's follow the girls
again shall we
yeah kelly
let's see what we can find
my body my body what dropped the ems
thing
what was that did you just say it sounds
like a microwave oh
your hot pockets oh there's a little
fingerprint here
does she listen to me i wonder if i say
something
i wonder if she reacts to that
petroleum what's up what's up patricia
clark
penny okay
offline what do you mean offline did
that beep was that you
yeah i heard it too it was like a
microwave kill death twice
it was a microwave she's making hot
pockets
oh better be a pizza pocket full of hot
right in the book
i threw it down here yes good at more
swearing
did she take the book you don't see it
the
pen oh wait put the line there again
girls put the line there didn't the pen
move
i swear i threw the book down
oh what is that
more cases to count um the book and the
book has glitched into the world
wait girl check the salt see if they're
um see if the
uv picks up anything
i moved where's the salt there's salt is
here
can you hear me go down
[Music]
over
they won't notice
it's a spirit it's a spirit it's better
to be a spirit oh
hi kelly
who had the camera
where are we really bad at this game
yeah the teeth sometimes scare me
i'm thinking it's a poster guys too you
think so but they what did they move
well it didn't step on the fault right
so uh they moved the book they threw
they checked the book
it's like it's like a little when you
like sprinkle on the floor
it's like hold it against the pile but
with the spirit walks on it
oh oh moshi moshi
mossy mossy
could be could be yeah it could be that
we just misplaced the camera
so that's why we didn't see any ghost
boards ghost orbs
ghost boars they should try to find that
ouija board
oh it's ringing again is that a thing
that the poltergeist does i wonder
oh i think they're leaving i think
they're leaving cali
oh what are they saying
[Music]
apparently
um yeah yeah okay let's go with all the
guys let's go
let's go i can't push this let's go
let's go
keep going you ready
yeah i know you don't hear me but yes
yes i'm going for all the guys what
about you kelly you too right
you're a two percent on the 15th same
oh really oh wow she wasn't serious
yeah she was losing it
it's got to be dust yeah it's only on my
screen right oh man
weird looting game
okay okay did we get it right from one
time
yes finally sponsor guys
finally fleshlight nice
finally
that's the first thing i got right
[Laughter]
yes we did it we did it
ghostbusters
high fives all around i died right at
the door though right
at the door i was about to leave i uh
you can't leave your money oh i tried
though i didn't
hide yeah yeah
[Music]
you found it so quickly
i i just remembered there was it was an
open door but i didn't even close the
door but then ah
on you i guess ah love is an open door
indeed love is an open
dog we did well
good job yeah we got one we got the big
one that was a chicken yeah
good job naruto
[Music]
nowhere to run yeah let's all
nowhere to walk run
yeah it's a naruto walkie walkie walk
all right i think uh two hours of ghost
busting is enough right
hmm
i'm sleeping right now it's fun oh yeah
i have fun too yes that was fun i keep
forgetting
we should we should go back to discord
oh yeah let's go back and see that
ah hello i'm back
a demon just kind of flew out of me in
that moment
that was fun i have to say i expected it
to be much much more scary
but the chat says it because we were
uneasy it wasn't so scary i guess it
gets much scarier
i mean it wasn't scary i mean that
wasn't bad
but level one number two um
[Music]
i have an idea i have an idea i have an
idea
so since since it's maximum four players
but we want
ami to be in there too how about i play
together with cali right like i visit
her at her house
oh we play a sniper we play just as one
player there's no other reason
i just wanted to so that amic enjoyed
the game there's no other reason why i
would want to do that
yeah let's do it really yeah ally can be
the mouse and you can be the wisdom
it'll be like it was
perfect yeah so we can play this five
next time yay
i'm up for that let's do it
yay okay and then
that way that way me and kelly can
mentally support each other
when when we're like scared in the
darkness yes
are we gonna play in the dark on here
big brain with brain all righty i think
that's it
yeah yeah does anybody have
uh any announcements for the week yeah
my new song is on all streaming
platforms go check out
and it's not it will be it will be there
it will be there
soon for spotify but itunes and whatever
go check it out please
i'm i'm collabing with polka senpai this
week
um well i still have to put up my
schedule so
oh yeah uh yeah i do too to be announced
soon
soon yeah i think tomorrow i'm instead
of bitching kitchen we're gonna be [\h__\h]
and movers cause i recently
[Music]
all right everyone thanks for watching
thank you
thanks guys catch up on the flip side
[Applause]
[Music]
then
so