[Music]
um
bye
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
good
hello hello
hello hello hello hello
scarf hello
hi guys can you hear us okay
hi everyone hello we have the hellos
in chat people can hear yeah
[Music]
shut up
oh my gosh hello everyone
here we're gonna go ahead and
switch on over to the
main scene you guys here we are
hi welcome back welcome back everyone
we missed you i'm back in the game
yeah i actually this is my first stream
since being back from break whoa
[Music]
thanks guys thank you i wanted to do a
little welcome back stream but it's
gotta wait for later just because um
this takes priority and this comes first
i actually just got off a plane
but i'm excited i'm fresh off the plane
so i'm uh i'm excited nonetheless to
continue our story
yes oh boy
because we left off at a pretty
interesting point
maybe we can build a tree house and we
can start living off the land
in a tree house yeah just forget about
being hunters that sounds like a great
idea
yeah screw that we're gonna be monkeys
yeah
living in trees now you become one with
become one with the nature that's uh
i mean it's possible if you guys wanted
to do that i wouldn't stop you
oh not stop you the problem is
convincing the others
uh to to also go along with the plan
what do you say everybody hey monkeys
i'm rebecca you're always welcome
no yes that's fine that's fine
maybe we can find the circus monkey and
we can bring them along and they'll like
do funny tricks monkey
yeah okay as long as there's wi-fi
uh there is no wi-fi here no
there's definitely no wi-fi here no
thanks getting out of here
maybe watching token can rig us um some
kind of
lte service machine or some kind of
light i mean you made a cool sound
gun that makes doggies really happy
if she can make a sonic sound gun
there's no way that watoto can't make a
uh some way to get television or
something
okay okay i like the ideas
got some good ideas here you guys now
it's now we got to put him into practice
yeah yeah i'm sure that you guys will
find a way
you guys will find a way to use those
wonderful imaginations because that
that is what will get you the best
results i would say in this campaign for
[Music]
sure if you're not sure if you can do it
just ask me just ask okay
okay well today the goal is to finish
this mission am i right
yeah that would appear
[Applause]
yeah so perhaps we should do a little
recap for um
for those that need a slight refresher
oh yeah
[Laughter]
you can put that on everything dude you
can put oh
yes sorry i won't
it's like it's like pancake stuff you
just add water to it and then you shake
it so hence the shake and then you bake
and then you're talking about bacon bits
oh
a little different i've always wanted
bacon bits i was never allowed to try
bacon bits what's that oh
is it just tiny bits of bacon yeah but
they like they don't come cold or
anything they just come like dry and
then you just sprinkle it on yeah it's
like it's like croutons but bacon
[Music]
yeah that's the only it's the only way
you can eat that salad you get the bacon
bits of cheese on it
um anyway sorry back to back to myth
bacon bits
um basically uh the whole team arrived
at the bar
and discovered that they were being
drafted into a brand new
hunter agency um that was
formally a long time ago um let's say
about
35 or so years ago um running very
strong
but something happened and they
disbanded and now and now
uh the previous owner's daughter has
chosen to restart up the agency
with you for um
[Music]
we have recruited yes you got recruited
that's right and you got sent on a
mission
but unfortunately due to poor funding um
they gave you a truck that didn't
exactly
run as planned some things got out of
control and you didn't really make it to
the mission
yeah oh unfortunately you guys got
stopped on the road when getting some
tasty
um uh what what was what was the other
landing
other landian flavored ice cream and
also the special
promotional shrek flavored yeah can't
forget the shrek flavor vulgar flavor
yeah dirt flavor what a flavor
water flavored yeah unfortunately
while eating the delicious ice cream
that you found on the side of the road
the truck broke down and you had to find
your way over to
scotty's motel where unfortunately
you met a world of cockroaches and the
truck was stolen
i get to start imagining my future as a
cockroach circus
uh maestro
i go ahead and hire the cockroaches no
need for me to compliment your tickets
to your shoes
yeah unfortunately that may have to wait
until next time though but they'll wait
for you
i'll wait for you yes in my
the world of cockroach society awaits
for you
so you guys uh unfortunately had to deal
with
some grand theft and away your truck
went into a junkyard
thankfully um after stealing a shopping
cart from
a homeless dude for no reason um and
walking
pretty much walking because the shopping
cart you just like you got inside it
and and walked there it was basically
the same pace
maybe you went a little faster uh you
made it to the junkyard
yes yeah
and we may not have gone much faster but
we look cool as hell doing it
i mean maybe little bit and our hearts
are going
very fast i can't argue with that next
time i may have to make your own
morality though
so i'll be careful yeah that'll be fun
you
you watch yourselves you got a freebie
but next time
oh next time might not be so lucky
i could be so lucky lucky lucky lucky
yeah take your mercy on the news that's
when i was singing uh the internet is
for porn
the internet is boring
yeah you're a girl boy
[Music]
oh this tension what okay
i don't understand uh okay no porn here
then
yeah keep your family friendly
you know how we do we gotta keep it
family friendly
that's right you can say whatever
true fact they're used to this is a norm
on my channel
can you please do it no problem no
problem
uh you guys as soon as you got to the
junkyard
things started to go down and by things
i mean
it turned out the junkyard was some kind
of trap in disguise
and there's a hunter but not necessarily
the same kind of hunters you guys know
someone is hunting you guys for sport
yeah set up the whole place to
specifically target
yes 80s bam so we can't get a head shot
that's how you take down a sniper we
have to think about how to take down a a
sniper guy
yeah assassin especially considering
you guys are in the arenda
grassy place right now you don't know
much about this place
um only that it has kind of uh entrapped
you into a maze
of sorts uh a green a albeit beautiful
green uh and very
winding and ever changing maze that
somehow watateau was able to discover
by burning unburnable unburnable
vine walls
we don't know how water did it uh but it
was quite something
it was something all right and now you
have chosen to rest
here for the time being and uhu is still
trying to get to you
tiara while being stuck in the thorns
from above but it's making some progress
so
in due time
yeah that wasn't me beautiful green
forest be a shame if somebody burnt it
to the ground
getting some funny ideas scout smells
like a campfire
yeah well if it's too thick do you think
maybe we could send smoke signal if
anybody knows how to send the smoke
signal or is the
it looks a little too thick the thicket
is too thick
for the smoke to get out right well you
could certainly try
it we're still trying to get out
but we've just reached like this this
like
i don't know what is this place right
a checkpoint a checkpoint a safe spot
for now if you will but before now
okay well does anybody have any like
high athletics because maybe somebody
could climb to the top of this big old
tree and see if they can see which way
is
which or we can like look at moss on the
rocks
i have been thinking of something but i
don't know if it is like applicable
here but i do have um direction sense
as a merit oh i don't know if that helps
um this is a bit of an unpredictable
area unfortunately
um you don't really have a good sense of
of where you
are and this place seems to be
ever-changing so unfortunately i don't
think that it will help you much here
so i don't have anything athletic so i
suggest someone else i have two
athletics but that's not much
i can start origin for stuff if need be
but i also have a pickaxe maybe i can
start hacking and chopping
like a machete i don't have any mine
would you all please
role perception for me the first
perception check of the game
the sessions what was the combo again
okay it's
wits plus composure please rule that for
me and re-roll your tens
please you guys are fast
uh eight or
uh smaller than eight right okay or
greater than eight
oh yeah yeah great night okay
oh nice
nice very good okay now everyone
uh please type how many successes you
got you have to do something
two two okay let's just do it right yeah
amelia one minute two guru
it is good i not want one because
greater than seven but it's greater than
eight oh
oh that was greater than seven last time
oh no it's greater than eight all right
one one it's okay no problem
okay and two i see so let's go ahead and
start off with both
scout and watato what you guys see
here so basically what you can observe
uh from this area
is that it's very uh well it's rather
vast and it's also
very um well fortified so
even though it's basically made of grass
and and greenery and thorns and whatnot
um it's very well protected so you get
the feeling that no sniper is going to
find you here
for long for long um definitely
unable to see anything from the outside
um
though you can see that there's light
filtering in so that's nice it's the
only way you're able to see
anything at all um and then
both uh let's see yule and tiara
you observe this as well um but you also
take
note that there is a patch of beautiful
flowers
beautiful white flowers they smell very
fragrant and seem
very lovely and nice um and they're kind
of surrounding
the tree um and seem to be
um yeah very beautiful unlike anything
you've ever seen before
um and the entire area is full of a nice
fragrance
i've seen such a beautiful before oh
yeah
but i can make some acid out of those
flowers over there we can
burn our way through this forest
but it's so it's so pretty i wouldn't
want to
ruin it nature's damn
see we've got some different viewpoints
here
but they do smell very nice and also one
last thing that you see is that there
are two different directions you can go
in there's
an opening to the right and opening to
the left and of course the place where
you came from
oh left and right
to the vote well whatever you guys
want to coin
uh maybe like can we flip
a total coin hey
slip what don't if he
yeah nose up or nose down no please
i thought i was scared of heights it's
okay we won't throw you up tonight
yeah just a little bit off the ground
[Music]
can we take a look at like kind of see
what's down each pathway
oh sure lit up that always goes well
you never split the party
never split the group
so ah
didn't we bring some walkie-talkies with
us i think we can split while carrying
the walkie-talkies with us
that is true that's a good idea
do the walkie-talkies work would you
like to test them then
yes okay all right
can you hear me all right
well you guys are rather close to each
other so of course you can hear each
other
well then since they seem to work i
think we should
split into two groups and while
communicating
walk through the paths
okay sounds good
yeah oh somebody's going to pick water
huh
me oh
um all right which way should we go
yes you must choose right or left i
total feels tingly for the left
i agree it must be the left alright
yes you and i are going right
all right today is let's go right
going right
all righty then so it looks like we've
got both scout and
ewell to the right and then wattato and
tiara to the left
all right and that's more wrong
what could go what could go wrong
what could go wrong i'm thinking can you
imagine
can you curve balls yeah at all
i mean hello you're speaking directly to
me if that's what you want
no i'm just kidding please have mercy on
us
maybe but you did split the party so
let's see what happens
i i believe it was i believe it was uh
all of you
so let's just see what happens let's see
what happens okay
so let's go ahead
and start off with hmm
let's see right left right left um
okay let's do it this way uh tiara
roll roll a 1d2
yes
okay so you guys go second so we'll
start off
uh with scout and yule
all right okay all right
you guys chose to go to the right
so as you make your way down the path
i'll go ahead and change the uh
the scenery for you as things do well
they do change a tiny bit
ever ever so slightly
the scenery is going to uh change a bit
here we go on europe i've been in this
place before
you've got some rather fire
maybe you've got some rather tall trees
here
very tall indeed and if you look closely
uh there are vines winding in between
them
yes you can make a didgeridoo out of
these trees you see how nice and long
and tall they are you can make a lot of
stuff out of these trees
yeah it looks like that maybe
and take them with us just in case
not a bad idea would you like to live in
it cut down the trees
yeah do you have something to cut down
the trees
um no i got me
a blade all right
i'm not gonna use my pickaxe though
cause it's very nice i'm gonna use my
blade
okay you wanna use your blades sounds
good yes
all right comment would chop all right
sure let's give it a try go ahead and
roll your dexterity
and weaponry for me
oh baby we're cutting down big trees
tonight baby
okay we're not gonna use the weapons
modifier because you're not using this
as a weapon you're using it to
to cut down some trees that it may not
be intended to cut down so just go ahead
and do a simple
weaponry and dexterity roll for me
uh okay
i believe in you i'll be a six so that's
a six
d ten greater than eight right okey
dokey yes
great sounds good i just wanna make it
yeah you got it
okay go ahead and re-roll that 10.
okay okay roll
one d one e ten
he's probably making a helicopter out of
that
okay wow
for success okay with four successes
uh you managed to very slowly but surely
chip away at the walls um and the vines
they don't like you doing that um oh
great
yeah really not big fans of you
uh chopping down the trees um this is a
really interesting part of this area
because it's not quite like
the other parts in that uh the thorns
are
unable to be cut through i mean they
certainly aren't made of anything that
is similar to uh
actual nature or anything there's
something magical about them but
these long trees are a bit different uh
these are sentient aren't they
you're alive i mean
i mean you're not totally sure you can't
really tell you're no experts on these
trees but when you cut into them it does
it does seem as though the forest is
screaming oh jesus
you managed to cut yourself are you
girls okay over there
hello
[Applause]
you do get a little message from them
you can kind of hear but you are busy
cutting at the same time
so
all right wait what were you saying
about the trees though
they're screaming the whole forest seems
to be screaming
as you cut down the tree like like that
like
or it's hard to describe not much like a
human scream but rather
you can feel it something reverberating
uh in your bones
as you cut down the tree as though some
great force within
uh is crying out but it's basically too
late because now you've cut a big piece
of the tree um
it's a decent size about half a human
all right yeah the vines are very angry
though
um and in fact as you take
the uh the piece of the tree that you've
cut uh the vines seem to be closing in
rather quickly
i think we might have to start running
uh uh uh all right
all right this is giving me flashbacks
yeah
once once again uh maybe we should uh
radio
into uh uh let me see if this thing
works
hindley left come in tingly live this is
wood shopping right
do you copy over water
we've got some tingly oh never mind
we've got some
trees screaming trees here and they seem
to be closing in on us how are you guys
doing over there over
it's a good thing that you asked it's a
good thing that you asked scout
because we're gonna go ahead and segue
on over
to
now for you guys the scenery is ever so
slightly
different
jackpot incoming
yes so for you all for for you two
you find uh this place that actually
does straight up look like a maze a
rather fancy maze actually
um but the walls are actually very tall
you see this isn't uh the scale that you
may see this right now
um is actually it's very very very big
you guys would probably be about the
size of
one of those tiles on the ground oh
yes wow very large and literally a maze
but the one thing that you don't quite
see in this picture
um is that those white flowers kind of
continue to grow
uh along the vines and along the way and
they smell so nice pretty
yeah would you like to do anything like
make a perception check
yeah yeah i want to see
if like when the mace splits up at
certain points which way the flowers go
if they go
only in one way and then we shall follow
the
flowers adam okay
sounds good maybe maybe maybe not follow
the flowers
all right good idea sure go ahead and
roll perception
both of us yeah uh sure if you'd like
let's do
both double the power okay
you have more dices anyway
okay okay sounds good so both of you are
kind of able to perceive
um that these flowers are the same ones
that you found in that nice little safe
area
and they make you feel safe um
they smell very nice and you're able to
observe that um
they go for a little ways but
interestingly enough they stop and they
don't branch off into any other
any other direction they just kind of
become a bit less and less
um and wasato you specifically are able
to
sort of perceive that there are no there
is actually nothing dangerous about
these flowers in fact they're very
inviting
i thought they'll take a flower pick
flower yeah okay
give to pretty bird lady
[Applause]
for me
wait thank you so kindly ara
i
it does indeed smell very nice um
can i pick a flower too sure
i'll pick a flower give it to watto
oh thank you thank you
you're welcome let's continue walking we
shouldn't
waste our time interestingly enough
even though you've taken these flowers
it doesn't seem that uh
the forest is angry or anything like
that so that's the good news
you do have some lovely white flowers
nice well can i use this for potions
i mean if you'd like to you have it now
so make it into a powder
yeah okay sounds good well you certainly
have it now you have it on your person
so that's good meanwhile
meanwhile where everyone seems to be
dying right now
psych psych
uh we're here and um unfortunately
uh unfortunately it seems uh let's see
they're right about now you guys uh the
vines are getting real wild
oh yeah uh shall we
make like a deer in headlights and run
yes can i maybe like search for
like any exits or anything on the
wall while we're running would you like
to be my guest
what was that i didn't hear you what
would you like to search for
like possible exits or exits
sure go ahead and do a perception check
for me
oh thank the lord
okay oh that is an exceptional success
all right so with that a very
exceptional success
you'll uh your eyes dart back and forth
as you look around for some possible
exit
uh the vines are closing in very quickly
and they seem to be uh definitely
interested
in uh taking you and making you a part
of them
uh however however the good news is as
you kind of begin to back up you'll
you perceive that behind you there's
actually um a perfectly
sized hole for people to fit through
that you might be able to escape through
that the vines aren't reaching right now
oh scout let's go this way
there's a way huh oh ho
it's perfectly suspiciously perfectly
sized for us to pass through but
better than nothing looks like one of
them game show halls when we got
through the uh the other side so let's
go let's go
what the clothes that's hitting this
this is the
this is the one up close according to my
my well on the television ma used to
watch this thing called
yoga yoga and they call this one the
tree pose
all right you go to the you go okay the
you go first scout you go first show me
how what the tree pose looks like
do i have to roll for this or can i just
go through athletics and dexterity
athletics
please
i mentioned in the beginning i hope you
brought some because i want to see it
i want to see you pushing scout butt
through the hole
did you say athletics and dexterity yes
ma'am
okay ma'am
threatening music okay one success is
all you need
scout you managed to wiggle your way
through there it is not comfortable and
it is very tight
however it is certainly uh nothing
compared to
the sharp vines that are going to pierce
your skin and uh
and make you a part of them you're glad
to not be a part of them
so thank you morning yoga
yes thank you we'll get them next time
very flexible but you'll fit
you're right
is it minus one if i have nothing in
athletics
uh oh you have nothing athletics yes
correct that would be a minus one
so scout you managed to make it out to
the other side and
you see that yule is wriggling through
the hole
as best she can however she gets stuck
right in the middle all right i got this
do i still have my blade
you do still have your blade however i
am gonna need
first yule to take uh one bashing damage
as the vines begin to hit at your feet
all right all right scout what would you
like to do
um
if i pull her through it's gonna cut up
god knows what on her which is gonna
cause more damage do you think
could i like cut the make the hole wider
is that the issue can i perceive can i
perception sure do a perception check
and let's let's find out what's going on
okay before things get too crazy help
come in
okay
okay oh yeah with two successes you are
able to perceive that the issue isn't
necessarily
uh that yule isn't able to fit um
in fact you guys are like probably
roughly the same size that's not so much
the problem it's just that yule is a
little slow
um not really the most dexterous not
really the most
muscle defined uh well-toned kind of
used to
used to crawling in the mud
in the mud uh like you have done in the
past so she just needs a
a bit of a pull if possible oh
all right she should be okay i did this
with a fella back in belt buckle and i
saved him from the man-eating minds
maybe i can do that for you here you'll
could i like do the same thing anything
with the paper pickaxe and
yoink sure if you'd like to try
okay yo we can either use the pickaxe or
i'm willing to use my pants again we can
tie
it around you nice and tight and give
you a nice tug
i'm gonna go with the go with the pig
you know if i lose my pickaxe because of
this then i'm gonna leave you behind oh
does it matter which one i choose like
if i lose
like a is there like a like a material
stability thing um it would be
a different role i would say which one
will i have more chance of success with
really
well the pickaxe is real sturdy
but your pants are real sturdy too i'm
using my pants
okay it'll work anything works sounds
pants today all right go ahead and roll
for me
you're let's see let's do athletics and
either strength or dexterity
and then do a plus one for strong pants
oh yeah stitched up by mama
mama's best okay stitch
so strength is three plus one very
strong pants
yeah and then plus uh athletics as well
i have no athletics so that's oh i
don't
most of my roles have been mistakes it's
okay so let's we know now
this is three yes okay let's do it
uh okay
come on mama pants
okay with one success that's all you
need
you go ahead and throw uh you'll align
that line being your pants like a leg
a panth leg you you grab on to that bad
boy and by god scout you tug
so hard you tug as hard as you tugged
back in the day at the county fair when
you had to play the the
the tug of tug of war rope game into the
mud
you are not going to be pulled into the
mud that day this is like that ma'am
no ma'am no ma'am just like that day
you channel that energy and you bring
yule
out of the titan hole and uh thankfully
uh her ankles are very scraped up but
that's about it
and you guys seem to be
all right for now
for now
we're gonna go ahead and switch back
we're gonna go ahead and switch back to
our other friends
i hear the birds chirping beautiful
well you're certainly in a better
position than the others
you are having a nice walk indeed um
however
the maze just continues to wind around
and around and around and
it doesn't really seem to be going
anywhere specifically you guys feel like
you could walk forever and nothing
would change very much
[Music]
can i try climbing up the bushes
sure if you'd like to go ahead and roll
an athletics and dexterity roll for me
athletics oh
i'll give you a boost thanks rosa so
what's it's a boost oh yeah can we add
that
please sure first re-roll your 10 and
then
wasato um actually wait before you
re-roll it
make it a two make it a two d-10 because
you get plus one to your dice pool
because wattato is helping boost you up
how about that
oh nice
oh oh so three successes reroll that 10
again
oh and one more oh uh
okay three all right
now let's see let's see where this takes
you
ciara where does it take me
i will always
[Laughter]
sorry the laughing was chiara laughing
how does tiara laugh
please don't ask me don't do that
all right let me go ahead and try to
see you climb up through the vines
and eventually actually do
make it to the top of what seems to be
a very large hedge maze
you've made it to the top here but it
seems that even though you are at the
top of the maze
um what's beyond the maze is just a
completely
indecipherable mess of green
however a friend comes to join you
yes i knew what finally it's uh
your side and um the vibes that you're
getting from uhu is that this place is
very confusing
and uhu was lost eh
come on you know where you came from you
know how we can get out
um no would you like to go ahead and
roll an animal can
uh let's see what's an animal can roll
to get more detailed information from
your bird
one and four and wait
from burp if if it's what was it again
if
i have a specialty in it i get one more
point plus one plus one dice okay
so six okay
oh no hello garlic phone
one of those days when communication
with uh with
who is not working very well ooh who
just seems confused
that's all that you can get from your
bird unfortunately
um um
at this point you can walk along the top
and then wato can walk on the bottom
yeah can i try to stand on it and see if
walking on it
is a possibility okay sure
you stand up and it seems fine but
it's definitely difficult and you will
be moving slowly it's a lot like moving
through
a snowstorm um or really high
sand dunes where you feel like um your
walking is definitely being um
sort of uh labored i suppose can i
um i haven't done a perception check up
here yet may i do that to see
sure if you see anything uh it was uh
well 3d 10 yes
okay okay okay useless perception yes
all right let's see we got here two
successes excellent
so let's see tiara you kind of look back
and forth around you at the top of the
hedge and
it seems that um there's nothing
particularly
strange except for what you've seen
before and also what's interesting
it actually particularly strange if you
think about it is that the
the hedge seems to be changing ever so
slightly
it almost looks as though the maze is
forming new paths
all the time and the places where you
came from aren't the same anymore
you also notice uh another thing you
notice someone from far away pointing a
gun
so you have one turn i point my gun at
him adam
i say while pointing my gun at the dude
oh boy oh goodness gracious
oh goodness gracious wait i have that
sound i have like
stuff like quick draw is that useful oh
i mean you have your gun
you have your gun now yes okay we're
getting the sniper off
shoot let me shoot please i want to
shoot
well see here's the thing
the sniper was looking at you first
unfortunately
um so it looks like we're going to have
a
we're going to have a little showdown
so i'm going to do a little roll here uh
oh
is that no one's gonna die right
it depends what's your def
actually no defense does not apply see
defense does not apply here with these
here firearms
here we go
oh oh no okay
one second
wait is that oh nevermind
okay
okay um in this case kiara
um let's see you are taken by surprise
um and so with uh these two successes um
you get knocked off
you get knocked off the wall and you
fall to the ground
um interestingly enough though these
bullets
they don't seem lethal oh
it looks as though you're being hit with
uh strange
bullets that actually aren't piercing
your skin but they hurt a lot
they hurt you a lot um so i want you to
go ahead and in this case let's see what
the modifier was
i'll take three bashing damage to your
health
is is that the square box under health
uh no wait yes it is excuse me okay that
is correct one
two three okay i go ahead and put three
slashes in there
okay i have now four because i had one
from last session
all right sounds good so now you are
effectively on the ground
[Music]
i land well i would say it's a little
late
water what would you like to do in this
situation you still have a turn
i won't have you guys roll initiative
just yet
she was trying to save me all long she
was just yeah
um let's see you can go i mean if you
would like to you can certainly try
watertow
i'll just certainly try okay go ahead
and roll your athletics
and either strength or dexterity
okay well it's only one right because i
don't have one in athletics and i only
have oh yeah
oh strength yeah it's only one all right
go ahead and roll along oh
um well oh man that's a luck die um
okay tiara uh i'm dead
wazozo tries to catch you unfortunately
you fall on top of watertow
um and watsuto's nose kind of hurts
[Laughter]
it's a you painful no just giving me
another passing day
no it's not it just hurts a lot it just
hurts a lot
but what's it so i will need you to go
ahead and take two bashing damage
some crazy dude is up there he shot at
me
but it's kind of weird the the
he didn't use normal um what's it called
again
i'm not even role playing bullets what
is it called bullets
but it's
[Music]
are we gonna get out of here maybe maybe
we have to kill him to escape
i i wanted to but i uh
oh he was so fast i couldn't even shoot
at him
has a special powder treated for this
powder
maybe older lady can use powder to
to kill hmm powder
what kind of powder is it on uh power to
make you
strong very strong and fast
so should i take that and climb back up
try it
see again i see no other option so let's
do it
okay sounds good but before we do that
before we do that who is drawing on the
screen
you can draw on the screen you can draw
on the screen
okay just like i thought i would not do
it really
weird notes and stuff i don't know how
to erase it
i see i see okay all right you guys you
know what you have your fun you have
really
fun that's what i thought that was
we're switching we're switching scenes
you can all think sorry
we are switching scenes now
if you'll recall um both scout and yule
went through a hole and arrived
somewhere most interesting because you
see
yule had a very very uh perceptive look
at the wall and found a place
that actually seems very
interesting
it's latter
yes you have absorption someone's home
oh go ahead and roll perceptions a kiss
[Music]
um
holy cow three successes oh
they found bibo who was bebo
all right now
what you both are able to perceive um
scout you see that this is basically
what just appears to be a normal home
it just looks like someone's house
really it's just in a hill
um that is also surrounded by uh by a
large hedge
but it looks like someone has made their
home here um in fact it looks like there
are two
two entrances and they live inside of
this hill um
you'll what you're able to perceive is
that nobody is home here at this time
all the lights are off in the home hmm
yes interesting interestingly enough
yeah go ahead um you can also
notice that there are some nice flowers
around here
but they aren't the white flowers that
you saw before
they seem to be like fake flowers for
whatever reason
oh yes this place is full of fake
flowers
[Music]
uh our gm is smiling when she's speaking
it makes me nervous
like she's planning something
that's the real deal when she has that
like panic face and she's smiling at the
same time
that's when you know what's up
why would i have fake flowers so that
doesn't understand
like a forest hmm
should we maybe try the door and see if
it's open yeah we can jiggle
jiggly all right
uh that's not going to take any um any
any turn or anything like that you
jiggle the handle and it doesn't open
you try the other one there's another
entrance we could try and see
the windows you're going to break the
windows
no no just the windows check the windows
if there's any open you know
okay sure you look through the windows
um everything is very dark in there
can't really see very well they've
definitely left this place
and uh turned off all the lights and
extinguish all the fires
we can try the chimney call a santa
claus
oh you sure could
up to you guys um we have we have
vine right so we can make a rope out of
the vine we took we told
you
i mean we could use it like a fire pole
depending on how strong you are you
could like go up and down it
as like an escape through the chimney if
we are really that
how sturdy is the is the wood that we
got
oh it's rather sturdy however you were
able to cut through it with a knife
um albeit a really good success so i
would say it's decent
decently durable is it still you make
like
i think it's long dead
yeah there are no more screams anymore
it's just a husk
can we possibly make some sort of like
cut down to smaller pieces to make some
sort of like lock picks or anything
oh you want to make a lockpick or like
like a hinge or something we can just
maybe like try some
oh probably open the door make a tool
he used it like a like a bashing ram
like the
police used to kick down doors
but it's a little bigger than what i was
thinking but
um maybe something like that's cool
ah you want to make a crowbar you know
oh i see i see it still has the knife
right
i'm gonna carve it down a little bit i'm
good at making weapons too
yeah true well once you guys decide on
what you'd like to make let me know and
we'll roll for it
[Music]
are we gonna use up our entire tree on
this crowbar like what if this is a trap
depends on the size flowers i mean it's
just gonna be
like
[Music]
30 centimeters this is a small one
i mean maybe a little longer how big is
the tree that we got
is it just a little shorter than we are
about half a human
half a human have a human oh and we can
probably use like a third of it maybe
oh okay yeah
all right i guess we're making a what
did you say crowbar
yeah crop or some kind of wedging
yeah something that we can just kind of
maybe watch the door
and stuff with okay you know jimmy
all right you guys want to try and
forcefully open the door with this tool
you're creating
sounds good go ahead and roll for me
let's see let's do wits in the moment
let's see either wits i'll let you
choose all you choose
wits or dexterity plus crafts
and let's see with this wood that you're
using it's fairly durable so i'll give
you a plus one
huh oh i got a 37
that's a good raw
uh so crafts plus what's ortex theory
right
yes plus one okay yes
[Music]
okay we roll those tens okay
so both of you you succeed you manage to
create something that can effectively
open the door without breaking the door
it's something like a crowbar something
similar i guess and it should be fairly
easy to use
uh thankfully because of your successes
and um
however the wood is mostly used up
you've got some left
but only a bit well we'll see
yes should we
can i is there a way to like further
investigate the fake flowers
like can you is it possible to roll like
some kind of
is there a role to further investigate
things okay
sure what would you like to investigate
in particular are you trying to look for
something suspicious or
yeah just like
the fake flowers are they made are they
like handmade
or are they like did they buy them from
like hobby lobby or something
okay sure so go ahead and let's see
um i don't have any points on an
investigation though right
you would have to roll investigation if
you wanted to get really detailed
information but with a perception check
you should be able to answer the
questions that you have so let's give
that a try
okay
[Music]
okay one just one all right so with one
success
[Music]
let's see these flowers actually um
are not particularly threatening
there's no threatening aura about them
but it seems strange that they'd be here
it seems more like they were bought from
some store
um or some place like a hobby lobby but
definitely not a hobby lobby because
you don't think a place like that exists
here likely maybe
you don't know though you don't you
don't know what this place could be they
could have one
well hedge hobby lobby you don't know
but basically you've got
some fake flowers on hand that you could
basically buy from anywhere and it seems
like they have
no real purpose to harm but rather to be
decorative yeah hmm just to be
decorative
that's very odd yes why not use real
ones
or something hidden in the flowers
little laser beams
you can get or like maybe like because
brightly colored things aren't they
supposed to be
like uh deep in your in your brain
certain colors are supposed to be like
oh danger like poison
this is a boys and girls like they're
trying to be
defensive somehow maybe there's
something underneath them
you would think so but they really don't
covering up this
or are you just creating the place
okay all right i guess we can go inside
then
you girls never want to use you got it
and walkie-talkies do you
oh
where you are
i think i think i don't know we'd be a
little distracted with the newly found
place
exploring it that's true we'll never
find each other ever again
hello are you guys okay
tingly leftover we found some
tiny wood-boring
here fancy colored fake flowers
and i don't know will you will and i
have made some kind of do hickey we're
gonna go on in and
see what's going on how did you guys
unknock first
what let's perform this later
well we are currently being chased by a
crazy dude shooting at us
there they go oh
oh if both of us disappeared then i
think tally you're the one that
disappeared
i'll come back it must be me
uh don't worry i'm on my way stay there
stay there i see that
i say that now the room that i created
is gone
nice tentacles oh nice
oh oh oh everything fell apart
no no problem
i'll just make a new one yeah i'm here
i'm waiting for you
i guess it's just me and good i left
infiltrated um complete
and then there were two i
gotta move some things again
can someone play some elevator music
there's elevated music playing
this celebrator music i don't know what
time is you've been
i mean it's nice yeah it's a really
spooky elevator
i wouldn't want to get into that
elevator i don't trust it oh nina's in
here
i used to go out and then jump
there you go why are you like that why i
thought it was fun
flying
okay the elevator bounced up and down a
little bit you know
that's a spooky elevator my dude
by the way i was doing those crazy ass
because i was thinking
the white nice smelling flowers might
have just been a way to manipulate us
and even though in the beginning it
seemed like scout
and you were going the wrong direction i
feel like kind of we went into the wrong
direction
after all yeah these flowers are
definitely suspicious
i don't know how much this is about the
white flowers what if they're like
you know one of those like mine can be
like
like lure people in you know
you know there's flowers that smell like
really really sweet and they like
lure the parade and they like that
we are the prey well we just picked some
it sounds like we
got somebody soon
all right we're back we're back sorry
about that you guys we've returned
we is back speaking of which we actually
should head back to uh the other two
see what they're up to yeah
all righty so let's see what's going on
with you guys
let's see is this the song i want
that's not the song i wanted sounds nice
yeah but unfortunately it's not a happy
end for you guys
i'm just not just yet i won't i won't
say what kind of end it is but you
haven't quite gotten there yet
side questions uh how much basting
damage do i have to take to die
uh so it's not necessarily how much
bashing it's how much aggro damage
um so basically you have bashing it will
turn into lethal
if you continue to accumulate it which
is an x not a slash
and then lethal will turn into
aggravated damage which will turn into a
full colored in block what the heck
a full colored in block um and then once
you get all of those filled in you're
dead
oh not a hotel okay yes
all right um however it was interesting
that uh those bullets didn't actually
hurt you
because you feel like they should have
go ahead and roll perception again real
quick i wanted to do that
yeah yeah yeah uh before i go up there
again
can we try i don't really want to go up
there again sure
oh no i don't see
i'm still confused from the fall out of
it hurts
i hit my head
[Music]
i can't i'm like keyboard
cute oh thank god i won one more were
you wrong
oh noise
oh yes
all right let's see what we got here
okay
okay all right with two successes
with two successes uh what's so what you
notice immediately after kind of getting
up after tiara has completely
fallen on top of you and crushed you to
the ground um
the first thing that you notice as
you're kind of sitting up is that the
bullets
that hit tiara are not rubber bullets
they are real bullets and they look real
menacing
oh yeah uh-oh
like they look to be the type that
should have hurt her very much
but they didn't whoa
well wait if she's looking at them right
now
can i pick them up and use them
in my own gun um
well let's see do you have a sniper
rifle
no i have revolver
okay all right you know what you can try
if you want
no i don't want to break it
like i'm thinking problem is kiara knows
way less about guns than tiara does
and uh chiara is being controlled by
kiana so
i don't know about guns maybe
can use a sound gun yesterday
i think that's a good idea but for a
lady
it'll hurt your ears so maybe we put the
flowers in your ears so that
the green does not scramble
what about your ears anna uh what's up
have damage already damaged already
i see i'm gonna bring in a little closer
oh
okay uh okay um i will
uh um
i will hold my hands on my ears and go a
few meters away from you
and uh also woohoo my burp i'll
i'll hold it and protect it that should
work
i want to try talking to whoever's
shooting with like uh
i don't know if it's possible but okay
sure amplifying my
voice with the sound gun thingy since
like a radio okay
sure yeah
sounds good okay let's see you want to
use the sound gun and you want to propel
your voice so i would say
go ahead and make this let's see
um in particular would you like to focus
more on getting the message across or
like what you're going to say in the
message for example persuading
or intimidating etc what would you like
to do what kind of message would you
like to say
persuading wait um
intimidation yeah okay okay cool let's
do intimidation
uh plus your presence um
and go ahead and add plus two for your
gun
okay it's a pretty good modifier because
you made a good gun
oh okay one
okay with one success what do you say
wattato
hello please stop shooting one hotel
where are we we're lost please
do help wanna you wanna maybe throw
something throw some uh threatening in
there
you better stop shooting emperor lady or
else
i will use my scramble on the sound gun
and a what total gun will hurt careful
yeah yeah that's good that's good that's
real intimidating let's see what happens
okay with one success
with one success there is some silence
out in the distance
and then you receive a callback
from some kind of intercom not quite as
powerful as your sound beam
but you do hear did you hear someone say
not on your lives my dear humans i'm
having too much fun
[Music]
you should be dead by now why are you
still alive i don't understand
let's kill them
excuse me can you hear me
the flowers are uh the flowers protect
us
oh okay maybe we collect a ton of
flowers and then we can run
yeah at him then and then uh
i could give you the powder and yeah you
shouldn't kill
that's right
i i let's do that okay cover me in
flowers baby believes in you
we could do that all right sure
so you want to collect flowers
would you like to a flower power let's
go
how will you hold them are you planning
to put them in your pockets
i'm putting them under my uh jacket
under my
pants everywhere underneath oh
i see i see i'm also brain
braiding them into my hair
oh it's so cute i love that
i'm getting ready for the party
okay oh and i want to give her the
powder that i had which
i traded um for originally forgot what
it was
making a bomb i don't remember
okay i'll take it thank you i'll do my
best
what do i roll anything at all
are you going to climb the hedge yes
okay go ahead and roll your athletics
and dexterity
[Music]
so do you remember um is the powder a
healing powder or is it
a a weapon powder it was like a buff
powder like
i remember it being like whoever takes
it like it makes them really
strong or something okay uh tiara would
you like to snort the powder
excuse me would you like to snort the
powder
powder yeah there's no it's all the way
is there no other way to take it can i
just drink it
i mean do you have any liquid with you
do i no
that's interesting just eat it you could
eat like a pixie stick but
you don't know i mean i mean i i don't
know what'll happen
it's up to you you know what you know
what i will
i will i will i cannot use my
do we even have time for this can i use
my crafts and my survival skill to like
mix the flowers uh with my hands
and then make some like you will get
probably at least a little bit of juice
out of that and then make it like into a
smoothie with the powder and then drink
it and then i
have a flower inside me i'll be
absolutely overpowered
i mean you make you make it very
creative i will say
um if you want to eat the flowers and
mix the powder in with the flowers and
make some kind of
dish out of it sure it will it will take
you about two minutes or so
but i'll allow you to do that let's go
ahead and uh let's see
if he if he tries to come at us maybe um
uh and watoto can distract him
while i overpower myself all right
sounds good
go ahead and rule your craft and
dexterity to create this concoction
though you do here yeah watch the
concoction while you're creating that
though you do hear
uh these the voice continues to speak to
you over the intercom
and eventually just says hey hey what
are you doing
what are you doing nothing
nothing you hear some wrestling above
and then silence oh did he leave
i don't know you don't know yet
okay well i'm making the juice all right
with two successes
you manage to make the juice do you eat
it yeah
yes you are strong i'm strong
yes you do feel as though you've been
energized quite a bit
it has buffed you in a sense i would say
go ahead and for any
role that is athletics oriented
give yourself a plus one and for any
role that includes dexterity
give yourself a plus one okay
so now i shall climb up the hedges again
okay go ahead and roll your athletics
and dexterity
okay uh
the sixth row
[Music]
even then only two all right
be careful i'm gonna climb back up okay
believes in you thank you all right
tiara you climb all the way back up the
hedge you pull yourself up through the
branches one by one
and you feel empowered doing so you're
definitely much stronger now
you make it to the top of the hedge you
look out to where
this uh this masked fiend was this
sniper
and you see that he is in fact running
away from you
in a different direction it may seem
himself he's running away at a should
[Music]
let me let me uh while he's running away
and uh
uh showing his back to me let me uh
throw a few
shoots at him sure you can certainly
start to take aim
so i want you to do a perception check
yes oh
oh okay all right we roll that ten one
success
you hear something in the distance
wathato
oh you hear doggies
ah they'll go oh oh it's not
the good kind of torah
wait aren't you good with doggies yeah
oh thank god
hello nice doggies come yes come to our
door
all right we're gonna stop there for now
for
you guys and let's make our way back
make our way back to to the hobbit holes
yeah indeed
off we go let's see
right back here beautiful
nice
okay oh yes very serene very calm
this home we returned to as you are now
breaking and breaking and entering
okay not from the inside
hello anyone anyone home
you hear nothing can we proceed
reception oh yeah look around the house
can i roll my turn again you always
re-roll it in yes
always well you guys didn't break into
the house yet did you
i think we cranked the door open at
least
i don't remember unless we got the rule
for that
yes you must we must roll for that okay
we can roll for that
dang it curse my short-term memory i
totally thought you guys did now i'm
remembering you did not
hit it done we could if we could have
gotten her you could have gotten me if
you couldn't i
i remembered in the end it's okay we'll
save this perception rule
that's fine um so go ahead and do
let's see in order to crank open this
door i want you to roll your athletics
and strength
and you get a plus one with this
question this is it
okay never mind that was for my
perception but i didn't add anything
what did we do go ahead
yeah what is your strength plus what
plus athletics plus one for your crank
okay
oh wait wait it was supposed to be a 2d
thing sorry i'll call another one
that's okay oh goodness
i'm on ina yeah
sometimes one success is all you need
man
cool well you go ahead and you witch
that bad boy in between the door and
and the uh the door frame and you go
ahead and you
lean into it you lean into it and hear a
little cracking noise
as the wood begins to splinter just a
bit ever so slightly without completely
damaging the door
and suddenly a crack and the door is
open
and it gently swings inward
oh now about those perception checks
yes about those perception checks so
let's see what we got here scott how
many successes did you get
uh one all right it's real dark
scouts real dark in here it's real dusty
and musty
real dark dusty must you like the forge
when it hasn't has been cleaned in a
couple weeks
uh-huh yeah yeah it smells like it
hasn't been cleaned in a while however
very clearly you'll you can tell that
someone has been living here
in fact uh well
it looks like the covers were thrown off
just this morning
yep there's still unwashed dishes with
semi-fresh food
on the table
someone's living here
well i don't want to find out who i just
want to
get out of here yeah
let's let's maybe uh wake the door back
up nope
can i do a can i do a it's survival i
have foraging can i use that here to do
that in the house
maybe or is that more naturey woodsy
oh let's see what would you like to
forage for
anything useful can i do that or is that
too
is that too vague um let's see you're
looking for useful items
that's probably fine um all right go
ahead
anything you can survive give us a clue
as to where we are
what's going on or how we can get out of
this situation
okay if you're looking for information
let's go ahead and roll a perception
check again if you're looking for useful
items you can roll a survival check
which one would you like to do
oh i'll do uh survival then items okay
stuff go ahead and connect to the
survival sorry
can i get the perception to look for
sure yeah teamwork information
yeah let's do it teamwork
no okay
comes mine here baby let's go
okay
oh my god
or ransacking this place are coming home
to nothing
oh my gosh uh got in for
every fingerprint nevermind
never miss a single detail wow these are
some very girls you guys got
all right let me see here so
first we'll go ahead and start off
uh we'll go ahead and start off with
scout
yeah all right i gotta load my playlist
again
um so scout you kind of search around
this area and you see that this
um this particular home um it's not
it's not especially full of very
useful items in terms of like um
like having an abundance of food or
anything like that but you do find
rations
that's nice you find rations you find
some rope okay
very sturdy looking rope oh rope's good
yup and you find some lanterns as well
oh nice that's right yes
yeah right write this down write this
down for sure so we've got we've got
rations
we've got rope we've got two lanterns
with matches
not bad and a shovel
oh my god
okay nice you found some good stuff
okay everything
wait do i have my pants back on um
that's up to you to decide
are they still intact are they like
ripped from the knees down or something
oh they're still intact they're very
sturdy ma did her best sewing them
so um changed
the pants are back on in case anybody i
was wondering
all right so ask your mom to make more
pants
i think artists want to know
all right we've got have you been
walking actually been walking around
without pants
until like we got in the house well he
didn't say you put him back
on so i think it's likely
all right i use this time now to put on
my pants again
all right sounds good
and as for you um you will
yes as for yule
you look around this home and you
realize that this place
belongs to someone who is not human
there are strange things here a strange
feeling
um not things that you guys could find
useful for example i think that scout
pretty much picked up everything that
hunters might find useful um in any way
but there are many
strange items here that just look odd
and also books there are odd books here
as well as a journal
oh it looks like some of the books here
are about this place
research about this place can i can i
read it
sure sure thing
so you read some you read the book
entitled
the hedge over the head
just that just the hedge
yeah i get i get where you're going with
that though uh the hedge
uh this place you're assuming because on
the front cover
there's a picture of what looks to be
this place
many vines entangling around very high
walls full of greenery that seem to be
ever-changing
this place is called the hedge
and it is lived in not by humans
but it can trap many a human
and changeling alike it stands as the
border
between this world and another
another place known as arcadia
a place a place where fairies live
hey oh yes
kelly again i'm gone
my information is too powerful for you
all
just too powerful i've whisked you away
i've whisked you away here you're making
a candy in there
maybe you guys got whisked away into
arcadia
no you didn't you're still in the head
you guys are stuck here
and apparently i'll continue talking
i've made i've made a new place if you
guys want to join
i'll continue talking um
essentially there you guys go
thank you um i can probably move
so this place um it seems to be a border
in between
you're not quite in the land of fairies
yet and you're not really sure that you
want to be to be completely honest
because some of the depictions here
seem to be very alien and strange to
what you know
um in fact it gets to a point where the
text is no longer
in um in the language that you can read
nope it now slowly begins to use
lettering that you've never seen before
an indecipherable language
even but the information that you could
read
um though it was a bit difficult
you were able to read it it was written
in a human language
but it looks like there's still yet more
secrets to be found deep within
um and what's also to be noted
is the journal that you found you see
the journal also had some interesting
information as well specifically
research on flowers
and their effect on certain fairy
yeah sure apparently apparently there
are some
fairy that don't play very nicely with
flowers
specifically some darklings
oh good flowers
they seem to be a sort of um weak spot
if you will
you're not entirely sure how but it
looks like whoever was living here was
doing some serious research about that
subject
okay you're not sure how that's a
weakness but it is a weakness
i still i still have my phone with me
right i think
you do can't take a picture of
everything
oh sure if you want to store this
information yeah you have a
phone i do
[Music]
wait did you wait did you bring your
phone with you did you say you brought
your phone with you
i assume i just have my phone like
attached to my hand or something
no i took it away from kiara so i can't
i can't i can't give you that but
you can you can take it with you if
you'd like you can take this info with
you
you could write it down if you wanted i
guess i'll write it down at least
okay sounds good you know your head is
so small one second
let me fix that excuse me who doesn't
take their phone any
gm okay okay next time we'll remember
i'll say do you guys take your phones do
you take your phones go to the toilet
without my phone oh man what a shame
i don't even eat without my phone my
phone is my best friend
oh man
next time we bring everything next time
we're smarter
that's okay that's fine no problem no
problem
it's a good it's something good to learn
early on
for sure for sure for sure
all right now next time we'll also bring
flashlights
how about that yeah but we got
flashlights now cause i i scavenged some
remember before we left yeah yeah and
also lanterns
we have lanterns you guys have lanterns
kind of far away but
maybe i oh i should have said i'll give
you guys a flashlight
wait didn't one of them grab flashlight
before
because i got two right yeah
i forgot where this who was holding the
second flashlight
dang we got red stuff i gotta write
stuff i gotta make notes from here on
out
we gotta i gotta make notes from here on
out all right not
uh consider it noted consider it noted
and uh let's see you have two
flashlights so that's good
um at least we know that you have them
so once we regroup we can figure out how
to split them up
okay um now guess i'll make
make note of what we found yes
i have also written it down okay okay
now you guys uh as you're kind of
scavenging and
uh and grabbing these things around you
you hear a noise outside no
no i knew it they were gonna come back
hearing noise outside someone's coming
home
at least that's the sense that you get
and with that being said we're gonna go
ahead and switch back to the other side
who are encountering some friendly
friends
some friendly friends well maybe who
could say
i don't know it's kind of kind of up to
how you guys take things from here
you two who are still in the hedge what
will happen next
let's find out uh actually you guys
would be here
as you have now fallen back onto the
ground
welcome back hello kitty we have my
my cat is uh asking for attention
intriguingly enough however we are
encountering dogs right now
you hear feet big feet
real big feet
these are some big doggies like caribous
serbis oh yeah cyrus
kerberos taboos yeah
they had a doggy yeah you're not sure
yet but you hear you hear some
some pitter-pattering feet uh quickly
approaching
what do you choose to do wait am i on
the ground
too now even though they don't fall down
nope you're still up on the top of the
on the head okay okay oh
you want to take a shot right with my
open arms
okay watso you're on the ground with
open arms sounds good
uh tiara you wanted to take a shot
didn't you
uh you know what i'll be looking at the
situation
and if they're attacked i'll be taking a
shot at the dogs
oh okay gotcha these could be some mom
okay sounds good
would you both roll perception for me
yeah
okay with your one success
it is enough to realize that what is
coming towards you are two
very large dogs question marks no
nay i say not dogs because when you see
them
these look like other worldly beasts
that vaguely resemble dogs
[Music]
in fact they look as though they came
straight from this place
the hedge straight from the walls
themselves covered in
vines and dirt and blood and nastiness
these are some grody looking mom girls i
thought to scramble to grab climb
the hedge roll your athletics and
dexterity
my total is gonna become like holy
nevermind all right
all right technically technically
you need a 10 but oh but
we're playing we're playing my rules
baby so with the one with your one nine
you are able to get about halfway up
halfway up the hedge wall um
before the doggies kind of begin to
start snapping at your heels
nice buggy nice doggy all right
go ahead tiara and roll your firearms
and dexterity
and do you remember the weapon modifier
it was a plus two i believe yes
don't add that to your dice pool just
tell me what it is the
the one from wait weapon modifier you
don't mean the the
push the boost that i just got from the
flowers you mean something else
oh yes i mean uh on your weapon the gun
that you're holding
ah did i is that
written down it's okay i remember it's
too lethal damage so just good to know
don't add that to your dice pool just
roll
roll your roll for me sorry uh
firearms and dexterity plus one
okay with your body okay uh
that is and and the gunslinger so five
uh
five six seven eight eight
okay let's go
okay okay
three successes and then with your two
little damage okay i'm writing this down
okay so with
your shot uh you aim directly between
the eyes of one of the beasts
that is right on watertow's tail sorry
one more thing
do i get a boost from gunslinger
this is so complicated but it says at
one dot can perform
short bursts with revolvers at three
dots can make a medium weight i have
i have a gunslinger i have four dots
so it says at at uh we see at three dots
can make a medium burst with revolvers
but doesn't gain an attack bonus
i don't know what the medium versus one
second
let me pull up my merit list because i
have all of these here
i've been looking at it the whole time
to trying to get it into my brain
did you have a specialty by the way yeah
yeah gunslinger
okay let's see and i also have subduing
strikes i don't know if that does
anything but he says you can pull off
you can pull blows with a weapon to deal
bashing damage without spending
willpower
but we haven't been using willpower i
don't know gotcha i see i see one second
you said that it's a specialty right you
had it marked as a specialty
yeah okay if it's a specialty it's just
a plus one
to your role okay yeah let's see
but you also have it as a merit do you
not
uh not that
i have something strikes loaded full
bear that was also something
loaded full bear gain extra reloads
but we have unlimited anyway right yes
we were going to change that to
something else
and uh yeah
i think for right now
i'm special whenever your defense is
available you can draw a weapon that
falls under
a chosen weaponry or firearm specialty
as a reflex
reflexive action yeah i don't think
reflexive action means that you don't
need to take a turn to do it
so you do it kind of oh
yeah because all of these actions take
turns oh so
can i not take a turn for shooting the
dogs ah let's see
what is the difference though it's the
reflection let's see what was the
reflexive action you said to shoot
it was a reflexive action uh when
whenever no to draw a weapon it is
okay it is yeah just to draw it in the
first place but we haven't been that
exact about it anyway i think yeah
i think that you already you already
drew it so you have the weapon drawn
okay okay that's just shoot yes
yeah that that is eight did you add the
plus one
the same for your gun i did
i i did let me check one more time uh
dexterity two plus one
three four ohms of five
i did i did okay good i think that we'll
change the name of that later to
something like gun specialist or
something like that or like revolver
specialist or something
um okay all right sounds good so with
your three successes
you aim right in between the eyes of the
dog the first one
um and you shoot
shoot and bang boom goes the dynamite
you actually land a really clean shot
that actually manages to knock the beast
back against the wall
hits them against the thorn and they
seem to be very wounded at this point
you've still got one more doggie that's
kind of uh snapping away at the heels of
watertow
at this point but so you can make
another uh another roll to try and get
to the top of the hedge
oh can i could i instead uh
you use it to use my sound gun maybe
i'll put it on a
happy happy dog mode oh yeah sure
sounds good but interestingly enough the
reason that uh you were putting
the uh initially had it um on happy talk
boat
was because you failed the role so what
you could do in this case is still roll
and if you fail
it ends up being a good thing for you oh
okay
do i just give it a go should i roll uh
let's see
go ahead and in this situation i'll have
you roll um
let's see this is a sound gun so we'll
do firearms
plus dexterity and let's do plus one
okay for the mods that you put on it
yeah all right oh my gosh
so uh you fully draw the sound gun and
blast it off with the intention to do
harm and it does the opposite of what
you want
um which is to make the doggies happy
and at this point the dog on your heels
kind of like backs off
and doesn't seem to bother you too much
the other one that's pretty wounded
kind of doesn't like you guys already um
there's kind of no changing that
situation
um but you did manage to do it to one
one of them seems to just not really
bother with you anymore just kind of
backs off and starts like sniffing
around
oh yeah now
you're hanging on the edge of the on the
edge of the hedge and
tiara you're standing at the top of the
hedge with your revolver in hand
i shoot again at the second dog to give
waterfall more time
all right roll again
[Laughter]
ah you can do it just hang in there
but maybe we can ride the donkey
you want a ride gonna need some good
animal ken for that just a little tip
well i mean i also have animal can but
i don't i tiana does not want to do that
i think
uh i well i'll uh
just be safe i i will i will
i will i will i'll do the thing that i
said in the first time hello
all right if this is your wish
go ahead and make the same rule
ah one more one d10
no okay once it is starting to stand up
again
all right one success okay let's see
i i mean the one that was dancing around
happily oh
ah
you've aggravated this dog again but you
have also done damage
um and it has been hit and it's it's
blown back and hit against the thorns
um and it's no longer a happy dog um
now they're both beginning to stand up
again so you have another chance to
climb the head
hey they attacked vatoto i need to
protect watoto
they're dangerous poor doggy
um
oh i thought we'll drop down to go near
the doggy
oh boy what are you doing
all right you dropped down to go near
the dogs
um they are not happy
they're not happy wato um but
you approach they're both very angry
what do you choose to do in this
situation do you want to use your animal
can
uh matato has one mushroom left maybe
the doggies were like the one mushroom
okay
all right you have one mushroom
okay sounds good what do you do with
this mushroom do you put it on the
ground
do you feed it and then
draw one to each dunk yeah okay
sounds good you throw the mushrooms to
each dog it bonks them on the head they
don't really seem very happy about that
but they sniff the mushrooms
[Music]
i need you to roll i need you to roll
a 1d2 for me yeah
[Applause]
okay
no all right um so
the dogs eat the mushroom they
in fact they give it a little lick they
just give it a sniff and a lick
and after that
the dogs stand up look at you
look at tiara and they begin to walk
away
and then walk into walk into the hedge
into the bushes they bump into the
bushes and they kind of back
up they begin to walk away and then bump
into more bushes
and then back up and and walk walk away
and then they fall down and stand up
again and then walk into some more
bushes
uh and then they fall down and then they
stand up and sniff the bushes and they
fall down again
and then they stand up and then they
walk into the bushes again and then they
turn around the corner
and you hear them continue walking into
the bushes and falling down and walking
into more bushes
are they okay i think you drug the dogs
quite powerful at least there's no more
danger on a good job at all
maybe we follow the doggies maybe they
know an exit
okay i jumped down from the hedges to
join
the blood all right
sounds good and do you follow the trail
of blood from the doggies
yeah sure sounds good so as you guys do
that we're gonna go ahead and switch
back to our other crew
yeah that is just now hearing someone
has arrived home
okay uh
can we hide do we i was gonna say do you
wanna like do a preception role and see
if we can hide in anything
sure start off with a perception check
okay come on your big
perception yeah
why
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'll wait one more
oh my gosh xena still doing
two more rewills i think no i think
nah she's done it yeah she did three she
rerolled the 310s ah
oh that was a single one okay so we've
got scout with uh one success and then
ina with six successes
so scout what you would immediately
assume
from the experiences that you've seen at
least in the small
amount of media that you've seen in your
life is
go hide in the cupboard you know
essentially
yes yeah go hide in the wardrobe uh go
hide under the bed
etc either that or pull like a like a
kung fu move or a spider-man move when
you stick to the ceiling right like you
know above the door like you
push yourself uh into the corner of the
wall for as long as you can and hope
that they don't turn around and look up
right exactly like yeah or like if you
stand behind the door when it opens that
people don't expect that and then you
can like
swipe out the door right catch it on
when they're closing in and slip out but
yeah that's that's the smart thing
but what do i do i do gm
well that would be up to you these are
the options that you've been presented
with you uh to to you
you have a wardrobe under the bed or
maybe
in a cupboard um but you'll
you actually notice that there is um a
secret area
behind the bookshelf that was full of
books
it looks like there's a small room
behind there
can try cry sneaking into there
sure you don't need to sneak you have
one turn before before anything starts
to happen
so okay make my way to the small gap
is there is there enough room for two
people or just one
it looks like there is oh
kelly looks so evil right now
wait she she isn't using the crazy face
yet we're okay so far
it's it's it's it's not until nervous
oh here it is okay
is it like like like closed behind the
door so i have to open it up
you have to push the bookshelf okay
i'll try to push the bookshelf over a
little yeah
that's okay i'll give it to you because
you succeeded so tremendously
you pushed the bookshelf
let's go go maybe you can hide in here
okay all right i'll go with you then
okay okay and then close it back
up okay you're now effectively hiding
behind the bookshelf and as soon as you
finish putting that bookshelf back into
place the door
slams open oh dear god
and someone enters
what kind of footsteps first you hear
pretty rapid footsteps as though they're
looking for something or someone
that they know has entered their home or
they have more than
two feet i don't just try to kill it one
person
okay humanoid at least
attacking us
huh uh
what do we do can we hide again do you
maybe get away from the book and maybe
see what the hallway or room
is yeah the room needs another
perception
sure if if you want to but if you move
around too much you'll need to roll a
stealth roll
no same spot but just like look around
and see
all right go ahead yeah we have lanterns
maybe we can
oh that's a bad idea never mind uh never
mind
it depends on if the bookshelf is like
like see-through
oh let's just check okay
what the heck okay
okay look around the room you look
around the room and it's pretty much
empty
for the most part it seems as though
this place was made
for hiding oh in some sense these are
some
good rules yeah um
but the interesting thing that you find
um are actually a bunch of fake flowers
in here
yep there are a decent amount of fake
flowers various ones
actually varying kinds varying brands
around here as scout you also kind of
notice the same thing
it's those dang fake flowers
yeah but there's some different ones
than the ones that you saw outside it
looks like
this person has been arranging a variety
of different flowers but
it seems like they're really just for
decorative purposes
not according to the book that you'll
find should we maybe take some maybe
if if there's like a darkling or
something we can use it against it
pretend that it's the real thing right
how fake
these look do they look real at like
like first glance but then when you look
closely they're fake or it's like
obvious that it's fake from first class
let's see up close
if someone was standing right in front
of you they'd be able to tell but from
far away
might be fine okay maybe it will take
an hour there are various colors though
is the thing
multiple yeah
all right make like a little small
bouquet little small bouquet
all right i need you to roll your
stealth if you're going to be picking
flowers
around these parts death
was all right can i craft a lay
sure for easy carrying sure
if you'd like but i'll need you guys to
roll
your stealth and dexterity
oh no i will
okay
so just dexterity minus one yes ma'am
maybe i should maybe i should leave it
to inna
god i got it all right you're able to
gather some flowers
you'll i would say several maybe about
six or so okay
yes you gather about six flowers you've
got two white ones
two red ones and two uh two orange ones
okay the did yul's perception
only reveal the flowers like not the
like what
what shape is the room where are there
windows or any doors or anything
yeah there's nothing inside it's
basically just a small room with like
the tiniest light
ever and many fake flowers
in the ceiling like a in the ceiling
like a hole
or is it yeah there's a tiny little
glass bulb that seems to have some kind
of like flying uh
light insect inside ah
yeah it's very fairy-like
[Music]
maybe it's for the better that it stays
in this little bubble
all right then
[Music]
uh what do we do i don't know what to do
i don't know what to do but to hide you
hear some wrestling noises outside
right outside the bookshelf that's right
as though they're realizing someone has
been through their stuff
what do they know about the secret
passageway
well it is their home isn't it it's
their house whoa
oh wait a minute you said there was two
exits right we went in one way how do we
get to the other exit
is there like a maybe there's a uh is
there there's gotta be like another
bookshelf or something in here to get to
the other side of the house
right in this particular room
the secret room in the house there was
but um
not in this little hidey hole this place
was specifically made to hide and only
has one exit
yeah okay
now we're gonna go ahead and switch back
to the others as you are left there kind
of looking very uh
very intently for some kind of solution
here i wonder
[Music]
all right i think maybe
can we help the drugged up doggies with
both of our animal cans
to maybe get back to their senses uh
sure i mean is that what you want i
don't know that's
is that what you want i don't know oh
uh i thought maybe we could just follow
the trail okay
okay because they're so drugged up i
don't know if they're gonna lead us
anywhere at all but
okay let's let's just follow them then
yeah so you guys follow the dogs
i mean they do seem to be going
somewhere it's just taking them a while
oh it's wrong they're bumping into a lot
of thorns
along the way but they are leaving a
little trail for you guys
[Music]
and over time it seems as though um
where they're taking you um the maze is
kind of shifting
and whatnot but eventually you get to a
point where it stops shifting
oh and
the the hedge begins to just kind of sit
still
almost as though um a way is being
created to a specific place
and before you know it the doggies have
taken
to this area
finally do you think
maybe we should now that we're in a new
place maybe we should check in on them
and uh
we can radio them you want to use the
walkie-talkies
yeah but they're good
we don't know that they're currently
hiding so i don't know
i think our natural choice would be to
yeah
try to contact them
um i didn't get a response
have you let's try all right
all right
we made it we made it out of the jungle
are you guys okay where are you over
[Music]
what's happening
um you can you can do that however the
damage has already been done
oh no you immediately hear i made a new
place by the way you guys
okay okay you immediately hear
um someone has realized you are here
[Music]
you hear someone kind of gasp behind the
bookshelf
well i never you've been here the whole
time and he pushes her
i think it didn't work why
maybe one more time make another one eat
if it doesn't um what should we do maybe
someone else
fine boy cardboard okay it definitely
did that time
i i found it okay
okay okay well i hope you guys are
preparing a response
a written essay for this being for
intruding on uh on his house
is it the sniper guy because he doesn't
like the flowers right
you're not sure yet uh you guys haven't
seen him
[Music]
yeah prepare your written essay
and you guys outside um outside the home
uh hear very clearly that the batteries
have been ripped out or that something
is suddenly cut off
but not enough to know uh that they are
inside that home
fortunately the door would be kicked
wide open right and they would see that
pretty much right away oh sure of course
but if it's you guys or not
i might not be sure about that and they
might hear the voice of the person being
like what
is that what are you doing in here well
maybe a role perception
okay okay let's
i guess should we go first or
are we going let's see you guys can go
ahead and roll
some stuff oh we don't hear
oh no um first with you guys
no okay let's see
right indeed um
you guys don't hear anything inside the
home as far as you're concerned
no one's there no one's there at all
uh maybe but lady we can uh ransack the
house and
find some useful things to take
that's a that's a good idea but wait do
we see that the door is open
yes okay well i think
since since the door is wide open we
should maybe
be careful about entering the house ana
see if someone's there first maybe sneak
through the window
or something okay
is good at being sneaky also
my danger sense is telling me something
is off
oh all right let's
let's take a look through the windows
okay you look through the windows
and roll perception again
wait did you guys just roll yeah but you
just didn't hear
any shots i see that's right you're
looking through the windows sorry
my short-term memory is uh breaking up
on me today
right go ahead and look through the
windows and roll
one more time
[Laughter]
all right um let's see tiara you see
someone pushing a bookshelf
um what's up you see the sniper pushing
a bookshelf
and scout yule
the bookshelf slowly is pushed to the
side
and you see a hooded figure in a korean
robe
shrouded in darkness looking at you too
with a sniper rifle in hand a mystic
well it's it's not a close range weapon
unless he's got really good like cod
gamer skills so he's pretty much useless
he knows could hit you with it yeah
that's true good but i've got a pickaxe
i think he's going to be on his weapon
take him by surprise like as soon as he
opens
just like jump we get out get on either
side of the doorway and then he comes in
right with his big stupid face and then
we just dog pile on him on the sides and
then i'll choke him out with my pickaxe
and then we can all head for the door
uh that's great while he's still like
opening
like at the moment where i see uh
where he's pushing the shelf and i see
the two girls stuck in there
and he's still with the back towards us
can i quick draw and shoot him in his
back
you don't see the other two yet but if
you would like to shoot
you may through the glass is that what
you want to
oh but now i want do move over to the
door and uh to the open spot
okay sounds good you move over to the
door and you draw your weapon
i draw my weapon okay powerful are those
bullets so like is he gonna go through
the guy and then hit one of us
[Laughter]
all right at this point after pushing
the bookshelf to the after pushing the
bookshelf
to the side um this being kind of points
at you guys and says what are you doing
here
what do you want with me we were lost
and we didn't mean any harm
sir we're scrapbooking we needed these
flowers for
our vacation
scrapbook i know who you are
and he pulls out his weapon and gets
ready to shoot you guys
sir that's a vessel that's us i know
you're not getting ready to shoot us
with a sniper rifle
all right tiara you can take your shot
if you want now
yeah you had one job
eight dices are you nicer than i missed
[Music]
and um the bullet scrapes past yule's
face
leaves a tiny scar
well but that must have startled the
dude at least so he does turn around
very quickly and points the weapon at
you
oh my god this is what but he sees my
face and he knows
i don't give a about his bullets
not much at least
well yes there is a moment of
realization where the homie looks at you
and realizes that you have white flowers
on you
i have them all over my body yeah
and takes a step back
i have a shovel i could bunk him over
the head right now
we haven't seen both sides right now
we're having from both sides he's
incredibly outnumbered
true either that or i could give
yule the shovel or bunk
and i mean i've got other weapons as
well i've got rope we can tie this fool
up and then
question your interrogator
yes you also got a taser it tastes too
oh yeah
and i can attack him from behind with
the taser but this might be
that sure this wouldn't be a morality
because they were
in a life or death situation potentially
so it is self-defense
yeah but
we need to watch from window yeah let's
do it
i mean we can ask questions later yeah
okay they'll survive
all right what do we roll all right
you're gonna
use the taser yes i've passed
oh the taser do i use the shovel or do
you use the shovel
you can use the shovel i have my taser
all right
all righty so let's see for shovel
go ahead and roll your
weaponry plus decks not dexterity sorry
weaponry plus strength
and i'm gonna give it a minus one
because this is a shovel and not
necessarily a weapon
bam anything is a weapon if you believe
in it true facts i guess
but still go ahead and take a minus one
and then for taser n is one
minus one unless you have um a specialty
in using shovels as a weapon or
improvised weaponry
yeah i have aggressive light weapon
would it count as
shovel's pretty heavy let's go ahead and
make it a weaponry plus
strength minus one and then you'll for
your taser
we're gonna have you roll weaponry plus
let's see you know what
you don't really you need to be strong
to use a taser do you
oh you just press a button yeah aim
all right i'm gonna make a special
exception in this situation i'm gonna
let you use dexterity and weaponry
okay now go ahead
all my practices scooping all the horse
poop
kill him okay i have one success
you gotta be rolled too oh my god oh
dear
oh my god
okay okay put the
put the kibosh on that right there all
right
um let's see so you go ahead and
wind up with that shovel scout
and you sway it forward
and you bonk them on the head and um
this sends the homie flying forward
actually
face planting into the ground and then
as soon as he faceplants it to the
ground
about comedically enough about one full
second later
the taser just kind of flops on top of
him and shocks him
he doesn't move too much though because
the shovel has already knocked him out
but now he's definitely out
like a light bulb no it's all right
like a light bulb
search buckets pickpockets
all right i feel like if we were to just
leave him he i mean if i mean wow
we don't know that actually never mind
maybe i can't say that
i don't know we have a rope maybe we can
tie him up and question him get more you
can question him
yeah okay
all right or we could just leave him
can i uh steal his sniper rifle please
thank you well nice
i mean you can take it why not
i'm taking it i wanted to search his
pockets
my character has a sniper rifle anyway i
was i was missing that in my inventory
all right well so if you want to search
the pockets go ahead and roll let's see
well you don't really need subterfuge
the dude is out so i would say
let's see to look through pockets um i'd
i just say i'd give you a simple
um let's see
i have a pickpocket skill on larceny
all right go ahead and use your larceny
pickpocket and also dexterity and
he's out so i'm gonna give you a plus
two oh
it really should just be an easy find
yeah unless
oh i got something right okay
with two successes so you search um
through this poor soul's pockets um and
you find
you find um some interesting bullets
um what a sniper rifle
yes lady oh yeah you find some
interesting bullets
um you find some binoculars
oh nice
for that sharpie and you find some money
that you can't use
oh shiny though yeah shiny
what to take
but that was like a seagull
and you also find a dog whistle oh
it's those doggos yeah who have now
effectively collapsed in front of the
house
they're alive they're just yeah they
need to rest they need to heal
bloom's smithers
all right so now what do you guys choose
to do
oh here in the hedge exchange
information
about what each team did on their
little travel can we can we uh tie him
up first though i don't want him waking
up
middleweight oh that's a good idea
yeah it's not tied up yet okay let's do
it all right
so to tie an effect if not somebody
please roll uh crafts and dexterity
oh i can do it okay
he rolls coming in
yeah you've got a couple turns before he
comes to consciousness big rolls
nice
okay
but a very nice looking knot
looks good
all right sounds good so you tie
you tie up this uh this strange new
character
to a chair um this strange hooded figure
um very very well it's a very good knot
um you don't think that he'll be
escaping at least not easily unless he's
got some kind of special magic that you
don't know about
but what are the chances of that you're
not sure
so it seems that you've tied a very good
and effective knot here
and now um he's still knocked out so all
you kind of have to do is wait or you
could wake him up yourself
all right well that's how you slap
what oh
maybe we can interrogate him
[Music]
all right but before we do that let's
take a small break everyone
okay okay go get some snacks
go get a drink go to the washroom
whatever you have to do
when we return we will kind of go to the
latter part of this
session and see how it all unfolds
see okay snack time it's next time be
right back guys
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
do
me
[Music]
hi we're back we've returned we've
returned
wakey wakey are you
last we left off you guys were planning
to interrogate this hooded sniper
and also exchange information uh on what
happened
and could it sniper could we pull a
scooby-doo and reveal who he is
or they sure oh
reveal their identity okay reveal their
face
sure you pull off the hood of this
hooded being
and below the hood is
well a humanoid creature that you've
never seen before
in fact someone very
intriguing looking actually with a bit
of a
a dark gray complexion
an l yes in fact in fact well you would
think that
i think that with um with the uh the
pointy ears
for sure they're the first thing that
you notice
yes yes indeed but there is something
a little unsettling about this this
being
rather tall rather thin and something
very shadowy about their face
like they're bond like they need to eat
more or yes exactly
i see yes
i um i will
just in case um stand behind him and
hold my dagger to his neck
hmm clever mm-hmm
when does encyclopedic knowledge come in
handy
let's see people too think of something
in this situation
uh let's see encyclopedic knowledge i
would say not only because
this is a creature that you kind of
haven't dealt with before
yeah i would say in this in this
situation but could be very useful in
the future
yeah let's see
especially um in regards to like your
research and whatnot
that that you've done in the past like
your specific field
uh you'll you can pretty much recall um
all kinds of useful information related
to that uh on the spot
by rolling intelligence and wits yeah
okay yeah but just for the time being
this is an entirely mysterious person
read him some wikipedia pages
he won't like that
read him to wikipedia about might cheese
it's not cool
what what might cheese m-i-t-e
cheese it's disgusting anyway continue
that sounds horrifying
wow oh my goodness
all right so um our hooded friend here
begins to kind
of wrestle a bit comes to his senses
oh my god good morning ada
aura
oh what has happened to me
oh i hit you with me
oh my head i'm
in so much pain oh it hurts i can't see
straight i think i think you blinded me
you've blinded me why you tell us ara
stop mumbling tell us who the hell you
are adam
i tell you nothing you have intruded
upon my house
then i'll leave you here and you're
gonna starve to death no
please don't do that jimmy out of this
rope
no i still have things listen buddy
we gotta we have a party we're supposed
to be getting to and uh if you can't
give us any useful information then i
guess we will just leave you behind
ah wait wait no no no no no the bird
lady
oh please the dogs they get hungry
please
don't leave me here i tickle him with
the dagger
on his neck
please please stop that i beg of you i
don't like that
huh yeah i'm sure you don't like it i
can slit your throat right now
if you don't tell us we are and why you
were trying to did kill us
maybe maybe we should we should give
them give them a little bit of room to
breathe a little and then
we can talk can't just i will not
give him room to breathe he has been
trying to kill both me and vatoto
maybe maybe he has his reasons let's
just let's just hear him out yes here or
not
why you shoot a water i'm listening
we were just we were just passing by
when we when we stopped stumbled upon
this uh
hedge and we were wondering if you could
tell us how to get out of here
and what why you were shooting at us in
the first place
sir well you came to my junkyard
everyone knows that if they come to my
junkyard they're going to get hunted
that's just how it goes and then of
course i brought you or at least led you
to the hedge where things become more
fun
a little closer to my home i like trying
to get
into the junkyard in the first place
playground you brought your big metal
machine here didn't you
because you stole it i stole nothing
i don't even know what that thing is
well we still want to know who you are
ah okay well you've got me in a bit of a
pickle here so i suppose that i should
give up a little bit about
myself my name is bowlin bowlin sniff
most people just call me sniff
yes what's so funny sniff
nothing it's just the sound we have
another friend
we need to know
oh okay uh maybe he's not so bad you
guys maybe we can untie it huh
no no not so far
look i just have some interesting
hobbies i know that you may not
understand them you humans but you came
into my territory i was only doing what
i normally do
came into your territory and look who's
tied up
yeah i think he's not very good at this
well no i'm just trying to say that
you're
not very good at what you're doing here
so has an idea
oh maybe we can trade his freedom for
for
a
do you know the way out of here i know a
way
out of here yes i can lead you
can we treat us freedom for our way out
any truck
a truck a what
what is that a junkyard big big
vehicle ah the big monsters
um well i suppose i could i could try to
help but i don't really know a lot about
that stuff
i really only deal with the dead ones it
has been a long time since the live one
came in
well you will have to give us back our
car
and then lead us out of here otherwise
we're not going to let you
stay alive ada watoto will feed you to
the dogs
no please i don't want to be no please
they get so hungry
you know a way out of here yes or no
yes i know where i know where a gateway
is but they don't stay open long
all right do you have directions to this
gateway
let's see hold on a second
i think i do know of a permanent one
there there is a permanent one actually
i remember it clearly um we must hurry
though i don't
i don't have i don't have much glamour
left what
we well i'm supposed to guide you am i
not
okay go find it by yourselves can just
untie his feet
and then we'll keep his arms behind his
back he can lead us the way
i thought i was watching you
seems like mr sniper here needs some
time in the chicken coop to calm down a
bit
no no chickens snappy one
all right then i'll go through the day
i will show you the way who's lifting
uh who's doing the fireman carrie i i i
will
do that
you have to roll something for that to
carry him
um i thought we're gonna let him walk i
mean
i mean he can walk but
all right sure i'm not gonna untie him
all right go ahead and roll your
athletics and uh strength
[Music]
and okay
all right
okay okay uh tiara you're able to
carry him pretty easily actually i mean
dude's pretty thin
um and you're pretty strong so that's
nice
but what's interesting is that he's
really trying hard
um to like touch you in some sense
like like get like not in like a weird
way or anything like that but just like
make contact make make skin contact
stop touching me or i will kill you
otter
why isn't it working this isn't normally
how this goes
uh wait we walk tell us where we have to
go
ada fine i'll direct you
go straight forward and keep going
straight forward for a long time
okay we're doing that
you guys walk and you continue
to walk through the maze uh i don't know
why i made
myself disappear excuse me you guys
continue walking through the maze but it
seems as though
um with the directions
of this uh this new character that
you're now holding
um in your arms for some reason um
it seems that uh he completely knows the
area
very well even though it's constantly
changing
which is very strange um
he seems to have like an actually very
clear and good idea of where you're
going
and eventually you guys arrive to what
looks to be some kind of garden
of sorts oh oh pretty
cute looks like this yes
and there's what looks to be a pair of
doors
and many beautiful white flowers
these ones are real actually can i do a
perception check if those are the real
ones and the ones that i
am uh did i have all over my body
sure
[Music]
okay yes they are the same ones
okay yes and um
bowen kind of uh wrinkles his nose
and like these flowers very much then
like you very much
you got these flowers on you mm-hmm
he's not a big fan i don't like them
that's why that why i have them on me in
the first place i don't know
i mean i can if he's trying to pull some
funny business maybe better if you like
threw him on the ground and stepped on
him while we took a break if he's trying
to
put the bad touch on you because we
don't know what he's planning
yeah his weird brain well
well my dear ballin or whatever the hell
your name is
where what is this place adam
this is the hedge though i'm sure one of
you figured it out already
rustling through my things i mean the
house oh this
well it's it's a gateway not nothing not
the gate itself
inside there's a mirror
you can go this will lead us to the real
world
yes especially especially kiara and ina
who just disappeared
and went to another world already gone
we're almost there we're almost in the
real world again not all right i throw
the guy to the ground and step on him
all right roll roll your roll your brawl
and strength
brolin bro wait do i have brolin
i do not have brown well you want to do
that
you want to do that big step i mean you
can if you wanted to do damage
if you wanted to do damage okay i wasn't
trying to do damage
right you're just trying to kind of
assert your dominance
yeah yeah i see all right
oh you throw him on the ground oh and
assert dominance
why can i not do we still need him ara
um you have to keep him around
i mean you want to bring him outside
into real world donna
maybe it'll kill him oh my god
let's kill him i mean he seemed fine
though to be honest
uh when you guys first met but who knows
where that could have been actually
up to you guys why can't i make a new
place
[Music]
okay guys it's a different one hold on
okay one sec they can
i mean they can leave them behind i
guess as long as but i mean if he was
shooting at you what's to say he's not
going to come back
for more yeah exactly
yeah i think we should kill him
i don't i mean i'm serious anna
what do you think about that bowling are
you supposed to
be killed we had a deal
did we not maybe if he promises not to
chase us
okay it seems that we had a
misunderstanding in the first place
no i'm happy to leave you alone if you
leave me alone and we pretend that this
never happened
and and i'll even sweeten the deal i can
give you access
i can give you access to somewhere
somewhere special
somewhere someplace i could get
in big trouble for telling you about oh
it's a nice place it's a place where you
can get many things that might help you
on your journey
oh it's a market of sorts
only available here in this area
why would you tell us that because i
want to live
and you can't get there without me
what do you guys say oh it sounds good
not by justin he was trying some funny
business with tiara right
yeah i don't really trust him but
i think it is worth checking
that thing is worth checking out
definitely
[Music]
my total need to go shopping we still
gotta buy
our uh our outfits for the party
maybe they have some oh oh good idea
that is also true all right
oh well
i think wait we can keep him tied up
though right we don't want to make it
too easy for him to get back to his
house anna
oh my god yeah
all right
all right show us to your magic
magician's closet then bowel
all right
ah okay sniff
can you my name is it's either bowlin or
sniff
you may choose one right now
all right fine let's go
it's through here it takes you to some
doors
um
inside this place is very simply just
uh it's a big bathroom
oh with a mirror
do a hidden dimension behind the mirror
there's a big
hole that leads to the outside world
wow how did you know shut up really
all right well this is where we part
ways um
i will give you a token as promised
here and he gives you um a whistle
made of thorns i already took a whistle
from his pocket
dog whistle doggy whistle
this is a different whistle this is a
different whistle yeah he summons it out
of thin air
oh what does it do
open doors maybe if you want to go to
the special place
where you can buy many nice things you
use this
but it won't work if i am dead oh
i don't i don't even think that is true
but okay we'll give you that anna
it won't work if i'm dead you must trust
me it is the truth
give him the benefit of that
take it and use it sparingly as it can
only be used once
oh right now let's never talk about this
ever again second one
there's only one that's the deal okay
okay hold on to it all right
so we're making a contract uh
now hold on there mister i'm not sure
i'm gonna be signing no
contracts it's very simple my life for
this thing
you want water to autograph
huh what excuse me okay
can i add some something um
you we'll give you your life as long as
you don't try to take hours again anna
okay i'm fine with the terms of this
contract
okay all right
okay sign here uh
and a golden piece of paper appears it
states the terms
they're very simple there's no fine
print
sandy on the back no fine print on the
back either
okay now
um
i mean what's also did make it make a
deal with the with the worm so i mean
i can see why he'd be kind of tasty here
as well
that's fine though it's fine my
contracts are solid
he says i'm i'm not one of those one of
those other sneakier type of changelings
i just like to hunt for fun
that's all you came to my property and
i'm willing to forget it i won't forget
it ever happened
don't hurt me and i cut his ear off as i
keep saying
that's not part of the deal
all right are we all signing
are we all off the side just one just
one is fine
oh okay you get in big trouble if you
break it though
okay
i don't want to be breaking those
contracts all right
goodbye goodbye
get out of my sight wants to take some
flowers for
later research okay
you may take them out they'll have a lot
of them on me
we can change that this was your problem
it is my property but these flowers
aren't mine i want nothing to do with
them
the property of the hedges i mean
technically it's also not really my
property it is my property but it's more
the hedges property the head is allowing
me to stay just for a little while my
true home is in arcadia of course
anyway uh goodbye and i wish to never
see you again
is he untied i'm just gonna hop home i
guess
we're
anybody got a zip tie
[Music]
the way he's hopping he doesn't seems
kind of uh
well we got the contract so he can't
harm us i think
that's what i'm saying a deal is a deal
yeah
all right get his rope making my rope
back
i mean his rope that is now my rope um
all right all right yeah all right
goodbye scram
it's mine now thanks bye that wasn't a
part of the deal
hi hi we're leaving we're leaving we're
leaving hey
wait a minute none of that he begins to
storm closer to you
hey that's my
gun i need that i point my dagger
in so into his face so that the the tip
of the dagger is like almost pinching
his eyeball
you sure that you need it anna yes
it is my special gun that was not part
of the deal
the whole time and he didn't have any
problem with it until now he's already
trying to do it because you said you
don't look so you don't look so big
without that big gun
and i realized oh he's blind
isn't he blind no not quite but you did
remind him of the gun he said
you said you blind blinded him with the
shovel
only for a moment oh for a moment when
you get hit in the head with something
and you get
it was about taking lives not about
doing damage we can
do some more damage if we wanna i'm
taking
behind what that means
part way contract so water cannot time
you can sure you can it's about not not
uh taking someone's life
no the contract was we shall not harm
each other
so he can't harm us here yeah later kind
of a weird situation
[Music]
how do we get into the market or we just
go through the mirror or something
oh the mirror is uh the gateway
yeah we're going for it i won't forget
this
bye i will not forget this
all right you should have killed him
yeah
yeah right thanks scout
all right with that being said you guys
enter the mirror as he's kind of
standing there realizing that he can't
hurt you because he just made this
contract with you even though you can't
hurt him as well
a very uh a very slippery situation
indeed
you guys enter the mirror
and you come out
on the other side
oh wait a minute on the other side
wait a minute along with the cockroaches
that also spill out from the
distraction i
knew it yes i think we still have time
for the tacos
what time is it what oh
yeah what time is it party time
it's taco time it's approximately
3 a.m no time has passed oh
oh barely any time at least
well at least we made it back
what the hell would they be
that was crazy i know
i suppose we can rest up now and then
hit the road early and well it's already
early in the morning though we can get a
nap in now and then hit the road button
earlier again
and we can find our way to the party get
some some outfit wear and then be on our
way to complete arm
do we have the car now though
yeah perception sure
look through the window see if the car
is there oh yeah
who wants to look oh look nice
was it actually stolen or done
one success yeah oh there is no
think we left the van yeah i wanted to
bring it but
he didn't really seem to want to guide
us to the car
yeah it didn't seem like it
i didn't know much about it
well we might be able to take a taxi or
something
well in the morning and then that'd be
small
maybe we can we can because the card
repair people will be here anyways in
the morning afternoon right maybe we can
hit your ride with them
to town or wherever they're located
look at him with some pretty eyes
indeed but it's rather late so what
would you guys like to do do you want to
sleep do you want to
you want to get drunk what do you want
to do
i guess sleep don't be trying to find
people have some injuries right so maybe
be smart
yeah first aid and then sleep
yes first aid all right sounds good
let's see would you like to roll your
first aid
yes all right i have three in medicine
right
all right let's see you have three
medicine all right whoever wants to do
medicine checks
cool all right um let's see who do you
want to do them on is the question
oh well
tiara get hit
oh true fact yeah first maybe maybe
uh scout and tiara and i can see if i
can
put like bandages on myself okay sure
okay
so let's start with um you'll doing
yourself bandages
all right let's see by the way i'm just
assuming
that my verb came with me or didn't he
is he here now
oh yes uber has been following you okay
good good good good
good grab good girl no problem
okay now let's see we're gonna have you
do
um let's do a dexterity medicine roll
for you
yule okay what if there's a specialty in
minus what's your specialty s first
aid okay let's see
um yeah that should be fine uh add a
plus one
okay okay
okay all right let's see what we got
here
okay two successes sounds good uh with
those two successes uh let's see you
how many bashing damage do you have uh
like uh like full oh full okay
go ahead and take two bashing damage
away
yay yeah okay next up scout you are
going to uh
perform some medical check on tiara
yes all right same rule please go ahead
and do a dexterity plus medicine roll
you got it
well don't take me it just kidding you
can thank me now
thanks nice one more okay
tiara heal 2 bashing damage
my total
all right so with that being said
do you guys sleep or do you do you party
no please drink we had enough partner
gotta give you guys the option just in
case you want to
party yeah there they go
away they go it's playing with the
cockroaches
play with the couch i'll try your
corner like crouch and get some sleep
sounds good let me make this again make
this again
okay um so you guys uh kind of settle
down for the night
essentially all right um
that's it that's it
oh gosh why this is
it please
well while cali is busy let me just say
uh saturday
if anyone is in germany and going to
dokomi i'll be there too so check out my
concert and my podcast at dokomi in
germany and dusseldorf let's go
yeah do it
and the following week is me and ame at
[Music]
megacon orlando that's right
yeah we can talk about a little bit like
the how the panel will work
so uh you guys will be able to ask us
questions there
in person and uh yeah karen and i will
be each be on separate days so i'm on
the
12th i believe and kiara will be on the
13th so you can come
talk to us but there'll also be like uh
you know an emcee there talking to us
too
and yeah it's a interaction and panel
yeah
yeah yeah looking forward to that
sounds exciting i'm gonna tune in
very excited yeah i don't know if it'll
be live stream i hope so
oh yeah if possible if not though it did
yeah it might not be
but i will be there in spirit and i want
to hear all about it afterwards
yes yeah i want stories yes
great people in the crowd thanks
nice yeah i'm gonna get to do that a
couple times as well
i'm going to a calgary expo and also fan
expo with uh
gura and watson
fan expo and then let's see watson and
kusatori for a calgary expo
so very exciting stuff if you guys want
more info on that maybe
check out the whole live english twitter
i think just
today or yesterday they posted a press
release and stuff on it
as well if you guys want to see the
dates
yes yes please check it out
yeah oh
oh yeah okay do you see it ah
yay okay
good yeah
i did not see you the other side the
other
the other one cursed all the way right
up to the end
right up until the end baby
[Music]
english yeah that's how we roll and so
it's okay we're at the end i guess so
it's all
it's all over yay there you are
all right oh i'm here yes
okay good let me grab you by the ears
i'll have you by the ears and drag you
over here call i hope he's in control
he's in control i'm in control
mostly hello and controlled i'm ena
ha ha
shout out to kelly's absolutely amazing
new music video
wow yeah thank you guys thank you
so cool thank you for enjoying it i'm
really happy you guys like it
i i really i'm very happy with how it
turned out thank you
[Music]
so amazing oh hold on
there i am there we are there we are
back together back together so we can
finish up this bad boy
all right so we sleep you guys sleep and
morning comes and before you know it
you hear it uh actually outside
you hear a most intriguing sound it's
the sound of loud banjo music
playing oh
ladies and gentlemen somebody ordered a
towing we got tacos
sir i should say breakfast
they're two mama rather friendly looking
overalled individuals
um in what seems to be a tow truck of
some sorts and they're wielding tacos
in hand because of course they are
of course how do they get so hungry
yeah we were talking about scratching
howdy
oh my banjo tickling i've been hearing
fellas
yeah you you like you like our you like
this kind of music
oh we're gonna have good time
break out the spoons start up the
washboard
now we're talking you got some good
jason
all right all right here you go and um
they hand you out the tacos hand you off
to tacos
oh no it's okay no i i made it no i made
you guys go away it's okay we're fine
i had to make myself bigger um they say
alrighty uh
so where's the where's the truck we're
towing
uh about that
we were wondering if you could actually
give us a lift to
town right oh this time right yeah you
you need to listen
kind of yeah kind of broke down beyond
repairs yeah someone stole a total
man oh man you got some grand theft on
your hands
man well we'd love to help um but we're
on a bit of tight schedule
oh man there's got to be something we
can do
someone make a persuasion role or
intimidation rule however which way you
want to approach this
persuasion persuasion
of which i have none so it shall not be
me if i have one persuasion that's
that's better than nothing
all right either manipulation or
presence will work
would you like to expend some willpower
me yeah we haven't been expending
willpower recently
no you can if you won oh sure wait what
do i have to i can't roll again like
just
i can't just roll again manipulation by
itself or i have to because uh
oh you can sure you can if you want go
for it
okay
[Music]
yes all right re-roll that 10.
all right now they're gonna roll the
resist
uh-oh what do you say by the way what do
you say to them
uh well i thought i is very thankful for
the water taco but uh
we have uh somewhere we need to be and
uh watod will have some coin if you need
it
and uh maybe we make a trade of service
in coin
right oh come on
oh my all right well basically cancels
cancels itself out they say well you got
coin all right
if you got money i guess that changes
things but oh man
all right go ahead and hop in we'll give
you a ride
thank you so much we appreciate no
problem
of course take you to the next town they
should have everything you need very
convenient place
they got a whole mcdonald's there
actually whole mcdonald's
yup couple other shops nice clothes
shops i've never even heard of them
before
do they have a kfp
okay kf kf what kfp kfp do they don't
do you guys don't have it in your
country fried turkey
chocolate pig hey of peaky kids
phoenix i've never heard of that before
it's good
it's pretty good never had fried beans
before we're all messed up
it should be worldwide right now but
i'll oh i guess i'll
i'll go for some kfc instead kft
kfc what's that you got no pepsi but you
got kft what is kft that took fried
turkey
all right i'll go for that all right
sounds good maybe we can pick up some on
the way let's go
these coppers ain't gonna hold forever
[Laughter]
all right so with that being said loaded
up into the truck wielding tacos in hand
you guys
drive into the sunrise off to the next
town where
you'll be able to grab some formal wear
and thankfully it's very close to your
next target oh
you can finally begin your big mission
congratulations on your first time
escaping from the hedge
the first time yeah as
got a neat whistle though true
nice side quest open blue whistles now
everybody can use that as like an escape
if like something really bad happens
oh there's hobbies yeah
good thing you did get a neat item out
of it i will say
yeah you guys got some good stuff yup
by the way you guys get a letter pack
sent to you it arrives at the motel
before you guys leave it's full of your
cell phones
[Music]
that's right that's right
all right so with that being said we
have finished the second session
yay
you guys did it you did it and we will
be awarding exp
on our own time as well and we will tell
you guys all about the brand new stats
before the next mission
yeah let's look forward to that please
anticipate
and decide i am anticipating
yeah i think the next one it'll be on
someone else's channel that isn't me or
kusatori
so yeah please anticipate
and uh we'll have ourselves a fun time
in the next session when you guys are
going to tackle your
your first big mark oh
[Music]
no problem guys i was really worried
about this one because i literally i
just got off a plane
i just got off and i was worried i was
not going to be high energy so i tried
my best
was totally fine i didn't notice a
difference at
all yay well you guys were also really
fantastic players as well and uh
very much making decisions on your own
and leading uh the story so that was
really great
yeah you guys are naturals naturals i
tell you
yeah because they have you here to guide
us oh man exactly you guys are making me
plush ah geez
thank you i can't wait to keep playing
we have so much more fun stuff
planned in the future it's going to be
great looking hopefully
yeah i'm looking forward to it heck yeah
thanks everyone for watching
thank you so much guys what should we
sign off on
i wonder hmm
well last time we said automotive right
yeah it's a myth
absolutely
okay yeah let's do it okay ready
three two one
uh
goodbye everyone see you next time
[Music]
you