[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
ah
[Music]
key
hello guys
i missed you
did you guys miss me
[Music]
yes
yeah
it's been a while
it feels like it's been a while i mean
it hasn't really been
much of a while but it feels like it's
been a while
yeah
and
yeah nice book and cook thank you wait
wait a second are you okay
okay
ah uh it's because my stream on monday
was so short and then today is
not really late but you know and
yesterday
was nothing
and yeah
now it feels like it's been such a while
yeah
[Laughter]
oh yeah yeah
well
hello everybody did you hear the
keyboard i think you did
listen
uh uh
i need to get used to typing with this
because it feels very unusual what
should we type
i missed
you guys
it sounds really good
but i don't know where some of the keys
are so i have to look at it and like
search for them i was like
where is where is delete and where is
enter and where is the
windows key windows key is called super
key here
i love my cats
isn't that beautiful
[Music]
tick tock
um
[Laughter]
i understand but no
i agree but i also
don't understand was that it
really
yeah i was really surprised because um
the keyboard
cable
i've never seen something like this
before it's connected with uh
there's two cables that you connect with
one another and they look like
so like as like some kind of sound
equipment
it's like some kind of metal screw
kind of thing that you connect with one
another but then the actual cable
is so
beautiful high quality too
like i look at it and
wow
it's like
the cable is like surrounded by like
wrapped around some kind of fabric
uh
a blue fabric and it's like oh it feels
very sturdy and high quality
yeah yeah
okay
sorry i'm moving the microphone back to
where it belongs
okay we're gonna play more cult of the
lamp today
also smoothie is with us right now she
has yet to leave the scene apparently
she doesn't mind
we've cuddled before the stream but i
guess she
she wants to cuddle more she's so sweet
now she doesn't want to go she doesn't
want me to go she doesn't want to be
away from me understandable right we we
we can forgive her
yeah
clickety clackety
it's probably a u what a usb cable fixed
to a
gx16 connector i don't know what that is
but
in theory it's a usb cable yeah but it's
like
yeah two parts
for whatever reason do like high quality
keyboards need
that kind of cable interesting it's like
i guess like with audio like cheap ass
microphones you can get like usb ones
but if you want to go you know more high
quality and all that usually
it's not usb anymore and you need like a
like um something in between yeah yeah
yeah yeah
no it just looks nice oh
oh
it's fashion
it doesn't snap when you accidentally
pull it
oh
oh indeed because yeah i screwed
something in there
oh
i see okay so it's not actually
necessary
[Music]
why does why does the game not show up
on obs you
come on
come on obvious
you can do it
there you go just takes sometimes i need
to tap into the game and then wait a
little bit until obs finally recognizes
it
i
played off screen a little bit because i
was bored and i felt like playing a
little bit
i didn't do a boss but i did um
[Music]
i i did like four days or so
we had some deaths we had some new peeps
i think we're basically still around the
same amount of followers
uh do you hear this
no you don't
see that's the problem
ah ever since popcorn
which we're also going to talk about a
little bit ever since popcorn
something is wrong
because i changed settings so that you
know
i could sing uh
and they hear my my music and all that
[\h__\h] hell why is it like this now
ausgabe give it output
yeah yeah yeah that's fine i would say
now that
is this but that doesn't matter
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] um
this one
cult of the lamp output
system question mark let me see if that
works
it doesn't
why not
okay then we'll just do it like last
time
i'll just put uh this
i'll just route this together
like the professional i am yeah now
there's like slight music right
okay
tell me if something is too loud or too
quiet not that i really would
immediately know how to fix it
so basically what i did off screen is i
added this i i first of all i had to
unlock it and then i added this i added
this too
we needed another grape someone yeah who
the [\h__\h] are you died but eventually
we're just gonna revive him
um
besides that
uh
wait who are you
surprised we have some
triggers this one's new because he
[\h__\h] triggered me that's his name now
um
let me explain
[Music]
i
i got a side quest
from a member
uh that told me to find his friend in
one of the in the more recent
thingy uh anura
is what it was called
anura
what do we do while i tell you the
stories maybe i could go fishing which
by the way wait okay let me first really
that since we're going there i went to
the fishing place
uh
i did one attempt and i immediately got
the lobster
chat is too high okay
i immediately got the lobster
unbelievable
off-screen first try lobster so i
finished that quest as well
uh
yeah
i i i went to some normal fishing here
too sold him some fish
okay let's yeah while while it's night
time here
uh let me tell you let me try to tell
you what i've been up to there you go
uh so i got the side quest
whoosha
keep fishing for better food okay mr
maybe i can unlock different fish come
on come on come on
come on big fish
yay ooh
what was i saying i got the cyclist
and it said go to anurah i think that's
the place the second the second level
the second door basically
ah
goddammit
and then i didn't realize
i thought that you know the friend will
just be like at the end or so or or no
matter which path i take they you i will
find them
um
but that
wasn't the case but i didn't realize the
first time the first time i go in there
and i
went
like a different path than the one that
tells you you get a follower
because i thought that's just you know a
random follower not the quest follower
so i went a different path and then
after looking at the path later on i
realized like i was still i was not at
the top yet i was just halfway through
but i realized oh
this is not it is it that one because
there's like a little exclamation mark
um
this little exclamation mark
next to the followers sign and that's
usually not there i guess
and i was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] time wasted
and then
then i
uh
i left i think
i just left and then i did it again but
i think that time i died cause like
suddenly the game throws this new weapon
at me and
three times in a row that's the only
weapon i [\h__\h] get at the beginning
it's this axe do you guys know the x
where you have to
load it up with x
uh
and it takes so much time
and in that time the enemies either hit
you or walk away
was it a hammer and i think it was more
of an axe
yeah well maybe i guess maybe it's a
hammer
but it pissed me off so much and it was
so difficult for me and you have to
consider it was also oopsy it was also
uh the enemies were more difficult this
time because it was the second or like
after the first time i cleared it that i
entered
ah come
on come on you little [\h__\h]
ah
crap
uh so i had quite some trouble with that
why do i do that
and then i died and then i raised then i
sacrificed someone but then i died again
pretty immediately
so
turns out you can't sacrifice two times
in one dungeon
so i still didn't get the quest member
and time was taking and i was getting
really triggered at that point
uh
so finally at some point the third
attempt i think it was the third attempt
i finally found the follower
and i went back and i called him
triggered because he triggered the [\h__\h]
out of me
yeah
i also did read it um just before that
just before that i redid um the other
one the which one was the other one
called
uh not the first
one the first area
just just for the sake of i don't know i
just wanted to fight
that's it
yeah then i don't know i did some like
i don't know stuff um i got i got a few
oh they became friends oh cute
i got a few new things maybe you see it
on the right side i can now perform
brainwashing rituals
uh that's a sermon
what the [\h__\h] uh 70 oh there you go why
did the audio go away for a moment
[Music]
ah
oh that wasn't even that necessary oh
they love me so much
so let me show you um
i also added the wedding i i wedded uh
i think patty
we have brainwashing tutorial that's new
um
i think those are the two new ones
uh i got a [\h__\h] done i farmed this [\h__\h]
ton of mushrooms that's why we have that
now
hey game are you gone
oh
i wanna
why
i pressed one button and suddenly it's
broken
oh [\h__\h] hell
there now now it's back
yeah yeah
um what was i saying
what's that thing
i pressed it again but it didn't work so
weird
ah
i added ah inspire is new
because i did level two of work and
worship
i also did level two of law and order
that's where wedding came from
and now this i kind of regret doing
because of kfp theme
but i wasn't thinking i guess i was i
was
i was not thinking in my streamer mind
i know that the cannibalism trait would
have
made more sense kfp wise but in that
moment i was just thinking
like how do i make my cult a little bit
less freaky
and i had so much grass you know i
thought
i i would always have more grass than i
would have follower meat
so i would get more out of this one
to be honest and then i made a [\h__\h] ton
of grass meats because
grass meals because i had nothing else
so it made sense
it just made sense i had so much grass
and i no matter how many berries i was
farming i never had enough berries
so that's that and then i added
wait i think yeah oh i can add another
one oh man oh yeah that was that you you
know i added uh law and order and we're
gonna worship
no
which one should we do next
the only one that's still on one is
possessions
should we do possessions i wonder what i
wish there was a preview of what i can
choose from if i go there
you guys can eat a grass sometimes you
don't always have to
[Music]
uh possessions can be good
let's see what they have
later grass is rarer than barry okay
that's fine you know for now it's good
believe in false idols trait
all cult members will gain the false
idol straight
but
gain more faith when placing a
decoration building
but
all club members will get a metro
realistic trade game when building sleep
ah
oh
now who do i see so if i build more
decorations
ah that's what they mean just build any
decorations they see it as a false idol
or ah
i feel like we'll definitely
upgrade the sleeping quarters but at
least for decorations i can build them
endlessly
i can i can plaster the whole place with
decorations while
the sleeping quarters
i'm not gonna make endless amounts of
that right
um
oh yeah it doesn't say which one it is
i guess i think i'll actually go for
this one do they mean any decoration
like even even some flowers
nah
they're not very clear here
i can't believe they mean just any kind
of flowers
or anything really okay well in that
case i believe you
what
we can test it out we'll build one new
flower field or whatever
and we'll see what their reaction is
okay thanks guys oh
free enlightened ones let me talk to
them first you
oh
uh wait weren't you all also
oh we have a sad quest again
again patty patty gives me so many
quests
she also forced me to make someone uh
eat poop again
eh
oh yeah
fluff frog yeah she make me
she made me have fluff frog eat with
she made me make fluff frog eat poop
there you go
she's just she's still talking about it
that was hilarious let's do it again i
know flapper will find the funny side of
it no not again
but again
he's gonna get sick again
[Music]
look that's bullying
i almost want to decline it
that's bullying it's the second time
is it gonna get worse and worse i wonder
if i keep on accepting her stupid
requests
i don't know 35 faith how much is that
decline
she has a lot of faith in me anyway okay
and in here can i talk to you
thank you
wait did we just
we didn't finish one did we
did i fill it up
i need more berries scene see i really
i've got nothing
see i can make a [\h__\h] ton of grass meals
though for now actually i do have some
berries but you know what i still make
some grass meals
gotta use it up
okay
okay okay
food time baby
salad i love salad
i don't mind a good salad
wow look at them
it spams that message that notification
about the grass eater trade which i find
a little bit unnecessary but okay
oh see they don't mind it at all i think
it's perfect i think it's
i think it's actually genius to use that
one
more effective than the
cannibalism one okay let's try this
thing with the decoration because i got
a couple new ones too
like um because i went to dark wood
again i got like two new ones here
um
that one's new too i think maybe i don't
know
let's make
lamb flax statue statue of the mighty
lamp here assert dominance that one
looks good actually where should i put
it we don't really have anything around
here
let's put it here
yeah
let's see when we finish that if there's
a notification about
more faith
make a lot of offer yeah that's why i
made a second one should i make even
more
maybe i should
ah
both idle straight seven fave up i guess
oh and a little bit of extra faith for
helping out
oh
i think that was a good choice
so it motivates me to make this place
pretty because originally i didn't see
any like i didn't have any motivation to
make this place look nice you know
now i do so i think that's a good trait
yeah
um shall we go to fight because they're
all taken care of
oh wait i should also do a brain one nah
i can do that another time
i guess that's fine
because a new door has opened
uh
what is it that one what it doesn't look
open who the [\h__\h]
you must need something i do need some
seeds
a coconut is always good for business so
many hungry followers are calling toys
and to sit up here and if you need of
crops you know i am you don't mind do
you but what do you want for it
two coins
it also has pumpkin seeds though
for frequents i'll have so much money
though i don't know if that's really
worth it when i still have enough grass
if i'm like in dire need perhaps wait
did the door close again because now i
only have nine
and now i only have eight followers oh i
need a new one should i buy that one
over there
it's a cute cat
footage
maybe i buy one
i guess i'll buy one how much was it 50
now i can just walk into one of those
recruit one and then teleport out
i'll do that i'll go into this one
please don't give me the hammer
hammer one month
okay an axe is fine the hammer is [\h__\h]
like
i i i died so many times because of that
[\h__\h] hammer and then i try a
different weapon like the dagger or
anything else
and no problem at all
i [\h__\h] hate the hammer
so much suffering so many sacrifices
off-screen because of the [\h__\h] hammer
ow okay
we're still warming up
what was that was that what was that
attack again
okay i don't necessarily like this one
either i prefer like fast attacks
oh sh but this is fine i'm just still
being a little bit careful
it's the gauntlet that doesn't drive
with me really i love the gauntlet what
do you what do you not like about the
gauntlet i think it's so easy to fight
with poor tor is crying
i've never seen that movie should we
watch it
ow [\h__\h] you
nah
is it good
i prefer the sword the sword you mean
the dagger i don't remember an actual
sword ah i did some ah can i see that
here no i guess not
i did some
what do you call those
uh curt
i got some new curses
from
uh was it a dog trains i'm not
[Music]
fire sure
neat okay now smoothie has left the chat
she's sick of me screaming
understandable bye-bye i love you though
i love you
oh she's still in the room
i just left the table
[Music]
same language right
oh i got this one this is new too
i thought my i i bought it i bought it
in one of the like different um
areas
oh ganondorf's style really really
oh
um
i think i'll do this
blazing trail
oh
i love it that's like like chihuahua in
in hollow cure
oh
genius
a little damage but i like it
also the hitbox is pretty big so you
don't have to be exactly
inside of them
oh [\h__\h] i'm like oh oh there must be
some hearts in here
recently i've been finding a lot of
hearts in the map but of course not now
when i actually need it
um excuse me
all right then i guess
that's a nice curse it follows the
ah there you go
it follows the enemy
what [\h__\h] hell
uh
i missed talking to you guys i actually
kind of
considered streaming
monday evening and tuesday
i was like considering it because i was
kind of
bored but but then i was like
i shouldn't because
i kind of
i kind of probably oh
cat hair
need it need a break
i guess
so
i like like like
turning my
stupid brain off
does it stack when i have a weapon
and the cards that both do poison damage
i wonder if it stacks
you understand thank you but
um
i mean
there you go there's a follower
what is that though
what is that
i don't remember that
that's also a shortcut
ah this map
this one
was so hard with the hammer i did that
that's where i got the
oh
that's where i got the the side quest
follower
oh
oh i was struggling so much here i i
think i died two times actually yeah
yeah yeah once i figured out oh the
follower is here
i died once i had to do it again because
i died twice actually you know
but without a hammer everything's cool
here everything's easy cheesy queen
please eat
lemon squeezy
okay
ow
how dare you
nice male hitchhikes easier
ah
okay where was i yeah i was considering
streaming because i kind of like
i don't know it was it was a very very
very rare
occasion
where
i had a day off and actually
didn't really do
anything work related
no not anything in particular i maybe
answered some some messages but
that's about it so that happens
once
once uh in two months or so
yeah
well not only nothing work related but i
also didn't really have to do anything
in real life like going to the doctor or
any appointment or whatever
yeah is that a fennec fox is that a
porka
a challenge man
last time i failed his challenge because
i had the stupid [\h__\h] hammer
if you hmm complete the next combat
rooms without thought it is not
happening
this is not happening
no [\h__\h] way like dodging is like in
my
it's so set in into my
routine
sorry we're immediately failing that i'm
not even gonna try
[Laughter]
it's like it's i can't
unless i i put like some
someone there with some spikes on that
button so i can't use it
too bad this one doesn't count
i am
[Music]
challenge fail rta i mean yeah no i
don't even i don't even wanna it gets me
out of my groove
when everything can be so easy you know
look at all those hearts let's go
hmm
nice
so what i did the yesterday instead
was um i fixed the
on the night from monday to tuesday
oopsie monday to tuesday i kind of fixed
my
sleep
schedule like you know back to somewhat
normal
as
as compared to how it was thanks to
popcorn
then i woke up early and i saw ammo
still needed some help
for the she was still looking for some
help for the car thingy like she wanted
to gather cars and needed someone
and i was like oh man you still need
help
you didn't get it done i can help you i
got a berlin
abbe was up i swear the whole [\h__\h]
day yesterday i was like are you good
are you okay
when are you gonna sleep
um i was a bit worried about her but she
said she's
she's fun i was like okay as long as
you're having fun
our leader is so kind yes yes
yes
i
hate these flying books
[Music]
looks like some kind of abdomination
yeah the bats suck
um
oh yeah so i had some breakfast and then
i
uh
locked into rest and
um me and amma went to get some cars and
repair some cars and we brought them to
we brought them to
um her place that she built
which was huge
that place was huge
hey where's that place again
ah that's the last bus right is it
that's
half to the last bus i think
i'll take this one
how many people does your intent invite
oh she was gonna invite like she was
gonna have four drivers but like
i was surprised it didn't really like
happen last night when i was sleeping
you know i was ready to wake up and be
like uh let's see what i missed
i probably missed so much didn't i
oh my god oh what the [\h__\h] is that
oh oh ah this is the one that leaves you
alone to do you know to deal with the
smallpox
okay
but apparently the derby didn't really
happen at all at all
um kind of unlucky uh that's you know
all the japan members were too busy to
um
to participate
in
that derby this time back
there's a big one a big bad
yeah going well though going well
oh yeah
ow
what are you gonna send out now
so i suggested to ahmed
that maybe she does it tomorrow because
the the wife isn't until the second i
think if i understood the info correctly
so today is the 31st
tomorrow is when i guess
if people are up for it people gonna
you know
mess around with each other
out should have gone out of the way
yeah
oh wait to get another follower that's
right
[Music]
tomorrow
all right i told her maybe if you do it
like tomorrow
should be
able to have
have it happen
um
yeah
and if it's around the time where i'm
uh
scheduled to play rest
i'm gonna go with this one
[Music]
pumpkin soup
nice
i have the witness
oh
what was that again
ah i can make food out of that maybe
if she if she schedules it this time
around the time where i'm i i play russ
because i saw bales and and kelly are
planning to play during that time too
[Music]
and then also i think japan members
would be available too or a little bit
earlier or a little bit later whatever
probably better to do it earlier than
later otherwise maybe someone destroys
that derby
yeah and then i could maybe participate
too because i actually i wouldn't mind
you know driving one of those cars that
i fixed up
yeah
but yeah i don't know what her exact
plans are now but it would be a waste if
we didn't use it properly there's so
many old people here fluff frog i
protected you from the poop for a prize
let's can i do a sacrifice do i have
enough for a sacrifice
um
enough bones
yeah yeah
yeah ah i got the thing that makes
rituals cheaper that's why it's so cheap
now
okay let's ascend
it's so cheap holy [\h__\h] it was so
expensive before
sermon first uh
that's fine
we will do
oh
[Music]
frog
so
fluffberg is now protected from the poop
no more poop for you
you're free
patty will no longer bully
[Music]
and let me do a sermon
yay
70 70 70 bang
i'm not gonna use my echo now because
apparently it [\h__\h] up something with my
settings
[Music]
can i do something yeah of course once
again
damn it it's going so fast right now
ah now we have everything on two out of
four
dosio
no
[Music]
which one should i do
which one should i do dona
earthly goods after life they're going
to die soon what do you mean they're
going to die soon
like as if they're gonna as if more than
usual i'm gonna die soon what do you
mean
i kind of opened the new door but then i
realized it didn't have enough people so
but don't worry i have enough people now
i may have sacrificed one but i got two
from the
from the thingy
i'm gonna get old
session three gives an o p oh really ah
okay ritual
almost for the poor rachel ritual
perform original and your temple in
which you distribute coins to all
followers to increase the all the other
yeah this one is this one
it's the other way around the opposite
perform ritual at your temple in which
all followers need money to you
hell yeah baby
please give
the other one
gives you somewhat loyalty too but
yeah
we want the money we don't want to lose
money that would be stupid
okay
but wait faith goes down for that one
what the [\h__\h]
quite a lot but okay
um
well while we're at it
we'll do this one
[Music]
dad
one two three let's go thank you
by the way thank you guys for the props
i'm using like
three different props
uh there's even more that i'll
uh use also next time so thank you
for making them they look wonderful
it looks so good
ah nani
garfield
what's up
garfield has been working 24 7 because
of the moon necklace while everyone's
sleeping he's always working
excuse me linda some creatures are here
sticking shout out without help but
they're sick should we let them join oh
more people yeah actually right now i do
need people so but too
oh they're okay then wait a second i'm
gonna
i'm gonna um
build some more shelters and we're
growing
and right now it's okay i do want us to
grill
uh
i don't know is that enough for now
oh [\h__\h] what am i lacking money
oh [\h__\h] okay what anyway uh wait wait
wait then
money please
extort thank you at least a little bit
you know
so you
will call you parka
did you hear that
yeah and
i almost want to keep you in that form
but no you have to be pigs
[Music]
you'll be blonde like polka oh maybe
some fluffy hair like polka there you go
what do you have materialistic
sloth
sickly oh dear okay welcome
we could have done like every cult
member named after
ah
named after a whole life member and then
choose the fitting animal for them
ah
what do i name you
you look like la prasu
at least right now it's going to change
now but
[Music]
you can be a purple pig then
accept welcome to the vlog
yeah you get this free t-shirt by
joining
for now you can just worship or sleep
whatever
another one
you're cute of the sick ones okay so
sickle one
[\h__\h] four new members yo
and since you're
supposed to be sick i'll make you green
at least for now you're sick
bye bye
bye bye sicko
uh oh dear here i'll tell you to bed
rest
and i don't know if we now really have
enough beds but
let's see
you are
sick or two
i hope to get well soon um i hope you
don't spread the the rona to everybody
else please don't
but you're also gonna be in green
what's that about poop you like poop
oh no get get faith when following you
oh well you're ill right now so
be faithful
very creative thank you
i do i sense some kind of sarcasm there
also since you're new give me money
thank you
[Music]
i got this one i got missionary by the
way
and i got
uh cheaper rituals there you go and i
got something else
oh
i think that's about it
the spirit of a demon so that they can
ah what
that's crazy
should i do that
it's great
you don't die it's safe
it's really good oh
cool oh i can summon too oh
what
freeze
oh it goes up to free holy [\h__\h]
oh my gosh
scared
okay i didn't wait why was i not able to
build there you go
there you go
wait let me help
one of the sickles is just lying on the
ground
oh yeah i built that fast come on come
on
faster faster faster
he needs a bed
oh i saw
i think you're blind this game is good
hell yeah it's good
okay now he can go into the bed
there you ah you're gonna go inside
right yeah
go sleep good
lying down on the floor late night
exactly
oh look at the berries okay i have to
take them
i really want someone else to harvest
these so we gotta work on that
ah let's make
wait didn't i get
ah
do i get the seeds after eating the
pumpkins that i got
from my crusade
your favorite knife
i i got the reference well lying down on
the floor like that yeah yeah oh you
mean a different one
of course i got it
it's my song
no no of course there's always someone
farming
always someone farming
even if i sacrifice the farmer someone
else will work on it if there's work to
do
that's sparks i know
i know
favorite knight was another reference i
know
i'm not
i know my songs guys who do you think i
am
don't be so cheeky
cheeky chickens
oh my god think faster guys think faster
keep up with me i'm just mentioning
several things at once
can you sing for us your fifth original
i wish i could
it's it's um
there have been some delays like
uh several delays but it should really
come out soon
um
i
however now the problem is even if it
was ready to be released
like
by the end of the week or by the end of
next week or so i don't want it to
overlap too much with the actual like
and second year anniversary you know
gotta be like business ladies smart
thinking
so
i have to think about the timing but
you know
yeah you will see i don't want to say
exactly when i'm planning to release it
now but
i'm in love but bro cooly junior doesn't
know i exist well that feels familiar
doesn't it would you gather ten flowers
for me from dark woods that i might woo
them does it have to be from dark wood
we have camellias here
we have chameleons at home [\h__\h]
oh my god really
oh man look sir you for real
okay we're just gonna gather some
flowers and then leave but 10
10 is quite a bit i
god think it why why
i have better things to do
but let's make it fast i hope it can be
fast
[Music]
oh no don't look at him don't look at
him don't look at him don't throw up
don't don't throw up
goddammit and now they see that someone
threw up so they're gonna throw up again
don't stop throwing up
stop it
you're good now
surprise i'm gonna i'm gonna revive you
eventually
[Music]
but he was old he was indeed old
don't worry i'll take care of it
if the sickness spread
no it was just old don't be sad
okay can i go now guys
you guys good without me
don't cry about him he won't come back
he'll come back even stronger than
before
uh
wood
got them in
[\h__\h] dark wood okay flowers
not the hammer
you will now see
oh already two flowers you will now see
how [\h__\h] terrible i am with the
hammer
okay that was that was a good hit though
that was good
but see you give them an opening to
attack you you have to wait so long
that was actually way better than i
played off-screen but
you know
lucky any chameleons here no
whatever
give me the chameleons
they don't
randomly spawn out of the grass today it
has to be the
camellia flowers
uh
right
oh two hearts wait i don't even
need them right now but hey there's
chameleon flowers wait there's no
enemies here six seven wait i'll come
back here after having a little fight
no not not the worst enemies in
combination
oh [\h__\h] i don't even know what that was
oh there you go oh hey what's so bad oh
wait that's that's the poison
okay
moving on i guess
what the [\h__\h] is that enemy
already
also i already went
through this
i
this more difficult dark wood before but
i didn't see that enemy that's
interesting
[Music]
ah
see so often because they're coming at
me i have to like um cancel my attack
like i wish it would still do it but
apparently
sometimes it just cancels it
come here oh [\h__\h] help
ah
you see that [\h__\h]
i seen this can't be
oh there we go
free me from my suffering please
oh my god
garfield has reached an old age okay
please don't die while i'm gone
uh oh
oh your necklace whole harvest bonus
races
nice okay okay okay
yeah more necklaces please
um
i think i'll go for the food
yeah
are these chameleon flowers
we can leave
after getting those in theory if you
wanna
hmm
wait don't we still only have eight out
of ten never mind
only got two here
okay
that's all i needed what is this
[Music]
ah it is a card shop okay well not a
shop but you know
i was wondering just it didn't know that
it was a map piece like that
okay i'll take the
chest hit the enemies and try to not get
what
nuts not helpful
oh i'll see you at the great buffet in
the sky
that's a nice way to think about it
but there's a all-you-can-eat buffet up
there
i'll go this way
get some resources out of this oh what
is this what's
this oh just more wood
a lot of wood
and some grass where are the flowers out
where are the [\h__\h] flowers
it
there better be two more flowers in here
give me the flowers i need the flowers
uh can i switch out the [\h__\h] hammer
now or what
nice aim though i'm getting better with
that weapon
that was pretty powerful though
i think
ah [\h__\h] you
just throw that at him
mommy
and
master of the art strike heart strike
fast structure
overall damage 1.2 plus
nice
[Music]
most people agree hammer is the worst
weapon
it's so difficult to use i'm glad i'm
not the only one then
[Music]
oh yeah
cause especially with like enemies like
those they're so fast they can just
swoosh through you and every time when
you're too close to them they just see
if they just walk away but oh nice hit
nice
i would like some flowers please
just two more please
i thought that sony guy
uh oh yeah
if i have to keep this [\h__\h] hammer then
at least take the rolling damage
that is very helpful
still no flowers oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
oh there's a screw
who's scrambling here
ah now we get what it's another [\h__\h]
hammer
i'm cursed guys
i am cursed
it's forcing me to use the [\h__\h]
hammer so why there's a dagger oh wait
let me see
[Music]
so much better
it's not even the speed it's the fact
that you have to charge it because like
the the
the axe is relatively slow too but it's
fine what you're telling me i'm getting
going out of here with my flower without
my flowers
oh [\h__\h] you
[Music]
this enemy is easy
easy oh what's gonna happen oh yeah
enemies okay
am i a pro gamer yet
i think so
oh
[Music]
ah
let me kill you first
[Music]
they got me again
now it's
dangerous how dare you
oh i wish i had like poison damage what
the [\h__\h]
don't i have like vampire uh weapon
right now
oh no
oh no just keep on rolling just keep on
rolling just keep on running just keep
on rolling this game
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
so much for being gamer but this is
pretty tough man
there's so much going on
[Music]
okay
come
on duh
ah where are you going
oh small [\h__\h]
okay
okay he's gone only the big one now
oh
i did it
nice
what is this small gift
i don't think nah uh you know what i'll
take the kid
quiet small gift
and lots of money but where the [\h__\h] are
my flowers
i have to go in here again
man
okay we're turning once just need two
more flowers
thanks guys at least i didn't die
ah
who needs hp when you just don't get hit
exactly
the pressure is real though
okay how's it going here
we need more than maximum
um
thingies here
more please
i want more here then we can get to the
next level what should we do a healing
bay maybe because i get a lot of sick
people
or
[Music]
why don't you want that
um
thank you
for the pink super chat i'll be reading
super chats later
healing canada is good no need to clean
um
i didn't see that much stuff around but
the only problem is like when i'm when
someone dies while i'm gone
then
they threw up and more people throw up
and more people throw up and i'm not
there to clean it up and then i get sick
from seeing that bleeble blue
he won't clean up a dead body though i
guess
what is this lighter cleansing fire and
harvest more devotion
oh even more
[Music]
i i need the healing thing for better
beds anyway okay let's go with that
[Music]
yeah they just walk up to the dead
bodies and just puke man that's kind of
disrespectful
isn't it though like kind of like hey i
would be sad if someone threw up in
front of my dead body
especially like it's not even like a
rotten body or anything it's a fresh
dead body
judging by the movies that i've seen
the body will still look look pretty
much exactly the same
unless someone murdered it or whatever
[Music]
it would look the same
yeah
anyway oh
bed has collapsed
oh just a fresh dead body yeah don't
make such a big deal out of it
okay let's make a sermon also wait this
is nothing right yeah it's just
decoration
okay
[Music]
today's sermon is about
how to praise kiwawa
every day
well just say she's cute you say she's
talented just say the truth because all
of the positive words that you can
possibly find in the dictionary are true
about kiwawa it's that easy oh see i got
this one and this one
yeah
um
wow
what's this again increase the total
where are you going to hold it oh you
know what i'll go for this one
no i said all the positive words
thank you for your love and support
ah feels good doesn't it
oh i see we have another oldie maybe we
should sacrifice them before they die
but then how many people will i have
enough for
going to the next level
i do have to go into the
other place again one more time
at some cool down anyway unless i do
this one
[Music]
grow your strength and unlock new
abilities and weapons
that's interesting the other one doesn't
give you abilities and weapons
what does this give me
i should sacrifice them before i die
yeah
okay let's do this one then
i'm so sorry oh wait do i get the item
back when they die because that one's
wearing garfield is wearing my necklace
i love you garfield you've been such a
good boy
[Music]
i i will get it back right it would make
no sense if i wouldn't get it back
[Music]
together
like
with the meat it will also give me his
necklace i'm hoping
unless if not then we can just revive
him with the necklace i'm guessing
[Music]
i don't think i saw a necklace but maybe
it went into my inventory anyway
okay uh how many are we one two three
four are we nine how many are we
oh bro cool is horrified that uh i
sacrificed someone
chill out
it's fine
come on
uh oh yeah let's build this
um oh [\h__\h]
i cancelled it
let's build this
maybe next to the beds i guess
here and um
i guess we'll build the demonic
summoning circle
around
oh it just flips like that okay
um
i'll build it here
okay
build it fast
build it proper
we're cool yeah come on chill the [\h__\h]
out
oh that one is enlightened let me get
you let me get you before you go to
sleep thank you
bye again patty
patty has been
really really a good good girl
okay i'm gonna go while you guys are
sleeping
mommy is gone for a little bit i need
more [\h__\h] flowers
unbelievable uh once i have the two
flowers i'm gonna leave though
vampires are seven
seven oh
that's just certain i know where that's
um the curse yeah
of course
okay i don't see any flowers here
oh i see that was here
that should be enough yeah
[Music]
i got him why was there only one enemy
in here
collect three wood from napolita
oh no that's that was faster than
expected let me check out some
nice oh
more flowers
okay i'll leave i think i'll i will
leave i will leave
i will leave after this one
it feels like so unsatisfying
when you leave before
uh you're actually done with the map
oh yeah get those bones get those bones
[Music]
how the baby changed its name probably
into fit with the game we're playing to
the baby that can be eaten
yo
no don't worry baby
not going to eat you
here's your shitty flowers
now i just need to work out the courage
to talk to them you don't sound like
that with us
nothing else would be more
let's describe it more
more like a brat about it like what's in
it about it
be like
they're not worthy of me they should
come up to tell me that they love me
before i do it and everybody should love
me anyway
anyway
okay we finally did that stupid quest um
now the question is do we have enough
people no we have wait nine
was it nine that was necessary or ten
i feel like it might have been nine
that's enough right okay before somebody
[\h__\h] dies
let me just
drop off some poop
okay
oh they're so cute why are they so cute
extort
and i don't know
triggered
you shall
i shall inspire you
yeah
let's do something with you portugal
uh i'll give you a gift
your small gift i did not get the moon
necklace back apparently okay
a cookie
thank you robin cat thank you
i appreciate it
um
i'll give a present to that buddha as
well here this
nature necklace to increase the loyalty
yeah better be [\h__\h] loyal now
he's hoes and loyal
let's go
i can go right now maybe i should make
some food could be could be gone for a
while
gohan
cooking with quinoa
[Music]
hi
which one should i go for sorry this
song is so fun
the the call and response is so much fun
name of song oh wait what does it come
on it or or does it actually have a
proper
title i'm not sure
[Music]
hi
hi hi hi hi working worship it sounds
good doesn't it it sounds like the most
these two just like just from the sound
of it make the most sense to me
i'll go with that one
ah
glory of construction perform original
at your temple that will immediately
build all structures currently on the
but then um
i would have to build so much at once
for that to make sense perform
originally your template will
temporarily increase the version
generation speed ooh at your shrine by
20 for three days
i think i'll do that one
it's like a exp buff
for grinding
i think i want that one agree
agree not that i
not that i need your agreement
enlightenment let's go
can i do that right now
it's 37 bones let's do it
wait did that work
huh
did that do the trick
oh hey you're [\h__\h] late
what's it
i didn't do it
more more oh we can go up now here
this one
yeah
and now we do the ritual okay
okay
unlock
whoa
only four come on
come on
the version of generation
okay sounds good
[Music]
who pooped in my shrine
that's so [\h__\h] disrespectful tell me
who was it
what the [\h__\h] was it
what
oh [\h__\h]
was it you was it you who was it more
poop
okay we're gonna try to get a janitor
soon i guess
uh
okay
[Music]
i'm about to leave uh just wanna
i haven't used this one in a while
yeah
get to work
oh sorry you in the toilet i wanted to
clean the toilet
that's awkward
always very awkward when something like
that happens oh oh and i should uh build
my broken farms again
there you go
that sounds okay for now
bye-bye
finally
finally the new level
yeah
anchor deep
is it like ocean themed what are we
doing oh
what
you guys just click something away
[Music]
let's go
good hunting boss thank you i'll do my
best see you on the flip side cat's on
the flip side oh thank god it's not the
hammer
not my favorite weapon still but okay
new mats crystal shirts
[Music]
i don't know what to use those for but
probably some fancy new items okay ooh
it is ocean theme look at those
jellyfish
the music is
nice too
[Music]
um
this is like like like a table table
hockey or i don't know
those enemies you touch them and they go
like
you
feels like playing air hockey table
hockey
[Music]
fun oh this one doesn't do it
oh he has spikes oh no
uh-uh
dangerous
oh but i like this ocean theme
wow
instrumentals and the btm are nice too
yeah table hockey fun yeah but i suck at
it
the hearts one and the hearts too wow
which that is hard choice
oh
fink kiwara kiwada kihano ki waba fink
[Laughter]
why would i go for a half heart when i
can have a full heart huh
it makes no sense dude
oh wait i can still i can also buy some
new ones here huh yeah i'm good
i'm good
free to play
it's the way to go really that's the
only thing you have in this room they're
going so easy on me i guess i'm like
used to
the other rooms now where everything was
so difficult because i i did them
several times after the first clear
where everything's like really
really tough
wait the first time you walk into these
levels are you really that easy
easy mold
it's too easy too easy those are they
have new weapons now those are new
inferior we have seen them before but
not with that weapon
actually makes them a little bit easier
to fight in my opinion
what the [\h__\h] is that
it has eyes carrying bombs oh my god
oh my god
nice
gonna be careful
oh big boy hello ah don't run away
oh he keeps on spawning more we have to
kill him
okay guys they want to chit chat a
little bit i have some topics not too
many but
some
because we didn't talk about popcorn yet
for example
yeah yeah yeah
so
you may have known that on
last sunday
yeah sunday sunday no saturday saturday
to sunday or sunday night like saturday
to sunday night
i think maybe
uh i
performed
made an appearance ooh
unnaturally long life nice
at popcorn which is a convention in
seoul in korea
oh oh it's so short um
i'll go here
popcorn not popcorn popcorn like pop
conventions what if we're the enemies
i hate califlower i hate it
give me broccoli
why is there cauliflower here
also this shouldn't be grass anymore
this should be seaweed to be honest that
would be a nice gimmick
anyway
you
it's not the same thing what the [\h__\h]
that we couldn't be any more different
oh hello you're offering me
[Music]
did you give me one you have so many
what the [\h__\h]
those poor souls look at them
this is
this is way more like
like terrifying than
my cult my so
so-called cult what isn't the cult
compared to this my place is heaven
oh you have sale wait
off
that's actually really cheap
yeah let me freedom
that's a good price to free
one of these poor souls
i love the crunch crunch of them that's
that's
no i can't hit this npc lame
lame
oh bye bye
so okay anyway
uh
so i did that appearance together with
bails
and i just want to repeat the fact that
the reason that we were
invited
i i would um
say a big part of that
oh oh oh they're gonna say hi again
yeah yeah yeah it's okay just say hi
faster
you're disrupting my story
uh
she has sent many vessels like you one
after the other day oval
you have gotten further than most
granted
i shall enjoy watching your cult rot
from the inside a disease no he's going
to make them sick
[Music]
of course it's sickle
i i i don't feel so good
oh no is he gonna give everyone the rona
again
ah that's fine i mean he was always
supposed to be sick just go to bed
just go
oh which way
um
okay
so i was saying i think
we have to thank
uh a certain someone especially
for tweeting at
popcorn every day to invite
takanasukiyata to popcorn
therefore grabbing everybody's attention
and then uh
i don't know how exactly the process
goes but they did then make a poll
i don't know who we were going up
against but
um
yeah because i didn't see the pole but
there was a pole where people could vote
like who they want to come to popcorn
[Music]
they're all nice
i'll go for the gauntlet i guess why not
i don't really care
can i hit that can i get meat no
um
yeah
and
i was i was so excited i didn't think
like it would actually work
but
really exciting
that it did work out
so thank you for trying so hard
to get me and then
uh also
additionally bales
to be part of this convention which was
hopefully just the first step
i hope that
you know not also also not only in korea
of course i want to be
[Music]
um
in as many conventions all over the
world as possible
they're fun i mean
they're like it's just it's just so
satisfying to see the fans in person
like that and to actually have like
an audio feedback of them
reacting like not just you know comments
but also
okay okay hey okay
yeah
yeah having actual applause and all that
it's just so so
satisfying and it feels like so real
and like as a b-tubler
it's it's often hard to grasp like how
many people really
like me
when you don't see it when you don't
feel it when you don't have any like
proof of it normally
it it can be really hard to grasp
[Music]
i'll go for this one
thank you soon
oh hello
are you already here
what's up i was going to spam my
attention hey
me
[Music]
the spikes are so mean yeah
oh he goes so fast
mine went both ways what the [\h__\h]
sick
oh not as sick as sickle
[Music]
oh compared to the big one the small one
just goes like a few steps it's so sad
so cute though
stop spamming the same attack
out
and this this fight is kind of like
boring right now also he keeps on
staying in the same corner is he good
ah there you go
what a stupid boy
you're such a sexy [\h__\h]
what is this problem
oh go for the money
wow
that was easy a band has collapsed okay
let's go and help the people help my
people
i do have to like open this door no okay
good
number one is done
so this time um
the panel was a little bit longer than
our panels usually are i think normally
we got like 45 minutes in in most
panels like in
all the american ones where usually 45
minutes and then we sometimes
took a little bit longer like up to an
hour as i said after an hour is fine but
like official time is 45 minutes or so
and then for this one because you know
they also have to consider that we have
a
we need
who's sick by the way oh god ah he's
fine
and we need a translator
so everything takes a little bit longer
and we
got like what was it one hour and a half
or so
i think it was pretty long
so
what we filled it with was um we started
out with
since both me and bales um like are
trying to learn korean
we did some like pickup phrases that's
why i asked you guys for some pickup
phrases on the night before
and that would work out for that but i
ended up not really using
any
or maybe just one
of the one that you guys gave me
i used one of the pickup lines on on
someone on twitter
uh but yeah i i had to think like what
sounds good in korean and what
translates well in korean and what's
funny because i
you know
um
obviously i wanted to have some kind of
comedic effect
so
um
i have a few good ideas
and
okay let me try to remember i had five
phrases
i didn't even go for them do you want to
eat ramen by the river one because i saw
that veils already had that one written
down so i didn't want to put in the same
one
so
i came up with one of them was like i
start with my eyes closed
and i go like
oh
you should you should wake me up and and
you should kiss me otherwise i'm not
gonna wake up
do it kiss me kind of like that
that was my first one i think the people
really liked it it was pretty cute i
would say
yeah very cute i was like
hey kiss me otherwise i can't wake up
come on
that one was cute i think
oh you want to yeah yeah okay okay blah
blah what is it no more flowers for you
oh
okay okay thank god i thought she was
asking for more flowers i care for
cooling junior flowers but it's not
enough i need to wow them can you make a
delicious meal for us to share
splendid vegetable feast
uh
i don't remember having such a recipe
but let's see um
modest mixed meal
pumpkin soup cherry cauliflower chowder
wait i don't have that
i don't have it how do i learn it
i need the food from all four doors it
but
it's a timed one i'm not gonna finish
that one
yo the the game should know i can't
possibly do that in time
that's a little bit man
i don't think i can do that before the
time runs out even if i speed run
huh eh
i guess i could already go in there if i
quickly get some more followers but
i don't know man
i i'll i'll see what i can do but
that's a little bit manduk-sai a little
bit annoying
okay
so another one was um
oh no you have to call the fire
department because my heart burns for
you
[Music]
oh no i'm burning for you or something
like that
that one was good too
i was like kind of like struggling with
the
pronunciation of these things though
like i let i i i came up with them in
english and then i translated them to a
korean with papago
um
because i didn't know who to ask
uh
yeah
i need to sneeze
[Music]
what a deal
there you go because this one was cheap
and
yeah and then i listened to papago to
get the pronunciation right but ah
i know listening to papa go and makes
everything so katakuto so
um stiff
like i wasn't sure
if like
uh
i sounded i probably sounded weird and
like a robot when i said those phrases
[Laughter]
i wish someone who spoke actual korean
could have like
um helped me with that one but yeah
um i hope i hope it was understandable i
at least i had like the korean writing
on the screen i prepared like graphics
on the screen so people could read along
when we
say it out loud
um i did that for both me and bales
in like some speech bubbles and showed
it on screen so it was probably fine
uh
you are
a baca a sassy vodka because she just
kept on bumping against the walls
these are so
cute
they're all so cute
come on
wait what color was that purple
i already forgot
i think it was purple
could be wrong
lines are good really
another one was uh
oh yeah i have some fresh chicken
breasts at home do you wanna
you know
come by have some fried chicken
basically something like that
and
what was another one
[Music]
there was one more normal one and then
one more where i didn't really know
um
[Music]
wait do i still have my memo let me look
it up
pick up lines there you go oh yeah
uh
ah ah the next one was really
ah
emotional and like deep and i'm proud of
this one because you could probably hear
it in some anime or something
i said i would give my last phoenix
feather to save you
even if it meant that would make me
mortal
because of losing my last peanut photo
you know
yeah yeah yeah
that one that one i'm pretty proud of
because i came up with that one on my
own yeah
yeah
and then you know i i already was
thinking
so hard for these four
and i saw bagels had five and i was like
[\h__\h] another one i can't come up with
anything else
so i just went with breast milk please
my
my usual
one that always makes people laugh and i
put that one last because i thought it
would get a good laugh at uh from people
at the end
[Laughter]
big thinking yeah moyu to say oh saigon
last one was the typical
milk please
which i wouldn't quite say is a pickup
line but yeah and then bails actually
she had like
let me tell you the ones that she had i
would say
no no hates bails but i think my lines
were better in terms of getting a laugh
from the audience because bales ones
were kind of serious and sometimes they
weren't even pick-up lines so i have to
say
um
i put quite the effort into mine hers
where did it hurt when you fell from
heaven
which is do you hear that a million
times and the other one was you are my
life which is
sweet it's sweet
it that one's sweet
and short you know how could you do this
to me did you not love me with one which
is not a pick-up line that's a
fight within the relationship
[Laughter]
another one was just basically a
confession and then the last one was
like the let's eat ramen together that
one i had to ditch because i saw she had
it already yeah yeah
yeah so i have to say
as an entertainer as a comedian
my lance worm
[Music]
superior
comedy hen
when wearing a pickup lenses in the
panel at popcorn in seoul that's what
i'm talking about right now
let's do afterlife i don't know i'm
curious what they offer to me now
respect your elder straight all cult
members will gain the respect of your
illustrated followers three plus five
faith for every elderly follower in the
cold
they're not gonna stay there for long
man
i'll call them as well gain that good
die young trade
er
gain 10 faith if an elder is sacrificed
murdered or consumed but lose 20
if uh faith if an elder dies naturally
okay i think i'll go for that one but
that's really dangerous when i'm like
gone and someone dies
while i'm gone but
that one's just stupid
this one just makes sense because we
we're aiming to sacrifice them anyway
the right one is too risky
how much is 20 faves
it's hard to like how much is a full
faith bar 100 or more
you guys know
it could pay off well yeah just gotta be
a bit more careful and aware of
who is in my cult
20 is a lot
but like when the cult grows bigger and
bigger then we're gonna have more old
people and higher risk that they die off
screen but
yeah whatever
whatever
oh yeah are you okay that will be fine
the other one just gives me nothing
it's
nah
do you i where you do this no yeah okay
i did
okay
i also still have to do a brainwashing
ceremony once
but that one has no time limit so we're
good we're good
yeah
so we did that and then after that we
answered some questions that
were submitted on
twitter beforehand
um
this will be better food write the
cauliflower so gotta put in a lot of
cauliflower
okay
and then after those questions
uh we did
uh some singing
i sang actually yeah for this occasion
uh we were allowed to sing like some
korean songs if we got permission
beforehand if we checked with them
beforehand
and and so i took the the opportunity
and sang
[Music]
a twice song yeah
yeah
it was hard to choose there were so many
songs i wanted to sing
wait we should we should sacrifice
donkey right now
otherwise we're gonna
regret it
um
and sang a twice song fancy fancy
[Music]
which was so fun to see the audience uh
like reacts to it because i i didn't
give them any proper warning beforehand
ah that cool down [\h__\h]
a little bit longer how much is that
i didn't give them any warning
beforehand but they um
like i guess like people just
know twice so well
that
a random crowd that gathers for
our panel
knows the chant for the song like
they knew
the freaking chant
what the hell
the twice chant
i don't even know the chant because i
never
have the opportunity to go to their
concert anyway
but i was impressed by that
everybody knows it
well twice it must be like i mean i i
know i i
i knew twice was [\h__\h] uh
popular
but i didn't expect them to be
like so
so populated
like this vegetable fan crowd
they all not all of them obviously but
loud enough that you would assume a big
portion of them um is chanting
the chant
oh wow wow wow wow so i was quite happy
with my choice of song and the audience
was vibing really good uh with it
yeah
good stuff good stuff
um and and bae sang a really cute song
called kiyomi
i was i found it really funny
when i saw that
she was doing
that song
ah didn't did i place this one i don't
think i did
i didn't i didn't
i thought it was hilarious that she
chose that song
um
because it's like such an insanely old
song but it's so cute
it's basically a song about doing cute
cute cute um well why is it so laggy
doing cute expressions and cute phrases
and all that
stop lagging
whoa
hello leg
hello
why am i so lucky
this is just this menu oh no no i'm back
to normal okay
oh
maybe janitor now huh or
yeah
i'll just go for this one
look
okay
let's build that one janitor station
[Music]
i'll put that where the toilet is
will the janitor clean the toilet
i wonder
we'll build this then cause i'm still
waiting to be able to do my ritual
latest update fixed it
it was an update indeed and i updated
but didn't fix it for me i guess
um oh well
and so then we signed to songs and the
crowd
was really good really good they were
all chanting
and uh
yeah cheering really sweet
i'm glad it went well
because i was kind of nervous about
doing it
um especially because like even though i
listened to a lot of uh twice songs
um
i sang them a lot in english before but
in
korean not so much so i really had to
practice my pronunciation there were
some difficult parts as well in the song
so i was nervous about like stumbling
over my words during the actual
performance but i nailed it i didn't
stumble over my words at all
yeah
thank god
i was so relieved
i was so focused fell and i really
didn't want to mess up so i muted the
feedback from
uh zoom we were doing it for zoom
um so i couldn't actually hear the
audience so i had to listen to it
afterwards in like recordings thankfully
i could listen to it and it made me so
happy seeing it
yeah
that was so nice
i wanna do more wish i could have sang
more songs actually we still had some
time left over after that so
spontaneously i sang
half
half of sparks basically and then bales
sang half of her song
some original songs yeah
squeezed it in there
nicely
but if i get a chance to perform at a
korean convention again
i want to take the chance to sing even
more korean songs i know maybe they i
don't know maybe they would prefer to
hear our originals in that situation but
i usually can't sing korean songs in
um my streams because i don't have like
permission for any instrumentals yet
if i have then i might be able to sing
some songs
but that's why i want to see more of
them
uh in conventions because um at least
they're
they're not as strict about it and they
have some
um they have the rights to the songs
yeah
now
i hope i get more chances to do that
okay
and are we good to go
i guess i'll go i'll make some food
though we have so much grass
hi
and let's extort
someone
i revived her off-screen like i killed
her once and then i revived her
yeah yeah
and you
will inspire you
it's so cute
you're probably gonna grow old soon
aren't you
that probably doesn't make sense to give
you a necklace
never mind then
sorry maybe maybe sicko sicko number one
okay you've endured a lot of sicknesses
and you're healthy again apparently so
you got a necklace we haven't had like
someone in prison for a while
that's a good thing
they're very happy with me
as they should be
thank you
you just finished the game
oh it's addicting it is
i'm gonna go now guys bye-bye
my cult is paradise it is
it is it's very comfy
[Music]
called the spicy chicken oh my
oh dagger nice
[Music]
and exponential
okay let's go
number two a crab oh what the [\h__\h]
flying crap
a little [\h__\h]
oh
ow
oh that one's tough
[\h__\h] you
kind of annoying this little bratz
yeah
oh and then um
after the panel
uh bales had it before the panel i had
up uh after the panel but
what the [\h__\h] is that it's like a mini
boss
at least it looks like it but no no his
health is not so bad
or the chest spawned on the fire now i
can't kill the fire
kill the fire
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um
yeah so for the
for the
uh for the meet and greet
i was
a little bit worried about it because
this time we had a translator translator
by the way also during the panel for the
tweet questions did a really good job
really fast um
oh i talked a lot and they still were
able to keep up so nice very
professional
clunker and bob hello we love that
you're saying you're somewhere doing
just like this i'm clunky
and this is bulk oh he has like a
poopy warm on his hands cute
after a friend
i did play with kratos once off screen
and i won i bet 10 gold coins and i won
of course i did
okay so we're gonna play with you there
maybe some time
talk about over playing your hand hi it
was hilarious i'll win it back though
yeah he lost his hand oh my god
say you should come you seem tough rich
and found for the risk for her to
knuckle bones i'll think about it
i don't think about it
yeah they had a good quality translator
thank god
okay
i'll go this way
whoa what the [\h__\h]
what was that meat damn impressive
impressive
and
yeah the meet and greet i was worried
also i didn't hear what they will see
the audio
it was kind of sucky so that's my
feedback to
i know whoever is in charge
we need a better microphone for
um
the
the people who come to the meet and
greet although they did say they had
like a microphone there
like a somewhat good
microphone like not really like
like streaming professionally quality
but
should have been decent enough but no
it was really hard to hear what they
were saying which made it more difficult
because you know
a lot of them didn't speak good english
or any english
so it was like hard mode meeting green
heart mode what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
this is also hard mode right now
i need to focus
[Music]
oh yeah that was that was also
interesting like usually in the american
conventions that we did so far
um we had like a big like seminar room
basically
um but in this case
it was like imagine a big convention
hall and then a stage in the middle
somewhere
not in the middle like on the side on
the wall but still like in the middle
and
so it wasn't closed it was within
some doors
what am i saying it was not closed it
was not within some some walls it was
open open space so
even the people who were just walking by
would be able to hear what's going on
and you know like basically this is
really good because like if there's
people who don't know us yet
they can catch a glimpse accidentally
and be like oh what is this oh they're
so popular oh what's going on what's
going on
and you know become fans
it's actually really good and
uh even though they arranged
barely any seating
they made it so spacious and like it was
such a low amount of seating
what more enemies oh [\h__\h]
um
there were so many people gathering
around standing and like
so close to one another so squeezed
to one another
that was quite something the the crowd
was huge
it was huge
but
i don't know why they had such a little
amount of space
prepared either they didn't expect that
they should have known like
because like judging by the
the
applicants for the meet and greet and
like how many people voted for us
i feel like they should have known but
maybe that's just their
their basic setup and they just didn't
want to prepare anymore
[Laughter]
for some reason
but i feel like it was basically seats
for like 20 people or so
okay maybe a bit more maybe 50 50. and
then around that was like
hundreds of people standing behind like
a fence
which was kind of weird because there
was really so much space in between the
seats that you could have added at least
like 100 more seats in there
oh
it was
kind of weird anyway your friend radar
was the last vessel sent against us the
sniveling coward and there were
countless before him all equally
pathetic and unworthy
nothing humbles quite like disease again
five of them
but they they'll just go to bed right
they'll just go to bed like the other
one
called pro-philliac trait
what
believes illness is divine punishment
right
should we go back
whoa holy [\h__\h] oh
skit
this room is amazing
oh my god
can we get these rooms more often please
oh wait i'm not leaving now this is like
insane
okay i'm gonna be fast i'm gonna try to
be fast
yeah i have a healing bait will they go
there automatically
oh i forgot what that weapon was okay
i hope they will go there automatically
wow
bombs on you
hey
they will not go all the way but you
have to
well that sucks
but at least they will go to bed i think
they will go to bed rest on their own
otherwise it would be stupid
um i guess i'll take a heart whatever
both of those cards were kind of [\h__\h]
but at least we got a lot of treasures
before
oh i will need flowers to heal them
nice hit
nice
[\h__\h] crabs
[\h__\h] those crabs i love crabs normally
but these it's [\h__\h] annoying
it looks sick
so as for how the meet and greet went
um we gave them a little bit maybe one
more minute or two more minutes than
usual a little bit more time than
people in like english-speaking
meet-and-greets get
because
communication problems like
i expected actually
a bit more english-speaking people
because i thought the people that would
sign up for the meet and greet they
surely know
some
uh english right look at these in the
mouth if they if they think they can
participate in the meet and greet if
yeah but actually surprisingly no
i would say that like 60 percent
60 of them had to use uh the translator
um then uh like one or two people i
spoke japanese with them and then um one
or two people i spoke english with them
yeah
almost everybody used the translator
which you know made the whole
conversation a little bit more um
stiff
i guess
sadly but i think it still went fine
like we still um exchanged a lot of
a lot of words what is this i can
increase the loyalty of any follower oh
um
oh
loyalty
huh don't know how about polka
also let me take a fruit candy i've been
talking so much now
thank you
this fool would follow you into the
deepest darkness from whence no one
returns you're not nice
yeah
like
i mean
it's totally fine you know i'm happy
that even the ones who don't speak
english got a chance to
talk with me that was fine
and actually
there was there was like
one person
that
well like several people but one
especially then
um told me like a really
emotional story
that was really really sweet good to
hear that
about i'm not gonna go into detail but
it was basically like
somebody
created something
um
um like kfp related
and then
it didn't get any attention
or any views or whatever
[Music]
for the longest time and that person
already at that point wasn't
let's say wasn't very happy in life or
like you know
um
and then
you know i'm kind of like unfortunate
so far
and then apparently i promoted that
thing
on my stream and suddenly it got so much
attention
and that person was like so
so happy and
ah
just like so blessed
ah [\h__\h] crabs no
i'm so thankful they were like you
like changed my life you saved my life
you made everything like
suddenly i can see happiness and
stuff like that you know
uh
so i had like a huge effect on that
person apparently
yeah that made me really happy to hear
that that
i can help like that i i do it a lot you
guys know i like to promote
what my fans do i like to promote the
clips that you guys create
and i like to retweet and use the fan
art
i like to look at your the homepage that
you guys made and all that kind of stuff
um
fan projects you know
i want to
appreciate you guys
for you appreciating me
[Music]
you hmm are lucky that i have so many
hearts
oh [\h__\h] you
oh [\h__\h] hell yeah
too crowded
okay nice
so
yeah not only that person actually a lot
of them told me stuff like
i i give them
like so much
motivation and inspiration and hope to
keep on going and
my
my energy in my my happiness on stream
makes them happy
and gives them energy too
also it was really sweet a lot of them
started the meet and greet by asking me
if i'm okay if i'm not super tired how
do i feel am i happy
a lot of them worried about me wait did
i get a card
yeah i guess i did
so considerate
sweet
thank you for asking
ow
ow what the [\h__\h] was that
oh
now the tiny [\h__\h] is also really fast
ow oh holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
what's going on
[Music]
what's actually going on
i guess i can oh my god i can use them
uh
the some of these monsters as like a
bomb holy [\h__\h] am i okay am i gonna be
okay am i gonna die
what's going on
i think yours you're supposed to use
them as a bomb
maybe oh my god
oh my god
i have no idea what's going on
[Music]
oh okay
calm the [\h__\h] down
am i even doing damage to him when i hit
it gives me like kind of a weird
feedback
oh [\h__\h] oh that was my accent
because i was like panicking
my health is still okay my health is
still okay my health is still okay
okay okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
okay
[Music]
wow what the [\h__\h] is going on man
interesting fight
um
i see they all they are no longer ill
yay
[Music]
i'll take the gift
i want to give my gifts to my fans
to my cult members we're halfway through
them
welcome to the cubs you
had me on my
tippy
tippy toes there you go
isn't that a cute name
i think that's a hecking cute name
let's give you blue
and make you fluffy and eat more fluffy
boys
what are your strong constitution
coprophiliac
a natural skeptic
good name
okay you shall
do whatever
i don't care
[Music]
you guys need to give me more devotion
yo
paradigm do i need another bed now
am i out of beds
no i have 13 beds and 11 people so we're
fine
let's get those berries
you know one funny thing
or
embarrassing thing that happened um
during the
meet and greet
like
around
at the very end
um
it was like i think it was in total it
was like 20 people or so
so it took like a little bit over two
hours actually
and i did it pretty much without a break
um
i was really really tired and the more
time passed the more tired i got and
also hungry because i didn't really have
a proper breakfast and all that i had to
get up really early i i got up at what 4
or so
um had like four hours of sleep which is
not enough for me okay for some people
you guys may say oh that's enough not
for me okay to function properly
and i had to sing too you know
but anyway
so i wasn't i wasn't in my best
uh
how to say
state
yeah it's not enough like if you were
like saying this enough then i don't
know how you're trying to flex on me but
that's not the way to go
yeah not the best condition yeah
um
so
um around the end
it was like only one person to go
and i said
in between i said oh no no it was
already the last person was already in
we were in the middle of the
um
of the meet and greet and
while i was listening and and i'm
telling you i'm i was 100 listening but
on the side
i wrote to my manager that i need to go
to an idol meeting but i was just like i
wasn't saying that in in like trying to
go there immediately
i just
on the side i just mentioned
i need to go to the idle meeting
and then
in the middle of the meet and greet
my managers or like the the people there
the staff people they're suddenly
they're like sorry sorry can you can you
leave the room for a second for a minute
and and i'm like shh
that wasn't necessary and the the person
in the meet and greet was like confused
he wasn't it
like they were probably thinking they'd
do something wrong or so and i didn't
want him to think that so i was trying
to be like
no no it's okay it's okay it's okay but
the staff kept on saying like please
please just go out for a minute i'm like
no no it's fine it's fine and then
everybody was like so confused about it
and i'm like oh come on
this is a very thick actually and then
because i didn't want him to think that
he did something wrong i was like
trying to explain that um afterwards
when i came back i was like
sorry i just needed to go to an island
meeting but
i could have waited until the end but
it was like i don't know it was so
awkward and embarrassing and i i i
didn't know what to do
so in the middle of a four minute
normally four minutes uh meet and greet
i
went to the idol meeting
and i came back and i was like well this
is awkward um
but thankfully the the meet and greet
person he was probably still confused
and he probably
didn't quite grasp what was going on so
he didn't make it awkward i was the one
making it awkward and the staff people
too
um but
thanks to that he kind of got a lot of
additional time
for the meet and greet
it felt like instead of four minutes it
was 10 minutes also because of other
reasons like they were trying to
um give me something that i wasn't
allowed to accept so i had to explain it
and i i i explained it because i wanted
it to come across nicely
well you gotta check this one out
um
but yeah that was a weird situation
yeah at least i got more a little bit
more time for being interrupted yeah
i see this as an absolute win i don't
[Laughter]
wasn't my fault from very first time
then
wait are you the last one that was there
are you the one
[Music]
first time
i don't quite understand yeah but
real really hey
now i'm even more embarrassed
that's um
that's that's funny
yeah well it wasn't your fault really
and i wanted to clear that up because
the way this the staff made you go
outside was um weird like it could be
misleading like as if something i don't
know it was so out of nowhere you know
we were in the middle of having a
conversation there like um can you go
outside for a minute it's like what why
what what what why did i do something
wrong so i wanted to clear that up
ah
that's so embarrassing
i didn't mean it like that
anyway
let's see what do we have um ritual of
the harvest perform originally temple
that causes all seeds to be merely ready
for home
oh cool perform originally at your
temple which for two days will make
special fish more likely to appear while
fishing
i think maybe
both are like kind of equal if you like
to go fishing a lot but i think
should i go fishing
really
i'll go for good
two days huh
okay you guys seem to really like this
one okay hold on
okay
[Music]
got some good fish
just had technical difficulties or
something would have been less awkward
no but like at that moment i was still
trying to say that like it's fine i'm
just gonna do the meet and greet until
the end but like they kept on like
pushing him outside so
oh man communication error
communication not found
okay um
[Music]
nice
next time maybe just gotta keep it to
yourself
[Laughter]
i was
i was just you know over sharing i guess
yeah
um
ah with automatic farms you would not
have the time to use the first one
interesting
okay then that's good um lucio
do we have someone old i hope not
because the rituals are on cool down
still
i
will
i'll bring someone back to life
well there's someone sick in there
i will bring back to life
56.60
[Music]
oh garfield because he has the [\h__\h]
necklace
come back garfield
you can't just go to afterlife with that
necklace no no no no no no it's valuable
very valuable
come back you little [\h__\h]
you're tempted to steal my necklace and
just [\h__\h] off huh
no oh ain't happening
okay
interesting did i do my sermon
did i
oh
ah garfield was dissenting what what the
[\h__\h] what
he was dissenting
yo bed rest go
huh oh oh sorry i interrupt i get minus
one faith for interrupting sorry yeah
give me money
oh sickle
inspire the sicko
i can heal
wait how do i can i do it from here too
no
ah
nice that's what they are also useful
for very good welcome back
why do you still look sick makes no
sense
oh there we go okay i just had to go
back to that bed
well then um
you know what i'm
what they're bugged or something
just sleep then maybe that will fix it
oh okay they look fine now they no they
don't look
but
they're not gonna throw up right
maybe it's just the avatar is bugged but
they themselves are fine
does this one work
yeah okay just checking
a visual bug okay i'll go again
nice
i told him to go to bed didn't fix it no
it's okay maybe if i leave the
this place once
then
you might
mix it
let's see can we do something can we
build something
um i need to learn more of these things
um
i know what we'll do we'll send someone
although
there was a hint that you die when you
send like the person who we send dies
when we send them on a mission how high
are the chances
is it
is it should i use it
depends
it tells you
oh it tells me the percentage of
if they die or not
interesting okay anyway here's some food
guys because you guys seem really hungry
and i sent them on a mission in the
middle of the night they probably won't
like it huh
okay i'll do something else then
uh i'll go no
no i don't i didn't turn the thing on
didn't do the ritual
but i might as well collect the
some of the
devotion
and once we restored this place to all
its shining glory i swore here's our
offering return praise the lambo lamb of
light
wow
oh
oh cute wait is that a
is that what's it called um a thing from
minecraft
uh another copybutter
wait what
axolotl yeah what the [\h__\h] oh god
nothing from minecraft yeah
yeah
whoa what the [\h__\h] is that fish
holy [\h__\h] oh i guess they're always that
big the big ones are always that thick
oh damn
[Music]
come on
nothing special
let's get another one why not while
we're here
[Music]
oh
a blueprint
oh these actually look decent
[Music]
not so bad
because i don't wanna i'm so cheap i
don't wanna buy
anything
for money
[Music]
organize your farm with this handy
signpost blazing beacon ooh
i like this one
no i don't wanna spend any money no
let's go back
this game did fishing right what do you
mean wow
oh so
no i wasn't trying to interrupt you you
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay what do we do guys
wait i should do this one called number
three upgrade temples temple shrine
collect more than what yes
finally
yay
can we get by the farms now soon
oh oh oh oh will not look different
it does look different
nice is it going to get higher and
higher
nice
okay
uh
i probably should go on an idol meeting
by the way for real
don't make it weird but i think i want
to go and then turn on the lights in my
room because it's getting dark or it is
dark
want us to leave no you guys can stay
just stay in the room
[Music]
isn't it like i find um
i find it funny that you know it's not
like you know i'm a v tuber if i go to
an idol meeting it's not like that
person who's in the meet and greet
will like see me or anything
but they made him leave i guess so that
they wouldn't know i just went to an
island meeting which i guess that that
itself is a good thing to do
do not make it awkward but it was
awkward anyway
[Laughter]
no don't leave
no
no you won't no no
there's nothing bad about going to an
island meeting to stay
oh what was that
let's do a ritual um
[Music]
never enough
no
i don't know i don't understand why this
one makes me lose a little bit of faith
they still seem happy about it though
uh
no okay
okay
okay okay go next go next but um also go
idle meeting
everybody please wait
yeah yeah it's just a meeting no no no
no toilets just meeting
us see you in a minute oh stretch oh
okay
i
am back
yeah
boycott of the land
i want to play more cult of the lamp
can i play more cult of the land please
i am addicted
um
wait i have one stone thingy
i can declare a new thingy right
hmm
oh i could but it's on cooldown i didn't
know it also had a cool down oh i'm too
fast
i'm so fast
okay
you're also enlightened
wait sorry
wait what happens
if i enlighten them and i already
okay it's already starting a new one
okay
sorry for interrupting i guess
oh god damn it
don't be so weird about it
what a deal you get a feather necklace
what a deal
oh [\h__\h] i can't stop myself i can't stop
myself i'm so popular i'm such a good
cult leader holy [\h__\h]
um
did i already give you a gift before
i feel like i may have you know what let
me inspire you
how much was it
nothing that's why it's such a deal it's
not even the deal
at this point
okay now i want to test out the
oh [\h__\h] i got two i got two now oh i'm
gonna send someone here okay let's see
um
low level has not leveled up medium
level medium level low level so i should
send someone with a medium or high level
there you go high level paddy
so
there's a 92 percent
chance that she will survive if i send
her for lumber for example is that right
i'm gonna test it out now
okay let's send her for
let's send her for
me
maybe
[Music]
this is not a sacrifice
she's not old
what do you mean she's old
she's she she was just sacrificed and
and revived several times but she's fine
oh bye bye
have a good trip
don't disappoint me
and now we're gonna summon
ah
oh cute
look they turn into little others only
three different ones though
they turn into little no four different
ones little demon skewn
oh automatically collect dropped favor
start an experiment with half a spirit
heart
flies away and returns with red hearts
oh how often though
more starting hearts
i see
shoot cooldown decrease choose a
projectile with an enemy every
trigger let's go i'll take you
interesting
follow me
[Music]
let's go oh cute you're gonna
interact
you're gonna follow me right
when i
you just stay here for now but when i go
you follow me
are they all going to the toilet
[Music]
oh we might need
more toilets
so far it looks like they can wait but
maybe let's build another one
do we ever get like a different version
of the toilet i wonder a more like
japanese high level toilet
i wonder
yeah followers need idle meetings too
should i should i leave
i'd have to learn it first
okay we're gonna go
on
the third third crusader is already the
fourth
you are idols in my heart yes
you can be whatever you want to be
hell yeah
i got that stuff
let me get that dude
and let me get that too is there
something here oh yeah
okay
oh and let me get that oh my god it
loads up so fast they create so much
devotion
so good
let's let's make some decoration
before i go
this one i haven't created this one yet
let's make a little
oh it's so tiny cute one here and one
here
yeah
enjoy okay i'm out of here
wait maybe a little bit more food
thank you
can i be a paid employee um no
what a stupid question i think you can
i'll meeting really important yeah
[Laughter]
i made it for like over two hours
actually in between the panel
and the meet and greet there was also
not that much time just like 15 minutes
so i tried to
gulp down a yogurt really fast
didn't have much of a break so it was
quite um exhausting but it was worth it
it was like
really really really really really nice
i really had a good time even though i
was suffering worth it
no
why does give me the hammer so often
oh [\h__\h] it
i hate the hammer
and i wish i could like
like ban the hammer from the selection
somehow
oh my god
oh yeah
i really have to like
uh put so much effort into it when i use
this weapon
no don't go away
no
oh thank god that hit
at least i have a little
little demon helping me
firing projectiles that's at least
something i guess
what
poop there's like mountains of poop
there
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
nice
oh
i'm gonna go mad i'm gonna go mad those
[\h__\h] crabs i swear to god
no
oh i thought it's not the enemy nice
thank you thank you my demon i'm just
gonna leave it all to the demon i'm just
gonna leave it all to them
oh that was still it that worked that
worked
oh my god
almost got hit again
[Music]
i hate this weapon
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
explosion
nice
that's an
interesting room
thankfully they're going easy on me
i have to go back to the other room
because that was a dead end apparently
pray for a tarot card no i'm praying for
a different weapon fast
um
okay poison damage i'll take that one
that helps a little bit
the trail one would be good though
blazing trail
my friend to buy tunic oh nice
nice i missed you nick
ah it was so good oh come here why are
you going away
oh only one anime
hey
[Music]
when it spawned the enemy it kind of
made a pooping sound
cute
skull necklace
hey yo
it dropped a necklace for my followers
not bad
what do we get okay
that works too
next up um
why should i go maybe this way
i'll go this way
oh
a shop
and this time we are not going to
kill everybody here although i have to
say that snail
really makes me want to insert a coin
into that big mouth
that's like the perfect slot for
inserting a coin
don't be so [\h__\h] terrified
it's okay
what do we want tuna the seed or the
cauliflower
nice
i'm really bad at using this hammer i
might by accident kill some people sorry
i wasn't on accident
hello
i'll take those i like those too
i will not hurt your snail don't worry
[Music]
i'll go for the seats yeah
it's fine
oh [\h__\h] this is a first
wow
what
[Music]
you're singing
my love took my heart to the sea
to see she took my heart to the sea
this way my heart will
take a moment to join me in my search i
look for the heart that once beat in my
chest
it's right behind you i think
that is until it was taken by her oh
oh interesting side story
i've been sitting here for so many years
even her face has faded from my mind yet
i keep searching
always searching
i have a dozen hearts you see but none
of them are mine they are yours if you
wish to have them crusader
okay
thank you
they're worthless to me i care only for
the heart that was once mine so that i
might look up on upon her face one last
time
oh
i'm so sad but oh wow they heal so much
thank
you
wow
i want extra hearts
give me some extra hearts to fill like
my hearts up oh wait oh
oh
a hundred
extra two
should i get it
we have 225
coins
worth
yeah and i unlock it forever we can
always get that one like randomly
yeah okay
oh [\h__\h] wait look at all the blue hearts
there oh
yeah
give me those give me those give me
those give me those
whoa
i'm like invincible
got any more of that where that came
from
i need more blue temporary hearts i
guess
guess that's enough
thanks dude
nice place to go here help you find your
own heart again
as it seems to be forever taken by the
one that you love
very romantic
romantic
i thank you for your help so selfless
you know
they'll need their own
hearts and all those hearts that they
found when they give them to me
in your face
thank god
oh did that even hit i don't know
i'm bad at aiming at that one
[Music]
nice
okay
now yesterday i cooked again i have to
tell you these days because i don't cook
that often anymore these days so i'm
proud of every time i cook
i just made a simple bolognesa it was
from hellofresh though but
oh
come on
it seems you cannot be stopped by the
seeds or hunger and he sends you back
from death stronger each time
please no it was not my idea to cast out
the red crown the other bishops my
siblings the blame lies of them
interesting
there are
they're not like threatening to hurt me
or so anymore they're blaming their
other buddies
they're scared of me now
please i beg you spare me or is it a
trap kill shamuda but not send me to
death do not send me to him
you will not find my temple i will be
saved there yes i will be safe
yeah do we like get a choice maybe if we
don't kill them we still get them as a
follower so i don't know now we'll kill
them
it seems like some just some kind of
mind play
oh thank god
the only other weapon they gave me two
curses but the other only other weapon
they give me is a [\h__\h] hammer again
i am cursed
literally
honobuki sayakun on the skittle
wait why did i
i should have gone for whatever
i should have at least gotten a
different
more helpful curse but okay whatever
it's the same
in the end
all of this
is terrible
hi miss of course i miss
oh why doesn't that hit
ow
nice dodge there though
and today i can eat the rest of it
wonderful wonderful
yeah
so i'm still doing hello fresh today i
got another delivery for
the following the coming the current
week i guess
yeah
i want to start making
like breakfast um like cook some
breakfast again
because recently i've only been eating
like bread a lot like croissants and
stuff but it's just nice too but i want
to make my pancakes again but it takes
so much effort who wants to do that in
the morning huh
oh how are you playing ball
would you closer look at the furthest
antiquities in the lens of the old
faithful lobby that's right as low as me
ships are floating blimbo's open for
business
you just went seriously come down to my
sanctuary but you'll find equally
acquainted
instant mix i should
i should
i've seen it in japan i don't i don't
remember seeing like
like a finished mix
uh
in in austria i need to check out those
supermarkets
eat bacon or eggs or something quick
i i would like my breakfast to be sweet
most of the time only sometimes i'm in
the mood for some eggs
[Music]
but
i was watching on my stream the other
day and she had like a breakfast bowl
with rice and some other stuff what was
in there avocado and stuff
i don't want the avocado but
but
i don't like the thought of the
breakfast bowl that she had so
i wanted to mimic it
but when i was in the supermarket buying
trying to buy ingredients to make a
breakfast bowl
i wasn't sure what to put into it so i
gave up
next time next time
okonomiyaki cooking stream i'm not a big
fan of okonomiyaki
if you ever get tired of sweet things
all the time no never
okay like maybe like
some like if i mean
i do want some savory stuff
during the day
like my dinner i don't want my dinner to
be sweet usually
and sometimes instead of chocolate snack
during the day i i like to have like
some potato chips or so as well
[Music]
so useless
oh mamma mia
finally finally a good weapon
oh
i've suffered for too long
[Music]
finally free of the hammer yeah relief
did you see that sorry i laughed a
little bit too crazy
i enjoyed that too much
its own spawned enemy
projected towards its mother and killed
it
[Music]
i love seeing that
um
where is that this one this is the room
we haven't had the shiny in a while yo
um
[Music]
oh yeah those are just those bombs oh
[\h__\h]
whoa
interesting
wait for it
that's what i thought
and you only can get like one hit and
what the [\h__\h]
well the poison will consume you
eventually there you go
thank you lasagna
oh
thank you my music i hope i can
finally release the last the next song
soon
tm
actually the music video is pretty much
done
there have been some delays in
in terms of mixing
oh point gonna go back
but it will hopefully be worth the wait
nice that hit quite a bunch of them or
all of them even
yay
taking time to make it perfect
yeah but um i have to say though like um
besides the song being delayed that
means
that means i also have to delay
like the start of creating the album
that i want to make
i can't really start working on it
until after releasing this song
and then also in terms of like concerts
um like i asked like can we do it
blue
um
but
like i mean in fairy yes but i haven't
even like gotten an answer on when i
could do it like it seems like there's
like
uh like um
how to say
a big waiting line
basically so it's not really in my hands
when i can do it
and i'll have to
adjust and um ah
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
i basically have to adjust myself to
them
um so i kind of doubt that it will work
the way
i originally planned it like in that
timeline
so
[Music]
you'll have to be
patient sorry about that guys
but
then in that meantime we can make more
and more songs
and more and more choreographies and
prepare more and more things so that we
make it even more awesome
yeah it will happen i will
not just accept it to not happen you
know
yeah more songs to look forward to
exactly and then at least i guess if
they if
if i'm being forced to do it later
rather than earlier then i'm
um
i get more time to prepare everything
and
yeah
we can
increase the quality then i guess and
also then i can be really really sure
that
i can use the studio in japan
because the later it is the higher are
the chances for me to
be able to go to japan to record it
okay um
i chose a gift last time
[Music]
i don't really need that much food right
now though
i will go for the gift because that
gives us more loyalty and then we get
more of those you know
these door thingies
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
defeat it
once again we have one more one more to
go
three hours so far and we've been doing
a lot of side stuff
i don't know if we're going fast or slow
today but i'm having a good time
having to wait a lot for everything but
let's hope for the best yeah
yeah i wish i wish sometimes things
would be faster overall
in many ways why are you not asleep
this dude
don't sleep
but it is what it is
you have to
have to deal with it
[Music]
welcome to the cold my friend
uh i will call you
tangent because i kept on tangenting
while i was fighting you
[Music]
know
what was this color [\h__\h] why do i
immediately a second after looking at
him i forget it what was his color
god damn it angelina oh
cute
green
i had a
i had a feeling yeah everybody says
something else brown wait there's uh
orange and orange and some browns okay
maybe something in between like this
[Music]
thank you
yeah i'll work i'll work hard on it
i'll do my
[Music]
how excited best was i returned from my
successful missionary missionary bearing
gifts
i'm so proud of you now go sleep i love
you i love you love you
oh my sweet daddy
working so hard for me
go sleep everybody i wanna i wanna use
my
uh doctrine there you go oh patty didn't
even get to sleep oh
how'd it go sleep
oh baby
now i will wake her up though if i
if i do something in here
no not you
you're not patty you're patsy it sounds
similar but it's wrong
can't wait to be on the concert one day
yeah
thank you
thank you for waiting guys
blue
oh
i guess we should upgrade this one
oh i'm sure
now i have to wait
[Music]
no i don't um
really watch much anime although we did
do that anime marathon
of the first episode of a lot of animes
the other day but besides that i don't
really watch anime especially not like
as you say
etchy you probably mean like harem type
of anime
it's not really my thing
i used to watch them
when i was younger but now not really no
thank you jim tracy
uh believe in the original sin trade
all are born guilty reduced faith loss
when putting a follower in jail who is
not dissenting why would i put someone
in jail who's not dissenting
freedom above all else every day that
begins without anyone in prison ah
hell yeah
currently we haven't had someone in
prison for a long time no one's
dissenting i'm doing so well
yeah
one of the 10 was reverse harem
which one do you mean
which one was that
uh can we do we have anybody who's old
because we could do
an ascension right now is anyone old
let me look at them they don't
they don't look old
oh they didn't really you need to sleep
oh thank you so much but please go sleep
holy [\h__\h]
wait don't interrupt them
there you go
the villainous one ah
you're still most familiar i'm doing it
yeah because i even though like probably
if i would watch it now for the first
time i might not enjoy it as much but i
i want to cherish the memories and the
enjoyment i had of for it uh back in the
day
back in the day i really enjoyed it
now it might not be up to my standards
but
i really enjoyed it back then so i'll
give it those uh credits properly
oh good night oh thank you
i always cry at the end of the first
season
oh i forgot what happens but
i probably cried too
i think that the follower has become
sick believes
what a deal is thrilled that the
followers become sick you little [\h__\h]
oh dear oh dear wait why don't we have a
[\h__\h] janitor
ah he's a janitor okay tippy toes
i wanted to see you clean that [\h__\h] up
faster look they're already
ah bedrest
broken
please take care of yourself man
dude
okay now he's cleaning properly
[Music]
okay
janet are not doing a good job here what
the [\h__\h] there's so much
unacceptable it's like even filthier
than before when we had a jan when we
didn't have a janitor
so
what the hell
what's up with that
also i still have so many mushrooms and
i can't cook with them so what am i
supposed to do with them i went to the
mushroom guy
and
fulfilled his quest
maybe if i go again now he'll take he'll
take some more mushrooms off of my hands
maybe i should go there again
i'm hungry
i know i have a ritual that unlocks it
yeah oh oh um oh grand shelter
or should we go for something else first
maybe the refinery
station tool i was away yes yes yes a
hundred times yes
yes
forever
no patty why don't you go to sleep i see
her at the top left trying to build
something oh man
oh no
patty
no patty i want to talk to daddy
it cutie patootie
who is it maybe it's not patty
you you are tired
me
i don't want to interrupt you
sorry
sorry go go go sleep
i just want to take care of you we're
married after all
but she have the nose
no i gave it to someone else i gave it
to garfield
okay
uh
if we make some food then i think we're
ready to go
holy [\h__\h] i'm really not lacking any
food now huh
oh wait no we're not ready to go i need
to do the farm
wait a second
that's exactly what i sound like when i
eat
noise noise
hell yeah
now i wanna
put some more of those here
uh
is that
that's within the scarecrow but is it
also living
[Music]
here i think so
maybe we should
is that
is that covered
wait ah there's i couldn't see because
they didn't build it yet
okay
there is a lot to pay attention to yeah
i didn't give the bone knuckles to
anyone yet no
i should
that's not in farm range oh [\h__\h]
i can move it
i'll just move it
huh
look at them being all
really really good workers
sorry tangent go on
okay so that is not in range
why is this book
janitor
just like the janitor and scrubs
barely does any work
okay let's edit this um
okay i might need to build another
scarecrow
or
another farming thing here so we can
make use of this area
[Music]
i'll just build another scarecrow i
think
question is where do i put it
[Music]
probably like here
hold up
maybe even lower because otherwise
i'm not making proper use of
this because the scarecrows area will
also overlap but maybe i shouldn't think
too much about it
okay i'll just put it here
hi kara hello
[Music]
dana is going to watch more scrubs did
she say so when did she say that
oh yeah maybe i don't know is there
anything i can talk about about the
sports festival sports festival it was
almost like a sports festival
but it was a summer festival minecraft
summer festival
yeah i don't know what to say i streamed
it so you guys already know pretty much
what happened and what i thought of it
but um
um it was kind of
so out of nowhere right and i wanted to
be more involved the only thing
like
we weren't
notified uh about like hey you can build
something a while ago
but that kind of was like drowned out i
guess a little bit
um
and
yeah
[Music]
i'll do this give me money
yeah it meant
a lot to her she said i heard i heard
holy [\h__\h] that's a lot of money
oh my god was that like a hundred
[Music]
640 coins
for just a little bit of faith
damn
and we just bring that back up with a
bonfire ritual
what
circumvents
you
oh my god
i i expect i expected like a hundred or
so not that much
wait
crown could i do something here so cool
down okay
wow now i don't need to
be so
cheap about buying things anymore
wow
that was nuts
but if i do
do they always give that much or it's
just because i did it the first time and
like if i do it i'm too close to one
another they won't give me that much
maybe
i wonder
but wait until canada finishes the bill
tree that ritual will become useless
what
oh
i'm garfield i help you no i want to
help you
well let me help you oh i couldn't help
you
garfield working all night
wait let me
uh
let me inspire you
yeah
i feel like
you get money instead of devotion points
i guess because then you don't need
devotion anymore
when you already have everything filled
out
i see i see
you know what i think i'll go on a
crusade now do they have enough food
just let me leave some food and then
then we go to the last crusade
hi oh it's already daytime okay
i thought i could sneak away in the
middle of the night without them
noticing
yeah i should get a demon
maybe send someone on a missionary to
[Music]
medium level medium level let's send
koduka
[Music]
for some lumber thank you unknown for
the pinky
thank you
and then we'll get
uh
i kinda want the same one again
it's not bad if i always use the same
one
it's got the ink on them
because i only have one of those of this
type
oh he seems to
enjoy it or at least not dislike it
okay no negatives okay
let me just do a sermon and then we'll
go
oh we do have someone old let me
sacrifice them they must have turned old
just recently
yeah get their level up that's that's
true yeah yeah should aim for that um
okay ritual
it's time for another death hooray
oh [\h__\h] i'm lacking
i'm lacking two bones
two
hey wait oh
but when i'm gone for too long
no that's not good so let me
let me just go quickly into one of those
and then leave again
after i get
two bones
yeah
oh hello
you're gone beast find satisfaction
elsewhere you will not cross the
threshold of my temple i will i will
though
yeah just keep on waiting for me go read
a book or something it will take a
little bit but uh
don't have my please
bones please
oh there we go one one boom
another one we could already leave
right i was only missing two
i think
did i go
let's just i'll just move on a little
bit
i have to
oh [\h__\h] brilliant
did i read it wrong
oh
i need 37 oh they are okay
[Music]
guess i'll stay here longer
okay thanks for paying attention guys
nine bones if
it comes together quite fast so
it's okay
audition for the stream now thank you
for watching
yeah
what else can we talk about
popcorn i think i pretty much said
everything
[Music]
and then the summer festival well that
was that i don't know what to say about
it but
you know
um
i'm glad i invited elena
uh
i'm glad she was happy about it and i
understand her feeling
garfield will take the cold tomorrow and
take how much money why would you take
my why would you leave that [\h__\h]
ah tomorrow
wait can i get 37 bones before tomorrow
i don't even know uh
um wait it's day time now if i return
before the night or like during the
night it will be fine right
garfield you can't
he's probably sick of me and like
overworking him too much
which is understandable i guess
[Music]
don't go how dare you
11 bones
[\h__\h] hell
god damn it 14 bones
bones speed run
16 bones
i think it could be imaginable i think
18 there you go
it's pretty fast
it's it's not impossible
must be a monday
no
ow
this room is huge
it'll take ages to gather everything
me your bums give me a bounce
put every bones in here too probably not
right
um
24 24
would you visit the horror uh the
whorehouse i did visit it like um
last year
uh yeah
unfortunate that we couldn't go there
this time but like it i think i would
have had to wait like two hours or so
yeah
oh hi
oh [\h__\h] sorry caramel is always
frightening of the red crown yes beer
made a coward of him oh shimmer it's
yeah karma told me to kill you instead
my door is next to be knocked upon knock
knock the lamp comes to raise end of
day's end of days
alright so you good with me
killing you first oh interesting
what
interesting enemies
oh on it
what
oh there's more
out
out maybe this is like a little bit of a
preview of what the
the fight with shamu rub will be like
okay easy
another necklace
flower nickel smaller generating
devotion faster okay
cool i'm kind of stressed out like right
now so can we go faster
oh i like that one
faster
it's still daytime right no it's night
time
i don't want garfield to leave
i'm gonna go [\h__\h] it i think um this is
more urgent
i can't i can't let garfield go
i can't let garfield go because like if
someone dies like at least i can revive
them but if someone just leaves i can't
get them back
shut them up
garfield garfield covered where are you
where where garfield goldfield
government garfield
paddy [\h__\h] garfield garfield
garfield
wait i can just choose from the prison
right garfield
for the sake of our love
i do not allow you to
leave you will you will thank me later
you
i love you
how can you descend against me
you
can't i came back early just for you and
then patty what do we do about you i
need
i need me some bones
can you survive a little bit longer
please
what is it
skeptics and heretics have made their
way to account cursing a way of life
they want to join should we welcome them
ah
sure
i can just send them directly to prison
oh it's an elephant fox
fatty tea
okay
hello
normally the the menu should come up did
my game crash
oh we'll wait we're late
[Music]
ah this is a known bug
uh well it saved when i came back right
from the crusade probably did it
wait is there auto save
was there an auto safe
there's all the safe right okay thank
god
it's just oh the time passes by okay
okay okay what the [\h__\h]
i have to kill kill the game once
game ah steam was unable to sync your
cult of lamp saves with the steam cloud
if you play now you may not have
previous game progress and you may
permanently lose it
what
play anyway cancel
[Music]
should i click play anyway
it's okay i'll just
it's probably fine right
i'll just have to redo the part where i
imprisoned um
garfield
[Music]
cancelling
[Applause]
oh this never happened to me before
that happens when you start the game
device oh [\h__\h] no
no
please
67 it's at least not the same as um when
i started today
where does this leave us
ah this dude is new yeah yeah now we
just need to find
uh bring angry holy [\h__\h] look at the
face oh no he's already here yeah bye
nobody look at my face what the [\h__\h] is
going on
hey was it like this when i came back
how could how could it get that long
while i was on the crusade for only a
little bit
and not enough beds
yeah we'll bring it back up
um
this won't give faith but i don't wanna
oh wait no we do have ah
ah for all these i need
wait i can do this one
break wash yes yes i need to do it
anyway and it doesn't need bones
oh thank god oh this comes in the right
time
[Music]
thank
i god shocked
now they're
brainwashed but that's just
normal it's fine
which one do we go for now
we can max out one of them
[Music]
greetings from germany
hallie hello guten abbent
afterlife
maybe that's good because i plan on
killing someone now
read the phone is a great building
gained two faith when followers grave at
the grave unlocks the natural burial
building the corpses of dead followers
may return to the earth by becoming
fertilizer
oh
but if that happens can i even revive
them if they become fertilizer
i guess we would go for this one no
[Music]
i picked the left one
you can't still
silver wipe down
no
yes
yeah this one brings me faith
i won't say anything bad about this
while this may have a chance of um not
reviving them used grave and respect
elders basically never had faith
problems
wait great you mean grief wait which one
do you mean this one right oh yeah yeah
okay okay
okay
getting two faith when follows grief at
the grave
okay
yeah i think they need proper grape
stones anyway
whatever whatever both are fine both are
fine
[Music]
okay
look at them
uh wait you guys are inside of one
another but one of you oh both of you i
want to talk to both of you
you have a quest
sure
wait i didn't listen return to sozo
ah
what
was that
what did i do for you
i don't remember
oh
ah
something yeah what did i do what did i
do
and now we can do this too
oh my god what do i do next oh should i
get one of those two bottom ones
or
all the grand shelters
[Music]
which all cool down
second form
already have that one what do you mean
tier 2 missionary
harvest
[Music]
oh no i don't have it yet
i'll go for a tier 2 demonic circle
okay next time next time i go for the
grand shelter
but right now i'm enjoying the demonic
circle quite much because it saves my
ass whenever i get the hammer
i hate the hammer
saves my butt do you not want to sleep
did i re-educate you
no
[Music]
yeah it's a backup plan
they can fight for me
what else what else what else what else
what else what else
oh i can upgrade it like this
nice i like the upgrading function
instead of having to build a new thing
from scratch it just lets you upgrade
this so easily
i like that
my crops are empty what the heck
okay we go
to
sozo where was so-so
who was sozo ah the
mushroom guy right
oh mushrooms boy grateau
maybe he'll give me another
way of using my mushrooms
yeah i did it
you did it didn't you you tasted the
power of the mushrooms yes you were just
like sothos those who knows you are a
friend
here you must take this aside our
friendship between two lovers of men
decide mushroom keep it safe you can
trust no one alright
[Music]
thank you oh that was the last piece i
needed finally
the reason why i got a missionary other
than the shelter is that they cost a lot
it takes time for our refinement
uh-huh
oh
i wish to give you something you're
starting to symbolize your
under-inauguration for the mental side
mushrooms and their limitless potential
flavor flour
[Music]
oh show your shoulder and grant you one
last gift
that's always there always replaces
dance not like those liars are out there
cute
i like him
total my friend
wait now that i have so much money
i want the gold flooring oh but wait
building that does it also take a [\h__\h]
ton of money
but then later
we will have so much money right
i want this pack this will be the path i
choose for my
cult
gold we walk upon nothing but gold
this is our way of life
okay i think we can go back
can i
um
change this path to the golden one all
of this or does this stay
as dirt
let me test it
ah this
ah this kind of stays like that the
middle part but this we can change
wait what does it need anyway
wait what are the materials that it
needs it doesn't say
wait
it doesn't need anyone
it's just the first
time payment
oh
what a deal
what a deal then i thought this would
cost me so much
[Music]
oh i can go like this
oh
wonderful
i wish it wouldn't go so zig exactly i
wish i could do like
half placements
but okay
it doesn't look as fancy as i thought it
would be
ah
move that one
let's have this oops whole thing
on gold there we go
ah if i go diagonal here like this
it looks
nice
oh no
i have fallen into the decoration
uh rabbit hole
at least it's easier to place than an
animal crossing
okay there you go that looks okay
perhaps one more here ah
oh like this that looks good that looks
good
and then
how to be effective and efficient
there you go
uh maybe it's easier yeah with the mouse
this one might actually be easier with
the mouse
e oh no
no i don't know how to
it doesn't work i thought i just could
click on each tile but no
not quite that easy
whatever i just do like this
come on come on
the more i look at this the less i like
it
[\h__\h]
no
it's nice right it will it'll make you
feel
warm when you walk on the golden path
it's the golden bath
should there be gold in the
here nah
it's the golden path guys
it was meant to be
i should
on this whole map
i should build the golden path guys
as an homage to tunic
left right up down right left left up up
right left down up up down down
oh no
okay for now that will do for now
it's nice it looks like pineapple
i still remember it perfectly yes of
course everything i just said was
according to the golden path
looks somewhat decent
you're a little [\h__\h] aren't you
i love pineapple yeah it's a pineapple
path
make some food
[Music]
oi i wouldn't mind going for some
pineapple pizza right now but
i'm gonna eat
spaghetti tonight spaghetti
[\h__\h] patty patty i forgot wait wait wait
wait patty don't die yet it will have
actually no never mind if she dies now
they're all brainwashed so it will have
no effect on them
it actually doesn't quite matter
i don't need to stress out about it now
let me get you in here though
um
oh
fake polka
you wear the second poker
well you're not the right one i'll make
you yellow
i believe the corpse sacrifice won't
leave of course true true true
it'll make them throw up
if they see the corpse
hey polka's dissenting oh yeah right
that was the quest wasn't it
in prison go go off you go
[Music]
that finger sign reminds me i wanted to
tell you guys of something
nami mama taught me
um a pose
with your fingers
while we were in korea like taking
photos and stuff
that i have never heard about well you
guys probably haven't heard about it
either
triggered why are you sleeping oh not
enough not enough [\h__\h] sorry sorry oh
my god really
oh yeah we have one one
less bed then we have people here you go
please
please sleep in there
although we just added a new dude now
actually it should shouldn't have been
an issue
no i didn't watch inaudible
just yet
grieve that grave very good
oh he eats first you go slave for [\h__\h]
sake
some of the
flowers
no
because also now it doesn't even matter
if i say no
i'm not gonna go on another one of those
shitty flower quests
i'll have enough
gold
go make it
for flowers no
get that idea out of your head
immediately
can i re-educate you yeah i did
[Music]
faster please
three how many was i missing
20. i have 16 okay i need four more
ah it takes so much time
[Music]
no flowers no
no
we have flowers at home
but mom
no
i say we have flowers at home they're
they're basically the same because
oh they became friends cute they're
basically the same because i got them
from there originally and then i just
put them down
no don't sleep i need the gold
can i do it i can do it too
oh no can i know
i can't actually do this one myself huh
okay i'll go out now
i'll go fight
fight fight ro-ro fight the power
we finish this last one now
they're fine right they're taken care of
i think
oh yeah
good weapon thank you
no fleece what do you mean no please
what
what oh
oh you mean the clothes ah next time
next time
okay so let me tell you
oh
the sign
she not even wants help oh i [\h__\h] you
mama told me that in korea this pose is
really popular among girls
cute girls they all do this pose when
they take a photo yeah
so
if you want to do it
reach out
your hand with the palms
facing upwards
reach it out straight
and then you make a peace sign
while still facing the palm upwards
but
oh wait how did you do it oh yeah
and
with your font and your ring finger
you connect those two
and then make it into a circle so it's
like you can look through that circle
and the piece is like
like kind of like aiming at something
like straight forward though
get it
so we did that pose several times
when we were taking photos together we
took quite a lot of photos together
it was really really nice of nappy mama
we took cute photos together i have like
i have like um printed out photos from
the photo booth and then also a lot of
photos on my phone now
you can't imagine it
can you show us
how can i show you
if i was pretty maybe but actually
um one of the fan arts i retweeted
recently had actually
a very similar or pretty much accurate
pose
um remember the garfield fan art that i
retweeted me with garfield standing
together
the pose that i did
in that image
kind of
looks like what i just explained to you
guys
if you look at it closely
so if you if you want to do
a popular pose
like a cute girl
do that one hi smokey
hi
thank you for saying hello
hey
oh crystal pillar cool
to raise my flag it would be nice if you
could um
make your own flag like an animal
crossing
korean girl peace pose oh it shows up if
you google that oh
i see
and then google that and then you know
it's the first time i ever
heard or saw
of that
peace sign i was very curious about it
oh my god
not so bad actually
ow
those [\h__\h] spikes
okay now this that's just weak chihuahua
speaking of smoothie oh recently
she's been letting me
um
brush her fur
just like
just like that
normally she didn't like it so that's
why i'm pretty
hyped about that
like for the first three years or so
she didn't like it
but now
this one i can get more than just one
yeah now now she will just let me brush
her normally if i would start brushing
her
she would like attack the brush
but ever since like three weeks ago or
so
she just lets it happen
it's fascinating
who are you smoovie
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
monkey time monkey time baby
oh thank god
oh my god
yeah anyway she really needs it because
um summertime
i mean
she she always sheds a lot but
summertime really really really really
really bad
it never ends like no matter how much i
brush her it never ends but still i need
to brush herself
good cat good cat chunkers never
mind set but smoothie just recently
started to accept it so
i'm very proud of smoothie
maybe she actually noticed that it's
better for her to let me brush her it's
not like she gets knots thankfully
but
the hair is insane
like every time i touch her she loses a
[\h__\h] ton of hair
ow
oh [\h__\h] i did i thought i had a
different attack for some reason
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
drop some there's a there's alcohol
there's alpha hugh
first time today
i need to sacrifice someone anyway uh
where's my oldie
patty
yeah old age
patty once again it's time
[Music]
once again
thank you i appreciate it i really
do oh [\h__\h] i did it wrong again
what just happened
did that
just
did he just fall in love with me that
enemy
i'm scared
what was that the heart effect
oh he got healed ah
[Music]
this one first
oh craps again
oh new weapon
stupid hammer i'm not going for the
hammer
okay yeah and enemy was gaming
now we go here
oh that was not a dead end
and the other one must have been a dead
end
that one with all the swords
oh it's all
we just got a new curse so we'll go for
one of those i'll go for a dagger
dancing
i'm getting so hungry guys
you know what we haven't eaten in a
while on stream
eating
[Music]
garlic bucket
i could make one i have garlic baguette
in the fridge
but i have to
have to um
i will have to put it in the oven it
will take a while
oh my god and then i'm not hungry enough
for dinner ow
i'm i'm so sick and tired
oh
oh [\h__\h] what am i doing
at least
those are
really stupid they kill themselves
finally ready to go for it i know you
guys really like the crunchy sound of it
oh thank god
oh garlic sounds so good doesn't it
garlic
that's for snacks now you know what
we're actually um at the end of the
crusade anyway like after this i
defeated another one of those doors
so
i think that's where i'll end it anyway
because we played for four hours
that's actually a good point to end it
and then i'll read super chats for like
one or two
hours depending on how much we have
and then i'll just eat my
all of my dinner
properly
a proper dinner
yeah it's been four hours
what
it goes by so fast
um
we have enough food we have enough wood
what's that one again
heart
empty heart too hard do i get more
hearts
because i'm so hungry oh my god
oh my stomach just made a boom sound
i'm really hungry i might not make it
maybe i need to get a snack afterwards
okay maybe i will get a snack
not right now but after the buzz
yeah i'm needed
garlic bread um
um nobody telling me what this one was
a crappy day until i started yeah that's
good i'm happy to hear that cheer up
baby
and i'm tired too why am i so tired
i got so much sleep
i lose hearts alone okay i'll just go
straight whatever no
give me that wood thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
i have to be careful
to not die to not lose so many hearts
until the boss
because i already don't have so many
hearts to begin with
these in the small spaces it's pretty
hard
to fight sometimes
the big ones too sometimes because they
um
have like a lot of obstacles often
if it's just something in between that's
the best
unless unless sometimes they only have
one enemy that's that's the best room
just one enemy
aye aye
the poison takes quite a while until it
does damage right when i walk into it
i don't really ever feel
any damage from that
yeah yeah i think something fills up the
longer i stain the poison
the higher
or the sooner i will get poisoned
more bones please more bones
and
half a heart
very nice okay
oh wow that was fast
i hope you guys enjoyed the tangents
today because now i am out of tangents
are we playing rust tomorrow
i scheduled it so that it overlaps with
cali and bales but i don't know what's
gonna happen
i don't know if people are gonna be
fighting or
what everyone will be doing i guess
callie wouldn't fight she's a peace
peace sheriff
right
i don't really know what to expect
well only one way to find out exactly
um
but
instead of having my house be destroyed
by others it would be smarter to destroy
everything on my own and then get the
scraps from you know all the things i've
been
um gathering like the weapons and so on
to
get the scraps and then build up the
tech tree even further
yeah i don't know i'll see what's
happening if maybe maybe if amma does
the derby
tomorrow at a different time when i'm
streaming then i might change my
streaming time a little bit
i gotta ask her what she's planning on
doing um
don't do this one i'm scared of the boss
fight bye-bye
i already sacrificed somebody so i don't
think i can sacrifice another
uh another cold follower while i'm here
i missed everybody
i see this again too much oh too much
going on on the screen it's hard to see
it
because of the obstacles too
look at him
at least often the grass and the stuff
here gives me back some hearts as well
hoping for overlap
well if i have to move it then i don't
know about overlap but oh yeah i guess
you mean you hope that ahmed overlaps
yeah yeah yeah but it's so it's a weird
time for amma to stream normally she
doesn't stream around that time but her
sleeping circle cycle
has been really [\h__\h] oh yeah speaking
of
when
my name was helping
uh
i'm going for this one when i was
helping i met yesterday
it was really nice we spent
like
like two hours or so
if not a little bit more
together
and um
i took the opportunity to have some
deep talk oh there's some sick people
my followers are no longer brainwashed
on y'all
[Music]
and took the chance to like have
something talk with a man
that
was really necessary for me
i really needed someone to talk um
recently i was like
urging
i was going crazy to be honest
it's cool it's going mad
uh
problem not necessarily solved but at
least i was able to talk to amit
like to someone you know
and that helped me
letting it out
yeah
no it's not really something i can talk
about
on stream um
i don't wanna
burden you guys too much
but
i'm i'm glad ahmed was
here for me
oh i think we're gonna go back to the
other room
yeah
love ahmed
she's a good listener
no hit thank god
you know
wait this is this wasn't a dead end room
oh
okay hold it this is maybe a dead end
nope okay then the other one was a dead
end
also at some point after after we were
done with our like um deep talk
anya joined the
voice chat but it was kind of weird
because
she didn't say anything she stayed muted
and just listen like for an hour until
we left and then
she left as well i was like anya anya
anya hello
anya
you know if you're talking we don't hear
you just saying
she never unmuted herself she was just
listening
elma was like oh she's probably just you
know
just like listening it listening to it
as if it's like a
asmr
a lullaby
i
am confused
she's plotting
oh i don't think she got really anything
out of it because we were only you know
talking about those cars and preparing
the cars
one of the deets
secret amateur podcast man
[Music]
i like the current one i have but these
ones are both one level higher but i
don't know it depends on the boss
if the boss spawns a lot of enemies then
this could be useful
[Music]
what
i don't know i'll go for this one
yeah
okay
yeah it's morning time for japan bros
oh oh we're already there
we're there we have arrived
wait what's the boss right behind the
door or where were there still rooms
after that
oh okay yeah okay
i see
i found you
hi
[Music]
insignificant krita you will learn your
place you do not understand lamb keep my
warning and stay away
no oh [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
he's becoming a monster even though it
already was a monster now oh my wait
that's uh what do you call isn't that
some kind of like
indian
um oh my god
okay i already regret it
[Music]
are you insane
you're insane
nice hit
where is my demon i thought do i have a
demon with me
no i don't i finally brought a demon
what
oh god
he's spawning more above those crabs but
they're really hard to find man
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] okay now it's not getting pretty
dangerous
i have to be very careful
ah no [\h__\h]
okay i don't think i'm gonna survive
this
i have a bad
feeling
just let me kill some of them maybe they
give me some
oh [\h__\h]
okay whenever i
just oh my god
i'm gonna die
what
oh leave me alone
uh
that's a lot of bullets man a lot of
enemies
oh [\h__\h] my favorite
at least i can't see it straight to my
face right now oh welcome back hi
welcome glad you made it back
no no no
no
can i
revive them then
lead i was badly injured during my
missionary i can die in peace knowing i
got to speak with you one last time
can i revive them then cause they died
here
oh what the [\h__\h] no
no
at least no one saw it
oh my god
it was so
that's so sad
i need to build it fast fast come by
this place is falling apart
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i'm not gonna wake them up yet because
they're gonna be angry if i wake them up
in the night
oh man
clean clean clean
let's cook something
holy [\h__\h] why do they i have enough beds
why do they
hate me so fast now have i been away for
that long
oh god there's a lot of sick people too
it's the scent cutie patootie is the
same thing oh god
oh listen to me
listen to me be nice
no bully please
you have to love me
otherwise i'll kill you
i'll put you in prison
it's the you know you have no choice
actually
just do it
[Music]
oh man oh dorcio
i could marry someone because um
my original marriage she's dead
let's see
not very convincing reasons
no
should i marry the one who's the most
mad at me right now
cutie patootie i love you
um
56 oh [\h__\h] they're all so old
oh oh mary
i wonder what that would do to them if
they're
dissenting
67 yeah holy [\h__\h]
i might just
sacrifice
oh wait no their age doesn't mean
they're old right now because i i
revived cutie patootie once
okay they're doing better now
oh no
oh maybe a new cape could help us with
the next boss deal double damage ooh
costs half the [\h__\h] oh
many weapon damage
and hell for half no
gain a deceased heart every time a
turret card is drawn 100 of the items
will be lost if killed
holy [\h__\h] these are all
harsh
draw four tear cuts at the start of a
run but none can be drawn after oh
at least you get like everything from
the beginning
so you're as strong as you can be from
the beginning onwards
all hearts over replaced by
1.5 the amount of blue hearts
how
um
so you can't heal them back but you get
a little bit more
i think this is the best one
they're all not like really that good
tbh
i heard people don't like the reps
because they all have down sense yeah it
would be nice to have like a little bit
of a like actual upgrade without a
downside
it doesn't have to be too
strong but like at least
you usually get more than four cards
anyway no
i don't think so i i'll go with the
white one
oh [\h__\h]
but can i
wear it now
am i wearing it oh my
i'm wearing it okay okay guys you can go
but you you're a little [\h__\h]
and then you say one bad thing about me
no the other person oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i ran out of prisons are you for real oh
god
not
someone help me build
i know um
re-educate ah he should be able to
be freed
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um release and help me immediately
help me
oh god
no no no
ah
and such a chaos here
[Music]
help me build a use of course
you couldn't possibly think that i'll do
all this alone no no no i need your help
you guys are as much
part of this
as i am
[Music]
okay that took like ages where is
everybody they're all sick
we've been talking and we're tired of
the food here we need some variety
please could you make yes yes i can
wait ocean's bounty
ah perform
ocean's bounty rachel okay i can do that
i guess
do i need to i don't need to do it now
bud can i
yeah
not sure
and i need to go fishing though
we need to make use of it
don't forget the card
what card
that's cute
there's a card at my feet
let me do that
um
i'll do this whatever
ah substance occurrence
trade all cult members will gain the
substances encouraged to trade oh okay
25 when brainwashing oh
hmm
all caught them as well gained a
prohibitionist trade was that ah
increased work speed and devotion
generation
uh increased by ten percent but fifty
percent chance of lowering the faith
uh if followers
of phil is becoming sick after oh oh
what
well then i think i would go for this
one because i like the brainwashing
ritual
yeah yeah yeah yeah
although if it already
fills up my faith and what why
and it doesn't make sense that it helps
me gain oh there you go
it helps me gain
a little bit 20 vape
oh nice
oh well
whatever
collect reward from garfield garfield
where are you
oh dear
oh boss
is albion's
i think it's back now
i just walked down here and i see one
two three four five six people are sick
wait i just need to heal them
why are six people sick
i wasn't
was this because of uh
the curse like from the boss or wasn't
that a different
one aren't they already like recovered
from that
and we're back we're back
you hurt six people
six people were freaking sick
that's why everything was going downhill
[\h__\h] don't listen to him
in prison thanks for reminding me i
forgot
okay
and i didn't re-educate you yet
feed them better food
okay
but they have no problem with uh grass
supposedly
does it make a big difference
oh you're done really
nice okay everybody's free again
finally finally
uh-huh
okay i will make some better food a
little bit
modest mixed meal
20 chance of increasing follow loyalty
wow
i'll make a couple of those
and i'll talk with you
garfield
ah love forever
oh forever
kiwawa forever
can i help everybody
oh nice
one more
oops well you know what i'll
i'll inspire you and then i'll extort
someone
there we go
okay and one more tangent
i know for you i don't have enough
flowers i'm sorry
i'm sorry
[Music]
get them some seeds
i hope we can
kill the boss on the second attempt at
least
you who are you sickle maybe i can give
you a gift
i have so many things now your loyalty
flower necklace for you
who else needs a gift sickle one tippy
toes tippy toes i never gave something
to you
a gift for you how about the skull
necklace more loyalty
triggered
i'll give something to you too
not a feather necklace
oh okay
you cute little idiot i'll give you a
big game
freak
let's go
okay if if anybody still has any
complaints
then i honestly don't know why
except maybe for this but i fixed it i
fixed it okay
where the hell is the janitor do i
always need to clean the poop house
is that really my job
okay i think i'm ready to go i'll leave
some more food there though just in case
um
cheery cauliflower chowder 25
oh wait five percent chance causing
illness really a chance of dropping
valuable resources
i mean five percent is not that high
vomiting instantly what
pooping instantly
[Music]
yeah i'll make those a good variety
everybody can choose what they like the
most
and now stop complaining
or there will be some heads rolling
can i go
no wait let me bring my let me bring it
so so so so
shall we go with this one again um i
need help i need help urgently
go fishing oh yeah okay just just a
quick
quick trip to
go fishing
uh
you have to make use of the
ritual that we did
whoa
i want to be fast so don't don't waste
too much time
nice nice nice smooth smooth smooth
oh so many
yo
that's hella good
come on
nice
fish spam literally holy [\h__\h]
oh look at those lobsters
[Music]
i never had lobster before have you guys
had lobster before
swordfish or something like that nope
nope oh most of you haven't
hate seafood yeah i don't really like it
that much either
blue fish
is that really safe to eat
lobster is delicious yes at red lobster
ah that's like a famous restaurant chain
right
crawfish
oh
that's is that like um that's the thing
i wanted to put in my aquarium that
doesn't exist yet that was a rainbow
fish or something like that what
didn't show up
it's turning night time though
ah i feel like if i don't fish all of
them then it's gonna be a waste
bye
huh i want to kill the [\h__\h] boss now
coco coco
gotta fish them all
go for the cheddar biscuits oh
honestly right now i would eat almost
anything
almost anything please i need food
where's my garlic baguette
come on come on fishy fishy fish
raw fish no preferably not
okay i'm really bad right now
come on
oh
the pain in the ass
there you go there you go there you go
there you go
oh a blueprint
only the finest dirt nice
yeah that's
that's what we needed definitely but is
that the same actually that um they use
in the middle so that could actually
match nicely to like
you know if you want every floor to be
matching and you can't change the one in
the middle
your family had lobster while you had
mac and cheese couldn't they have waited
until your dental surgery thingy was
dealt with
that's mean
as if they couldn't have had it on a
different day
hey yo
they were just trying to save some money
probably
oh no we can only eat lobster today
otherwise we'll die
it has to be today
it's destiny
it was written in my horoscope
horoscope
my main job is now not cult leader
anymore but fisherman i guess
it's holoscopes
i mean the thing that sana was
yeah doing
liked it did she ever reach um cancer
because i don't think she did
i was waiting for it
is she
i wonder she didn't do all of them right
yeah she stopped at capricorn when is
capricorn
i was like really into that because i
like um bread
i wanted her to tell me what was the
right bread for me i mean i know it's
garlic baguette but i want you to
confirm it
so i can officially marry garlic
baguette
there's so many fishing to see
literally
i think i'm gonna go now
there they keep on spawning more and
more
okay
let me check the cult and then i'll go
for fighting
now but we got a good amount of fish so
how's it going guys there's another
oldie
i see you who is that what a deal is old
no
uh oh yeah beds beds beds you think
they'll be happy about the beds
give your phone in the luxury they
deserve collective ocean while they
sleep
never collapses
all right i said i would get it so i'm
getting it
oh okay we're close to the next one
can we already upgrade them
oh they need gold to be built
interesting
i actually wanted the gold for something
else i think but oh well
oh well wait we still have one like
grass bed
good not good okay
uh wait do i have enough beds anyway
14 beds 12 people okay
okay
should be good
[Music]
oh yeah they're already killing him no
cutie patone is good hey patodi i
believe in you you did nothing wrong you
know we make mistakes sometimes i know
it's okay
we all make mistakes sometimes
and you can show that you're a good
person
by forgiving and by learning you know
the other people should be forgiving and
you should be learning
learn about your mistakes
and do better
a trip to jail so spoof
no preferably not
we don't preferably we don't want to
have to do that you know
uh
curse or merciless weapons have a chance
to deal a critical hit when attacking
enemies ooh okay
sure
don't need any more curses we have so
many curses
actually i don't need this either i
don't i want i just i i think i like
poison weapons the most
they're reliable and strong
another one holy [\h__\h] we're like it
maxing out everything
um
i'll go for law and order i don't know
it doesn't matter
loyalty in the forest perform a ritual
at your temple in which you appoint a
follower as your loyalty enforcer aka a
police offic tasked with patrolling the
cult and raising the loyalty of your
followers
there's there seems to be no downsides
to that one and then we have performed
rachel at your temple in which you
appoint a follower as you tax enforce
invoice
tasked with collecting money from other
cult members
i actually prefer this one because
money seems not so much an issue with
that other ritual that we have
um
i prefer to raise a loyalty i don't want
to extort them anymore
than we already do
i'll go for the loyalty yeah
[Music]
yeah
good
okay
and then uh if i can i would like to
sacrifice
one of the old ones
it's very sad but we have to do it we
have to do it
um
it's you what a deal
i'm sorry to say goodbye but it was nice
having you i'll have you back eventually
probably mimi
have fun in heaven
yeah great the other chickens
from me
yay
follow me tell me
okay
and with that
everyone seems happy
i just need some extra food
let me
take care of that
mighty meat fest
ooh
it oh
i thought there might be some wait
delicious fish fest oh
yummy i thought there might be a
follower meat in there but it doesn't
look like it unless wait is that
follower meat the steak no right
dropping valley for research
oh
chance of a sick fall recovering from
illness when nobody's sick right now but
what else do we have poultry pumpkin
causing illness diarrhea
increasing there you go not oh wait
oh
it just has one star
i'll go for this
how's that should i make more ah
[\h__\h] don't eat that don't eat that
no
what a waste
my brother and i were traveling together
for dark no
no that took me so long last time
i'll do it but i'll do it off screen
after killing the boss i hope i hope i
have enough time
um
i'll make a bit more
just just a tiny bit
okay can i go now can i go now there's
always so much to do oh wait let me let
me just talk to
you
i already did it today okay
okay okay
clean up the poop houses okay ready to
go
ready to rumble
nice
i love you
good job
all right here we go
i can have two demons oh did i
i thought it would autumn ah
okay okay okay okay okay
how do i make one more just do i just
get two of those
i don't have to make another one of uh
[Music]
i don't have to upgrade it maybe
here i don't have enough wood right now
whatever it's okay one one should be
good help
hopefully i will try to speed through it
a little bit we don't need to
get all the ingredients and all that
one nice weapon to start off with oh
there you go use the four cards
[Music]
okay
could be better see uh this way you
don't even get a choice that's the
downside you get the four cards right
at the beginning so you might be
somewhat stronger than you could be
don't believe but
you know
you can't choose
[Music]
it's okay
i don't want to lose my heart
okay
you have to be careful
speed run
yeah
oh did i talk with you guys about the
new
game of friends episode
i think i guess i tweeted about it
oh
i tweeted that i really liked it more
than the first episode definitely
i'm also getting used to the faces of
the actors that i said before that i
didn't like much
ah
i'm getting used to them
um
wait so now i don't need to go into the
rooms with the
cards are they automatically different
rooms now
oh
[\h__\h] those enemies are free of them
for real
he killed him i need to kill that dude
first where is he where did he go did i
kill him
i didn't okay
oh my heart
maybe there's a heart room maybe we get
to go for a a hot room
that would be nice a terrible show but
don't expect too much
yeah i have
i'm not as critical you know as other
people maybe
i'm fine
um
i i mean it was it could have been
better the episode could have been
better er i guess it could be considered
a little bit boring
oh but
overall
i liked the moment with the
you know uh what was her name
and there's too many names to remember
and i feel like they were easier to
remember in game of thrones
what's the main character
me can't just name the girl
what's your name
oh [\h__\h] on the same
yeah when she was like
she showed up with her dragon you know i
don't really think this is a spoiler
because there's not it's not too
meaningful
well it doesn't really matter i think
but but i thought it was
that was a good moment
good moment
spawn me some hearts please
[Music]
already not going very ideal
okay i don't care i don't care i don't
care
i'll pass on this one yeah one of the
issues we play the game of friends
travel stuff meaning
anything and people just started
appearing where they need to be oh yeah
i never really
thought of it like that or like
um
[Music]
yeah i don't know
yeah
we should go for a path where we don't
have to fight that much but i guess it's
always the same
unless like this could be a fight you
know
ah this one
no that's also a fight
it's always at least two fights
and i'll go
i'll go for that one
i don't care whatever here's one two
really what
on the second path from the left
god damn it
there was no actual healing room though
and that shop is not healing
the chakram is not healing though
as far as i know
oh well okay
in the end we will have to fight no
matter what let's just hope we get some
easy rooms out of this
[Music]
yeah
and yeah i think they just um change the
turret rooms
[\h__\h] they change the targets into enemy
rooms or just get rid of them completely
because there was no no card room
there was a heart symbol
isn't that just um
you know the one where you lose hearts
or so for
exchange of something
else
oh thank god the heart
anyway it doesn't matter
i'm really excited for more of gamer
phones and i'm really excited afterwards
we have the new
lord of the rings spin off which people
say will not be good but i don't care
it's better than nothing that's my
my way of thinking
better than nothing
think positively guys
yeah nice i think i did that with no
damage
nothing is vented that's not true really
hot rings of power me too
i think the trailer was nice
ah
[\h__\h] hell
i got hit twice by that sucker
[Music]
i recorded me
ah it's not looking good guys
not looking good but at least
if i die during the boss fight and don't
die until then i can still sacrifice
someone so just try to not die at least
my one mission
can't be that hard
[Music]
nice explosion
okay okay okay
i i still don't quite know if the hearts
only spawn
um
when you're low on hearts because i feel
like that's what's happening but i'm not
sure
because i feel like i see more hearts
around
spawning when i'm low on hearts
i really don't know
nice this is like almost like a practice
for the boss fight ow
okay
hallelujah
sometimes games do that yeah i'm just
not sure but i think i think that's the
case um
our drops seem to be pure rng in my
experience really
that would be fine too i would like to
fill up my hearts even though i'm not
that low on them
with the amount of rooms that we've been
having i think they get rid of the card
rooms completely and not uh
replace them
okay we have necromantic gauntlet
ooh summon a ghost
i'll go for that one
some of the ghosts more more things to
attack with always welcome
and more cauliflower which i absolutely
hate
thanks i guess
okay
oh [\h__\h] i didn't realize
uh what kind of room is that it had like
a skull ah
double gold enemies drop poison oh no
i should have chosen a path with a
normal
room
[Music]
but okay the poison in itself is not
that bad it's just kind of yeah by that
every [\h__\h] enemy has it now
oh god
but so far i've always been dealing
quite well with the poison
ah
[Music]
let's just stay out of its way guys
it's still doable yeah
oh
they don't release ah they just drop it
after they die
oh yep yep just when they die okay
at least it's not like in between
the fight
holy [\h__\h] okay that's that's a bit of a
problem uh
um
okay
nope it's fun
there we go wasn't so bad it wasn't so
bad don't be scared
[Music]
nice it's a nice chain reaction yeah
okay
it's definitely like progression is way
faster
when i already have the tarot cards
it's saving me quite a bit of time
ah
there you go
you're doing good thank you
i like all the ornaments for your
avatars now
what what ornaments
i mean
you mean the things the png's i stick to
myself
i like them too it's fun
actually just today they they made an
update that kind of improved
the whole function
even more
um i didn't get the update yet though i
didn't update my
my program
it's not really something that you guys
will notice though i think but for us
it's improved
um
this okay now that i know the boss i
know that this will be helpful because
he spawns so many [\h__\h] enemies i'll
go with that london
and i can kill the crabs
no it's not about the lag
make it easy to stick to specific that's
exactly it actually
yeah so you guys won't really notice but
we will have to struggle less
what i still i'm hoping for is um
that we can stick something to our backs
like behind our models that would be
nice and also i want to be able to stick
like
uh animations gifs gifs
always say twice so no one complains
onto myself because that's
not
possible
yet
good demon
who's a good demon you're a good demon
who's a good demon
no no just
[\h__\h] off
those are pretty annoying when the room
is so
pretty big
so far
okay
okay wait so the other room is maybe
where dead end rooms so i'll check him
out even though maybe i should just
ignore them
so we get through it faster it's not
like i'm getting exp out of it
i'm only getting damaged
ooh weapons though yeah yeah yeah yeah
i will take the sword as a chance to
heal the wheel oh
what
there you go using life force of a slain
phone hell yeah if i kill all the crabs
then we might get some
[Music]
uh health back that's a good combination
i think
and you know what i won't go up up there
i will not
i already got the weapon the other room
will not have
a weapon
oh fast
okay
[Music]
a good amount of health
combined with the current weapons
we might be fine but i might still [\h__\h]
up in that case i'll just do it
off-screen probably
okay
focus shoot your shield
thank you
thank you thank you guys
oh god
already got here
ah he's starting with his bullets now
about going well so far i think
going to save distance out did he hit me
now they're going they're going oh god
oh
[\h__\h]
the projectiles went not towards the the
crabs
oh
leave me alone please
oh god oh my god
yo this bus is really tired
is my demon still there
should be there yeah yeah okay oh
[Music]
oh
no one's old i think but
[\h__\h] that's really tough
that's really tough
oh broccoli
gives me so much he wouldn't be mad
right
it gives me like six hearts
sorry gotta be you i'll revive your
promise broccoli my my
[Music]
no mercy
no mercy for me
i don't know what's going on right now
oh wait he's almost dead yeah
maybe i didn't need to sacrifice bro
cooley what what we're already so close
to killing him
oh i didn't even use the hearts bro
cooley
oh
[Music]
i will
make it up to you i'll marry you again
i'm so sorry
but we made it
a brick floor nice won't use it though
yeah berkeley is strong because of um
him eating all the broccoli
he used to be another one of those
bosses
no
that's why he's so strong
oh there's another thing
his sacrifice was not in vain i don't
know about that
because like
it wasn't really much of use i could
have just gone with a different
one that doesn't give me as many hearts
but oh well
let me take what we can get
his love
was so strong you know
it made me even stronger
oh [\h__\h]
wow finally finally finally
damn
that was a tough boss
oh
[Music]
i was always a coward this land is a
better place now his pathetic sniveling
carcass is nothing more than a moon of
rotting flesh
soon i shall be freed and the world
remade in my image
all will pledge themselves to the cult
all will bow to my name
i have a feeling i will eventually have
to fight him huh maybe he's the last
boss oh
suffering shall turn to tree triumph
that which one sits perish what what
something like that
hey how mad are you guys at me now
on the scale of one to ten please don't
be mad yeah i got the heart celebrate
celebration
oh look at this looks it looks pretty
good
the faith is very high still
hallelujah must have been the food and
the beds yeah
he did say that there's only one who can
carry that crown
and by that time i'll be so so power
hungry this little crazy lamp
will be so power hungry
that uh i cannot accept
being under him beneath him i want to
revive berkeley immediately
i feel really bad about it
we're cooley
you served me well in your past life
don't worry your new life starts
immediately
with sugani
forgot to say
are we still married now i wonder
she's correct that's crazy
i feel a good song
pretty easy to read if that's the case
not so difficult okay we can get
once a day eat a meal uh to receive oh
oh
to receive a blue heart receive a
deceased heart on the at the beginning
of each ah
i mean both are like pretty similar
it doesn't matter i'll go for the
deceased heart first
yeah that wasn't broccoli
oh [\h__\h] i had two huh
okay i'll get the other one also
soon soon
now i'm on cool down
did i get berkulli in that berkeley
junior well if you think about it
berkulee has been waiting longer so
it's only fair
[Laughter]
maya okay next i will go for
possessions
we're almost maxed everything
seiko architecture trade all club
members will gain the same when when a
new building is constructed game plus 5
faith
any building
uh gain more faith when delivering a
sermon oh
both are good
no downsides
because we're still like building a lot
of things but
at some point we'll stop building things
i guess
but at that point we'll probably also
stop playing the game
i'll go for this one yeah
yeah more sermons than building things
yeah
that is true
i'm so hungry
[Music]
nice to have you back i guess uh
some money i demand though for reviving
you
loyalty rewards once again
starting all over
cooley you want a necklace
oh i don't have a necklace but i have a
gift welcome back
so let me catch you up on how things
have been here
i think that things have been kind of
crazy but uh people still love me i'm
still the cult leader deal with it you
better love me or else
also inspire you
yeah you've got the whole full program
what is this why is this one
i can receive it like oh there you go
oh
nice
cool stuff okay
um
[Music]
i guess that's
it for today
i'll still be like cleaning up a little
bit and making food
magnificent mixed meal
splendid vegetable feast isn't that the
one that we needed for a quest
yo look at all those gorgeous meals that
we can do now where did all those come
from
wait
oh
[\h__\h] yeah these need more skill
okay i'm so sorry i [\h__\h] up these
precious meals
ah look at those
[Music]
from fishing
i don't have that quest anymore though
or is it just um
[Music]
there's only a certain amount that can
be displayed there
you're good bro
hitbox very small hill
i failed it
yeah
that's okay
that's okay i guess
maybe that was one of the reasons why my
faith was so low momentarily
um
[Music]
okay
the fishing thing is not active anymore
right
[Music]
that's actually good i might do that off
screen again
if i play again
five percent causing illness i don't
like that
yeah but i have to use these ingredients
maybe not so many
yeah
hi
okay
what else can i do before i go
re-educate you
[Music]
i had a girlfriend that managed to burn
fish sticks once mmm fish sticks i loved
those when i was a child i don't think i
would still like them now but i don't
i don't make them anymore i feel like
back in the day you know my mom heard
certain
certain foods that she would make uh
sometimes when she didn't want to cook
one of those was
those fish sticks and then another one
was obviously frozen pizza
gotta love the frozen pizza
the easy foods fish sticks pizza i think
that exists doesn't it
oh i don't think i would like it though
but now i really want fish sticks [\h__\h]
i don't have fish sticks right now
oh you're enlightened aren't you buddy
let me talk to you
i love frozen pizza too
who doesn't
do we have any one of you like working
in a janitor station yo
i don't know i would hope so
okay uh
i'll send someone out too
91 for meat
oh broccoli
i'll send you up for some meat bye bye
i don't want to stop playing but i'm
hungry and i need to read super chat so
we're going to end it here
we are going to end it here whether i
like it or not
wait we're almost we're almost there
[Music]
more devotion
two more
devote yourself to me
do it
fish fingers yeah fish fingers
oh thank you fly white guy thank you
thank you
very sweet
nice and what a nice way to end the
stream isn't it killing the boss and
then upgrading to cult
uh four level four okay tempo is trying
it gets even bigger
this is the last upgrade we get
apparently
like for call twice
everyone gather
work
quack quack quack quack
wow that looks cool
oh final stains
[Music]
it's our anthem
quick quack
[Music]
this kfp is anthem yeah
i can't stop working
ah dossier
i need to stop
someone stop me
this game is so addicting
like there's never an end to it
it's like
kitty kitty really really idi a good
balance uh where it's getting not too
much work although sometimes it feels a
little bit like it but it's a good
balance where
you
i always have something to do
in this game that's a good thing
so
yeah i'll do i'll do that one off screen
hopefully i'll make it in time
could be kitty enough time
yeah
[Music]
no
okay
i'm so hungry okay what do i do
hope i get this gonna be too much
because then
i can't eat my dinner properly what else
do i have i'll go look for something
really quick
and then and then
i'll see you guys in my office okay
um
slice it in half
no i don't know it's like
packaged
like the full thing is packaged and when
i open the package then i think i should
make the whole thing
if anything
thank you for watching so far you're
welcome to stay until i'm done with
reading super chats
you're welcome or you must well well
well
i'll leave that judgment up to you
you know what the right decision is
don't you
[Music]
already
foreign
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
she
[Applause]
[Music]
me
and pulling me
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
moving on
yummy
[Music]
um
there's no such fingers too loud you
know tony yeah
that's right
[Music]
where am i
one more bite
[Music]
ah
you guys hear the music
because i don't but
you should be hearing it
okay good
now
i was just a small piece of toast with
some cheese and some salami on it
just a quick snack to survive
what's going on in my dms
genma told me the communist song is
called
good to know
i sang it fully in my karaoke before
i think it was archived so if you want
to hear it
then go listen
[Music]
okay
okay okay what else is there anything
else important no
no
okay
then we shall read subjects does anybody
remember where i'm supposed to pick up
empty
empty yeah
including that one or starting after
that one
the sound is really nice
the sound of these keys is really nice
i'll give you that you know i was kind
of expecting it to feel like those
um like the cheaper older keyboards with
the chunky
[Music]
keys but
it does feel different although i
haven't had a keyboard like that in a
long time
but i think it feels different
yeah i guess because it's a mechanical
keyboard and that's why it's so heavy
huh i don't know anything about this
kind of stuff but
i finished unique fun okay okay okay
then i think i understand
where's me
[Music]
you guys like my hat my cult hat
i like it
it's gorgeous
this one looks like it has a machined
face so it's made out of metal
could be
it's [\h__\h] heavy
cute hat
thank you
looking good
good
i would have been shocked if you said
anything else
and he supports the hat um addiction
okay let's start james lovely says uh
with a pinky
uh hey tantra just caught up on a number
of your what so i'm a little late saying
this i'm sorry if it's already been
addressed but the portfolio's the unit
is better than none take it from an
aussie who knows
thank you i looked into it again and i
still um because of several reasons
think it's
not a good idea so far as long as i have
the
fan on next to me
i can survive and also it's pretty much
september now so one more month of
suffering but i think in september
it should be
cooling down recently it's been cooling
down anyway outside too
it's just kind of weird that in my
apartment it's always hotter than
outside even when throughout the whole
night
i i have the windows open
like when i have the windows open it
cools down but the moment i close them
it's [\h__\h] hot again like i don't know
how
but yeah
um
it's gonna be worse every year well yeah
maybe next year i'll think about it and
you know eventually i want to buy a
house too but i'm not sure like
i kind of think i would wouldn't buy a
house
until after i'm done with holo so that
might still take a long time
um but for now i'll survive it i'll
survive it who knows maybe next
year
i'll just
rent
an airbnb with air conditioning or go
for free months to like i don't know
sweden or
uh
i don't know finland
yeah just go somewhere else another rent
my rents out my apartment as an airbnb
yeah make some money from it
and i have to cup of coffee
that's a bit too cold
oh
welcome to caffeine yeah
movie and chocolates will take oh [\h__\h]
yeah that's that's that's a problem
that's the problem
i can't go overseas for three
months that would not be too good and
although if it's like i don't know
germany or something and i go by car or
by train then taking my cats is still
manageable i would say
[Music]
i guess i can go
a little bit north with my cats
not germany i mean more north north
north
yeah germany was just random example
germany is not really cooler than
austria no no no no
no no no
high up in the alps oh
yeah
go up in an airbnb in the mountain
but you know what about the internet i
doubt that the internet will be good
there ah
[\h__\h]
that would have been nice would have
been a good idea
very relaxing but
we already have [\h__\h] internet in general
in austria
um so when you go up on the mountain
it's gonna be even worse
i can't bring my own internet it's like
stuck here it's not like portable
a good night
hope you have sweet dreams
i've been having so many nightmares
i think it's like people have been
telling me that when you sleep in a very
hot environment
that um
it's it uh adds to the nightmares
and that could have been a thing and
besides that i've also been generally
just
very stressed out and like had a lot of
worries on my mind
that contributed to
the dreams
i think it was a combination of that
last night i had the
um i had my room pretty chill
and all that and you know it was after i
talked with ahmed so maybe that's a
reason why i didn't have a night oh wait
i
i wouldn't quite call it a nightmare but
it wasn't also necessarily a good dream
either i remember
i was like shopping at azara
and while i was inside the whole
building was like falling apart like it
was several floors and i was up pretty
high and i had to escape
i had to get out of the building while i
was falling apart everything was like
falling down on me
that's interesting normally my
nightmares arm
and have been recently always like me
being chased by
something
some like people several people
sometimes just one person but it's
always like a chase and
they want to kill me usually
the usual sour dream no not really the
use of lemons
that was not a good dream but i when i
woke up i didn't feel as upset about it
as
the other times and last time it was
it was weird it was like a a really pale
big
um
[Music]
a bold guy i think he was wearing like a
suit or something
but really big like the the statue
statue is
was really broad and
big
like not thin maybe b i don't know what
slenderman looks like
that's yours that's short
very very big it looked more like
[Music]
similar to
well maybe not
it was kind of scary
like a hitman yeah
yeah scary scary
and it was
i was looking into like dream
explanations and i thought it was
interesting that there was a difference
between
being chased in general
and then being chased in a game
like you dream about being chased and
that's inside a game which i thought was
interesting because
that specific dream with the bald guy
i was actually
in my mind i was in a game for part of
it but then it kind of got blurry and
then somehow it felt like more reality
but it was like um
it felt like uh
uh like he was an
enemy
and i
could fight him
but he was too strong and too high level
so i started running away but he kept on
chasing me down a narrow
corridor
um
how often do you remember your dreams
after waking up
normally only when it's nightmares
the other ones i quickly forget
but the other ones were not games the
other ones were just normal normal
normal chasing dreams were
trying to kill me often in these
situations
it's really weird that i can actually
fly
like in a desperate situation of being
chased i i
i try to run away so hard that i
kind of start like you know flying
slightly
and
but it's like
it doesn't work so well like it's hard
to control
and i fail
in like very critical moments
it's very stressful
when they
get like really close to me that's when
i seem to have problems with
like flying away hmm
well me and my dream i run so slow
but also when you're being chased or
what
[Music]
no i didn't talk about my dreams of amen
no no
though
in my head from that damn nothing about
that's cute it's suffering i hate those
dreams like
like if it was just a dream about flying
that would be fine but it's me trying to
escape in a really really really
dangerous situation
um
yeah it's always right on your heels
yeah
[Music]
yeah i mean i read like what the
nightmare explanation means mean and um
i could say that a lot of it feels very
accurate
um
yeah but
it's getting
not like the situation is getting better
but my mind i'm i'm i'm calming calming
down again maybe
um
i don't know
think about other things yeah
i just die in my dreams
that's
like that
i never get to that point i never
actually die
that's terrifying
it's it always stops like kind of right
where
they reach me i guess
thankfully
i wake up when i die you always wake up
before you actually yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i would think so
anyways we're super chats huh i only
read one
already had like a 30 minute tangent
let's go
falling dreams
[Music]
rainbow
wow
thank you
hi girl my birthday is on the 26th but i
had a bad one in this year i lost my
bird last week she was a java sparrow i
took one last look at her before she was
cremated cremated cremated
on the 18th when i held her body in my
hands i felt cold when she was alive i
felt she was a little
eater warming my hands now i just feel a
cold body
i had a dream while i was sleeping that
same day that someone was blaming me for
not taking care of her now i'm trying to
get used to being without her and taking
care of my other birds oh you still have
other ones at least that's something
but well i can imagine you know birds
probably don't have a very
long lifespan especially the smaller
ones that you can keep at home
so please don't blame yourself
it's
how long do they live with two three
five six years
it can't be that long don't blame
yourself it happens it's a circle of
life you know
don't worry about it
i'm sorry that happened though
well happy belated birthday
thank you for the beautiful rainbow
please cheer up you still have this bird
right here
me
i
hopefully will outlive you
so yeah
i wish you the best take care of your
birds but don't blame yourself okay and
cheer up please
please
your birds love you i'm sure
it's nice that you have pets pets are
awesome
get some some love some fluffy
warm
warming
love from the other birds well yeah
as i said i know i know some surely live
longer but the smaller ones i can't
imagine they live that long
yeah thank you for the rainbow
happy birthday to you
happy birthday even if it's
happy birthday blue tien
yeah
congratulations
sorry for being late
myself to read this sorry
yeah got a duncan
felix
oh it's been such a long time since i
saw your name i think
he's still here
thank you for the red super chat oh
glorious kiara we praise thy name mother
of us all be bowed before thee all in
the kitchen your thighs clean all in the
fryer goes our meat
i'll hand piano we shall be one to eat
thank you
beautiful
you should be
like in my in my cult of the lamp
gameplay inside
preaching
the goodness of me
yeah you should be telling everybody
every dissenter should have a talk with
you and they would change their mind
immediately
um
if only
thank you so much felix
hope you're doing well nice to see you
okay
hey
thank you for coming by to the previous
uh cult of the live stream wonder if you
were here today too
thank you the converter
yeah it could be a name for him
spread the word do it
that's it
thank
did you catch it
did you get it
i hope so
let's translate a name
sparta
in korean oh cassanita
oh you failed for a meet and greet
hopefully we can do another one sometime
big brain gamer thank you
oh
i just found out fema knight is a fire
song i was sleeping on it but now it's
my number one song on spotify at the
moment can't get it out of my head
let's go thank you thank you for
listening lots to it thank you soon
i want same thing for the pinky
what is this this looks weird
uh-huh
okay
it's basically like one two three four
five six seven
or eight different ways of writing
chicken
[Music]
yes thank you uh you wanna eat chicken
so urgently please uh make an order
at the counter thank you
good luck today with your other not a
cult what do you mean other
lovely streams buzz the story driven
rpgs are almost as enjoyable as the
stories to tell while reading donations
especially travel logs
and you just got back but where would
you like to travel next glory to lady
kiara
[Music]
i mean besides the obvious japan
choice yeah
right now i don't have like a really
clear
one in mind there's there's many
different ones that i don't know i would
like to go to
there's not one big goal right now that
i say oh i want to go to this country
next hundred percent
um
[Laughter]
no no no
but for a while i won't be traveling
anyway actually actually actually never
mind i want to go to dusseldorf right
[\h__\h] now
i'm kind of triggered
my
good friend wrote to me
yesterday
that she
did she very spontaneously
traveled to dusseldorf
and showed me a picture of
her eating tonkatsu at my favorite
tonkatsu place
i got a little bit salty looking at that
she went alone and she went really
spontaneously because i think she has
like some kind of like train ticket that
we have right now in europe where you
can travel for all of europe for how
long two three months or so
um for
like an insanely cheap price and you can
basically use every [\h__\h] train
yeah nine euros it's like nine us
dollars
wait how what are the terms for that
it's insane guys
it's actually insane
no wait that's that's just for germany
what's the other one
isn't that one just for germany
what's the european one um
oh maybe it's that one
oh could be oh wait okay that's much
more expensive but
is it this one
it was some kind of super special deal
though
i don't know
i don't know i can't find it now but
yeah we sometimes have some good deals
within europe and it's just like really
really
like so worth it because
within europe
you could travel to so many countries
relatively fast with the train for such
a such a cheap price
see so many places in a short time
yeah so she just went to germany there's
a lot to eat at home cups and showed me
a picture and i'm like
girl you [\h__\h] kidding me i was
craving toll cuts recently
how
and and
let me have it i think
you know even if the train ride is like
10 hours or so
i think it could be fine if she gives it
to me directly
i want to go back i really want to go to
the tonkatsu place again
maybe like i don't know
maybe in october
or september i mean it could really just
be a one night trip really
isn't that a waste just because i really
want to eat tonkatsu
it's probably kind of a waste
it's not worth it
we do have some good japanese food here
too so
i just need to perfectionize my own
tonkatsu skills
yeah that would solve a lot of problems
um
[Music]
what do you call them tonkatsu breading
i have it
but it's oh it's more than just that
it's your technique too and
i'll try again
sometime thank you docker deck
mr casper
whitfield one
nine nine thank you
thank you for
pinkies thank you
that's right
i said well guys
suck swinging europeans have to travel
so much for specific foods that's
actually about not that much to queso
generally
like
because we're in europe i feel like we
have a big mix of lots of different
foods everywhere
it's just home console
i think i could probably find a
restaurant that sells or makes tonkatsu
here in austria but
they're not very authentic that one in
dusseldorf is just 100 authentic that's
why i like it so much
it's not much it is it is it's not that
easy
you don't get it
the way you explain
the way you explain it i could just make
schnitzel
there's
differences you know
now
anyway
um
[Music]
if i could yeah if i could take like 10
times like 10 servings of tonkatsu bring
it home and eat it anytime like put it
in the freezer so but that's no i can't
i can't because it won't go bad by the
time i'm back and i can't do it anyway
deduction for last year
noise what do you think will be the best
investment i already know though i
hereby invest in quality content and not
a cult can't be has a progress again
wow nice way of investing your money i
think it's the best choice yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's that's where
your money is safe your money is safe
with me
thank you very much
i actually
[Music]
i should really sit down like
asap to do some tax related stuff
my
my tax person has been
like
she kept on delaying it she says it's
fine
like she kept not even me it's not even
me but she kept on delaying it but now
apparently it's finally time to do
something
so
i have to look uh
find some more
things that i could deduct so
sit down for a moment but my printer is
not working anymore i don't know what
happened
it's not working anymore so if i want to
scan or print something
it's not working right now it sucks
yeah that does taxes cheap
no no no no as long as she says it's
fine it's fine she's not even like
giving me a harsh deadline or anything
it's kind of weird but she says it's
fine so it's fine
yeah they have a i guess they have a
later deadline yet she said it's fine
i was surprised too but she said it's
fine
yeah
yeah that and something else i
uh
something else i need to do sometime
soon
[Music]
i don't wanna do
a document kind of [\h__\h]
no no
everything that has to do with paper
burn burn it burn
i don't want to deal with it no
no
no yeah responsibilities [\h__\h] that i
don't want to deal with it mommy
mommy
no it's not that it's low on ink it has
everything it needs but something's
wrong
like i don't know whatever i'll have to
ask rbf or someone
take a look
[Applause]
thank you for the thinking optimus prime
thank you also for pinky finally
firearms how are you doing kiara how are
you doing kfb i hope you're all fine you
all deserve to be happy yes
also cafe is not a cult but it is good
yeah so to make this crystal clear
family friendly farmer optimus thank you
why did you have to make it clear that
you're family friendly farmer
why why was that necessary i i never
doubted that
how would an
not family from a family-friendly farmer
be right
just to be sure no one down with you
okay
thank you very much for the pinky very
nice support i appreciate it thank you
so much
so you're so kind asking about the
others too i hope everybody's doing well
too
i want you guys to be happy
and
let's just say
i should be able to read that
chunky chunk thank you red super chat
shall we rename
prison to the usual room
can you do that
can you rename
buildings in
the game i don't think so
but thank you
nice to see you hope you enjoyed the
stream thank you so much for your
support and the big kiss goes out to you
[Music]
thank you
i'm happy with you around
oh
i read a nokia live stream until sunday
what what what the [\h__\h]
timing bad
[Music]
hmm
that's probably pretty outdated now
moose thank you for the red super chat
enjoy today is my birthday thank you all
for making me laugh and practice my days
love potential ow
oh sorry i got something in my profile
thank you and happy belated birthday
moose
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday
dear moves
happy birthday moose congratulations i
hope you celebrate it nicely hope you're
happy hope you got everything you need
in life
to
succeed at the things you want to
succeed at i wish you all the best
please continue supporting kiwawa
is
uric acid it's also another food like
that you eat like parmesan cheese it's
from the way hershey condensed milk with
a pressure cooker it has tangy taste but
she has better tasting brands than the
standard hershey bar no no that's some
some very detailed
hershey knowledge that we
we kind of touched the subject last time
yeah yeah
yeah yeah the vomit tasting
chocolate yeah
yeah
thank you
did you google that and copy paste or
did you already know
alright thank you
i'm hiding in the grass come find me
ah
unfortunately yeah we can't do that i i
was kind of
thinking should i maybe
try playing on twitch but i don't even
have a twitch account set up and it
sounds like a lot of
blah travel to just do this one stream
and then
i would be expected to do more but i
already need to keep up my
my german channel which will start soon
i swear i swear i mean there probably
won't be more content than once
per week or once per two weeks but
yeah
um
if anything i'll sacrifice my
streams to that and not to twitch
i don't know
that's the smartest thing but
yeah you know
yeah
even once per week doesn't sound like
much but
the way i make my schedule when i look
at it it is much it takes away much
a week only has seven days one of those
days is usually a break day so only six
days
minus one german stream is only five
streams uh
on on this channel then per week
sometimes even only four if you consider
a second break day or
um
a stream on someone else's channels or
whatever
it's not
it's actually quite the
investment so yeah anyway
i'm glad you are watching thank you so
much
mwah very sweet just still see you
around thank you
yeah the streams will be shorter unless
i ever ever ever get gothic perms
which is looking difficult i guess it's
like one of those games where
you know it's kind of dead so you don't
get a reply
[Music]
don't know what to
specifically play instead in german
that would make a lot of sense
i don't know
a gothic remake
people said they want me to play normal
graphic but
i don't know
we'll see i'll think about it first i do
a debut stream
and then
i have an idea for the second stream
and i have a clip ready as well so
that's gonna be something too like if i
don't have time to stream i'll just
upload some
um clips that are translated from
english to german or a german channel um
only holland with four deviants yeah
finally a new debut
i'm excited
yeah
but this time i won't be like mimicking
my normal debut streams you know how it
usually was the joke
so i'll just make a completely new
debut but
yeah yeah we'll see we'll see
i'll tell you things that you all
already know but i'll tell you in german
so
uh thank you skye thank you sir
thank you so much
just realized girls in panther is 10
years old now and i can't recommend it
to you for the watch as long as this was
get what getting old means anyways tanks
are cool cute girls are cool attention
is cool all is good in the world back to
my tank show
yeah no i wouldn't have picked that one
nothing against that anime but
[Music]
but
yeah you guys are welcome to enjoy it
i'm not saying it's bad or anything it's
just i'm not interested you know
chad please watch it and do him the
favor and watch girls and panzer girls
yeah ah
how's it going bro
how's it going i'm tired
not that anybody asked but this is my
stream so i'll tell you i'm tired
drink energy drinks but the energy
drinks i drank for popcorn
uh and the night before they [\h__\h] me
up so bad or the night after the day
after
i drank two one per day
they [\h__\h] me up so bad
then
bin
you
they didn't give you wings no not really
they
they made me really really dead
and then tummy horde
yeah
not good
no not good to drink energy drinks i i
don't understand people who drink them
all the time i remember in my workplace
my old workplace people would drink
energy drinks all the time and i
understand you know
you need something to keep you awake but
then then drink coffee come on drink
coffee
i don't like coffee either but
that seems to be healthier than energy
drinks
yeah it's not good for your heart yeah
at least like in europe where the energy
drinks are pretty strong i don't know
about other countries i know in japan
they're pretty weak
so not so bad but in europe they're very
strong or at least in austria i don't
know
other countries might be different
thank you
ah you gotta go again
they're still restocking they update on
twitter so you have to check the updates
sugar free energy drinks diluted with
water
[Music]
coffee stronger than energy drinks
yeah yeah stronger but like it doesn't
like it's not bad for your heart at
least
as long as as far as i know
may have a slight addiction no no
at least that's past tense
coffee gives me more tummy horn and
makes me have to use a bedroom so i
prefer energy drinks
how does that not have that effect on
you too
the hell you build up some kind of
immunity but be careful of your heart
now we know media i don't allow that
i don't allow you
spamming energy drinks
no no that's a no-no from mommy kiwawa
i'm worried about your health
don't drink too many
don't drink too often
very bad
be careful be healthy
be healthy little [\h__\h]
do i have to be angry
i'll try we mean you'll try you'll do it
just do it
be healthy
i worry about you you're gonna make me
worry about you
all of you energy drink addicted
idiots
do it just do it do it
just be healthy for [\h__\h] sake
what do you mean me i don't drink
alcohol i don't drink energy drinks i
don't smoke i don't do the other yeah
bye things you know i don't do any of
that kind of [\h__\h]
for that matter i'm probably living a
healthier life than most of you guys
don't tell me to be healthy
i want to hear that from the guy who
just drives around in the tank okay you
probably have a quite um
quite a healthy muscular body but still
oh [\h__\h]
me not working out or whatever is made
up by the fact that i live healthy in
other
ways okay
like you know as i said
no
no no none of those things i'm straight
edge yes
yes i'm healthy i'm gonna outlive all of
you guys you're aware of that are you
i'm gonna get really really really old
and you all be gone and i'll be crying
and y'all are gone
so stop [\h__\h] on me like that
now i might have like a really crooked
back at that point
but at least i'll still be alive
anyway hmm
[Music]
i don't know how to say that name but
thank you thank you
so much
i'll never play that space wonderful
condition crispy chicken thank you
i've been gone for two months boss i got
moved tonight and i'm out of your time
zone no
i finally seen i'm a stream since new
year's but i only love chihuahua high
school question also got your birthday
merch thank you
you're in a night shift now huh well at
least you can watch vods right
um fight though cruise down
okay i'm done with those
why did i tangent so much
why
it's stupid
guys
i'll never be done
i'll never catch up
no i will i will
i'm embiid i'm getting more of that this
week
because
i still have everything
on the table right next to me
so i'm like okay
we'll do it again before i put
everything away
and also it was fun so yeah
you guys seem to like it too
it's nothing compared to your birthday
super chat exactly that's what i'm
saying
addiction nikolas know this toys thank
you for the pinky oh the mother of
chickens the letter is finally sent
hopefully you get it before christmas oh
you slipped it so far ahead of time good
job
i had to restrain myself to not write
like 20 pages have an awesome and fun
crafting stream i'll catch up with the
vlog team lots of love
thank you i'm excited thank you i love
the letters from you guys so
looking forward to receiving it at some
point
yeah i wonder what you
wrote curious
i'm excited thank you for considering
writing a letter to me i appreciate it
very sweet of you thank you
give me your thank you soon
[Music]
i love that emote so much it's so cute
thank you
wow
alright so free dancing thank you
[Music]
proper mechanical relay switches inside
the keyboard instead of cheap circuit
board with rubbery carbon pads that can
be disrupted by dust
okay that tells me nothing but that
sounds cool
because of you have an earring of dream
the night away
don't you mean dance the night away
for four days and it doesn't disappear
hey where did you come from
german speaking
where did you come from
now german speaking uh super chats stand
out to me because there's not many
you look like a
a newcomer to me
thanks for the pinky
i don't know which song you mean because
you wrote
you had a typo in there and in different
words but i'm guessing you mean the
twice song because i keep on singing it
in my
heart of the lamp play
huh
[Music]
thank you for the coffee stream just
what the doctor ordered
tgif what does that mean again i just
remembered from a katy perry stream
which i a stream song where they chant t
g i f p g i f e i o
ah thank god it's friday
there should be a tgim but thank god
it's monday i think garfield would be
using that a lot
finally i know
thanks james mcphee now i know the more
you know
mwah
whitfield 1999 duncan
but at least he but at least he eats
lasagna on monday
wouldn't you look forward to i guess he
eats lasagna every day
but
i don't know what my logic is
don't question me it's late
boy i are done looks and honored
gym choices
thank you
i'm confusing myself with garfield oh
could be
i am garfield no
i thought it was garfield
i thought that was garfield reborn
reincarnated
ah that's when john leaves for work
oh
it's so cute but that's so cute
ah i only remember garfield like a
little bit from when i was younger when
i read some comics but it's been so long
like i really
i'm such a faker i'm a fake fan i don't
know much about garfield
that's why i need to watch the movie and
you know what if i have to i wasn't
alone i watch it alone yeah
cause you guys are being [\h__\h] about it
i don't want to watch it because
[Music]
i feel like it would be too late unless
we now
don't play the game again until the
chicken releases
if it ever happens
look i don't even know how long i need i
would need to wait so it's like hard to
wait so
even if they added now
uh i probably wouldn't make use of it or
maybe i
maybe i would but then i would do it on
twitch
maybe just because
there's chickens and then i can play
with you guys
maybe i would i'll see i'll see how long
it takes
uh maybe that could be post game stuff
yeah
maybe who knows
um
[Music]
i'm done with the iron beads
does the next one have a lot
no
has less okay then let's do that one too
rest
sir a blessed key
thank you
so sweet
[Music]
thank you
tomorrow is your day actually i can't go
tomorrow because i got you know what
disease
no
you missed out on something amazing
i have a self quarantine for seven days
from today just sad that i can't see you
in there but i hope you have a good time
and soul popcorn
but at least you were
what's the word um
responsible enough
stay at home
not get anybody else sick
so that's
good job
that deserves some praise
even though you missed out on something
that you really wanted to go to probably
but a lot of a lot of the korean bros
told me
they got the the thing right before
which is really sad
yeah
hopefully that'll be another chance for
you
um
thank you all for your support
hope you feel better now
[Music]
is my first super chat i'm going to the
popcorn that starts in a little while
sadly i failed at the meet and greet
draw but no it's okay anyway i hope you
enjoyed the convention and i really
really look forward to your aoe 2 stream
oh yeah see you there
oh
yeah i'm doing that at the end of the
week
finally it's um i hope it's going to be
good um i just remember it a bit from my
childhood
so
don't expect too much
it will probably be a really chill
stream
because you know you just build [\h__\h]
for
hours and hours
what
nina wants to collab with you and fana
what what
she can always collab with me where did
you get that from now
you can't just i don't think i have any
tangents left at that point i used a lot
of my tangents today and tomorrow in
rasp
i already
don't have much to go on about
no i didn't watch the concert
i did not
maybe partially because i'm sad that um
we couldn't be part of it
but also
i was watching something else
i was watching
maybe i'll watch it
the archive
at some point
um
yeah i heard it was nice
just you know in general we weren't
included in the whole live summer at all
and that's fine you know i understand
they don't have
like the resources or so to do it for
all of us
to be like that
we are a very
big
now we have so many members
within the whole life
so
do be like that i just hope that next
year hopefully we get
our chance
to do something like that in that scale
something cool
you want to do something like that too
please
all that kind of stuff
yeah well in general just more 3d stuff
i want to be able to do more in 3d
japan please
japan
don't let us in please
although
not only
issue of japan but more it's more
factors playing
a role in that but yeah
working on it
well they for for tourists today
she changed it up a little bit more
again
now you can enter
um
still only with a registered tour but at
least it um
no i mean you can go through a travel
agency only before it had to be a guided
tour now it can be without a guided tour
but it still has to be kind of like yeah
for a travel agency tour thingy
but it seems like you have a bit more
freedom now
a bit more not much more
but still
kind of controlled and
if i go then
i needed to be like so that we can work
you know
and do some stuff
yeah everybody all of us
work visa
now
is definitely more obtainable i know a
lot of people who
got a working visa
for going to tokyo game show very easily
but tokyo game show and then i mentioned
it the other day
on the other that anime convention a big
one
those were kind of like
a deal
with
what could be like it could have been
easier to obtain those because of those
events
if you go
unrelated to those events it could still
be a little bit more difficult but it's
definitely
like possible to obtain
work visas now i know several people
who have done it so
um
that's that but still um these kind of
things take some time with preparing and
processing
and then other things need to be
considered to like schedule of
our studio and all that because if we go
then
they need to make space for us
and all that
so it all has to match up nicely and
yeah planned well
please wait please wait
always working on it
always waiting i'm always ready
i'm i have my bags packed my bags are
packed and i'm ready to go i'm standing
here outside your door
i hate to wake you up to say
goodbye
but my visa's ready
my vaccination too
i'm gonna take the
flights to you
already my 3d debut
is coming up
eh
so kiss me and smile for me
tell me that you wait for me
hold me like you'll never
let me go
cause i'm
living
on a chat play
i don't know when i'll be back again
oh babe
i
hate to go
such a nice song
i remember the lyrics differently though
it's kind of weird
ah
thank you guys okay
yeah yeah
wipe your tears
weaklings
thank you well that's uh for the flash
chats by the way and then thank you
thank you for the red super chat
the red flash chat
my power thank you and please donation
we were new thank you entity thank you
for donation oh thank you for the sneak
shots guys i'll skip those two
jeff star donkey shoot sugar hatsuko
thank you for the rare pinky
i received my kia plushie the mouth is
my father valley girl crafting with hand
cam when anime watch along all in a week
now today i wake up to a wonderful
interaction with iris kiana thanks for
being part of the whole life and being
you
thank you
thank you you know that's nice to hear
i think last week was a was a good week
only uh um
i didn't have to like cancel the last
stream i'm sorry about it it was such a
good week
but
yeah
kind of was
all messed up because of the energy
drinks
and the
popcorn in the middle of the night
until morning time
now thanks for understanding
thank you soon
we've been out of control this year in a
good way i hope
cancer streams the least in all vans
really
that's all
don't know about that but in any case
even if i
cancelled more
or less i don't know i'm still
currently i think as far as i know
still
number one
streamer indian
longest streams
most streams
so
i am taking any complaints anyway
actually yeah
you guys
are blessed
to have me as your aussie
yeah
some might even say i stream too much so
maybe i should be streaming less but i
can this is the minimum for me
in my mind this this is the absolute
minimum
if i stream any less than this
i feel like i'm not doing my job so i
have to stream stream dream stream
i'm not addicted it's my obligation and
also
like you know
um
some of you guys with normal jobs
probably work even more than i do
depends on how you see
what you count as working in my case but
because a yeah of non-streaming time is
still work time
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and
streaming can be very mentally taxing
might
not
but entertaining
like this
can be very exhausting
especially
voice wise
i'm pretty happy that you stream the
hours that you do love you thank you
thank you
[Music]
yeah mentally and physically yeah yeah
i'm tired let's go let's finish this
thank you sugarless show me the plushie
which one
i don't know which one you mean
[Music]
um
i didn't practice my korean for a while
again no now i'm unsure again
[Music]
for the pinky
yay
thank you for the pink super chat
it says
only kiana
in korean
thank you thank you thank you
good
chicken i trained you well thanks for
the pinkie me soon and last but not
least julian b thank you for the pinky
i wish you some more tv interactions in
the future we are here for you cheer up
and be well oh thank you i mean i was
oh i was like satisfied with um the
amount of interactions i got last time i
guess i mean
i don't know i think it was okay
oh
um although they were probably not so
much titted but more uh some frustration
in there
some some fighting
uh
some surprised
deaths i don't know if you can call that
tati
indeed something
could be nice next time i don't know how
it will go tomorrow
don't expect too much tape day guys
yeah
i still have to make the thumbnail and
[\h__\h]
okay then thankfully i'm done with this
now
delete
this one
[Music]
someone else made the thumbnail for me
please although rust thumbnails are
using just
some image and put the
logo on top kind of low effort
[Music]
i'm tired so thank you everybody for
supporting me with my calls today once
again
you know the account of this game made a
really funny tweet today that i found
like to be
very challenging
they tweeted like
that they had what 100k or 1 million
100k i think 100k followers now and then
compared it with a certain other cult
and like eh we have more followers than
them now
and i'm like oh
you got some balls
lamb of the cult cult of the lamp game
very interesting
you saw it
ah
oh
challenging
fantasy
[Music]
well
i hope they'll be safe
anyway thank you very much for watching
today
yeah
um i'll see you tomorrow
maybe
before next time i'll also
play a little bit
off screen
i don't know
if i want to
i'll see what i can do
yeah otherwise we'll probably
maybe finish the game next week i don't
know
like in theory there's one door left but
bad but but
maybe it will do a big bamboozle on me
like um
tunic
yeah
so
oh i'm not sure what do you guys think
um okay and two more hair okay i'll kill
again and i'm guessing two more parts
yeah i will not call it finale then okay
okay fine with me fine with me
okay then
thank
no i will stream when i want to
this cult leader is not
does not enjoy being told what she needs
to do what she should do
what stream would i want to
[Music]
love you guys i missed you guys it was
nice talking to you guys today
i enjoyed it
hope you did too
now sleep well
don't drink energy drinks
don't
spaghetti
[Music]
you my favorite person you're so cute
you're always such a charmer
thanks for the stream kiara thank you
for watching
if you have a pleasant sleep tonight i
hope so too
you too
please
drink energy drink you can't stop me
oy
[Music]
hey
bye bye
one week for you buddy
[Music]
checkmate yeah
you