the thing is that just wasn't really My
Vibe the point is as a phoenix I've
lived many different lives no matter how
beautiful the tail is when you die
that's it everyone believes the same
fairy tale and no one's allowed to
argue then I heard a clock chime and
when I opened my eyes again I was all
alone in a strange
Place K
KY welcome to K right Phoenix yeah yeah
hold your feathers it's just me I got
the stuff you asked for those sunflowers
should really brighten the place up Yow
is a great color to convey warmth and
happiness you've got to be some kind of
cyborg right I don't know if a normal
human could pull off some of the stuff
she does no kidding like building a
working Cannon out of a papier-mâché and
making a mess of my
restaurant yeah why you look away girl
yeah gooda you should clean up after
your own mess
hey they're talking about you too you
know all right all right all right break
it up we're going to take a break share
our past
right all right all right how about I
figure out a way for the underworld to
survive without Souls will that shut you
up if the world is a canvas and all of
us are the painters then I'm going to
spend my life making it more beautiful
for everyone I love performing with you
girls and seeing the audience's smiles I
couldn't have asked for more from this
life everyone believed that fairy tale
except for me I knew there was a world
outside of Atlantis I don't actually use
my Powers much anymore though I like
hanging out in this time period with you
guys we're together and we're happy and
I just want to have fun with you all is
that
weird this is right this is how it
should
be for now I'm just going to enjoy our
time
together D of time the Shadows