[Music]
do
hi
it's my birthday
[Music]
hello
wow
i'm so nervous
oh
sorry uh
well
technical issues
may persist i'm having a fight with
technology lately as you probably
noticed so excuse excuse any
scuff that happens
i don't know how loud i am right now
but hello i might be peeking the
microphone because i'm so excited
hello
it's my birthday
hello okay i need to stop just saying
hello because we do have
we have stuff to do today oh my gosh
there's so much to talk about with the
fest
that happened i'll talk about that
sometime
but today is my birthday and i've been
overwhelmed with all of the kind
messages i wanted to look at twitter
more today but i had to prepare for the
stream but i was scrolling for a while
we have
i have some of the fan yards in the back
as you may see
oh yeah welcome to my garden by the way
we're having a little garden party today
now this background was made by
bren pc who has
done a lot of
a lot of art for other young members
and they're able to make it for me
really quickly so i'm super grateful to
them
[Music]
but yeah it's my birthday i was yeah i'm
really thankful to everyone who's who is
um
yeah i mean done anything if you mean
fan art or send me a nice message or
are just here at my birthday party
thank you for being at my birthday party
wait i forgot to tweet
[Music]
should i tweet
again
i told you me and technology we don't
get along i guess that includes twitter
starting
now
that's good enough
oh yes um we are doing collins today um
they will start in about 25 minutes
until then we can do a bit of chatting
and also i want to sing some songs um
i'm kind of scared
because i'm nervous i don't know if i
can sing them well i mean even under
normal circumstances i don't know if i
can sing them well but
you know i'll try
i will try just a couple songs to you
know get the party started it is my
birthday party
so we should have
a festive atmosphere right
moko moguyami was great at the expo
thank you i was really happy to sing
that's one of my favorite
halloween songs okay senpai's mobile
mogul yummy it's such a cute song
and i love how she whispers at the start
welcome
super cute
yeah everyone was so good at this oh my
gosh i could talk forever at the fest
too at the concerts i could talk forever
but
maybe
should we sing
oh i'm scared to sing i'm nervous
i'm nervous thank you guys for coming to
my party
thank you thank you
okay let's sing
oh i'm nervous
[Music]
how i can't just keep saying i'm nervous
that's not going to make me any less
nervous
okay okay okay okay
i didn't i don't know which one
we shall sing first
[Music]
which one is the easiest
i don't know
okay
let's sing um
classic first
to warm up
um
i have i have maybe three songs
but
just three okay i better
hurry up
okay
[Music]
i'm nervous stops
no more nervous
[Music]
okay
i'm gonna sing it
[Music]
thank you for all the birthday wishes
thank you thank you
okay
[Music]
i forgot to turn the music on
acappella
i'm too nervous
yes
[Music]
is
i want to do it justice more than this
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
ah
it's hard to sing
when
you're nervous
[Music]
as i think
music was a bit out of sync
um
i'm always really bad at sinking though
i tried to sync it before the stream but
usually i just make it worse
[Music]
thank you guys thank you guys
no more no more nervous
no more nervous
[Music]
okay okay why don't i
if if the music is ahead of me
do i make the sink offset for my
microphone positive or negative
positive
i think
negative or negative
positive
[Music]
yes and
well
yeah we can test it
[Music]
okay let's sing another song
this might be
more out of sync
we'll see
[Music]
um
this one
might be familiar
if you
watched
um a reason members watch along
you want a sync test first okay let's do
a stink test with sweets parade then
well i changed it a little bit is this
better or worse
[Music]
was it better or worse
oh i'm seeing mixed results
so i need to go further
even further
[Music]
even further beyond
all right i'll try again
[Music]
how's that
worse
[Music]
was that too far
now i'm behind okay okay
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you for giving me the gift of
helping me sing
music on my birthday
[Music]
foreign
how was that
um
i'm late
so go a little bit further
[Music]
almost perfect
okay okay maybe this will be the one
[Music]
anymore
how's that
[Music]
wait was behind me and i go less
or more
was that worse
[Music]
no one knows anymore
um
i don't even know anymore there's
there's so much
should we just go
is it better than it was at the first
start
or at the very start
[Music]
it's worse
better
[Music]
well we'll try another song i guess
we gotta we gotta go because we gotta do
collins
it's time for a party it's not time for
sing the music
[Music]
oh
she
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
me
she
[Music]
me
okay we have time
for one more
[Music]
i think if we go fast
my
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
you
oh
[Music]
we found it
um
[Music]
yo
you
[Music]
okay just in time
just in time
or
[Music]
hold so much
oh
i think our first guest is already there
okay okay let's go
[Music]
let me make sure
i have
png
[Music]
okay me just tell our first guest
that i'm ready whenever they are ready
[Music]
who will be
caller number one
time to find out
[Music]
oh oh hello
it's inna
hello welcome welcome you're the first
caller
which means you're kind of
my test subject
[Music]
wait oh they cannot hear you see this is
the first
i thought that it would work
that's okay hold on
[Music]
can you talk
oh okay hello hello i think they can
hear you now hi
what sorry i was just busy looking the
cake here delicious chocolate yes feel
free to stick your hand in and grab a
bite
oh yes stick my whole face in it
delicious
also since you are the first caller
um i prepared
a special wheel today a wheelchair
if you would like to spin it
[Music]
it has various um
prizes
private
or perhaps punishments
punishment
yes all depends on your point of view i
think
i think
they're
size of the same color you know
exactly
some people's attachments to some
people's rewards okay well here's the
wheel
um if you would like to tell me when to
stop okay i will pause it it might hurt
your eyes though um
i'm trying to read it but i can't say
stop
oh
this might be a punishment for you it
says do your best
i see i see this is what has
says down to you um this is not this is
not it this is not the fight
hey hey i gave you the choice or not
you may be doing i was like because i
feel like i could have refused
you could have refused i'm sorry if that
wasn't clear
yet you're out of high
[Music]
i think i'm more of an oil type i'll be
honest but yeah it's kind of your your
signature signature
but thank you thank you for for blessing
us with your atta prayer
[Music]
equivalent well what about a
oh yeah
i feel like that's not how you do it
though
i mean that worked my heart something i
just did
but said oil oil instead
is there a technique for it you do
it's imagine you know that that emote
that i have in the server the the
sparkly eyes when you're gonna imagine
yeah with the face yeah
then you have to go oh yeah oh yeah
[Music]
thank you for calling in i appreciate it
thank you for being my my test subject
oh any time
first to spin my wheel
oh now i can read the wheel oh do you
want to oh no
oh okay forget it's okay now it's
spinning again
oh no what are we ever gonna do you
don't have to do this one i'll do this
one instead
you're gonna refresh it i mean i don't
know if you can pull it off on no you
don't think
be a little too hard
i need a little more
you know
some some practice yeah
anyways oh i hope you have a great
birthday it's your first birthday in
hollow how do you feel are you nervous
i'm very nervous oh don't worry i'm the
first test subject so
hopefully i feel addy is all right okay
good
good it'll be fine i'll be fine you'll
have lots of fun
[Music]
and uh
yeah i hope you have an even better year
from now on to your next birthday thank
you not doing my best
yeah eat lots of cookies i'm gonna take
some on my way out
just feel free we have plenty
i licked the cake all over the cake let
everyone read the cake
sharing is scary
anyways yeah um do you have any birthday
wishes
oh
birthday wishes yeah i don't know
i wish i wish to have another fun year
with
with everyone in holland
my wish for you is that
we can all stand on top of the stage
together
yes i want that too
i can't wait one day one day one day
okay thank you okay yeah i'm thinking
thank you so much
[Music]
and our next guest
should i drag her in
[Music]
hello
hey
happy
yeah
thank you welcome welcome
thank you it's uh good to be here nice
tea party that you have going on thank
you feel free to help yourself you know
already licked the cake but you can have
a lick too if you want
oh
indirect kiss i see
exactly exactly
um would you like to spin the wheel
uh
the wheel i have a wheel of fortune here
it has various prizes and punishments on
it oh prizes i like prizes do you like
punishments
uh um i kind of prefer prizes but
okay well we'll see do you want to spin
it and find out
uh
yes go for it spin the wheel okay let me
know when you want me to stop it and
i'll stop it okay
uh
stop
oh i think this is
just barely in the orange of ask fauna
anything
that's one of a prize
that is that is a prize um
ask fauna anything
hmm
any burning questions say when i got
this with bae
i didn't know what to ask her so i ended
up just asking her how
how how
how how how what
how
how an open-ended question
oh okay um but you can ask anything you
want
um
[Music]
how do you
what do you think about
uh humanity as a
as a guardian of nature
well lately me and humanity are well at
least i'm not getting along with
humanity's inventions
technology
not
not really on my side right now gotta be
honest kind of having a feud but you
know i love humans wish they would
return to nature but
we're working on it
huh every day is one day closer
but isn't it complicated isn't it a
complicated relationship oh yeah like
facebook you always talking about
facebook relationships
it's complicated it's complicated just
like facebook
ah who uses facebook nowadays
humanity humanity
lame that's why it's complicated yeah
but we're not supposed to be talking
badly about humanity because it's a it's
your birthday and the main focus is eu
not about humanity nothing so
yeah yo thank you
[Music]
anytime happy
birthday thank you
all right thank you for coming to my
party
no thank you for inviting me
yes of course
yeah
happy birthday thank you yay
all right i'll talk to you later
[Music]
fun well thoughtful and well
okay she's gone
our next guest
i never know if i should drag them in or
let them come in on their own
have have the power
to force them into the garden
oh hello
hello kovana
[Music]
it reminds me of um bon jovi the music
oh
it does sound a little bit like that
yeah
hello thank you i love the background
it's so pretty
isn't it nice
and the foreground and whatever that is
in the middle
hey hey that's me
i like your wheel too that was
interesting would you like to spin the
wheel
spin
the wheels please
you can just let me know when you'd like
to stop it can i spin it twice
like you want you want two prizes yes
because one of them could be something
bad too so
stop stop
oh another one
doing your best okay and that's why we
do it twice
well okay i'll do it though
let's let's hear it
[Music]
is very powerful oh my goodness
i don't know if i've heard your arada
before
i mean it's probably not my first time
but
um i can tell
i didn't think that
someone would still ask me in 2022 to do
an araa
oh you know
i lives forever oh no
can i spend one more time
[Music]
[Applause]
stop
[Music]
oh
describe a fauna in three words a
classic totsumachi question
okay
i think um
[Music]
wait is that the right word let me go
dick dot cc
is that the right one
that was the wrong word okay um
cool
um
[Music]
but actually i wanted something else i
actually wanted to ask you a question
can i ask you a question
question because we have extra time
anyway apparently
it was like a five minute break in your
plan
was there yeah it's like five minutes
open so i get ten minutes to talk to you
while the others just get five minutes
which isn't really fair but i have a
question
because you need to talk more it's your
birthday
um
i have a question is there anything
weird that your kitty cats do
oh
they always do weird things
[Music]
let me think well actually lately so
they don't really
um like each other that much
um like they don't fight but they don't
really like each other
oh no
so lately snail
uh the younger one
will
sit on my bed
and stare at clover and clovers down
below and just like taunt him because
clover is an old man
[Music]
it's very interesting i think snail is
fascinated by clover and enjoys
observing him like watching a nature
documentary interesting
and one more question
yes
if you recall your past birthdays
was there any birthday
where like something
um crazy happened or something like
scandalous happened like someone's
stealing your cake or so that happened
to me before oh
[Music]
oh well there was actually this is
my most embarrassing
story oh let's go
no now or never it's actually not my
birthday party but someone else's
birthday party
i think i told this to my members
um well this was and you might relate to
this because i know you also like
cosplay um i was just getting into
cosplay as a little baby weeb and it was
like the height of my interest you know
it was so cool and new
um
and i got invited to my friend's
birthday party and
i really wanted to wear my misa amane
cosplay
what a weeb
so
um somehow i convinced them i was like
hey you should make it a costume party
even though it's your birthday party oh
and smart
big break they agreed somehow
except when i got there i think i was
the only one eating any costume
but i didn't even care i was just happy
to be wearing the cosplay
where the others at least also kind of
like weebish yeah they they didn't judge
me or anything okay they're very kind
about it but looking back
in me and my like cheap uh halloween
costume wig that's like so frizzy
um
it's quite an embarrassing story
he
convinced my friend to make it a cosplay
party so that her costume party so i can
wear my
misa cosplay and then i'm the only one
dressed up well if you think about it at
least uh like misa from how i remember
that character um if you wear something
like that in in real life that it's
basically you'll just look like an edgy
teenager that's true it's true except i
also had my death note notebook
oh it was also something an edgy
teenager might have
and
did you ever write something in the
death note no i didn't i wasn't quite
that edgy
ah
i see oh that's interesting see i got
some a nice story out of you
yes only my most most embarrassing story
that's your most embarrassing story
i don't know it's pretty embarrassing
when i look back i can't help but cringe
at that maybe it's not the most
embarrassing i'm sure there's more
embarrassing things that happened to you
i mean
i can already think of something on the
up the top of my head that i can't even
say
because it would be too scandalous
yeah i'm sure i have things like that
too but
but
chat doesn't know about that
some things are too embarrassing
yeah
and we're already putting ourselves out
there all all the time almost every day
streaming in front of thousands of
people
uh already at all times ready to show
people any embarrassing moment so i
think we're already giving out enough of
us
exactly
yeah
they'll have to try
the party city
wig
oh you mean like a really bad like
halloween
carnival yeah exactly
yeah those look really bad seven dollar
wig
yeah
uh well i already took ten minutes now
um so i'm gonna go thank you for i
didn't even realize there was a break
the time goes by so fast really
just like the time that goes by since
you have joined us in council thank you
for joining who live english farmer i'm
really happy here thank you that's nice
nice enjoy your time make the best out
of it every day is a special day that
you can use to
make make it a special memory for
everybody involved so do your best happy
birthday
celebrate bye-bye
[Music]
cute kiwawa
okay let me have a water
[Music]
bottle water
okay okay
um
looks like our next guest is ready
i'll drag her in
hello
hola
[Music]
hello
how are you doing
anyway you're breaking up a little i'm
sorry oh no am i waking up i'm sorry
um i'm in bed and i think i think i'm on
the court okay happy birthday thank you
welcome welcome how are you doing sana
um i just woke up to your lovely voice
the sun's out the birds are chirping it
smells good it smells like sunflowers
and chocolate cake hmm
it's a chocolate cake is it just
chocolate oh it's not a dirt cake
oh
what have you like natural dirt cake
do you know the dirt cake that's made of
oreos pudding and has gummy worms in it
[Music]
maybe it can do that
yeah
not bad from the that's the funny stuff
i like
oh yeah
nice nice and dirty
would you like to spin my wheel so now i
do want to spin your wheel wheel okay
okay go go go spin spin soon let me know
when you want to stop
stop
[Music]
whoa
you get a free paint drawing
from me
[Music]
i can okay it's about to use this
well
[Music]
well it is your that is your birthday
you know sometimes you want to do some
do some drawing on your birthday
do you have any any requests should i
draw you or would you like something
else
[Music]
i want to leave it
up to you i feel like i'll be happy for
anything i do
okay let me draw
quickly
[Music]
okay um
could you draw something quickly and
i'll
use it as an emerge
you want to use it as an emote
but what if it's bad
it can't be bad it's a paint jordan
it's like pretty early when you start
your birthday stream so i have like
um i've set alarms for every five
minutes
oh
thank you for waking up for me
yeah but um i turned on your stream and
then
um i was thinking about how your scene
was just so
calming that i could fall asleep
thank you
yeah
i think maybe
my stream is better at uh putting people
to sleep
[Music]
uh
a long time ago do you remember a long
time ago we were chatting and you said
that if people said your streams make
you your voice makes you feel feel like
it feels like
you want to fall asleep it's a
compliment
i still think it's a compliment
[Music]
so yeah i was thinking about that
well because sleeping is hard you know
this can be hard to fall asleep
[Music]
even i like to listen to
youtube videos or streams to fall asleep
hmm i was thinking
whether i could fall asleep to asmr or
not because it makes you kind of go
doggy docky
oh true certain asmr
[Music]
maybe it depends on
the person oh i am so cute
because you are cute
[Music]
i want to i wanted to answer the first
impression question actually oh sure
okay i thought i thought you would be
more of a cruella deville kind of girl
yeah when i first saw um avatar that
when i heard your voice
well well pretty much i thought you
would be like that kind of character so
that's why the first thing i asked you
was like can you tell me to
right right i remember
[Music]
yeah but then when i hear your voice
it's just
cute
you're just so cute
thank you you're cute
it's just such a pleasure to talk to you
because you're just so cute and uh we
both like keep stuff and yeah which is
huge keep
going to see us yes
i'm very happy to to know you sana
okay i think this is as far as i can get
in our allotted time
[Music]
okay i wouldn't take much more time for
the next person
thank you
[Music]
sana is so cute
i wish i could have
spent more time okay okay
our next guest
i will bring her in
oh hello oh i got dragged oh hi
interrupted
hello
that is such a good idea
actually i think um ollie did something
similar
i was inspired by her one of her
totsumachi's
oh it's so good
okay let me know when you want to when
you want to stop
um
i like to be like olive garden when they
ask you how much cheese you want you say
when and then
[Music]
what was your first impression of fauna
my first impression of fauna was she
looks like she tastes healthy
[Music]
you recently did a stream where you
talked about eating
holo members right i did
and you were definitely in the taste
healthy category i guess this is the the
shark brain speaking
yeah i think could be a meal
yeah i remember when i debuted i started
with puya the people watching without
intent to eat but that is very very
drastically changed as i've learned more
about the hololive ladies so yeah
unfortunately everybody's up for grabs
or bites
i've seen just nibble just a little okay
just to taste just a little taste i'm
sure it'll grow back right you can it's
like a starfish right you can grow back
limbs and stuff oh lim
ah
well
maybe if i use some of my golden apple
but uh
what's the power of the sun called that
the plants do
oh
photosynthesis yeah
but i'm not a plant you know
my name is
like animals
well you have planned powers don't you
uh
sure
you can do it
plants are also nature plants are also
nature
that's true why are you saying that if i
uh
i uh if by happenstance one of your
horns broke you wouldn't be able to grow
it back
no i think i would but not because i'm
like
only because i'm you know magical keeper
of nature you know
an ordinary person wouldn't be able to
do that
well they also say that humans can
randomly spontaneously combust so
[Music]
maybe
maybe you could also grow a limb back
would you like to try it sometime
i can ah
i have room in the schedule i could
pencil you in you know maybe maybe i'll
put that on the wheel next year and um
you know we can just see if if you
happen to roll it then we can consider
it
i see a game of birthday chance i look
forward to it by the way your birthday
party is so freaking cute
thank you yeah isn't it cute oh am i
still cutting out sorry yeah that's okay
cute garden party
so cute with the yogurt parfait and the
the bunting flags or whatever they're
called triangle flags are always so cute
feel free to have a bite especially if
it means uh
you won't nibble on my arm instead
i can't make any promises i'm sorry uh
your arm is more tasty than chocolate
cake i see
this is true
this is factual
[Music]
spoken like a true carnivore
i can't help it
it's true it's part of your nature right
yes nature yeah luckily you're in the
sea and i'm on land so
that's true
well happy birthday fauna thank you
thank you for coming
of course thank you for having me thank
you for letting me spend your birthday
wheel oh thank you for spinning it
thank you
[Music]
cute everyone's so cute i just want to
say cute after
afterwards
tosomachi is so fun you just get a
sample of everyone's cuteness
[Music]
and speaking of cute
hello
[Music]
good morning
thank you
thank you for waking up
for me i appreciate it
you sound so cute
oh thank you
uh
beastie's currently licking my forehead
but there's that cute
happy birthday happy birthday
it looks so cute
thank you
would you like to spin the wheel yes
your butts
is pure genius oh my god
okay i'll start
spinning it let me know when you want to
stop
um
oh again
this is the wheels favorite today do
your best
but if you want to do a re-spin i will
allow it since we've
oh this one you know
you know i was literally looking at the
wheel during um goodies turn and i was
like
[Music]
all right there's no reverb today but i
hope it's okay
[Music]
so
powerful oh my god basically just put a
pore on my face
she's like stop
stubby
that's how my cats are too they always
get annoyed when i like singing or voice
acting
[Music]
yes let's do it soon yeah
i want to continue too
yeah
yeah have you gotten have you ever
hoped
birthday prep wasn't too stressful for
you
it was it was all right i think
i'm having fun now
[Music]
getting to talk to everyone is nice yeah
thanks for inviting me thanks for coming
thanks for coming
i'm sorry i wasn't as high energy
you don't have to be high energy however
you are is perfect
just the fact that you're here
and and we got it
out of you so i don't think anyone's
going to complain
[Laughter]
man
you know doing an auto auto lying down
is actually very um
i've never done that before
um
the first first time
first time for everything anyway
leave for the next person
thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
i don't know if our next person is ready
just yet
[Music]
that's okay gives me a chance to have
some water
cute bae uh
morning boys bay
area
yes don't forget to hydrate
i'm not used to talking so much
anymore
the last few days
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
good morning
good good morning chris
i never wake up at the morning
good morning i'm sorry to force everyone
to to wake up no it's a good habit it's
very good we are getting blessed by
various morning voices though
i feel so healthy right now
do you want some
some breakfast cake
yes please
healthy breakfast cake
give me a i've never had carrot cake
before oh i love carrot cake really is
it good it's scary yeah but carrots are
sweet you know
yeah
are they
yeah they're they're one of the sweetest
vegetables i think
and you put like spices in it like
cinnamon and ginger
[Music]
with carrot
yeah
possible nature
veggies
of course of course
would you like to spin my wheel iris oh
my god i woke up and i saw this wheel
and just like man
you ran
that's genius yes i want to spin the
wheel all right let me know
when you want to stop it
all righty
there's there's lag on the stream so i'm
like okay i can't i can't say you never
know
man
um uh boop
stop stop
this again
is the wheel weighted or something
if you want a re-roll you can re-roll
you know
since it's your birthday
since it's your birthday i'll do two
i'll do two oh two yeah
i feel like i feel like me uh just
waking up might actually um level up my
usual ottawa it's true yeah okay
[Applause]
oh my goodness the power
i think everyone's awake now
neuron activated that's what people say
right
okay do you want to give it another
quick spin sure okay okay let it roll
what was that i just saw for a split
second
okay
um my brain says stop
oh
[Music]
this is one of the most powerful
man
what i can
i can
i could tweet on your account you can
send one tweet on my account oh my god
what should i or should i make you tweet
i gotta think of this is this something
that i redeem like right away um you can
rename it now or later
you can think about it if you want just
let me know about it i will think about
it i will think about it very hard okay
[Music]
i'm gonna use this power of mine to the
fullest to the fullest potential because
one of them the best rewards on the
wheel oh man
yeah
what did you think of that reward
yourself too i did
well so i kind of knew what i was
getting myself into
someone someone's in for some trouble
i think well it can't be too bad of my
my my son pirates will go easy on me
right
yeah sure yeah yeah
[Laughter]
and i'm excited
okay thank you i feel like i was
rewarded
thank you for
for calling iris
[Music]
virus
oh my gosh she's so cute
oh hello
hello
can you hear me i can hear you
welcome
thank you happy birthday
happy birthday to you
thank you
am i saying right yeah
do people say
[Music]
what kind of cake is this
it's chocolate
with gummy worms inside like oh it's
like a dirt cake yeah
yeah
nature's finest dirt
not real dirt i promise
yeah you do like dirt that's true
i put
[Music]
would you like to spin my birthday wheel
yes please
okay okay just let me know when you're
ready to stop it
oh okay
does it make noise or can i do this you
can do the
noise oh i missed the button
[Music]
wait wait let's redo it let's redo it
that one wasn't fair
i tried to stop it but i missed
stop
you say a line of fauna's choosing
the power is in my hands this time kind
of suffering will you subject me too
no i'll go easy on you um
chad's saying i had to know we had
enough
yeah you guys haven't had enough i know
the wheel
loves the ada
um
whoa can i
[Music]
i'm satisfied yeah thank you
that was very cute is there a contrast
is this the only wheel
oh this is the only wheel today i did
have some more wheels when i did my
getting over it stream i had a
punishment wheel oh yeah
dang you're like a car or something huh
oh
burr
[Music]
sorry i'm revving my energy
no i'm done have you eaten anything
tasty today besides cake for your
birthday oh i was too nervous to eat
much
i had some yogurt oh god yeah i'm gonna
eat after this after this when
everything is done i'm gonna
have a feast birthday feast
what do you what do you what does your
diet consist of
i don't know
well i know in my diet you eat leaves or
something like oh
i mean i guess i i sometimes i eat like
a salad but
salads are not like my favorite thing to
eat but they're okay sometimes
anybody's favorite thing to eat is salad
yeah maybe if you cover it with dressing
[Music]
yeah a fruit
oh yeah a fruit salad that's not really
salad
wait i didn't miss the merch
announcement yet right it's coming up
yeah it will be um after the i should i
didn't mention this to my chat either
actually first announcement will be
after
um
did i spoil it i'm sorry oh well i mean
they probably saw it coming
[Music]
although i have been teasing them yeah
i've been teasing them saying i don't
know who knows maybe i'll be the first
to not have birthday merch wait this is
actually scripted and um there might not
be merch guys so don't get your hopes up
yeah actually i just i just decided
you know no merch no i'm just kidding
stay tuned
all right well happy birthday father
thank you for you letting me spin your
wheel yeah thank you for for saying
thank you for ride
oh
ride
the wheel
the wheel of misfortune
yeah
all right thank you
bye bye
oh my goodness doki doki
oh cute she left right after she said
that i couldn't stay it back
i love you mommy
can i come in here
yes yes hello
yes yes hello welcome let me get
you on the screen thank you
actually you sent me such a special png
that i want to talk about it cause it's
3d cali
yeah
3d kelly
[Music]
yeah special for for your for your
birthday i'm here in 3d png format to
wish you a happy birthday thank you
but you know what it's fine because your
warm and soothing voice is going to make
me fall right back asleep after this oh
thank you yes please get some sleep
we're getting to hear everybody's
morning voices today
yeah i mean there are there are quite a
few that are happening kind of
who wake up but i know inna's on the
same time as me so yeah i guess
makes sense but that's fine you'll put
us all back to sleep it's all good i
hope that you have a fantastic b day i
haven't checked out um your
i don't know if you're releasing any
merch or anything but i'm excited after
this
[Music]
not right after this but after that
i have to talk to everybody oh yeah well
i'm gonna have to probably have the
stream running then so i can listen to
it
i also i have a wheel a fortune
today if you would like to spin it it
has various prizes and punishments go
spin spin spin to win let's go okay let
me know when you want to stop it
okay all right sounds good
all right is it spinning now it's
spinning yep anytime
okay stop
oh
you got uh
perhaps the most powerful
with the most powerful
reward on the wheel well what's this you
can change my icon on twitter for one
day to anything of your choosing
wait are you sick yes it will start
tomorrow though because today is my
birthday so it will start tomorrow but
that gives you a day to figure it out if
you want i'm gonna draw you something
nice and special father oh thank you
you're welcome leave it to me
oh man i have too much power now it is a
lot of power oh wow okay don't you worry
i'll make sure it's it's something extra
nice i'm sure i'm in great hands
cali senpai would never
would never betray me right of course
not fana come on i think i think it'll
be something real great and
and uh you can definitely trust me
i'm an artist i draw
well i saw what you did for iris buffers
buffers yeah so i guess i gotta come up
with something
equally special for you fafa yes
i'm excited or maybe i shouldn't be
excited but i am excited to see
yes i will see what fate awaits
you betcha oh man
i hope you have a really great birthday
fauna it's it's crazy that like all
these birthdays have kind of like crept
up on me usually i write a rap for
everyone and like uh there's a lot in
march
yeah
jay and iris and cronie and now you and
i'm like yeah that's a relay
i gotta i gotta do something maybe it's
released like a big like video or
something like that
at the end of the month speed rap like a
pokey wrap but hollow yen
but that's just saying all our names
that's not that hard
yeah i know right i could i could do
that right now just be like irish bay
cronie fauna
we're done
great rap sasuka rap god cali
it's the best rap i've ever laid down
i'm in tears from from
i'm touched as you should be
it's real touching
you have a lovely birthday okay fauna
i'm gonna go turn on your stream so i
can see what crazy surprises
thank you callie and then i'll probably
fall back with sleep but happy birthday
thank you
have a great rest of your birthday and
we all love you so much we're so glad
that you're here with us so happy
yeah
have a great birthday and i'll talk to
you later okay okay bye bye
bye bye for happy day
so peace
so cute
okay okay
our next guest
oh
hello
[Music]
is that is that ollie senpai
you wouldn't know my face is censored
that's true i've never seen this zombie
in my life she looks pretty cute though
[Music]
happy birthday
sweet
[Music]
um i was actually inspired by you ollie
i made a birthday wheel i don't know if
you saw it i saw in one of your
totsumachi you had like a
a gift that like would flash different
things
ah it would like land on it and people
would do that thing
oh the chocolate gotcha you got inspired
from that i was inspired so i made a
wheel a birthday wheel if you want to
spin it
your wheel is a lot more terrifying than
my gotcha
it might be
i i would love to play your wheel okay i
will spin it um just let me know and you
want to stop it anytime
okay but before that i sent you a
birthday card
oh it's nothing much
oh my goodness
wow let me put this on the screen
[Music]
hopefully it fits
let me
i have to show everyone
thank you this is so cute
you're welcome stop
[Music]
it's like your pigtails i can wear them
it looks cute on you it's cute i don't
know how big this should be
it looks like a pair of cabbages now
that you mention it yeah it kind of is
cabbage like
thank you
[Music]
it's the cabbage
yes
cabbage
um your fate has landed on describe
fauna in three words oh thank all yeah
go in matsuri thank you
i'm close to
it was another close that close um
everyone's been landing on it today
okay efona and j words here sweet
you are
um
[Music]
full of ambition i know that's three
words already but let's just
let's just pretend that's one word
and you are also very determined i feel
like you put a lot of effort
into what you're doing
and then uh you think about all of your
uh what are your listeners called again
saplings
yeah blings
and
and i just feel like um i learned a lot
from you like uh when you when you you'd
when you deputed you were amazing
the book was amazing you have
you're like a breath of fresh air
you're super super cool
that's really sweet now i want to say
nice things about you too you're amazing
ollie and yeah
obviously i took a lot of inspiration
from you today but also always and your
energy and your outgoingness is really
inspiring
oh shut up
it's your birthday don't do not give me
the spotlight you don't even know if i'm
olly i don't have buttons that's true
should should i give you my cabbages
no thank you
nothing no you know what the cabbage is
no thank you no thank you you can have
them
in the cabbages no no you have it
it's for you
thank you
anyways i hope you have a great day fawn
love you i love you thank you
happy birthday
bye
[Music]
she's so
nice where can we put the buns
i want to put them somewhere oh hello
hello
louie
[Music]
thank you for coming
happy birthday
thank you
yeah welcome
i am happy to talk again
we talked before off
yeah yeah
but uh in stream in the first time right
yeah it's the first time on stream
so thank you for joining
i know it's
it's early
for you so thank you yes
eight o'clock a.m
[Music]
generally but it's okay i sweep out
yesterday
oh it's okay
don't worry about that how about your
birthday no
it's good
good
yeah i have this
wheel
on screen
um
with different
batsu but also
prizes
i see
if you want to spin it you can
but you don't have to
thank you
would you like to give it a try
try
yeah would you like to try
would you like to try
what
um the wheel
i will
ah
okay okay stop i i say stop i can say
stop right yeah yeah okay okay
[Music]
stop
this is
um
a powerful
result
powerful results okay
you can um tweet
on my account
send one tweet on my account
okay i
okay okay okay
you don't have to do it right now
you can think of it and send me later oh
okay wait to tweet if you want
like uh
take it to eat right
oh anyway
okay i will
i will send teddy to it oh no no you
don't send to me
um uh okay okay
i will tweet it
on my account yeah yeah so
you can make me say whatever you want
on twitter
i i want to
i want to tweet
account so
okay
yeah
good to eat for you
thank you
ah happy birthday
i want to
meet you
in the future
yes
in japan yeah yeah yeah i want to go i
want a
guide for you
yes please
please guide me
then when
if you
come japan
i will
gift send gift
for you
you don't have to
you don't have to that's very
the pasty present i
give you
i'm excited
can you understand why
yes yes i understand your english is
great thank you and i want to
invite you
japanese blessing
please dream
i need
japanese lesson
okay
watashi
so i will invite you
okay
thank you yes yes
i would love to
thank you please uh teach me
english
sure
yes
we can both help each other
yeah thank you
thank you
okay
okay have a nice good
[Music]
birthday okay
thank you i will
happy birthday thank you thank you for
coming bye bye
ah cute
she's so sweet
[Music]
i wanted to put the buns on
on small fun oh hello is our next guest
here
hello
happy birthday
thank you
thank you for coming
happy birthday
[Music]
it's good it's good are you doing well
too
yeah i'm doing well everything yeah with
the background the cake and
the flowers too oh thank you
feel free to help yourself to any sweets
i have a lot of sweets on the table oh
yeah can i take a bite of the cake
yeah
take a bite although
some other members have already uh i
think licked it so
[Music]
[Laughter]
just just a warning
oh i see nah it's okay that's that's
also another form of detai
you're right exactly right
indirect kiss
i'll take a bite
um would you like to
to spin my wheel
oh yeah the wheel will a fortune or is
it yeah is it misfortune because that a
little bit
well some people have the power to tweet
on my account you could you could win
the power to send a tweet
oh my god that sounds spicy let's do it
all right
let me know when you want to stop
okay
this might be a punishment it's kind of
neutral
it's do an impression of me
do an impression of you
yes ah
ah
i think i think one of your most famous
line
might be the uh but i don't know how you
usually say that
i don't know either to be honest it just
comes out oh
oh it just comes off
naturally because your natural itself
um
shall i just talk like you
or you can say what's a phone a line you
can say
conflana
hello saplings will you return to nature
today
oh okay i'll do that
i'll do that
hello saplings
let's return to nature to the day
[Music]
and you have you have a very soft
talking voice that was that was really
good you have a soft voice as well good
information oh that was good
yeah
i'm impressed
i was just admitting
you saying that
like a few seconds ago uh-huh
i think your voice is also soft so it
works oh thank you by the way by the way
i just want to make sure
do we really have 10 minutes of talking
time oh was there another oh
yeah
oh i was wondering
hmm yeah i think there were really yeah
i think there were some we don't have to
talk for 10 minutes um oh
we can i mean i mean i could do the
wheel of fortune you want to do the
wheel again
sure yeah if i can then sure we have
plenty of time
okay the schedule has blessed us with
five more minutes so we can yeah spin
the wheel
okay okay wondering okay
why are you spinning it yes it is
spinning oh you are
stop
oh
why do i feel like this is going to be a
bad suit i think it's not i think it's
just barely on the orange oh my
yeah you got another jackpot
oh my power
i will be tweeting a lot
yeah the power of new
[Music]
on something by the way um she didn't
decide yet yeah you can decide
uh whenever you want
oh okay just send it to me and tweet it
or you can decide
yeah
whenever you want
yeah i think i will i will decide later
and then i will send you yeah you can
you can think about it and
figure out the best thing
or the worst yeah
oh yeah
thank you
yeah thank you
now enjoy your birthday and i can't wait
for the merchandises yes
thank you i'm excited too to reveal it
for everyone because
it's been in the works for a while now
i can't wait to see yeah i'm excited
thank you for having me
[Music]
have a good rest of your day bye bye
bye
cute cute
[Music]
okay
we have maybe a few minutes
which i think our next guest
is another jp member oh hello
[Music]
senpai
uh
[Music]
happy birthday
to
[Music]
link to what about snow white so i don't
know
amazing
i know
i want to translate
something
google translate
today
[Music]
uh places i want to be
a priest
to
[Music]
please
okie dokie
[Music]
thank
you can
stop stop
[Music]
hi hi first
so
[Music]
my microphone
sapling translate
[Music]
oh
what's the impression it's beautiful
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
amazing
[Music]
oh
poca
[Music]
your
voice is very cute
soothing
asmr
[Music]
happy birthday
thank you arigato
[Music]
yes
i am very happy here
[Music]
thank you
okay
[Music]
thank you
i love polka senpai
but but translating
is hard
nihongo muzukashi
but she's so cute
sorry she was quiet at the start
i'm sorry okay
but
um she wants an asmr lesson it sounds
like she doesn't need it her asmr was
already so good
[Music]
um
okay our next
guest
is
here
should i drag her in
[Music]
hello
ah good morning good morning
good morning
[Music]
wait let me just
um how do i send message i forgot hold
on um
wait
i
i wanted
to sleep but i ended up
um watching
horror games so i look perfect
um let me
ah there we go
[Music]
oh my gosh
oh my goodness this is so cute rainy
thank you
show
let me show everyone
ah
thank you
by the way those are very delicious what
the food the so many delicious
oh yeah feel free to help yourself
yes please
i will
bring home some of these can i put this
in my my tupperware
oh yes i'll use this
i'll use that and then put it on the
fridge i'll eat this for like two days
or something yay
also i've always i've always wanted to
write you found it and then like yes
thank you so much so cute i love it
yeah
that's so cute
your art is so cute always
on thank you thank you thank you
thank you
would you like to spin my wheel
yes yes of course i want to
okay the wheel
hey it's spinning so let me know when
you would like to stop it
[Music]
this one again we keep getting this one
if you want okay
reroll
we've got the re-roll
power up okay let me know when you want
to stop again
stop
oh we had this one before too but i
think okay re-roll okay okay
we can't re-roll yes we can yeah re-roll
uh this is our last re-roll for you
renee we can't really
let's go
okay
re-roll uh stop stop stop stop stop
um
yes
why do i feel like this was planned
why don't i feel like you were just
going to keep re-rolling until you got
this one
actually there's a there's a there's a
lot of
stuff that's nice all of this is nice
but this is also nice kensington one
tweet
ah
so you don't have to think of it right
now if you don't want to everybody help
me out later everybody help me out
anybody else got this one on the stream
yeah actually you might be are you the
fourth now
no four three other people four tweets
now
nice
there's a lot
your twitter is going to be so colorful
yeah it will be interesting
[Music]
nice and nice and nice and nice
have a wonderful
wonderful birthday i was thinking that
oh yeah what should i say on her
birthday and then i was thinking on so
much about so much stuff but then um
right now my brain is dead
that's okay it is it is morning
i
there was so many wholesome stuff in my
brain
just all
evaporated but it has something to do
with you know let's play more puzzle
games yeah
i want to
yeah let's
let's watch more
more horror videos oh yes much more hard
together yeah yeah yeah
yeah anytime anytime i haven't there's
some stuff on my backlog too that i
haven't seen oh yeah let's watch it
let's watch it
yeah yeah okay okay okay
enjoy your birthday thank you
yeah i'll i'll rest up yo you're welcome
to join me anytime if you want i'm jesus
okay
okay i want you yay
yay
bye bye bye
thanks for coming
by
[Music]
and just like that we're on to our last
guest oh it went so fast
ah
hello renee
[Music]
hello
mommy
happy birthday
thank you
thanks for coming
nice to hear your voice
oh it's so nice to hear your voice i
have a gift for you you have a gift for
me did i save it hold on um i'm not
prepared i'm sending it
oh gosh that's not it either
okay
are you ready
yeah i'm ready are you sure
maybe is it anything like your beautiful
drawing of me from before
you go
this is cute
what do you mean wait this is cute
i mean
it's a different style from your
adorable
oh it acts a little different yeah
this is like also
mermaid gap moe in a way
put it at the start of the screen
when you expect something
horrific
but you get something adorable
i mean when you expect something
how should i put this gently
when you expect something beautiful
and
instead you get something beautiful
oh i love when that happens
[Music]
i just thought i'm sitting on your lap
am i not
i did i did think about that when i was
uh putting everyone's pngs in it doesn't
sort of look like everyone is sitting on
my lap
yay
it's like when you go see santa right
i'm santa and you guys are all lining up
to
talk to me for five minutes and yeah in
my lap but then
like i give gift instead yeah and so
it's like reverse santa
reverse santa oh my gosh i can imagine
you have the beard anyway um
how's your birthday how how's that it's
so good
would you like to spin my wheel
yeah i'm scared but i would like to how
does it work do i tell you when to stop
yeah i will start spinning it
and then yeah you can tell me to stop at
any time now
okay um
um
do you have any plans after ah you can
stop now
oh
we had this one before as well but this
one's pretty fun do an impression of
fauna
okay um
i can't do it i can't do it fine okay i
have a different one
yeah yeah
you can give it a shot
i thought
as i kind of thought i would be able to
then it came out and i was like oh god
no i can't yeah well that's how i feel
when i try to do impressions of you as
well
yeah
i feel like
i don't know i feel like i could but i
just can't maybe with more practice yeah
i gotta practice
[Music]
did i get a different one yeah you can
have another one okay
uh you choose one to stop
oh
[Music]
okay that's too much i've never had this
much power before i'm gonna close my
eyes and do it because i don't want to
be biased stop
no
the wheel keeps landing on this one what
is it it's do your best
oh
oh gosh the wheel i was scared this is
okay um
wow that was oh that was so good my
heart is pounding oh sorry sorry oh my
goodness sorry about that
i don't know if i'm gonna recover from
that one oh sorry have you done one yet
i did you want me to do another yes
please
arara
oh my god
you can't do that to me you can't
thank you too much too much gosh it's
your birthday but i i got the greatest
gift of all things everyone's getting
spoiled today
thank you bye
all right
oh
is my time up well it's not really but
i have to announce my merch in three
minutes oh i don't know
i want to watch it
you haven't announced it okay uh in
three minutes
can i uh what's the word can i advertise
it for a second
yeah
wow it's so beautiful wow so handy dandy
i cannot wait to lift it to my lips
oh i cannot wait to smell it oh i bet it
smells like fauna oh
lovely oh
awesome okay
amazing
thank you
okay
sorry i'm so tired i don't nothing feels
real okay
bye-bye thanks for coming
bye bye
[Music]
oh my gosh i went by so fast
that all went by so fast
that was our last guest
[Music]
whoa
wait but there was one more thing do i
have time
i have a video i almost forgot i think
we have time to watch the video
[Music]
wow that was so fun i like totsumachi i
was kind of worried because i'm shy but
it's fun to talk to everyone all my
friends
okay um
i have one video
okay we better watch it fast i guess i
hope it works
good morning wait wait wait wait
[Music]
get rid of this wheel
did you see who it was
good
morning happy
[Music]
birthday very
how many
[Music]
um
typey typey
i think she's talking about another
collab
i want to
corner
with you
summertime
yes please
oh yes
oh yes oh yes yes oh yes yes thank you
thank you yes
[Music]
that was so cute
she's so cute
[Music]
i want to marry her i mean
yes
oh yes
okay okay okay i think it's time
i want to watch it again but i think i
have to
i think it's time for the merch i'm
scared okay
i think it's time for merch
are you ready
do i show it
oh
[Music]
this is
you see this art
it looks like maybe
it's drawn by a soggy mama
that's right you guessed it i do have
merch after all
believe it or not there is merch
birthday merch oh i'm so nervous
we've been working on this for a while
okay okay okay
exciting merch announcement let's go
first on the list
we have a sweatshirt
with the art by asagi mama i want to
show you the art
in a bigger print because
it uh is very beautiful
and you should see it
fully wait also i want to mention this
merch set has a theme maybe you can
figure out the theme i'll leave the
theme to you to figure out but it is a
themed set
and um
the shirt i believe the size you have to
check for the exact details but i
believe it is like an
extra extra large so
um
you know depending on
you
it might be
like for me i want it to be oversized
and i'll go to sleep in it but maybe for
it depends on you of course
but that's the idea
um
next up should we go next
a keychain
with art by tanuki
it is a double-sided keychain i want
to make it bigger
with a golden apple
you can put your keys on it or whatever
you want
ah one sweet side and one yonder side
just like me
[Music]
cute keychain okay
next up
i'm excited
[Music]
is
wait can i put it over here first
i'm kind of not in the middle
i'm pushing this all over the place okay
okay
[Music]
wait but doesn't this look familiar
that's right it's been sitting in front
of me this whole time
this teacup and saucer set wow you can
actually buy it and have it yourself if
you want
it's real
[Music]
wow
yeah since i love tea and maybe some of
you guys like tea as well i wanted a a
tea set
so it's a cute little tea set with a
saucer
kind of fancy
actually somewhat of a tea drinker
myself
[Music]
yeah i went in i asked when pc to
sneakily draw this into the set
[Music]
it's real
and
well maybe by now you've figured out the
theme of this set it's kind of like a
sweet ex yandere theme like a sweet and
yandere theme
but you might be wondering how is a
teacup
yandere
well it's all a matter of what you put
inside the teacup isn't it
okay
now this is the bonus if you buy
the complete set
now who drew this
who's the artist for this one
um i'll have you know you actually
all of you know this this artist
[Music]
it's
me
i drew it
yeah and i wrote a little message that
is a secret but you can see the message
if you buy the complete set and you can
get this little postcard
drawn by me yeah i've been talking about
how i wanted to do more drawings and
more serious illustrations so this was
one that i got to do
[Music]
thank you
yeah i was excited to get to draw
something for you guys i don't know it's
drawn from the heart
right
something like that
oh wait but there's more as well
there's more and there's also voice
packs i have
two voice packs coming out as well um
well i guess they're already out i guess
you can get them right now and listen to
them i guess
one of them is an asmr style voice pack
it's about 15 minutes long
and it is called
a double fauna sweet ex yonder ear
cleaning asmr
double fauna
um
uh
what could that entail i don't know it
seems like you'll have to read it but i
will say
it does feature
the araada voice
and there's also a set of alarms that i
did um not asmr just regular alarms um i
did a variety
pack of different alarms so hopefully if
you download it and you want to use them
hopefully one of them
will suit you
[Music]
and yeah that is the complete set we
have
the sweatshirt the keychain the teacup
and saucer set and then the two voice
packs and
if you buy
everything
you get the postcard
[Music]
yeah we have all been working on this um
for a while so i'm excited to finally
get to show it to you
okay
um and
i think this has yeah this has the full
art hold on
to make it bigger it's so pretty a soggy
mama drew it see it has
sweet fauna and yonder
on it
yeah soggy mama is amazing
she did an amazing job
i kind of want to flip it
yeah now we can see
now you can see the yonder face a little
better
yeah
okay
but that's that that's the merge
[Music]
can i put this
the screen is getting crowded
let me move
move
this
[Music]
i don't want to put these on
on wide fauna
[Music]
rearrange everything
okay that is the merge let me
i think the link is already in the
description
but i will also quickly try to
pin it in the chat
for you
[Music]
there you go
and
um i do have a few more things
today
for the birthday stream
i can't believe it's been two hours
already
oh and i think the sale is also open now
my chan just told me
thank you so much to mani-chan for
helping me out so much for the birthday
stream
very big appreciation for manitan um
yeah i think the sales should be
out now
or for error
did you crash the site
it may be working soon
[Music]
just please hold i'm sure it will work
eventually
or maybe try refreshing
but thank you guys
or um
is the link bad
the link in the description works okay
hold on maybe we should just
um
go through it in the description then
maybe my link is bad
i think maybe it combined the link
but just try the description
i think that will work for you
[Music]
give that one a shot
um
but thank you guys
i can't say enough thank yous there's
not enough thank yous
for everything for i don't know all the
the support and everything wow
i saw some really cute things already on
twitter and i don't know
i don't know i
was feeling so touched by uh everyone's
kind messages and especially because
i've been dealing with so many technical
problems lately and like i don't i don't
like when i'm not able to stream and
hang out you know
um i
i don't i don't
i don't like that so
but like getting to hear that everyone
is still there for me and
is so kind
um
it really means a lot and i'm very
thankful to
be here and to have such a nice
community
who is i don't know like you guys are
just the best
really like seeing everything that
everyone has worked on and i don't know
it's hard to feel like i'm deserving of
everything but uh it makes me want to
keep keep doing my best
okay
i'm sorry i'm trying i will not be too
mushy
i won't be too mushy but just know that
i'm very thankful
i'm really thankful
okay
there is there is more
to do
we have
the screen is getting a bit crowded
though
[Music]
um
okay
so the next thing i wanted to do was i
um
commissioned
um some of you might know them they're a
clipper in the community called slack
fun day
i commissioned them to make a clip
compilation
for us to watch together
to uh
remember some of the moments from the
past however many months
so watch it together i haven't watched
it yet
oh i think it's about 13 minutes long
so
i might need to move myself over a
little bit first
[Music]
let's do
um
and i'll move everything
so we have room to watch
[Music]
um
put this down here
it's like cleaning
okay um
this is probably enough room
yes clip watch along
and then
there might even be something after the
clip watch along so
stick around to the very end
man i wanna
the toad samachi was so fun i wanted to
say like i'm so thankful to everyone who
came
and chatted with me
it's
um
it was very nice getting to talk to
everyone
[Music]
it was fun it's fun
i'm happy okay
okay enough enough mushy
um
okay let's show let's watch the clip
video and then after the clip video
there will be one more
something
and then
uh after
that
well
it will be over
[Music]
but i'll be back again soon okay
let's let's watch
[Music]
hey
turn the music off too hey
wake up
it's time to wake up
already this is a throwback
[Music]
can you guys hear it
uh
[Music]
this is good pickle
not
pick
perfect
oh this just looks like i almost forgot
about the
pickle
[Music]
so we might see some
i'm gonna kill
what kill
wait what
what
this one is a real throwback
[Music]
i told you i'm a baby i can't even
handle this
you know your ears are right here wait
actually this has always been a dream of
mine oh no um
um um
why do i want to eat her ears so much
if i if i just they're pretty edible to
be to be fair
[Music]
i didn't see oh this is so cute we got
to see both of them today
i don't know romantic isn't it
is it okay to sleep that is cute i don't
know it's so cute
together
it's too much it's too much for me to
handle
i'm lost
do you want to
work
for buncaroni yeah
the memories give me and give me a job
the memory so what are your respects
um i'm very strong
okay
that's good well what are your
weaknesses um i'm very weak okay you're
hired that was the most perfect
interview i've ever heard
okay
oh no my most devious prank
oh no
oh
weird
you know i think i
i feel like i hear someone getting fired
oh i'm always fired up the moment i get
out of here
uh it's gonna get pretty lit up here
wow this is actually pretty nice
you know saved me i'm glad that i've had
this experience at least it's quite
pretty
yeah
[Music]
right there
oh no
this is the perfect time for me to
escape i mean leave
oh no i still regret saying that you
know like when we were when we were
preparing we noticed that you know you
you see you see the braids in our head
they kind of like mirror each other
wait we have this we have the hair this
is this hair strand too
yeah we do we have the hair strand and
the bangs on one side uh-huh
twins
yay
no oh this cannot be
fauna i think that's the longest time
somebody's ever like
back and forth with me with who speak
and i'd like to say thank you from the
bottom of my heart i'm immune to cringe
so oh
fantastic
the latter's gone
all my friends
no this is when i was still alone
don't say it
don't say my daddy
i said it right i hear noises already
i'm scared i'm pausing you can't
let you can't give power to things that
hurt you things can't hurt you not
without your own consent that's great
you
oh my god you do it
i can't believe that worked
oh my gosh bae you're the best
you're the best she is the best
please i don't want to just die again
why
aren't in the closet
not me
still one of my favorite streams
did cody die again i think how do you
die again ah the
the crony horror game away it's gotta be
one of my favorite things these are
genuine screams oh no
no you
cease this
sees this
saplings saplings saplings i need you to
murder this axolotl for me
i need you to grab this axolotl for me
but another it's like a gamer moment
thank you
please be
maybe a little bit
i use my power for evil
should we play hide and seek oh this is
the secret this
stream i found you oh wait there's
someone here got to play hide and seek
[Music]
oh no don't cry it's okay
nice hat same hat
found you
i
yay
[Music]
everyone is so cute i'm so happy
i'm so cute
so close
so oh so close so close
[Music]
it only goes up from here
about that fauna actually follow me not
much since wait
the very first moment he'll just be my
companion
i'll bring him back one day oh i have i
did not bring him back
i do have a place you can live
yes
wow
are you
oh
yes i'm sure daughter thanks mama oh
mama
my heart
yes
um
i want to buy the golden pipe but i
don't have enough money
cute
oh
[Music]
hey how long have we been here sitting
down in this cafe and still no one has
come to take our order
don't you think that's a little strange
hmm
i'll be right back
[Music]
what do you think
what do you think feels so nostalgic i
can't go fast
see
i go fast and i fall
see see that's what you wanted from me
you wanted me to go fast and that's what
happens when i try to go
is this what you wanted
is this what she wanted
no no no i'm i'm gonna cry i'm gonna cry
i'm gonna cry
it's
[Music]
it'll be worth it
you'll have a golden pot one day fauna i
love this slide
don't worry about me because i'm not
actually insane
i don't know if i believe her these look
like the eyes of an insane person
[Music]
i have
someone
to introduce to you today
oh
[Music]
there she is hello hello
hot pickle no it's not not pickle
and no it's not my first son either
she is
my new mascot
[Music]
oh well how fast was that
oh that was pretty fast
that was really fast
oh my gosh i really i could hear my
heart pounding in my ears
you know
is somebody else here i don't know what
was that wait no maybe i was just
imagining things i didn't hear any
mother
there's somebody else
is that mother nature herself
it's me
[Music]
only if you want to i got 50 wins i
didn't
[Music]
it's blinding i can't i see my
reflection in it
yeah
bye bye
[Music]
bye
that was so cute
[Music]
i cannot help but feel nostalgic after
watching that
yeah i didn't i didn't watch it before
because i didn't want to spoil myself
that was really cute
[Music]
oh yes big thank you to
slack funny for making that you did an
amazing job i love the clips that you
picked thank you for putting it together
also pretty last minute
man
[Music]
i am really glad to be here and to have
been able to meet so many amazing people
and to have such a wonderful community
of saplings
and
i'm very thankful to have everyone
to be here
[Music]
i'm just so happy
thank you guys for everything i cannot
thank you
enough i want to keep
keep going and keep doing my best and
ah thank you all
and thank you to
everyone who joined my totsumachi today
and every thank you to all of my my uh
fellow yen members and to my senpai and
to my my kohai
and
i'm just thankful
thank you
my
[Music]
my heart feels very full
today
thank you for such an amazing birthday
everyone
i really appreciate it
let's keep i don't know i just keep
wanting to say cheesy idol things like
now i understand like in the idle anime
when they always say i'll keep doing my
best i understand that feeling now i
didn't get it before i was like oh what
a cheesy idol thing to say but like now
i get it i'm like yes i your all your
your support and you're encouraging it
reaches me and it makes me want to do
better
so i don't know if it's cheesy i don't
think i'll still say it and
let's make more memories together
[Music]
yeah one day maybe i'll get to
perform on the stage like my senpai too
but i don't even
oh i mean obviously
that's really cool and i care about that
but most importantly i just care about
being together with everyone and
spending time together and getting to do
cool things together
so
whenever that day comes
i will be happy but until then let's
keep having fun together keep doing fun
things with
all of ian and id and jp
and and and the cyberplanes
[Music]
okay is that enough cheesiness i don't
know i don't know my heart is just mushy
it's all coming out at once i um it's
too much cheeziness though because i
said there's one more thing although
this side could also be sappy about
happy birthday fauna
[Music]
okay
oh i'm so scared
to announce this
ah okay
do you guys remember when i said that a
while ago there was something that
happened that i wanted to tell you about
but it was like a dream come true
this is that thing
just saying
i'm scared mom
uh okay i guess i should just show you
[Music]
i guess i should just show you
wait it's on the screen already i didn't
really love the screen already i showed
you i showed you already i was gonna do
a thing but it already showed up ah yes
i'm doing an original song with the she
button records oh my god i'm gonna
explode
you might know them um for the iconic
touhou bossa nova remixes that they've
made
yes bad she buying records yes
yes
those ones
[Music]
so yeah um
yes
i'm extremely excited um
the song is currently still in
production um but it's close to being
finished so we're looking at a release
of late april
uh
i'm very excited
because i i've been a fan of shiva
records for so long and it's like a
dream come true that they were uh
willing to work with me on a song and
it's my original song it's
mine and i'm singing it and
i'm really excited
[Music]
oh my gosh i know i can't believe it
it's it really is a dream come true it
really is and i can't wait to share it
to you and
uh i mean like it's crazy that i wait
for my not being able to well i mean i
still am not the best singer but you
know i
i
i went from thinking that i could never
sing and that i was just doomed to be a
bad singer forever and now i'm gonna
have a song
with with a group that i really look up
to
and it's all thanks to you guys it's all
because that i'm i'm here that i'm able
to do so many amazing things
so thank you
okay
oh i'm so excited
i hope that you guys will
enjoy the song i know you will because
you're gonna love it
i'm not gonna be
uh humble about the song because
it is it is
by she buying records it's
amazing
i can't wait okay
okay wow it feels good to announce that
i don't have to keep it a secret anymore
you'll have to wait just a little bit
while we put the finishing touches on it
i didn't
see i thought about you know we
considered like could it be done for my
birthday but um we didn't want to rush
it
so we're taking
um
our time
but it should be ready
in late april
[Music]
yeah i'm excited
okay wow
wow
[Music]
yeah and i can't i won't tell you the
name of the song yet um i'll probably
tell you
um closer when we have a definitive
release date i will tell you more
but you'll just have to wait for now but
please please get excited
anticipate it as cali would say
also if you haven't go listen to shabbat
records other works because they really
are amazing and um
you know i love i love bossa nova they
do other things besides boss nova as
well but
um
i i really love bossa nova so it's
actually a dream come true and exciting
okay
i'm so excited
is that it is that it for my birthday
did we do it this went by so fast it was
all like a blur
it was all a blur
wow
wow thank you guys
for an amazing birthday
i need to go on twitter i wanna
um
try to reply to people and retweet a
bunch of stuff
[Music]
but first i'll eat something
oh but thank you guys so much
i'm really happy i'm
i'm i'm i'm nah you guys you guys know
i'm just happy i'm just happy
i'm just happy to be here and happy to
be surrounded like i don't know i can't
say enough you guys really are such an
amazing community
i
love the saplings there's a video on my
twitter of some saplings who got
together and played happy birthday on
the kalimba for me and i was truly
touched when i was watching that i
almost like started tearing up i was
getting a bit emotional looking at all
the supports and
yeah i'm gonna try to retweet more stuff
but uh do check my twitter and
um
go look at all the amazing
art and other things that people have
created because there's really a lot and
i put some oh wow like that one very
quiet
[Music]
no but it's beautiful art and also feet
oh yeah i put some of them up here on
the slideshow but i might have been
blocking it some of the stream
but yes thank you guys very much for
everything
thank you for everything
that's all i can say
thank you
oh so beautiful so much beautiful art i
need to go
or retweet it i really appreciate
everything
and i how many times can i say that
i just hope that my words reach you
because i feel like there's so much in
my my head
and it all just turns to mush when it
comes out of my mouth and i just want to
say
i want to to
give all of my thanks to you and i hope
that it comes across
even though words are hard and it all
turns to mush as soon as it leaves my
mouth
but yes i'm i'm i'm thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you for celebrating thank you for
coming to my birthday party i hope that
you had fun i had fun that was so fun
let's do this again um are you guys free
like a year from today
maybe we can do this again
um a year from today mark your calendars
uh oh yeah don't forget about the merch
if you want to buy it
[Music]
there is
a variety whoa
[Music]
it's gone
okay that's fine there is a variety of
merchandise for you to purchase
oh this was a cake someone made it's a
real cake and it has i think they're
like cookies on top of clover and snail
and getting over golden pot and i
thought that was so amazing
thank you guys okay okay i really will
go now thank you guys for hanging out
and coming to my birthday party it means
so much to me
please have a great rest of your day
and i will see you soon i think i
have gotten
uh many of the technical problems out of
the way so we have at least a like
temporary scuffed setup uh that we can
use until i get everything started but
thank you for bearing with me and i will
see you soon
i appreciate you guys very much
i will hug you but the microphone is
tiny now
[Music]
okay
goodbye fun well thank you for
celebrating with me
i appreciate it and i will see you guys
soon
bye bye
bye
[Music]
you